Any chance of getting this thing
running again?
The simplicity of the thermosyphon
cooling is sheer elegance.
The capitalist dictate
of constant improvement
often pushes us past the pinnacle
of achievement into inferior products.
And this your brain off of drugs?
Hey, don't weed shame me. I know stuff.
So, is that a yes? Because, soon enough,
someone's gonna see
that J. Edgar Hoover's missing,
and the timeline's gonna start changing.
If I can find some water, yes.
Oh, Gary, can you check the back seat
for some water, please?
I think I saw something
under Hoover's coat.
Please don't mention his name.
This guy is giving me
terrible indigestion.
It was probably all those cigars. Ugh!
Or all the bigotry.
Oh!
Uh, I've got some soda. Does that work?
We'll find out.
How about this?
A radio!
Oh. We can pick up some newscasts.
The lovely and lethal
Bullet Blondes remain at large.
Last seen driving east
on the Bankhead Highway.
Caution advised.
They are considered armed and dangerous.
Huh. I can't believe the name stuck.
Yeah, and they didn't mention Hoover,
which means
they think he's still alive.
Well, he's not.
Nate, what's up?
We've gotten out of tighter spots
than this.
Have we?
Mick's gone, Astra's down for the count,
Zari is nursing a broken heart
in a pocket dimension,
and I killed J. Edgar Hoover.
It was an accident, and it could have
happened to any man of steel.
That's not funny.
I spent my whole life studying history,
making sure
it's preserved and passed on.
By killing Hoover, I personally
messed up the entire 20th century.
Look, we're gonna fix it, okay?
Are we?
Because without Gideon or the ship,
there's no way you can guarantee that.
Nate, you are spinning.
I murdered a man, Sara.
And for the first time in our lives,
we have to accept that
that could be permanent.
Okay, look...
Uh... Wife, Nate,
we've got a big problem.
Hoover was supposed to be on a train to
New York from Midland, this afternoon.
If he's not there,
the whole timeline's screwed.
No, it won't be.
Nate, history needs saving,
and you are just the man to do it.
So long as the world thinks
that Hoover is still alive,
then the timeline remains on track.
No, no, no.
I know what you're thinking. No.
There's no way I can impersonate Hoover
all the way to New York.
I could barely do it
in some podunk Texas town.
- Gary!
- Huh?
Can you do some kind of spell
and make him look like Hoover?
Uh...
Technically, yes, but I'd need some
of Hoover's spit, or a fingernail.
Or hair.
We're mobile, people.
Well, good, because J. Edgar Hoover
has a train to catch.
I did a spell to resurrect a machine.
I don't know what this is.
I'd recognize
that smug little smile anywhere.
It is Gideon.
She doesn't look like a machine.
Well, not a machine exactly, Mami.
A computer, who speaks. Usually.
Hello, computer.
On the upside, it looks like
you got your magic working again.
My magic is clearly garbage.
Stop that.
She's still Gideon though, right?
What's two plus two?
There you go.
Wow. Computers are very exciting.
Sorry.
Is it ready?
Not yet, it needs to fully ferment.
This is just the primary stage.
Okay, we need to come up with
some kind of distraction or something
because that train leaves in five
minutes and Hoover needs to be on it.
And to the public eye, he will be.
Look, because they're
not gonna be looking at him.
No, they are going to be looking
at the most wanted women in America.
What?
- Oh, I'm not sure about this.
- Just follow my lead. Come on.
My safe word is "core competency."
Coming through here.
Look out, we've got the Bullet Blondes!
This isn't the last you're gonna hear
of the Bullet Blondes.
That's right, coppers.
Who you calling the cops?
We're the Bureau of Investigation.
That's right, and J. Edgar Hoover
always gets his man, or woman,
or gender nonconforming individual.
I'll need four extra tickets
for my associates.
Are those the Bullet Blondes?
Well, we're not a pair
of cancelled stamps.
Mr. Hoover, let me find some seats
for you and your men.
Our most secure cabin
is the honeymoon suite.
In the name of J. Edgar Hoover,
I am commandeering this cabin.
Oh, no. No need to commandeer.
We don't wanna spoil your honeymoon.
Spoil? Phonus balonus.
After them Palmer Raids, we'd be proud
to help out a patriot like Mr. Hoover.
- Congratulations.
- Congratulations, best wishes.
Phew! That was close.
Can you please take these off now?
What were the Palmer Raids?
After World War I, America
was freaking out about communism.
So Hoover and the DOJ arrested thousands
of immigrants, union workers,
anything that smelled like
organized labor.
A real champion of civil liberties.
Oh, he pretty much codified racial bias
into our judicial system.
Okay, but morally, he's repulsive.
Historically, however,
he's one of the most important men
of the 20th century.
He founded the FBI.
He ran it till he died.
Yeah, well, great men
aren't usually good guys.
And that is our cue to disappear.
Oh, B, key me.
The key, Time Bureau manual
and some honeymoon chocolates.
Say hi to Z for me.
Capitáns, hey.
Are we home yet?
How did your bank robbery go?
Did we figure out
who blew up the Waverider yet or no?
Am I talking too much?
Am I talking not too much?
- I think she's a little high.
- I'd say very.
We're still in 1925.
And now we're on a train.
What? Where are we going?
But really, where is
anybody really going?
You okay, Z?
I thought you didn't partake.
See, I found myself on a journey,
and that journey
is with these tiny little bears.
And I'm going on that journey
à la carte.
Allah carte!
Allah... carte.
Okay, well, we'll be upstairs.
Yeah, if you need anything, please don't
hesitate to come and find us.
Actually, hesitate a little.
- Oh. Hesitate a lot.
- Mmm!
Ugh. Gross moms.
Hey. Maybe we won't even
need that potion.
We just hide out in the cabin.
You in there, Speed?
"Speed"?
That was Hoover's nickname.
Only his closest friends
called him that.
It's Francis Baker.
Junior, of course.
Oh, the GW boys are gonna go wild
when I tell them I saw you.
- Gary, potion.
- It's frothing ready.
All right, how long does the spell last?
It depends upon your metabolism.
Could be an hour. Could be 24.
Hey. It sounds like Hoover
was a supreme douche.
You really sure you want to be him?
I have to clean up my mess, B.
Wait, don't drink it in front of us.
Did it work?
We don't know,
since you drank it in front of us,
we'll only know if the magic works
when someone else sees you.
For the love of...
This is silly.
Let me see your...
face.
Edgar, there's that handsome mug.
Let me buy you lunch, Speed.
The oysters here give Old Ebbitt's
a run for their money.
Director of the
Bureau of Investigation at 29.
Speed indeed.
I think you fellas
will be more comfortable elsewhere.
Yeah, sure.
More comfortable.
Ew.
No, thank you.
Oh. She made a little doll.
I wish the Legends
would just get back already.
They would know exactly
what to do with her
and her creepy outsider apple art.
They can't find this Dr. Davies guy
soon enough.
Oh! Oh, Gideon!
Great, now she's broken.
Hey! You okay?
Yeah, why?
Oh, man. Are you mad
that we're honeymooning in your house
after everything that
happened with John...
Shh, Aves,
I love you.
I love you both.
I love your love.
I love that you're loving each other
right now,
even if that love is happening directly
above me while I eat sugar foam.
Okay, well, if you ever want to talk
or anything, just come find me.
No, seriously, I am A-okay, golden.
You know what, just hear me out, Z.
No judgment, okay? I'm just...
I think you and Behrad
are very different people,
and I think that maybe
your coping mechanisms
might not be the same
as his coping mechanisms.
You know, honestly, I'm not sure that
I'm doing this stoned thing correctly
because I either feel like very hungry,
or tired all of the time.
That can't be it. Can that be it?
I don't know. You're a doer, though,
you know, you're like me.
Oh, it's true, I love a project.
You love a project?
Let's find you a project.
Ooh! Cleaning. Cleaning!
That's a good one.
I'm gonna clean this place.
I'm gonna clean this place
clean of John vibes.
Yes! Yes, that's my girl.
You know, at minimum,
it will give me an excuse
to leave this room because...
you guys are very loud.
What? Come on, we're not loud.
"Core competency." Boop!
I don't even know
what you're talking about.
God!
So, tell me, is there a Mrs. Hoover?
Oh, no, ma'am. I'm married to my job.
Well, let me give you my card
in case you and your job
ever get divorced.
My purse, it's gone!
Never fear, madam.
You have the nation's finest detective
at your service.
Should we round up the usual suspects?
Those are my men.
No one is leaving this car
till we get that purse back.
Now, what was in your purse?
Jewelry?
Money?
Anything of note?
Hmm...
My calling card, my comb,
and one of those delightful pastries
from the breakfast cart.
You never know when you might get
a flash of the grumblies.
Hmm. Oh, my.
Goldie!
I believe this is
what you're looking for.
Huzzah!
Thank you, Mr. Hoover.
- Hip hip hooray! Hip hip hooray!
- Thank you. Thank you.
Stop. What are you doing?
Oh.
Well, I must get back to work.
If only all the bad guys
were as easy to catch as Goldie here.
Marvelous seeing you,
Francis Baker Jr., of course. Okay.
It's working, they're buying it.
Yeah, they're buying that Gary and I
are petty thieves because of our looks.
I'm trying to be as authentically Hoover
as possible.
I wouldn't mind
a little less authenticity.
Why don't we go back to Plan A?
Hunkering.
You're right. We should play it safe
till we get to New York.
Ow!
Get off!
Director Hoover.
Thank God. We just got word from HQ.
There's a plot afoot to kidnap you.
We need to get you off this train.
Give me a minute.
I'm sure we could find a way
to get to New York
that doesn't involve Hoover cosplay,
or kidnapping.
Listen, the real J. Edgar Hoover
was never kidnapped,
so he must have solved this.
No, this is getting
way too out of control.
I mean, I'm sure we can fix this
with a do-over.
What if there's no more do-overs?
What if this is it?
We owe it to history to make it right.
Gentlemen, this sounds like a case
for the Bureau of Investigation.
Has she had anything to drink?
She doesn't need anything to drink,
she's not a person.
I may not know what a computer is,
but I know a heartbeat.
And you made that, Astra.
You are not only a very powerful witch,
you're also a mother now.
- I am nobody's mother!
- Dang.
Now, what will the team do
with a human Gideon?
Probably just give her Rory's old room.
There's always space for one more
with the Legends.
Where are your Legends now, anyway?
They went to New York
to meet this time-travel guy.
Once they find him,
they're gonna come get us.
Okay, I'm no expert, but it seems to me
if you have a machine
that can travel through time,
what do you just go back to,
right after the moment you left?
- I mean, unless...
- It didn't work.
What was the word from HQ?
Not a lot of detail.
The Dallas field office
intercepted a telegram.
"Hoover on tren, northbond."
"Train" and "northbound"
are both misspelled.
- So he's a foreigner.
- Or a bad speller.
The men in Little Rock
are gonna alert DC.
Planning to have agents
at every station on the route.
Good.
Mr. Hoover says
we're looking for a foreigner.
- I didn't say that.
- Stay put in here, Mr. Hoover.
We'll turn this train upside down
till we find our man.
Hoover doesn't run an investigation
from behind.
All right, all we got to go on
is this telegram,
which doesn't give us a motive
or a means,
but its timing does narrow down
a list of possible suspects.
Donovan, Rodgers, get me a list
of all the passengers
that got on this train since Midland.
- Go!
- On it, sir.
The three of us are gonna start
at the front of the train,
and we're gonna work our way back.
We're looking for anyone
who has a reason to hurt Hoover.
Who would possibly
want to hurt that guy?
A "please" would have been nice.
Is there anyone on this train
you may suspect
of having anti-government sentiment?
Anti-government?
The government is the only thing
keeping this country
from going to the dogs.
Have you heard anyone
talk about anarchy or...
socialism?
Well, that depends.
Would you call a working wage socialism?
Then, yeah,
I'd say we're all talking about it.
Lovely to see America by train car.
Be a lot lovelier if I wasn't
being spied on by a bunch of dicks.
- By "dick," do you mean cop?
- Mmm.
You think someone on this train
is a ne'er-do-well?
Good luck pulling one over
on America's finest lawman.
That's very nice of you.
Hoover?
That man is cursed.
You have no idea.
Hoover? Leaves a bad taste in my mouth.
Ugh. Tell me about it.
Everybody on this train loves Hoover.
Yeah, everybody with
first class tickets.
The people we talked to
would be happy to kill Hoover.
If we're looking for motive, we got it.
Lots of it.
Which is as good as finding none at all.
We're switching this investigation
away from the why and onto the how.
And with agents in every city,
it would be pretty hard pulling off
a kidnapping in any of the stations.
They'd get caught immediately.
Or congratulated.
But if you get the train
off the main route...
No one would be guarding the track.
And if you could redirect the train,
you have control of the train.
Ooh! Inside job!
- Inside job?
- Inside job!
Director Hoover, meet Igor Lewandoski,
the train's engineer.
A Russian and a labor organizer.
He wasn't scheduled to work today
but had a change of heart.
He joined the crew back in Midland.
Awfully convenient.
- Did he confess?
- He won't say diddly.
But he's our guy, I'm sure of it.
Trust you can get the confession
we need.
Do your worst, boss.
Yeah.
Boy, a very sad party of one
happened in here.
It doesn't matter.
Zen in ten.
Here I come, starting with the fridge.
See, even I know
you don't keep whiskey in the fridge.
- Aves.
- Hi, Z.
How many bottles of whiskey
are there on the table?
- Um... Two.
- Two!
- The fridge is making whiskey.
- What? That's fantastic!
The Waverider.
Yeah, I guess it's
kind of like the Waverider.
Although, the fridge doesn't
take requests like Gideon.
No, no, no. This bottle,
this bottle is the Waverider.
And this bottle is the mystery Waverider
that blew us up.
So if there's two Waveriders...
who's to say there isn't...
A third Waverider.
And a fourth. It will never end.
Oh, I get it.
You're still really stoned.
So, let's say we go back
and stop the mystery Waverider
from blowing us up, that's great.
But that Waverider came from somewhere,
which means if one showed up,
then another one could
and another and another...
Okay, wait,
let's just slow this train down.
Take this. Remember this?
Here, grab this. Hi, hi, hi.
Look, squirt, squirt. Squirt and wipe.
Squirt and wipe,
and the gummies are gonna wear off,
and then you're gonna be feeling
the natural high of a job well done.
Look, show me. Show me.
I'm watching. Squirt and wipe.
You got this. You got this.
You can be mean.
You can be mean as hell.
He's all ready for you, sir.
Good.
Uh, sir? A quick word?
- How are you gonna swing this, Nate?
- I don't know.
- I don't want to hurt the guy, but...
- No way, man.
Look, those two agents
are expecting Hoover.
They have all the evidence they need.
That's more than enough.
It's not enough! I need a confession!
Look, Nate, I know you feel like
this is the end of the world,
but you're just a good guy
who made a bad mistake.
What was the alternative?
Let him kill you?
You're worth a thousand Hoovers.
By comparison to Hoover,
I am nobody in the timeline.
Come on, Nate, you know that's not true.
You've got to forgive yourself.
This isn't about me.
So, what are we gonna do?
You ever hear the one about
the black lady, the brown lady
and the broken computer
who walked into a bar in 1925?
Uh, no.
Yeah, because it would never happen!
Let's face it,
there's nothing we can do.
The Legends are on their own.
Great, more decapitated apple heads.
I think she's trying
to tell us something, Astra.
Uh... An apple a day.
Easy as apple pie.
Don't put all your apples in one box.
That is not a thing.
It's six apples, in a box,
off the table, on the floor.
Thank you, Dr. Seuss.
It's clearly apple...
sauce.
Okay, you know what, enough!
Just stop trying to tell us things!
I wish I could just shove you back
into the wires and the sockets,
or whatever makes you work
on the Waverider,
because then maybe
you could actually help us!
So, why are you so mad at Gideon?
She hasn't done anything to you.
Because... she's a constant reminder
of my giant failure.
That's why you don't want to go
after the Legends.
I'm useless to them, Spooner.
You made one mistake, Astra.
Ease up on yourself.
At least you still have magic.
Hey, you have things to offer, too.
Like what? Without aliens,
what do I bring to the table?
Ranch wear.
You know, I guess
we're both pretty useless.
You mean the three of us are...
What is that?
Gideon, no!
Gideon.
Why did you do that?
Wires and sockets.
She understood you.
Hey, Z, can Sara and I
grab one of those bottles of... whiskey?
Oh. Hey, girl!
Hey, buddy.
Uh, what did we talk about?
More cleaning, no more gummies, yeah?
Oh, no, I'm not stoned. I'm enlightened.
See, I finally realized
why John gave me this key.
To clear my head
and think about the bigger picture.
See, I was so focused on my phones
and skincare sales
and romantic entanglements
that I never stopped to think about
what was really going on with the team.
The team? Our team?
Yeah. See, without those distractions,
I was able to dig deep
and really think about how we got here.
So, I read your Time Bureau
agent manual earlier...
What? That thing is over 200 pages.
Yeah, and I started thinking,
it's not about the how they blew us up,
it's about the who.
I made a list of suspects.
Do you wanna see?
- Um, yes. Yes, I do!
- Great.
Time to spill the beans, Lewandowski.
What did you say?
- Please, you're making a mistake.
- I'm making a mistake?
I'm making a mistake?
Get out. Out!
No, no, no.
Please.
Sounds like he's really
putting the screws on him.
Let me know if he needs backup.
I gotta take a leak.
Don't do this, Nate.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to tell you
that you don't have to tell me
anything you don't
want to because...
I will find the answers I want
some other way, okay?
This is even worse than last time.
I've interrogated you before?
Of course, you don't remember.
You and your men came after me
and my family and hundreds of others
on your manhunt for Emma Goldman
back in 1919.
I knew nothing about her,
but because of your "Red Scare"
no one believed me.
My wife and children had to flee,
and your men beat me for being Russian.
I lost everything because of you!
I'm sorry, Igor.
Makes total sense
why you were planning on kidnapping me.
Me?
I've tried to stay
as far away from you as possible.
But when you're looking for enemies,
that's all you see.
Makes it easy to miss
what's going right in front of you.
Where did those mountains go?
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
Somebody switched tracks 15 miles back.
Igor.
Thank you, Igor.
I'll untie you in a minute.
Grab him!
The jig is up, Hoover. Get over here.
It's kind of silly, huh?
Put on the right kind of suit
and you can fool anybody you want.
Even America's best detective.
Pretty dumb,
pulling a gun on a Bureau agent.
You think you're the smart guy here?
If you hadn't made such a stink
back in Midland,
we never would have known
you were on this train.
Funny thing is, we've been trying
to pinch you for months.
Snorky's offered a nice chunk of cash
to whoever brings you in first.
Snorky.
Snorky, Snorky?
Who the heck is Snorky?
These guys work for Al Capone.
Come out with your hands up, Hoover!
And so do all of them.
You got two minutes!
I ain't got all day, Edgar!
Come out or we start popping passengers.
Oh, we can totally
take these guys.
No.
Without Gideon
it's hard to keep track of the timeline,
but Hoover wasn't killed
by mobsters, right?
So don't we have to fight?
In the real timeline,
none of this happened.
And the world still thinks I'm Hoover.
I'm gonna have to make this right.
Come on.
Well, congratulations.
You got me.
Who are you?
Damn it.
I'd give the multi-verse
a low probability.
- I mean, what even is a Paragon?
- Mmm-hmm.
I think we are onto something
very important here, Z.
Me too, Aves.
Okay, so who's left
on our villains' list?
Uh, Damien Darhk.
Loves us way too much
to kill us, I think.
Mallus, Mallus, Mallus.
Big Beebo...
Hmm. David Bowie.
You know, he got
that really great song out of us.
- Yeah, it was very catchy.
- Yeah.
- Let's put him in the "maybe" pile.
- Okay.
What about those guys over there?
These guys over here.
We got time pirates,
time wraiths, time witches,
clones, doppelgängers, ourselves,
time itself.
Okay, let's call that the
"Why the hell not?" pile.
Copy that.
Oh.
And then there's this one.
I mean, that's too out there, right?
Sorry. We've been chased by a demon dog.
Who's to say
that we're not being hunted by...
Sara? Ava?
- Is that...
- Guys?
Hello? Anybody?
Hello?
We got a Hoover-shaped Nate problem.
That doesn't sound good.
- Guys.
- Hate to cut it short,
but we could really use
some backup out here.
Yeah, Nate's been kidnapped
by Al Capone's men!
Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
We need to find a way to stop this
with zero casualties.
What, with weed gummies and magic booze?
Yes!
- Yes?
I ain't gonna ask you again.
We want Hoover, not some nobody clown.
You're right. I am a nobody.
But I'm the nobody
who killed J. Edgar Hoover.
- Killed?
- Yeah.
I'm supposed to bring in the head
of the Bureau of Investigation,
instead I got Mr. Nobody.
This is not the plan.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Ah, Snorky's gonna pop me, for sure.
Doesn't seem fair.
I mean, how could you know
the guy you were supposed to kidnap
ended up getting killed?
Some things are outside of your control.
I could just bump you off
and mess your face up,
real good,
pass you off as Hoover's body.
You can do that.
It may work, for a while, but...
But you can't outrun a lie forever.
Eventually, you'll just end up
hurting the people you care about.
Sometimes it's easier
just to face the music
and accept the fact
that you made a mistake.
Hey, take a deep breath with me.
Come on.
Now repeat after me.
I forgive myself.
- There. Now don't you feel better?
- No.
Oh.
But that makes me feel better.
- You all right there, big guy?
- Better now.
Hoover's death
must have been quite the shock,
so we brought you a little something
to soothe your grieving souls.
And there's plenty more
where that came from.
Oh. Never ending, one could say.
Holy smokes!
The Bullet Blondes!
The big fella loves you gals.
I would like to formally apologize
for how I treated you both.
And I would like to ask for a do-over.
- Already done.
- My man.
Your photographs don't do you justice.
It's a lot of company
for the middle of nowhere.
Boys.
Ladies.
Another Hoover?
I thought you said you killed him.
I... I did.
Okay, two Waveriders and two Hoovers,
that cannot be a coincidence.
Is it me, or does he look
even more pissed off now?
We're kidnapping you.
And I'm arresting you.
In fact, you're all under arrest.
Over our dead bodies!
Maybe we should just skedaddle
right over here, yeah?
Everybody, take cover!
Get in there! Come on! Move it! Go!
We can't let Hoover die again.
I don't think we need to
worry about that.
Whoa, whoa! Whoa, slow!
Wait, wait! Wait, wait, wait...
Look, guys, this is out of control.
The timeline's
at serious risk of changing.
Give me this.
Oh!
Come on.
Oh, no. Did we kill him again?
There's no blood.
Whoa. That dude is tough.
I don't even think he is a dude.
I think he's a...
Robot!
Robot.
What are the chances?
Wait, so robots blew up the Waverider?
J. Edgar Hoover, a robot.
That explains a lot.
I ate a robot?
Sorry stomach and small intestine
and small stomach and third...
Gary, shush. Shush.
You did not eat a robot,
you ate the real Hoover.
This, this must be his replacement.
Guys, what... What is he doing?
Rebooting himself?
Self-destruct sequence initiated.
Twenty seconds.
Guys, I don't think that... Yeah.
We gotta go! Come on, let's go. Move it!
Boy, I hope Spooner and Astra are okay.
They're probably having
the chillest time at Gloria's right now.
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Nine, eight, seven...
Six, five, four...
Three, two, one, zero...
Hey, Gideon. Hey.
I'm sorry.
I'm so used to the old you.
The one who always had all the answers.
I never thought you'd be the one
needing help from us.
Do you think we could try again?
I wish we could figure out a way
to communicate with her.
I mean, she's obviously trying.
Tranquila, mi amor. You'll find a way.
You always did.
Esperanza, you didn't speak
until you were six years old.
I don't remember that.
You communicated with me in other ways.
We always understood each other,
you and I,
even if we weren't using words.
You would come over and hug me,
or hold my hand.
Your little touch,
it made me feel heard.
It's your gift, Esperanza.
Gracias, Mami.
I know this must be tough for you.
I get it.
I know it must be really hard
when no one understands
what you're trying to tell them.
And I hope you that you're not useless.
You're just... figuring it out.
How did I even get here?
- Why can't they understand me?
- I can hear her.
I can hear Gideon's thoughts.
- She's scared.
- What's she saying?
Hey, it's okay. Gideon, I'm right here.
Just breathe and focus.
Dr. Davies' machine in New York City,
time travel experiment
takes place November 7th, 1925.
She's saying Dr. Davies'
time travel experiment
will take place in New York City
on November 7th, 1925.
That's two weeks from today.
Precisely, Captains.
She's back!
That's fantastic!
The plan's gonna work.
Two weeks, maybe that explains
why they're not back yet.
But we have to get to Dr. Davies fast,
or the Legends will die.
Or maybe that's why.
Pack up that ranch wear.
We've got some Legends to save.