Previously on
Legends Of Tomorrow...
What kind of egg is that?
It's a dragon egg.
Okay, you got possessed by Neron.
Can't stop.
I give up. You hear me, Neron?
Spare Nate, and I'll let you have me.
Neron?
I can make you whole again.
My nipple.
Gary, no.
Nora, I need your help.
I'm asking you to face another demon
as a member of the Time Bureau.
Let's do this.
All right,
enough of the sightseeing.
Can we go now?
I'm a bit knackered,
to be honest with you, mate.
We're not here as tourists, Johnny.
All right, you're gonna get rid of me
in some dramatic fashion.
Get on with it, will you?
I'm not gonna kill you. Not yet anyway.
- I need you for a favor.
- Is that right?
Mmm. I need you
to open up a doorway to Hell.
Oh, right, well, why didn't you say so?
I will gladly open up a vortex
right here
and give you the old heave-ho
into the great beyond.
The door is not for me, Johnny.
It's to bring someone here
from the other side.
Tabitha.
Ah, that's right. If she comes
straight through the doorway,
she doesn't need a human vessel.
And what in that demented
demon brain of yours
makes you think that I'm going
to open a vortex for you, mate?
Unlike Gary,
I've still got both my nipples
so you don't have much to bargain with.
Speaking of which,
what have you done with the muppet?
Gary's just fine.
He's back at the Time Bureau
taking care of business.
Okay, Nora, you can do this.
Just be normal.
Hey, you can be normal
because you are normal...
Next!
Come on!
That's your ID picture?
They wouldn't let me retake it.
It can't be that bad. Let me see.
Uh...
Maybe we'll just use your photo
from the wanted poster.
So, your ID's in process.
And you have me to help you
with your orientation.
All that's left is this.
What the hell is that?
It's your start paperwork.
No, I should be out looking for Ray.
I really need to fill all this out?
I know. I know, Nora.
But until we have a line on Neron,
there's really nothing we can do.
And let's be honest, Nora,
you have a storied history here.
I need you to prove
that you can be a team player.
Have fun.
Oh, and you know what, Nora?
I'm really, really proud of you.
Welcome to the Bureau.
Director Sharpe.
I've been waiting for you.
Gary, I told you no playing
with my chair until after hours.
Oh. Playtime's over. Shut the door.
We need to talk.
If Neron wanted John dead,
he would've killed him on the spot.
He must need something from him.
We have to find him
before he can get what he wants.
And who knows what he's doing
in Ray's name,
or his perfectly grass-fed,
organic-butter body.
If Haircut's even there.
We don't know that Ray is gone.
Look, everybody, just breathe.
Gideon's already on it.
I've attuned the magicometer
to Constantine's frequency.
When he uses his abilities,
I can zero in on his location.
And what do we do till then?
- Stress eat?
- Drink.
Yeah. How'd you lot survive until now?
Look, until we get an alert, we wait.
Right. We wait.
I gotta go clear my head.
What do you think
this is about?
With everything that's been going on,
I bet Director Sharpe
is about to lay down the plan of attack.
I've gathered you here because today,
we're setting time aside
to conduct performance reviews.
But this time,
I thought it would be useful if you were
assessed by one of your peers.
Agent Gary Green.
Gary?
Thanks, doll.
How are my babies doing?
Let's rap for a sec.
Is Gary cool now?
That's impossible.
Now, I know performance reviews
can be quite a drag,
but this year's gonna be different
'cause you've got Super Agent Gary Green
in your corner, so no need to stress,
unless your infraction
is looking too good in that suit.
Agent Reyes
knows what I'm talking about.
Oh, my God, I think she just swooned.
This is a nightmare.
So I'll be meeting with agents
one-on-one,
and, uh, wait till I call your name.
Looking forward to some good face-time.
Ava, are you sure this is the best time
for performance reviews?
There's no better time to assess
the performance of our operation.
But are you sure Gary is qualified
for responsibilities?
Of course, Mona.
Gary Green is all the man we need.
Oh, my.
What a big, scary knife you've got.
I'd sooner be filleted
than do your bidding.
This knife is not for you.
It's for Raymond.
The human body is fascinating
and delicate and fragile.
Did you know
that if I cut this artery right here,
it will take only a matter of minutes
before Ray's body goes into shock
and eventually expires?
Hey, big man, come on,
I know you're in there.
Snap out of it, eh!
Ray's gone.
I've taken over his body.
We made a deal,
and you of all people should know
what it means to
make a deal with a demon.
No, if Ray was still in here,
would he do this?
I knew I could make you use your magic.
Great. Yeah. So you got me.
What's that big grin all about, then?
Patience.
You'll see.
Huh.
I always took you to be more Springsteen
than "The Rite of Spring."
It's not for me, it's...
I read that classical music
is good for babies.
Wow. This is very, uh, impressive.
Yeah, I found a book about dragons
in Constantine's collection.
"The egg must incubate under the mother
at her body temperature
lest the egg expire."
Yeah, I'm not gonna sit on that thing.
I figured as much.
That's why I got a heat lamp.
We have to do everything possible
to make sure nothing bad
happens to this egg.
Hey...
Hmm.
The egg's gonna be okay, I know it.
Wait till Ray sees that
we have a dragon.
- He's gonna love it.
- Yeah.
I've picked up an alert
with Constantine's magical signature.
That's them.
The signal is coming
from 1.3 million years ago.
That's the Ice Age.
He's in the part
of North America
that would come to be known
as "The Donner Pass,"
named after a doomed group of settlers
in the 1800s
who resorted to cannibalism
after their food supplies ran out.
There's such a thing
as too much exposition, Gideon!
A-ha! There they are.
Our heroes.
Captain Lance.
Thanks for coming all this way.
If you're looking for Ray,
he's, uh, checked out.
Is Neron on comms?
But if you'd like to join him,
I can make arrangements.
Sara, open fire now!
This may be your only chance.
We can't fire, that's Ray!
Ray made a deal with a demon. He's gone.
We can't lose anyone else
to this bastard! Do it!
What about you?
Blow us both to Kingdom come!
I'll be happy to go down for the cause.
- Gideon, ready the blasters.
- Yes, Captain.
Whoa, whoa. Hold up.
If we kill Neron in Ray's body,
we lose Ray forever.
If you let Neron walk, then things are
gonna get much, much worse, trust me.
Sara?
Come on, boss.
Something's wrong.
Awaiting orders, Captain.
Gideon...
Fire!
It's a trap!
We gotta move. They're getting away!
Get us out of here, Gideon!
That's not good!
By my calculations,
we're buried
beneath 357 feet of ice and snow.
Plus, our primary temporal delineator
has been rendered non-functional
with the extreme weather.
So that's it, then.
We're just snowed in?
Yeah, at the Donner Pass.
No one's turning me into beef jerky!
Everyone, calm down.
Gideon, hail the Bureau.
Should we leave a voicemail?
Ava will get the alert.
In the meantime, we wait.
Gideon, how long until the ice thaws?
The Ice Age ends
in 11,121 years.
All right, who are we eating first?
'Cause shotgun, not.
Captain, we're running
on reserve power.
I recommend disabling
all non-essential functions
to conserve energy for life support.
Do it. We need to be responsible
and conserve power.
Cut off the main generator,
the fabricator and the thermostat.
Neron is out there
with Ray and Constantine,
all because we fell for his trap,
because you fired on Ray!
And what was your plan, pretty?
Beat him to death in a snowball fight?
We were supposed to take him in,
not take him out, Mick.
Ray's gone.
When a team member goes dark,
you end them before they end you.
Rory, with me.
You made the call,
you're helping us get out of here.
No problem.
All right.
I just assumed I'd go out alone anyway.
First, you kill my friends,
and now you bring me
to this miserable era.
Oh, Johnny, quit being such a cry baby.
I just did what I had to do.
Can't have your friends
getting in the way
of us creating that door to Hell.
There's still no way I'm helping you.
Besides, the vortexes I make
are strictly one-way. They suck you in.
Don't you think if my magic was powerful
enough to stabilize a vortex,
I wouldn't have saved Desmond or Astra?
Yes, and that's why we're here.
As powerful as your magic is,
you can always teach
an old dog new tricks.
Yeah.
And it's more than magic
that you need to learn.
Yeah, right. So, I'm supposed
to learn something
off one of these yokels, am I?
Oh, Johnny, not from them,
from a king.
Hold on a minute,
that bloke's got my face.
That's because he's your ancestor,
King Constantine, ruler of these parts.
And progenitor
of your magical bloodline.
What kind of creature
do you think they're hunting?
I can't be sure,
but I'm guessing it wasn't rabbits.
Make way for your king.
Start paperwork, am I right?
My forms keep getting rejected
because records show
I am 15
and living in a mental institution.
I forget that we don't have
normal problems anymore.
Speaking of which, Ava's having Gary
do performance reviews.
Okay.
I mean, he's not my first choice
for responsibilities,
- but don't we have bigger issues?
- Exactly!
And when I pointed that out,
Ava shut me down.
Not to stereotype, but I think
a clone might have replaced her
and we need to look into it.
- No.
- Yes.
No!
I just earned my freedom,
and I don't want to get caught
going behind Ava's back.
You heard what she said,
I need to focus on being a team player.
She said, "Gary is all the man we need."
That's not weird to you?
Why is that weird?
Gary Green is all the man we need.
Okay. I will check on Gary,
and you contact the Waverider
and see if Sara knows anything.
And then,
we're gonna find out what form 37-C is.
Okay.
Ah, this is useless.
Why don't we just blast a way off?
Using your heat gun
in here, Mr. Rory,
will deplete our low supply of oxygen.
Yeah, ease up, Mick.
Last time you pulled the trigger,
we ended up here.
You're pissed at me for firing on Erica.
Oh, well, it's a good thing
that this Snart bloke
kept a supply of jackets,
though, isn't it?
They smell good, too, actually.
What is that? Is it sandalwood?
Look, I'm pissed at you
because that wasn't your call to make.
Someone had to make it.
It was our only chance
to take out Neron.
I made the call you should have.
All right, guys, come on.
Just pick away, will you?
No, this is good. All of a sudden,
now you care about the mission?
Where were you
when Neron took Ray in the first place?
Oh, you're gonna put that on me as well?
All right. As much
as I wanna watch you guys duke it out,
let's save it
for when we're not freezing to death.
You know what? Both of you,
off scamming people
at some book convention,
while there is a demon on our ship.
Hmm. Let me get this straight, Captain.
You're the only one that can have fun
outside of this rusted bucket of bolts.
All you do
is spend time with the girlfriend,
and nothing's ever, ever your fault.
You know what? You have all the answers.
You get us out of here.
Oh, when I was a boy,
we used to run wild
in these woods around the village.
Not a care in the world.
Now these same woods
where your children play today,
and where my hunting party
just encountered
another dangerous beast,
that threatens not just our safety,
but our entire way of life.
Oh, this bloke is right tedious.
Why are we here?
'Cause I want you to learn
that it was your ancestor that created
the rift between humans
and magical creatures.
And why would he do that?
Because fear is a powerful source
of energy for magic.
The more he exploits these creatures
to stir up fear in his people,
the more powerful his magic becomes.
I come from a long line of bastards,
but not even we would resort to that.
- Because your kin are always so right.
- Yes.
And if the king is sending
this creature to Hell,
then surely it deserves it.
Do you really think that
everyone in Hell deserves to be there?
What about Astra?
Or Raymond Palmer?
Or my Tabitha?
This is your opportunity
to make things right.
Starting with her.
You know, if your plan is
to guilt me into doing what you want
by showing me the sins of my forefather,
it ain't working, sunshine.
...but to another.
Behold! The unholy beast.
Hold on a minute, that's a Puca.
It may not look threatening,
but sometimes in order to see
the true nature of a creature,
one must draw it out.
No, no, no, he's got it all wrong.
They aren't evil.
I guess your bloodline isn't
as righteous as you think it is.
He's clearly misinformed.
Well, if you think that,
maybe you should go
and have a chat with the king.
You are truly blessed that I am here.
For I alone can save you
from these monsters,
and tonight at the rise of the low moon,
I will banish this creature
straight to Hell.
Agent Powell,
please report to my office
for your performance review.
Just need to signal the Waverider.
That's weird.
What are you doing in here?
Uh...
Just thought I would check
on the timeline.
Yep. Looks good.
Do you have clearance for this?
Have you completed
your performance review?
Yes. I've had my performance review.
And? How did it go?
Gary Green is all the man we need.
Gary Green
is all the man we need.
- Nora?
- You were right. We have to talk.
But we can't do it here.
The heat lamp must have turned off
when Sara shut down the generator.
It's okay, Wickstable.
You're gonna be okay.
Wait. What did you call it?
Wickstable.
The drawing I made of Heyworld
when I was a kid,
the one that inspired my dad,
the dragon in it, I named it Wickstable.
So I thought we could just name it that,
but I'm open to other ideas.
No, uh, I like, I like Wickstable.
Our little Wicksty.
I can't believe
I'm about to say this,
but I think it needs
skin-to-skin contact
like the book said.
I think it's working.
Hey, uh, why does it feel like
we skipped past all the fun stuff into,
you know, this?
We can still do the fun stuff.
- What about the egg?
- Uh...
There's other ways we could create heat.
Seriously, dude?
Yeah.
Come on, Gideon, there's got to
be a way to boost the engines.
Ray would know how to read this.
How much longer do we have
on life support?
Power reserves
are at 34 hours, Captain.
- Hey, you got a second?
- Not now, Rory.
I actually came here to apologize
for blowing up before.
Well, that's...
Thank you.
- And I should've never...
- And another thing.
Give it up, Charlie.
Why were you wearing my face?
Were you about to apologize?
- Only because Charlie was catfishing me.
- All right. Shut up.
Do you think Ray would be fighting
right now?
No. He would be trying
to get us out of here.
Yeah, you're right.
He's always got a plan, it's annoying.
All right. Let's search Ray's quarters,
see if we can find something helpful.
Thanks.
Hmm.
I tried talking to Ava,
and all she'd say was,
"Gary Green is all the man we need."
Gary must be controlling
the Bureau somehow.
It's those performance reviews.
If we can find out how he's doing it,
maybe we can find a way
to snap them out of it.
I can try tapping into my power,
see if I can read him.
- If I can get to his office...
- No.
We're all we have left.
We can't risk losing each other.
I've got it.
We'll tell Gary you found some security
issues in the containment cells.
You walk him over here, like this.
Then I'll close the cell doors
and you courier out, trapping him.
That's a great idea.
Yeah, just like that.
Okay, it works.
You can let me out now.
I'm sorry I can't do that right now.
Sure you can. Just use the hand thing.
No, Mona, you need a timeout.
Gary Green is all the man we need.
No.
Go and tell the others
to prepare the ritual for tonight.
As you wish, my lord.
You're wasting your time
focusing on that monster.
A Puca
only reflects the person it's with.
It's only angry
because you scared the fur off it.
That creature doesn't deserve
to go to Hell.
I see not why I should heed
the advice of a stranger.
Then perhaps you will heed
the advice of your kin.
I know not of any kin
outside of this village,
and yet the similarities
in your features...
I am a cousin from afar
and a practitioner of magic like you.
If you wanna rid your village
of a real monster,
then I know of a demon in our midst
that we can banish together.
A demon?
In my village?
Well, then lead the way, my kin.
Put this face-stealer
with the other creature.
Aye, my liege.
Hell shall have two more guests
by the end of the night.
"Cards to save the timeline.
A team-building card game
by Ray Palmer."
Ugh.
I miss hating him.
Do you remember that night
we all met standing up on that rooftop,
and Rip told us
that we were gonna be Legends?
Mmm-hmm.
Embarrassing.
You know what?
We're the last of the originals.
Weird.
Yeah, weird.
Legends were different back then.
We were different back then.
Look, I know that book convention
was important to you.
And I'm really glad that you got to go.
I'm glad you have Ava.
Thanks.
Guess we're growing up,
and hopefully not growing apart.
Ah. Here we are.
What is it?
"Ray Palmer's Survival Guide."
Yes, it is.
Oh.
Hey.
"What to do if you're caught
in an avalanche."
Oh. What does it say?
We've already tried all of these.
"If all fails,
remember you still have each other,
so enjoy that as long as it lasts."
Ah. We're dead.
Yeah.
Maybe.
Hey, it's all right, little one.
I don't bite.
I see your talk went well.
I knew you'd be here.
So, I come from a long line
of bloody bastards. Big reveal.
Have you even considered what it's
really gonna be like for you in Hell?
With all those pissed off folks
you sent there
just waiting for you.
- Including my Tabitha.
- Tabitha...
Who is this bird anyway?
Why is she so important?
- Who is she?
- Yeah.
Just like your ancestor.
So convinced you're always right,
you don't even know
who you're sending away.
Fitting that he's
about to do the same to you.
But once you see how powerful
magic can be when fueled by fear,
then you can save yourself
from being sucked into Hell.
Oh, you'd love for me to stabilize
that vortex, wouldn't you?
You see the thing is,
I'm not afraid of going down.
I've always counted on the fact
that I'd end up there one day,
no matter what.
And what about this innocent creature
beside you?
Well, I guess I'm just a bloody bastard,
then, aren't I?
What's the bad news now?
Oh. No bad news and no more fighting.
Gideon, fire up the ship.
If I do that, life support
capacity will be reduced by half.
You heard me, Gideon.
Turn on the fabricators
and turn on the heat.
I'm thinking s'mores,
maybe some hot cocoa.
- The captain's gone mad.
- She's not mad.
She's right.
I could go for a s'more.
Look, Ray would want us
to have faith that we will escape.
He wouldn't want us cold and miserable.
So right now we are going to enjoy
our time together.
Let's go.
Finally. Let's get some music goin'.
Who's gonna bring me food
if I'm stuck in here?
This is how I'm gonna die, isn't it?
Without any books or laughter
in the basement
of a government building!
Whoa.
You're right. I'm not alone.
I have you.
I'm sorry you're stuck here with me,
little one.
You should be out there in the woods
frolicking about.
Or whatever it is
you Pucas get up to these days.
Well, to tell you the truth,
I'm bloody well terrified.
No.
It's not the eternity of torture.
Or all the people
who are after my head, no.
It's that I'll have to watch
Raymond and Astra.
And all the others I have failed
be tortured along with me.
I even led the Legends to their death,
and you're next in line.
Yeah, that's right. You sense
the rottenness inside me, don't you?
No better than the bloody king.
Why would you heal a bastard like me?
Up with you. Time to see the king.
Come on, then, little one.
Let's go see what this party
is all about, shall we?
We live in a world
of wonder and amazement.
At times, it's beautiful, breathtaking.
At other times cruel, dangerous...
and monstrous.
Before you are two foul creatures
of the dark.
One, a grotesque woodland creature
that would not hesitate
to tear out your heart.
The other, an impostor.
A wielder of the dark arts
that would usurp my very body and soul.
Now, my people.
I seek your wisdom in these matters.
What would you have me do
with such wretched beasts?
To Hell. To Hell.
To Hell. To Hell. To Hell. To Hell.
To Hell. To Hell. To Hell.
We're very excited for you to receive
your performance review.
But what actually happens
at the meeting?
Feel free to give me any spoilers.
Don't worry. I had my doubts, too.
But then I met with Gary and realized
Gary Green is all the man we need.
Bye.
Please step forward, Miss Wu.
Take a seat
and make yourself comfortable.
Mint?
- Uh... No, thanks.
- Don't mind if I do.
Let's see.
Mmm.
I see you've made quite an impression
in your brief time here.
But lately, you've been slacking off.
It says right here,
you've been very disloyal
to the Time Bureau.
Not yet, Wolfie.
All right, I'll judge this round.
"You and your team
are stuck in a trash compactor
in an impromptu
and possibly fatal homage to Star Wars.
What do you do?"
Boom, that's the one.
Yep.
Ooh. Gonna have to go with "steel up"
as Sara scales the wall.
- Another point for me.
- Favoritism.
Why would I display favoritism?
'Cause you two are obviously shagging.
- What?
- Hmm?
- Yeah.
- Yes, finally!
This is great. Maybe you guys
won't be so weird now.
Okay, I'll judge next.
"A teammate turns on you,
lost to the dark side.
What do you do?"
"Escape via musical number."
Not this time.
"Fabricate evening-wear
and infiltrate a party."
You guys know I love a good party sneak.
"Don't give up on each other.
Work together.
You're more than a team.
You are a family."
Well, I guess
that card's a winner, then.
Point to Charlie, I'm on the board.
What the hell was that?
Due to your reckless use
of our rapidly depleting energy,
internal temperature of the ship
has melted the surrounding ice
enough to shake the ship loose.
- What do we do?
- We work as a team.
Zari, engine room.
Get the thrusters back online.
Seal the Cargo Bay. You two with me.
My dear people,
I hear your cries and feel your anger.
And, therefore, by your command,
I send these creatures
where they belong.
Straight to Hell!
Straight to Hell! Straight to Hell!
Be gone, you unclean beasts.
Come on, Johnny.
You know what you need to do.
Oh, bollocks.
Run. Run.
What have you done?
I've used your own magic against you.
We may be kin, but we are not the same.
You may not agree with my methods,
but I will always protect my people.
Now, the question is, Miss Wu,
what shall we do about your disloyalty?
Uh...
Maybe, I lose my snack room privileges
for a week.
Oh, no. Not my almonds.
Oh.
I wouldn't worry about your almonds,
because as I'm sure you've heard,
Gary Green is all the man you need.
Now, gaze into the nipple.
Wolfie, now!
What's a wolfie?
Wolfie?
Bravo. I knew you could exploit fear
to make yourself even more powerful.
Well, it looks like you taught
this old dog some new tricks after all.
But now I'm gonna use those new tricks
to strike you down.
You know,
I do have a few tricks of my own.
We're running
on very low reserve power.
The odds of us successfully
pushing through the avalanche above us
are 3,720 to 1.
Never tell me the odds, Gideon.
Everyone, hold on tight.
- Oh, this better work.
- It will.
- You got Wicksty?
- Yeah, I'm not letting go.
Come on. Come on.
- Boom!
- Whoo!
Yes!
All systems
are back online, Captain.
Fantastic, Gideon.
Now, let's go find Constantine and Ray.
Damn executive privacy button. Uh...
Hey, can you do me a solid
and press that button, over there?
Do you really think
I'm letting you get out of here alive?
Help!
Get away from him, you beast.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
But I'm guessing he had something
to do with it.
Whoa.
It may be too late to save Ray,
or Desmond, or the Legends.
But at least I'll get to send you back
where you belong.
Oh, you bastards. You did it.
You bloody survived.
I've never been so happy
to be wrong in my life.
Don't do it, John. Don't kill him.
Don't give up on Haircut.
What are you going to do, Johnny?
You're all out of moves.
No, I'm not.
I'll see you lovely lot in the end.
I'm gonna save Ray.
John.
The magicometer is picking up
strange activity on the ground.
Tabitha, show yourself.
So wonderful to be back.
Brimstone was so awful
for my complexion.
But you look ravishing, my love.
- Hold on. Is he kissing...
- Ugh. The Fairy Godmother.
Is that tongue?
More singing.
We're so screwed.
Come with me, my pet.
Let's find you a new host.
It's his nipple.
He tried to hypnotize Mona
with his nipple.
His nipple.
Neron gave you back your nipple,
which became bad in Hell.
Which is now poisoning your mind
and making you evil,
and that's why you came back
to the Time Bureau.
So that you could nip-notize everyone
and Neron could take over.
Yeah.
You will do no more harm
with your nipple.
No, no! No, please. No!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It wasn't me, it was my nipple.
I swear.
Save me.
As you wish.
You have to go.
Tell the Legends what's going on.
- What about you?
- I'm not leaving Mona behind.
Always knew you were a team player.
- Ava. You okay?
- It's a long story.
But Gary took over the Bureau.
He nip-notized everyone.
Yeah, you're gonna have to explain that.
The germ turned?
- It's not just him. It's Neron and...
- Fairy Godmother... Tabitha.
- She's Tabitha?
- Yeah.
- You missed a lot.
- And Ray is still in Hell.
I know he hasn't given up,
so we're not going to give up on him.
Now, let's do this. For Ray.
Bloody hell.