Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Your shape shifting
days are over, sweetheart.
He decided to exploit her
for information
and to help us track down
other Fugitives.
I know you're writing a novel
and it's really good.
Taco delivery. My name's Mona.
So, what's a Time Bureau?
That was supposed to be top secret.
I'm not losing another kid.
The magic he used
was pretty powerful.
If magic has him on death's door,
then maybe magic can save him.
I think I know someone who can help.
There's got to be
another way to fix him.
Something Gideon missed.
John used magic to save
those kids at the camp.
Magic's the only
thing that can fix him.
And you really think
Nora Darhk is the answer.
She's the only witch I know.
Can we even find her?
That is the problem.
She has a time stone.
She could literally
be anywhere or any-when.
The Bureau can't seem to find her.
You know, when I was a kid,
there was this one escaped
con that my dad was after.
And everyone assumed
that he had fled the country.
You know where he found him?
Not a block from the police precinct.
Do you really think she's hiding
in the Bureau's backyard?
Gideon, do a Nora Darhk
facial recognition scan
of 2018.
I have located a potential match.
That's her.
Right in the Bureau's backyard.
Great work, Detective Lance.
Captain, our systems
have identified the presence
of a new Fugitive.
This one is in 1951 Tokyo.
All right, let's divide and conquer.
I'll go take care of Tokyo
you go find our witch.
Make her fix our warlock.
Everybody to the bridge.
We got a Fugitive alert.
Hello? Can anyone hear me?
- Crap!
- Hey.
Closed door means stay out.
Sorry, Sara called a team meeting.
- Were you...
- Yes.
I was watching porn.
On a typewriter?
Hey, no judgment here.
All right, Andiamo los case.
Chop! Chop!
'Oy, enough shouting.
That my whiskey?
It was.
Oh, well, look
who finally pried themselves
away from their important business.
Look, hobbies are very important.
Right, Rory?
I take my porn very seriously.
Okay, back to work.
In the summer of 1951, a film
screw shot footage of a monster
in Tokyo Bay.
Two days later,
the city was destroyed.
We need to get that footage
before any panic sets in
and to capture that monster
before it can do any real damage.
And because we're shorthanded,
you're up.
Time to earn your keep.
Oh, I didn't ask to be here, Mum.
But you are a Fugitive.
So, your choices are help us out,
go back in your cage.
Bloody humans.
All right, fine.
But it's only to stop you
blinkered lot from giving
a harmless monster
a one-way ticket to hell.
At least with me there,
the poor chap gets a fair shake.
I like her. Yes. I like her.
As you can see, Mr. Heywood,
the Time Bureau is putting
your money to great use.
We now have multiple teams
deployed throughout history
tracking down and securing Fugitives.
All trained by your son.
We only have the most highly
qualified Time Bureau personnel
dealing with... oh, boy. And...
Here's Gary with a live one.
Oh, say hello to Baba Yaga.
We caught her trying to
eat Chinese gymnasts
at the 2008 Olympics.
- Sorry about that, sir.
- What did she say?
Just a typical Russian greeting.
Are you sure this room
is secure enough
to hold these creatures?
It's a temporary arrangement
until our containment facility
is up and running, sir.
And they're heavily sedated,
right, Gary?
Yup. Double doses of elephant
tranquilizer all around.
This way.
Well, Director Sharpe,
looks like you have
things under control here.
Yes, sir. We sure do.
I'll be seeing you tomorrow
for Thanksgiving.
Your mother's really looking
forward to it and so am I.
Oh, I wouldn't miss it for the world.
What are you doing
for the holiday, Director Sharpe?
Me? Oh, well I was planning
on spending it
with my girlfriend,
but she's working overtime.
So, I'll probably just be
sticking around here, I guess.
You should join us.
It'll be fun, right, Nathaniel?
- Absolutely. Absol...
- Bye, sir.
Yeah, that is if you don't
mind starving all day
while your family slowly
gets loaded and starts fighting
and then your dad gets called
for a "work emergency."
Well, at least your family
are real people.
Mine are actors.
According to historical record,
the director we're looking for,
Ishiro Honda,
should be in this stage.
Oh, I'm feeling a little conspicuous.
Just ask like you belong.
No one will question it.
You. Coffee, now.
- Hai.
- Yeah, see?
It's all about confidence.
All right, you guys know your cover?
Yup.
I beg your pardon,
but this is a closed set.
Are you Ishiro Honda,
the film director?
Honda-san, pleasure to meet you.
We're Producers from K&G Pictures.
We got word of an unusual
animal sighting out in the bay.
We were told that you might
have some footage suitable
for our news reel.
How do you know about that?
We're from Hollywood.
We know everything.
Oh, gracias.
You must have misheard.
We were out on location
by the sea, yes,
and we saw a whale,
and that was it.
You're sure it wasn't something else?
Something strange?
Perhaps we can take a look
and see for ourselves.
I'm afraid the footage
was ruined during transport.
I'm sorry.
It truly is impossible.
Nah, bloke's lying.
Oh, finally. Something we agree on.
- Stay here.
- What? Where are you going?
To find that film.
Oh, not if I find it first.
I have to go now.
Mr. Honda? Mr. Honda?
Could... could
we trouble you for a tour?
Of course, please.
When we are on a mission,
I give the orders.
Whose rubbish idea was that?
You are lucky
I am a reformed assassin.
It's quite a remarkable effect.
If we shoot at low angles
with a wide lens,
it feels as though we are ants
in this enormous city.
That is fascinating.
It's got to be
in his office somewhere.
If I was hiding something,
I would put it where
no one else would look.
Like under a bloody bomb.
Genius.
It'd look amazing on fire.
Thank you so much for the tour.
If you are ever in Burbank,
be sure to look us up.
I've successfully digitized the film
and it's ready for viewing.
Roll it, Miss G.
What is that under the water?
Guys, I think we're going
to need a bigger time ship.
Okay, what is it?
You're supposed to be
the Fugitive expert.
Oh, well that's no Fugitive.
So what, it's just
some other magical monster
that's not supposed to be here?
Maybe you just haven't met this one.
Or maybe if you weren't
so quick to blame us Fugitives
for everything,
you'd see the more likely scenario.
That creature is man-made.
It's probably a mutant or something.
Created by one of the countless
nukes you humans dropped
on the Pacific in this era.
Or didn't you think of that?
Nice try, genius,
but if that were true
we wouldn't have got a magic alert.
So, why are we here?
Oh, you're the time traveler.
Why don't you figure it out?
Okay. Gideon,
scan Tokyo Bay for any
unusual marine activity.
Right away, Captain.
Hopefully Ray's having better luck.
I had a dream like this once.
Maybe more than once.
More mead, wench.
As you wish.
Oh, a thousand pardons.
A Palmer Tech phone?
Great software.
Terrible hardware.
My phone!
Get ye out of my sight, scoundrel.
- What?
- Oh.
I'm just... What are you doing here?
- I need your help.
- What?
Chris and Tyson,
you two get back here right now!
- Hi, Nate.
- Hey, Patty.
- This is...
- Hey...
Ava Sharpe.
Hi, Grandma!
That's my grandma, Violet.
Do not let her rope you
into playing cards.
It's a lose-lose situation.
And there's my Uncle Rich.
Don't mention Obama.
- There he is.
- Hey!
Good to see you, son.
Glad you could make it,
Director Sharpe.
- Thanks, sir.
- You must be Ava.
- Hi.
- Oh, hi.
Thank you so much
for letting me join you.
Oh, of course.
We wouldn't want you all alone
on such a special day.
He's into the good stuff.
Nate, show her around.
Make her feel at home.
- Wow.
Oh, your family seems nice.
Oh, it's still very early.
Okay, everyone,
the turkey is almost done...
- Wait for it.
- Brining.
Yeah, it just has to sit
for another hour and a half
and then I'm going to pop it
into the oven.
So, that means dinner is when?
- Give or take six hours.
- What?
Oh, my God.
- Tyson!
- Buckle up, Ava Sharpe.
It's going to be a bumpy ride.
Happy Thanksgiving, Mr. Green.
Hi, Mona.
Thanks for bringing me
food on a holiday.
It's literally my job.
Why are you working on
Thanksgiving?
What's the Time Bureau do anyway?
It's like Groundhog Day.
Oh, we regulate time zones.
So, you got any plans
for the big meal?
Heck yeah, I do.
My family's in LA,
so it's just me, instant ramen,
and Bestflix binging.
Oh, well, if you want you could,
have Thanksgiving with me.
That's really sweet, Mr. Green.
But I don't want to eat all
of your food.
Oh, I happened to have
ordered enough for two.
You're vegetarian, right?
Nora Darhk, what the blooming
hell are you doing here, eh?
I owed this guy a favor.
She shouldn't be here, mate.
I thought I warned you.
Can you help him?
Gideon is showing strange
marine activity in this area.
Fish disappearing on masse,
seismic tremors...
Do you need all that just to end up
back where the film was shot?
Just being thorough.
Using fancy toys instead
of your noggins, more like.
You know, I think I liked you
better when you were in a cage.
All right. Enough.
All we got to do is draw
this thing out,
we shrink it down,
and we're good to go.
And how do you expect us
to do that?
We'll just summon it with
a friendly call?
"Oy, monster, come up here.
Promise it's not a trap."
Or feed it like that guy.
Isn't that our friend
the film director?
- Feeding the whales, Mr. Honda?
- What?
You. What are you doing here?
You first.
Start talking.
What the hell is that?
It's evil.
Truly evil.
I think we found our Fugitive,
but it's not a monster.
No.
This is something much, much worse.
This, chaps, is no ordinary diary.
It's an agent of Brigid.
Brigid.
The Celtic goddess of art,
creation, and healing.
This book has the power
to make the imagination...
a reality.
You are not film producers, are you?
No, we are not. But we saw
what was on that film, Ishiro,
and we're here to stop it.
Tell us how you found the journal.
I was out scouting for my film.
And I found this book.
You didn't find the book
it found you.
It's drawn to creative types.
Once I opened it,
I was flooded with inspiration.
An image that has honed
in my nightmares.
Suddenly came to life on those pages.
And then to my horror...
in real life.
I told you this book is evil.
Whoa, hold on a tic.
Brigid created this book
as a gift to you humans.
To bring your dreams to life.
You turned it into a weapon.
She's right.
I did create something horrible.
- What is this thing?
- I call it Tagumo.
A giant land octopus.
Capable of destroying entire cities.
When I realized Tagumo
had come to life,
I tried to destroy the journal.
But it always comes back.
Of course it does.
The power links you in this book.
It won't be released until
the story of your creation
is played out in full.
How did you end it?
You pushed the octopus
in a volcano?
Nope.
Tagumo wins.
Tokyo is destroyed.
- Oh, brother.
- Oh, Rich!
You break it, you bought it, Rich.
Well, this is a disaster.
Hey, no one's killed each other yet.
Chris? Tyson?
Dad, have you seen the boys?
Oh, last I saw them,
they were down in the basement.
Playing with Nate's old air rifle.
Mom!
Guess they know how to load it.
Wow.
Okay, if we can't stop Tagumo,
then draw a new ending.
Preferably one where no one dies.
It's not working.
Like I said,
Brigid created that book
to help artists express themselves.
You can't expect him
to write a happy ending
if he ain't had a happy life.
Ain't that right, Ishiro?
You're right.
Every night,
before this journal came to me,
I'd close my eyes
and be back
in the ruins of Hiroshima.
Choking on ash, wondering
where all the people went.
Not realizing they were
all around me in my hair,
on my clothes,
in my lungs.
They turned to dust.
Drawing Tagumo helped me
turn the nightmares
into something I could understand.
A monster.
But now I am the monster.
Ishiro, you went through
something truly unimaginable.
We all deal with our pain
in different ways,
and you chose art.
And that's beautiful.
Don't blame yourself.
This is not your fault.
So, can you save him?
Life force is the most potent
form of energy in the universe,
and you're like a battery
about to run out of charge.
But you already knew that,
didn't you?
Then why didn't you say anything?
What? And help push you
off the wagon?
You're clean, Nora.
It's best we keep you that way.
You can recharge him, right?
You don't want me to do that, Ray.
Yes, I do.
- Otherwise, he's going to die.
- Ray.
My power comes from my father.
It's in my blood.
It's always going to be calling me,
wanting me to give in
and be consumed,
but I can't give in.
I won't.
Now this is where we monitor
time zone infractions.
Isn't that a little overkill?
No, here at the Time Bureau,
there's no such thing as over kill.
You need to come with me.
Come, come, come.
There's something else amazing
to see right in here.
- Why are you...
- What? Yup.
Oh, Gary? Hello?
I... I think you forgot to unlock
the door.
I am so fired.
Sorry to bother you,
but we have
a bit of a situation in here.
The prisoners are loose.
What? How the hell did that happen?
The tranqs must've worn off.
- Okay, we need to go.
- No, no, no.
We leave, Hank will know
something's wrong.
Something is wrong, Nate.
So, you want our liaison to the DOD
knowing that we messed up?
- No, I don't.
- What do I do?
Shut up, Gary.
- All right, I got a plan.
- Okay.
- I'll be back.
- No, no, no.
Your family's going
to notice that you're gone.
Not if I courier back ASAP.
- Oh... no.
- Just stall.
- No, no.
- Stall!
No, I don't even know... I...
Hey, buddy, you okay?
This is the worst Thanksgiving ever.
- Yeah, scary stuff.
- Yeah.
But, like I said, I have a plan.
So, let's go get our hands
on some tranq guns.
- Okay.
- Oh, my God.
- Is that a Kaupe?
- No.
What the hell is she doing here?
She was supposed to stay
locked in the closet.
I was going to flash her later.
- What?
- That didn't sound right.
Oh, for the love of...
Excellent hiding spot.
Yeah, well, I'm not hiding.
My father sacrificed himself
to give me a second chance.
I don't want to ruin it by
backsliding into dark magic.
Who says it has to be dark?
John needs a magical transfusion.
Normally, I'd have to drain
someone's life to save his.
Well, life force
is essentially energy.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Well, then I have an idea.
Oh, look at this.
Look at this.
Dot, you have outdone yourself.
I hope you all built up an appetite.
Care to do the honors
this year, Nathaniel?
Nathaniel?
Oh, he... he's probably
just in the restroom.
- We should wait for him.
- Mom, I'm hungry.
Me too.
Just a little bit longer, boys.
Oh, I'll go check on him.
Oh, wait... sorry, sir.
Do you know what
we would do in my family?
We'd actually go around
and list all the things
that we're thankful for.
What a lovely idea.
I'm thankful I'm still breathing.
Well, I'll go first then.
I am thankful for so many things.
So many... many things.
I can't believe you guys
have magical creatures here.
This is, like,
the coolest place ever.
Wait.
I've seen this before.
They're hangry.
These poor creatures
are starving to death.
What does a Kaupe, Chupacabra,
and a Baba Yaga eat?
That'd be Hawaiian BBQ,
Birria, and Veal.
Babies, more precisely,
but veal will do in a pinch.
- Really?
- I read a lot.
Wow.
Where are we going to get all
those things on Thanksgiving?
- I'm on it.
- No, get back here.
Ishiro can't change the story.
Plan C it is.
What if we got the book
to bond with another artist?
We could change the story altogether.
Do you see another artist around?
It's not like you can
just find some rando
with a paint brush.
Who knows what they could unleash.
And we're sure there's not
a single artist amongst us?
Why don't we just burn
the damn thing?
Hey, why don't you tell Sara
you're a writer?
Because I'm not.
Rory, I read your novel.
As much as it pains me to say it,
you are very, very talented.
Well, it doesn't matter.
I can't write anymore.
Nothing comes out.
You have writer's block.
No, I dropped a deuce this morning.
Guys?
What is happening?
The Tagumo...
it's headed straight for us.
It's moving fast.
It's getting closer.
- By land?
- It's in the sewers.
Like an octopus,
Tagumo can squeeze through
the tiniest opening.
It's coming for me.
We're not going to let that happen.
Rory, Z? Keep him safe.
Charlie, with me.
What's the plan?
You distract it I'll shake it down.
What? You want me as bait?
Not bloody likely!
Charlie! Damn it.
Get your slimy mitts off of her,
you wanker!
Yeah!
Come more over here, you muppet!
Come and get me!
Yeah!
Bloody brilliant!
Aren't you glad that I came back?
Where did it go?
Sara, how's it going out there?
Good news, we shrank Tagumo.
Bad news, we have no idea
where it went.
Dez.
- Nora, don't.
- Don't talk.
- Save your strength.
- Nora, listen to me.
Listen to me.
As smart as Ray is,
he doesn't understand
what you're about to do.
Choosing a life of magic,
you're either all in or you're not.
There's no half-measures.
And you and I both know
it never leads to a happy ending.
So, if you're going to do this,
you don't do it for Ray.
You don't do it for me.
You do it for yourself, all right?
It's your choice.
And I am thankful for the new
Whole Paycheck grocer
by my work, you know?
Did you know they have
a full bar? And...
And I think you mentioned
everything the rest of us
are thankful for.
So everyone, please, grab a plate.
Oh! We should say Grace, right?
Grace!
I'll check on Nathaniel.
That... just...
Why couldn't I just tell sober,
grounded stories
instead of indulging
in silly monsters?
Sober and grounded is boring.
You had a story to tell
and you told it.
You brought that monster to life.
Don't pretend for a second
you're not a little bit proud.
I was so afraid
of what people would think
of my creation.
And now
that it's here in the flesh...
Story complete.
And I no longer have to fear
what was locked inside my head.
No.
No, you don't.
Pen.
The ink... it's not disappearing.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I want to do this.
Oh, what a rush.
Mona's here with the food.
Listen...
Oh, crap.
Come on out, son. Time to eat.
You know, maybe we should
just start without him.
I'm sure he'll be out soon enough.
Oh, look at that.
Maybe, maybe he went to the store
to grab some Pepto for you know.
I'm going to ask you
this once, Director Sharpe.
What are you hiding from me?
The prisoners have escaped, sir.
My son is alone with those
creatures on the loose?
- You take me there now.
- Sir, it's not safe.
My son is not safe, Director Sharpe.
We're going. End of discussion.
What the hell is this?
Oh, dinner.
The key to any
hangry creature's heart.
We let them fill up and then it's...
night-night again.
This time, without the
life-threatening shenanigans.
Señor, I couldn't find the Tapatio,
but here's some Sriracha.
- What are you doing?
- Quiet, I'm concentrating.
Mick is a writer.
The journal has bonded with him.
Bloody hell. That's it, we're doomed.
We cannot stay here.
Tagumo will find us.
Ishiro!
Meet Garima. Queen of Thanzanon.
- Should we help her?
- No, no, no.
I think she's got it.
Get it, girl!
Yeah!
It's beautiful.
Hi, I'm Mick.
"With the monster vanquished,
"Garima and her beloved Buck
made passionate love
in the ruins of the city."
Okay. Let's go. Now.
Where is everyone?
Your compatriots
grew tired of waiting.
Oh, sorry about that.
Got a bit messy in there.
I'm going to take this with me.
Oh, please.
It clearly likes you.
Your creation was magnificent.
I was thinking about a fourth boob.
Three was plenty.
Listen, Honda-san,
forget about the octopus.
Lizards.
Lizards are king.
This girl can drink.
Care for a nip?
I know it won't quite
make up for the bottle...
bottles that I pillaged.
It's a start.
Look,...
I wasn't too keen on what
you were doing out there.
Hunting Fugitives.
But if someone's got to play copper,
it is a small comfort knowing
that she has a heart.
Don't tell the others.
They'll never listen to me again.
I should've known
you'd had an eye for talent.
Just like your old man.
Your creature handler, she's great.
Oh, yeah, she's gonna...
She's gonna fit right in.
Hey, look, Nate.
I just wished you told me
what was going on.
Honestly, I thought I could
put out the fire
before anyone noticed.
Oh, now I know how
you must've felt
all those times you had to duck
out of the family gatherings.
You're the guy they called
if there was a disaster.
And I may have also
been looking for a way
to get out of the house.
- You old so-and-so.
- Sir.
I know what you're thinking,
but I can assure you
this will never happen again.
You're damn right it won't.
I'm going to green light
additional funding
to fast track the completion
of your containment facility.
Well, thank you so much, sir.
That will help a lot.
And your mother is gonna kill us.
Not necessarily.
Perks of time travel.
We can portal back
into the second after we left.
- That's fantastic.
- Yeah.
Let's make like a tree and leave.
Not sure that's how it goes, but...
- How are you feeling?
- Hunky-dory, love.
You know, in fact, I feel like
I have a new lease on life.
How are you feeling?
Better.
You know, my whole life,
I always believed my power was evil,
and then my dad died,
and I feared using it.
But I saved you,
and for the first time in my life,
my magic doesn't scare me.
Good.
John.
That man I saw.
Who was he?
The past.
Hooray.
Hey, cheers, big man.
And now I am gonna go and satiate
my most wonderful habit.
Gonna have a smoke.
What? No, no, no.
Don't ruin it. We just cured you.
I can't believe that worked.
Well, I for one always...
Always want to see the best
in people.
Even me.
Yeah.
I should be one my way.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Run.
As far as you can.
Don't tell me when and where.
Just go and stay hidden.
But your team will know
you let me go.
- Again.
- And I don't care about that.
I care about you.
And I want you to be free.
This is the Time Bureau.
Nora, what are you doing?
You got to get out of here.
I can't keep running.
You want me to be free?
Repentance is my path to freedom.
It's time for me to pay for my past.
Nora Darhk, hands up.
Get on the ground.
Get on the ground!
You can lay on the long side
Wherever you'll be someone
Staring out at the bayside
If you need me, just throw your gun
Going out with a head start
And kissing you in the pouring rain
We can live on the outside
Or we can live in America
"Garima was as strong
as she was stunning,
"and with her by his side,
"Buck had at last vanquished
his true enemy.
Fear."
Playing games with the lawman
High telling it's time to run
Riding out in the sunset
Screeching tires we hit the road
All right.
It's okay, Dad. Take it.
Take it.
Oh, look at this.
Thanks for getting back to me.
I know it's hard to get away
during the holiday.
The creatures are controllable.
I've seen it.
I don't care how much it costs.
We're going to make this happen.
Project Hades is go.