- In 2166, an immortal tyrant
named vandal savage
Conquered the world and
murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
And stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately,
my plan is opposed
By the body I'd sworn
my allegiance to:
The time masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
But if we succeed,
They will be remembered
as legends.
Previously, on
"legends of tomorrow"...
Savage has kept his movements
hidden throughout history,
But professor aldus boardman
is the world's leading expert.
- Savage was an egyptian priest.
- Kendra and I reincarnate.
- And every time he kills you,
it passes to him.
That's what maintains
his immortality.
- Professor boardman
has sustained
Severe internal injuries.
- 100 years from now,
your lives
Have minimal effect
on the recorded timeline.
- You lied to us.
- I don't give a damn
about being a legend
As long as we end savage
once and for all.
- So how do we find this guy?
- And we've arrived.
Gideon, if you wouldn't mind
camouflaging us
As an alpine meadow, perhaps?
- What are you
complaining about now?
It's not like we time-jumped.
- I hate flying,
especially in...
Whatever this thing is.
- Where exactly are we?
- We're still in 1975, right?
- Indeed.
October 1975 on the fjords
of northern norway.
- Sounds like a vacation.
- Which we can take
as soon as the threat of savage
Has been neutralized, mr. Snart.
- That's aldus's notebook.
- Now he theorized
that savage might
Be here, and if he's right,
And if we can capture savage,
then at least
Professor boardman didn't
die in vain.
- Can't we just go back
and save aldus?
- He was our son.
- Look, I'm sorry.
We can't go back and change
events in which we participated.
Time would fold in on itself,
creating a temporal vortex.
- Which sounds way cooler
than it is.
- Forgetting physics
for a second,
Shouldn't we figure out
what savage is doing in norway?
- According to gideon,
there is a large meeting
Of terrorists and fringe groups
looking to buy illegal arms.
- Now that sounds
like a vacation.
- Arms dealers and terrorists
Aren't exactly
our kind of people,
But they're the next best thing.
- Well, looks like you
and your lapdog
Get to earn your keep.
- I'm no one's lapdog,
bird-man.
- So what exactly does one wear
To a black market arms bazaar,
anyway?
- The waverider has
a fabrication room
Which can fashion
temporally-indigenous,
Uh, fashion.
- You've got a room
that makes clothing?
- Doesn't everyone?
- All right, first thing
we need to do
Is work up a plan.
- Got a lot of experience
Infiltrating criminal
gatherings?
Didn't think so.
I'm calling the shots.
- Actually, I'm in charge,
In case any of you
have forgotten.
- No, I remember.
I just don't care.
- Do I need to remind any of you
that I'm a time master?
Making discrete alterations
to the timeline
Is what I do, so we're not
just gonna charge into the past
Like a bull into a china shop--
- Half of what you've told us
About the mission turned out
to be lies.
- None of you
have ever encountered
Vandal savage before.
I have,
and I'm telling you now,
You are making a big mistake.
- [scoffs] already did that
when we trusted you.
- Back soon, captain.
[ominous music]
♪ ♪
- Looks like
they're checking credentials.
And we don't have any.
- We got this.
Trust us.
- [grunts]
- excuse you.
- Ids.
You don't look like an
amhad ahmed izz-al-din.
- I'm arab.
On my mother's side.
- Is there a problem?
I don't like delays.
Do you know who we are?
My associates and I are the
operational arm of "scimitar."
The lombardo square
bombing, 1963.
Murder of henri tyran,
canada, 1970.
Konig airport massacre, 1971.
Bottom line?
You don't want to doubt me.
[intense music]
- You're a special
kind of crazy.
I like it.
- We're in.
[chattering]
♪ ♪
- So why don't I get
to play terrorist?
- This is just a kidnapping.
No need for your
nuclear fireworks.
Savage'll be one of the buyers.
Once we get eyes on, hang back.
We'll boost him
once this is all over.
- Any sign of him?
- No.
- He's not here, boss.
- Let's get ginger and
the professor and move out.
- If I could have
your attention.
Thank you all for coming.
I promise, it will be
well worth your time.
- Seems we were wrong
about savage.
He's not one of the buyers.
- He's the seller.
- This is a variable-yield
nuclear warhead,
Capable of producing a blast
Equivalent to
one megaton of tnt.
- Shall we begin our bidding at
$100 million?
[gunshot]
$100 million.
Do I hear $105 million?
[gunshot]
$110 million?
$115 million?
- Is everything all right, sir?
- They're here.
[suspenseful music]
That group.
Where are they from?
- It appears we've drawn
some unwanted attention.
We need to bid.
Fire your gun in the air.
[gunshot]
- that's $125 million.
- Um, what's happening?
- Going once...
- It's what's not happening
that is the concern.
- Going twice...
- Nobody else is bidding.
- Sold!
- Congratulations, professor.
You just bought yourself
a nuclear weapon.
- Well, well.
We seem to have a new player.
But you seem a bit academic.
How did you get in here
and who are you?
- As of a few seconds ago,
I'm a nuclear power.
- Yet I don't know you
or your organization,
And I know everyone.
- Hey. Back off.
- Watch your tone.
- Is there some sort
of problem here?
- Yeah, the master race here
is starting to bug me.
- We're just gonna get
our nuclear warhead
And be on our way.
- Not without paying first.
- Once we've validated
that the warhead's operational.
Personally, I find it
highly unlikely
That you were able to accumulate
Enough fissionable material
in this era
To fashion
a workable nuclear device.
- This era?
- Figure of speech.
- I got a feeling
you guys might want to get
Those helmets of yours on.
- Change of plans.
I'll provide a 25% discount
To the organization
which brings me
The heads of these men.
- Can I burn some stuff now?
- I wish you would.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[grunting and screaming]
- [gasps]
Now would be a good time--
- yeah. To kill you.
- I wasn't talking to you.
- Oh!
- Aah!
♪ ♪
[grunting]
- Aah!
♪ ♪
[relentless
bass-heavy drum beat]
♪ ♪
- Savage.
- Prince khufu.
As always, the fashion plate--
- [grunts]
- And your better half.
- This ends here and now,
savage.
You're coming with us.
- I doubt you can
apprehend me...
And stop a nuclear explosion.
[beeping]
[grunting and screaming]
- You screwed that up
pretty good.
- I had it handled.
- I like how you
actually believe that.
[men screaming]
- Aah!
Ugh!
- Um, we got
a nuclear bomb here.
Ray!
What did you do?
- I didn't do anything.
It must have a fail-safe.
- Professor, jax, we need you!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- You have to get
to a minimum safe distance.
- Okay, what now?
- We wait for the warhead
to go off,
At which point you're going to
have .06 seconds
To absorb the massive release
of atomic energy.
- Your plan sucks.
You know that, right?
- Concentrate, jefferson.
♪ ♪
- Aah!
[heavy breathing]
♪ ♪
- Well, I'm really glad you were
the one calling the shots.
- I had it under control
until the professor
Started picking fights
with the plo.
- You let your ego endanger
our entire mission.
- No, mr. Rory's temper got
completely out of control--
- I thought we were friends,
professor.
- At least there's one less
nuclear bomb on the planet.
- [clapping]
here, here.
Now you all deserve
a hearty congratulations.
Not only did you fail
to capture savage,
You exposed yourselves
and your powers to him,
Giving away the element of
surprise for now and all time.
Well done, team.
- We don't need
the element of surprise.
We know he's in norway,
so let's find him--
- Unfortunately, we now have
larger problems than savage.
If only you'd have
listened to me
About the dangers
of upsetting the timeline.
- What are you talking about?
- While you were busy
saving norway
From nuclear annihilation--
- you're welcome, norway.
- Savage sent one of his cronies
Back to the site
of the arms sale.
Anyone care to guess
what he found?
- Whoops.
- I am unversed in modern
american colloquialisms.
Is "whoops" slang for "oh"--
- Yes, dr. Palmer seems to have
Thrown a spanner in the works
for the entire timeline.
- Come again?
- Armed with dr. Palmer's
future technology,
Savage's engineers
develop a weapon
Far more destructive than
anything here in 1975.
This is central city in 2016.
At least it was.
I'm not sure what
the neo-fascists
Who took control of it
are calling it these days.
- [sighs]
- There must be a way
to correct this somehow.
- Fortunately, gideon is just
showing us a forecast
Of the future
you've all created.
Time is like cement.
It takes time
to become permanent.
In this case,
until savage's team
Have worked out the mystery
of your future technology
And molded it to their own ends.
And when they do,
What you see here is
no longer just a forecast.
This...
[sighs]
This is history.
[dark music]
♪ ♪
- Where is he?
His body, I mean.
- There's cryo-storage
in the medbay.
I promise we'll get our son
a proper burial
Once we have a chance.
- It's still so weird
to hear you call him that.
But even though
it was in a past life,
It feels like
something's missing.
- I know.
- What's that?
- I found it in his pocket.
- I've seen this knife before.
This is the knife
that savage used to kill us.
In our first life.
- So thanks to raymond leaving
a piece of his suit in the past,
The rest of us don't have
a future to go back to?
- Unless we do something to
change this course of events,
The future will
become immutable.
- Exactly how much time
do we have?
- Until savage's weapons team
reverse-engineer your tech.
- We're talking 1970s terrorists
With 21st-century weapons.
And since we don't know
where savage went--
- We don't have to find savage.
We just have to find
the other piece of my suit.
Which shrinks because
it's made of an alloy
Which mimics intra-molecular
compression of dwarf star,
Thus emitting alpha particles.
- So we just need
to be able to track them.
Fortunately, alpha particles
are highly trackable.
- Yet unheard of in the 1970s.
It's like we're trapped
in the stone age.
- I'll have you know that I was
researching alpha particles
When you were eating crayons.
- So to track that piece of
raymond's super-suit,
We just need to talk to...
- Me.
25-year-old me, rather.
- You two are just in time.
- Show them, kendra.
- Aldus was carrying this
when he was killed.
It's a newspaper article about
an egyptian dagger.
- The one savage used
to kill us.
- In central city, we learned
that objects associated
With the night of our deaths
can also be used to kill savage.
- According to aldus's notes,
the dagger needs to be wielded
In conjunction with
an incantation inscribed on it.
- What does
this incantation say?
- I don't know.
I can't read the language.
- It's okay.
I'll help you remember.
- Splendid.
Now, as for the dagger...
- You need someone to steal it.
- Okay, fine.
Whatever.
I'll do it.
Article says it was purchased by
some rich russian douche bag
Named sasha mahnovski.
- I'll go with you.
- I already got a partner.
- Who I trust
even less than you.
- Look, you're more than welcome
to go with them.
Just don't take along
any of your future tech.
Oy!
Where do you think you're going?
- To break into my old lab
and bring us back
The particle tracker.
- Fine, but perhaps,
You should take jefferson
and sara with you
To act as your intermediaries.
Look, interacting with yourself
in the past
Can have catastrophic effects
upon the future.
- Fascinating.
Let's go.
- Setting a course
for the united states, captain.
["disco inferno"
by the trammps]
- ♪ I heard somebody say ♪
- ♪ burn, baby burn ♪
- ♪ disco inferno ♪
- People actually
wore this crap?
- People smoked a lot of pot
in the '70s.
It clearly had
a deleterious effect
On the fashion of the era.
- Let's just hurry up
and get that particle tracker
So I can get the hell
out of these go-go boots.
- Remember, when we meet
my former self,
It is imperative that we don't
let on we're from the future,
So let's just be cool.
Oh, my god.
Look.
[gasps]
I'd forgotten
how handsome I was.
My hair, it's so thick
and silky.
- Do I know you?
- No. No.
I'm professor musk. Elon musk.
- Mm.
- And these are my two
lab assistants.
- Hi.
I'm marty.
Are you sure
we haven't met before?
- Uh, that's
a very interesting question.
Um, suffice it to say,
I am familiar with your work.
- That's actually
why we're here.
To see you.
You're a leading expert
in alpha particles?
- [chuckles]
no, I'm the leading expert.
- Well, we were hoping
to pick your brain
About your area of expertise.
- Physics?
- Mm-hmm.
- Which are you interested in,
Applied or theoretical?
- That is just the thing.
I can't decide.
I love them both.
- Cool.
Well, let's go spark a doobie
And rap about physics.
- Lead the way, marty.
- Uh, are you sure
that's actually you?
[laughs]
oh, man.
- Concentrate, kendra.
You know how to
read the inscription.
At least, you used to know.
- Yeah, well, my hieroglyphic is
a little rusty.
- Lapidary hieratic, actually.
An ancient language
lost to the ages.
- Don't you know how to read it?
- It was a language known
only to the clergy.
- If we only had
a rosetta stone,
I might be able to--
- Well, you are
our rosetta stone.
Just close your eyes.
Think of it as meditation.
I need you to relax
And open your mind.
In order for you to remember
how to kill savage,
I need you
to let your mind float
Back through your hundreds
of previous lives.
Your name is chay-ara,
And you are a priestess
in the temple of horus.
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
- What?
What is it?
- Us.
We were together.
Like, together-together.
- Well, I have been telling you
That you and I should be
destined--
- What are you doing?
- What part of "destiny"
do you not understand?
- The part where I have to stop
thinking for myself.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- The group that disrupted
the arms auction.
Any idea who they were?
- A man in a robotic suit,
Weapons that shoot ice and fire.
Suffice it to say,
they're not from around here.
I would assume the future.
- That's impossible.
- So is immortality.
Besides, how else
do you explain technology
Beyond anything we have seen?
♪ ♪
What can you tell me about it?
- It contains a miniaturized
missile-guidance system
Capable of delivering
high-explosive ordnance.
- You have 24 hours
to reverse-engineer it.
- It could take weeks,
Months to figure out
the circuitry.
♪ ♪
- It looks simple enough to me.
You just press this button here.
- Aah!
Ugh!
♪ ♪
- I said 24 hours.
Suggest you all get to work.
- I'm seeing motion detectors
on the ground floor.
Hardware on the doors
looks standard issue.
- I can't see any smoke alarms.
- Just stay close.
I saw at least three
armed guards on the perimeter.
- Right, boss.
What the hell are you--
- I recognize
the security system.
My parents had the exact one.
I'll have the access code
cracked and security disabled
Before you could say
"breaking and entering."
There.
We're in.
- I wouldn't be
so sure about that.
- Why's that?
- Because you just tapped into
a dummy box,
Which means those guards
are gonna be here--
- Quicker than you can say
"rookie mistake."
- Hands up.
[suspenseful music]
[grunting]
- Ha.
['70s rock music]
- So, who wants a hit?
- Yeah, man--
- I believe you told me
you were trying to quit.
- Oh, none for you, silver top?
- I...
I don't partake in cannabis.
Anymore, that is.
In fact, perhaps you should
take it easy.
- Ah, it helps me think better.
Dad.
- [chuckles]
Yes, but what about the
long-term health consequences?
Speaking of which,
you might want to lay off
The saturated fats.
So, uh...
Alpha particles.
Oof.
Exciting stuff.
Too bad detection is
at least a decade away.
- Mm, more like two decades.
But I've worked up
a little something.
Science is all about
the future, right?
I've developed a prototype
particle tracker.
Cutting edge.
Probably gonna mint me
$1,000,000.
- Wow.
A whole million.
- Mm, be right back.
I think I've got some chocolate
chip cookie dough in the fridge.
[giggles]
- I cannot believe that
that is you.
- Seriously, I had no idea
you were ever cool.
- I wasn't cool.
I was an arrogant little snot.
- Was?
- What are you doing?
- Looking for my younger self's
particle tracker.
Keep an eye on the door,
and when I get back,
Stop flirting with me.
- You were the one
flirting with me.
- Look, what's the big deal?
I mean, younger you
isn't married yet,
So technically
it's not cheating.
- October 1975.
This is right when I meet
my future wife, clarissa.
So obviously, we wouldn't want
my former self
Tempted by a sexy assassin
from the future.
- Aw, you think I'm sex--
- Do not finish that sentence.
[tense music]
- Found it.
♪ ♪
Is there a trick
to opening the case?
♪ ♪
- Ah.
- What are you doing?
Let's grab the dagger
and let's go.
- Raymond, you don't
break into a candy store
And steal one gumball.
- You guys grab the goodies.
I'll find the safe.
- What do you think
you're doing?
This is what we came here for.
- No, it's what you
came here for.
Take your hand off me.
- I'm not gonna let you
jeopardize another mission.
- I'm done asking politely.
This is my mission.
- And I'm gonna listen to a guy
Who's spent half of his life
in prison?
- Oh!
[alarm blaring]
Great.
Now we're both going to prison.
- [gasps]
Eureka.
I remember building this.
It's...It's like déjà vu
all over again.
- Put that down.
- Excellent job
watching the door.
- What are you doing?
- Oh, just, uh...
What is this?
- Something you shouldn't be
fooling around with.
- It's very interesting-looking.
- How about you cut the crap?
- To which crap
are you referring?
- I hold two phds,
and I'm working on a third.
I'm a five-time winner
of the carlin award.
My point being,
is I don't believe
Either of those kids
you're hanging around with
Can even spell "physics."
- You know, I'm beginning
to like the younger gray
Less and less.
- Either you tell me
what the hell is going on,
Or I'm calling campus police.
- I'm not supposed to tell you.
It could cause--well, trouble.
We're here to interview you
for a profile
In next month's "wells journal."
- The "wells" only profiles
nobel candidates.
- An exception is being made
In light of
your obvious brilliance.
I know a photograph of this
device would make
A spectacular cover if we could
just borrow it for a few hours.
- Thanks, but that's
Two years of my life.
I'm not letting you
walk away with it.
Stay back!
- That was taking too long.
- You just knocked me out.
That beautiful brain,
struck unconscious.
- The only way to shut you up.
What are you doing?
We have to go.
- I have to make sure
I wake up in time
To go to this
faculty mixer tonight.
One of the professors
is bringing his niece,
Aka my future wife.
Let's go!
[alarm blaring]
- What the hell happened?
- It was this idiot's fault.
- Your partner's fault.
- I told you we shouldn't
have brought him.
- Agreed, but we got
bigger problems.
I need you to find
the fuse box and--
- Trigger a system default.
This ain't over.
[hollow tapping]
[solid knocking]
- How did you know
how to do that?
- When I was a kid, my dad
brought me along on jobs.
I had little hands.
I could get into tiny spaces,
Do whatever he needed me to do,
Like...Rewiring
a security system.
- In another life, you could've
been an electrical engineer.
- Guess I dodged a bullet.
You think I want to be like you?
- You make being
a tech billionaire
Sound like a bad thing.
- You spend all your time and
money inventing a super-suit,
And what do you do with it?
Fly around like some incredible
shrinking schmuck
Trying to save the world.
- Robbing banks for a living--I
suppose that's more important?
- It's sure as hell
more satisfying.
- Thinking like that is what
makes you a criminal.
- No, it makes me a survivor.
And there's gonna come a day
When you wish you were too.
- Here.
You flip the solenoid,
Saves you the trouble
of rewiring it.
- I take it back, raymond.
You're not completely useless
after all.
- I wanted to apologize.
I'm not afraid of my past.
I'm just
Unwilling to believe that
you're my future.
And the more you keep repeating
That we're destined
to be together,
The more I want
to prove you wrong.
And maybe that makes me
childish, and I'm--
- No.
It doesn't.
Not at all.
Look, 4,000 years
is a long time,
And maybe I've been
taking us for granted,
Expecting you
to fall in love with me
Because that's what you've done
the last 206 lifetimes,
But you're right.
Does not make us destiny.
- More like...Probability.
- Look, kendra.
You don't have to love me
in this lifetime.
As many lifetimes as it takes.
I know you're worth the wait.
All right, well, uh,
Let's try this again.
You know what to do.
- [exhales deeply]
- Your name is chay-ara,
And you're a priestess
in the temple of horus.
- You're giving me a knife...
As a present?
Your conceptions of romance
Require some adjustment,
I think.
- It's sacred.
I was told that
only a high priestess
Could read the inscription.
It's a--
- a poem.
"and though my soul
departs the earth,
"I count my days
till my rebirth.
"I will wait across eternity
For my love to come back to me."
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
[gasps]
The knife.
You gave it to me,
And the inscription,
It was a poem--a love poem
Which promises...
- Promises what?
- That we'd be together forever.
- Perhaps I really am a genius.
My younger self's tracker led us
straight to savage's lab.
Reading's at 96.6%
it's definitely down there.
- Be right back.
- Whoa--wait, wait, wait.
Shouldn't we handle this?
I mean, you're pretty stoned.
- I could be unconscious
and still be able
To kick the ass of a few
rent-a-thugs from 1975.
- Hey!
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I do see why I found her
so attractive.
- Lookin' for this.
- Yeah.
- And y'all have
a lovely evening.
- Huh.
Looks like rory found
the fuse box.
- We got a slight problem.
The owner just came home.
You're not gonna believe
who it is.
- We meet again.
Oh, I'm grateful
for another opportunity
To kill you.
- I've never
saved the world before.
Feels good.
- We should've picked up some
donuts on the way back.
- Oh, my god.
My ring.
When you knocked me out,
I must not have woken up,
Or did, and decided not
to go to the mixer.
Clarissa.
- Holy crap.
Now, do you want to tell me
who you are
And where you're from?
- Stop struggling.
I've had 4,000 years of training
In every hold and
pressure point known.
But you already know that,
don't you?
That I'm immortal.
- I'm gonna kill you anyway.
That's a promise.
- Oh, what have I done
to deserve such enmity?
No, let me rephrase that.
What have I done to you?
Perhaps you have targeted me
For something I've yet to do.
You traveled here from
some point in the future.
- Catches on fast, this guy.
- Visitors from another time.
- Oh!
[groans]
- You won't be so happy when
the rest of the team shows up
And knocks that smug grin
off your face.
- Oh, why wait?
A communications device
of some sort,
I imagine.
Please.
Contact your friends.
I'm looking forward to seeing
At least two of them again.
- Un-believable!
Is that a tachyon manifold?
- Hey, how did you find us, man?
- You think I couldn't
build something
To track my own tracker?
- Do you have any idea
what you have done?
- What I've done?
You guys knocked me out.
- Which we wouldn't have had
to do in the first place
If you weren't
such a monumental jerk!
- Okay, uh, can I just--yeah.
- Watch him, sara.
- Yo, you need to calm down
And you need to stop
yelling at yourself.
- His arrogant curiosity--
- yeah.
He's curious and too smart
for his own good,
But I'm sure you can relate.
You're just pissed you didn't
see it coming sooner, and--
- That's not it.
Although you are correct
in observing
My ire is self-directed.
It's a rude awakening
when one realizes
That despite decades of
what one thought
Was maturation and experience,
You haven't really
changed at all.
That same arrogance I derided
In my younger self
Was on full display
at the weapons bazaar.
Over 60 years on this planet,
And I have learned nothing.
- I think you're being a little
too hard on yourself.
Which makes a nice change from
you always being hard on me,
But yeah,
You're arrogant.
But you're also smart,
And kind, and selfless.
I mean, you want
to make the world a better place
And you're willing to risk
everything to make that happen.
That?
That is not a bad guy.
And neither is this one.
- Meeting clarissa was one of
the great moments of my life,
And meeting you was another.
You are a fine young man,
Mr. Jackson.
- Hey.
Come on.
- Can someone please tell me
what's going on?
- You didn't say
anything to him?
- I figured we screwed up
the '70s enough.
- Hey, w--what are you
talking about?
A--are you saying that you're--
- Don't say another word.
Don't even think it.
You are to get off this ship,
post haste.
- Oh, wonderful.
Another unauthorized passenger.
That worked out so splendidly
last time.
- It's all right.
He was just leaving.
- I'll show you out.
- So, have we met before?
- In a manner of speaking.
Ha--have a wonderful life,
martin.
I mean that sincerely.
- I'm not even going to ask.
- Captain hunter, we're getting
an incoming communiqué.
Mr. Snart on mr. Rory's
comm unit.
- On speaker.
- I'll make this short.
The owner of
the mansion we burgled
Is vandal savage.
He's really interested
in meeting you guys,
Especially our
feathered friends.
- They have the dagger.
- And savage has them.
- Doesn't matter.
Just get me close enough,
And I'll do
what needs to be done.
- I have the coordinates.
- Let's do this.
- Your friends are cowards.
- They'll be here.
- They're taking too long.
They need an incentive--
Oh.
The burning man.
- I don't just burn, pal.
- Aah!
[heroic music]
♪ ♪
- I blast things too.
Hey, you okay?
- I'm pissed.
- Stand back.
♪ ♪
It's all good.
Savage is down.
- Savage is not defeated
by earthly means.
- Well, I hit him
with a nuclear blast,
So, you know, not that earthly.
- Go get that son of a bitch.
- Are you ready to end this?
- We've only been waiting
4,000 years.
♪ ♪
- We got company.
- Friends of savage.
You'll be needing this.
Don't leave any pieces of it
behind this time.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [speaking egyptian]
The aman dagger.
Of all the knives I've collected
across the centuries,
That one is my favorite.
- [yells]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[grunting]
And though my soul
departs the earth...
- Aah!
Aah!
[choking]
[cackles]
Such a beautiful poem.
I remember it well.
Though, as you can see,
I can make the dagger
do its work without it.
- Aah!
- Carter!
- [gasping for air]
Aah!
- This was your lover's blade.
It must be her hand
that wields it.
[dramatic music]
Something to consider
in your next life.
- [yells]
Aah!
[heavy breathing]
Carter.
- Aah.
- It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
- I will wait
Through eternity.
- Please, just
save your strength.
- Come back to me.
- No...
[cries]
[dark music]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- Murderer.
Aah!
[grunting]
- I am not a murderer.
I'm a force of nature.
A servant of fate.
I enable destiny.
- Aah!
- I love you, chay-ara.
I always will.
- [gasps]
- But we are both tortured
By this circle of death
we are imprisoned by.
[dramatic music]
- Carter.
- He's lost.
Get kendra
before savage recovers.
- Come on, we can still
kill this bastard.
- Kendra is
the only one who can.
- We gotta go.
Kendra needs medical attention.
[men shouting]
- Gideon, get us underway
As soon as firestorm and
the atom are onboard.
Get her to the medbay now.
I assure you, dr. Palmer,
There's nothing more
you can do for her.
- You can't let her die.
- I don't intend to.
- Sharp force injury
resulting in rupture
Of several major blood vessels.
Her pressure is currently
82 over 30 and stable.
I will begin by
irrigating the wound
And cauterizing it to prevent
any further hemorrhaging.
- Thank you, gideon.
- Carter...
Carter...Carter...
- Gideon, if you wouldn't mind
administering a mild sedative.
- No!
Carter!
I didn't get to tell him.
I didn't get to tell him
it came back to me.
I finally remembered how I felt
about him in our past lives
And I didn't get to tell him!
- Shh...
- I didn't get to tell him--
- It's okay.
- I felt the same way.
- Shh, shh...
- [whimpers]
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
- How is she?
- Stable, I think.
Sara told me about
what's happening with your wife.
I'm sorry.
- I was so seduced by
the prospect of
Time travel, of adventure,
I never stopped to consider
The consequences of
what we were undertaking.
- Gideon has managed to
stabilize
Miss saunders's condition,
But another time jump could
aggravate her injuries.
- So we're stuck in '75?
- For the time being, yes.
Given that, can I have a moment
of your time, martin?
There's something that
I would like to show you.
- Of course.
[chattering]
Apparently it's true that
The guilty return
to the scene of the crime.
- Oh, don't be so maudlin.
Look at your hand.
- How--
- I contacted your younger self
And encouraged him to attend
the faculty mixer.
Turns out one of the professors
brought along his niece.
- You risked the timeline
for me.
- Hardly seemed fair
for you to sacrifice your wife
In order to save mine
from savage's future.
One thing
that time travel teaches you
Is that time changes,
People don't.
- A painful realization
I've recently come to.
- I have traveled countless ages
into the future.
We're still asking ourselves
the same question:
Why are we here?
I believe that we're here
to learn, martin.
Be glad that you still can.
- Thank you, mr. Hunter.
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
How's kendra?
- The same.
- So what now?
- Now?
Now it's up to you.
- To do what, rip?
Last I checked, every time
we try to do anything,
It all goes to crap.
- Oh, once again
I must disagree with you.
Thanks to miss lance,
dr. Palmer's future technology
Is no longer in the hands
of vandal savage's
Black market weapons designers.
- But it didn't do anything to
change the fate of your world.
- No.
Vandal savage will still rise to
power in the year 2166.
- And your family
will still die?
- So what you're
really asking is,
Do we want to fish or cut bait?
Return to 2016 and live out
the rest of our lives
As insignificant losers or--
- Make another play
at becoming legends.
Figure out how to end savage
and save the world.
- Preferably, without causing
any more nuclear explosions.
- Savage has my attention.
- Look, we didn't know
carter from adam,
But if you take out
one of my crew,
You better pay the price.
- Surely captain hunter
has a sound plan.
What about you?
- You're asking me?
- I didn't give you much of
a choice the first time, did I?
- Well, I say
we kick savage's ass.
For carter.
All:
- So, captain.
Where are we going next?
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
- Greg, move your head.