PROFESSOR STEIN: Previously on The Flash,
Arrow and Legends Of Tomorrow...
(ROARS)
Since we learned of them,
we've been calling them the Dominators.
- You can't do this alone.
- I don't plan to.
BARRY: Guys, thanks for coming.
This is Kara Danvers, Supergirl.
I went back in time
to change the timeline.
It's called Flashpoint
and now things here are different
- than before I left.
- You just erased
a daughter from my life?
He took it upon himself
to change the timeline.
And because of it my brother was killed.
There's no amount of feeling bad
that could ever make up for that.
PROFESSOR STEIN: I'm having memories of a stranger,
- but she's not really a stranger.
- (GIRL GIGGLING)
What if when you interacted
with your younger self in 1987, you...
Inadvertently changed my past.
You're back. (LAUGHS)
Oh, it's so good to see you.
I love you, Dad.
Call Lyla, tell her these Dominators
aren't here peacefully.
Maybe they chose us because
we couldn't fight back.
DR. HEYWOOD:
Because none of you are meta-humans.
RAY: What is their plan?
(SPEAKING ALIEN LANGUAGE)
GIDEON: The phrase loosely translates to
"We are nearing completion of the weapon. "
I can't believe that you guys escaped
an alien spaceship.
Key words, "Alien spaceship."
- I have questions.
- They can wait.
- Thanks for helping me get my sister home.
- Yeah, man.
What's our status?
Nothing since the Dominators
paid their little visit
to mess with our heads.
- Why would they do that?
- What if they were trying
to pit us against each other
in order to gain intel about meta-humans?
Man, I wish they would just send
us an IM with a questionnaire.
Metas pose the biggest threat
to their invasion.
It would make sense
they'd wanna get to know their enemies.
By kidnapping people.
Perhaps they were searching your minds
for potential meta-human vulnerabilities.
I think it's time we return the favor.
What do you wanna do?
Kidnap one of them now?
Ever since we fought off that one ship,
they've kind of been in short supply.
Actually, I know where to find one.
I've been reviewing old army footage
of their first encounters
with the Dominators.
And I think I've pegged the fight to...
(GUNFIRE ON TV)
Redmond, Oregon, 1951.
(RAPID GUNFIRE)
(DOMINATOR TRILLING)
PROFESSOR STEIN:
You're suggesting we travel to 1951,
abduct a Dominator and interrogate it
to determine their intentions.
They kidnapped us.
Seems fair.
- Time travel. I'm definitely in.
- Okay, hold on there.
Professor Stein and Caitlin
have been talking about a way
to take down the Dominators.
- They could probably use your help.
- Pass.
Yeah, I mean, I'm with him.
Mostly because
I don't wanna lose my geek cred,
but time travel...
I could take Amaya and Mick.
- Do it.
- Okay.
Yes!
And, uh, the new president called,
which would be cool
under different circumstances.
But she wants to meet with us.
Let's bring Ray and Sara as backup.
What about me? I can do backup.
Let me talk to you for a second.
I don't know.
I would like to minimize
your involvement in this.
Why? Because I'm an alien?
I also happen to be your biggest weapon.
You are an unknown quantity
and this is not personal.
Except that's exactly how this feels.
Kara, when I started living this life,
it was just me.
I was going up against human threats.
That I could handle.
Then it was meta-humans,
and I can handle that.
Now, I learned
that there are multiple arsenals
brainwashed aboard an alien spacecraft.
I'm sure that was unnerving.
I don't get unnerved.
But when I go up against something new,
I push back.
Right or wrong,
it is who I am and it is what I do.
So, I am asking for a little bit of space
because I have to draw the line somewhere.
I need to claw back a sense of normalcy.
Please stay here.
This ship is everything.
What type of propulsion system
does it use?
- No idea.
- Oh, my God, that construct on the bow
looks like it could be
some sort of Time Sphere.
- Yeah, no idea.
- To operate a ship of this size,
the deep-link nets would have to be...
Oh, my God, you'd have to use,
like, a quantum neural chipset...
Hey, guys, guys. Amaya and Rory
are waiting for us on the bridge.
Can we just keep moving this along?
- This ship is...
- Automatic.
- Supersonic.
- Hypnotic.
- Funky fresh.
CAITLIN: Professor?
It's highly unlikely
we can fashion a weapon
with sufficient force
to overcome the Dominators.
I was thinking the exact same thing,
which is why I invited...
So, what if instead
we try to attack them
with something infinitesimally small.
I'm sure you're familiar with the story
of the lion with the thorn in his paw?
You used to love telling me that story
when I was a kid.
Oh. Hello.
The lion with the thorn in his paw
is a parable.
A story about a big, ferocious creature
that is felled by something small.
So, what do you need help with?
I'm afraid it's classified.
Oh, juicy.
Some sort of secret
government space weapon, no doubt.
Something like that.
Only this sort of work
is slightly out of my wheelhouse.
Yeah, if only you knew someone
with a PhD in nanotechnology.
Unfortunately, Raymond's busy
working on other things.
I was talking about me.
Did the six years I spent at MIT
magically slip your mind?
Of course not.
Good. Okay, let's get to work.
We made it. This is the '50s.
Oh, sick.
(VOMITS)
Severe time jumps can cause nausea,
temporary deafness...
(GROANS AND SPEAKS GIBBERISH)
Linguistic disorientation.
(SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
You, clean it up.
We're gonna kidnap an alien.
(CHUCKLES) Okay, I know I did not just
travel through time
so we could stay on the ship.
Ponytail, you're staying on the ship.
(YELLING GIBBERISH)
I'll take that as
"Have fun storming the castle."
Oh, for real? You're gonna use
Princess Bride against me?
- Against me?
- (VOMITS)
Okay, I got you, girl.
Celebrating July 4th early?
Ray made it for me.
You look like a star-spangled idiot.
- We need to find the Army.
- (EXPLOSIONS)
(GUNFIRE)
I think we found them.
(GROANING AND YELLING)
What are we waiting for?
Let's grab an alien and get out of here.
Just waiting for one of the weaker ones
in the herd.
(GROWLING)
I don't think there are any weak ones.
Oh.
Do you have any idea
what's going on out there?
It's a real-life Spielberg movie.
And we're stuck in here.
Okay.
I think I know
what's really bothering you.
I'm having the worst case of FOMO
while everyone else is out there
kidnapping an alien?
No.
I think you escaped 2016
to get away from Barry.
Mmm-mmm. Excuse me,
I escaped 2016
so that I could come see the Waverider.
And so that I could time travel.
- And?
- And...
Also, yes,
I wanted to get away from Barry.
Ha! You realize that's insane, right?
You're holding a grudge
against your best friend
when the world
is potentially going to end.
I'm sorry, "my best friend"?
He only killed my brother.
- He didn't kill...
- Okay, you're right,
he didn't literally kill my brother.
What I mean to say is, he was responsible.
Okay, he just needed to save his family,
and in doing that,
he ended up destroying mine.
(SIGHS)
(CHUCKLES) You know, all this
time traveling, fighting aliens...
This is stuff I used to dream about
as a kid.
Heh. Yeah, me, too.
It doesn't feel like a dream.
- No.
- Just feels weird.
Well, exactly,
and it's only gonna get weirder.
So, that's why we have to be able
to rely on our friends.
I really wish I could right now, Felicity.
But he's not my friend.
(DOMINATORS CHITTERING)
- They're taking off.
- I don't get it.
Why are the Dominators attacking us,
then just leaving?
It's an RIF mission.
Reconnaissance-In-Force.
Ah, look.
A straggler.
We need him alive, Mick.
I'm just gonna rough him up a little.
- Hey!
- (ROARS)
(DOMINATOR SCREECHING)
Squeal, you pig.
Hey, Dad?
- Dad?
- What?
- Um, I'm sorry.
- Can you hand me those induction clamps?
Yes.
This reminds me of that time
we stayed up all night
building my seventh grade science project.
Remember how mad Mom got
when she found out
you let me drink coffee to stay awake?
No.
I mean, no, no, I should never...
Never have let you do that.
Uh... Sorry, will you excuse me?
Are you okay, Dad?
I'm just, uh, preoccupied with my work,
that's all.
(SIGHS)
You know, you're really taking this
whole absent-minded professor thing
to a new level.
I don't know what you mean.
Your daughter.
Ever since you've come back,
you've treated her like a total stranger.
That's because she is a total stranger.
Sorry. It's just that
when I last left 2016,
that young woman did not exist.
Wait, you're saying
Lily belongs to another timeline?
That when Barry created Flashpoint...
Unfortunately, this is all my fault.
You see, a month ago,
I interacted with my younger self
back in 1987
and unwittingly motivated him,
me,
to sire a child.
So, it's because of my carelessness
that this Time Aberration exists.
She is not an Aberration.
She is brilliant and funny
and a lot like you,
just a little less uptight.
Please stop talking about her like this.
She is not a real person.
She is a real person. She's your daughter.
Wait.
When we finish fighting the Dominators,
you're going to go back in time
and erase her?
No.
I'm going to restore the timeline.
Unlike your friend Barry,
I have the luxury of fixing my mistakes.
AGENT: Well done.
(GUNS COCKING)
I see that you've managed
to catch us a specimen.
I'm afraid we're gonna
have to keep this one.
Who are you?
Just a humble civil servant.
- I don't like guys with badges.
- Easy, Mick.
We just wanna ask a few questions.
We'd love to answer them, but...
- We're in a bit of a hurry.
- AGENT: And so are we.
(ALL GRUNT)
(GROANS)
You don't understand.
We're here to save the future.
And you can tell me all about it.
When you wake up.
Crap! Where do you think
they're taking them?
Those Men In Black types
are probably gonna take them
to a secret lab
and run experiments on them.
Have you seen Stranger Things?
Uh, maybe too much TV, Cisco.
Life imitates art, Felicity.
Either way, whether you like it or not,
we're gonna have to be the ones
to rescue them.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
But we're the tech support.
No, this is tech support.
Set your phasers to stun.
This is why I hate the government.
Can't you two use your powers
and get us out of here?
Whatever they tranqued us with
is screwing with our powers.
(DOMINATOR BREATHING HEAVILY)
Hey, he's still alive.
Although, something tells me
none of us are gonna be alive for long.
DR. HEYWOOD: Wait.
This is the exact opportunity
we've been looking for.
To get captured?
No.
To talk with one of the Dominators.
And find out what they want
with our planet.
Well, this is a first.
Talking with an alien.
(CLEARS THROAT) Excuse me, Mr. Alien Guy.
(SHRIEKING)
SARA: So where's the President?
She's late.
Well, you gotta figure
she's got a lot on her plate,
what with the whole alien invasion thing.
And her predecessor getting killed.
Hey, uh, what'd you say to Kara earlier?
She seemed pretty angry.
I didn't know she was capable
of being angry.
- We've got movement.
- (VEHICLES APPROACHING)
I'm sorry. President couldn't make it.
Who are you?
If I tell you,
I'll have to kill you.
Look.
We just wanna know
why you attacked our planet.
I mean, we're just down here
minding our own business,
then you guys just drop from the sky
and attack us.
Why?
There has been a recent emergence
of meta-humans on your planet.
Wait, he's talking about the JSA.
DOMINATOR: We are here to determine
if your kind are a threat.
Let's start with him.
Rest of you will have to wait your turn.
Uh, I think we have a misunderstanding.
See, we're the good guys.
The President invited us here.
Barry, I think it's time we do something.
And fast.
(MEN GROANING)
(BULLET RICOCHETS)
- Sniper.
- On it.
(ALL GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
We're trying to help you.
This is how you thank us?
You don't understand.
The reason the xenomorphs are here...
is because they have a beef
with the meta-humans.
Tell us something we don't know.
Like, what exactly have we done to them?
Nothing yet.
But they see individuals
with powers such as yours
as a future threat.
And, frankly, so do I.
(DOMINATOR SCREECHING)
What do you think they're doing to him?
Same thing they're gonna do to us
unless we get out of here.
- (LASERS FIRING)
- (MEN GROANING)
Oh, yeah! Y'all call for tech support?
Great. Saved by geeks.
Waverider is ready
to take us back to 2016.
(DOMINATOR SCREECHING)
If we leave him here,
they're gonna kill him.
So what? He's an alien.
Just 'cause they're douches
doesn't mean we have to be.
- Well... (CHUCKLES)
- We gotta send him home.
How?
Don't we have one of their ships
aboard the Waverider?
Yeah, but it's damaged.
- Felicity's gonna help me fix it.
- FELICITY: I am?
- I'm gonna help him fix it.
- See?
- (DOMINATOR GROANING)
- Oh, that doesn't sound good.
(SIGHS) Guys, it's up to us to show
the Dominators we're better than this.
(SCREECHING CONTINUES)
Fascinating.
The creature's nervous system
is not unlike our own,
which means it must be capable
of experiencing pain.
(SCREECHING)
Maybe that's why he's screaming.
(GRUNTING)
Don't worry,
we're gonna get you out of here.
Bye.
- He didn't even say thank you.
- What is that?
I think it's a transponder.
Where'd you get that?
I may or may not have stolen it
from his ship.
What does it do?
I think we can use it to communicate
with him when we get back.
- Oh, my God, like an alien pen pal.
- Exactly.
You kids finished?
- Gideon?
- GIDEON: Yes, Mr. Rory.
Prepare for, um...
- Time jump.
GIDEON: Course plotted
for Central City, 2016.
If you're such BFF's with the Dominators...
Then, why don't you call them off?
We know you sent them packing
once before back in 1951.
That was just a reconnaissance mission.
What brought them back?
You did, Mr. Allen.
He knows who you are.
You threatened the entire universe
when you used your powers
to upset the normal course of time.
You're talking about Flashpoint?
How do you even know about...
They told us.
I made a mistake, okay,
I'm not gonna let it happen again.
For the past 60 years,
we have enjoyed a truce
with your so-called Dominators.
You broke the truce.
What do they want?
I've negotiated a deal with them.
If Mr. Allen surrenders himself,
they will leave us in peace.
You really wanna save the world?
Here's your chance.
(SIGHS)
I can't see. Why can't I see?
At least you're not throwing up.
- (VOMITS)
- (BEEPING)
What's it doing?
I don't know.
Either our food's ready,
or this guy's trying to call us.
Hey, how do I answer?
Hey. Oh, my God, it's him.
He's even uglier
than the last time we saw him.
Sixty-five of your years ago,
you saved me from capture.
Listen, you don't need to thank us.
Yeah, he does.
He can thank us by turning around
and heading home.
I will show you my gratitude
by sparing your lives.
But I cannot do the same for Barry Allen.
If your friend does not turn himself in,
we will have no choice
but to deploy a weapon
that will exterminate all meta-humans.
SARA: It's a trap.
If they're that threatened by meta-humans,
it's hard to believe
they'd be satisfied with just one.
Yeah, well, if I know Barry,
he's gonna wanna be that one.
Well, Oliver's trying
to talk him out of it.
And if he does, what's the collateral
damage of the meta-bomb?
Projected casualty count
is around 2 million non-meta-humans.
Okay, so what if we negotiated with them?
CISCO: Yeah, I don't know if you noticed,
but our last chat with them
didn't go so well.
Well, what've we got to lose?
Look, maybe we should contact them.
And make it fast.
We got incoming.
- Dominator ships are coming in worldwide.
- Including Central City.
Yeah, but they're not moving or anything,
- they're just sitting there.
- For now.
So much for the truce
Secret Agent Man negotiated.
They're trying to leverage us
into handing Barry over.
Contact the Dominators.
Looks like your friend's
not calling you back.
- No, he's not, but I got a plan B.
- Go.
If this came from their drop ship,
and the drop ship came
from the mother ship,
theoretically, I could use it
to vibe us up there.
And if you can't?
Then, I'd be vibing us into the cold,
unforgiving vacuum of space.
- So, let's not do that.
- Yeah, let's not. Okay.
What an unusual gift.
You appear to be a meta-human as well.
Yeah, well,
I figured you'd cut me some slack
seeing as how we saved you back in 1951.
Remember that?
Much has changed on your planet
in the last 60 years.
The threat of your kind
has become imminent.
Listen, ET, we're not a threat.
Metas are protecting this planet.
And besides, the guy who tortured
your ugly ass back in 1951 was human.
But what happens when a man like him
inherits abilities like yours?
We have seen it happen
on countless other worlds.
Which is why we must exterminate your kind
before the scourge of your planet
becomes the scourge of ours.
(BOTH PANTING)
Well, he's out of his giant mind.
What if he's right?
What if in using our powers
to make the world better,
we actually end up destroying it?
Dude, I get it. Barry screwed up.
Yeah, so did we.
Back in 1951.
(SIGHS) We messed with time
when we freed the Dominator.
Who is now coming to kill us.
This whole time I've been mad at Barry.
Now I'm the one who messed with time.
I just wanted to make things right.
I only ended up making them worse.
I'm an idiot.
I can't stabilize
the nanomolecular reaction.
Damn it!
Well.
Speaking as a daughter,
I'm not sure that outburst
had anything to do with her project.
What, you think it's related to me?
She doesn't know
that you think she's an Aberration.
All she knows is that her father
is keeping her at arm's length.
The world is being invaded by aliens.
I don't think this is the time
for family therapy.
It is when the world's best chance
at a workable weapon
is focused on getting
her daddy to love her.
Lily?
Hey. I'm sorry. (SIGHS)
Morn always said I got my temper from you.
No, no, I'm the one who owes the apology.
If it feels like
I've been keeping my distance,
I assure you, it's nothing personal.
Yeah, it feels personal.
No, I mean, it's not personal to you.
I'm sorry. I wish I could explain,
but my life has gotten
rather complicated lately.
So?
You raised me to enjoy complexity.
That's...
The nanomolecular reaction
keeps breaking down
because the replication
is sequential, not...
Exponential.
The reaction requires greater complexity.
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
Why are you looking at me like that?
Because I truly believe
I'm seeing you for the first time.
(CELL PHONE BEEPS)
LILY: What is it?
My friend Barry.
He's about to do something terrible.
This isn't up for debate.
It's not even a close call.
I turn myself over to the Dominators,
they leave the rest of the world alone.
- It's simple.
- No, it's not simple.
Barry, it doesn't matter what you've done.
You can't do this.
It's been an honor to know all of you.
To fight alongside of you.
Now it's up to you to keep our home safe.
OLIVER: Barry. I'm not letting you leave.
No offense, Oliver, but you and what army?
This one.
Listen, Red, I don't like you,
but when you've got a crew,
you don't take a hit for the rest.
(CHUCKLES)
That's actually pretty inspiring.
I mean, up until the point
that Mick compared us
to a bunch of criminals, but...
AMAYA: According to the Dominators,
we might as well be.
And maybe they're right.
Maybe we do more harm than good,
but this is our chance to find out.
CISCO: We're not letting you
sacrifice yourself.
There's no way.
I don't care if that's what it means
to be a hero.
You're not a hero to me.
You're my friend.
(CHUCKLES)
JAX: Yo, guys.
You know that ship
that landed in Central City?
It's opening up.
Here we go.
(ALARM BEEPING)
I'm reading reports of ships opening
all over the world.
- Oh, frak.
- Talk to me.
Something from the Dominator's mothership
just broke atmo,
and not to get too technical,
but it's really, really big
and falling to Earth really, really fast.
BARRY: It's the meta-bomb.
Why would the uglies drop ships on us
if they're just planning on blowing us up?
Because the ships were a distraction
to keep us from stopping the meta-bomb.
Too bad 'cause we're gonna stop it.
- We're gonna stop it, right?
- Let's hope.
BARRY: We have to keep
the Dominators at bay.
PROFESSOR STEIN: This might help.
I've mass-produced a small device,
that when placed on individual Dominators,
will cause indescribable agony.
Not the nicest invention, but this is war.
Nice going.
The caveat, of course,
is that if we activate the weapons
before all the devices are placed
on the Dominators,
they'll know what we're up to.
Well, we gotta do it fast.
Only way I know how.
Damn, that's big.
I didn't think it was gonna be so big.
- What're we gonna do?
- You got me.
I only know how to stab, punch
or skewer things.
(DOMINATORS CHITTERING)
Fry, you freaks.
(SCREECHING)
See you later, Dominator.
(ELEPHANT TRUMPETING)
This thing has to have
a tractor beam, right?
Yup.
It's slowing down but, like, barely.
Thank you, Cisco, I haven't noticed.
- (CLATTERING)
- (SIGHS) Strap in.
Firestorm, if you're done playing
with your friends out there,
we could really use your help.
I'm on it.
(GROANS)
(SIGHS)
(RAPID BEEPING)
Good work planting
Professor Stein's nanoweapons,
but we've still got Dominators
all over the country.
This looks like a job for Supergirl.
FLASH: Thanks, Felicity.
I'm not the least bit insulted.
Uh, sorry. I meant Supergirl and Flash.
This is totally a job
for the both of you.
That's what I meant. Supergirl and Flash.
Firestorm, we're holding it up.
But, like, barely.
Not helping, Cisco.
- SARA: Firestorm, do it now.
- Do what?
PROFESSOR STEM:
I believe Ms. Lance intends for us
to transmute the meta-bomb
into something harmless.
I was afraid you were gonna say that.
All right, devices are being planted.
Let me know when I can bring the pain.
Come on, Firestorm.
(GRUNTING)
Grey, I can't do it, man. It's too big.
Still waiting on that signal.
Do it.
Done.
(SCREECHING)
It's working!
What about the superhero bomb?
I can't. I can't do it.
PROFESSOR STEIN: You must, Jefferson.
I have a daughter. Her name is Lily
and she's counting on you.
She's counting on both of us.
(GRUNTS)
(SHOUTING)
(CHUCKLES) They did it!
They can do that?
They did that.
Ground, what's your status?
They're retreating.
It's not just them.
It's all around the world.
He did it.
No, Oliver.
We all did it.
Many responsibilities have fallen to me
since the President's passing
at the beginning of this crisis.
Sobering, sad responsibilities.
This is not one of them.
Today, it is my distinct honor
to bestow upon you
a small acknowledgment of the great debt
that the world owes to you all.
Is it just me or is she really hot?
Although your brave efforts must
remain a secret...
She's hot.
Know that meta-human or not,
masked or not,
each and every one of you is a hero.
(APPLAUSE)
- (MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
- Whoo!
Thank you.
Hmm? Hmm?
Let's go drink.
Cheers.
It's like looking into a mirror.
Hey, you know what's funny?
She really kind of looks like my cousin.
- Hey, hey, guys.
- Hey.
Either of you ever saved the world before?
Mmm-hmm. Last year.
- Oh, it doesn't get old, does it?
- No.
It sure beats screwing up the world.
Hey, you are too hard on yourself.
That's what people usually tell me.
And for good reason I'm sure, but...
Back on my Earth,
it's just me and my cousin.
Between the two of us,
we're more powerful than...
- Yeah, everybody in this room combined.
- No, no.
That's the point.
That's what you've all proven here.
Meta-human or not, superpowers or not,
you are Earth's mightiest heroes.
Um...
I owe you an apology.
Keeping you at arm's length
was the wrong move and, uh...
Well, the truth is that this Earth
could probably use a Supergirl.
Well, that's funny.
Because I was just thinking
my Earth could use an Oliver Queen.
I know you said you don't get unnerved.
- (SIGHS)
- But if you did,
I think hardship
is what makes us stronger.
That's probably why these people
look to you as their rock.
You guys feeling the group hug?
- No.
- Come on, come on.
- Okay.
- All right.
Hey, Kara,
- I made you something. Yeah.
- What? Cisco.
What, uh...
What is it?
Oh. (LAUGHS) It's, uh...
- It's an inter-dimensional extrapolator.
- Oh. Uh...
It creates small breaches,
so you can use it
to cross over to our universe
anytime you need to.
(LAUGHS) Oh, my God. That's amazing.
I also included
communication functionality,
so if you ever need any help
you can always contact the team.
RORY: Hey, skirt.
Call me.
(SIGHS) All right, Grey. Spill.
How is it you have a kid?
I didn't think I had to explain
such matters to you, Jefferson.
Come on, you know what I mean.
When we traveled back to 1987,
I gave my younger self a lecture
about neglecting Clarissa and he...
And he followed your advice
all the way to pound town.
Wait.
You created an Aberration.
Which is why you cannot tell the team.
If you don't want me to tell the team,
that means you...
I do not want to lose my daughter.
Something tells me
you weren't invited here.
Dr. Heywood.
Don't Dr. Heywood me.
What the hell are you doing here?
I like parties.
And I'm here for the mop up.
Cover up. But you can't cover this up.
- (LAUGHS)
- Agent Smith.
It's so funny seeing you here.
I was just having the loveliest chat
with your President about you.
I was telling her on my Earth,
we have a Department
of Extra-Normal Operations
which deals specifically with aliens.
She thought it was an excellent idea.
She also loved my pitch about
reassigning you to Antarctica.
Maybe next time, you're a little nicer
to strange visitors from another planet.
Pack a jacket.
BARRY: You ready to see
if Cisco's gadget works?
KARA: Ready.
And remember,
if you guys ever need me,
I'm just a call away.
Same here.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
It's weird to think that
all of this started with the two of us.
Ever think about what it would be like
if we never got on that boat?
I don't know if I have to think about it.
I mean, maybe the Dominators showed us
what our lives would have been like.
I know it was a prison, but in a way...
In a way, it was a gift.
- Stay out of trouble.
- Yeah.
DIGGLE: There she goes.
Off to her spaceship,
time traveling as if it's totally normal.
Well... (CLEARS THROAT)
John, it's like you said.
Normal sort of went out the window
when this one arrived.
I may never understand you, man, but...
You're one of the best men I know.
Thanks, Digg.
So, will you forgive me for what I did?
Barry, it's like I keep telling this guy,
you have to forgive yourself.
- Yeah.
- Good luck.
Yeah, thanks.
Well. We ought to do this more often.
Get together, I mean.
I don't know if the world could take it.
I meant, like,
without the world being threatened.
If the world wasn't being threatened,
what would we do?
(MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
I'm just saying that
next time I'm gonna get you.
I'm just saying I've beaten you twice.
The first time was a tie.
And the second time?
- There were no witnesses the second time.
- (CHUCKLING)
Super speed and arrow tools.
Our lives aren't exactly normal.
I told Kara that I was looking
to reclaim some normal.
Thinking on it now, I'm not so sure.
I know what you mean.
We both got a look
at what life would look like normal.
It would've been happy.
But not full.
No. No, nowhere close.
To things not being normal.
To life being full.