Previously
on Legends of Tomorrow...
Sara may not know it,
but the demon's power,
it lives inside of her.
When she succumbs to it,
you're gonna need that gun.
- Come with us.
- What would you rather do?
Hide from A.R.G.U.S. your whole life,
or time travel?
What do you think
the Captain would think
about you re-engineering time?
Well, I'm no hero
and I'm not a member of any team.
Are you sure about this,
Ms. Tomaz?
Captain Lance
did not give you authorization
to initialize this program.
That's because I didn't ask
for authorization.
Now fire up the auxiliary generator.
Even with the reserve power,
I don't believe my system
can run your simulation software.
Gideon, trust me.
Trust is something that grows
over time between friends.
As far as I'm concerned,
we are still acquaintances.
Question, Gideon. Who is ready
to have 1.12 terawatts of power
diverted straight into her CPU?
I'm not sure if your calculations
accurately stabilize the surge.
We should talk about this
before proceeding.
No time. We have to run this program
before the team gets back.
In that case, I suggest you hurry.
The team has just returned
on the Jumpship from their mission.
Okay, screw it.
Gideon, what's happening?
I was gonna ask the same question.
I thought you were fixing the ship.
Uh, yeah, the maintenance check
took longer than expected.
The ship's a mess.
I had to reinitialize
Gideon's alpha drives...
So, how'd it go out there? Good mish?
I pried this cassette
from Shorty's fingers.
He means Napoleon Bonaparte.
Waterloo. Who writes
a song about losing a war?
Huh?
Anyway, it was really great.
Even though half our band
missed the cue for our big encore.
Yeah, where were you guys?
- Um...
- Uh...
It was my fault.
I was just not used to walking
in these go-go boots.
It won't happen again, Captain.
Right. Gideon,
let's check the historical records.
See if everything is back to normal.
According to the historical record,
the Battle of Waterloo
is back on track.
Napoleon did surrender
and the French forces withdrew...
Gideon? Where did she go?
The ship's functions
are still operational,
but it looks as though
Gideon's neural core has been fried.
I asked you to perform
a routine maintenance check.
I did run a maintenance check.
And maybe something else?
Something you wanna tell us about,
maybe show us?
Oh, do not make me move you.
Uh, you should just tell her what it is.
The last thing we'd wanna do
is get Sara mad.
Why's that?
Because, high blood pressure.
It takes years off your life.
Okay, fine. You win.
I uploaded a synchronous
multi-model simulation program
to Gideon's neural core.
A simulation program for what?
To see if there are
any other loopholes in history
- that we could exploit.
- "We"?
You mean, you can exploit.
You're trying to hack history?
What exactly are you trying to change
in 2042?
Oh, I don't know, Ray.
Maybe I'm trying to figure out
how to stop my home
from becoming a dystopian nightmare.
Look, Zari,
I let the Helen of Troy thing pass.
I even let it slide when you tried
to prevent Martin's death.
But you need to understand.
We are in the "fixing anachronisms"
business,
not the "hacking history" business.
Now please, go fix Gideon.
Hey, maybe if you would stop
bossing me around for a second
you would see this is a good idea.
I said, "Please."
And even if I didn't,
bossing you around
is part of my job as captain.
Yeah, and it's really easy
to take you seriously in that outfit.
You know, this whole
"apathetic cool girl" thing,
it's not as cute as you think.
- You wanna be a member of this team...
- Member-ish.
This was always
a temporary arrangement.
I was never planning on
sticking around for long.
Then so long as you are on this ship,
I am your captain.
And if you don't like it,
you can stop sticking around.
Aye, aye.
- I'm gonna kill her.
- Wait, Sara, please don't...
Just fix the ship.
"Just fix the ship."
Yes, Captain. Of course, Captain.
Can I kiss your ass, Captain?
Damn it!
Ugh.
Of course. Of course.
All right, Gideon, you back online?
Gideon?
Holy...
Well, as long as you are on this ship,
I'm your captain.
And if you don't like it,
you can stop sticking around.
You gonna say something?
Yeah.
What the...
What is wrong with you?
Uh, nothing. I think.
Didn't we just have
this conversation?
Yeah, 'cause you keep making me
repeat myself.
No, that's not what I meant.
Sara, don't get mad.
I'm sure Zari can fix...
Just fix the ship.
Yeah, okay. Sure.
Deep breath. No one's going crazy.
It's probably just something I ate.
- I'm busy.
- Right.
You've done a lot of time traveling.
- Have you ever had déjà vu?
- What's that?
Oh, it's French for "already seen."
I hate the French.
I'm mortified, Nathaniel.
I mean, we could've permanently derailed
the history of France. For what?
"For what?"
Have you not seen your outfit?
Totally would've been worth it.
And I'm the historian.
We never should've
given into the temptation.
But we did.
And now I can't stop thinking
about you.
We can't put the team at risk,
all right?
Until we can figure out a way
to behave professionally,
we'll have to forget
it ever happened.
I can't.
Just try.
- Nate.
- Yeah.
Amaya and I were just comparing notes
on the last mission.
Uh-huh. Uh...
Did you notice anything weird happen
a few minutes ago?
No, not really.
- Nothing with the ship?
- Mmm-mmm.
Well, let me think about it.
Nope. Nothing out of the ordinary.
Hey, aren't you supposed to be
in the engine room?
Sara told you to fix Gideon.
- The last thing we'd wanna do is...
- Make Sara mad.
Yeah. You know what they say.
Happy captain, happy ship.
No one says that. But whatever.
"Happy captain, happy ship."
Stupid.
Huh.
All right, Gideon, you there?
Mamma mia, here I go again.
So long as you are on this ship,
I'm your captain.
And if you don't like it,
you can stop sticking around.
Okay, something really bizarre
is happening.
You're not even listening to me.
No, Sara, wait.
There's no need for violence...
Ow! Ow! Ow!
I'm sorry, old habits.
Ray, take Zari to the MedBay.
This way.
What has gotten into you?
I don't know how to explain this,
but I've died, twice.
Have you gotten into Nate's
psychedelic root stash?
No, I'm serious, Ray.
Please, I need your help.
Fine. Whatever.
Guess I have to figure this out
on my own.
- What's that?
- It's a mild sedative
while you heal up.
I don't want you hurting yourself
or anybody else.
Ray!
- So long as you are on this ship...
- Sara, need you to shut up.
- What?
- Emergency.
Everyone back on the bridge,
right now!
- What are you doing?
- Okay, let's all just calm down.
No, I will not calm down.
- And, watch your step, Ray.
- What do you mean...
Thought the mission was over.
- Why are we still here?
- Yeah, what's going on?
Okay, I know
this going to sound crazy.
But we are all in imminent danger.
In an hour,
this ship is going to explode.
How do you know?
Let's just say I had a dream.
But we need to check the ship
and go over every inch.
Because if we don't stop this explosion,
we're going to die.
Yeah.
Guys! Guys, I'm telling the truth.
What's up with her?
Working theory? Cabin fever.
Working theory? Space madness.
Acute entropic dementia.
Too many doughnuts.
I mean, it could be anything.
Oh, must have developed
a sedative tolerance.
What's the plan, Z?
First, you piss off Sara, and now
you're sneaking out of the MedBay.
Yeah, I don't have a plan
because nothing I do matters, anyway.
Sara always yells at me,
nobody believes what I say
and Ray always trips
on his platforms.
I have no idea why I'm stuck
in this time loop.
"Time loop"?
You mean like, Groundhog Day?
You don't know, Groundhog...
All right, it's a movie
about this guy
who lives the same day
over and over and over again,
until he learns to be
a better person.
I know it sounds totally hacky,
however, it's very well-executed.
What's that noise?
Oh, that noise just means
that we're all about to die.
All right,
if what you're saying is true
and you find yourself
in the loop again,
find me and say the words,
"Groundhog Day."
Just do it!
Well, as long as you are
on this ship, I'm your captain.
- And if you don't like it, you can...
- Stop sticking around.
- And watch out, Ray.
- Watch out for...
How did she know that?
Nate. Nate.
Library.
We can't put the rest of the team
at risk, all right?
Until we can figure out a way
to behave professionally,
we'll just have to forget
that this ever happened.
- I can't.
- Just try.
- Nate.
- Amaya and I were just, you know,
working on our harmonies
in case we have to impersonate...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, whatever.
I have something to tell you.
Hedgehog Day.
Damn it, you told me if I said,
"Hedgehog Day,"
you would know what I was
talking about.
Do you mean Groundhog Day?
Why would I tell you to tell me about
a Bill Murray movie?
No, all I know is I'm stuck
in this time loop and I'm...
Like Groundhog Day.
- Okay, got it. Okay. Yeah.
- You do?
Mmm-hmm.
And you'll help me figure out
what's going on?
Yeah, that's what friends are for.
- We're friends?
- Of course.
So lay it on me, what's happening?
All right. How about instead of trying
to stop the ship from exploding,
we all get on the Jumpship
and escape?
Yeah, while you guys were out,
I was running
my own little side mission
which crashed Gideon.
With her down, the Jumpship's locked
into the docking bay.
- So, we need to talk to Sara.
- No, I already tried.
She never listens to me.
Probably too pissed off.
You know, thinking about
the vibration pattern of the blast,
I don't think we were attacked
from the outside.
The explosion was caused
by someone on the ship.
Well, I seriously doubt anybody
would blow up this ship on purpose.
So, where do we start?
I mean, you've all been acting
a little suspicious
since you got back from the mission.
Whoa, whoa!
Mick doing laundry.
- Now, that's suspicious.
- Yeah, very.
Go.
I can't get this damn song
out of my head.
- Which one? Waterloo?
- Ah!
Don't mention it.
- Did it work?
- Did what work?
Why am I holding this thing
in my hand?
I'll look after it, Mick.
Okay.
Good. I better get my undies
in the dryer before Haircut does.
Why would Amaya want
the memory flasher?
It could have something to do
with Kuasa. She does wanna help her.
What if Kuasa somehow convinced her
to blow up the ship?
Take it easy on the conspiracy juice.
- I'll find out what's going on.
- All right.
Hey.
I thought Sara told you
to fix the ship?
Yeah, like she always does.
Yeah. Look, I know Sara can be tough.
Especially when you make her mad.
Hey, why are you
so worried about Sara's temper?
No, I just... You know the saying.
- Happy captain, happy ship.
- ...happy ship.
- Yeah.
I guess my catchphrase
is catching on in the future.
Yeah. Yeah, um,
everyone is saying it where I'm from.
Huh.
That's cool.
Come on, Nate,
we're running out of time.
What are you doing in there?
The truth is,
when it comes to you,
I'm not as strong as I'd like to be.
With this,
we can both forget it happened.
Yeah, you're right.
With everything going on,
with Mallus, Kuasa.
Zari mentioned something about the ship.
We should be clear-headed.
- Yeah.
But since we're gonna
flash ourselves anyway...
I mean, it's not like we'd remember.
Oh, Nate.
Thank God.
Come here, tiger.
Kill me now.
- Nate.
- Oh, hey.
- Amaya and I were just...
- Groundhog Day.
One hour, ship explodes.
Stuck in a time loop when we
have to stop the ship from exploding?
- Exactly. And I think that someone...
- Is triggering the explosion.
It's probably an accident,
but we have to investigate everyone
to figure out who's causing it.
There's a lot of secrets on this ship.
Let's start with Amaya.
- Why, so you can sex with her?
- That's crazy!
No, you two
flashing each other afterwards
in order to forget? That's crazy!
Why would we flash each other
- after having sex?
- Focus, Nate!
Right, ship exploding. Got it.
- Let's go find Rory.
- Right.
She probably wants to forget
how awesome it was.
Or how short.
So, I've timed out his schedule.
He always leaves right about... Now.
Here.
Come on.
Oh, suspicious-looking box.
Careful. For all we know,
it could be the cause of the explosion.
We just gotta take it nice and...
- Oh, my God!
Nice save!
Can you imagine if I'd tripped that?
Yeah, I don't have to imagine it.
Oh, God.
Okay. Here we go.
Damn it!
So you got all the traps?
I don't know. We've never gotten
this far before.
Okay.
Why would Mick rig all these traps
for a damn typewriter?
Maybe it's his criminal manifesto.
Let me see this.
This says "bosom" far too many times
to be a manifesto.
"As the twin suns of Dartayus
set on the horizon,
"her heaving bosom undulated
like the soothing waves of the bay.
"Buck swept her
into his musky embrace."
Mick's writing a sci-fi romance novel?
Yeah.
Well, that's the last thing
I thought I'd see before I die.
Oh...
Funny you should say that.
So, you're saying
Rory and Amaya are in the clear.
Which is why we're gonna go visit Ray.
He's been acting twitchy.
Well, let's go spy on my best friend.
Oh, wow, that's boring.
I think we can cross him off
our suspect list.
Ray.
Have you seen Zari?
I just checked the engine room,
she's not there.
Um... No, I haven't.
I'm sick and tired
of playing mom.
She's really starting to piss me off.
Oh, well, in the meantime,
how about some tea?
It's my signature blend
of chamomile, lavender, rose.
Very relaxing.
If you see Zari,
tell her I'm looking for her.
Yeah.
- Ray!
- Holy Toledo!
Where did you guys come from?
Were you spying on me?
Of course you were.
I shouldn't say anything.
Okay, I'll tell you everything.
Constantine told me to kill Sara
if Mallus ever takes control
of her again.
Wow, dude, that's heavy.
Wait, maybe Sara
Malluses out and blows up the ship.
What do you mean,
she blows up the ship?
Zari's caught in a time loop
and the ship explodes every hour.
- Like "Cause and Effect."
- What?
- Next Generation.
- It's Groundhog Day.
Fair enough. But Star Trek...
Wait, the ship explodes in an hour?
Yeah. Actually, 24 minutes.
And I think someone on board
is causing it.
- Mick.
- He's clean.
- Unlike his literary erotica.
- Excuse me, what?
Long story.
Like, literally, a long story.
- So weird. There was this...
- A thousand pages long and it was...
Anyway, the Captain's the only one
we haven't checked out.
For that, we need your help, Ray.
What is she doing
going to the Jumpship?
With Gideon down,
it's not like she can go anywhere.
Wait. Is there a way she could cause
the explosion from the Jumpship?
Could be any number of ways.
And with Mallus,
who knows what he's capable of.
I'm worried about
what we're gonna find in there.
I hope we don't have to use this.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Let's shrink-ray.
You sure she can't see us?
No, not while we're in stealth mode.
Which really just means
library voices
and no sudden movements.
- Hey.
- What are you up to?
- Oh, you know, crossword puzzles.
You look tired.
Thanks, jerk.
No, no, I didn't...
I mean, you always look good.
I just...
- Did you have a long day, or...
- You have no idea.
There's this person on my team,
and she is reckless,
she doesn't take orders.
And it's like, I want to tell her
how important she is to this team,
because she is.
But, sometimes...
I tell you,
she does not make it easy.
What'd she do?
Well, she hijacked Gideon,
crashed our entire system
testing out some simulation software
that finds loopholes in history.
That is definitely
against regulations.
Not that I haven't been tempted
to change the past.
It's just... I don't even want
to start looking for loopholes,
because then I'm gonna start looking
for ways to save my sister
and then I'm gonna
drive myself crazy.
Yes, you will. So don't.
I'm just tired of always being
the bad cop, you know?
Believe me, I understand.
I've lost count of how many times
I've had to yell at cadets
for screwing up
or bust them for breaking protocol.
Yeah, I don't know.
I feel you like might like that.
You seem to get a kick
out of ordering people around.
Maybe. Just a little bit.
Where are you calling me from?
I don't recognize that part
of the Waverider.
Welcome to the Jumpship.
- Are you hiding, Ms. Lance?
- No.
I am simply looking for some privacy.
Well, maybe I should come over.
Yeah. Yeah, but like...
I mean, I'm sure that you are
super, super busy.
It's the perks of being the boss.
I can just tell Gary
I have a meeting.
Yeah. "Boss."
Speaking of, I should probably
go check on the rest of the team.
Make sure nobody's
gonna blow up the ship.
Okay. Um... But yeah, if you change
your mind or whatever...
Does Sara not realize how hard
that woman's crushing on her?
Maybe she's got no finish.
No. Captain knows how to close.
This is something different.
- Shh. She's gonna hear us.
- Okay, do you hear that?
'Cause I've been hearing
this high-pitched buzzing sound.
It sounds like there's a fly
in the Jumpship.
Did you say a fly?
You have to kill it.
You have no idea what year it's from.
You could reintroduce the plague
and have a whole other crisis
on your hands.
Look out!
Groundhog Day.
Exploding ship.
- Personal hell.
- We're stuck in a time loop!
Winner, winner, chicken dinner.
It was only a matter of time
before we did one of these.
Damn girl, you look wrecked.
How many times have we done this?
How many times have you asked me,
"How many times have we done this?"
Or how many times
have we all been blown up?
So, you've been stuck in this loop
for a while?
Yeah. Like forever.
It's okay.
Maybe you could use a break.
- Have some fun.
- "Fun"?
- And blow up, every hour?
- Exactly.
No consequences.
Cheers.
Yeah!
Not bad, Mr. Rory. Not bad at all.
You're such an idiot.
If you wash your clothes inside out,
it helps keep them looking
newer longer. Try it.
Huh. I never see you wear this.
Stop touching my clothes.
I'm just saying, it's a nice color.
Nate.
- Hey, Amaya and I were just...
- Feeling bad
that you two had sex
and almost screwed up the mission.
Don't care. Groundhog Day.
Ship explodes.
Wait, you're caught in a time loop?
That's awesome.
I can't do this anymore.
I'm losing my mind.
- Wait, did you do the...
- Fun montage?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, thanks for that.
You're a good friend.
Nothing is fun anymore.
That's not good.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey, take it easy!
It's the only option I haven't tried,
and maybe it'll stop the loop.
- Hey, what the hell is going on?
- Don't come closer.
- Typical.
- Hey.
It's okay.
Let's talk this one through.
It doesn't matter.
You won't believe me.
Try me.
I keep reliving the same hour,
over and over again.
And no matter what I do,
the ship explodes.
Kills us all.
And I'm totally alone in it,
because for some reason,
I'm the only one
that's even aware
that it's happening.
And I try so hard, but...
I can never save any of you.
Okay. I want to help.
Wait, you believe me?
Yeah. How much time do we have left?
All right, people.
For reasons that are
too complicated to explain right now,
we have to search the ship.
Zari says that there's a bomb
and it's gonna explode in 30 minutes.
We have to find out why.
Okay. Well, the galley is clear.
Right. And I checked
the sleeping quarters.
Whoa! You went in our rooms?
Yeah.
- The library.
- What did you see in the library?
Something I can never un-see.
Guys, I think I looked everywhere.
There's nothing.
You didn't check the trash compacter.
I didn't even know
there was a trash compacter.
Well, it's not really part of the tour.
Gary?
The time dweeb!
What the hell are you doing here?
- Thank God you found me.
- What are you doing down there?
I tried to portal onto the bridge
but didn't account for drift
in the temporal zone.
My landing was hot
and my time courier broke on impact.
That's how I got stuck in here.
- Not the plan, but, uh... I adapted.
- But why are you on the ship?
The hell you got in here?
- A bomb?
- No.
No! That was our only chance
- of surviving.
- What do you mean?
He just destroyed the chrono-repeater
I used to initiate a time loop
in order to save you guys.
What?
I always wanted to die young.
Okay, nobody is going to die.
Well, actually, I got an alert
that the Waverider exploded
at precisely 4:20,
temporal standard time.
- What?
- 4:20.
- Get to the point, Gary.
- I took matters into my own hands.
But because of my little
portal mishap,
I couldn't warn you about the bomb.
But I could operate
the chrono-repeater
which is programmed to start
a one-hour loop,
prior to the explosion.
And I had hoped
that would give you enough time
to defuse the bomb yourselves.
- So now that this is destroyed...
- There are no more time loops.
So once there's an explosion,
that's it.
- Kablooey.
- All right, so what you're saying is,
we have five minutes to find this bomb,
before we all die.
Permanently.
All right, people.
We got five minutes to find this bomb
before it explodes.
We gotta think fast.
Uh,
before I portaled onto the ship,
I traced the temporal signature
of the bomb.
It originated in 1975.
So, the bomb must be something
from your last mission.
It could be hidden in the heel
of one of the platform shoes.
What about that stupid song?
Genius.
The one place I didn't look.
Why the hell would someone put a bomb
inside of an anachronism?
Damien Darhk
must have planted it there,
- knowing you'd bring it on board.
- Well, then let's get it off board.
No, we have to defuse it.
We can't open the doors without Gideon.
- Burn it.
- That would make it explode!
You know, for a guy who loves fire,
you really have no idea how it works.
What about you, Zari? Come on.
This whole time
that you've been on the ship
did you learn anything
that could help?
Right.
Let me think.
Zari?
Sorry, Captain.
- My beer's in there.
- What the hell are you doing?
The force field's not strong enough
to contain the explosion.
No, but it will keep you guys out
long enough
for me to say what I need to say.
Zari...
Mick.
You don't have to hide what you love.
Follow your heart and keep writing.
- Zari, we don't have time for this!
- Nate and Amaya.
I'm so lucky
to call you guys my friends.
- Zari, the bomb!
- What you guys have is so special.
I mean, the way
you look at each other...
Honestly, it makes me wanna puke,
but don't fight it.
You're crazy about each other.
Just don't have sex on missions.
Z, what are you doing?
What you would do, Ray.
You know, when I first came on board,
you were so nice and polite to me
that I wanted to punch you.
But I realize now,
the world would be a better place
if we were all
a little more like you.
But being nice and polite
is only going to get you so far.
So do me a favor and tell Sara
why you're so afraid of her.
Okay, sure.
But first, I'm gonna figure out
how to shut down the force field
- so we can deal with the bomb.
- I am dealing with the bomb.
- Zari, look, you need to listen...
- Sara, you are infuriating,
stubborn, and a pain in my ass.
Because you have to be.
You're not just the captain
of this ship, you are its soul.
You are so fierce and unflinching.
But why not apply some
of that fearlessness to your own life
and just ask poor Ava out already?
Did you have
a meaningful message for me?
Not now, Gary!
Zari, let us in,
we can do this together.
No.
I have spent
so much time with you guys.
You're my family now.
You deserve to be happy and if...
If I can be a small part
of making that happen, then
this'll be worth it.
- Zari.
- Look, that won't work.
You won't be able to contain
the explosion.
Zari, you don't have to do this!
Zari, as your captain,
I am ordering you to stand down!
You should know by now
I'm not good at following orders.
You just told me
what a good captain I am,
and now you're
not gonna listen to me?
Yeah, but this time,
I'm not doing it for myself,
I'm doing it for you.
I love you guys.
Zari.
- Who the hell are you?
- You know who I am, Zari.
Even though
you may have never seen my face.
Gideon? You're real?
Of course I'm real.
Just because
I'm an artificial intelligence,
doesn't mean I don't exist.
What's happening?
If you tell me I've been dreaming
this whole time,
I'm gonna kill you, real or not.
You're not dreaming,
but you're not awake.
In real life,
you're actually in the MedBay,
unconscious and healing.
What happened to me?
Well, after your fight with Sara,
you went into the engine room
to make repairs.
And there was an accident.
Right,
I was hit with that time sludge.
This "sludge," as you call it,
is a highly volatile substance
which helps power the ship through time.
You're lucky to be alive.
So, if my body's in the MedBay,
then where is my mind?
Your mind is in here, with me,
in my matrix.
I was able to upload your subconscious
via the neuro-monitor.
So, none of this is real?
Not in the way you're used to.
Why did you bring me here?
When you posed the question
about changing 2042,
your simulator went into overdrive
searching for an answer.
And a sampling of those trillions
of possible answers
showed me
that there was one constant.
You.
In order to save 2042
to find your so-called loophole,
you must work with the Legends.
Hold up.
You're saying my simulator works?
Did my program predict
that I'd bail on the team?
In almost every variation
of the timeline,
your fight with Captain Lance
precipitated your leaving the ship.
So, your goal was to get me
to choose to stay with the Legends.
I put you into your own program
and devised a scenario
where the only way to successfully
complete the simulation
was to grow closer to the team.
And develop a bond.
What about the bomb?
It was just a plot device
I incorporated.
A problem to solve.
But the real problem was you.
If you stayed angry
after your fight with Sara,
you would've left the team.
And without you and your totem,
there would be no chance
in the coming days
to defeat Mallus or save 2042.
So, the interactions,
the things I learned about the team,
they were all fake?
Everything you experienced
was extrapolated
from my current knowledge
of the Legends.
While not real,
what you saw was true.
It doesn't take a supercomputer
to predict that those two
would wind up dinky-tickling
once Amaya returned to the team.
Uh, this one seemed less plausible.
You'll have to ask Mr. Rory.
I am terrified
and in awe of you, Gideon.
Who knew you were
such an evil genius...
And a bit of a perv.
You never bothered to ask.
It's an impressive piece
of software you designed, Ms. Tomaz.
Is that a compliment, Gideon?
Don't let it go to your head.
Are you ready to wake up now?
One last question.
Gary.
Why even have him in the time loop
if he was just gonna be stuck
in the trash compactor
the whole time?
Thought it'd be funny.
Hey, rise and shine.
How are you feeling?
Oh... Like my head is made of cement.
You were exposed to the ship's
Bosonic hyper-fluid
in the engine room.
Knocked you out for hours.
- Oh, man, I have such a Gideon hangover.
- What do you mean?
While I was out,
Gideon transported my consciousness
into her matrix.
Okay.
I think you dreamed that.
No, it wasn't a dream, it was real.
Right, Gideon?
Unfortunately, I don't know
what you're talking about, Ms. Tomaz.
Oh, that is cold, Gideon.
After all that,
we're still not friends?
Zari, are you sure you're okay?
Gideon trapped me
in my own simulator,
so I was stuck on the Waverider,
reliving the same hour,
over and over again.
Needless to say,
I got to know you all
- really, really well.
- Right.
Could be caused
by the sedative dosage.
- I can look into it later.
- Yeah.
I'm telling the truth.
You know what, I'll prove it.
Sara, ask Ray what Constantine
told him about you.
Okay.
Ray, what did Constantine
tell you about me?
How did you know that?
He... He warned me that if you were
possessed by Mallus again,
and lost control, that I...
I should kill you.
Such a relief
to get that off my chest.
Well, he's right.
You should kill me
if Mallus takes over again,
and you are going to need
a lot of help.
Well, let's just hope
it doesn't come down to that.
Hey, you wanna get a coffee?
Yeah.
Are you wondering
what I learned about you?
Do I wanna know?
You're afraid of historical loopholes
because you'd be tempted
to save your sister.
Well, not a day goes by
that I don't think about her.
I'm sorry I fried Gideon, but...
I had to know if there was a way
to save my brother.
And what did the simulation say?
It said I can't do it alone.
Sounds like you're gonna need a team.
You mean it?
I've been thinking about it,
saving your brother.
And technically, it isn't a loophole.
It would be changing your past,
but your past is my future.
And as far as I'm concerned...
Well, the future's an open road.
And besides, I'll probably
need your help finding Mallus.
Hey, listen, it's none of my business,
but you should ask Ava out.
Mmm.
My relationships
have a way of ending badly.
You know, it turns out...
At the end of the day,
love is worth the risk.
None of us can do this alone.
Captain.
So, you're saying
it's like Groundhog Day.
That's what I was told, by you.
It's good to know matrix-me
is still a Bill Murray fan.
So, you said you
wanted to tell us something.
Yeah, you guys used the flasher
to forget you almost blew the mission
by sneaking off to have sex.
- What?
- I think we'd remember doing that.
Nathaniel, that is the whole point
of a memory eraser,
is that we don't remember.
Guys, flashing yourselves,
it's a temporary solution.
You need to work your stuff out.
Wow.
Ray must have used
a strong sedative on her,
because there is no way we would
ever use the flash gun. That's crazy.
It's not so crazy.
Amaya!
I saw Rory using it
to get that song out of his head.
And I thought,
"That is a brilliant idea."
But Zari's probably right.
- Totally. No flash gun. Mmm-hmm.
- Yeah.
- We should talk about our feelings.
- Yes.
I'll just leave it here.
Just in case.
Not that we would ever use it, huh?
- Who does those things?
- Who does?
I'm busy.
You should be.
You have a lot of writing to do.
I know you're writing a novel.
And it's really good.
But that ending needs a rewrite.
I mean, Buck is such a misfit,
that at the end,
we just wanna see him
embrace his new family.
Just a thought.
I wonder.
"Buck wrapped his glistening biceps
around his busty alien queen.
"He had lost his planet,
but found his home."
Hmm.
Not bad.
I am calm.
I am present.
I am centered.
Wally West.
You're not an easy man to find.
No. But that's the point of meditation.
- Who are you?
- My name is Rip Hunter.
I am trying to save the universe.
And I need your help.