In 2166, an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan
is opposed by the body
I'd sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future, my friends
may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered as legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Hold on to something!
I want to marry you, Ray.
Tragedy or heartbreak,
that's how it always ends
if the man's not Carter.
It's Carter!
He doesn't even remember who he was.
Kendra, what are you waiting for?
If I kill Savage,
his mind will be lost.
I'm so sorry, Rip.
Who are you, Gareeb?
Ramses's men inform me
that you still refuse to speak,
to reveal your name
or why you tried to kill me.
Who are you?
The man who is trying
to save the world from you.
And how are your efforts proceeding?
You can't even stand
for lack of food and water.
I will always rise up against you.
I will never give up.
Soon the sky rocks
will lay waste to this kingdom,
and you along with it.
This cell will be your tomb.
What do you know of the future
that I don't, Gareeb?
Mission almost accomplished.
That bottle of Scotch was given to me
by Rob Roy MacGregor in 1689.
It's not half bad.
We should be toasting
to Savage's death.
Apart from celebrating murder,
Savage still has Carter brainwashed.
I don't know if you've been
paying attention, Professor,
but murdering Savage
was always the plan.
Besides, Carter reincarnates,
which is more than I can say
about us.
As long as he's on board
and breathing,
Savage is a threat
to everyone on this ship.
So what, we just kill Savage
and leave Carter a brainless drone?
Yes.
Sorry we're late,
but we found something.
We've been running diagnostics
on Ray's suit
after his battle with Savage's
Rock 'Em Sock 'Em Robot.
The telemetry data included a
comparative scan of the robot's tech.
Amazing.
This neuromorphic profile
is astonishingly futuristic.
Yeah, it's from 2166.
Well, that's the thing. It's not.
This technology's light years
more advanced
than anything from 2166.
- Who cares?
- The Time Masters.
They refused to take
action against Savage
because he didn't pose
a threat to the timeline.
But if he comes into possession
of future technology...
It means he's been engaging in
exactly the same manipulation of time
that the Time Council
were designed to prevent.
So now they'll finally sign off on
undoing all the damage
Savage has done to the world.
Last time I checked, the Time Council
was at the edge of the timeline,
and this bucket of bolts
can barely hold it together as it is.
Gideon, what's the status
of the Time Drive?
Stable, Captain.
Plot a course
for the Vanishing Point.
Tonight, Vandal Savage
faces justice for his crimes.
Quite the reversal of fortune,
isn't it, Gareeb?
4,000 years ago it was you
who was the prisoner.
Ever since I met you again,
I've always wondered
how you managed to escape.
Another time, perhaps.
For the moment,
I'm more interested in this.
The brains
to your robot super-weapon.
At least a century more advanced
than anything to be found in 2166.
Do you have something to ask me?
How did you obtain the ability
to travel through time?
From you.
When I saw you again in 1975,
I realized that time travel
was the only explanation.
You showed a caveman fire.
And I had almost 200 years
to figure out
how to strike the flame.
All this time, I've been wondering
why it was so difficult
to locate you throughout history.
Because you've been
moving through history.
Well, you'll come to learn
that this is just one of many things
we have in common, Gareeb.
We're both doing
what we must to save the world.
Subjugating the world
to your rule is not saving it.
You would create a wasteland
and call it peace.
Do not misquote Tacitus to me.
I knew him well.
I have lived long enough
to watch civilizations rise and fall.
You weep for your son.
I have held dozens of my children
as they perished from old age.
You might be a Time Master,...
but I'm a master of time.
And I play a far deeper game
than you could ever hope
to comprehend.
Gideon, go to maximum
on the Time Drive.
Inadvisable, Captain.
When Dr. Palmer siphoned power
from the auxiliary Time Drive,
he reduced the ship...
Gideon! Take us to maximum.
We need to get to the Vanishing Point
as fast as possible.
Where am I?
Somewhere safe.
Safe as long as those cuffs hold.
Do you know who you are?
I'm Scythian Torvil,
adjunct to Lord Savage.
And you will release me,
or I will kill you where you stand.
Your name is Carter Hall.
You used to be Prince Khufu
of the Middle Kingdom.
- And I am...
- Kendra Saunders.
Oh, you seem surprised.
You didn't think Lord Savage
would warn me of my enemies?
Let me go and I promise you
I will show mercy.
I will kill you without
making you suffer first.
Not to sound like a six-year-old,
but are we there yet?
No, the Waverider was severely
damaged in Savage's last attack.
Yeah, I can tell by the way
she's flying.
You sure you're not
pushing her too hard?
The longer Savage
is on board the ship,
the greater the danger to all of us.
To us, or your family?
I checked with Gideon.
Bringing Savage onboard
didn't change the timeline,
and your family still dies.
The timeline is always in flux.
Once we get to the Vanishing Point,
all will be well.
Is that why you're pushing
the ship beyond its limits?
This has been my ship
for the last 13 years.
No one knows its limits
better than I do.
Not even Gideon.
The Waverider will hold together.
I promise you.
Bollocks. Gideon!
Time Drive failure, Captain.
The mains are offline.
- What happened?
- It appears the Time Drive
is in need of some repair.
Miss Lance,
if you wouldn't mind going,
- checking on our guest?
- On it.
Mr. Jackson. I'm going to need your
assistance in fixing the Time Drive.
What if Jefferson
can't get the ship moving again?
Oh, thanks for the vote
of confidence.
No, what I mean is
if the ship can't be repaired,
we're marooned in the Time Stream.
There really is no need to worry.
The Jumpship is equipped
with an auxiliary Time Drive,
capable of a one-time jump
back to 2016.
Which will not be necessary,
considering you are going to
fix the Waverider.
- I'll do my best.
- That's the spirit.
You look concerned, Martin.
I'm remembering
what Mr. Snart said about
Savage's presence on this ship
being a danger to us all.
Have you spoken
with your sister Laurel lately?
How do you know so much
about us?
Oh, I've only had 191 years
to research my enemies.
Well, then you'd know
I don't scare that easily.
You should be scared...
of Captain Hunter.
His obsession to save his family
will be the death of you all.
Thanks for the tip.
Enjoy being incarcerated.
Captain Hunter lied to you so often,
and still you persist
in believing him.
You do know why he selected
all of you
for this endeavor, don't you?
Great bone structure?
He chose people he could manipulate,
people that would believe his lies.
Well, the lies I don't believe
are yours.
Do you blame him for putting
his family's lives first?
I'd tell you to go to hell,
but you'd probably
just feel at home there.
Okay, I've got eyes
on the Time Drive.
There seems to be
a large crack in it.
Well, if the housing's intact,
we should be all right.
I am going to need you
to re-route the power
from the secondary manifold.
Okay. I'm on it.
Gideon, what is the level
of contamination in the engine room?
Levels at three percent
above maximum, Captain.
- We have to get him out of there.
- Don't worry.
He should be able to finish
before the radiation
has any adverse effect.
Jefferson?
Mom?
What are you doing here?
Good question. I'm supposed to be
meeting my son at Jitters.
But clearly he misses his
old job more than his mother.
I am so sorry.
I must've lost track of time.
Well, this should help.
I know it's not much,
but it belonged to your father.
At least it was going to.
I bought it for him
as a birthday present
before he passed.
It's awesome. Thanks.
Maybe you can use it tonight.
Dinner at your Grandma Louise's.
Yes. I will be there.
And I won't be late.
I just got to stop
by the university first.
The university?
I got to say good bye to a friend
who's leaving town.
- But I will be there.
- 6.00.
- Okay. All right, I love you.
- I love you too, baby.
Jefferson?
I did it. I got it working.
You said he wouldn't be harmed.
It must be the surge when he brought
the Time Drive back online.
- Gideon?
- Mr. Jackson has suffered
an extreme amount
of temporal radiation exposure.
- That sounds ominous.
- Oh, it is.
And there's nothing I can do
to reverse the side effects.
What side effects?
Mr. Jackson's internal organs
are aging at an accelerated rate.
The rest of his body
will soon follow.
Why are all the snacks
in the future sugar-free?
So much for progress.
You remember Alexa?
Yeah. From the security deposit job.
What about it?
Just had a feeling about that one,
a sixth sense things would end badly.
And they would have, if you hadn't
have pulled us out of there.
- So what?
- I'm getting the same feeling now.
Gideon, how effective were
Mr. Jackson's attempts
to bring the Time Drive back online?
The drive's functions
have been restored,
but the entire system
will require a master reboot
before we can continue on
to the Vanishing Point.
Yes, please begin.
And in the meantime,
could you check the timeline
for any variations
in my family's future?
I believe Miss Lance
already told you the results.
Please.
The timeline remains unchanged.
Were you expecting
something different?
Hope springs eternal, Miss Lance.
If it didn't, I would've surrendered
to despair a long time ago.
I assume Mr. Savage
is still secure in his cell?
He wasn't exactly short
on opinions on you, though.
I'd imagine not.
Among them being
that you would sell us out
to save your family.
He's not wrong.
Mr. Jackson is currently
in the med bay
facing death due
to temporal radiation exposure.
- Wait, what?
- I sent him to fix the Time Drive.
I could have gone myself.
And I'm left to wonder if...
in some way,
I did it because of the risk.
So you sent Jax on a suicide mission
so that you could stay alive
to save your family?
I don't know, Sara.
That's what vexes me.
You know what vexes me?
Thinking that we've thrown
in with a captain
who cares more about himself
than he does his crew.
Kendra, are you sure about this?
Do you remember him?
He was our son.
Aldus.
Do you really
expect me to believe that?
I expect you to remember
your feelings.
We were together.
And we were happy.
We were a family.
Kendra, stay back!
Oops.
Are you okay?
- I should've known better.
- But are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Stay away from him.
I'll be right back.
- Where are you going?
- To end this.
Dr. Palmer. To what do I owe
the pleasure of this visit?
You're gonna tell me
how to free Carter's mind.
Well, all you had to do was ask.
Are you sure you want me to?
Of course I'm sure.
Because the moment I release him,
you will lose her forever.
You don't know Kendra.
I know Chay-Ara.
And I know the man who stands
between you and your love
has stood between me and mine
for millennia.
We're actually quite alike,
you and I.
We're nothing alike.
You're insane.
But yet Chay-Ara once loved me
as she professes to love you.
Oh, you didn't know that, did you?
I don't even think
Chay-Ara remembers,
but 4,000 years ago
I discovered that my Chay-Ara
had been reborn
but with no memory
of what had happened.
- Like you murdering her and Carter.
- True.
She had no recollection of my...
my crime of passion.
And she fell in love with me...
very deeply.
And I with her.
That is perverse.
No, that is fact.
That is history.
And we were happy,
Dr. Palmer, very happy.
None of us blinded by our cursed past
until he came.
He took her away from me.
He poisoned her against me.
He stole the happiness
that we shared, Dr. Palmer.
No.
No. Carter is a good man.
And you are my only enemy.
Am I?
Or am I just a man
experiencing the same things
as you are right now?
We have the same enemy.
If Carter's free, you lose her.
But then she would hardly be
the first woman you've lost,
now, would she?
I am really gonna have to beef
up our security around here.
It was pretty easy
to bypass the system,
considering I designed it.
You like my ride?
- Those are some pretty hot wheels.
- Yeah.
Maybe that's your new name.
- How you feeling?
- I'm okay.
- What are you doing here?
- I came to drop off a note.
Let me guess. It says,
"Hey, Felicity. I hope you're well.
I'm off to travel through time
and fight an immortal bad guy."
- Is that me?
- Yeah.
- That was pretty good.
- Thank you.
So, obviously, Oliver told you.
Don't let his broodiness fool you.
He can be quite chatty sometimes.
He also happened to mention that
you're going on this suicide mission
because you think
there's nothing for you here.
You think it's a suicide mission?
I don't think going after
Vandal Savage is a vacation.
But don't change the subject.
You have a life here, Ray.
Actually, everybody thinks I'm dead.
Nothing puts things in perspective
more than seeing yourself
become a ghost.
You're not a ghost.
You just need to come back
to the world.
And I will, after we take out Savage.
I became the Atom to make
the world a better place.
And I'm pretty sure
that saving it counts.
I'm pretty sure it does too.
See you soon.
You know, I would've stayed for you.
I do. But who knows?
Maybe the future Mrs. Palmer is out
there somewhere in the past,
the future, some parallel universe.
I'm off to save the world...
not fall in love.
"And though my soul departs
the Earth,
I count the days till my rebirth.
I will wait across eternity
for my love to come back to me."
Please.
Come back.
Ray?
Ray...
Ray, stop!
Please.
Just give me a chance to explain.
- What you saw back there, it was...
- What? Wasn't what it looked like?
You were reciting a love poem
to your brainwashed ex-boyfriend.
I am just trying to help Carter
remember who he really is.
Your soul mate.
Yeah, that's the part
in the conversation
where you're supposed to say,
"No, Ray, you're my soul mate."
Ray, you know that I love you.
I know.
It's just not enough.
I can't believe I'm saying it,
but Savage was right.
Loving you is like a curse.
Oh, Ray.
You have to know, whatever he said,
he's just trying to get inside
your head.
I know that.
But he's right.
Kendra, I don't think
I can do this anymore.
What are you saying?
Oh, what?
You want to end things?
Unless you can tell me
that I'll ever be anything more
than just Carter's placeholder.
Ray.
Are you certain
these results are accurate?
Jefferson's blood chemistry
is akin to that of a...
A 63-year-old man.
Actually, I don't feel a day over 60.
This isn't funny.
No, and it's all Rip's fault.
I'm afraid he's also suffering
from early-stage osteoarthritis.
The exposure to the temporal
radiation
has led to an accelerated rate
of intracellular degeneration.
This is what happens
when Rip goes with Plan B.
Plan A being taking Savage's
head in with that mace.
We're endeavoring to resolve
this without bloodshed.
And how's that working out
for you, Gandhi?
Look, there's nothing
we can do about it now.
We can talk to Hunter.
Even if Kendra was to kill Savage,
my situation's still the same.
We're talking about our situation,
Pops.
We're not waiting around
for the other shoe to drop.
You deserve better.
- Alexa?
- You bet your ass.
- We need to talk.
- We saw what you did to Jax.
And we're worried
it's just the beginning.
- The beginning of what?
- It's like I said, Rip.
As long as Savage is alive
and on this ship,
he is dangerous.
The Time Drive is rebooting.
We will soon be on our way.
I'm asking for a little faith,
gentlemen.
Sorry, fresh out.
I take it you and Mr. Snart
are of the same mind?
Yes.
And what of you, Miss Lance?
You're the one who said
you'd sell us out for your family.
Well, if that's how you all feel,
none of you is obliged
to continue on this voyage with me.
As I told Martin, the Jumpship
can make a one-time voyage
back to 2016.
Are you saying it's ours?
I'm saying that this mission
has always been
a voluntary enterprise.
And the mission was to kill Savage.
Which doesn't seem
to be on the table anymore.
Very well.
Leave, if that's what you...
It's been a blast, Rip.
Good luck getting
to the Vanishing Point.
Tell your pals Chronos says,
"Kiss my ass."
What about you, Sara?
Never been one to run from a fight.
Hi.
Impossible.
When I saw you last...
I know.
A miracle...
when I thought there were
none left to be had.
I needed to see you.
Look, I don't know how,
but I'm gonna get you out of here.
This isn't your fight anymore,
Ta-er al-Sahfer.
I'm not gonna let you rot here.
Not when you're in here
because of me.
I am in here because of my choices,
beloved.
I made them
ready to accept my punishment.
I won't leave you in here.
If you love me, you will.
If you love me, you will leave
this place far behind,
and live a life unburdened
by your past.
It's easier said than done.
Anything worth doing always is.
Well, finally an intellect
approximate to my own.
My imprisonment was starting
to get dreary, Professor.
I'm not here
to play mind games with you.
I'm here to ask you
if you remember a night
in October, 1975,
a place called the Greyhill Building.
That night, you and your acolytes...
Were celebrating the acquisition
- of your friend Carter Hall's body.
- Yes.
It's my understanding
this ritual involved
you sharing your immortality
with your followers.
And you wish for me to do
the same for someone else.
Someone dear to you.
Your nuclear counterpart,
perhaps?
Yes.
And as impertinent
as this may sound,
I need your help.
Well, clearly, your friends
didn't give you
the full account of the ritual.
You see, it was Carter's blood
that worked the magic.
Perhaps you should talk to him.
Or better yet, Dr. Palmer.
I'm sure that he would be
more than happy
to help you spill some.
And I'm certain
you would enjoy that.
Pitting me and Raymond
against Carter, against Kendra.
Having all of us
at each other's throats
while being stranded
in the Time Stream.
But...
we're not stranded.
Not entirely.
Thank you, Mr. Savage.
As I'd hoped, you've provided me
with a solution to my problem.
I don't get it, Grey.
What's in here that's gonna fix me?
Well, nothing inside the Jumpship,
Jefferson
but rather the craft itself.
You see, this ship is pre-programmed
to return to 2016.
I've made some additional adjustments
according to the theory
of quantum-retro causality,
and if my math is correct,
the trip through the Time Stream
should reverse your condition.
No... no.
I'm not leaving you or the team.
Which is why
I'm not giving you a choice.
What did you do?
I've administered a mild sedative.
You roofied me again?
When I tricked you
onto this ship the first time,
I was only thinking of myself.
Now I'm thinking of you.
You can't do this!
If we're separated, you'll die!
I've already lived my life,
Jefferson.
Now you must live yours.
Give my love to Clarissa.
Tell her I'm sorry.
She deserved
a proper good bye.
Grey! Grey, no!
No!
- Knock, knock.
- Oh, hello.
I hope you don't mind,
but I thought I'd see
if I could interest you
in a lunch date.
Oh, my darling.
I'm right in the middle
of some research
that simply cannot wait.
What's the topic?
As a matter of fact, time itself.
The irony.
Oh! Damn, I completely forgot.
I promised I'd meet
with some fellow academics
to help resolve
an experiment of theirs.
Does this experiment have anything
to do with time travel?
Almost certainly.
But it won't take long.
In fact, I'll be home
before you even know it.
Clarissa?
You, you know that I love you.
There's nothing I do
that isn't driven
by that very thought.
Now let's get the hell out of here.
- What'd you do, Poindexter?
- What do you mean?
The Jumpship. Where is it?
Well, it's really more a question
of when.
But, oh, yes.
You both wanted to return to 2016.
Got it in one.
I did what I had to do
to save Jefferson's life.
Now we must do whatever's necessary
to repair the Waverider
and deliver Savage
to the Vanishing Point.
Oh, back so soon with the stench
of defeat written all over you.
Can't say I didn't warn you.
Trying to get under my skin?
Is that it?
Got your little game figured out.
For all your intelligence,
you still didn't manage
to make Chay-Ara yours.
I wouldn't expect a psychopath
like you to understand.
Kendra is free to do what she wants.
You know what I see
when I look at you?
I see weakness
masquerading as goodness.
I'm not the one trapped in a cage.
Well, if it weren't for this cage,
you wouldn't have
that arrogant look on your face.
- You think I'm afraid of you?
- No.
I know you are.
At least Carter had the courage
to face me like a man.
No wonder she didn't choose you.
Oh...
You feel better now, Dr. Palmer?
Not even close.
And I thought
you were nothing like me.
I'll leave you
to contemplate on that.
Time Drive reinitialization
complete, Captain.
The primary systems
are back online and stable.
Begin ignition sequence
and resume our route
to the Vanishing Point.
You're a fool, Professor.
I'm trying to save Jefferson's life.
Savage has escaped.
- What?
- I'm sorry.
Pull up all the surveillance
monitors, now!
I'm afraid Vandal Savage
has already freed Carter Hall,
and is preparing to disengage...
That can't be good.
Gideon's entire
operational matrix is offline.
And without her help...
We'll have to make our
approach the old-fashioned way.
Shouldn't we be
more worried about Savage
and his brainwashed crony?
Yes. Which is why I need you
and Dr. Palmer
to go and recapture him.
In the meantime, if the rest
of us can't figure out
how to pilot the ship without Gideon,
we're never gonna be able
to leave the Time Stream.
If we live through this,
you bumbling idiot,
I might just kill you.
Exactly how old-fashioned
are you talking?
So, if the Time Stream
is like this vast river,
these maps plot the safest course
along that river's path.
Exactly. I keep these here
just in case of emergency.
Well, this certainly qualifies.
What's Jurgens Ridge?
Pray you need never find out.
Martin, you're gonna be our engineer.
I need you to adjust
our energy output
to avoid over-taxing
the Waverider.
And you, Miss Lance,
you're gonna be our navigator.
I was League of Assassins,
not NASA.
I need someone
who can make tough calls
under extreme pressure.
No one fits that description
better than you.
Come to join the party?
You should've left me back in 2166!
Yeah, yeah,
we know that, mullethead.
Who are you to stand up against me,
Vandal Savage, destroyer of empires?
Leonard Snart, robber of ATMs!
We need more power
to the Time Drive, Martin.
How much further can we push it?
25 percent,
and only for a brief burst.
But it might be all we need.
It's still two against four.
Come on!
What's our trajectory
looking like, Miss Lance?
Just give me a second here.
Well, oddly enough,
as the Vanishing Point
is at the very end of time.
Yeah, and we're never gonna
make it there
if you don't lower the ship
negative 12 degrees on my mark.
Three, two, one, now!
- Did it work?
- Well, we're not dead.
I got this. Handle Savage.
Haircut! Move your fat head
so I can get a clean shot!
- They seem to be getting closer.
- I'll go help them.
No! I'm not gonna place another one
of you in jeopardy, I'll go.
But who's gonna pilot the ship?
Gareeb, I was wondering
where you were hiding.
Bring her to me.
Chay-Ara, my love.
I'm sorry that it has to end
like this again.
Carter.
I will wait for eternity.
Come back to me.
Kendra...
He's alive.
You saved him.
You saved us all.
- Is that...
- Welcome to the Vanishing Point.
I can't believe we made it.
And what did you do
to your shoulder?
Oh, I might have jumped
in front of a laser blast
intended for Miss Saunders.
What?
I couldn't have my team thinking
I cared more about myself
than them, now, could I?
Really?
I think I just lost control
of the ship.
Yeah, that might have
something to do with us
being the most wanted time criminals
in all of history.
Timeship Waverider,
we've taken control
of your guidance systems.
Disable your weapons
and prepare to be boarded.
- Oh, it's good to be home.
- Captain Hunter.
This is unexpected.
Well, I have a reputation
to maintain, don't I?
And I hereby request
an immediate assembly
of the Time Council in accordance
with General Order 52.
So you've returned
to answer for your crimes?
No. I'm here to justify them.
If this truly is good bye,
would you mind answering
just one final question?
Well, it seems only sporting.
How did you manage to escape
my prison all those years ago?
There were no signs of damage,
no clues to your tricks.
It left me puzzled for centuries.
The best magic tricks
have the simplest solutions.
I bribed your guard
with a novelty pen.
Had a picture of a woman on it.
Turn it upside down,
her top comes off.
I won it from a drunk GI
in a Philippines bar in 1944.
It's a tacky souvenir,
but in this case, a lifesaver.
Now, unfortunate for you,
the guards at the Vanishing Point
won't be quite so easily swayed.
- Hey.
I was making sure that he was okay.
I think most guys would be
more inclined
to smother him with a pillow.
Just because he stole my girl
and tried to take over the ship?
But seriously,
Carter saved your life.
He's a part of this team.
Always has been.
- I wish things could be different.
- Yeah, me too.
I need you to know
that what we had was real.
In a way...
a broken heart is
just what the doctor ordered.
- It is?
- Yeah.
When I lost Anna, I thought that...
I could never find anybody
who I could spend
the rest of my life with.
You proved me wrong.
Thank you for showing me
that it's possible.
Rip Hunter,
on behalf of the Time Council,
you are hereby ordered...
Yeah, before you do that,
there's someone I'd like you to meet.
You remember Mr. Savage?
Of course.
And we remember how you pled
for us to remove him
from the timeline once before.
Well, as the first Time Master
was so fond of saying,
that was then, this is now.
Incontrovertible proof
that Vandal Savage
has been engaged
in the manipulation of time!
Including a confession.
When I saw you again in 1975,
I realized that time travel
was the only explanation.
You showed a caveman fire,
and I had almost 200 years
to figure out
how to strike the flame.
Impressive, Captain Hunter.
You and your team
have accomplished
what none of us here
in the Time Council
believed you would.
If the prisoner
would step forward...
Vandal Savage,
by the power of this chamber,
it is my duty to return you
to Earth immediately.
What?
This man you've brought
before us
is needed back in 2166.
You're in league with him.
I wouldn't expect you
to understand our reasons.
For all your wisdom,
you were never able to take
the long view of history.
Take him away.
Search their ship for the others.
- Did you hear that?
- Don't try to distract me.
We need to find somewhere to hide.
Why do we need
to find somewhere to hide?
Alexa.
Damn.
If you're here for Savage,
you're too late.
- Mick, what's going on?
- You're under arrest.
If I had a nickel
for every time I heard that.
Druce's men have taken your ship.
Your friends are under arrest.
And you are once again
my prisoner.
This time, I don't plan to lose you.
Oh, and yes, I do remember
the guard very well.
He died.
Now, if you would excuse me,
I'd better be getting back to 2166.
I've been waiting so very long
to meet your family.
Wouldn't miss it for the world.
No! No!
No!