My name is Damien Darhk.
In 2016, I was murdered
by the Green Arrow.
But I was removed from the
timeline 31 years before
my death by a speedster from
the future named Eobard Thawne.
Together, with Malcolm Merlyn,
a former head of the
League of Assassins,
the three of us are going to
locate the Spear of Destiny;
a mystical object which
can rewrite reality itself.
With the Spear in our possession,
we will change our past and our future.
And the world as you know it.
Previously on “Legends of Tomorrow”...
A deep scan reveals that Captain Hunter's
neural architecture
has been reprogrammed
with a new identity.
The Longinus Medallion.
Rip!
I know that you're one of the protectors
of the Spear of Destiny
and I know that you know
where the other pieces are hidden.
You're gonna torture me, aren't you?
I'm not gonna torture you.
They are.
Damien Darhk, the man behind
tonight's siege of Star City,
was killed by the masked vigilante
known as the Green Arrow.
Amateur cell phone video
captured his final moments,
putting an end to the chaos
that has gripped the city.
This is the great Malcolm Merlyn?
I am unimpressed.
Well, he's fallen on hard times.
But this man used to be Ra's al Ghul.
Uh, we haven't met. I'm Eobard Thawne.
I'm... from the future.
What the hell is going on here?
Excellent question. Here's another...
Do you believe in second chances?
I just watched you die.
Yeah, I hear 2016's not my best year,
but I plan on fixing that.
But the question for you, Malcolm, is:
Do you wish to see your
fortunes similarly reversed?
By time travel?
No. No.
Something much better.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
- Well?
- No luck. So far.
It's not that Captain
Hunter's uncooperative.
It's that he's not fully in
possession of his marbles.
So he won't tell us where the
rest of the Spear of Destiny is?
Uh, it's more like... can't.
Which wouldn't be such a problem
if you two idiots hadn't
lost the Longinus Medallion.
I seem to remember
you being there as well.
Until you weren't.
I hate when he does that.
If you have something
to say to me, Malcolm,
I suggest you keep it to yourself.
I'm sorry.
Am I supposed to be afraid of you?
Oh, I would be.
Considering I can kill you
before you even knew I was doing it.
Ah, yes.
But then you wouldn't get what you want.
You brought me and Damien into
your little quest for a reason.
Without the Medallion,
Hunter is our only way to
get the rest of the Spear.
You need me to get it out of him.
We already tried torture.
I'm not talking about torture.
I'm talking about hypnosis.
Regression therapy.
Hunter's mind is locked away.
I've got the key.
Is this some technique you picked up
with the League of Assassins?
The League didn't call me
“the Magician” for nothing.
Well, be quick about it.
Speedsters aren't
known for their patience.
What's to keep Hunter's crew from finding
the rest of the Spear
before Merlyn finishes
unscrambling Hunter's brain?
The workings of the Medallion
are lost to history.
Trying to get it to reveal its
secrets will prove difficult.
Plus, we have an additional
advantage over them.
Enlighten me.
They're idiots.
- You're all idiots.
- Excuse me?
Pot, meet kettle...
Yeah, Mick. Given your glass house,
you shouldn't throw stones.
Mixing metaphors isn't
going to solve anything.
How about instead of bickering,
we figure out our next
move against the speedster
and his allies.
“Legion of Doom”
has a sexier ring to it.
I'm not calling them that.
And we need to figure
out a way to rescue Rip.
All you gotta do is trade
the Amulet, or the Medallion,
for the Englishman. It's really simple.
The only thing is, I
don't know how it works.
Hmm. You're an idiot.
You want to put an artifact
that can rewrite reality
into the hands of the
enemy and we're the idiots?
- Mm-hmm.
- Our priority has to be
identifying this speedster.
Of course you'd say
that. I mean, he is the one
that killed your boyfriend, so...
He's at the center of this,
and you can't defeat an
enemy that you don't know.
Look, Amaya's right.
And I hate to say it, but so is Mick.
- I'm not an idiot.
- Not about being idiots.
About using the Medallion as leverage.
But first, we need to
figure out how it works.
Well, in my defense,
it's a mystical object.
It doesn't come with
a set of instructions.
Maybe's that been the
problem, approaching it
from a mystical vantage instead
of leaning into our strengths,
- which are...
- Technological.
Exactly. And as it happens,
I have a colleague in
Central City whose knowledge
might prove to be advantageous.
Gideon, set a course
for Central City, 2017.
Jax, stick with Martin.
And let's work on putting
a name to our speedster.
Aww, here comes a man
who looks like he just struck out.
Don't get smug with me, Damien.
I may not have all my prior resources,
but at least I'm not dead.
Look, I couldn't get Hunter to remember
because his memories aren't
buried or locked away.
They're gone.
It's like his old self didn't exist.
Are you sure about that?
Do you think you can do any better?
You are welcome to try.
We already tried torture.
You know what I love about torture?
I'm not sure if you have
enough time for me to list
all the reasons, but mainly it's because
there's always another gear to find.
This is what I get for relying
on a washout and a dead man.
I don't like that guy.
Hmm, you know.
I'll be honest.
Which I have to admit, I
don't have much practice in.
I don't like this situation.
Not one bit.
For one thing, Mr. Thawne
has this habit of treating me
like a henchman.
And do you know what all
henchmen have in common,
Captain Hunter?
No thoughts on this one?
The thing that all
henchmen have in common
is that they all end up dead.
A fate that I am
fastidiously trying to avoid.
Maybe it's that I just
hate taking orders.
Or being threatened.
You don't like being threatened, do you?
Hm? What's that?
Oh, sorry.
Oh, God. No.
Yeah, neither do I.
Which is why I need your cooperation.
To end Mr. Thawne's tedious threats.
Look, I... I don't know anything.
- I swear.
- Shhh!
I can't take your word for it.
But don't worry.
I will start you off
with an easy question.
Right eye or left eye?
No, please. Please, don't.
I'll do anything, I'll...
I'll tell you anything
you want to know. Even
if I don't know it!
- Please, don't!
- Shh.
Second question.
When was the last time you
had any dental work done?
What? No, no, God.
It may not be in the best
condition, but then again,
Captain Hunter is British.
You pulled out his tooth?
As torture goes, isn't
that kind of bush league?
Look closer.
Thank you, but no.
There're some markings
on here, like a barcode.
Account information.
From a security deposit box
in Switzerland.
Who puts that kind of
information on a tooth?
A Time Master.
That's no ordinary security box.
My thinking exactly.
Now, it's possible the box could contain
his son's birth certificate
and the like, but...
Given the exotic nature of the
care that's been taken here,
I would have to assume...
- It's the rest of the Spear.
When was it last accessed?
January 2025.
Oh, you got somewhere to go?
Funny, just like clockwork...
Take the Time Sphere back to 2025
and secure the rest of the Spear.
The next one of you who screws up
will lose more than just a tooth.
Well, I'd hate to see you
lose another hand, Malcolm.
Seriously, Grey?
I know you didn't bring me
to 2017 just so we could get
lattes and frappuccinos, man.
Of course not.
Just my colleague merely frequents
this establishment at this hour.
Sorry, Jefferson.
You should go back to the Waverider.
I can handle things from here.
What the hell is going on with you, man?
Dad?
I didn't know you were coming to town?
Well, I... I wanted to surprise you.
Oh.
Wait. Your colleague
is your daughter?
Lily, this is my friend Jefferson.
Jefferson, this is my daughter.
Nice to meet you.
Hey.
- Should we, uh, sit down?
- Yeah.
This is... So weird.
Uh, because I didn't think
I'd get the chance to meet you.
Like, ever. But, uh, here we are.
I was explaining to Jefferson
how you might be able
to assist us with the, um...
Research project.
Uh, sort of like Indiana Jones.
Yeah, sort of.
You brought it to a coffee shop?
Oh, well, for one thing.
It's throwing off low
levels of ionic radiation
Is that an ionic transmographer?
I've never seen one
smaller than a house!
Yeah, I had an idea
for hyperminiaturization
when I was in Tahiti.
I don't vacation well.
You know, I'm thinking a
shortwave ionic pulse might...
Whoa!
Hey.
Perhaps we should, uh, take
our little research project
somewhere a bit more private...
A temporal navigation vessel.
I... I absolutely cannot believe it.
Um, hello, who are you?
Oh, hi. Hi, I'm Lily.
I'm... I'm Martin's daughter.
We didn't know Martin had a daughter.
Yeah, you told me
you didn't have kids.
Well, I like to keep my
private life... private.
There's private, and there's lying.
Sara, do you know about this?
Oh, I know all about this.
What are you doing?
Trying to make up my mind.
I mean, Eobard has
such a delicious selection
of killing devices.
We can't just storm into the bank
and demand to see the deposit box.
We absolutely can.
We're former members of
the League of Assassins.
This operation requires subtlety.
Not a bloodbath.
Well, I... I'm sorry. I'm
not up on current events,
But might this squeamishness
that I'm witnessing
be the cause of your downfall?
Hunter is an asset.
One that we can use to gain
access to our objective.
To not use him is foolish.
Oh. Well, in that case,
I would have to defer to
your superior expertise
in foolishness.
But if your plan goes south,
it's not our speedster friend
you need to worry about.
One thing I hate more
than taking orders from him...
is being threatened by you.
Luckily, Damien...
I don't find you threatening.
What's the big deal?
The professor didn't
have a kid, now he does.
Mazel tov.
Thank you.
The big deal is Lily
is a Time Aberration,
which was all well and good,
until you plucked her out of
2016 and showed her a timeship,
which could cause more aberrations.
Hey, what you looking at me for?
Because you were with him.
I quite simply missed my daughter.
If Lily's presence
on the Waverider posed
any temporal issues, I'm sure Gideon
would have detected them.
Plus, Grey said Lily
could hook the Medallion
up with Gideon, so...
Wait, she wants to try
networking an ancient amulet
with an advanced AI system?
I'm totally helping.
Fine. Then I would
appreciate it if you...
If none of you would reveal to
her that she's an Aberration.
Why you looking at me?
So where are we on
identifying the speedster?
I think the technical term is nowhere.
All the speedsters the Flash faced
are either dead or his friends.
Or people he thought were
his friends and are now dead.
Okay, we will figure this
out. And in the meantime,
you and Lily keep working
with the amulet to figure out
to figure out where the
rest of the Spear is.
Who's to say he won't kill us anyway?
Even after we've gotten
his precious spear?
Oh, forget it. Why am I asking you?
I don't know, man.
I don't know anything.
I don't even know why you're
getting me to wear this...
This... this... this...
This monkey suit.
And my mouth is so sore.
Quit whining.
The fact of the matter is,
we have something in common, Rip.
My name is Phil.
Whatever.
We are both dealing with
unstable individuals.
And that is not something I enjoy.
Hey, this is not exactly a
walk in the park for me, either.
Which is why
you will do exactly as I say.
And maybe, just maybe,
you will make it through this alive.
Cool. Right.
Um, what... what is
it you want me to do?
Tell me, Phil. Have you ever been
to Switzerland?
Put this in your ear.
What is it?
Communication device.
Really? It's so small...
Do it, or I'll shove
it down your throat.
It will allow us to monitor you.
This is very simple.
You go to the bank
associate and you tell them
you want to access security box 4587.
4587, right.
Um, what... What do I do then?
Bring the contents
of said box back to us.
If you don't, you'll be killed.
Really?
What? I'm motivating him.
In and out.
Take no longer than five minutes.
You will be fine.
I'll be fine.
I'll be fine. Okay.
This would be easier if
we just killed everybody.
Hi, how are you?
I'd like box 4587, please.
Well, sure, have a seat.
What do you think's going on with him?
It's simple. His mind is pudding.
Not Hunter. Thawne.
It's strange how he never stays
in one place for very long...
Perhaps that's why they
refer to them as speedsters.
What, you think he left us
behind in 1967, Los Angeles,
because he had a more
pressing engagement?
What about what he said to us earlier?
That he wanted to kill one of us?
No. That he didn't know
why he was relying on us.
I mean, fair question.
Why does a time traveling speedster
need to rely on anyone?
Thawne's hiding something.
Wouldn't you like to know what it is?
Thawne said we knew
each other back in 2016.
Do I really become so stupid
that you think these mind
tricks will work on me?
I am not trying to...
In a trio such as ours,
turning one against each other
for your own benefit is not
only obvious, but cliché.
Thawne does not treat
us as equals to him.
And until he does, neither of
us is getting what he wants.
All right. Let's go over this again.
I already been over it, Sara.
Mm-hmm, again and again.
And again.
We're obviously dealing
with a new player.
Whoever this speedster
is, it's someone you
and your friends haven't
encountered before.
Which means the
speedster's from the future,
which makes sense, because
speedsters can time travel.
Then would the speedster
need the Spear of Destiny for?
He could just go back and
change history himself.
But not reality.
That's why he needs the Spear.
Question is, what is the
speedster trying to change?
Or fix?
That's the question.
He knows what we want to do
with the Spear of Destiny,
but he's being very coy about his plans.
Very well, Mr. Hunter.
Please lean towards
the panel, if you would.
Excuse me?
A retinal scan.
- Rectal scanner?
- What?
It's an eye scan. Part
of the bank's security.
You know,
this whole situation sucks,
but man, I love being in the future.
- What?
Retinal scan. Right.
Oh.
Why, uh... Why is it not working?
Voice ID is next.
You need to speak your access code.
Access code.
Oh, boy.
Yes, so, the one you set
when you opened your account.
Uh...
Get out of there now.
Yeah.
No, don't.
Go. Move.
Don't.
This was your plan.
Which I am trying to execute.
And failing spectacularly, per usual.
Look, we can't just
let them call security.
I am calling security.
Great idea. Security, no, that's...
Security is awesome.
You aren't planning on going
rogue on us, now, were you, Rip?
I have told you. My name is Phil.
All right, Phil. It
was lovely knowing you.
Don't! We still need him.
He's useless to us.
Hey, I can be more useful.
Ah, damn it.
Security is gonna be on
top of us at any moment.
Might I suggest you kill them instead?
Try and run, and I will find you
and feed you your testicles.
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Ahh!
- Ahh!
Reinforcements are on their way.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Okay, that should just about do it.
And now we just have
to activate the Medallion
and see if Gideon can access its data.
Okay.
So what are we waiting for?
Nothing, it... It's just if...
If we've underestimated the size
of the artifact's data stream...
We'll fry the ship's
CPU and we'll all spend
the rest of our lives
stranded in the Temporal Zone.
The ship's CPU has a name.
Sorry, Gideon.
Can we at least talk about
this before you connect...
Gideon?
You still there?
Oh, my God, we killed her.
Artificial intelligences
cannot, by definition,
be killed, Dr. Palmer.
Yes, I know.
It's pretty remarkable
considering we just mainlined
1.2 zettabytes directly into her brain.
Yeah.
I'm processing the Medallion's
temporal output as we speak.
- Nice work, doctor.
- Doctor!
You don't happen to have any
champagne on this ship, do you?
Hey.
Ah, 1998 Blanc de Noir.
I like beer.
Gets me drunk.
To Lily.
To Gideon.
Wow.
That tastes real.
It's completely synthetic.
The food fabricator can make anything.
Except American Cheese,
which is pretty much
synthetic to being with.
Beluga caviar?
Fake food never tasted so good.
Fake food for a fake person.
What did you say?
Uh, no. He didn't say anything.
Everyone has been looking
at me weird ever since
I came on board this ship.
What are you not telling me?
Cat's out of the bag, Haircut.
You may as well tell her.
Tell me what?
Sweetheart, I don't
wanna rain on your parade,
but you're a, uh...
How would the Professor put it?
An abrasion... No, that's not it, um...
An asphyxiation, hmm...
Aber... Aberration!
You're a Time Aberration.
Ray?
What is a Time Aberration?
Um, I think maybe you
should talk to your dad.
Perhaps we could all just
talk about what went wrong.
- Shh!
- Oh, I know what went wrong.
I listened to him.
If you'd have listened to
me, we would have walked out
of that bank instead
of being chased out.
Either way, we came out empty-handed.
I seem to remember Eobard mentioning
how he was going to punish your failure.
If anyone's a failure, it's you.
You were the one who learned
about Hunter's secret account,
yet seem not to know about a passcode.
Sloppy, Damien.
No wonder they passed
you over for Ra's...
You see, this is where he reminds me
that he was Ra's al Ghul.
Poor Malcolm. Always living in the past.
This is when I remind
you about your future.
Aww, that's right.
I've been there.
I've seen how pathetic you are.
In this future that you're from,
do I at least have two hands?
Either way, I intend to change
my future, but look at you now.
You're pathetic. I don't even know
why Thawne recruited
you in the first place.
We could argue all night, Damien,
but I don't want to bore our guest here
with your impotent
insults and recriminations.
What are you suggesting?
Do you recall how we resolved
disputes within the League?
Mm-hmm.
Now...
I suggest you choose a blade
that matches that sharp tongue of yours.
Excuse me for a second.
Gladly.
You did it, my darling!
You created an interface
between a mystical relic
from the first century and
a 22nd century supercomputer.
Only a Stein could be so brilliant!
What is a Time Aberration?
I'm sorry, what?
You heard me, Dad.
An Aberration... Is
an unnatural alteration
of history as a result of time travel.
Dad? Am I...
Am I an Aberration?
That word could never
describe who you are
or how much you mean to me.
- So it's true?
- Please let me explain.
That's why you were acting so weird
when you visited Central
City the first time.
The reason you were
treating me like a stranger...
Was because you didn't
even exist the last time
I boarded this ship
and... And left 2016.
But now you do exist and
that's all that matters.
How could this be happening?
But it's... it's... It's
really quite simple.
You see, I interacted with
my younger self back in 1987.
And who then interacted with
your mother's former self.
And, and...
When two former selves
love each other...
Okay, Dad. We've already
had the birds and bees talk.
I was ten. Or did we?
That's a very interesting point.
I... I mean, who is to say
which of our realities is real
and which one is aberrant?
It's really a matter of perspective.
Actually, it's quite fascinating.
This is not fascinating, Dad!
This is a nightmare.
Oh, Lily, I'm so sorry.
This is not how I
wanted you to find out.
No. No, I get it.
You didn't want kids
when you first came
on board this timeship.
And now you have me.
You just reminded me of something.
Which is?
How much I've missed this.
Okay, stop, stop! Time out, time out!
Can't you see that this
is what your boss wants?
For his underlings to be
at one another's throats.
Like, literally.
He is not our boss.
Did he call us underlings?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Uh... Henchmen.
Try again.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What if he's right?
You actually care
what this pudding-brained
hippie has to say?
It's just like the movie
“The Good, the Bad, and the Ugly”
Three bad guys.
No one knows who to trust.
So they all end up
screwing each other over.
It's an interesting theory.
Which one are we?
The point is that neither
of you are Clint Eastwood
and so neither of you end
up going home with the gold.
We're not after the gold.
Yeah, I know, I know.
I know what you're after.
You... You wanna change your past.
And you... You wanna change your future.
And, uh, the fast guy is the only one
who could make those
two things, uh, happen.
I told you.
Thawne doesn't treat us as equals.
Even the hippie knows it.
And he also knows that
the only way to stop Thawne
from screwing us over is
for us to work together.
Two former members of
the League of Assassins
versus a speedster.
I am liking those odds.
Dude, what is going on with you?
What do you mean?
And don't call me dude.
I've gotten used to
sharing a brain with you.
But, this, whatever this is.
This is something new.
Just enjoying a cup of Earl Grey.
Is that whiskey?
Of course it's not whiskey.
It's brandy. What do you
take me for, a sailor?
Okay. Let's start this over, hmm?
Come on.
Fine.
I made a terrible mistake.
I should never have brought
Lily on board this ship.
She found out.
She knows she's an Aberration.
Mr. Rory spilled the
beans, as predicted.
So what you gonna do?
What can I do?
Just tell her how you feel.
She knows how I feel.
It goes without saying.
Yeah, for us, it does.
We have a psychic
connection, but for her?
She just hears whatever comes
out of that big brain of yours.
Just tell her you love her.
That's what dads do.
Clearly, you never met my father.
You know, the...
The reason Clarissa and I
chose not to have children
the first time around was because...
I feared that history
would repeat itself,
that I would be
the kind of father that he was.
We're legends, Grey.
Changing history is what we do.
Why would a speedster
need to change reality?
Ohh. How many times are
you gonna ask that question?
Until we have an answer.
She's right. Speedsters can time travel.
So what's stopping him
from changing history
even without the Spear?
Unless he doesn't exist.
Okay, so what, he's a ghost?
What if he's a Temporal Aberration?
- Just like...
- Excuse me.
Have any of you seen my daughter?
- One second, Professor.
- I'm sorry!
This is quite urgent.
Look, what if instead of
creating a person
like you did with Lily,
our mystery speedster
erased himself from history?
Why would he want to do that?
I don't know, but it would explain
why we don't have any
evidence of his existence.
Okay, so, we just need to
ID someone who doesn't exist?
Eobard Thawne.
Um, is... Is he okay?
I'm fine. Eobard Thawne is a name.
The name of a speedster who...
Who what?
Thawne was erased from
existence when his progenitor,
Eddie Thawne, committed
suicide in order to stop him.
Which would explain why
the Time Masters didn't
have a file on him.
But if Thawne doesn't exist, then how?
He was protected from
his ancestor's death
because he was a member
of the Speed Force.
It's a little complicated.
A little?
Oh, and for the record,
this is how I wanted to approach
things in the first place.
Only because you enjoy
killing a lot of people.
As if you don't.
Hmm.
All right, that's pretty
impressive, Malcolm.
But how did you get Hunter's passcode?
It's not Hunter's.
It's the bank manager's
security override code.
It only cost him three fingers.
Uh, yes!
Ow!
Oh, God.
Going somewhere?
No.
Yes.
What do you expect me to do?
Your partners just left
me here all tied up.
Where are they?
They... told me...
Not to tell you.
The bank. They're...
They're at the bank.
Look, you could help yourself
to... to whatever is in that
safe deposit box, but please...
Please, just... Just let me go, man.
Let me go.
Does this look like a spear to you?
It most certainly does not.
It's a mnemonic archive.
I'm sorry, are we supposed
to know what that means?
Since it won't be
invented for a century, no.
This device is designed
to store memories.
Rip Hunter's, I'd assume.
Guys, I think I just figured it out.
Why a seemingly invincible speedster
would need to take on partners.
By all means, Dr. Heywood,
please enlighten us.
Okay. What if Thawne
isn't just chasing us?
What if he's running from something?
But running from what?
Time.
Time takes time to harden.
And if Thawne ceased to exist the moment
his great-great-whatever
killed himself,
then, maybe, he has to keep moving
in order for his own nonexistence
not to catch up with him. Poo!
That doesn't even begin
to make any kind of sense.
I don't know, it could work.
Professor, what do you think?
Per the scientific method,
there's only one way to prove it.
You'd have to trap Thawne in one
place and then see what happens.
What do you think you're doing?
Renegotiating the
terms of our partnership.
And it is going to be a partnership.
We need a bit more of a guarantee
that you're going to uphold
your end of our bargain.
I'll guarantee you one thing.
If you don't open that door,
I'll kill you.
Yes, but I'm the only one
who knows the code to open it.
Perhaps you can persuade
our friend to cooperate?
Me? No.
I'd rather see how this plays out.
Aww.
It seems you two have
formed an alliance.
There's just one problem.
That you're the only
one who could give us
what we want... Yes, we know.
You're always so quick to remind us
how much we need you, Eobard.
But, clearly, you need us.
You could have gotten in
this vault all by yourself.
Why didn't you?
And for that matter...
why would a man who
can travel through time
always be in such a hurry?
We don't have time for this.
Oh, I've got all the time in the world.
Okay!
Okay, you two have made your point.
I need you as much as
you need me, all right.
But if you do not open that door,
he is going to kill us.
He is coming for me!
Who's coming for you?
It's not a who. It's a... it's a...
A what? A thing.
What thing?
Can you be a little more specific?
My ancestor killed himself in an effort
to erase my very existence.
Well, you look pretty spry despite it.
The Flash pulled me from the timeline.
He held me captive for months
and when I finally got loose,
I found myself... pursued by something.
I-I thought it was a time wraith,
the monsters that hunt
speedsters who mess with time.
But, whatever is hunting me is...
far worse than a time wraith.
It can sense the Speed Force.
And it's trying to kill me.
Interestin... so that's why
you keep running out on us.
Huh. So you're kinda
like a shark who'll die
if you stay in one place.
We are all going to die if you don't...
It's too late.
It's here.
Ah, well, the good
news is you two finally
got what you wanted, you managed
to balance our partnership.
We're now all equally dead.
Oh, I wouldn't worry about that.
This isn't the first scary speedster
that we had to put in his place.
We're gonna get you out
of this bank vault, Eobard.
But on one condition.
You stop treating us like lackeys.
You think you can stop that?
Good luck!
Was that a yes?
- Yes.
- Great!
Let's go to work.
Right, so, you say this thing
is attracted to the Speed Force?
What if you don't use it?
What are you suggesting?
That you stop running.
It knows I'm here.
Good.
Because we've only got one shot at this.
Remember, as long as you stay still,
he can't sense you.
Easy, Eobard.
Easy.
It won't stay trapped for long.
We have to go.
We?
We...
Partners.
Better.
Gideon, can you please take
the ship back to Central City?
If your goal is to return to 2017,
I'm afraid your father has instructed me
not to permit you to leave the ship.
Well, considering he never
wanted to be my father,
that should draw his parental dictates
into question, wouldn't it?
You share my fondness for erudition.
You truly are my daughter.
Well, I am sorry about that.
No, I'm... I'm the one who's sorry.
For what?
It's not your fault I'm a mistake.
Uh, I've made many mistakes
in my life, Lily, but you...
most certainly are not one of them.
The apology that I owe
you is for not telling you
about the unique circumstances
of your conception.
You didn't want me to
know that you didn't want me.
No, you're right, I...
I didn't want children.
But if there's one thing my travels
aboard the Waverider have taught me,
it's that time often doesn't
provide us with what we want.
But it... it's quite adept
at giving us what we need.
And I... I nel ed you...
in my life...
In ways that I... I could
never even dare to imagine.
I just don't want there to
be any more secrets between us.
Well, in that spirit, I
suppose I should tell you
that I am one half of a
nuclear powered superhero
called Firestorm.
So not funny, Dad.
Anyway, as fun as this was,
I probably should be getting home.
You're sure you can't stay?
I... I would. I just, um...
I'm working on a series
of synthetic proteins
that are not gonna
fold themselves, so...
So then, I guess this is good-bye.
Good luck folding those proteins.
Good luck rescuing your friend, Rip.
Hm.
Bye, Dad.
Feel no pressure to tell
us what all this techno-crap
is about.
We're sure we can
figure it out ourselves.
This, uh, techno-crap,
as you so eloquently put it,
is Captain Hunter's memories.
Including the locations
of the other pieces
of the Spear, I hope.
That is my working assumption, yes.
All we have to do now
is upload his memories
to his cerebral cortex.
And that's not happening now because?
Well, we would hardly be doing
Captain Hunter any favors
if we just restored the memories
without taking the liberty
to address some of his shortcomings.
What, like, stopping him biting his nails?
Not exactly.
Can I help you with something, soldier?
No, General Washington, I'm fine.
You, on the other hand...
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --