Seriously, you idiots haven't
figured this out by now?
It all started when we blew up
the time pigs,
the Time Masters.
Now, history is all screwed up.
But it's up to us
to unscrew it up.
But half the time,
we screw things up even worse.
So don't call us heroes.
We're something else.
We're Legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
You're my grandfather.
You are more than that.
- You're a hero to me.
- My quarters. Tonight.
I'll give you something else
to think about.
- You can't date Amaya.
- She has a destiny.
And so do her descendants.
Have either of you gentlemen
heard of the Spear of Destiny?
The Spear can alter reality itself.
- Who's coming for you?
- It's not a who, it's a what.
- And it's trying to kill me.
- He has to keep moving
in order for his own non-existence
not to catch up to him.
Captain Hunter
is the only one who can tell us
where Commander Steel
and the final piece of the Spear is.
- Where am I?
- You're home.
So, I've been told you were bumped up
to the prime crew for "Apollo 13".
Yeah, man.
We'll see about that.
Welcome to Manhattan, 1965.
I have been dropped off
behind enemy lines
and cities all over the world.
Never been dropped off
in the future.
Now you have to disappear,
start a whole new life.
The Spear of Destiny
must be protected at all costs.
Roger that, sir.
I know this mission won't be easy,
Commander Heywood.
For me or for Bettie?
She'll think I died in Leipzig.
Little Hank is barely a month old.
Your family's sacrifice
might just save the world.
Give those to my wife and son.
Godspeed, Henry.
- I don't see him.
- That is odd.
I dropped him off right here
a moment ago.
Where could he have gone?
Henry!
Oh, I'm sorry. My mistake.
Where is he?
We used to call Henry
"the Chameleon."
He speaks seven languages
like a local and he's a master
in the art of camouflage
and concealment.
If you told him to disappear,
that's exactly what he did.
Don't worry, If it's hard for us
to find your grandfather,
it's hard for the Legion.
1965 was a bust.
Oh, sorry, buddy.
It's all right, Rip said
he dropped my Grandfather off
in 1965 New York and told him
to assume a new identity.
Well, he'd need to find work.
Why?
Henry was a military man.
He wouldn't have become
an accountant.
He would have wanted a job
that still offered adventure,
and yet was still
somehow patriotic.
FBI? CIA?
He was a fighter pilot before
he was recruited by the JSA.
In the '60s, the fledgling
National Aeronautics
and Space Administration
used to call upon
test pilots to apply
to be astronauts.
Exactly, what could be
more patriotic, more adventurous
than exploring space?
Nice, Gideon,
pull up anything you can.
Press clippings, newspaper articles,
re: NASA circa 1965.
Certainly, Captain.
Okay, okay, okay.
Come on, come on.
Wait, wait, stop, stop.
Right there.
I'd recognize that Heywood
jawline anywhere.
April 13th, 1970.
"Mission Control works
to save 'Apollo 13.'"
Come on, could your grandfather
get any cooler?
I think I may have found a way
to track Commander Heywood.
Don't worry, Mr. Hunter.
We've already found him.
- You did?
- We're headed to Houston, 1970.
Elvis at the Astrodome.
And then we're going
to rescue my grandfather.
Then Elvis.
We still need to figure out a way
of contacting Commander Heywood
without arousing suspicion.
To that end, I suggest that we...
It's simple.
We infiltrate NASA.
Today, NASA Flight Controllers
are monitoring "Apollo 13",
NASA'S seventh manned mission
to the Moon.
We need to figure out a way
to get into Mission Control.
I don't think that's included
in the tour.
Commander Heywood is not
at Mission Control.
- How do you know that?
- Because I'm looking right at him.
That's the Flight Director of NASA.
They're probably debating
on how to talk to the press
about the oxygen tank explosion
on "Apollo 13".
Henry.
Great to see you.
You son of a wench.
Sorry, folks.
He doesn't have
the right credentials.
We take press access
very seriously around here.
Surprise!
We're back.
Why are you doing this, Henry?
I was never supposed
to see him again.
So you punched him?
That's between him and me.
What brings you to 1970?
Oh, well, I supposed Nate
should probably tell you.
Nathaniel's here too?
Sir?
They say they know you.
You could say that.
Henry.
Amaya.
As I live and breathe.
It's good to see you again, son.
Come here, man.
I thought I'd never see you again.
Look at you. You still got it.
Is that Rip?
Get him out of there!
As soon as one of you explains
what in tarnation is going on.
We're here for your fragment
of the Spear of Destiny.
See, there's a Legion of villains
who are hunting anyone
who is trying to protect it.
We have Stargirl's fragment.
But... Mid-Nite died trying
to protect his.
I appreciate your concern...
but I hid my piece of the Spear
somewhere safe.
Believe me,
there's no place on Earth
safe from these guys.
Exactly.
You old fox you.
You want to clue us in?
He hid the Spear in the flag
Neil Armstrong planted on the moon.
Well, that is pretty ingenious.
The whole reason I worked
my way up through NASA
was to make sure that my piece
of the Spear remains safe.
Speaking of, I really should be
getting back to Mission Control.
Yeah, I guess
you gotta figure out how to save
the "Apollo 13" astronauts.
What are you talking about?
The mission is textbook.
Didn't an oxygen tank explode
and the moon landing get aborted?
No, everything is going great
up there.
Unless...
history's changed.
Houston, we are about to enter
the dark side of the moon.
Loss of signal in 30 seconds.
Roger that, "Odyssey".
See you in 28 minutes.
Happy sailing.
Over and out.
Time to sit back
and enjoy the view, fellas.
Sorry, fellas.
Change of plans.
We have to intercept "Apollo 13"
before it lands on the Moon.
Where's Commander Heywood?
He and I need to have a little chat.
He's introducing the rest of the team
to the Flight Director.
Interesting. Why?
Because we need somebody
monitoring on the ground.
These are flight controllers?
Yes. They're with the...
British Space Program.
They're here to study our procedures.
What's your area of expertise?
I'm a Booster Systems Engineer.
They call me "the Rocket Man".
And him?
He's a man of few words,
but makes up for it with...
personality.
All right. Fine.
But if any of you Brits
get in the way of my controllers
or jeopardize the safe return
of our astronauts,
you'll answer to me.
Of course.
- All right. Good luck, fellas.
- You're not sticking around?
We might need you to run
a little more interference for us.
No can do.
I gave up my life for that Spear
and I'll be damned
if I let anyone steal it now.
I'm going with my grandson to space.
Would you look at that?
Outer space.
Never gets old.
Martin, how much longer
before "Apollo 13"
should reestablish radio contact?
17 minutes.
All right, we got 17 minutes
to figure out what's going on
before the whole world is watching.
Yeah, you're not wrong there.
Gideon, pull up Apollo 13's
original flight pattern.
We need to find it first.
Henry. Perhaps now would be
a good time to have a chat?
Actually, Captain Hunter,
I don't feel much like talking.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
You know, in 2017,
men share their feelings.
I'm just saying.
My wife has spent the past 14 years
raising our son by herself.
And it is Captain Hunter's fault.
The man has a wife and son
and still he asked me
to abandon mine.
He doesn't have a family.
I mean, he did.
It's just...
they were killed.
I... I didn't know.
You know, I often wonder
what Hank would have been like
if you hadn't left.
Yeah, I call my dad Hank.
We don't have the best relationship.
But I don't need to tell you
all that.
I'm sorry, Nathaniel.
This is all my fault.
But once this is over,
I'm getting Captain Hunter
to take me back to 1956...
to the day
I abandoned Bettie and Hank.
Wait, I was...
I was just talking hypothetically.
Why?
I mean, this is a timeship, isn't it?
It'll be like I never left my wife
and son.
Think of all the heartbreak
I could save them.
Huh, I never thought of it that way.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
But we found "Apollo 13".
Oh, this isn't right.
The spacecraft shouldn't be
in this position.
Can the astronauts see us?
No, no, no. We're cloaked.
- What's our plan?
- Well, I thought that we...
All right. I've got Ray suiting up.
He's gonna fly over there,
shrink down
and let us know what's
going on inside.
I'm entering the Command Module.
I see Lovell and Haise,
but they're unconscious.
What about Jack?
Dr. Palmer?
Thawne's here.
I'm gonna follow him
into the Lunar Module.
He's going to land on the moon.
Well, I'll stop him.
Who's Thawne? Where is Swigert?
Ray, whatever you do,
just don't let Thawne see you.
Yeah, about that...
Well, what do we have here?
Looks like a stowaway.
What's happening?
NASA expects radio contact
in three minutes!
We ran into a problem.
If we come back online,
you're gonna have to cut the feed.
Yeah, I'm on it.
He doesn't have superspeed
without gravity.
Newsflash, Raymond.
I don't need superspeed
to kick your ass.
What's the red button?
It separates the LEM
from the Command Module.
That's not good.
Dr. Palmer, you're gonna have
to fly the LEM.
Houston, we have a problem.
Yeah, tell me something I don't know.
Jefferson, the entire world
is about to listen to Raymond
crash on the moon.
Wait.
Haircut's on the moon.
Guys, I'm gonna need more time.
I need you to create a distraction.
Day-o!
Day-ay-ay-o!
Daylight come
and me wan' go home
Day, me say day, me say day
Me say day, me say day,
me say
Day-ay-ay-o
Everybody.
Daylight come
and me wan' go home
Work all night for a drink a'rum
Daylight come
and me wan' go home
Stack the banana
till the morning come
Daylight come
and me wan' go home
Come, Mr. Tally Mon,
tally me banana
Daylight come...
Lift six foot, seven foot,
eight foot, bunch!
What the hell are you two playing at?
Okay. I got it. I cut the feed.
Oh, it's a...
It's a British tradition, sir.
Flight, I had radio contact
for a second
then I lost it again.
- Nice voice, Professor.
- Thank you very much.
- Guidance?
- It was the darnedest thing.
The LEM appeared for a second.
But it looked like it was about
to crash on the lunar surface.
Where the hell
is the Command Module?
It's spinning off course.
Ray.
Are you all right?
I'm alive at least.
I was able to salvage the descent.
But it burned up too much fuel.
There is no way the LEM
will launch into space.
What about your suit?
My thrusters were damaged
in the fight.
You guys are gonna have
to pick me up.
NASA must be going berserk
right now.
Fred and Jim...
Don't worry, we're gonna get
"Apollo 13" home in one piece.
Gideon, plot a course
for the Command Module.
Right away, Captain.
- Ray, we'll pick you up later.
- Roger that.
We landed near
the Sea of Tranquility.
So, I'm gonna head out
and retrieve Commander Heywood's
piece of the Spear.
Which is, needless to say,
very exciting.
Good luck, big guy.
What about Mr. Thawne?
He's a little tied up at the moment.
Puns, the lowest form of humor.
Can I talk to you?
About what?
I overheard you and Henry
talking about returning him to 1956.
Okay, look, I know
what you're gonna say...
That you're a historian
as well as a Legend.
You know the consequences
of returning Henry to the timeline.
Yeah, my dad grows up with a father.
Look, my childhood was miserable.
My dad was a cold,
disconnected jackass.
But maybe, just maybe
returning Henry to that time
could change everything.
This is my chance to fix three
generations of Heywood men.
You don't need fixing.
Your childhood made you
into the man that you are...
the person that you are today.
And without that man,
then, well, this ship would
probably still be stuck
at the bottom of the Atlantic Ocean.
That's conjecture.
My grandfather's happiness,
my father's happiness, that's real.
Excuse the interruption.
But you might want to brace
for impact.
Good news,
we found the Command Module.
Bad news, it's heading straight
for a bunch of space rocks.
- The meteoroid belt.
- Don't we have a tractor beam?
Can we pull the Command Module
away from the meteorites?
No, no, the velocity
of the Command Module
would merely bring us closer
to the meteorites.
Which is why I'm swinging
the ship around.
I'm gonna try and stop the trajectory
of the Command Module.
Sara, you need to abort.
We're going to hit the meteoroids.
Better us
than the Command Module.
Can't you at least to try
to destroy the meteoroids
rather than using my ship
as a human shield?
It worked before back in 1942.
You put the Waverider
in front of a nuke
and it absorbed the blast.
At least I had the decency
to time-scatter you all first.
Decency? Did you ask any of us
if we wanted to be time-scattered?
- Sara.
- I was trying to save your lives!
You put me in a time period
where they wanted to hang me
for being a witch!
Sara!
Shield integrity at 63 percent.
34 percent.
Rerouting the reserve power
to the shields.
I'm afraid the Jumpship
has been critically impaired.
Oh, dear.
Our landing gear has...
We're clear.
Waverider crew...
we are now the proud owners
of the last fragment
of the Spear of Destiny.
Copy.
That's all I get is a "copy"?
Guys, I'm standing
on the freaking moon!
Yeah, about that.
The... the Waverider has sustained
major damage, Dr. Palmer.
Same for the Jumpship.
Wait, the Jumpship...
That means...
Unless you can figure out
a way to launch the LEM...
You're stranded on the moon.
And now I know
how Matt Damon felt.
I'm Dr. Raymond Palmer.
Time traveler...
superhero, and most recently,
astronaut.
It's April 13th, 1970, at 2200 hours,
and I am stranded on the moon.
Fuel on the LEM is close to zero.
The food and water provisions
were designed to last days,
not months.
So, yeah.
I'm gonna have to science
the crap out of this.
What are you doing?
I'm filming us for posterity.
In case we don't...
make it back.
I'm not dying on the moon.
Sign... signing off.
Certainly not doing it
in a tin can with the likes of you.
And to that end,
I propose an alliance.
You untie me
and we'll figure out a way
to get ourselves off this rock.
And I'll play nice until
we get back to Earth.
I promise.
Yeah.
Not a chance.
And for your information,
I already have a plan.
All I have to do is transfer
the fuel source from my exo-suit
and power the fuel cells.
Use the dwarf star
to power the LEM.
Yeah, that should work.
Of course, you've taken the gas
spectrometer into account.
Well, unless you adjust
for the relative volatility
of the dwarf star, then the LEM
could explode mid-launch.
I'm a scientist from the future
and I'm here to tell you,
this is two-person patch job.
Look at it this way:
If I'm lying, we're both dead.
We'll be over Ray's launch
position in 18 minutes.
We only get one chance
at this intercept
before the moon's gravity
slingshots us back to Earth.
Henry.
You need to understand
how time travel works.
My grandfather understands it
just fine.
You can't return to 1956.
- Amaya.
- Why?
Every time we change history,
we create what we call an Aberration.
Now, if your son grows up
with you around,
he could become
an entirely different person...
choose a different life.
That, in turn, could change Nathaniel
and the person he becomes.
If he's even born at all.
She doesn't know that.
But it's a possibility?
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because my dad needs you.
And as much as I want
to protect history,
I want to protect our family more.
We both should have learned
by now, the mission comes first.
Thank you for telling me.
I was just trying to protect you.
Nathaniel, changing
your family's history
would have changed you.
And in case I haven't made it clear,
I like who you are.
You and I don't have
a future together.
What do you mean?
When you stowed aboard
the Waverider,
we pulled you from the timeline.
Back in 1942,
you have a destiny waiting for you.
- How do you know all this?
- Ray told me.
He knows your granddaughter.
I don't think
I should be hearing this.
Ask Ray what happens to your village.
Ask him what happens to your daughter
and your granddaughter.
Then tell me...
tell me you'll choose history
over your own family.
That offer to clear the air
still good?
So long as it doesn't involve
punching me in the jaw again.
I'm sorry about that.
After five years, I found myself
blaming you for the choice I made.
Turns out that abandoning
my wife and son,
even to save the world, was...
a mistake.
Oh, it's the great irony
of time travel.
That, despite it, we still find
ourselves living with regret.
One of mine is that I couldn't find
a better way to protect the Spear.
One that would've...
spared you such a personal sacrifice.
When you showed up,
I thought maybe I could go back...
change history.
But what's done is done.
All we can do now is look forward.
Oh, I gotta say, you really
turned this team around.
When I met the Legends in 1942,
they were constantly bickering.
Unable to work together
in any cohesive way.
Actually, I'm not the one
who deserves your praise.
Menial labor without superspeed
is really quite tedious.
Then again, I've missed working
with a fellow scientist.
Cisco and Caitlin and I,
as you know,
worked together
for some time and...
I miss the camaraderie.
Legion of Doom doesn't have
Karaoke Fridays?
I know it's easier for you
to think of me as a monster.
But I've met some
of history's monsters, Raymond.
And believe me...
I'm not one of them.
You killed Barry's mother.
Twice.
Rex Tyler.
Brainwashed Rip
into killing Dr. Mid-Nite.
Time travel has a way
of revealing the truth to you.
And you and I have more
in common than you think.
Pass me the pliers.
We're both scientists.
We're both obsessed
with achieving the impossible.
You dedicated your life to learning
how to shrink yourself down
to the size of an atom
and I spent mine learning
the secrets of the Speed Force.
I became the Atom to help people.
You could use the dwarf star
in your exo-suit
to power an entire city.
But instead,
you chose to become the Atom
because you weren't satisfied
with your small, pathetic life.
There is no shame in wanting
to be great or to reach higher.
To...
walk on the moon.
Is that why you want the Spear?
Reach higher, become greater,
run faster?
No.
I'm after something much more...
elemental.
I want to live.
Surely, you can sympathize.
One minute to the intercept,
Raymond.
Are you ready up there?
Yeah, we're ready.
"We"?
Long story. Let's do this.
Rip, how's our trajectory looking?
Keep her steady.
Martin, are you sure
about these calculations?
I'm piloting manually here.
- Did I or did I not win six Carlins?
- No.
Yes, I did.
20 seconds to intercept.
Jax, be prepared to restore
the feed on my signal.
Ten seconds.
You're just gonna have to trust me.
In three, two, one...
Distance to target, 100m.
And closing fast.
Intercept successful.
You, ma'am, are a steely-eyed
missile man!
I take that as a compliment.
Ray, I'm gonna dock with the LEM.
Be prepared to get your ass
back on the ship.
Copy.
Head up, son.
We got work to do.
I'm sorry, sir,
but they're just... gone.
Tractor beam disengaged.
"Apollo 13" is headed home.
Jax, restore the feed.
Let's get history back on track.
"Odyssey", this is Houston.
Do you read us?
Come in, "Odyssey".
"Odyssey", this is Houston.
Houston, this is "Odyssey",
do you read me?
I repeat, do you read me?
We read you, "Odyssey".
Loud and clear.
You don't seem happy, Professor.
The intercept might have been
a success, but...
the Waverider is on reserve power.
Not to mention the difficulty
of re-entering
the Earth's atmosphere.
What are you saying?
I'm saying that our crew
has an infinitesimal chance
of ever returning home.
By "infinitesimal", I mean...
A snowball's chance in hell?
That would look rosy in comparison.
Welcome aboard.
Relax.
I'm not gonna kill my ride home.
Yeah, we still don't trust you.
Rip Hunter. It's good to see you.
I guess these morons
figured out a way
to restore your original personality.
Enjoy the brig, Eobard.
I've been waiting for this
for a long time.
Sara, you have to power down
every non-essential piece
of hardware on the ship.
Gideon is already shut down.
Waverider is using gravitational
inertia to float back to Earth.
What? I know science.
It isn't enough.
If you want to activate
the heat shields
and survive re-entry, you have
to conserve more power now.
Stein is right. We need to
shut down the water filtration
and the heating systems.
Right, because clean water and heat,
we don't need those to survive.
You got a better idea?
At the moment, no.
Well, bundle up,
'cause it's about to get chilly.
Actually,
if the shields don't work...
atmospheric re-entry will burn us
all to a crisp.
Science.
- You lost, son?
- No, sir.
I won a contest
to see "Apollo 13" land.
I'm Hank.
Hank Heywood.
This place is turning
into a damn circus.
Stein, we're ready for re-entry.
What's the status
of your secondary thrusters?
It's sporadic.
She's still got
a couple pushes left in her.
Just need to point her
in the right direction.
There's been a rather
interesting development
down here on the ground.
Nate, are you there?
Yeah, Mick, what's up?
There's some kid in Mission Control
calling himself Hank Heywood.
That's your son.
I fixed an essay writing
contest so Hank would win.
I should've told you earlier.
I had to meet him.
Well, our guidance system
failed to power back up.
Can we enter the atmosphere
without it?
We need to figure out
a re-entry angle.
If it's too steep,
the ship will burn up.
If it's too shallow, we'll bounce off
the atmosphere
and go into orbit around the sun.
Stein, little help here?
I'm working as fast as I can.
But I need a supercomputer,
which is not readily
available in 1970.
We have a supercomputer.
Gideon is off-line.
I'm not talking about Gideon.
38 degrees.
You don't even know my question.
At what angle do we need to re-enter
the Earth's atmosphere?
38 degrees.
I'm from the 22nd century.
I've learned astro-navigation
in grade school.
38 degrees.
Or don't you trust me?
The re-entry angle
needs to be 38 degrees.
How do you know?
Thawne.
He wants to get back to Earth.
Same as the rest of us.
So that he can kill us when we land.
I'm with Amaya, grudgingly.
I don't trust him.
Agreed.
Professor Stein, does 38 degrees
sound right to you?
It could be,
but without more time I...
I can't be certain.
We haven't gotten any time.
Someone needs to make a decision.
Ms. Lance.
You're the Captain.
Do you trust Thawne about this,
after everything that he's done?
I do.
Then I trust Ray.
Let's go.
Stein, we're a go for re-entry.
If we don't adjust the angle,
we'll burn up.
The thrusters are toast.
In a few seconds,
we're all gonna be toast.
We need to blow the cargo bay door.
- What?
- He's right.
The depressurization
will correct your angle of descent.
The air pressure is too great.
If anyone opens up the door
at mid-descent...
they'll die.
- I'll go.
- No.
I'm Captain. I'll go.
Where is Henry?
I'm in the cargo bay.
It's the only way to right the ship.
Talk me through this.
You have to secure
the inner door first.
Check.
Right, there should be a lever
to your, to your left.
I see it.
Hey. Hey!
Hey, don't! Don't do this.
I am so sorry, Nathaniel.
No, no. You open that door,
the explosive decompression
will suck you out.
If I don't, you will all die.
I can do it. Let me do it.
I have powers now.
No, no.
I won't let you risk your life.
I have fulfilled my duty,
protecting my piece of the Spear.
But I'm just a grunt.
Now it's your turn.
You can figure out a way
to destroy the Spear.
Don't let it ruin
another person's life.
Your son is at Mission Control.
He's there, he's waiting for you.
Come on.
Don't.
Give him a message for me.
Tell him...
I'm sorry for leaving.
Don't. Please don't. Please don't.
It's working.
30 degrees.
36.
38.
Commander Heywood's done it.
We're gonna make it.
Yes, we are.
Nathaniel.
It's a funny thing about Rip Hunter's
anti-speedster weapons:
I invented them.
I knew you'd escape.
You're on the run.
Because you're a time remnant.
You should have died when
Eddie Thawne killed himself.
And now something's chasing you,
trying to correct the Aberration.
One of history's worst monsters.
Speak of the devil.
Well, I guess you won't have time
to search the ship
for the Spear now, will you?
Till we meet again, Raymond.
Re-entry successful.
It's pretty cool, huh?
Got to witness history.
You an astronaut?
No, no, I'm...
I wish I was that brave.
They made it home.
Not all of them.
They're my dad's.
Or they were.
He was gone before I knew him.
I'm sure he was sorry he left.
My dad wasn't really there
for me either.
But I knew he loved me.
He just...
just couldn't show me.
- It's not fair.
- No.
No, it's not.
But if you can accept that...
you'll be a better man for it.
You and your son.
Drinking alone?
Only as metaphor.
You're in here feeling sorry
for yourself?
Oh, no. I've got more than one way
of feeling sorry for myself, surely.
Thanks for backing my play earlier.
I wasn't entirely supportive
on this mission.
Indeed.
Still...
must be hard coming back
to your ship
and finding someone else in charge.
No.
That was the easy part.
The harder adjustment
was seeing that you are
a much better captain
than I ever was.
So that's why you're in here
feeling sorry for yourself?
I'm in here trying
to figure out what my place is
if I'm not this team's captain.
So, you're saying you don't fit in.
You're an outcast.
A misfit.
Let's assume.
Sounds to me like you're a Legend.
I'm sorry, Nathaniel.
This was my fault.
If I hadn't told Henry
that he shouldn't return home...
He would've still thrown
himself off of the ship
to save us.
That's just who he was.
Maybe destiny
has plans for all of us.
Not just me.
Yeah, about that.
I am...
so sorry I said those things.
No one should know too much
about their future.
I'm not afraid of the future.
Whatever is supposed to happen...
it's bigger than just me.
I know this is cheesy...
but...
once you see Earth from outer space,
you realize how small we all are.
In a good way?
Yeah.
In a good way.
Gideon.
I need you to help me
with something.
Of course, Ms. Jiwe.
I need you to show me
the historical record on Zambesi...
starting with my return home.
You're asking for me
to show you your future.
I must counsel you against
doing this.
Please, Gideon.
Hey, Mr. Tally Mon,
tally me banana
Daylight come
and me wan' go home
Come, Mr. Tally Mon,
tally me banana
Daylight come
and me wan' go home
Lift six foot, seven foot,
eight foot, bunch!
Nice voice, Professor.