Grey's hit.
We got to get him out of there!
Where's Barry when you need him?
Just tying up some loose ends.
He's almost at the breach hangar.
If we don't stop him,
he's gonna blow up
our only ticket home.
Not to mention us.
A little help with that, please.
No, no, no, no, no!
Grey! Stay down!
Grey! No!
Grey!
Fall back!
He did it.
- He opened the breach.
- Let's go.
Hey.
Barry, the breach is open.
Where are you?
We got to take him out now.
I have an idea.
Throw another lightning bolt.
- We already tried that.
- Just do it.
Now!
Barry, we need to you to hurry up.
Stein's hurt.
All right, we're on the move.
He's alive,
but his condition is critical.
All right, Gideon will fix him.
No, it's too dangerous to move him.
Not if he's Firestorm.
Yeah.
Grey! Grey.
Grey, come on.
- Thanks for your help.
- We're not done helping yet.
Our enemies are still on your earth,
Ollie.
Don't call me that.
Give it time, I'll get through
that crusty exterior.
- No, you really won't.
- I was talking to you.
- Oh, my God.
- Kara.
What are they doing?
This next sound...
metal through a bone,
that's my favorite.
You should probably close your eyes.
This will all be over in a minute.
What are you waiting for?
- Do it.
- I'm trying.
I'm trying but...
Mitts off, Mengele.
- Ray?
- Hi, how are you?
Oh, I got your S.O.S.
How was the wedding?
All right, don't worry.
The rest of the Legends are here
and we're busting everybody out.
Wait, we need someone
to lock the time vault.
I got it.
You guys get Kara out of here.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
Look, I know I'm late to the party,
but why have Nazi doppelgangers
taken over S.T.A.R. Labs?
They're from Earth-X.
They hate everybody.
They want to steal Kara's heart,
and they have this giant robot.
Oh, I've actually fought one
of those before.
Little known fact the suit
doesn't just shrink...
Ray!
It embiggens.
Attention all prisoners:
Great news.
The cavalry has arrived.
About time.
I knew I could count on you,
Pretty.
Did you bring beers?
Better yet, an army.
Who needs an army
when you got Legends?
We have a problem.
I need you to wake up, Kara.
The General is no longer safe here.
I'm well aware.
Retreat to the troop carrier
and prepare for the invasion.
- Without you?
- I'm staying.
Supergirl is not leaving here alive.
Do not make it personal.
That is not a good idea.
Are you questioning
your Fuhrer's orders?
Of course not.
General.
Stay here. Stay safe.
And I'll be back for you
with her heart.
So this is Earth-1? Cute.
- We need to find Kara.
- Then we need to split up.
- I got Supergirl.
- I got Group B.
- You're late.
- Don't mind him.
He's just pissy
'cause he came out of a steel box.
Actually he's always like this.
What the hell?
- How much further, Ray?
- Waverider's on the roof.
How do you two know each other again?
- We used to date.
That's awkward.
Careful.
Oliver got the girl,
I got a life of adventure
on a time-traveling spaceship.
Step away from her.
There's no way.
My grandparents didn't survive
the Holocaust
so the world could be ruled
by Nazis. So if you want Kara,
you got to go through me.
And even if you do,
you're not gonna win.
'Cause we will not back down.
We will keep fighting.
So get the hell off our earth
while you still can.
As final words go,
those weren't bad.
Lower your weapon.
Or I'll kill her.
This guy's like the Terminator.
Why are you laughing?
I just love a good
pop culture reference
in a moment of crisis.
Also, that!
Let's kick some ass!
Her neck doesn't seem invulnerable
so I will say again.
Lower your weapon.
Don't listen to him. Just shoot her.
No! No.
I can save your wife's life.
There's only one way to save me.
We have friends at S.T.A.R. Labs.
There are ways to do this
without hurting Kara.
He's lying.
Do it for the Fatherland,
just kill her!
I thought that jerk
was supposed to be dead.
- Hey, hey.
- Hi.
- I am so sorry.
- It's okay. It's okay
You're safe. You're safe.
Oh, I shouldn't have said
what I said.
What if it was the last thing
we ever said to each other?
It doesn't matter. Nothing matters
except that I love you.
Okay? I don't need anything else.
I don't need to get married.
I just...
I just want to be with you.
- Okay.
Gideon, fix him!
His pressure's dropping.
We have to stanch the bleeding.
Right away, Dr. Snow.
Jax, relax.
Professor's going to be fine.
He's a tough bastard.
Jackson's hit.
- I can't find an entry wound.
- Look at their vitals.
It must be
because of their connection.
What the hell does that mean?
Even though Jax isn't injured,
their life functions must still
be linked somehow.
- Well, how do we unlink them?
- We can't.
Their connection's the only thing
keeping the professor alive.
Are you okay?
I can't even begin to answer
that right now.
We should be on our honeymoon.
We should be on a beach,
drinking mai tais out of coconut.
Instead we're on this space ship,
looking for our friends'
evil doppelgangers.
- We should have just eloped.
- Yeah.
- Kara?
- Alex?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- I can't believe they almost...
- I know, I know.
- I thought I lost you.
- Me too.
So much for getting away
from it all, huh?
I should have known better
than to think that a wedding
on another Earth is gonna solve
all of our problems.
Yeah, but...
you know, fighting
the evil versions of ourselves
does kind of put those problems
in perspective, doesn't it?
Way to see the silver lining.
Hey there, friend.
No need to numb your feelings
with alcohol.
The ghost is back.
No, not a ghost. I'm Leo.
Leo Snart from Earth-X.
It's okay, buddy.
I know you're hurting over Firestorm.
Get your hand off me.
What is wrong, partner? Talk to me.
You're not my partner.
You're a gangbanger.
I think you mean "doppelganger."
And there was one of you
on my earth, too.
Rest his soul.
Wait. I'm dead on Planet Nazi?
Let me guess.
In a fire?
You just kept going back
into that burning police station
until the last officer
had been rescued.
I died trying to save pigs?
I'm gonna be sick.
How you feeling, Jax?
Oh, don't worry about me.
How's Grey?
I have him sedated. Don't worry.
Gideon and I are doing everything
we can to fix him.
Okay. Good.
Still no improvement?
He's getting worse.
Marty or Jax?
Both.
I just can't believe
there's nothing Gideon can do.
Medically speaking, Professor Stein
shouldn't even be alive right now.
The only thing that kept him
from dying is...
- Jax. Bonding with him.
- Yeah.
Jax is basically functioning
as a human life-support machine,
able to keep the professor alive
but...
only for so long.
Does Jax know?
That he's gonna die too?
I didn't know how to tell him.
It'll be okay.
We got a whole mess
of smart people on this ship.
Somebody's gonna figure out
something.
Okay.
Oh, man. I have just died
and went to geek heaven.
Told you we picked the right guy.
Picked the right guy to do what?
Hunt Nazis.
Meet out resident Earth-X expert,
The Ray.
Well, you can use my real name
Ray Terrill.
Your secret identity is your
first name with the word "the"
- in front of it?
- Yeah.
Why? What's your secret identity?
- Mr. Terrific.
- Really?
That's a little boast-y,
don't you think?
Nah, it's just one
of my favorite wrestlers.
Still... that's... you should
change your name.
- Can we talk about these Nazis?
- They vanished.
Owing to the fact that they
have their own Waverider.
A Nazi Waverider?
Yeah, we had been tracking them
using the radiation
signature given off by Overgirl
- because of her...
- Extreme exposure
to the solar radiation.
Are these readings right?
Yeah, of course they're right. Why?
Well because the trace
radiation readings on here
are slowly approaching
the Chandrasekhar Limit.
- Which means?
- Overgirl isn't just dying...
Yeah, if she doesn't get
Supergirl's heart,
she'll create a supernova
that will destroy...
the entire Midwest.
Jef... Jefferson?
Jefferson.
I need...
I need to tell you something.
Well, talk fast.
Because unless you're sedated,
Gideon can't do her thing,
patch you back up.
Can't you see that...
I'm dying?
What... what are you talking about,
man?
I'm old, Jefferson.
And even if I hadn't been shot,
no one lives forever.
Grey, I don't even want to hear you
talking like that, man.
As long as we're connected,
I'm nothing more than an anchor
around your neck.
Which is why you must help me.
I don't understand. I...
Not Cisco's drug.
Gideon resynthesized the liquid.
She assures me it will free you
from my body's biology.
And it will free you of mine.
I'm the only thing
that's keeping you alive, man.
You're asking me to kill you, Grey.
I'm asking you
to let me die so that you may live.
- Please hand me the vial.
- No.
I know, I know you think
you're strong enough for both of us.
But unless I do this, we'll both die.
- Then we'll both die. I don't...
- No.
You...
You have your whole life
ahead of you.
Grey.
But now it's time
for you to let me go.
- No, I'm not ready for you to go.
- I'm not either.
But when you think about it,
compared to the Cosmos,
one's life is but a blink of an eye.
Really?
You're gonna lecture me
about astrophysics right now?
Grey, please don't do this to me.
I can't do this.
You once told me...
that I was like your father,
and I said
you were my son.
How could a father do anything less?
- Grey.
- Please. Please.
Thank you, Jefferson.
Grey, no, don't.
Stay with me, please.
I'd prefer not to be alone.
Yeah.
Please...
tell Clarissa and Lily
that I love them.
I promise.
Thank you, Jefferson...
for the adventure of a lifetime.
I hope your life is long
and full of love.
Just as mine...
has been.
Grey.
No.
No, no.
Jax.
He did it for me.
Where's Jax?
I'll get it, honey.
Jefferson.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
No, no.
How are you holding up?
I'll cry at the funeral.
Sara.
I'm fine.
We need to gather everyone.
Overgirl's gonna go nuclear,
and the Earth-Xers are gonna
use their Waverider
to threaten Central City
and leverage us
into surrendering Kara.
How do you know that?
It's exactly what I would do.
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
For being so weak.
I've managed to stabilize
her deterioration,
but without a transplant
she'll be dead within an hour.
Quiet!
Now don't you listen to her.
There is more strength in you
than in this entire planet
of lesser humans combined.
Nice outfit.
Yeah, I didn't want to feel left out.
Where are we with locating
the other Waverider?
We got a pretty good idea.
I mean, we've all heard
of the Chandrasekhar Limit,
I assume?
The data indicates it's still
in the vicinity of Central City.
Which also indicates that Overgirl
isn't long for this world.
Which means that this world
Failure's not an option.
Losing is not an option.
We are gonna win.
And we are gonna show these
people that this earth
belongs to us.
Great speech.
Sorry to interrupt, Mr. Queen,
but we're being hailed
by a fellow Timeship.
Put it on.
- What do you want?
- To offer a truce.
In exchange for what?
We will return to our earth
peacefully
if you meet my one demand.
Supergirl comes with us.
Here's another difference
between you and me.
I don't abandon my friends.
All right.
- Everybody ready to go?
- Never been more.
We can't bring Marty back,
but we can protect the city he loved,
and the family he left behind.
For the Professor.
Now let's go kick some ass.
Let them run.
We'll turn this city
into a mausoleum.
Kill them all.
Yes, sir!
Excuse me.
You can't just go around
roasting people.
- Why not?
- You ever heard of due process?
- Rule of law?
- No.
Could use a little help here.
I got you covered.
This is just like Star Raiders
on Atari except it's real.
Cut the chatter, Red 2.
Fly the ship.
- Launching torpedo one.
- You don't have to say it out loud.
Okay, guys, is it just me
or is this not working?
- It's not working.
You need to take down their shields.
Open fire!
Guys, this isn't working.
I think we need a bigger gun.
Way ahead of you.
General, we've got inbound.
- Then fire counter-measures.
- We can't.
It's hovering directly off our bow.
General, would you care
to step outside?
Waiting for some good news here.
I don't have any for you, man.
The only way to take out
their shields is to get
someone onboard that ship.
We're on our way.
We're on the bridge, Felicity.
And we don't know
what we're looking for.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
I'm working on it.
Felicity's got it.
I'm sending you the source code
for their deflector shields.
Yeah, got it.
Manual override protocol.
If I am reading this correctly,
all you need to do now is...
Hit the big, blinking red button.
Got it. Shields are down.
Harry, you think you can
handle this bad boy?
Walk in the park, Kazansky.
- Where are you going?
- Getting our friends off that ship.
Count of 10,
hit them with everything we got.
You got it.
Come on, Ramon.
Nailed it!
Go on! End it.
End it!
What's stopping you?
Oh, I forgot.
Barry Allen is above killing.
Isn't that right?
Get out of here.
I wonder what face
I'll be wearing next time we meet.
Flash.
Can't wait.
I'm detecting dangerously
high radiation levels.
Disembodied computer voice
lady's right.
Supergirl-X is about to go
super-nova.
Supergirl, your doppelganger's about
to have a meltdown.
- What do I do?
- You need to fly her up.
Up. And away.
Now.
No!
I'm gonna kill you.
Wha... what?
How did you?
I figured it'd take the man
of steel to catch the girl of steel.
That and, you know,
a tremendous amount of help.
Thank you both.
This world owes you a lot.
Well, it's my world too so...
Punching out Nazis
is kind of our thing.
Well, if you ever need us to do
any punching over on Earth-X
- just let us know.
- Will do.
- Take care, Barry.
- Take care, Ray.
- Barry, I need a hug.
- Okay.
- Be good, Leo.
- Always.
I'm gonna get ready.
- You got this?
- Yeah.
All right, fellas.
You ready to go home?
Sure. So how does this thing work?
It's a very complex two-part process.
One, I open a breach. Two...
You walk through it.
Cool.
Leo?
I think I'm gonna stick
around here for a little while.
I...
I won't stay here forever.
I will come home to you.
Promise.
Okay.
- I love you.
Clarissa asked me
to say a few words.
But, as you all know,
it was Grey... Martin
who was the wordy one.
But...
I got used to hearing
his voice inside my head.
And even now,
I can still hear him.
'Cause even though he's gone,
he's still a part of me.
He's still a part of all of us.
He was the best man
right until the end.
The best teacher.
Friend.
Husband.
Father.
Clarissa...
I'm so, so sorry.
I couldn't save him. I...
All he wanted was to come home.
To you, and you, and Ronnie.
To his family.
Oh, Jefferson.
You were his family too.
I just...
I don't know how to do any
of this without him.
Then, don't.
You said it yourself.
He's still part of you.
That's it, big guy. Let it out.
Allergies.
Good-bye, my love.
Thank you for believing in me.
Tell Ronnie I miss him.
Thank you for bringing me home
to her.
So, you're going to another earth,
and I'm going to another time.
Yeah, that's kind of
how we roll, huh?
Totally normal.
- Should we...
- It's... it's a hug thing, okay.
- Okay.
Thank you for putting things
in perspective for me.
Does that mean you're gonna
take my advice on Maggie?
Yes, I'm gonna trust my instincts.
I mean, there's got to be
somebody else out there for me.
- Right?
- For sure.
Just like there's somebody
else out there for you.
And for more than just a night.
That's funny.
- That was my takeaway too.
- Boss.
Ship's ready.
Catch you on the other side.
- You hit that?
- Shut up.
You ready?
Oh, so, so ready, yeah.
Thank you guys for everything.
And thanks for inviting us
to your wedding.
Sorry it didn't turn out
the way you wanted it to.
- Well, at least it was memorable.
- Yes.
Well, we'll be back out
for the do-over.
Iris and I talked about it and...
And yeah, we're just gonna
get ourselves a justice of the peace
and get it done, quick and simple.
Fewer Nazis that way.
Well, take care, guys.
- Oh.
- Oh, that's good. That's...
Yeah, bring it in.
All right.
- Let's go.
You guys really not going to have
a wedding now after all that?
- Now she's pro-wedding.
- Hey.
Well... I mean, we've already
had the ceremony.
So all we need to do now
is exchange vows and rings.
Hey, can't a mayor marry people?
Very flattered, but I think
that we would have to be
within the limits of Star City
for it to be official.
And we definitely want it
to be official.
Well, if you want it to be personal,
I think we know a guy who's ordained.
It's a good thing I didn't vomit,
right?
- Yeah.
Are you okay?
- A little warning next time?
- Sorry.
What's up?
You got ordained to marry
your brother and Carly, right?
Yeah.
We were hoping that you could give us
the same treatment.
Wow, really? I'm honored.
- Yeah?
- I am.
All right. Well, let's do it.
Okay, that's great.
I guess that makes you
the best man
and you the maid-of-honor.
- "Honored" is correct.
- All right.
- Let's get into position.
- Oh, my goodness.
- You're here.
- Okay.
- You're there, you're there.
- Oh, I see.
Did you guys write vows
or you just want the boilerplate?
Yes, I... wrote mine.
I tried to write mine.
But then I realized
that I didn't need to.
My entire life has been marked
by two things.
The first one is change.
From when I was a kid
to when I was an adult,
things were always changing.
But no matter
how different things became
or what new challenges
I had to face,
I always had the other thing
that my life was marked by.
And that's you.
You've always been there.
As a friend, as a partner,
as the love of my life.
You're my home, Iris.
And that's one thing
that will never change.
That was really nice.
When I was nine years old
I wanted to be a ballerina.
Remember?
Even though
I was not a very good dancer.
And the day of the recital I froze.
I couldn't move, and I wanted to die.
And then I looked in the audience
and I saw you.
And you got up
and you climbed onto stage
and you did
that whole routine with me.
And we killed it.
I mean...
We brought the house down.
And from that moment, I knew that...
With you by my side,
anything was possible.
The Flash may be the city's hero,
but you, Barry Allen,
you're my hero.
And I am happy...
excited...
and honored to be your wife.
Wonderful.
Well then, I pronounce you both...
Wait! Wait.
Wait, just one second.
If you guys don't mind...
I mean if you don't mind,
really if you don't mind,
but would you marry us too?
Will you marry me?
I thought...
I mean, I thought you didn't
believe in marriage.
No, but I believe in you, and...
I believe that no matter
what life throws at us,
our love can conquer it,
married, unmarried.
I love you.
My greatest fear...
My greatest fear in life
is losing you.
- I...
- Yes.
Okay.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
I do.
John, what do you say?
You kidding me, Oliver?
I'm the guy for the past six years
that's been trying to keep
you two together.
It's only fitting that I marry you.
Okay. Vows?
- No.
I mean, we can't do better than them.
Definitely not.
We kind of did those fake vows
when we had that fake wedding
with that psychopath
serial-killer archer lady.
I remember saying something
along the lines of...
You're the very best part of me.
Felicity, I'm a better human being...
Just because I've loved you.
Well, since we don't have
any rings just yet.
I'll skip right to the part
where I say this,
Oliver Jonas Queen,
Felicity Megan Smoak,
Bartholomew Henry Allen,
and Iris Ann West...
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
Please, kiss your brides.