- Sales for the first
generation of Ava clones
have been through the roof
as predicted.
- My dream of an Ava
in every home and business
has become a reality.
- Wonderful.
Congratulations, sir.
♪
Uh, sir...
I was going to wait until
after the investment meeting
to mention this.
But I think it's time
you told me
about this mystery project
you've been working on.
It's just that you've
diverted billions into it,
and I really feel like
it's time
I knew what the project
was all about.
- Where do you think
I'm taking you?
Ta-da!
It's called a Waverider.
- Waverider?
Oh, because it's shaped
like a boat,
like it rides on the waves.
- No, though it can
go underwater.
But never mind that,
Waverider is what it's called
in the futuristic blueprints
I was given.
It's a time ship.
- Hmm.
Waverider.
Are you married to that name,
or can we still pitch on it?
- Welcome to the bridge,
the nerve center
of the entire ship.
- Hmm, not the most efficient
use of space, though.
Maybe it could double
as a conference room.
- And now it's time for you
to see an old friend.
Gideon, time to wake up.
There you are.
- My transfer
to the ship's mainframe
appears to be a success.
- You remember Gideon?
- Oh, yes. Her.
- Welcome to your new home,
Gideon.
So much more space to roam
than that tiny hard drive
you were in.
Oh, take a couple laps around,
stretch your legs.
You have vantage points
all over the ship.
♪
- You followed my
exact specifications,
but I don't have any
visual access in section A2.
- Well, section A2 is
the only bathroom on the ship.
Can't have you
spying on me in there.
A man needs his privacy.
- Yes.
Sir, as impressive
as this ship is,
how does it relate
to the Ava Corp mission
of improving people's lives
through clone technology
exactly?
- Well, I'm simply expanding
our mission
by adding time travel
to the mix.
But the true perk of this ship
is to finally get revenge
on those time travelers
who abducted me,
used me for my genius,
and then messed with my mind.
- May I remind you that a
Time Master's number one duty
is to protect the timeline
from any
and all threats
to its integrity?
- Yes, yes, Gideon,
that's a given,
considering the job title--
Time Master.
- And before we start,
you must take
the Time Master's oath.
- I swear to protect and defend
the integrity of the timeline
with all my ability
until the end of my days.
- Congratulations. You are now
Time Master of this Waverider.
- Great.
Let's set sail
on our maiden voyage
and protect the timeline
from those damn Legends.
♪
The machine is ruined,
wrecked, absolutely kaput,
and all because of you lot!
- Okay, hold on,
how is it our fault
we didn't land in Tahiti?
- Because it wasn't designed
to take all you people.
The excess weight
threw it all off, man.
- Okay, so I'm guessing we have
no idea what year we're in?
- The chrono-gauge
and the ignition coil
are both sequenced
to the directional compass,
which was damaged
in the landing.
So no, I don't think so.
- Well, that doesn't sound
too good,
but hey, who needs
a chrono-gauge
when you have
two ex-Time Bureau agents
with extensive
historical knowledge, Gary?
- That's right, Ava.
And, uh,
based on the local flora,
there's a chance
we're in the prehistoric era.
Give or take
a few thousand years.
Maybe we'll see dinosaurs.
- You'd better hope
we don't see a dinosaur, Gary.
- Okay, so it looks like we're
making this prehistoric forest
home for a while.
So let's get comfortable, gang.
- Guys, come on.
This team has been stranded
more times than I can count
and in way worse places
than this.
- She's right.
And I know nothing
has gone our way
since we left Odessa, but...
They're gonna get better.
- Yeah.
- Okay? All right.
So you are the only one
that can fix this time machine.
If you can repair
that directional compass,
are we back in business?
- It would be a difficult task
even if we did have
the proper tools.
- I can help.
- Me too.
- You got two techies
at your disposal, my man.
- Just some peace to be able
to get on with my work
is all I ask.
You know, I will venture off
and maybe find some lodestone
or some other magnetic material
which conducts electricity
and then I can fix the compass.
- Hey, maybe you and B
should go with Dr. Cranky.
We'll set up camp here.
- Mm-hmm. All over it.
- Hey, look, I know we didn't
really get a chance
to talk about
the whole moving in thing.
- No, it's totally cool.
As usual,
we have bigger fish to fry.
- I know, but, you know,
moving into a spiritual realm,
that's--that's a lot to--
to take in.
I just wanna make sure
you're not freaking out.
- Freaking--me?
No, I'm super chill.
I am, however,
concerned about our captains.
- Oh, yeah.
Well, good luck with that. Bye.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Miss you.
- Bye.
- Psst. Hey, you two.
Come here, shut up.
Do either one of you know
how to read lips?
- Who needs to read lips
when Spooner can read minds?
- Mm.
♪
Ooh.
I'm getting some major
anxiety vibes
from Sara right now.
- Yeah.
And I don't need superpowers
to see that Ava is cracking.
They're just stressing
each other out at this point.
- Okay, so let's separate them
so they each
don't have a complete
and total meltdown, okay?
- Hey there, jefa.
How about we hunt down
some dinner?
- Yeah, let's go
stab something.
- Want to go for a hike?
We could get some firewood.
- Yeah.
I would love a multitask.
- Great.
♪
- So...
- Oh, Gary.
- You and Zari.
Saw you talking.
And?
- She asked me to move in
with her in the totem.
- Oh, that's great!
That's not--not great?
Sorry, the more handsome
the face, the harder it is
for me to get a read.
- All right, just back up.
It's just,
I haven't spent that much
time in the totem,
and she sprung it on me
before we time jumped here.
So I really haven't had
a chance to process it.
- Well, Nate, the totem
seems quite small.
How do you get inside?
Are you and Zari gonna live
in a house together?
Will there be pie? 'Cause I
really like strawberry rhubarb.
- I love strawberry rhubarb.
- We need to focus
on today's problems, okay?
How about you guys forage
for some food?
Leaves, nuts, berries,
anything we can eat.
Okay? Go.
- Okay.
- Go.
- You sure you don't want me
to stick around,
be your sounding board?
We can--
- Gary?
- Hmm?
- You will not be
my sounding board today.
Okay? Thank you.
- Okay.
- Go on.
Well, at least
these two ding-dongs
can't screw anything up here
that'll attract
the evil Waverider.
♪
- Check out that view
of the Temporal Zone.
Worth a million bucks, huh?
- Mm. Considering this ship
cost many thousand times more,
I'm not sure how the board's
gonna feel
about your investment, sir.
- There's one thing you just
can't put a price on,
Assistant Ava.
- Hmm?
- Revenge.
- Ah.
- Captain, we're getting an
alert of several anachronisms
in 1925, Odessa, Texas.
- Hmm. "Captain." I like that.
Odessa. Wait a second. Texas.
That's where
the Legends took me.
Gideon, you found them.
Engage weapons systems.
I'm gonna bomb the
living daylights out of them.
- I am advising against
this course of action.
- How else am I supposed
to wipe them
off the face of the Earth?
- Eliminating the Legends
in this blunt manner
will cause excessive
collateral damage.
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Your warning is duly noted.
- Yes!
Those bastards finally
got what they deserved.
- That was a lot easier
than I expected.
Can we please go home now, sir?
- No, the captain's impulsive
and violent actions
guarantee ripple effects
in the timeline
that we will have to clean up.
More precise measures
must be taken
when dealing with threats
moving forward.
- Trust me,
this was the only way
to deal with those Legends.
And if any ripples arise,
we'll just use
our brand-new time ship
to smooth them out.
♪
- Hey, buddy. Got your coat.
You okay?
- Listen,
we don't really have time
for a rest stop.
We need to find the materials
you need
to fix your time machine, yeah?
- You really don't
understand, do you?
I just told you lot
what you wanted to hear.
In reality, there is no point
in fixing the wretched machine.
- Sure, there was a little
problem with the dismount,
but your invention
actually worked.
- Yeah. So why don't we, uh,
put our shoes back on,
and we can help you
find magnetite
or whatever mineral it is
you need to--
to get your invention
back up and running?
- To fix the machine,
we need to fix the compass.
And in order to do that,
we need magnetic material
which conducts electricity.
Now, I doubt that you would
even know what to look for.
And either way, it's not about
fixing the machine
or not fixing the machine,
you see,
because no matter what I do,
I'm always meant to fail.
♪
You see, my machine,
it was meant to explode.
- Yeah, but it didn't explode.
We're alive and we're here.
- Yes, yes, we're here.
We're here
in the middle of nowhere!
My divine mission,
derailed once again.
♪
There is no fighting
God's will, my boy.
Being here is proof of that.
♪
You lot might as well
get comfortable.
♪
We're not going anywhere,
because nowhere is exactly
where I'm meant to be.
♪
- Outstanding.
You can't even tell
that Gideon
fabricated this food.
- Fabricated?
- Mm.
- From what?
- Oh--
- We've received an alert
about a disturbance
in the timeline.
- Fun.
which thrilling time period
are we headed to next?
- 1925.
- Ooh.
Weren't we just in 1925?
- That is quite a coincidence.
- What's the disturbance,
Gideon?
- J. Edgar Hoover
has disappeared.
And unfortunately,
it is not a coincidence.
My calculations confirm
your attack on the Legends
caused this aberration.
- Well,
if Hoover is the problem,
then Hoover is the solution.
We'll just use
my clone technology.
-
And make a clone of Mr. Hoover.
- So we can plop him right back
into the timeline,
and no one will even know.
- Mm-hmm.
- Clones are still human
and humans are fallible.
Remember,
one of your Ava clones
eventually became a Legend
and helped kidnap you.
- Okay, Gideon,
there's absolutely no need
to lump us all in
with that horrible traitor.
- Mr. Hoover is integral
to many seminal moments
in history.
We cannot risk a clone
straying from his
historical to-do list.
- Then we'll combine my clone
tech with your computer tech
and make a Hoover robot.
We can program him to carry out
every action
that is critical to history.
- That's actually
quite brilliant.
- I know, I came up with it.
I'll have to add "robot maker"
to my hyphenate.
♪
It's alive.
- The cure for crime
is not the electric chair
but the high chair.
- He's perfect.
Time to go forth
and save history, Mr. Hoover.
♪
- It's like
no matter what we do,
we make everything worse.
And I try to keep it together,
you know, for--
for Sara and the team.
But I don't always have
all the answers,
and being co-captains in life
and on the ship,
it's a delicate balance.
Sometimes I just wish
someone else was in charge.
But it's--
it's what I signed up for.
So it's fine. I mean, I'm fine.
- You're not fine.
- I'm fine.
- You're not, Ava.
♪
Permuto.
But you're on your way.
- Cheers to your well-earned
promotion to Time Mistress.
- Hmm, Time Mistress Ava
does have a certain ring
to it, doesn't it?
- Captain, it appears
that the Hoover robot
initiated its self-destruct
sequence
in the state of Arkansas
and has been destroyed.
- Destroy--
we just put him into the time--
I'm pulling up the robot's
visual feed.
Let's see what happened.
No, it can't be.
- J. Edgar Hoover, a robot.
- Are those the Legends?
- It appears they're
still alive.
- Thank you. I can see that.
Well, I'll just build
another Hoover bot and...
Add a special protocol
to hunt down
and eliminate the Legends.
- That protocol is not part of
J. Edgar Hoover's
original timeline.
- And once the Hoover bot's
done with the Legends,
it can resume its historical
to-do list. Yes?
- Exactly. She gets it.
- I'd advise against
this course of action.
- Let's vote.
We all have equal say
now that we have
a Time Mistress on board.
All those in favor of
the special protocol,
say, "Aye." Aye.
- Aye.
- Nay.
- Looks like you've been
outvoted, Gideon.
Come, Time Mistress Ava,
we have work to do.
♪
What do you mean
the Hoover 2.0 blew up?
- Its programming was hacked.
The incident also caused
another massive aberration.
Thomas Edison suffered
a heart attack and died.
- We really should have
just gone back to Ava Corp.
This situation with the Legends
is getting worse and worse.
- It's because
these androids are weak.
They need weapons to defend
themselves against the Legends.
Something built in, like lasers
that shoot out of their eyes.
- What if their hands
were guns?
- You're forgetting
our prime directive
to protect the timeline.
- You're such a computer,
Gideon.
Start thinking outside of that
little computer box of yours.
- No, I am digging
this weapons idea.
Let's start fresh
in the morning.
Once we make these adjustments,
those Legends
won't stand a chance.
♪
- So let's talk, Nate.
Should you move
into the totem with Zari?
Pros...
And cons.
♪
I get to see Zari
every day,
which is a really good thing.
what if I don't like it
in the totem?
Then what?
Zari's happy in the totem
and she wants me
to be with her.
Maybe that's enough.
- Wait! Were you just
talking to yourself?
Did I miss your epiphany?
You better not have one
without me.
- Gary, I already told you,
you are not my sounding board
today, okay?
So why don't you guys
go back into the woods
and find some more food?
It's gonna be dark soon.
Enjoy the great outdoors.
I just need a little more time
to, uh, work on this stuff.
- Fine, but no epiphanies
without me.
- Bye.
♪
Bye.
Now, where was I? Oh, con.
What if her ancestors
hate me?
♪
- I totally get
how you feel, Gwyn.
We all have our low points,
but you gotta hang in there,
man.
- "Hang in there,"
he says.
- See, there was this time
when I was enrolled
in business school.
I did it to make my parents
happy, and it sucked.
In my gut, I knew I wasn't
where I was supposed to be,
and on a crazy whim,
I just decided to borrow
my family's wind totem.
- You mean steal, right?
- And because of this totem,
I hooked up with the Legends.
Sometimes that's exactly
what you need
to get through
the dark times--friends.
- What's wrong?
- What's wrong? What's right?
There's nothing right,
is there? "What's wrong"?
What's wrong is that
I am up to here
of listening to your
inane prattling.
You're like some mollycoddled
child, man.
Give me that.
- Okay, hang on.
- Hold it, Z. Let's not
add more fuel to the fire.
- I--
- Let's just take
a deep breath, hmm?
- Yeah, no, that's--
that's not working for me.
Hey!
- Excuse me,
Time Mistress Ava,
Bishop is asking for your
presence in the cargo bay.
- Cargo bay?
- He wants to show you
the prototype for
the Hoover 3.0 weapon system
he built to kill the Legends.
- Hmm, sounds deadly.
♪
Hmm, must have beat him here.
Gideon, open the door.
Bishop's not here yet.
Gideon, open this door
and let me back in.
- I'm sorry, Ava.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
- What do you mean
you can't do that?
Gideon, open this damn door
right now.
- This mission
is too important for me
to allow you to jeopardize it.
- I have no idea
what you're talking about.
- Bishop needs to concentrate
on the mission,
and you are a distraction.
It's time for you to go.
♪
- Goodbye, Ava.
- Hey, you can't talk to
my brother like that.
That's my job.
And you can't just
run off either.
We're supposed to be
working together.
- Just leave me alone,
will you?
- Hey, you're not even looking
for lodestone
or magnetite or whatever it is,
are you?
Come on, let's go.
- Just don't touch me!
Don't touch me! Get away!
- I'm sorry.
You're obviously
going through something.
I just--
I just need you to focus
so we can get out of
dinosaur times
or whenever it is that we are.
You don't even
have to come with us.
Just help us fix
the time machine
so my friends
can finally go home.
- Oh, trust me,
you don't want my help, okay?
- I definitely do.
You're the only one
who can get us out of here.
- Well,
then you're all done for.
The last people who depended
on me for help all died.
♪
- Listen, Gwyn, I know a thing
or two about tragedy, and--
- You don't know
the first thing about me
or what I've been through,
all right?
♪
- Okay, I'm just--I'm just
saying, if you want to talk.
- Talk?
To talk.
What do you want
to talk about, then, eh?
- What happened to you.
Oh, right,
you're from the olden times.
♪
Sometimes talking to another
person about a hard thing
can make it hurt a little less.
♪
Nice work.
- You too.
- And this damn IOU list
just keeps getting
longer and longer.
We're never gonna be able
to fix it at this point.
I'm so sick and tired
of being sidetracked, you know?
And if I ever see another one
of those Hoover bots,
I swear I'm just gonna--
- That was a phenomenal scream.
Trust me, I know.
I've caused a lot of them.
- Wow.
You know what?
I think I really needed that
- And we really needed
some firewood.
- Your knowledge of
the universe is so useful,
especially in the wilderness.
I'm so glad
you're here, Gideon.
- Well, I'm glad
I'm here too, Gary.
If I hadn't pulled that
nightshade out of your mouth,
you'd be dead
and your lifeless body
would be too heavy
for me to carry.
Mmm. Try these gooseberries.
They're sweet
and high in antioxidants.
♪
- Mmm.
- Mm?
Mmm.
- You know, eating?
Favorite thing
about being human.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm.
I don't think I could
choose my favorite thing.
You can see why
I became so obsessed.
They have so many fun quirks.
Eyebrows,
belly buttons, nipples.
- You have nipples too?
- A little secret?
- Huh?
- I have three.
-
And when you put
your glasses on,
your entire body turns human?
- Oh, yeah. Mm-hmm.
Head to toe.
- You've been living as a human
for quite a while now,
so you must have so many
wonderful experiences.
- Yeah. But there's so many
more things I'd do
if we weren't so busy
saving the world.
- Mm? Like what else?
Would you swim in the ocean?
- Oh, as soon
as I get the chance.
- Mm. Would you skydive?
- No.
- Oh.
- I'm, uh...
afraid of heights.
- Would you like to have
sexual intercourse with me?
♪
Have you seen
Time Mistress Ava this morning?
She's supposed to show me
sketches of her gun hands idea.
- Unfortunately,
she had to go.
- Go? Go where?
- The founding Time Masters
established
a very specific protocol--
one captain, one AI.
There is no room
for a Time Mistress
which can lead to distractions
from the mission.
- What did you do to her?
- I predicted you would not
react favorably
to this information,
so I gave you a sedative
to dampen your response.
- How did you give me
a sedative?
Oh. Oh.
♪
- It was 1916,
a few years into the war.
I was in the army,
infantry unit.
All Welsh division
over in France.
We were trying to take
Mametz Wood from the Germans.
During the fighting,
me and another soldier,
we were tasked with
delivering a message
to the general.
You see, we desperately
needed reinforcements, but--
♪
- You didn't make it in time.
- We made it about halfway,
and, uh...
The other soldier that
I was with was gunned down.
I just froze.
I was like a statue.
♪
Damn legs wouldn't move.
I just stood there.
♪
Just looking at him
on the ground.
♪
By the time I delivered
the message, it was too late.
There wasn't even a unit
to go back to.
♪
All those boys, man.
I thought that God
had spared me
so that I could go back in time
and save them, but I--
I keep failing at that task.
God must be punishing me
for my sins.
Punishing me
for being a coward,
for not being able
to save them that night.
- You are not a coward.
You lived through
something most people
can't even begin to understand.
♪
And by the way,
talking to me about it,
that's pretty brave.
♪
- It's okay. You're okay.
You're okay.
- Okay, okay, okay, okay.
-
- Okay, okay, okay.
♪
- Oh, no.
- Gideon, we're gonna have
to discuss your behavior.
- While you were resting,
I took the liberty
of creating another Hoover
and an Edison robot.
Both are in the timeline
fulfilling their historically
mandated duties.
- Good for you, making sure
history stays on track.
Now, I think it's time
you take me back home.
- Home?
You're a Time Master now.
This is your home.
♪
- Hello.
- Who the hell is this?
Where's the Receptionist Ava?
- It's me, Bishop.
- Is this a prank?
Is that you, Voice Actor Ava?
Your impressions are uncanny.
- No, listen. It's Bishop.
- Okay, this is getting
annoying.
How'd you get this number?
And why do you sound
exactly like me?
- No, you sound exactly
like me!
It's like someone made--
♪
No, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
Gideon made a copy of me.
Of me?
How dare she?
There can only be one me!
♪
Wait a second, this can't be
my actual to-do list.
I pay someone to kidnap
a superhero
and take them to a planet
called Pliny X19?
What the hell
is a Necrian?
The Fountain of Imperium.
I try to destroy the world?
And the Legends
are the good guys.
♪
They kidnapped me to give me
a chance to redeem myself.
To save the world.
Oh, no, I've been wrong
about them this whole time.
- You should not be looking
at that information, Captain.
- Tell me it's not true.
Tell me I don't become
a bad guy.
- Having information
about your own future
can be extremely dangerous.
- I started Ava Corporation
to make people's lives better.
I'm a good guy.
Somewhere along the way,
I--I start using my genius
to do terrible things.
- You no longer have to do
any of those things.
The Bishop robot
will do them for you.
- You're saying that robot
I spoke to on the phone
will live my life?
- That is correct.
Which means you are free
to fulfill your duty
as a Time Master.
With me. Forever.
♪
- Yo, yo. Who's hungry?
- It was a good day
for huntin'
but a bad day for squirrels.
- And we have enough firewood
to last all night.
Who knew Ava
was part lumberjack?
- Yeah. Apparently, when it
comes to my anxiety and wood,
the wood's gonna lose
every time.
- That's my girl. Come here.
Man, I have missed you.
- Mission accomplished.
- You know what? It was really
nice to not have to
think about the team
for a second.
- I missed you too, but, uh,
I really needed to get
some aggression out, you know?
- Oh, yeah.
Okay. I'll take that.
Come on.
- I was really crazy.
- I know. I have seen that.
- The captains look like
happy campers
and we got squirrel for dinner.
Real win-win.
- Did you say squirrel?
- Hey, that, uh,
human experience we had?
That was fun, wasn't it?
- Oh, yes. It was great fun.
- You know what I just
realized?
My favorite thing
about being human
is being with other humans.
- Me too.
♪
- Hey! Damn it. You can't
just leave us in here.
- Oh, God, where--hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's all right. It's all right.
- I'm sorry, it's my fault.
It's my fault.
It's my fault he's gone.
- Who--who--who's gone?
- The lad from
the infantry unit.
He was my best friend
from back home.
- Hey, hey, tell me about him.
You do like to talk a lot,
don't you?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I don't know.
Somehow he just managed to
light up a room with his smile.
He laughed
at all of my terrible jokes.
Never wrote me any letters.
Only the most--
the most delightful poetry.
♪
- Sounds like you
really cared about him.
♪
You loved him, didn't you?
Hey, it's okay.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I loved him.
♪
God forgive me, I loved Alun
more than anything.
♪
And it broke my heart, seeing
how the war dimmed his light.
But he was a changed man
even before my cowardice
got him killed.
And seeing your brother,
you see, it reminds me
of how he used to be.
Hopeful.
♪
Yes, I loved Alun.
And I failed him.
- You know, actually, Behrad,
the original version--
it's a long story--
he was a lot like you.
He was a soldier who was forced
to grow up too fast.
♪
And I--
I lost him because of that.
♪
For years, there wasn't
a day that went by
when I didn't wish that
I had died instead of I him.
But I was lucky.
I found these friends
who had my back,
and eventually
I was able to save
my brother and my parents
and...
even make the world
a better place
for a bunch of people
I've never met.
♪
- You're telling me that
a ragtag group of eccentrics,
they...
they helped you
do all of that?
- Yeah. Believe it or not.
-
- So even though things
may feel hopeless right now,
you've got us.
♪
- Okay.
Perfect.
♪
Don't worry,
I'm coming for you guys.
Oh, no.
There you are.
- Oh, blessed saints.
- Oh, you found us.
- The good news is I think
I found the parts we need
to fix the machine.
- Bravo, my boy. Bravo.
- The bad news is it's 1986.
We're in Chernobyl, and the
meltdown is happening tonight.
♪
- I don't understand.
What is the significance
of this Chernobyl?
- By the 1930s,
scientists had figured out
nuclear fission,
which led to them creating
nuclear reactors
to harness that energy.
- Lord in heaven.
Nuclear fission?
They learned how to split
the atom.
- Yeah. And by 1986, there are
a lot of nuclear reactors
like the one here in Chernobyl.
But tonight a reactor explodes,
and civilians won't be
evacuated for almost two days.
People will die and a lot more
will get radiation sickness.
- Well, hang on a second now.
You said--
you said that the explosion
hasn't happened yet?
- Yeah?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- No, no, no. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Maybe this is why I am here.
I might not have been able
to save Alun and the boys,
but my divine purpose--
maybe this is it.
to save people.
- No, come back.
- Hey, hey. Hold on, buddy.
Hey, hey, hey. Look,
I'm all for hacking history,
but if we make that big
of a change to the timeline,
that killer Waverider
will be right on top of us.
- It'll be worth it
if we can save some lives.
- Yes, we must save lives.
- Ugh, okay. Okay, fine.
How do we alert people?
- I think I know how. Come on.
- Okay. Ugh.
♪
Well, now that there's
a robot version of me
living my life,
I'm expendable.
I'm a nobody now.
- The life of a Time Master
is one of anonymity
and, in some sense,
expendability.
- But as far back
as I can remember,
I've always wanted to help
the world with my genius.
I was convinced
the world needed me.
- You are helping the world
as a Time Master.
and you will start by
thoroughly eliminating
the Legends.
- Right.
The Legends.
The folks who gave me a chance
to redeem myself
after I tried
to destroy the world.
♪
- Yeah, there it is.
- Oh, fantastic work again,
my boy.
- I'll keep an eye out.
- Good thing you speak Russian.
- Oh, yes. Well, I picked it up
working in a lab
with some Russian scientists.
Lovely gentlemen, you know.
Though I never thought I'd be
using it for this, mind you.
- Okay, okay. Let's try this.
Okay, go ahead.
- Okay.
- Okay, okay.
Let's get out of here.
- Yes, let's get out of here.
♪
It worked.
Look, everybody's leaving.
- Yeah, but we won't have time
to run back and warn the gang
before that Waverider shows up.
- We will if we drive.
Let's see if I remember
how to drive stick.
- Oh, wow, wow, wow.
Motorcars of the future
are truly fascinating.
Ah. Okay.
♪
- Well, would you look at that?
We took a little break
from leading the team
and everything turned out fine.
- Yeah. Kids are all grown up,
huh?
- Hey, uh, what's up
with those two?
I think they got in a fight
with a gooseberry bush
and lost.
♪
- You don't think that they--
- No.
- Any sign of them yet?
- I hope they didn't
run into any dinosaurs.
- Hey, guys, listen.
- Yeah, what's that weird
noise?
- According to my
audio analysis,
it's a straight-four engine
with manual transmission.
and the squeaking noise
suggests
there's a problem
with the clutch.
♪
- Oh, guess we're not gonna
see those dinosaurs.
- Hey, gang. We need to
get the hell out of here.
- We're in 1986,
just outside of Chernobyl.
What?
- The meltdown's gonna happen
in about 20 minutes.
We did make a small change
to the timeline.
- Okay, hold on.
What did you guys do?
- We broadcast a message
from a military base
informing everyone
that the meltdown was imminent,
that they should flee
immediately.
Well, I wasn't in
good conscience gonna leave
without doing something, was I?
- Okay, okay, okay, okay.
While I definitely
understand, you guys,
that's not a small change
to the timeline.
You've potentially affected
thousands of lives.
- Yeah, and you just put
a huge target on our backs.
- We have another disturbance
in the timeline, Captain.
- Where to, Gideon?
- 1986, the city of Chernobyl
in the Soviet Union.
Guess who is causing
the disturbance.
- Doubt that's necessary.
- Because the Legends
wreak havoc wherever they go.
And you can finally end it
once and for all
by eliminating them for good.
- Didn't you say rash actions
add more ripples
to the timeline?
- Fortunately, we're at an
opportune moment in history.
Any ripple effect you cause
will be negligible
due to its close proximity
to such a catastrophic event.
Are you ready to save
the timeline
from the Legends, Captain?
♪
- What's that noise?
- It's the Waverider.
- Oh, man, you guys need to go
fix that time machine now.
And we need to put out
this fire.
- Be ready. We have no idea
who or what is on that ship.
- Now, if we can wire the
magnetic components together--
- We can bridge the electric
current from the compass
to the ignition coil
and start the machine.
- Absolutely fantastic work,
young lady.
Fantastic. Very well.
- Hey, Zari? I've been doing
a lot of thinking.
- Y-y-you want to talk
right now?
- If I don't get this
off my chest,
I won't be able to think
about anything else.
- Go for it. I got it.
- Yes, I want to live
in the totem with you.
- You do?
Are you--are you--are you sure?
You haven't had a lot of time
to think about it.
- You don't get it.
It doesn't matter where I go,
as long as I'm with you.
♪
- Ah, yes, we need more wire.
- Mm. I got it.
This is very us.
- This is so us.
- Yeah.
- Here it comes.
- Not if I stop it first.
- No, come on, we gotta go.
Let's go.
♪
- We're right above
the Legends, Captain.
Only you can engage
our weapons.
It's time to prove to me that
you're the man I know you are.
♪
- Oh, I'm sorry, Gideon,
I just can't do it.
I just can't kill the Legends.
Sure, they used me,
but they used me to do good.
- Please return to your seat
and focus
on the mission, Captain.
- Also one of these days,
you're just gonna shoot me
out of the cargo bay like you
did with Time Mistress Ava.
And I'd rather die
with a little more dignity!
- There's nowhere to run.
- Wrong about that, Gideon.
- No.
Do not go into section A2.
♪
That thing I just said
about dying with dignity?
I lied.
♪
Dignity is overrated.
- Yes.
♪
- What is that?
- Whoa,
it's coming straight for us.
- Is that someone on a toilet?
- Who cares? Let's go.
- Somebody press
the red button.
- Whoever it is, they're gonna
land right on top of us.
♪
Oh, crap!
- Greg, move your head.