Time travel is real
and all of history
is vulnerable to attack.
Which is why we must
travel through time
to stop the spread of these
so-called time aberrations
and to erase their damage to history.
We are a team
of outcasts and misfits.
So please, don't call us heroes.
We're something else.
We're Legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
We're The Justice Society of America.
Dr. Mid-Nite, Star Girl.
Copy that.
Have either of you gentlemen
heard of the Spear of Destiny?
The Spear allegedly
has the power to rewrite reality.
I know that you're one
of the protectors
of the Spear of Destiny,
and I know that you know
where the other pieces are hidden.
Oh... okay, okay.
The piece of the Spear's
inside your telescope.
Will you put the gun down, Jax?
He's with the Legion now.
Why are you protecting him?
I'm protecting you.
Hello, Charles.
Oh, I see you found a way
to cure your blindness.
The future is full of marvels,
Captain Hunter.
No longer a captain, I'm afraid.
Wow.
What do we have here?
This is a bio-morphic implant
capable of modifying
its host's neural processes.
One day, this could end
violence as we know it.
Or, by the same means, amplify it.
I thought none of us were supposed
to contact the other again.
A new threat, I'm afraid.
A cabal of sorts is after the Spear.
I'm rounding up the fragments.
Why?
They're safer apart
than they are together.
They'll be safe
at the Vanishing Point.
Really?
You said the Time Masters
couldn't be trusted.
Did I? Bollocks, so I did.
I suppose we're gonna have
to do this the hard way, then.
Now, where is
the fragment of the Spear
that I had you protect?
I don't know why you want it,
but you'll never find it.
Well, seeing as you've been posing
as a researcher
in cybernetic implants...
my guess is that you have
hidden the fragment...
Inside you.
What's going on?
Lily's algorithm located
a piece of the Spear of Destiny.
When? I mean, I know just now,
but where are we headed?
Detroit, the year 3,000 AD.
Journey into the distant future.
- How exciting.
- Speak for yourself.
Come on, man.
Who doesn't like the future?
I like history. Yeah, I know
it's filled with terror and violence,
- but the future just...
- It's uncertain.
Yeah, and it freaks me out a little.
Then just stay on the ship.
You think I should stay on the ship?
I don't care. It's up to you.
I am a time travel professional.
If you need me to visit the future...
I can visit the future.
And I'm just saying
it's entirely up to you.
And I'm just saying shut up.
Nate, you'll stay on the ship.
The rest of us
will go find the Spear.
Unfortunately, the medallion
is no longer sensing
the presence of the Spear fragment.
So we came here for nothing?
Maybe not.
Gideon, do they have booze
in the year 3,000?
Better yet, Gideon.
Do you have the last position
of the fragment?
Somebody find
a light switch or something.
What the hell does
a light switch look like
in the year 3,000?
Yeah, I guess there's not many places
you can go with a light switch.
But everything else
is leaps and bounds
beyond our current science.
Amaya...
- Charles.
- How do you know the stiff?
This is Dr. Mid-Nite
of the Justice Society.
What's a member of the JSA
doing this far into the future?
Rest in peace.
That's sweet, Mick.
No, it's what
he wrote on the floor...
R.I.P.
That's not "Rest In Peace".
It's the name
of Dr. Mid-Nite's killer.
I just don't get it.
Please be more specific.
That could be a very long list.
Okay, even assuming
the Legion took
the Spear fragment from here...
how did they know it was here?
Without the medallion, you mean.
Rip must've told them.
Somehow, he remembers where
the pieces of the Spear are.
Well, then it's a good thing
you let him escape.
Do you wanna say something to me?
Jax told me about how
he was gonna kill Rip in 1776
and about how you stopped him.
Because we're not killers, Amaya.
Except for yourself
and Mr. Rory and...
I'll stop helping now.
I'm not condoning murder
but the JSA would've captured Rip
without regard for sentiment.
You think I let Rip go
- because of sentiment?
- Yes.
All right, let's just
all take a breath.
I'm sorry
that your friend got killed.
And it may be sentimental...
but my team comes before tactics.
And as a result, you've put
the whole of reality at risk.
Maybe this is why
your team loses so often.
Pardon the interruption...
Excellent timing, Gideon.
Your daughter Lily's algorithm
has identified a location
for another piece of the Spear.
Well, when it rains, it pours.
Where is it, Gideon?
A small island known as Britannia
in the year 507 AD.
Medieval England.
See, this is what
I'm talking about...
a nice,
well-documented piece of history.
Knights in shining armor...
damsels in distress...
and best of all, jousts.
Well, jousting didn't appear
in England till 1300 AD.
Don't take this away from me.
Raymond.
Just forget about history
for once, all right?
We're in the Age of Legend.
Well, remember
as Santayana once said.
"Those who cannot remember history
are condemned to repeat it."
Was he a knight?
I don't remember his name.
And I was pretty obsessed
with Arthurian lore as a kid.
Well, if you were...
you would know
that there were not jousts.
Oh... well...
agree to disagree.
Fair.
Are you skipping Medieval Times,
as well, Professor?
Yes, I was just catching up
on some research.
- What'd you do?
- Excuse me?
Don't say excuse me.
It makes you sound guilty.
I haven't the foggiest idea
what you're talking...
- What are you doing?
- Thieves.
They have a certain smell.
I thought that was just
because you didn't bathe.
What'd you steal?
How dare you even suggest...
What did you steal?
Dr. Mid-Nite wouldn't be needing it,
so I figured I'd...
I couldn't resist.
Though I prefer the term "borrowed".
Impressive.
There's hope for you yet.
Look, all I'm saying is...
the stories you grew up
on are just that.
They're stories, all right?
The Medieval world
was a time of turmoil.
It was the collapse of Rome
which led to the collapse
of civilization itself.
And don't even get me started
on the health and sanitation.
Yeah, please don't.
Cholera, diphtheria...
typhoid fever, and I'm not
even touching skin diseases.
Speaking of which, why did you
choose to dress like a leper?
I didn't.
This is historically accurate.
You all look like you're going
to a Renaissance Fair.
- What is it?
- We're being followed.
And by the way,
even if I was a leper...
it'd be way less obvious than
a bunch of knights in shining armor.
Wait... I mean, hold mean...
I mean, hark!
Good knight, we intend you no harm.
We are but mere travelers
in this land.
Your dialect is way off.
I, Raymond of the Palms,
and my band of merry men
and women, humbly request
safe passage to Camelot
and an audience with King Arthur.
King Arthur?
Yes, you can see his crest
on their shields.
I am Guinevere.
We shall escort you to Camelot...
but your leper must remain
outside the castle walls.
I'm not a leper!
Still think this is just a story?
This place shouldn't exist.
There's no need of that here.
We're all equal
in the court of Camelot.
That's why I love this guy.
Our paths crossed in the wood
while tracking the Black Knight,
Your Grace.
How then are we to know
that they're not in league
with that vile rogue?
- Ray?
- Your Grace...
I swear we are not your enemies.
We are warriors on a quest,
a race against evil.
A great evil haunts my land
these many days...
kidnapping my noble Knights
of the Round Table.
Therefore,
it'll fall on my wisest adviser
to measure the truth of your words.
Oh, please don't say it.
Summon Merlin!
Get ready to fight
our way out of here
if Merlin rules against us.
That's Star Girl.
What are you doing in Camelot?
This ship never ceases to amaze me.
Well, speaking of amazing... Merlin?
Just an identity I adopted
to fit into this era.
But what are you even doing
in this era?
Let me guess, it has something
to do with the Spear of Destiny.
We found Dr. Mid-Nite in year 3000.
He's dead, Courtney.
We think he was killed
because he possessed
a piece of the Spear.
What do you know
about the JSA's final mission?
Obsidian told me
that the JSA disappeared
after a trip to Leipzig in 1956.
The mission was to recover
the Spear of Destiny
and keep it from falling
into enemy hands.
And how was it that you were
all scattered throughout time?
We were joined
on our mission by someone
who called himself a Time Master.
- Rip Hunter.
- Yes.
He said the Spear
could alter reality itself...
that it was too powerful
for any man or woman to possess.
So, we broke it
into four separate pieces.
Mr. Hunter took one...
And took the rest of you
to three different time periods.
When I arrived in Camelot,
it was a middling kingdom.
To help me protect
my piece of the Spear,
I fashioned it into the
legendary court of King Arthur
and his Knights of the Round Table.
Courtney, I respect your devotion.
But shouldn't you at least tell me
where the fragment is hidden?
Don't worry, Amaya.
I promise,
the piece is somewhere very safe.
Your tracking
in the woods was excellent.
There's not many people that can
get the jump on me like that.
I was a warrior
long before I was a queen.
Why does it sound like
you preferred that?
Politics is not one of my passions.
But Arthur is a true friend and ally,
and I believe in his vision
for a more just
and peaceful kingdom.
From what I see,
Camelot lives up to its reputation.
Where is the good king?
On hunt...
no doubt chasing a boar
through the brush as we speak.
Do your worst, knave.
I'd rather die than surrender.
Then you are an idiot.
You're not going to run me through.
No.
We have something else in mind
for you, Your Majesty.
I can't believe Marty and Mick
are missing this.
Like, right?
I mean, when's the next time
we're gonna get to feast in Camelot?
Hey, guys, check it out.
That's Sir Galahad.
How do you know that?
Because he's sitting
in the Siege Perilous.
What?
Come on.
Some kind of historian you are.
Siege Perilous is a special seat
reserved for only
the purest of knights.
I don't how many times
I have to tell you.
There's a difference between
legend and history.
I'm gonna go introduce myself.
Sir Galahad.
Oh, is this seat taken?
It is now, my friend.
Apologies. You must get
this all the time.
But I must tell you,
I am a really big fan.
A fan?
So you make wind?
No, no, no, no, no...
Well...
I mean, maybe after all this food.
No, what I mean is I'm a...
I'm a big admirer of yours.
You've heard tale of my exploits?
Yes! Yes!
Since I was a wee lad.
It's hard to explain.
I am but a servant.
It is my honor to serve the true
inspiration of Camelot's glory...
King Arthur, for was it not he
who said that might must serve right,
lest it bloom into
the cruel flower of tyranny?
Yet another reason I love him.
They sound the return of the king.
Arthur's captured the Black Knight.
Arthur, I was beginning to...
Oh, sorry about the ruse,
but I figure it was
the only way to get inside.
Oh! Hey, guys.
I see you've met
my friend Arthur here.
Give us a smile, Arthur.
Arthur...
The king has left the building.
You don't get the reference?
Oh, pity.
Basically, your king now does
anything I want him to do.
So if you don't want him to spill
your blood all over this floor,
I suggest that you hand over
your fragment of the Spear.
My patience is running short.
The fragment. Where is it?
As long as I live,
you will never have it.
That might turn out
to be shorter than you think.
Stand fast, or your king dies.
All I have to do is think it,
and he slits his own throat.
Ultimatum time.
Deliver the fragment to me by dawn
or I'll come back with an army
just as obedient as Arthur here.
Choice is yours.
Camelot...
or the Spear.
Galahad, may you rest in peace
where sorrow and pain are banished.
May the everlasting light
of Camelot shine upon you.
How do you know this Black Knight?
His name's Damien Darhk.
He works with the speedster
who turned Rip Hunter
against the JSA.
Well, Rip's not the only one
under their control now.
That thing's dark magic
has turned my king...
my own husband into my enemy.
- It's not his fault.
- And yet I watched him
strike down Sir Galahad
with my own eyes.
You have to believe that
your husband can be saved,
or else he will be truly lost.
Unless we stop
the Black Knight's army...
we may never find out.
My Queen, you must be strong.
With King Arthur missing,
the Knights of the Round Table
will look to you to lead them.
The mantle of king is Arthur's.
Not mine.
Guinevere, wait.
Look, sometimes the mantle
just falls into your lap.
Trust me.
I know that it's hard.
You're clever...
you're brave...
and you are a natural-born commander.
I know you can do this.
You saw what they did to Arthur.
Imagine what they could do with
an army of brainwashed knights.
What are you suggesting?
The fragment of the Spear...
we need to get it out of the castle.
How can your team protect the Spear?
You couldn't even protect
Dr. Mid-Nite.
That's not fair.
I'm not going anywhere,
and neither is the fragment.
Fascinating.
It seems to contain some sort of,
sophisticated receiver.
Clearly, it's the same
technology I...
I... I found in Dr. Mid-Nite's lab.
- Grey, you didn't.
- You bet he did.
Nicked it off the dead guy.
Even I was impressed.
I was simply curious.
And it's a good thing I did.
These components appear to be a set.
Perhaps functioning together
as transmitter and receiver.
- Or commander and soldier.
- Exactly.
The commander wears the transmitter,
sending orders via
an electro-telepathic signal
to this receiver
worn by the soldier.
Well, anything with a signal
can get hacked.
That is the hope, yes.
So all we need to is somehow
boost the brain power
of whoever's wearing this.
Or find someone
with a preternaturally
powerful brain.
You mean you?
Fine, if you insist.
Now, all we need is a test subject.
Someone who's mind is pliable.
What?
Hey, Sir Drools-A-Lot.
Prepare the rest of your tin men
to get ready to march.
Perhaps I didn't make myself clear.
Prepare your men, King Arthur.
As you wish, my liege.
Prepare to march.
Who knew these things
would come in handy?
Now, Mr. Rory, I want you
to get up out of that chair.
No, I command you
Do... do you feel anything at all,
a foreign impulse...
just like twinge perhaps?
Wait, I'm picking up on something.
Oh, my God. It's working.
I'm hungry.
This is a disaster.
Wait.
It seems our adversaries
are sending a signal of their own.
What does that mean?
Oh, dear God.
It means the Legion
is coming for Camelot.
Valiant Knights of Camelot...
I know the fear you feel.
We stand now
on the precipice of doom.
Our king has been taken from us.
Evil draws close
and hope, it seems, is lost.
But we must rise
and face this challenge
as Arthur would have wanted.
We must remember who we are.
We're brothers and sisters.
We're fighters and friends.
We are not mere knights.
We are Camelot!
The dark army approaches.
It's reached the great wood.
It seems your wizard is too late.
Is she talking about Professor Stein?
No matter.
We shall settle
this at the point of our swords.
Camelot calls
to you in its hour of need.
Will you answer?
Who will follow me
onto the field of battle?
Dude, what are they doing?
These guys don't stand
a chance out there.
Is this really worth the risk
for some dream?
Yes, because a long time ago
that dream meant
the world to a little boy...
and he still remembers.
This isn't gonna end well.
What are you doing?
If Star Girl won't give us
the fragment for safe-keeping...
You're stealing it?
She's not thinking straight.
I should have known.
You sure this is the way
you wanna do it?
Star Girl was your teammate,
not to mention your friend.
The Legion of Doom
are closing in on us as we speak.
There's no time for sentiment.
Do you really wanna
chance Damien Darhk
having the power to rewrite reality?
I guess not.
It's set in stone.
Not for long.
Damn, that was badass.
Let's get out of here.
Put it down.
We should attack now.
Let me tell you
how an ultimatum works.
The so-called Legends have until dawn
to deliver the Spear.
You don't actually believe
that they'll hand it over, do you?
Perhaps not,
but meeting on a battle field
is infinitely more wise
than laying siege to the castle.
Right.
I just thought that
you would want my expertise.
After all, I have already retrieved
two fragments of the Spear, but...
Word to the wise,
speak to me with respect.
That little thing on your head
doesn't control me.
I don't want to fight
with you, Amaya,
but I will if I have to.
Then get ready, because I'm
not leaving without the fragment.
Hey, we have enough
enemies as it is
- without fighting each other.
- You left us, Amaya.
I was there to protect the Spear,
and I will continue to protect it
until I take my last breath.
Because you know
that doing the right thing
is more important than
doing what feels right.
You're still a member
of the Justice Society.
No, I'm not.
My heart belongs in Camelot.
Your heart?
You of all people should understand.
It wasn't duty that led you
to join the Legends.
You've fallen in love with Arthur.
Your make-believe kingdom
is a real soap opera.
How can you expect me to turn away
from the truest
thing I've ever known?
All I know is that the Legion of Doom
will not stop until they get this.
And once they do,
the world, as we know it, is over.
Which is why you're taking it, Amaya.
I can't go,
so you have to fulfill my oath.
Protect the Spear.
All right, you heard the wizard.
Let's boogie.
Ray, this is wrong.
Please tell me
that's not Galahad's sword.
I know, it's not
historically accurate, but...
I couldn't resist.
It's like a saber made of light.
Yeah.
Oh, just don't call it a light saber.
- Major trademark issues, right?
- Yeah, trademark.
Have you lost your complete mind?
No, I focused the ionic energy
into Galahad's sword.
That's great, Ray.
But Sara says it's time to go, so...
What? But the battle
hasn't even begun.
Precisely why we're leaving now.
Listen, Amaya found the fragment
so there's need
for this medieval warfare.
That's great news, right?
Let's go.
In case you weren't listening,
this is the part where we run.
- I can't.
- Sure, you can.
Left foot, right foot, repeat,
let's go.
No, Nate. Look around you.
All of these men are willing
to die on the battlefield
not for some Spear, but for an idea.
And I get it now.
Camelot isn't about history.
It's not even
about some dusty old books
that got a lonely kid
through childhood.
It's about one noble idea...
that we can all stand up
for what's right,
no matter what.
And I can't walk away from that.
I believe you, Ray.
I do. And Camelot's great.
But if you don't leave right now,
- you're gonna die here.
- Would it kill you
to be just a little bit
more supportive?
You don't get it, man.
I checked the manuscript.
I saw your funeral.
Well, sounds to me like
the stuff Legends are made of.
All right, Gideon,
let's get ready for takeoff.
- Yes, Captain.
- This doesn't feel right.
We don't just leave people
in trouble.
They're knights and they're
fighting so we can get away.
- With the piece of the Spear.
- And without Rip.
Take comfort
we live to fight another day.
The Legion already
has two pieces of the Spear.
I don't like it, but we cannot
risk them getting a Yahtzee.
What the hell's a Yahtzee?
System's online, Captain Lance.
We are ready to time-jump.
Where's Raymond?
With this sword, I dub thee
Sir Raymond of the Palms,
defender of Camelot.
Rise, good knight.
I tried talking to him,
but he's hell-bent
- on getting himself killed.
- Doesn't he know
that we have the piece of the Spear?
All he seems to care
about is being remembered
in some BS bedtime story.
- We can't leave him behind.
- We're not leaving him.
He chose to say.
Amaya, I know you're following
JSA protocol at whatever cost
but this is seriously screwed up.
We can't risk losing
a piece of the Spear,
especially when the Legion
is being backed by
evil Knights of the Round Table.
I thought you were gonna
un-evil-fy them.
We were if we just had
a little more time.
- We still can.
- And what happens if you can't?
Well, as much as Haircut's
a pain in my ass,
I'm not gonna let him fight alone.
Sit down. That's an order.
- What's an order?
- Don't test me, Mick.
Don't threaten me, blondie.
I can't believe I'm actually
agreeing with Mr. Rory.
- Sara.
- I said sit down.
Stop.
I've already lost one team.
I'll be damned if my decision
rips the Legends apart too.
- What are you saying?
- Listen to your gut, Captain.
Don't abandon Ray.
He may be sentimental, but the team
should come before tactics.
You're right. Let's do this.
Guinevere's knights are not
gonna able to last long
against Damien Darhk's army
unless you three...
Take out Mid-Nite's
mind control tech.
- We're on it.
- We are?
Amaya, Nate...
you ready to go get
medieval out there?
Wait, you have got it reversed.
I need the transmitting device,
not the receiver.
I got an idea.
What if it's not about brain power
but about intensity? Like his.
We don't have time for this.
Put the dog collar on, Professor.
I have more patents
than Mr. Rory has felonies
and that's saying something.
To think that his mind
is more powerful than mine...
Shut up.
Wait, did you shut up
because you wanted to
or because he told you to?
Make him answer.
Answer the man, Professor.
- Astonishing.
- It worked.
I knew it. Okay.
Now all we got to do
is amplify the signal.
- What do you want me to do?
- Just rest your brain, Mr. Rory.
We'll let you know
when it's time to take control
of the evil army.
Oh, finally
I get to fulfill my destiny.
God help us.
So, came to fight for
an imaginary kingdom after all?
I came to fight for a friend.
A really dumb friend.
Okay, I need you
to unleash the darkness
on those brainwashed knights.
Let them inside your head.
Fill their minds
with every brutish impulse,
every traumatic memory.
That just be enough
to overload the system.
Spare nothing.
Poor babies.
Be gone, devilish sorcerer!
Damien...
Sorry, I don't do rescues.
Yeah.
Damn it, Ray!
You're here to finish me off,
Captain?
What are you doing?
Saving your life.
Give it up, Raymond.
You're a glorified nerd,
not a knight.
I'm Sir Raymond of the Palms.
and on behalf
of my 12-year-old self...
allow me to retort.
Yield, Damien!
Okay, okay, I submit.
Ray!
Ray. Oh, come on, buddy.
Open your eyes, you stupid bastard.
Ray, come on!
- Ray!
- Stop yelling at me.
Ray, you brilliant bastard.
It's not Ray anymore.
It's Sir Raymond of the Palms.
Yeah.
I'm never gonna call you that, buddy.
Thank you, Amaya.
Tales of your deeds
will honor these halls
for longer than you can imagine.
The honor is mine, Your Grace.
Hey.
So you're staying?
Like you, I found a new home.
- Like me?
- With the Legends.
The team suits you.
Take care of yourself, Courtney.
You too, Amaya.
What was that all about?
- Just a little friendly advice.
- Yeah?
We should get going. Where's Ray?
He said something about
paying his respects
to the queen before we left.
Funny.
Sara said the exact same thing.
I just wanted to say good-bye.
I enjoyed meeting you.
And I you, Sara Lance...
a lot.
Sara Lance-A-Lot.
I should go.
Do you really have to leave?
It is I, Raymond of the Palms,
my lady...
come to bid my fair lady adieu.
Oh, well...
A thousand pardons, Your Majesty.
- Sara.
- It's okay, Ray. Come in.
And a thousand thanks
for your service to the realm.
If ever your travels
bring you back...
there will always be a seat
at the Round Table
for Sir Raymond of the Palms.
Thank you, My Lady.
You know, every good legend
ends with a kiss.
Goodbye,Guinevere.
Surely, you must admit
that it's not
a superior intelligence
but rather, the murky depths
of your mind that proved vital.
Just admit it,
my brain saved the day.
I will admit nothing of the sort.
All right, I'll admit it.
Walking around in a legend
felt just as real as
walking around any part of history.
And you know what?
Maybe, legend and history
aren't so different after all.
Maybe they're just stories
to remind us where we come
from and who we can become.
So what do you say?
You wanna find out
how you're gonna be remembered
in everyone's favorite bedtime story?
Nah.
I think I'd rather make up
my future as I go.
Nice.
I got something I wanna say to you.
Well, I'm a captive audience,
aren't I?
I was gonna kill you
for what you did to Sara.
But she stopped me, and I'm glad.
But make no mistake...
you are not Captain,
and this is not your ship.
Not anymore.
So if you even think about
hurting anyone on my team...
I will not hesitate to end you.
Feel good to get
that off your chest, did it?
Gideon.
I'm here, Captain.
You always are.