All right, Legends.
Let's get this show on the road.
Can't let this immortality buzz
go to waste.
For your convenience,
I started a countdown timer.
Twenty-three hours and 45 minutes
to save my brother.
- You're welcome.
- All right.
You heard the lady.
Clock is ticking.
Yeah, let's get back to the ship
and fire up the loom
before it's too late.
Has anyone seen Gary
because someone at your party
has stolen my Shadow Stone.
So, if you come across
a disembodied voice
floating around,
crying out like a baby,
then that's your culprit.
Yeah, Gary went back to the ship.
His bunny has IBS.
Yeah, and serious gas issues.
Wow, that is some arctic breeze
blowing in.
Why are we in England?
Where the bloody hell is the portal?
Has anyone seen Astra?
How's your tummy, my bunny-wummy?
Gideon, can you do me a favor?
Can you fabricate more veggies
for Gary Junior II?
Gideon? You there?
Gary, the ship's compromised.
They're shutting me down.
If Gideon is down, then...
Who's flying the ship?
Oh, come on.
Are you lot off your trolleys?
Because I mean,
why would Astra steal the Waverider?
I know we're "friends" with her now,
but maybe she wanted to use the Loom.
Or what if my sisters got to her?
If they get control of the Loom
before we do,
we'll never get a chance
to bring my brother back.
Okay. Let's all just keep our cool.
Gideon, what's going on?
Gideon?
- Okay, no Gideon.
- Yeah, it's okay, it's okay.
We'll figure this out.
What just happened?
Did you have another vision?
No, it's, it was nothing.
As in, you saw nothing or what?
It was just a flash,
and then it was nothing.
I think it's the Chalice.
It's probably messing with my powers.
So, what?
Now, you're just blind?
- Mick, that's insensitive.
- That's not helpful.
Wait, wait, wait. I think
I just came up with an amazing plan.
Rip set up Time Bureau safe houses
all over the world,
some of which are still standing,
like the one in London.
Yes?
We go there, we get a Time Courier,
he'll take us to the Waverider.
- Yes.
- Yes. Okay.
Yeah, babe, that is a perfect plan.
And you know what? We're gonna do it.
We're gonna go to London
because we are immortal superheroes.
- Except me.
- Except for Zari.
And nothing is gonna stand
in our way.
We're immortal and we're superheroes,
and we have to wait for the bus.
Yeah.
Well, at least Constantine got us
these nice warm clothes.
- We're ready for anything, right?
- Yeah, like a pheasant hunt.
But in our defense,
we do look pretty good.
Okay, tell me this.
How do you live here
and not have a car?
Never needed one, love.
Always bummed a ride.
So, exactly how far is it to London?
Well, according to my phone,
it says 275.8...
- Miles or kilometers?
- Doesn't matter, it's far.
When is the bus supposed to get here?
According to the schedule,
it'll be here in either one minute
or three hours.
- Wait. Guys, is it a holiday?
- Is it a holiday?
- Finally.
- Yes.
- There we go.
- Okay.
Now, hold up. Who's paying the fare?
Does anybody have any money?
No.
Sir, I know this sounds ridiculous,
but the fate of the world
depends on us getting on this bus.
I don't care who depends on who.
When I'm driving this bus,
everyone pays the fare.
Have it your way.
Well, come on.
I really am so sorry, sir.
Believe it or not,
we're the good guys.
Bollocks!
Thank you for delivering
this lovely Timeship.
And Atropos,
thank you for shutting off
that aggravating talking computer.
She thought she was so witty.
You don't have to thank me.
It's not like I had a choice.
You called in your favor, after all.
Everything comes at a price, Astra.
I gave you a shot
at killing John Constantine,
and you squandered that.
You drank from the Chalice
of Dionysus.
You're immortal for a day
and can operate the Loom of Fate.
Are you asking me to work with you?
Because I'm not hearing a question.
Fine, I'll join you.
- But I have some demands.
- Demands?
- Really?
- Yeah.
Now I've experienced life
on Earth again,
some things have got to change.
Like prunes.
Disgusting. I want them gone.
And dogs,
they should stay puppies forever.
Oh, and there's just one more thing.
I want to bring
my mother back to life.
Let's kill her.
I'm immortal.
- Remember?
- For now.
Astra's friends
will be searching for us by now.
Do something productive
and take care of them
while I chat with Astra
about this list of demands.
Now, tell me about these prunes.
Should I tell Mick that he's driving
on the wrong side of the road
- or just...
- No, definitely not.
It'll just confuse him more.
- Okay.
- Speaking of driving,
maybe you should run point
on this mission.
What? Wait.
Is this because you're blind?
Because you totally killed it
at beer pong.
Thank you.
But now that I can't see the future,
you know,
just thinking maybe
I'm more useful as a foot soldier.
And plus, you're exactly
who the team needs right now.
Okay, fine.
But this is only temporary.
Because as far as I'm concerned,
we are co-captains for life.
Always.
Rise again, oh fallen souls.
We seek revenge.
Help conquer our foes.
Who's that?
We're gonna get your brother back.
We're just taking,
you know, the scenic route.
Oh, you have got to be kidding me.
Oh, you must be joking.
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm just having a little chin wag
with an old friend.
- Come on, give it here.
- This is not your friend.
I thought you quit.
Why are you starting again?
Because I trusted Astra
and then she betrayed me
by siding with Charlie's sisters.
You know, once they use the Loom,
we're all as good as dead anyway.
This doomsday act
is getting super old.
Look around. The sky hasn't fallen.
The world is still here.
And for whatever reason,
the cabal of mystical seamstresses
hasn't started spinning yet.
Which means
we still have time to stop them.
So, just don't do that.
- Fine.
- It's so gross.
- Oh, damn, Mick, you killed her.
- No, I didn't.
How do you know?
She's moving.
Ma'am, maybe,
maybe you should just stay down.
Are you okay?
What is it?
Punch it! Punch it!
Nice one.
Oh, we've seen this before
in the forest
where Atropos was chasing us.
My sister will do everything
she can to stop us.
Then we're probably
gonna start seeing
a lot more of these zombies soon.
Or now.
Let's go!
Oh, come on, really?
What the hell, John?
Now you have a death wish?
Oh, come on. Don't be daft.
See, apparently, the good thing
about having a damned soul
is these zombies
aren't interested in me.
Cool demo.
Could you do something now?
Yeah, okay. Watch.
All right, team.
We gotta stick to the plan.
Let's get this bus up and running
before more of these come back.
Maybe this cable
will get Gideon back online.
Gideon?
Should have paid more attention
in computer science.
Wake up, sleepyhead.
Are you an angel?
Am I dead?
Oh, you're not dead, Gary.
And I'm Gideon.
You're Gideon?
But you're so...
You're so... human.
Are you real?
Well, I could explain,
but it wouldn't matter one bit.
Now, listen to me very carefully
because you have a rather important
job to do.
- I do?
- Yes.
You must hide those very important
and powerful rings
from those evil sisters.
The fate of the world depends on it.
Now, come on, Gary.
It's time to get to work.
Guys, come on. We gotta keep moving
before my sisters
send something else our way.
Well, the engine's busted
after the fight,
and the fuel pump's got no power.
Even if we fix the pump,
all this leaking fluid tells me
this is a lost cause.
- Okay, whoa, whoa, whoa, relax.
- Doesn't...
Remember when we all worked together
to defeat a time demon?
We can make it to London
if we just work together.
All right. How long is it going
to take to fix the engine?
- An hour.
- Maybe two.
To be honest, I don't know anything
about mechanics, so...
All right. We're running out of time.
You live around here.
You must know someone with a car.
- Yeah, I might know a bloke.
- Great.
Wait, Zari.
Shouldn't you stay with us?
You're not immortal.
Look, I can't just sit here
and do nothing.
- What...
- Hey, hey, hey.
- I got her. It's fine.
- Hey, no, no, no.
Where are you guys going?
We're not supposed to split up.
That's not a part of the plan.
Astra, dear, we have been
very patient with you,
especially considering
you betrayed us
without saying a word.
You betrayed me first.
Besides, I had to take my destiny
into my own hands
and try to bring my mother
back myself.
And I appreciate your gumption.
But I'm afraid you don't fully grasp
what that means.
Right now, my mother is dead.
I would like her to be alive.
Fairly simple concept.
But as you know,
life as a human is very difficult.
If you insist on having a normal life
with your mother,
you will be bound
to the rules of nature,
which are not kind to humans.
See for yourself.
Why would you show me that?
Because
that is what is going to happen
if you bring your mother back.
Life as a human is a life of pain
and suffering.
Constantine promised
to bring your mother back
as if it would solve
all your problems.
But what he didn't tell you...
is you're just postponing
the inevitable.
Why bring your mother back,
only to lose her all over again?
Look, I couldn't just sit in that bus
and do nothing.
Oh, I suppose it's good to go
through the motions.
At least it gives you
the illusion of control.
Yeah, I'm not just going through
the motions,
I'm actually doing something
to save my brother.
Yeah, and I was actually
trying to help Astra,
and look what happened there.
You may see no point in trying,
but I'm not giving up.
Have you ever considered
the possibility
that your brother's fate
is doomed in every timeline?
Apparently, this bloke, Rip Hunter,
used to say that,
you know,
certain things are just inevitable.
Go to hell, John.
You know,
I've been there and back, love.
Look, I'm just trying to save you
the disappointment, is all.
You know what?
Let's just walk in silence.
Cool? Cool.
Yeah.
Real smooth, Johnny.
Real smooth.
She's so intriguing.
Gary, she's positively evil.
But she's so talented
with those weird knives.
Well, never mind her
many splendid talents, Gary.
I must ask you to focus,
pay attention now.
Okay,
but how are we gonna distract her
to grab the rings
so she doesn't notice?
I've got an idea.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
What's up?
I really don't think
I should have let John and Zari go.
What if we get the bus up
and running before they get back?
Or even worse, more zombies?
- Then what am I supposed to...
- Hey.
Don't sweat it
if the plan falls apart.
Sometimes, the best solutions come
when there is no plan at all.
Besides,
Legends are all about improvisation.
It's kind of like, free-form jazz.
- I hate free-form jazz.
- Yeah, me too.
Sounds like we have company.
Whoa, I think those are soldiers.
Maybe they can help us get to London.
What did I tell you?
- Oh, hey, guys, hi.
- Hands up!
- Oh, we are so glad you found us.
- Stay where you are.
They've got blood on their clothes.
They might be infected.
- What? No.
- No.
Oh, no. It's not.
No, no, no, we're not infected.
Ava.
Oh, my God.
My God.
These zombies
can withstand headshots.
Since when do zombies talk,
you idiot?
Super zombies have become sentient.
Round them up and take them back
to base camp.
Your hands where I can see them.
Lachesis?
- Yes.
- The rings are gone.
I don't understand.
How could this happen?
There must be someone else
on the ship.
You're right.
Someone else is here.
And I know exactly who it is.
I got the rings.
We make an amazing team.
We should have our own spin-off.
Gideon and Gary
Having adventures
Solving problems
And saving the world
Brilliant song, Gary.
You must teach it to me once
you've managed to wrestle control
of the Waverider
from those pesky sisters.
I know how we can do that.
We'll blow up the ship.
Or, perhaps, we'll do something
just a smidge less suicidal.
Oh, that sounds like fun.
Let's track down a Courier,
so we can jump the rest
of the Legends here.
Well, what are we waiting for?
Let's go to the lab
and make those Couriers ours.
Gary, you're making me blush.
Let's go.
This is charming.
How did you hear about this place?
Back in the day, old man Joe
called me about
a demon-possessed '75 Fiat.
It was a right messy exorcism.
And a right crappy car.
Now, there's a beauty.
All right, come on.
We don't want to be out here
any longer than we have to be.
What was that?
It is not a sound we want to be
waiting around for.
Okay, let's go, this way, go.
Okay, I'll go find the van keys.
Yeah, all right, yeah.
You do that.
Okay.
Thanks, Old Man Joe.
What is that infernal racket?
Are you all right?
Yup. Yeah. I am fine. Just...
Filing this away for future therapy.
Okay.
We better leg it to that chip van
before you become zombie fodder.
John, there's too many of them
out there.
But they're not interested in you.
You need to take the van,
find the team and save Behrad.
No, no, no, that is a terrible idea.
Why, because you didn't think of it?
Because I'm not leaving you here
to die, all right?
That's it.
Oh, now you're good
with leaving me to die?
Yes to death, no to leaving.
You see, there was this spell
that the ancient Egyptians...
I don't need the history lesson,
John, just do it.
Yeah, all right,
but it means stopping your heart.
And when I do that,
we've only got a few minutes
before the rest of you stops.
It's risky and anything can go wrong.
You know what?
This whole day has gone wrong,
so, why stop now?
Why, indeed?
You're making a huge mistake.
What sentient zombies
are this well-dressed?
Damn it. I promised Lita
I would never get locked up again.
This stays between us.
Okay, I am,
I am just gonna make up a speech.
About what? I don't know.
Just made up on the spot.
Ava's lost it, she's lost it.
- She's thinking...
- Okay.
You know what, guys?
We are not wasting any more time
in this tin can.
Let's try to get creative
and think about
- what resources we have.
- Okay.
Look, we've got a guy
who turns into steel.
We've got a shapeshifter, right?
That's friggin' amazing.
We've got a kickass blind assassin.
And a reformed thief
turned romance novelist.
Who you calling reformed?
Oh. Well...
Wait a minute.
I've been locked up in one
of these before.
There's a weak door,
down here somewhere.
Steel boy, punch.
I'd be honored.
Whoa, wait, what, so we're gonna just
jump out of a moving car?
Well, you know, we're not gonna die,
but it's really gonna hurt.
- Okay, who's first?
- You!
- Oh, God!
- Out of here, sucker!
All right, then,
well, come on, step right up.
- You got her?
- Yeah, got her. Yeah.
I'm actually glad I can't see
what's about to happen.
Ready? And jump,
Gravity's actually
not a part of the plan.
Well, Ava,
as far as inspirational speeches go,
- I give that a gentleman's seven.
- You know what?
I will take it because now we are,
80 miles from London, which is,
you know, closer than we were before.
- Yeah.
- We're never gonna make it.
- Hey. Never say "never."
- Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
- Can you help us?
- Let's just out.
Don't stop, Wilbur.
Zombies!
Damn it.
You're giving off a vibe.
Oh, man.
- Come on, babe, we gotta walk.
- I'm coming.
All right, love. Can you give me
a bit of room here, eh?
Sure.
Okay.
If I die,
I can't believe the last thing
I'm gonna see is your face.
Yeah, well, better than those zombies
out there, eh?
Debatable.
Yeah.
All right, love.
Close your eyes now.
Okay.
(Foreign language)
Oh, no, no.
Don't do this to me.
Come on, Zari, come on.
Come on, don't do this.
Come on, come back to me, love.
Come back to me.
Is this what a hangover feels like?
We need to get out of here.
- Got one.
- Smashing job, Gary.
Now, let's go get your friends,
so we can finish this adventure
once and for all.
Easy enough.
Drop it.
She means it.
She'll skin you alive.
What are you doing, Astra?
Why are you working with them?
Now, give us the rings.
We know you have them.
Gideon, run, save yourself!
The moron is speaking to the rabbit.
The rings are in your pocket.
Give them to us.
Gideon?
Help me.
I can't, Gary.
I'm just a figment
of your imagination.
But you must believe in yourself.
And don't give in,
no matter what they do.
How could I give you the rings
if they were never really here?
- Trickery.
- Yeah.
I may have been electrocuted
by Gideon's mainframe,
but I could still do
a simple obfuscation spell.
Time for more persuasive tactics.
Those headlights are coming in fast.
All right, everybody. Just be cool.
Yeah, try to act as un-zombie-like
as possible.
Maybe Mick should stand in the back.
Get in, losers, we're going looming.
Yeah.
Hello?
Ex-Director Sharpe here,
who's manning this post?
Well, cheers to this nightmare
of a day coming to an end soon.
- I'll drink to that.
- Yeah, well,
we're not out of the woods yet, love,
but you can sign me up
for a beer anytime.
Yup, John was right.
We are not out of the woods yet.
Is it dead?
Yeah, how did you know?
Great, that's just great.
My brother's gone forever,
and the world's gonna end
because someone forgot to charge it.
Great.
Smoke break?
Actually...
I quit smoking.
Again.
Don't tell me you finally
found something to live for.
There's no point.
The Fates are literally against us.
I mean, how else do you explain
an overnight zombie apocalypse?
Or the fact that we're now
at the mercy of a charger?
You know, I gotta say, all this doom
and gloom attitude
really don't suit you, love.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize you had
a monopoly on doom and gloom.
No, I'm just saying, you know,
you stick to what you know best,
is all.
Yeah, I'm not gonna take advice
from a professional exorcist
with a savior complex.
Come on,
I do not have a savior complex.
Are you serious right now?
"Oh, save me from my demons,
John Constantine."
Oh, what about you, then? I mean,
you talk about savior complex,
what with all your self-help
and advice videos.
Saving your minions
from a life of drudgery.
I give my followers something
to aspire to.
Aspire to? Really?
What's that, then?
Oh, yeah,
it's being a superficial git.
If you think I'm superficial,
then why are you here with me?
Do you know what,
I don't know, I just think
I haven't had enough punishment
for one day.
Punishment?
You should just go, then. Right now.
You want me to leave?
Because I will leave.
I will go right now
- and not come back.
- Good, great. Leave.
I wouldn't wanna be with you
right now,
if you were the last man on Earth.
Well, good,
because I wouldn't wanna be with you
if you were the last woman...
So, where should we start?
Head, shoulders, knees or toes?
How about none of those things?
You can hand me those rings
or you can give me your hands,
it is that simple.
This isn't you.
You're not like them.
You don't know a thing about me.
I do know that when you had to choose
between staying in hell
or putting your trust in the Legends,
you grabbed Ava's hand
and took a leap of faith.
That was a mistake.
A moment of weakness
when I still believed
I wanted to see my mother.
Wait.
You don't want your mother
to come back anymore?
Not if it means losing her
all over again.
Lachesis opened my eyes
and showed me her death
and what it would be like
if I brought her back.
You actually had to see
your mother die?
Are you okay? Because if I were you,
I'd be a big puddle of...
Of course I am not okay.
It was bad enough losing her
when I was a kid.
But did this Lachesis lady
show you anything else?
Like, what about
all the good moments?
- Before she died.
- Why bother?
Those memories
would be painful reminders
of what I would one day have to lose.
You must have some memories
of your mom
when you were little
that make you smile.
Right?
Well, maybe, instead of torturing me,
you could...
I don't know, share one?
You guys good?
Yeah, feeling a little better.
Wow. Those yams?
Horrible, aren't they?
Look, guys, I know today was...
was rough. I mean...
You got shot in the head,
for Pete's sake.
Do you have to bring that up?
And if I could,
I'd spend every day like this.
Sitting around with my pals.
Well, you could end every day
any way you like
with the Loom of Fate, mate.
You know, after we best your sister,
any one of us might be called
to use the Loom,
and you got to ask the question,
what kind of temptations we'd have?
I'm actually pretty happy just...
flying through time with you guys,
and I got my lady.
I'm pretty happy.
Same.
I'd be a criminal again.
The simple life.
You know, if Behrad were alive
and we were together and happy, I...
I don't know, I would use my talents
to make the world a more...
inclusive, better place, I guess.
Well, I, for one,
would throw a multi-continent rager.
- Would you really, though, John-o?
- I would, yeah.
There's nothing a little deeper...
little closer to your heart?
Oh, you know...
Even after everything
that's happened.
I'd wanna do right by Astra,
you know.
Make sure she was happy growing up
in a big house,
and I could keep an eye on her.
Sure is nice to dream.
I'll drink to that.
- Cheers.
Okay.
What are you not telling me?
Nothing.
Come on.
Let me guess.
You didn't really lose your powers.
Yeah?
You had a vision.
And you saw the future,
and you don't want to tell me
about what happened. Am I right?
The Courier
is not gonna charge in time.
In time for what?
In time to escape
before that front door
gets busted down by what's outside.
Why'd you lie to me, babe?
Because my vision ended
with me dying here.
In this pub.
Sorry, what?
Oh, my God,
I can't really think straight.
- I just...
- It's okay.
This is why I didn't wanna tell you.
I didn't want to distract you
from getting the team to this moment.
Okay, so you have been saying goodbye
and just pushing me
to take over this whole time?
Yes, but it's a temporary goodbye,
all right?
Because you guys,
you're gonna, you're gonna fix this,
and you're gonna save the day.
Did you happen
to have some sort of vision
of how we saved the day, Sara,
because that would be
really helpful right now.
I wish, but, no,
I couldn't see anything past
my death.
That was it.
Okay.
And what if we don't succeed?
I have faith in you, babe.
And I have faith in this team.
And after I go,
you will fix it, I know it.
I don't wanna freak you guys out,
but...
we're completely surrounded
by zombies.
Looks like they're biding their time
until our immortality runs out.
Well, damnees,
the inevitable has arrived.
Kiss your immortality goodbye.
It's strange the memories you hold on
to when someone's gone.
My mom loved strawberries.
And one year we went
strawberry picking at this farm.
And we just ate them
right off the vine.
They didn't even make it
to the basket.
We just spent the whole day
stuffing ourselves.
Sounds like a cool lady.
She was.
Think about all the strawberries
you could pick if you came...
Okay, enough wheedling.
Just show me
how to use this damn thing,
so we can get help
and I can bring her back already.
Okay, yeah.
- So...
- Congratulations.
You're just as weak
as any other human.
Your immortality has run out.
Time's up.
The rings.
Or join your friend on the floor.
We just have to hold out
until the Courier charges.
The door's not gonna hold.
Once they're inside,
I'll hold them off as long as I can.
Sara.
- Co-captains for life.
- Always.
Come on.
The bloody thing's still charging.
Hey, deadheads, over here.
Sara!
It's charged.
Charlie, you have to go.
Deal with your sisters and fix this.
- How?
- You've outsmarted them once before,
you can do it again.
Hey.
Gary.
Charlie, thank God you're here.
Your sisters took over the ship
and they somehow convinced Astra
to work with them,
and then I convinced her
she was wrong,
which is how she ended up
on the floor.
Where's everyone else?
There's no time to explain,
where are the rings?
Okay, yeah.
We have to be careful.
Your sisters were just...
What a pity.
You've come crawling back.
You're just in time, Clotho.
I'm done running.
Now, let's get to work.