Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Well, you really have
buggered everything up this time.
Guys... I think we broke time.
As you can see,
my agents are hard at work,
dealing with these anachronisms
that you created.
Anachronisms?
People, places, and things displaced
from their native time periods.
I am Gaius Julius Caesar of Rome.
I told you, I was leaving
to create an organization
to replace the Time Masters.
Rip doesn't think
he needs us now that
he's got the Time Bureau.
'Cause the Time Bureau
is capable of getting
the job done without the mess.
We're the ones who broke history.
We should be the ones that fix it.
- Problem solved.
- I got to say, Ms. Lance.
Now that I've seen your team
in action with my own eyes...
Howdy.
You are even worse than I imagined.
Don't look!
What are you doing here?
I live here.
What's all this?
What part of "I'm making
your birthday surprise.
Stay out of the apartment"
did you not understand?
I thought you meant
lingerie and, you know, sex.
Not whatever this is.
I'm making donuts...
chocolate-covered donuts...
'cause you said
they were your favorite
when you were little.
You're making them from scratch?
How else would I make them?
You do what my mom
did. You go to the corner store
and you get them for two bucks a box.
Nobody makes anything
from scratch anymore.
So all this was for nothing?
No. Donuts are never for nothing...
and I'm being creative.
I'm sure I can figure out a way
to use that chocolate sauce.
I got it. Don't worry.
No, got it.
All right.
Five-second rule.
We're good. We're good.
I'll make some more.
No, no, no. You are done.
You can't do anything else.
We are doing
the rest of this, 2017-style.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the corner store
to get us chocolate-covered donuts
the way my mom used to buy them.
Tonight's breaking news
Vixen caught on camera.
This video is rare footage of Vixen,
Detroit's own super-heroine,
who has waged a one-person war
against drug dealers
and corrupt cops alike
since she first appeared
in the city three years ago.
All right.
I got all my mom's favorites.
I got chocolate donuts...
crème cake...
Hello?
Amaya.
Hello? Anybody home? McFly?
Sorry, guys. I was just...
I was just thinking about donuts.
Okay, so, where are we?
I was saying, I reverse-engineered
the Time Bureau tech
that Mick stole from Rip.
Now, we can locate anachronisms too.
- Nice work, man.
- Also, check this out.
Our run-in with
Caesar got me thinking.
What if there was a way
to contain the anachronisms
that we pick up
and not have them causing
trouble on the ship
or taking things they shouldn't?
Yeah, that's what
we got the brig for.
Well, what if we have another
LA situation?
Try putting a dinosaur in the brig.
- Not going to happen.
- No.
Unless it's an Aquilops.
- Or a Compsognathus.
- Or a cute little Oviraptor.
Okay, so just...
how do we contain them?
We make it smaller.
You built a shrink ray.
I'm not particularly
fond of that name.
I'm calling
it the hyper-molecular compressor.
It's a more powerful and portable
version of the tech from my suit.
So a shrink ray?
Essentially.
I perfected the work
I was moonlighting on at Upswips.
Nice.
It'll return to normal size
in 24 hours.
Or, if you don't want to wait...
Oh, ho, ho, you are on fire, dude.
All right.
Let's gather the rest of the team
and check out
the new anachronism map.
We really messed up time.
Looks like we gave time acne.
Each of these dots
represents an anachronism
we created by breaking time.
Rip's Bureau rates them
on a scale of one to ten
according to their magnitude
of impact and potential difficulty.
Gideon, can you analyze this data?
Certainly, Dr. Palmer.
Look at all these.
It's going to take a lifetime
to clean up this mess.
Maybe several.
Where should we start?
What about Great Wall of China,
level six?
I had Chinese last night.
Where can I get a steak?
How about the North Atlantic Ocean?
April 1912?
I hear the Titanic had amazing food.
Absolutely not.
I refuse to set foot on the Titanic.
Whoever built that ship
ought to be shot.
Anyways...
I'm sure Little Miss Time Bureau
would love to see us mess this up.
So let's find something easy.
A nice slam dunk.
Oh. Wisconsin, 1870.
It's a level one.
Oh, I do hope you choose that one.
The anachronism is located
at the grounds
of a P.T. Barnum's Roving
Museum of Freaks
and Hypnotic Hippodrome.
Although he is erroneously credited
with the phrase
"There's a sucker born
every minute"...
in truth, Mr. Barnum would
have never
belittled paying customers.
Perfect.
We're bringing the circus
to the circus.
This is a classic slice of Americana.
The air is thick with the smell
of popcorn, candy, and wonder.
If I see a clown, I'm out of here.
What? You afraid of clowns?
No. I...
just don't like their stupid faces
and funny shoes and...
razor-sharp teeth.
Their what?
All right, guys.
If you were an anachronism
hiding in the circus,
where would you be?
How about in there?
King Tut's tomb? No way.
No way indeed.
They covered it in flour
to make it look old.
Bearded lady, hormone imbalance.
Mr. Rory would make
a far more convincing Cro-Magnon.
Marty, you can't look
behind the curtain.
- Spoils the fun.
- Fun?
Tricks and humbug are all I see.
And these uneducated rubes
come here in droves...
begging to be fooled.
No. People want to live in a world
where anything's possible.
They wanna be amazed.
Yes, and amazing as this is,
we're wasting time.
Let's split up.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Welcome, one and all,
to the Best Show On Earth!
That is a working title.
My roving show of wonders
has the most remarkable of oddities
in store for you today.
Is it beautiful?
The very definition.
Is it deadly?
It can take your head
from your shoulders
in a single bite.
What makes this creature
such a marvel
is that it has been extinct
for the last 10,000 years.
Are you guys hearing this?
Could be our anachronism.
Or another humbug.
Check it out, just to be safe.
This exclusive,
once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
could be yours...
for only a nickel.
Yo, what's that smell?
Where there's poop...
There's a prize.
Check it out.
Well, do we have to?
This is definitely feline feces...
but unlike any I've ever seen.
You've studied
a lot of poop, big guy?
As an Eagle Scout, I can interpret
175 different droppings.
The color and viscosity
indicate a carnivorous diet.
But this movement took
a long time to pass.
The meat looks like it was tough...
like a rhinoceros or elephant hide.
I speak of a creature
that comes to you...
from the distant past!
I know what our anachronism is.
Contain it, quick.
We can't let these people
see the anachronism.
We don't want this
to get any worse.
Bingo.
Gentlemen...
may I present to you...
the saber-toothed tiger!
Did I mention that...
I'm allergic to cats?
Please tell me you brought
your shrink ray.
"Molecular hyper-compressor."
And yes.
Ray...
Shrinking a vase
is very different
from shrinking an extinct tiger.
Okay? I have to account
for speed, lifespan...
gender... you think
it's a male or female?
I think it's awake.
Ray, shoot it! Shoot it!
- A few more adjustments...
- Shoot it!
Oh, no.
Are you guys okay?
I heard a roar.
Looks like our problem
got a whole lot bigger.
Let me get this straight.
You three released a giant
saber-toothed tiger.
"Release" isn't the word I'd use.
Yeah, more like...
"didn't contain".
Gideon, what's the status
of the anachronism?
The anachronism has elevated
- from level one to level four.
- What?
How is that even a thing?
We made it worse, that's how.
Okay, so we just get Ray
some allergy medicine
and go back out there.
None of us even have
experience with animals.
Stay on the ship.
Stay out of trouble.
Where the hell's she going?
Hey, girl.
How 'bout one final mission
for old times' sake?
I can't go with you, Sara.
Look, I'm not asking you
to join back up.
Just one, easy mission.
Trapping a giant
saber-toothed tiger is easy?
For you. Your powers
are the quickest way to handle this.
Look. Amaya, I can't
give the Time Bureau an excuse
to take the Waverider again.
I want to help you...
but my life's a little complicated
right now.
Amaya, Amaya! Amaya!
Foyinsola, this is Sara.
Hey. What you got there?
I found it in an acacia tree.
No, please! No!
You should be asleep, little one.
Now run along to bed...
before I have to summon
the ashe of a cobra to scare you!
Normal life. It suits you.
You seem at peace here.
Good-bye, Amaya.
It was good to see you.
Wait.
Does Nathaniel know
that I'd be returning?
Yeah.
He's thrilled.
I raise the pot one...
dishes duty.
All right, Professor.
You sly fox, I will raise you one...
Amaya.
Can't bet what
you've already lost, pretty.
Hello, Nathaniel.
Amaya!
Hey, what's good, girl?
Come on. How you been?
I missed you.
- Hello.
- Professor Stein.
Ship's not the same without you.
But we're fine without you.
Everything is running smoothly.
Is that right?
Haircut here
"embiggened" an extinct tiger.
Which Amaya and I
are going to catch.
And then I have to return to Zambesi.
We're going to need your
shrink ray, Ray.
Well, I... I thought we talked
about... not calling it that.
And don't you need the rest of us?
- We can handle it.
- Really?
You don't want us to come along
and mess things up?
Enjoy your night.
You didn't tell Nathaniel, did you?
It's cool.
This is so not cool.
First, Amaya ghosts on me
on my birthday.
No heads-up.
Then she shows back up
on the ship
again, no heads-up.
Bro... she's from 1942.
Did you really think
that was going to work?
Nah, but we were happy.
What happened?
I don't know,
but instead of drinking,
maybe you should go find out.
No.
She didn't want to talk then.
Why would she want to talk now?
And look...
I don't want to sound like a jerk...
but she kind of let herself go.
Yeah, you keep telling
yourself that, buddy.
The tiger's heading east.
It looks like he stopped here
to sharpen his claws.
Don't tell me the infamous Sara Lance
is scared of a big cat.
Giant tiger.
Don't worry.
To animals, humans are the predators.
Even to other humans.
Whatever you do, don't run.
I spent my last greenback
on that feline oddity.
Circus is shutting down.
You know I'd rather die
before going back to Salem, Phineas.
There's some small-minded
folk back there.
Small-minded folk everywhere.
Even the most retrograde ingrate
wants to be entertained.
The human spirit, it longs
for edification and delight.
We just need a show-stopper
to edify and delight them.
- Are you on Upswips?
- Yeah.
Connected through the Waverider.
This is Cindy.
- 5'9". Profession: weather reporter.
- Okay.
Loves kale.
Says she wants to meet up.
That's nice.
"Do... you...
Have a time machine?"
Just talk to Amaya.
That's what Jax said. Wait.
Are you two conspi...
Are you conspiring against me?
Hey, hey, hey!
Hey! You owe the lady an apology.
That's not a lady.
That's a freak.
Are you trying to
pick a fight with me?
Because I would love
to get into a fight right now.
If she's a freak, what am I?
That was marvelous!
A round of drinks, on me!
It's... actually,
it's time for us to be going.
No, no, come on,
hey, we just met. Please.
Oh, you got to tell me.
Where did you learn
a humbug like that?
Well, that's no humbug,
P to the T.
You see, people like us,
we got to stick together.
And by the way,
your beard... it's beautiful.
- You're so sweet.
- She said I'm sweet.
I'm sorry, "people like us"?
Yeah. My friend Jax here
turns to fire and flies.
No, no, that's...
that's just the whiskey talking.
Right, buddy?
No, it's true. And my friend Ray
here turns teeny-weeny.
Teeny-weeny.
That's very funny, Nate.
Also, they're both capable of flight.
Yeah. But if you want to know
a real freak, P.T.,
it's my ex-girlfriend.
She can summon the power
of any animal.
Is that right?
I have an idea, fellas.
How 'bout we meet...
retire back to the circus...
for a little private show
where I guarantee I've got
the most beautiful and flexible
acrobats you've ever seen?
P.T. Barnum, you're on.
You had me at "circus".
Shouldn't you ashe up?
No, no, that'll just provoke him.
Move downwind.
I'll distract and you shrink.
Easy.
I'm not here to hurt you.
It's kind of cute.
Well, I'm glad Nate
finally took our advice
and went to talk to Amaya.
Yeah, true. But man,
he is about to miss out.
I thought we needed the tin man.
In due time.
We have his friends.
Oh, smile, Hildy.
We just might save the circus yet.
Hey, sunshine!
What are you doing in my room?
Oh, this is not my room.
Where are Jax and Ray?
Yelling.
I'm going to die. I don't remember.
What's the last thing
that you do remember?
Oh. Whiskey.
So...
So what's...
It's all...
it's all coming back to me.
We were headed to a circus
for a private show.
And then what?
You decided to peel off
and sleep in the cargo bay?
How could you abandon
your own team?
Oh, you... you're one to talk.
All right, let's stop wasting time.
Let's go.
The loss of my saber-toothed tiger
was indeed a blow.
But the fates have smiled
on me again.
Because the "God of Fire"
and "The Incredible Shrinking Man"
have joined my troupe.
I think we've had a...
slight misunderstanding.
And I am truly grateful
that you have not used
your special abilities
to try to escape.
"Special abilities"? Man...
like I told you before...
that was just the liquor talking.
He's right. Okay?
My friend and I, we're just regular
plain, old folk from 1870.
Dishonesty is not
your strong suit, my good man.
I saw what your friend did.
That was no trick.
And he says you two...
are capable of wonders
just as marvelous.
So...
chop-chop.
Don't be shy.
We can't.
- Oh, poppycock.
- But he's right.
He can't fire up without his partner,
who's not here.
And I can't shrink
without my exo-suit.
Also not here.
So you might as well just let us go
'cause we are obviously useless.
Totally useless.
Don't worry.
I'll make marvels out of you yet.
You said Ray and Jax
would be here.
They're probably eating
breakfast sandwiches
and eating a handful of aspirin.
Or, maybe they're in trouble.
Here?
This place is harmless.
Then why are we being watched?
Guy in the hat, 6.00 o'clock?
That guy?
Gary?
Nice work, Nathaniel.
What, you think I spooked him?
The smell of your breath
alone would be enough.
You know what?
You don't get to criticize me.
And you know why?
Because you're no longer
a member of this team.
You're right.
I am?
I don't blame you for going out
and getting pie-eyed last night.
That's cool. I don't blame you
for saying "pie-eyed".
My point is...
Sara should have told you
that she was bringing me back
from Zambesi.
It must have been upsetting
when I just...
Whoa, whoa, hang on.
You think last night
was because of you?
Oh, my God. Amaya,
you are so conceited.
Last night wasn't
even remotely about you.
- At all.
- What was it about?
It was about me and the boys
doing what we do.
Hanging out. Sharing a few laughs.
Having a few drinks.
Ending up in a freak show.
You like meat, huh?
Yeah, all right.
There we go.
Come back here,
you little rat bastard!
I don't understand.
Who is this man and why
have we taken him prisoner?
Professor Stein, meet Gary.
Please don't kill me.
I won't, if you tell us
why you were tailing us.
- You two know each other?
- Gary here
works for Rip's Time Bureau.
And I'm guessing Agent Sharpe
had her little stooge spying on us.
Isn't that right, Gary?
Well, I'm not at liberty
to discuss the nature of my...
All right, yes!
Oh, she sent me to spy on you.
Good thing, too.
Since you arrived here,
the anachronism has jumped
from a level one to a level six.
We found the saber-tooth
and it is safe and sound in its cage.
So, I don't know how we could have
made the anachronism worse.
My guess is we can thank
our two missing teammates for that.
Nate, Amaya.
Please tell me
you found the Hardy Boys.
Let's just hope
they had the good sense
to stick together.
Oh, they're stuck together,
all right.
P.T. Barnum has them dressed
as conjoined twins.
Guys, get us out of here.
Man, I thought I had a rough night.
- Not funny, Nate.
- Yeah, come on.
This harness is really uncomfortable.
Okay. I got this.
I must be dehydrated, man.
This never happened
to me before, I swear.
Where have I heard that one before?
Not from me.
She never heard that from me.
Amaya, an elephant actually would
come in really handy right now.
Well.
Look who joined the circus.
We're gonna need a bigger tent.
I take it you're still too dehydrated
to get us out of here.
Oh, God...
Just stop judging me
and just summon your animal powers.
Believe me, you do not
want me using this totem right now.
What does that mean?
I'm sorry, Nathaniel.
For what? For not using your powers
or ditching me on my birthday
to hitch a ride back to Zambesi?
I didn't go to Zambesi.
Not right away.
First, I went to Detroit.
Detroit.
I had to see her in person.
Mari. My granddaughter.
I had to see if she was
as incredible as people said she was.
I watched her save
five people in one night.
She never knew I was there.
But, I knew that she was perfect.
I know it doesn't help...
but, my decision to leave
had nothing to do with you.
You're right. It doesn't.
'Cause if your badass granddaughter
was in 2017, why'd you
have to go back to 1942?
I asked Rip the same question.
He said that time
hadn't yet solidified.
But if I stayed too long in 2017...
then Mari would disappear.
Why didn't you say anything?
I hated you for what you did.
I needed you to hate me...
so that you would move on.
If you knew how much it hurt me...
I would've found you.
I wanted to protect
my granddaughter.
And I wanted to protect you.
Well, no offense, Amaya.
But considering we're both
stuck in a rhino cage,
I say your plan backfired.
This is agent 1-0-6-6.
You failed to turn in
your status report, Gary.
And then, you ignored
my attempts to contact you.
And somehow, during all of that,
the level one has escalated.
To a level eight.
And where the hell are you?
Is that the Waverider?
I told you
to keep an eye on the Legends,
not to join them.
Turns out...
the Legends had things under control.
Oh, it was my interference
with their, to be honest, expert
handling of the situation
which caused things to, well...
escalate.
Gary, if you are in over your head,
I can send backup immediately.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no backup.
Oh, like I said...
the Legends
have things under control.
Oh, nice chatting.
- Got to go.
- Gar...
- How'd I do?
- You were great.
I sense that Jefferson
is extremely nervous.
Don't worry.
We just have to rescue the team
and get back on the ship
before that saber-tooth "embiggens".
At least we know why
the scale of the anachronism
keeps climbing...
P.T. Barnum with real superheroes.
He'll expose Nate and Amaya
to the entire world.
I'm detecting increased
chronometric interference, Captain.
Agent Sharpe has boarded
the Waverider.
Get Rory.
You two have to save the others.
Wait, wait. The two of us?
Are you mad?
You can do this.
- I have faith in you.
- Why?
Oh, just go!
I'll hold her off as long as I can.
Sara Lance.
On behalf of the Time Bureau,
I am placing you and your team
under arrest.
Took you long enough.
I've been expecting you for hours.
Pursuant to title 16, section 3053,
of the Global Treaty on Time Travel,
I have the authority
to bring you and your team in.
Which arm?
The Global Treaty was negotiated
between Director Hunter
and the United Nations.
No, I mean...
if you try to bring me
in to the Bureau...
I'll break your arm.
It's up to you. Right or left?
Your threats may work on
Confederate zombies,
Quentin Turnbull's cronies,
and speedsters,
but you don't scare me.
I've spent the last five years
watching your screw-ups.
I know everything about you.
Now, where is the member of my team
- that you've taken hostage?
- You mean Gary?
This ship is probably like a vacation
after having to answer to you.
Last chance.
Come quietly, and I'll make sure
you get your job back
at Sink, Shower, & Stuff.
When did a Legend ever go quietly?
What are you looking at?
Clowns...
Get a grip, man!
We're already down
four members of our team.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to the Greatest
Show On The Planet!
My roving museum of freaks
and hypnotic hippodrome
has traveled this great nation.
And, I must say, I have never seen
quite a good-looking and, dare I say,
astute audience
as the one gathered
before me here today.
But a word of warning
before we begin.
For the jaw-dropping spectacle
that you are about to see
is not for the faint of heart.
May I now present you
Yin and Yang.
The wondrous and world-renowned
Siamese twins.
Oh, my God.
A miracle of Biblical proportions.
One mother, two fathers.
I'm not judging.
Both sons capable
of amazing strength,
intelligence, and coordination.
So juggle.
You need to create a diversion
so we can get past those thugs
and merge with Jefferson.
You're on your own,
Professor. Clowns.
Don't leave...
Now what?
So, you ready for your debut?
Kiss my ass.
Don't have time to convince you
of the creative joys
and lucrative appeal
of being my show-stopper.
Those hayseeds out there
are going to burn my circus down
if we don't give them
their money's worth.
Let me make it very simple for you.
Become the "Man of Steel"...
that is very catchy,
make a note of that...
or get shot.
I don't respond well to threats.
- Nathaniel...
- No.
I'm not one of your freaks.
Would you steel up for her?
Fine. I'll do it.
Rip should have recruited you
to the Time Bureau.
Rip knows I'd never leave the team.
Your mistake.
You want to take a break?
- I could use some water.
- Yeah.
Hope that thing's potty-trained.
Probably not. Cats are jerks.
Let me guess.
You're a dog person.
I like them dumb and loyal.
Speaking of, we should
probably check on Gary.
Whatever you do...
don't...
Run.
Where did you get a Time Courier?
Oh, would someone mind untying me?
That is stolen government property.
It's just that I have
really bad circulation.
You're just mad
'cause I saved your life, again.
Captain Lance. I hate to interrupt.
But I thought you'd like to know
that the anachronism
has reached a level nine.
My team's on it.
And if they fail,
maybe Rip will finally give up
on the ridiculous belief
that your team
could actually defeat...
You know what?
He's going to take your ship
away, Ms. Lance.
Again.
Oh, no.
Son of a gun, it worked.
You really are quite marvelous.
No more.
- No more.
- Oh, come on. One more.
Take care of that.
Gordy!
Hey!
Die, clown!
Mr. Rory, a little help here.
Balloon animals, Grey? Really?
The applause
might have gone to my head.
This is amazing!
Guys, Amaya looks like
she's going to kill him.
Wow.
Stop her, Jefferson!
Amaya, no!
Amaya, no, no, no.
No, no, hey, hey,
hey, you can fight whatever this is.
You're Amaya Jiwe.
You're a member of the
Justice Society of America.
You're the most courageous
person I know.
That totem
makes you a protector, not a killer.
Amaya.
Come back to me.
Sorry.
- Nate.
- I'm right here.
I'm right here.
I got you.
And that's a grand finale, folks.
I told you it wasn't
for the faint of heart.
We had it all.
We had action.
We... we have romance.
We had flaming things in the sky.
You wait until next week's show.
Well, Mr. Sneezums
is now a more manageable size.
- Mr. Sneezums?
- Yeah. You like it?
The most important thing
is we put on one hell of a show
and Grey now loves the circus.
- I don't believe you.
- Oh, it's true.
He now thinks
that without the circus,
the world has lost one
of its last true places of wonder.
I mean, I don't believe that
the anachronism has been dealt with.
Believe it, Agent Sharpe.
As I've already communicated
to Director Bennett,
1870 Wisconsin is anachronism- free.
Oh, even our AI doesn't like you.
Yep. My foot is definitely asleep.
- Gary...
- And my leg.
- Could be permanent.
- Wait. Who is this guy?
That's Gary. Can you give him a hand?
I need to speak with you.
In private.
Your sister, I presume?
And our friend Oliver.
So.
I suppose congratulations
are in order.
You get to keep your ship,
for now, but...
You will be watching us. Yes, yes.
I've heard this before,
so why don't you cut the crap
and tell me what we're facing here?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You said,
"that Rip will finally give up
"his ridiculous belief
that your team could actually..."
and then you stopped yourself.
So let's have it.
Who are we facing?
That information is need-to-know.
And all you need to know is that you
and your "ridiculous" team
could never handle it.
Aren't you forgetting something?
Gary.
Hey.
Do you want to talk
about what happened back there?
Not especially.
Look, it might help.
I'm glad you and I talked
about why you left me and...
- it made me feel better.
- It did?
A little.
In that case, I think the whole team
deserves to hear this.
It... it started a month ago.
Whenever I would tap into my powers,
I could feel myself losing control.
as if the animal was
in charge, not me.
One day,
Belgian soldiers came to my village.
I told them that Zambesi
was under my protection.
And when they attacked,
I killed them all.
Well, sounds like
you didn't have a choice.
No, you don't understand.
These soldiers were just boys.
When they tried to run,
I hunted them down
one by one by one
and I ripped them to shreds.
That's the real reason
you came back.
I needed a place to think.
This...
this totem is my birthright
and my sacred duty.
Something's terribly wrong.
What if I lose control
around my village?
I'm sorry. I...
I wanted to tell you...
all of you but, I was too ashamed.
Well, we've all done things
we're not proud of.
Except Haircut.
Well, no, actually...
I'm actually really bad
at returning library books.
I can't go home.
Not yet, but I'm not sure
that I can stay here either.
You saw me earlier.
You could all be in danger.
You are one of us.
Maybe now more than ever.
We'd be crazy to let you go.
Besides, we're really going
to need your help now.
We got a new problem.
Rip has been hiding something
from us.
There's a greater evil coming.
Something even the Time Bureau
is afraid of.
What can be worse
than an immortal Egyptian demigod?
Or an evil speedster?
Well, I'm afraid
of the time boogeyman.
I'm literally crying.
Welcome back, Kuasa.
Who are you?
A follower of Mallus.
And we have work to do.