RORY: Seriously, you idiots
haven't figured this out by now?
It all started when we blew up
the time pigs, the Time Masters.
Now, history's all screwed up...
And it's up to us to unscrew it up.
But half the time
we screw things up even worse.
So don't call us heroes.
We're something else.
We're Legends.
RAY:
Previously, on Legends of Tomorrow...
DR. HEYWOOD: You're my grandfather.
You're more than that.
You're a hero to me.
My quarters. Tonight.
I'll give you something else
to think about.
RAY: You can't date Amaya.
She has a destiny.
And so do her descendants.
Have either of you gentlemen
heard of the Spear of Destiny?
COURTNEY: The Spear
could alter reality itself.
Who's coming for you?
It's not a who. It's a what.
And it's trying to kill me.
DR. HEYWOOD: He has to keep moving
in order for his own nonexistence
not to catch up with him.
PROFESSOR STEIN: Captain Hunter
is the only one who can tell us
where Commander Steel
and the final piece of the Spear is.
- Where am I?
- PROFESSOR STEIN: You're home.
So, I've been told you were bumped up
to the prime crew for Apollo 13.
Yeah, man.
We'll see about that.
Welcome to Manhattan, 1965.
I have been dropped off behind enemy lines
in cities all over the world.
Never been dropped off in the future.
RIP: Now, you have to disappear,
start a whole new life.
The Spear of Destiny
must be protected at all costs.
Roger that, sir.
I know this mission won't be easy,
Commander Heywood.
For me, or for Bettie?
She'll think I died in Leipzig.
Little Hank is barely a month old.
Your family's sacrifice
might just save the world.
Give this to my wife and son.
Godspeed, Henry.
DR. HEYWOOD: I don't see him.
Yeah, that is odd.
I dropped him off right here a moment ago.
Where could he have gone? Henry.
- Oh, I'm sorry, my mistake.
- Where is he?
AMAYA: We used to call Henry
"the Chameleon."
He speaks seven languages like a local
and is a master in the art of camouflage
and concealment.
If you told him to disappear,
that's exactly what he did.
Don't worry. If it's hard for us
to find your grandfather,
it's hard for the Legion.
1965 was a bust.
RAY: Ah, sorry, buddy.
That's all right. Rip said he dropped
my grandfather off in 1965 New York,
and told him to assume a new identity.
- Well, he'd need to find work.
- RORY: Why?
Henry was a military man.
He wouldn't have become an accountant.
He would have wanted a job
that still offered adventure,
and yet was still somehow patriotic.
FBI? CIA?
He was a fighter pilot before
he was recruited by the JSA.
In the '60s, the fledgling National
Aeronautics and Space Administration
used to call upon test pilots
to apply to be astronauts.
Exactly. What could be more patriotic,
more adventurous than exploring space?
Nice. Gideon, pull up anything you can,
press clippings, newspaper articles,
re: NASA circa 1965.
GIDEON: Certainly, Captain.
Okay, okay, okay. Come on, come on...
Wait. Wait. Stop. Stop. Right there.
I'd recognize
that Heywood jaw line anywhere.
"April 13th, 1970.
Mission Control works to save Apollo 13."
Come on, could your grandfather
get any cooler?
I think I may have found a way
to track Commander Heywood.
Don't worry, Mr. Hunter.
We've already found him.
- You did?
- We're heading to Houston, 1970.
Ah, all of us to the Astrodome.
And then we're gonna rescue
my grandfather.
Then all of us.
We still need to figure out a way
of contacting Commander Heywood
without arousing suspicion.
- To that end, I suggest that we...
- SARA: It's simple.
We infiltrate NASA.
Today, NASA flight controllers
are monitoring Apollo 13,
NASA's seventh manned mission to the Moon.
We need to figure out a way
to get into Mission Control.
I don't think that's included in the tour.
RIP: Commander Heywood
is not at Mission Control.
How do you know that?
Because I'm looking right at him.
That's the Flight Director of NASA.
They're probably debating on
how to talk to the press
about the oxygen tank explosion
on Apollo 13.
Henry.
Great to see you.
You son of a bitch.
Sorry, folks.
He doesn't have the right credentials.
We take press access
very seriously around here.
Surprise.
We're back.
RIP: Why are you doing this, Henry?
I was never supposed to see him again.
So you punched him?
That's between him and me.
Now, what brings you to 1970?
Er, well, I suppose Nate
should probably tell you.
- Nathaniel's here, too?
- MAN: Sir,
they say they know you.
You could say that.
- Henry.
- Amaya.
As I live and breathe.
It's good to see you again, son.
Come here, man.
I thought I'd never see you again.
Look at you. You still got it.
Is that Rip?
Get him out of there.
As soon as one of you explains
what in tarnation is going on.
Er, we're here for your fragment
of the Spear of Destiny.
See, there's a Legion of villains who are
hunting anyone who's trying to protect it.
We have Stargirl's fragment,
but Mid-Nite died trying to protect his.
I appreciate your concern,
but I hid my piece of the Spear
somewhere safe.
Believe me, there's no place on Earth
safe from these guys.
Exactly.
You old fox, you.
You wanna clue us in?
He hid the Spear
in the flag Neil Armstrong
planted on the Moon.
Well, that is pretty ingenious.
The whole reason
I worked my way up through NASA
was to make sure that my piece
of the Spear remains safe.
Speaking of, I really should be
getting back to Mission Control.
Yeah, I guess you've gotta figure out
how to save the Apollo 13 astronauts.
What are you talking about?
The mission is textbook.
Didn't an oxygen tank explode
and the Moon landing get aborted?
No. Everything is going great up there.
Unless...
Unless
history's changed.
Houston, we're about to enter
the dark side of the Moon.
Loss of signal in 30 seconds.
MAN: Roger that,
Odyssey. See you in 28 minutes.
Happy sailing.
Over and out.
Time to sit back
and enjoy the view, fellas.
Sorry, fellas.
Change of plans.
We have to intercept Apollo 13
before it lands on the Moon.
But where's Commander Heywood?
He and I need to have a little chat.
He's introducing the rest of the team
to the Flight Director.
Interesting, why?
Because we need somebody monitoring
on the ground.
- These are flight controllers?
- Yes.
They're with the British Space Program.
They're here to study our procedures.
What's your area of expertise?
I'm a Booster Systems Engineer.
They call me the Rocket Man.
MAN: And him?
Uh, he's a man of few words,
but makes up for it with personality.
All right, fine.
But if any of you Brits
get in the way of my controllers
or jeopardize the safe return
of our astronauts, you'll answer to me.
Of course.
- All right. Good luck, fellas.
- You're not sticking around?
We might need you to run
a little more interference for us.
No can do.
I gave up my life for that Spear,
and I'll be damned
if I let anyone steal it now.
I'm going with my grandson to space.
Would you look at that?
Outer space. Never gets old.
Martin, how much longer before Apollo 13
should reestablish radio contact?
Seventeen minutes.
All right. We've got 17 minutes
to figure out what's going on
before the whole world is watching.
Yeah, you're not wrong there.
Gideon, pull up Apollo 13's
original flight pattern.
We need to find her first.
Uh, Henry, perhaps now
would be a good time to have a chat?
Actually, Captain Hunter,
I don't feel much like talking.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
You know, in 2017,
men share their feelings.
I'm just saying.
My wife has spent the past 14 years
raising our son by herself.
And it is Captain Hunter's fault.
The man has a wife and son
and still he asked me to abandon mine.
He doesn't have a family.
I mean, he did. It's just...
They were killed.
I... I didn't know.
You know, I often wonder what
Hank would be like if you hadn't left.
Yeah, I call my dad Hank.
We don't have the best relationship.
But I don't need to tell you all that.
I'm sorry, Nathaniel.
This is all my fault.
But once this is over, I'm getting
Captain Hunter to take me back to 1956,
to the day I abandoned Bettie and Hank.
Wait, I was...
I was just talking hypothetically.
Why?
I mean, this is a time ship, isn't it?
It'll be like
I never left my wife and son.
Think of all the heartbreak
I can save them.
DR. HEYWOOD: Huh.
I never thought of it that way.
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but we found Apollo 13.
Well, this isn't right. The spacecraft
shouldn't be in this position.
- Can the astronauts see us?
- RIP: No, no, no, we're cloaked.
What's our plan?
- Well, I thought we'd...
- All right, I've got Ray suiting up.
He's gonna fly over there, shrink down,
and let us know what's going on inside.
ATOM:
I'm entering the Command Module.
I see Lovell and Haise,
but they're unconscious.
DR. HEYWOOD: What about Jack?
Dr. Palmer?
ATOM: Thawne's here.
I'm gonna follow him
into the Lunar Module.
He's going to land on the Moon.
ATOM: Well, I'll stop him.
Who's Thawne? Where's Swigert?
Ray, whatever you do,
just don't let Thawne see you.
Yeah, about that.
Well, what do we have here?
Looks like a stowaway.
PROFESSOR STEIN:
What's happening?
NASA expects radio contact
in three minutes.
We ran into a problem.
If we come back online,
you're gonna have to cut the feed.
Yeah, I'm on it.
He doesn't have superspeed
without gravity.
Newsflash, Raymond,
I don't need superspeed to kick your ass.
What's the red button?
It separates the LEM
from the Command Module.
That's no good.
Dr. Palmer, you're gonna
have to fly the LEM.
Houston, we have a problem.
Yeah, tell me something I don't know.
Jefferson, the entire world is about
to listen to Raymond crash on the Moon.
Wait, Haircut's on the Moon?
Guys, I'm gonna need more time.
I need you to create a distraction.
♪ Day-o ♪
♪ Daylight come and me wan' go home ♪
♪ Day, me say day, ♪
♪ me say day, me say day ♪
♪ Me say day, me say day-o ♪
Everybody.
♪ BOTH: ♪
♪ Daylight come and me wan' go home ♪
♪ Work all night on a drink of rum ♪
♪ Stack banana till de morning come ♪
♪ Daylight come and me wan' go home ♪
♪ Come, Mister tally man, tally me banana ♪
♪ Lift six foot, seven foot, ♪
♪ eight foot bunch... ♪
What the hell are you two playing at?
Okay. I got it. I cut the feed.
Oh, it's, uh...
It's a British tradition, sir.
Flight, I had radio contact for a second
then I lost it again.
- Nice voice, Professor.
- Thank you very much.
- Guidance?
- It was the darndest thing.
The LEM appeared for a second,
but it looked like it was about to crash
on the lunar surface.
Where the hell is the Command Module?
It's spinning off course.
Ray, are you all right?
I'm alive at least.
I was able to salvage the descent,
but it burned up too much fuel.
There's no way the LEM
will launch into space.
What about your suit?
RAY: My thrusters were damaged
in the fight.
You guys are gonna have to pick me up.
NASA must be going berserk right now.
Fred and Jim.
Don't worry. We're gonna get Apollo 13
home in one piece.
Gideon, plot a course
for the Command Module.
GIDEON: Right away, Captain.
- Ray, we'll pick you up later.
- RAY: Roger that.
We landed near the Sea of Tranquility.
So I'm going to head out and retrieve
Commander Heywood's piece of the Spear.
Which is, needless to say, very exciting.
- Good luck, big guy.
- What about Mr. Thawne?
He's a little tied up at the moment.
Puns. The lowest form of humor.
- Can I talk to you?
- About what?
I overheard you and Henry talking about
returning him to 1956.
Okay, look, I know what you're gonna say.
That you're a historian
as well as a Legend.
You know the consequences
of returning Henry to the timeline.
Yeah. My dad grows up with a father.
Look, my childhood was miserable.
My dad was a cold, disconnected jackass.
But maybe, just maybe,
returning Henry to that time
can change everything.
This is my chance to fix
three generations of Heywood men.
But you don't need fixing.
Your childhood made you
into the man that you are,
the person that you are today.
And without that man, then,
well, this ship would probably still be
stuck on the bottom of the Atlantic Ocean.
That's conjecture.
My grandfather's happiness,
my father's happiness. That's real.
GIDEON: Excuse the interruption.
But you might want to brace for impact.
Good news, we found the Command Module.
Bad news, it's headed straight
for a bunch of space rocks.
Meteoroid belt.
Don't we have a tractor beam?
Can't we pull the Command Module
away from the meteorites?
No, the velocity of the Command Module
would merely bring us
closer to the meteoroids.
Which is why I'm swinging the ship around.
I'm gonna try and stop the trajectory
of the Command Module.
Sara, you need to abort.
We're going to hit the meteoroids.
Better us than the Command Module.
Could you at least
try to destroy the meteoroids,
rather than using my ship
as a human shield.
Worked before.
Back in 1942, you put the Waverider
in front of a nuke
and it absorbed the blast.
Well, at least I had the decency
to time-scatter you all first.
Decency? Did you ask any of us
if we wanted to be time-scattered?
- Sara.
- I was trying to save your lives.
You put me in a time period where
they wanted to hang me for being a witch.
Sara.
GIDEON: Shield integrity at 63%.
34%.
Rerouting the reserve power
to the shields.
I'm afraid the Jumpship
has been critically impaired.
Oh, dear.
Our landing gear has...
We're clear.
Waverider crew, we are now
the proud owners
of the last fragment
of the Spear of Destiny.
SARA: Copy.
"Copy"? That's all I get is a "Copy"?
Guys, I'm standing on the freaking Moon.
Yeah, about that...
The, uh, the Waverider has sustained
major damage, Dr. Palmer.
Same for the Jumpship.
Wait, the Jumpship? But that means...
Unless you can figure out a way
to launch the LEM,
you're stranded on the Moon.
RAY: And now I know
how Matt Damon felt.
I'm Dr. Raymond Palmer.
Time traveler, superhero,
and most recently, astronaut.
It's April 13th, 1970, at 2200 hours,
and I am stranded on the Moon.
Fuel on the LEM is close to zero,
the food and water provisions
were designed to last days, not months.
So, yeah.
I'm gonna have to science
the... out of this.
EOBARD: What are you doing?
I'm, uh, filming us for posterity,
in case we don't make it back.
I'm not dying on the Moon. All right?
Signing off.
Certainly not doing it in a tin can
with the likes of you.
And to that end, I propose an alliance.
You untie me and we'll figure out a way
to get ourselves off this rock.
And I'll play nice
until we get back to Earth,
- I promise.
- Yeah.
Not a chance.
And for your information,
I already have a plan.
All I've to do is transfer the fuel source
from my exo-suit to power the fuel cells.
Use the dwarf star to power the LEM.
Yeah, that should work.
Of course you've taken the gas
spectrometer into account.
Well, unless you adjust for
the relative volatility of the dwarf star,
then the LEM could explode mid-launch.
I'm a scientist from the future,
and I'm here to tell you
this is a two-person patch job.
Look at it this way.
If I'm lying, we're both dead.
We'll be over Ray's launch position
in 18 minutes.
We only get one chance at this intercept
before the Moon's gravity
slingshots us back to Earth.
Henry?
You need to understand
how time travel works.
My grandfather understands it just fine.
- You can't return to 1956.
- Amaya...
Why?
Every time we change history,
we create what we call an aberration.
Now, if your son grows up with you around,
he could become
an entirely different person.
Choose a different life.
That in turn, could change Nathaniel,
and the person he becomes,
if he's even born at all.
She doesn't know that.
But it's a possibility.
Yes.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because my dad needs you.
And as much as I want to protect history,
I want to protect our family more.
We both should have learned by now
the mission comes first.
Thank you for telling me.
I was just trying to protect you.
Nathaniel, changing your family's history
would have changed you.
In case I haven't made it clear,
I like who you are.
You and I don't have a future together.
What do you mean?
When you stowed aboard the Waverider,
we pulled you from the timeline.
Back in 1942,
you have a destiny waiting for you.
- How do you know all this?
- Ray told me.
He knows your granddaughter.
I don't think I should be hearing this.
Ask Ray what happens to your village.
Ask him what happens to your daughter
and your granddaughter.
Then tell me...
Tell me you'll choose history
over your own family.
That offer to clear the air still good?
So long as it doesn't involve
punching me in the jaw again.
I'm sorry about that.
After five years, I found myself
blaming you for the choice I made.
Turns out that abandoning my wife and son,
even to save the world,
was a mistake.
Ah, it's the great irony of time travel.
But despite it, we still find ourselves
living with regret.
One of mine was that I couldn't find
a better way to protect the Spear.
One that would have
spared you such a personal sacrifice.
When you showed up,
I thought maybe I could go back...
Change history.
But what's done is done.
All we can do now is look forward.
Oh, I got to say,
you really turned this team around.
When I met the Legends in 1942,
they were constantly bickering,
unable to work together
in any cohesive way.
Actually, I'm not the one
who deserves your praise.
Menial labor without superspeed
is really quite tedious.
Then again, I've missed
working with a fellow scientist.
Cisco and Caitlin and I, as you know,
worked together for some time, and...
I miss the camaraderie.
Legion of Doom
doesn't have "Karaoke Fridays"?
I know it's easier for you
to think of me as a monster, but, um...
I've met some of
history's monsters, Raymond.
And believe me,
I'm not one of them.
You killed Barry's mother. Twice.
Rex Tyler?
Brainwashed Rip
into killing Dr. Mid-Nite...
Time travel has a way
of revealing the truth to you.
And you and I
have more in common than you think.
Pass me the pliers.
We're both scientists.
We're both obsessed
with achieving the impossible.
You've dedicated your life to learning
how to shrink yourself
down to the size of an atom,
and I spent mine learning
the secrets of the Speed Force.
I became the Atom to help people.
You could use the dwarf star
in your exo-suit to power an entire city,
but instead, you chose to become the Atom
because you weren't satisfied
with your small, pathetic life.
There is no shame in wanting
to be greater, to reach higher,
to walk on the Moon.
Is that why you want the Spear?
Reach higher? Become greater?
Run faster?
No.
I'm after something much more
elemental.
I want to live.
Surely you can sympathize.
PROFESSOR STEIN:
One minute to the intercept, Raymond.
Are you ready up there?
Yeah, we're ready.
- "We?"
- Long story. Let's do this.
Rip, how's our trajectory looking?
Keep her steady.
Martin, you sure about these calculations?
I'm piloting manually, here.
Did I, or did I not win six Carlins?
- No.
- Yes, I did.
Twenty seconds to intercept.
Jax, be prepared to restore the feed
on my signal.
Ten seconds.
You're just gonna have to trust me.
PROFESSOR STEIN: In three, two, one...
Distance to target, 100 meters.
And closing fast.
Intercept successful.
Mmm! You, ma'am,
are a steely-eyed missile man.
I'll take that as a compliment.
Ray, I'm gonna dock with the LEM.
Be prepared
to get your ass back on the ship.
RAY: Copy.
Head up, son. We've got work to do.
I'm sorry, sir, but they're just
gone.
SARA: Tractor beam disengaged.
Apollo 13 is headed home.
Jax, restore the feed.
Let's get history back on track.
MAN: Odyssey, this is Houston.
Do you read us?
Come in, Odyssey.
Odyssey, this is Houston.
Houston, this is Odyssey. Do you read me?
I repeat, do you read me?
We read you, Odyssey.
Loud and clear.
You don't seem happy, Professor.
The intercept might have been a success,
but the Waverider is on reserve power.
Not to mention the difficulty
of reentering the Earth's atmosphere.
What are you saying?
I'm saying that our crew
has an infinitesimal chance
of ever returning home.
By infinitesimal, I mean...
A snowball's chance in hell.
That would look rosy in comparison.
Welcome aboard.
Relax. I'm not gonna kill my ride home.
Yeah, we still don't trust you.
Rip Hunter. Good to see you.
I guess these morons figured out a way
to restore your original personality.
Enjoy the brig, Eobard.
I've been waiting for this
for a long time.
Sara,
you have to power down every non-essential
piece of hardware on the ship.
Gideon's already shut down.
The Waverider's using
gravitational inertia
to float back to Earth.
What? I know science.
PROFESSOR STEIN: It isn't enough.
If you want to activate the heat-shields,
and survive reentry,
you have to conserve more power.
- Now.
- RIP: Stein's right.
We need to shut down the water-filtration,
and the heating systems.
Right, 'cause clean water and heat,
we don't need those to survive.
You got a better idea?
At the moment, no.
Well, bundle up.
'Cause it's about to get chilly.
HENRY: Actually,
if the shields don't work,
atmospheric reentry
will burn us all to a crisp.
Science.
You lost, son?
No, sir. I won a contest
to see Apollo 13 land.
I'm Hank. Hank Heywood.
MAN: This place has turned
into a damn circus.
SARA:
Stein, we're ready for reentry.
What's the status
of your secondary thrusters?
It's sporadic.
She's still got a couple of pushes
left in her.
We just need to point her
in the right direction.
There's been a rather interesting
development down here on the ground.
RORY: Nate, you there?
Yeah, Mick. What's up?
There's some kid in Mission Control
calling himself Hank Heywood.
That's your son.
I fixed an essay writing contest
so Hank would win.
I should've told you earlier.
I had to meet him.
Well, our guidance system failed
to power back up.
Can we enter the atmosphere without it?
We'd need to figure out a reentry angle.
If it's too steep, the ship will burn up.
If it's too shallow,
we'll bounce off the atmosphere
and go into orbit around the sun.
SARA: Stein, little help here.
I'm working as fast as I can.
But I need a supercomputer,
which is not readily available in 1970.
We have a supercomputer.
Gideon's offline.
I'm not talking about Gideon.
Thirty-eight degrees.
You don't even know my question.
At what angle do we need
to reenter the Earth's atmosphere?
Thirty-eight degrees.
I'm from the 22nd century.
I learned astro-navigation
in grade school.
Thirty-eight degrees.
Or don't you trust me?
The reentry angle
needs to be 38 degrees.
How do you know?
Thawne.
He wants to get back to Earth,
same as the rest of us.
So that he can kill us when we land.
I'm with Amaya, grudgingly.
- I don't trust him.
- Agreed.
Professor Stein,
does 38 degrees sound right to you?
It could be, but without more time,
I can't be certain.
We haven't got any time.
Someone needs to make a decision.
Ms. Lance,
you're the captain.
Do you trust Thawne about this?
After everything that he's done?
I do.
And I trust Ray.
Let's go.
Stein, we're a go for reentry.
If we don't adjust the angle,
we'll burn up.
The thrusters, they're toast.
In a few seconds,
we're all gonna be toast.
We need to blow the cargo-bay door.
- What?
- He's right.
The depressurization
will correct your angle of descent.
RAY: The air pressure's too great.
If anyone opens up the door mid-descent,
they'll die.
- I'll go.
- No.
I'm captain. I'll go.
Where's Henry?
I'm in the cargo bay.
It's the only way to right this ship.
Talk me through this.
You have to secure
the inner door first.
Check.
Right, there should be a lever
to your, uh, to your left.
I see it.
Hank! Hank! Hank! Don't... Don't do this.
- I am so sorry, Nathaniel.
- No.
No, you open that door,
the explosive decompression
will suck you out.
If I don't, you will all die.
I can do it. Let me do it.
I have powers now.
No. No, I won't let you risk your life.
I have fulfilled my duty
protecting my piece of the Spear.
But I'm just a grunt.
Now, it's your turn.
You can figure out a way
to destroy the Spear.
Don't let it ruin another person's life.
Your son is at Mission Control.
He's there. He's waiting for you.
Come on.
Don't.
Give him a message for me.
Tell him,
"I'm sorry for leaving."
Don't. Please don't. Please don't.
It's working.
Thirty degrees.
Thirty-six.
Thirty-eight.
Commander Heywood's done it.
We're gonna make it.
Yes, we are.
Nathaniel...
It's a funny thing about Rip Hunter's
anti-speedster weapons.
I invented them.
I knew you'd escape.
You're on the run.
Because you're a time remnant.
You should have died
when Eddie Thawne killed himself.
And now something's chasing you.
Trying to correct the aberration.
One of history's worst monsters.
Speak of the devil.
Well, guess you won't have time to search
the ship for the Spear now, will you?
Till we meet again, Raymond.
MAN: Reentry successful.
It's pretty cool, huh?
You got to witness history.
You an astronaut?
No. No, I'm...
I wish I was that brave.
They made it home.
Not all of them.
They're my dad's.
They... They were.
He was gone before I knew him.
I'm sure he was sorry he left.
My dad wasn't really there for me, either.
But I knew he loved me.
He just, um...
He just couldn't show me.
It's not fair.
No.
No, it's not.
But, if you can accept that,
you'll be a better man for it.
You and your son.
Drinking alone?
Only as a metaphor.
You in here feeling sorry for yourself?
Oh, no, I've got more than one way
of feeling sorry for myself, surely.
Thanks for backing my play earlier.
Uh, I wasn't
entirely supportive on this mission.
Indeed.
But still,
must be hard coming back to your ship
and finding someone else in charge.
No, that was the easy part.
The hard adjustment was seeing that
you are a much better captain
than I ever was.
So, that's why you're in here
feeling sorry for yourself.
I'm in here trying to figure out
what my place is
if I'm not this team's captain.
So, you're saying you don't fit in?
You're an outcast?
A misfit?
Let's assume.
Sounds to me like you're a Legend.
I'm sorry, Nathaniel.
This was my fault.
If I hadn't have told Henry
that he shouldn't return home...
He still would've thrown himself
off the ship to save us.
It's just who he was.
Maybe destiny has plans
for all of us.
Not just me.
Yeah, um...
About that.
I am so sorry I said those things.
No one should know
too much about their future.
I'm not afraid of the future.
Whatever's supposed to happen
is bigger than just me.
I know this is cheesy,
but once you see Earth from outer space,
you realize how small we all are.
In a good way?
Yeah.
In a good way.
Gideon, I need you to
help me with something.
GIDEON: Of course, Ms. Jiwe.
I need you to show me
the historical record on Zambesi.
Starting with my return home.
GIDEON: You're asking for me
to show you your future.
I must counsel you against doing this.
Please, Gideon.
Hey, Mister tally man, tally me banana
BOTH:
♪ Daylight come and me wan' go home ♪
♪ Come, Mister tally man, tally me banana ♪
♪ Lift six foot, seven foot, ♪
♪ eight foot bunch ♪
RORY: Nice voice, Professor.