Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
I want to break up Firestorm.
If you guys are getting cold feet,
we can call the whole thing off.
It's time for Jefferson to claim
the power of Firestorm for himself.
This totem is my family's.
Only my blood may bare it.
- And they do.
- That's impossible.
That I am your granddaughter?
Why does Darhk care
if we fix Anachronisms or not?
That's the thing about daughters.
When they see you die at the hands
of one self-righteous hero,
they really don't want to see it
happen again.
We're stronger together.
We know that.
Darhk knows that.
Still nothing.
What are you doing, Grey?
Oh, since...
Gideon took Sara off sedatives,
I've been looking for a salient
stimulus to pull her out of the coma.
What the hell is that?
Salient stimulus, a noise or sound
she might have an emotional
connection to that would wake her up.
Here, would you like to give it
a try?
No, actually,
I was wondering if you needed
help with our other project.
Uncoupling Firestorm?
Oh, oh, yes, yes, that project.
I've been looking
into those equations
and it's very promising, indeed.
All of Firestorm's power
will safely reside in you.
Well, you're the smartest man I know.
So, if anybody can figure it out,
it's you.
That's why the smartest man
you know is heading right back
to the lab to double check
his calculations.
Everything okay?
You're hitting the bag like
it's insulting your mother
and you haven't said anything
for like 30 minutes.
What is there to say?
I don't know.
Talk about your granddaughter?
And not the superhero either.
The psycho water witch.
The who?
Your granddaughter.
I mean, I'm sure
she's really not that bad.
You just called her
a "psycho water witch."
Yeah, and I instantly regret it.
I'm sure she's just,
you know... confused.
Well, I'm not.
Kuasa and I will confront
each other again.
It's inevitable.
When we do...
I won't hesitate to stop her,
even if she is my granddaughter.
Okay.
Good talk.
Way to get the emotions out.
I really wish I had better news
about Sara,
but she's still in a coma,
thanks to Damien Darhk's
daughter laying her out.
Well, in the meantime,
we could do what we do best
and fix a few Anachronisms.
How about you drop me off
on an island
full of beautiful women like
Zari did with that Helen chick.
Rory, you weren't supposed
to say anything.
Wait, you didn't take Helen
back to Troy where she belongs?
That's what the Time Bureau does,
but we... we do something different.
No, we do it differently.
Yeah, more messy.
Okay, if you look
at the historical record,
the Trojan War happens
with or without Helen.
See? No Anachronism.
How do you think the Captain would
feel about you re-engineering time?
Well, we can argue about that later,
because I know exactly what she'd say
if she wakes up
and finds us doing nothing.
We owe it to Sara
to keep doing our job.
So where do we start?
Well, I was thinking we'd just
leave it up to chance
and my index finger.
Oof.
Vietnam.
1967.
Also known as the height
of the Vietnam War.
Gideon, what kind of Anachronism
are we dealing with?
A level eight.
Scans of the historical record reveal
redacted Pentagon reports
about a creature of unknown origin
attacking American
and Vietcong soldiers in the jungle.
Dozens have disappeared
without a trace.
No way I'm going to 'Nam.
All I know is that if American
soldiers are being targeted,
I am ready to do my duty.
This war's a little different.
Unlike World War II,
the military objectives in Vietnam
weren't so cut and dry.
Yeah, it was controversial
and the reasons for getting
involved were murky.
You know, come to think about it,
this team should be right at home.
Sole survivor of the last patrol
attacked was named Ryan Sanders.
He's supposed to be on R and R here.
This doesn't look like a good place
for American GIs
to rest and recuperate.
Looks more like
they're just trying to escape.
Hey, I found our guy.
Mr. Sanders.
We're with the Associated Press.
We wanted to ask you a few questions
about what happened with your squad.
I don't want to talk about it.
We won't take up much of your time.
Yeah, people need to hear your story.
You could save lives
telling us what you saw.
It must have stalked us
for several clicks.
Took us by surprise.
Whatever was out there
was pure evil,
and it had a message for us.
Stay out of the jungle.
I hate the jungle.
You sure this is the right way?
Well, according to the field reports,
the last known location
of Alpha Team was right... here.
I should have stayed in Aruba.
What could have taken out
a whole patrol of U.S. soldiers?
Nothing good.
But this missing squad's
gonna stay missing.
Let's get out of here.
Hope Mick and Nate
are watching their backs.
If what Sanders said is true,
they're in real danger.
Who knows if what he said was true?
He was clearly intoxicated.
Forget about him.
I think I found someone
who can tell us what's going on.
Hey, you've been staring at us
since we got here.
I heard you asking about the jungle.
It can be a dangerous place even
if you are carrying a machine gun.
Well, we're journalists here...
Who the hell are you?
My name is Anh Ly.
And I know what's out in that jungle.
You've seen what's been
attacking these soldiers?
Attacking them?
Come with me.
I won't just tell you
what's happening.
I'll show you.
Too many trees.
Too many plants.
We'll be back on concrete in no time.
Bugs!
Flies.
What's going on with you?
You're grumpier than usual.
What?
I'm in a good mood.
Is it because I made your boots
too big?
Look, I forget you've got small feet
and why would you not want
to come to Vietnam?
This place was like made for you.
My dad.
What about him?
He's here. 'Nam, the war.
Oh, buddy, you don't really think
you're gonna see him, do you?
There's almost no chance
we're gonna run into your father
in a jungle this big.
You said, "almost,"
meaning there is a chance.
I'll buy you a six-pack
if we bump into him.
Hands up, pretty boy.
You owe me a six-pack.
No.
Hands up.
Now.
Dude, what are you doing?
I'm Operations Officer
Nathaniel Heywood of the CIA.
This is my partner...
Officer Schwarzenegger.
We're here to investigate the
disappearance of Alpha Team.
Can't be too careful.
Sergeant Dick Rory, Echo Team.
I think it's in our mutual
best interest
if we conduct
this investigation together,
find out what happened to our men.
Actually, we were just leaving.
Sounds like a plan,
but I got to say, your partner here
doesn't look so gung ho.
Give us a minute.
Look, I'm sorry
you have to see your father,
but you need to suck it up.
If it wasn't for this time-travelling
stuff...
I would've never run into
that bastard.
Okay, you know what?
We're changing this operation.
This has become
Operation Tough Love.
Yeah, I'm gonna go all Dr. Phil
on your ass.
It's time for you to man up
and sort out...
Daddy issues.
I was going to say unresolved grief,
but let's go with what you're saying.
You want to know
why I've never seen a shrink?
Why?
I don't regret killing my old man.
What?
That's right, Pretty. You heard me.
I let my old man burn to death.
How's that for tough love?
Pecan.
Oh, hell nah.
What kind of monster eats
my mom's pecan pie
and puts the container
back in the fridge?
Gideon, who is the thief?
There must be a theorem
that supports the deceleration
of the subject's rate of fission
to individually power the thermacore.
Any insights, Sir Isaac Newton?
Or do I have to throw an apple
at your head?
Perhaps if you afforded us
a brief reprieve.
We've been working for hours.
And when, dare I ask,
do I get to return home?
You'll go home
when I say you can, Galileo.
What about you, Madame Curie?
You've been awfully quiet.
How many time do I have to
explain it to you, Martin?
There's only one way to safely
split the thermacore.
Yes, but doing so would result
in both
Jefferson and I losing our powers.
I personally have no compunctions
about that, but Jefferson...
There you are.
My colleagues and I were just...
You didn't have to lie to me
if you couldn't find a solution, man.
Look, I'm sure it's not easy learning
that your granddaughter's
in league with Damien Darhk.
If you ever want to talk about it...
What happened to men?
When did you all start talking
about your feelings?
Early '90s?
You are unusual journalists.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Most people run away
when they hear about a monster
grabbing soldiers in the jungle.
Us, we run towards it.
Monster?
What kind of monster
stops the fighting
between the Americans
and the Vietcong?
He's no monster.
He's Ong Troi Moi.
The New God.
Hey, what's going on?
Must be some sort of dead zone.
We are here.
Ray, can you hear me?
Can't go a whole day without
talking to your boyfriend, huh?
I think the comms are down.
Don't drink the ground water.
It's probably contaminated.
Those are some pretty rough burns
you got there, son.
You get hit by Napalm?
I ain't your son.
Yeah.
Do you know
what's on your father's head?
A little French-ie hat.
That is a Green Beret.
President Kennedy called them
"a symbol of excellence,
a badge of courage."
- Courage?
- Yeah.
The only thing my old man was
good at was sitting in a chair.
Cigarette in one hand,
beer in the other.
And the only time
he ever got up was to...
No, Mick, come on.
Come on, come on. This is good,
this is good. Look.
Thanks to time travel,
I got to talk to my grandfather
and I got to work out
a lot of my father issues.
Stand down. Stand down.
Is that you, Petey Adams?
What are you doing out here
on your own?
You get lost or something?
Lost?
No, I've become enlightened.
You can be enlightened too
if you join us.
Who's us?
This country does not belong to you.
It belongs to Ong Troi Moi.
I don't like where this is heading.
Handle me that rifle, Petey.
We'll work on getting you a hot meal.
You will surrender to him.
Or die.
Get off me.
Bunch of damn traitors.
American and North Vietnamese
soldiers working arm-in-arm?
This Anachronism is even crazier
than we thought.
And I think I know how they're
blocking our communications.
Hey, what is this place?
I thought we were looking
for a monster.
You wish to speak to Ong Troi Moi?
I've got a really bad feeling
about this.
We'd be honored.
We have guests.
They're reporters, as you wanted.
I am Grodd.
Welcome to my kingdom.
You saw what I saw, right?
There's a gorilla
sitting on a throne?
He spoke better English
than Mick.
Well, he's clearly intelligent enough
to trick these GIs
to abandon their posts.
He's a monster.
He needs to be stopped.
Look, he's turned these men
into his slaves.
Ong Troi Moi freed these soldiers.
He is the reason they are
no longer killing one another.
Yeah, it's a real utopia
he's created for himself.
I brought you here to help spread
Ong Troi Moi's message to the world.
You are only here to document
what you see.
Of course.
I need your shrink-ray.
I dislike that the name
is catching on.
Look, even if you can miniaturize
Grodd,
there's still 10 miles of jungle
warfare between us and the Waverider.
Yeah, which is why you guys
are going to take down
the communications jammer
and call for backup.
While you take down a
hyper-intelligent telepathic primate
by yourself?
All I need is one clean shot.
You saved my life today.
Didn't want to have to put you
on my list.
These are the names of all the men
that died under my watch.
Keep them with me
to remind myself it's my job
to protect my men,
get them back home.
That's my girl.
Gonna marry her when I get back.
Quit looking at her.
Maybe even start a family someday.
You want kids?
Why not?
As long as they never end up
in some godforsaken jungle.
I've seen things out here...
No, I hope I never bring home
with me.
I've never told anybody this before,
but...
I'm scared.
I don't know who I am
if I'm not a part of Firestorm.
But you've never had any superpowers
and that's never stopped you
from being the most
kick-ass person I've ever met.
Well, good talk, Captain.
Wow, I knew Grodd
was a power-hungry tyrant, but...
He's one hell
of an electrical engineer.
The key is to jam the jammer without
anyone realizing it's jammed.
Did that make sense?
Perfect.
Where are we taking Grodd
when we return him
to where he belongs?
Well, last I heard
he was in an ARGUS prison.
Wait, he's just another
persecuted meta?
Look, I know
you're not a fan of ARGUS,
but Grodd is a psychopath
and, well, a giant gorilla.
Ray? Jax? Can you hear me?
I think there is something up
with Mick.
He's got that look, you know,
when he's eyes get all crazed.
I think the jungle's finally
getting to...
Hey, man, you good?
Mick?
What were you doing?
What does it look like?
Looks like you were...
burning your own skin.
But that would be completely insane,
right?
My whole life I saw him as a monster.
Blamed him for all the sick things
that I've done.
But now I see...
I'm worse than him.
Should have been me
that burned in that house.
- You're a genius.
- Thanks.
Sorry, I was talking to myself.
Hello?
Can anybody hear me?
Nate, is that you?
Yes, our comms are down.
No, no, no, no, they were jammed
and I just fixed...
I mean, Zari un-jammed it.
Where are you guys? We need
to get out of this jungle ASAP.
Oh, no. What's wrong, buddy?
Well, when Mick and I started,
we were doing "Predator."
Then, we ran into Mick's dad,
and now we're doing "Apocalypse Now."
That's why Mick didn't want
to come to Vietnam,
on the off chance he'd run
into his father.
Which is about as unlikely as Marty
meeting his great-great-grandfather,
Sir Stein.
Right, or young-you befriending
a time-displaced alien.
Do you people not hear me?
Listen, the monster-slash-Anachronism
is Gorilla Grodd.
We're stuck in his compound.
Did you just say "Gorilla Grodd?"
Grodd's displacement in 1967
probably explains that.
Guys?
Our Anachronism just jumped
from an eight to a level ten.
Gideon, what you got?
The timeline is currently in flux.
However, the following headline
recently appeared in my archives.
It appears that Grodd
is using the powder keg
that is the Vietnam War to
somehow ignite World War III.
- What?
- Where's Amaya?
We have to figure out Grodd's plan
and get out of here.
Yeah.
This is how you repay Grodd
for his hospitality?
By trying to kill me?
Let me help you
with that weapon of yours.
You think I am the enemy.
Look at what you humans
have done to one another.
Look at what humans did to me.
So you're raising an army of humans
to get your revenge?
Revenge?
No.
My only wish is to help your kind
find peace.
And how do you plan to do that?
Welcome to Vietnam, Mr. President.
Good lord, it's hotter than
a preacher's knee out here.
You hit the nail on the head,
Mr. President.
Follow me. We'll get you
into some air conditioning.
You're planning
to kill the President?
We're defending our home
against those who have attacked us.
Which I'm all for, believe me,
but you need to draw a line
somewhere.
Grodd is only doing
what is necessary.
Necessary for who?
He only cares about himself.
That's how dictators work.
I have lost both my parents.
My brother, my village.
Ong Troi Moi is the only one left
to protect us.
Hey.
I know what it's like to lose the
people you love in a senseless war.
It makes you desperate, but...
if you really want peace,
it starts with you.
Did you guys hear that?
They're targeting
the President's convoy.
Anh is weak.
Grodd.
- Where are you going?
- You heard Zari.
To save L.B.J.
It's sounds like the team's
got their hands full.
It's too dangerous.
We'll go together as Firestorm.
No, we won't.
I got to do this on my own.
Please, don't.
I'm still working on a way
to split the thermacore.
Okay, I don't know
if this is your way
of making yourself feel better
about us splitting up
by making sure I've got powers,
but I can do this without any.
And soon enough, I'm gonna have
to stand on my own without you.
We just intercepted
radio communications
and triangulated the enemy's position
to a base just east of here.
That's where they're holed up.
Don't know about you boys,
but I'm ready to go to work.
We can't let them get near that camp,
okay?
These yahoos are gonna shoot
anything that moves.
Our friends are in there.
Amaya's in there.
Do you hear me?
You fellas ready?
Actually, Sarge, you're gonna have
to tell your men to stand down.
I just received intel that the
encampment is a no-fire zone.
Nobody told me about any intel.
Well, the intel
was on a need-to-know basis
and you didn't need to know 'til now.
Can you explain the situation
to my men?
Yeah, no problem.
Listen up.
I don't take orders from the CIA.
You in or you out, son?
I'm in, pops.
Figure of speech.
What's going on?
Well, Grodd wants to start
World War III.
The sooner your great nations
destroy one another,
the sooner there will be peace.
One nation under Grodd.
Grodd!
The U.S. President will pay
for his atrocities.
Hey, you don't have to do this
to get what you want.
She's right.
We're here to bring you home.
You have every right to be angry.
This world is cruel.
What was done to you by humans...
it's unforgivable.
But you must understand
that we are not here to hurt you.
And how will you bring me back home?
Unless...
you're time-travelers.
I will not go with you.
There is nothing for me
where I am from.
Only pain.
You're right.
- Maybe we don't take you home.
- We don't?
We can take you to a time
before humans.
A time where you can live out
your days in peace.
And why would Grodd trust you?
Because I'm different.
There's been a breach!
All squads defend the perimeter!
You betrayed me.
No, I promise we had nothing
to do with this.
I didn't mean for any of this
to happen.
You have to believe me.
Humans will always fear Grodd,
hunt Grodd,
but with your time machine
at Grodd's command,
there will be no humans.
Grodd will alter the course
of evolution.
He will no longer need
a gorilla country
because Grodd
will have a gorilla planet.
You better tell the Professor
he's gonna have company.
Who's in charge around here?
What in the world?
Get off me.
Call in an air strike.
We'll let Napalm take care
of whatever the heck that was.
We got deserters to deal with.
Raymond, I must have misheard you.
Did you say Grodd
was on his way here?
Sure did, man. He's planning
on stealing the Waverider.
I swear to you, if I die today
because of a telepathic gorilla,
I'm going to be very upset.
Yeah, well,
then get the Waverider moving.
Hands on your head, traitor.
Let's go, move it.
- Amaya.
- Nathaniel.
Shut up.
Are you okay?
Mick?
Mick.
What's wrong with him?
I'm afraid he's gone full Kurtz.
What does that mean?
It's a movie reference.
Great movie, terrible situation.
They say life is the sum total
of all the choices you make.
As your misfortune sinks in,
maybe you want to ask yourself,
what choices did I make
to find myself here?
Today I want payback
for what that monster did to my men,
my brothers.
Excuse... excuse me.
- Shut up.
- We're journalist.
Shut up.
And we've uncovered a plot
to kill President Johnson.
We need to alert
the proper authorities.
Shut up.
- See?
- Hey, he's telling the truth.
The President landed in Vietnam.
But we can still save him.
You're reporters.
What are you gonna do?
Question him to safety?
It's a little more complicated
than that, but...
just trust me, okay?
We're the good guys.
Haven't you hear?
There are no good guys here.
Stop!
Stop, stop, stop!
Hey, wait.
Wait. Wait, wait.
Don't shoot.
I'm an American.
You've got to back the heck up.
Son, we're gonna be on you
like a duck on a June bug
if we don't start moving again.
Mr. President,
your life is in danger.
Okay? That road block is a trap.
You've got to get back to base.
- Step back, sir.
- Wait... no, no, no.
Mr. President, stop!
Mr. President. Don't move!
Don't. Move.
Enough talk.
Time to pay the entrance fee
to this circus.
Don't.
- What are you doing?
- Saving your life.
What are you talking about?
I know what's going on
in that head of yours.
But killing these people is not
gonna bring back your men.
What do you know about anything?
Mick, you do realize what
will happen if you kill him?
Don't care.
This is insubordination, son.
I wouldn't have expected
that from you.
Well, you don't know me.
Lower your weapon.
Lower yours.
I got nothing to lose.
But you do.
You get to go home.
But if you kill these people,
you'll hear their screams forever.
And one day...
when you have a family,
you won't be able to look them
in the eye.
Because this day,
this act you're about to commit,
will be burned in your memory
forever.
Why'd you do that?
I always wanted to.
Route is clear. Weapons hot.
Okay.
You guys walked through a mine field
and I'm pretty sure you're caught
in a Soviet trip line.
But by freezing it,
you should be able to step away.
Should?
Okay, on the count of three,
I want you to step away slowly.
One, two, three.
I'll be a damn humdinger.
Sounds like our Viet Cong friends
are circling in.
Okay, well, we better hustle
through this minefield.
Follow my lead
and if I don't blow up, path's clear.
And if you blow up?
Then you're on your own, sir.
Well, that wasn't so hard.
That's because I'm helping.
That your idea of helping?
I'm afraid we have
an unexpected passenger.
You're afraid?
Follow my steps exactly.
I wasn't planning on improvising.
Okay, come on, Mr. President.
One more step. You got this.
Come on.
Where is Captain Lance
when I need her?
Sara...
were you just waiting for the right
moment to make a dramatic entrance?
Are you all right?
There is no Sara.
What?
Only Grodd.
It appears that the Captain is under
some sort of telepathic control.
Really, Gideon? You think so?
I claim this ship for the New God.
Kneel before Gro...
Oh, how I do love proving
my laws of motion.
Please, save that lecture
for another day.
Professor Stein, a U.S. military
air strike is approaching.
And Grodd is still clinging
to the Waverider.
I have an idea.
Hey, are you sure
you won't reconsider?
I can get you out of here.
You can start over somewhere
where there's no war.
No, my struggle is here.
I realize now, my people,
they do not need a god.
They need a leader.
Like you said,
peace starts with me.
Got some R and R scheduled
in a few days down in Eagle Beach.
You CIA boys ever get time off,
maybe I'll see you down there.
Anything's possible.
You saved innocent lives.
You saved me.
Pulled me back
from crossing that line.
Well, I've been pulled back from
that line a couple of times myself.
Listen...
if that kid of yours happens
to be a boy...
Yeah?
Nevermind.
Looks like Operation Tough Love
was a success.
Yeah, figured you'd want this back.
I don't need it anymore.
Raymond, are you in there?
Yeah, I'm in here.
Just trying to rebuild
the Molecular Hyper Compressor.
You mean the shrink-ray
that I didn't get to use Grodd?
Yes, it took quite a beating.
What are... what are you doing here?
I came by to say that you were right.
Well, you and Nathaniel,
but I'd rather
you didn't say anything.
No, of course not.
I won't say a word.
About what exactly?
Kuasa.
This experience with Grodd...
he wasn't born a monster.
He was made into one.
And for all I know, the same
is true of my granddaughter.
So, thank you.
Yeah, you're welcome.
Well, I'm relieved you're all right.
Got a little close back there.
By the way, you were right.
I... I was putting myself
under a lot of pressure
to resolve our separation problem.
I just wanted to make sure
I had done everything I could
to keep you safe before I left.
But you're gonna be just fine.
You already carry the most important
part of Firestorm within you.
His spirit.
You getting all soft on me, Grey?
But for real, I'm gonna miss you
when you're gone, man.
Anyway, you said you had something
to show me.
Oh, yeah, so...
after I saved L.B.J.'s life,
I thought I'd get, like,
a medal or something,
but he just tells me
he's got some top secret information.
And hands me this.
Oh, dear God.
This is incredible.
So, instead of a medal for bravery,
President Johnson
gave you a pie recipe.
Well, not just any recipe.
Ladybird Johnson's pecan pie
was legendary.
The ingredients were very closely
kept secret for a long time.
It's almost as good as my mom's pie.
I don't know.
First Lady pie is pretty good.
This is a great gift.
Way better than a medal
'cause you can eat it.
What?
You guys weren't going
to save me any pie?
Aye-oh-what!
Welcome back to the land
of the living, Captain.
Gideon gave me a clean bill
of health.
- Hello, love.
- Hi.
But I don't know
about this bump on my head.
Who's the new guy?
Oh, don't ask.
Well, this was quite an adventure.
Where to next?
Shut up, you bop.
Vietnam.
Crappy war.
Bitching music.
Where is Grodd?
Who are you?
Is that any way
to treat your number one fan?
A nuclear crisis in Central City?
Masterful.
Why else do you think
I'd pull you out of Vietnam
before you fell
into that Napalm inferno?
Send me back.
I know you wanted a time ship,
but who needs a lumbering tin can
when you can time travel
with a single thought?