Previously on Legends Of Tomorrow...
The more the timeline is corrupted,
the weaker the prison
holding Mallus becomes.
Maybe these totems are the keys
to stopping him.
The Fire Totem
wasn't meant for me.
Damien Darhk?
What has he promised you?
A chance to protect our village.
- No.
- We'll fix this.
We'll get your totem back.
Gideon, delete file 354-Z.
Yes, Director Hunter.
Sara can never find out
the truth about Ava.
Look, I don't deserve you.
- Sara, yes, you do.
- No, Ava, I don't.
I'm not gonna do this. I'm sorry.
I am not just walking out
on the team, Ray.
She says as she's literally
walking away.
Sara, we appreciate
that you may need a break
after what happened
with the Death Totem,
but this is the absolute worst time
for you to leave.
At least let us lock you up
in the brig.
We need you here now more than ever.
Yeah, we've almost won
the totem race.
Which is exactly why I need to go.
Look, we are so close
to gaining control over the six,
and getting the upper hand on Mallus.
I just...
I need a day to clear my head.
Who's gonna stop Mick from burning
down the ship with the Fire Totem?
Someone's gonna have to fill in
the role of captain while I'm gone.
Oh. Well, I hadn't exactly thought I'd
pick up the mantle this soon, but...
I'm putting Amaya in charge.
Good luck.
Sorry about that, big guy.
Hey, hi.
Um, do you think that maybe you could
do that somewhere else?
We do have a galley.
You want a dog?
It's pork.
So what?
No, thank you.
Ah.
Wow, I'm sure that's what those
ancient folks had in mind
when they created the Fire Totem.
- Every man's gotta eat.
- There you are, Mick.
- You ready?
- For what?
Training. Do you remember?
We spoke about learning
to harness the powers of the totem.
Hmm.
I got a new trick. Pull my finger.
- What?
- Pull my finger.
Do not pull his finger.
Let's just say hot dogs
aren't the only thing
he's learned how to light on fire.
Sorry to interrupt, Ms. Jiwe,
but Dr. Heywood requests
your presence in the library.
Captain's duties
are never over.
But, seeing as you're not busy...
No. Please no, please don't ask me.
I can't think of anyone better
to learn to train a new totem bearer.
Yeah, sure.
I'll get right on it.
Good luck.
So, what's going on?
It's your granddaughter, Mari.
She's been hurt. A minor wrinkle
- in the 2018 timeline.
- How badly?
The article says she was burned
trying to save people
from a warehouse fire in Detroit.
Doesn't she have superpowers, though?
This is all my fault.
Ever since I lost my totem,
the timeline
must be starting to solidify.
Which means, in this new reality,
the totem
was never passed down to her.
So, Mari is a vigilante
without her totem.
I have to go and talk to her.
What? No. You cannot talk
to your own granddaughter.
- That would cause...
- Unforeseen consequences.
I know, but how much worse
can things truly get?
Sara put me in charge
while she steps away.
All the more reason why you
should stay on the ship, okay?
I'll go to Detroit,
and I'll talk to her.
- And I'll help him.
- Yeah.
There's nothing this dynamic duo
cannot do.
Okay, fine.
Just be careful.
Look, Sara.
For what it's worth, I know it wasn't
the real you who tried to kill us.
That's just it, Ray.
That was the real me.
Which is why I need to...
Ms. Lance? It's Gary.
Sorry to drop in on you like this.
What are you doing?
Open your eyes, Gary.
Oh, hi.
Sorry, I didn't wanna accidentally
portal into your quarters
and catch you and Director Sharpe,
you know...
- Together.
- You don't have to worry about that
anymore because we broke up.
Wait, what? Why didn't you tell us?
No, no, you guys can't break up.
I was shipping you so hard.
That's why you're leaving.
That is not why I'm leaving.
And if you're looking for Ava,
I suggest you check her office.
Uh, well, that's the thing.
She hasn't been to work
in a few days,
which is very unlike her.
I've already been covering for her.
I forged her signature twice.
What am I supposed to do next?
Put on a wig and pantsuit
and pretend I'm her?
- No, don't do that.
- What if she's in trouble?
I mean,
we already lost Director Bennett.
What if Grodd got to her, too?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Gary, Gary, deep breaths.
Deep breaths.
Don't worry, Gary,
because we're gonna find her.
"We" will find her?
Thanks for taking the time
to talk with us, Mr. McCabe.
Mari's resting.
I'll have someone come grab you
when she wakes up.
We're from the Detroit Chronicle,
and we'd like to do a story
about your foster daughter's heroism.
To tell you the truth,
I wish she was less interested
in saving everyone else's lives
and more compelled
to protect her own.
Mari's a brave woman.
But, maybe you should remind her
that there are police
and firefighters, too,
and that the safety of Detroit
isn't, you know, her responsibility.
You don't have to tell me that.
Sometimes I feel like my daughter,
she's walking around
with a target on her back.
Excuse me for a second.
Ava comes back and finds us
snooping through her office...
We're only snooping
to find out where she went.
What are you doing?
I'm hacking into the Bureau's network
to access Ava's personnel file.
- Huh.
- What is it?
Director Sharpe's personnel file
has been erased.
Someone deleted it remotely
from the Waverider.
Wow, she must've really
wanted to go off the radar.
Wait, you think Director Sharpe
erased her own file? That's crazy.
Yeah, so was putting on a wig
and impersonating your boss, Gary.
I didn't actually do it.
Mmm-hmm.
- What are you doing?
Looking for clues
as to where she might have gone.
Birthday card from her parents
in Fresno.
Think she might have gone to Fresno?
That mean we have to go to Fresno?
You sure you saw Kuasa?
Yeah, just be on the lookout
for a badass in a leather outfit.
Or a suspicious puddle of water.
Hey, there she is!
I got her.
Whoa!
Dude, don't just stand there.
Hello.
Not so fast.
- Wally, wait, she's...
- Dangerous, I know.
Soon as I catch my breath, I'm gonna
stop you from hurting your sister.
Hurt Mari?
I'm here to protect her, you idiots.
Well, this isn't exactly
how I imagined meeting Ava's parents.
Not that I imagined
meeting Ava's parents, I just...
Hello. How can we help you?
Pam and Randy Sharpe?
Says so on our marriage license.
Looks like they stepped right out
of an L.L. Bean catalog.
Now we know where Director Sharpe
gets her perfect bone structure.
And you are?
We're friends of your daughter.
Well, unfortunately, Ava...
Hasn't shown up for work
in a few days,
and we're getting a little worried.
We haven't seen her in months.
I hope she's okay.
We were hoping that
we could come inside.
Maybe, together we could figure out
where she's gone.
Sure. Pammy here just baked up
a storm of her famous cookies.
Snickerdoodles.
Come on in.
If you folks work with Ava,
you must work for the government.
Yep, we're government suits.
Our daughter won't tell us what
she does. It's all so "top secret."
You have so many photos of her.
Where was that one taken?
Oh, that's at the Grand Canyon.
Hmm.
Such a beautiful family.
Almost too good to be true.
Sara, why don't you try one
of Mrs. Sharpe's snickerdoodles?
I don't want a snickerdoodle, Ray.
What about this photo?
Where was this one?
Oh, yes, that's Ava's
15th birthday party.
She had friends in for a sleepover.
They stayed up all night long
watching horror movies.
Uh-huh.
- Sleepover, really?
- Uh-huh.
I remember it well.
Well, I know for a fact
Ava went paintballing
for her 15th birthday.
Oh.
Pam meant her 16th birthday.
She always gets that part mixed up.
Always.
Who the hell are you guys?
- Oh, God, I hate the sight of blood.
- Sara.
Okay, fine, we'll tell you
everything, just don't kill us.
- And, why the hell shouldn't I?
- Because we're just actors.
What?
Yeah. Okay, four years ago,
we responded
to this online ad for a gig.
They gave us backstories
for our characters,
they told us if Ava
ever comes around to visit,
we just act like her parents.
And who hired you?
No idea.
The money is automatically deposited.
Look, it's not such a bad gig,
considering Ava rarely
ever comes home to visit.
Why in the world would you agree
to be a part of such a charade?
Do you know how hard it is
to get an acting job in Fresno?
Right, well, I apologize
about the knife thing.
It is a gut reaction.
Nothing personal.
Sorry to bother you.
We'll be on our way now.
You have a lovely home, Mr. and Mrs.
Whatever your real names are.
Okay, you said to wait until
after your second lunch.
This is your fourth.
Amaya wants me to teach you
how to use your totem,
so let's get cracking.
If I wanted to learn,
I would have gone to school.
You know, you are a...
Okay.
Be patient, be kind,
abstain from negative thoughts.
Sorry, blood sugar thing. Fasting.
Fasting?
Yeah, I'm not eating.
Trying to lose some fat, huh?
No, I love my body.
I'm trying to observe Ramadan.
So observe it on a full stomach.
Is this bacon?
You're Jewish.
I don't even know what... I can't.
What kind of person invents
a fake family and backstory?
When I was a kid, I told my friends
my dad was an orthodontist.
Sounded much cooler than dentist.
If she was lying
about where she's from,
there's no telling what else she...
Sara, what are you doing here?
Uh...
Gary was worried
that you were missing, so...
Naturally, we were concerned,
and thought we'd
investigate it further.
Clearly, I'm no longer missing, so...
- You sure you're okay?
- I'm fine.
Don't I look fine?
Where have you been?
If you must know...
Gary, straighten your tie.
I was visiting my parents in Fresno.
Home-cooked meals and all.
- Hmm. Fresno?
- Mmm-hmm.
Nothing like a tray
of snickerdoodles.
I mean, any other kind of cookie
to mend a broken heart.
You know what,
I have a lot of work to do.
I'm sure you two
can see yourselves out.
You okay?
No one likes running into their ex.
I'm fine.
Like I said,
let's find out what else
she's hiding from us.
So, this is Mari's Vixen cave.
Ever since my grandmother
lost her totem,
I figured I better start
keeping tabs on her.
It's a good thing I did.
I thought you hated Mari.
She's still my sister.
And even though I resented her
for inheriting the Anansi Totem,
I'd rather see it around her neck
than on Nora Darhk's.
So, let's get it back
to where it belongs.
- You wanna help me?
- We wanna help Amaya.
You wanna help your sister.
Either way,
we have to get that totem back.
The Darhks will kill me
if I turn on them.
Don't worry,
this isn't the first totem
that we've lifted
from under their noses.
Soon we'll have five totems.
Do you really wanna be one
against five?
If we work together, we can defeat
the Darhks and Mallus.
And you get to protect your family.
Isn't that what you really want?
Fine.
But we do this my way.
Maybe Ava wasn't lying
about where she was,
but when she was.
I thought the worst thing about her
is she's from Fresno.
Well, I'm not...
I'm not seeing anything
in her Time Courier records
that wasn't Bureau-sanctioned
and by the book.
Wait, what's that?
Her first mission,
Vancouver 2213. I can't access it.
The Bureau sanctioned 2213
a no-fly zone.
Meaning?
Meaning the Courier you stole
from Ava doesn't do you any good,
and the Waverider
can't fly there, either.
And the only person
who can override the restriction...
Is the Time Bureau director.
Yeah.
- But, why wouldn't Director Sharpe...
- Want us to know who she really is?
I'll give you one guess, Gary.
Oh, my God, oh, my God.
Do you think
my boss is an anachronism?
The only way to know for sure
is to go to 2213.
So how do we get there?
I guess the only way
would be to hijack the mothership,
but unfortunately,
I failed flight training.
Damn astigmatism.
Like I'd let you fly.
Let's go.
Wait, what?
What do you mean the mothership
is on the move?
I mean, someone's stealing it, ma'am.
Track it.
I'm going after it personally.
Should we really be doing this?
I mean, I'm sure
there's a good reason
why no one is supposed to come
to this time period.
Maybe Gary's right.
Maybe we should just ask Ava
what her connection is to this place.
Why? She's just gonna lie
to us again.
Well, if you wanna ask her,
now's your chance.
Director Sharpe.
Director Sharpe?
Just down across, make a left.
Director Sharpes.
What kind of world is this?
Paradise?
I'm surrounded by my exes, Gary.
This is hell.
Pleasant day, citizens.
I had a dream like this once.
Yeah, me too,
but mine involved less clothing.
Mine, too.
Okay.
Well, I guess this is why
they declared 2213 a no-fly zone.
Director Sharpe
didn't want us to find out
that she's secretly a robot.
I did not have sex with a robot.
No, you didn't, Sara.
You had sex with a clone.
Here at Advanced Variant Automation,
we are working to bring
a brighter future.
Our cloning program
has produced the Ava.
Ava is the perfect woman
designed to keep us safe
and restore order to the chaos.
It makes sense they'd clone Ava.
She is the perfect woman.
Oh, calm down, Gary, she's okay.
Before I have an Ava overload,
should we return to the comfort
and safety of the Time Bureau?
No.
We're not done here yet.
I think an ambush would work best
in this situation.
Sure,
if you wanna die a quick death.
Quite frankly, you two...
Oh.
Are no match for the Darhks.
Okay,
so what's your plan?
We lure them to us, with bait.
No, no. You are not using a totem.
No.
We have the next best thing.
A Legend.
That's crazy. Why don't we just go
to where they're at,
I'll swipe it
like I did the Fire Totem.
You overplayed your hand.
Now, they know you have a...
Whatever you are on the team.
What I am is the fastest man alive.
Thanks.
Second fastest.
She didn't need to know that.
Nathaniel?
Amaya, hey.
- How's Mari?
- Her doctor says she's gonna be fine.
She's strong, just like you.
Thank you for checking in on her.
So when are you coming back?
We're gonna stick around for a while.
You know, talk her out
of this whole superhero business.
Or at least until you get
your totem back
and the timeline's back in order.
In that case,
just take care of yourself, okay?
I love you, Nathaniel.
Yeah, me too.
Shouldn't we be bringing
Amaya into this?
- No.
We already have one Vixen
in the hospital as it is.
Agreed.
My grandmother will want
to play the hero
and get herself killed.
If that happens, Mari and I
will be wiped from existence.
Right, so, we're gonna need you
to keep her out of our hair.
- But...
- I know, I know.
I'll be fine. I just need you
to keep an eye on Amaya.
Damn it, Wally.
This place is creepy.
How about I wait outside?
How about you calm down?
Is it too late to mention my fear
of things covered in sheets?
Hey, guys, over here.
How is this even possible?
Looks like they created Ava
from what they believe
are the best genes from
around the world
to make the perfect woman.
Though she's a little pale,
if you ask me.
I should've known
she was too good to be true.
That doesn't mean that what you guys
had wasn't real.
That is exactly what it means.
Uh... Guys?
Everything that she's told me
about herself has been a lie.
- Guys?
- What, Gary?
Oh, crumbs! I think I woke one up.
Your are in violation of Bylaw 575.
You do not have clearance
to be in this room.
We were just leaving.
Just let us go, it'll be fine.
If I let you go,
I have to let everyone go.
You must be terminated.
I think she wants to kill us.
You don't say.
Should we help?
Not unless you want both of them
to kill you.
All right, tie her up
before she comes to.
This is weird.
Ah.
These chains won't be nearly
as convincing
if you can turn to steel.
You know, I'm a good actor.
I could have sold it.
And what's with these vigilantes
and their dark spaces?
It's like they're afraid
of that healthy bronze look. Hmm?
Oh, I know.
I didn't mean you.
You look great, honey.
I underestimated you, Kuasa.
You brought us
a valuable bargaining chip.
Uh-uh-uh.
I want something in exchange.
My grandmother's totem.
It belongs to me.
You didn't actually think she was
gonna hand that over to you, did you?
- She's right.
- You what?
The power of Mallus flows through me.
I don't need some trinket.
Besides,
Kuasa's proven herself
a loyal acolyte.
The plan worked. Free me.
I once thought that losing this totem
was the greatest threat to me
and my family.
But you are in love with my Nana Baa.
And should she choose
to love you in return,
me and my sister
will never even exist.
- This is not the plan.
- Plans change.
This is better than
The Brave And The Bold.
For a PhD,
you're remarkably gullible.
Kuasa, you're better than this.
Be the woman your grandmother
believed you to be.
I'm being the woman
she knows me to be.
When you kill him, do it slowly.
Is that too tight? I can never tell.
Not that I have experience
tying people up, because I don't.
Stop talking to it, Gary.
Sara, she isn't an "it."
She's a real person, they all are.
Our Ava's just an anachronism,
somehow displaced 200 years
in the past, a.k.a. our present.
- Sorry, sorry, sorry.
- I know.
I mean, I get it.
Why would she tell me she comes
from a place where she's just
one of a million copies?
- There you are.
- Oh, God, another one?
Gary, that's our Ava.
What does he mean "another one"?
Don't mind Gary.
You know, it's interesting,
I would've found you sooner,
except I seemed to have misplaced
my Time Courier.
What are you three doing in 2213?
We are investigating an anachronism.
An anachronism, really?
What is this place anyway?
Oh, come on, Ava.
The jig's up. We know.
What are you talking about?
Oh, my God.
Well, maybe she's not a card-carrying
member of the clone club after all.
I must prepare
for the master's arrival.
I trust you'll be able
to make him talk.
No problem, Nora-doll.
Talk? You don't have
to torture me to talk.
The trick is, you gotta get me
to shut up.
It's not much of a trick.
You will have the Legends
bring the missing totems to me.
Or you will die.
Your, um, daughter,
she looks different. No offense.
None taken.
Her face...
How long has that been a situation?
You know what, since you're gonna
die, I might as well tell you.
The closer that Mallus gets
to escaping his prison,
the worse the situation gets.
You know, stop looking at me.
Don't look at me. I'm just gonna...
I'm sorry. It's not you, it's me.
Torture just doesn't bring me
the same joy anymore.
It's okay, you're distracted,
I get it.
You made a deal with the devil,
now he's come back to claim
your little girl, am I right?
Yes!
I wanted to burn the world down
and rebuild it in my image,
not lose the person
I was doing it for.
Damien, this is deep stuff, man.
Let's just keep digging.
Let's keep digging.
- Just do me one favor.
- Yes, what?
Can you lose the cattle prod?
I mean, I'm gonna die anyway.
Let's just make this a safe space.
- A safe space.
- Director Sharpe?
- Mmm.
Director Sharpe, are you okay?
Oh, Gary! God! Get out of my face.
I'll take that as a yes.
What do you remember
before you hit your head?
Uh...
I came to 2213
to find the mothership,
and I stepped out of the portal,
and then you were breathing
in my face.
Is there something I'm forgetting?
Well, before your little mishap,
you were commending us
on our great work,
and you even mentioned something
about a promotion.
- This is terrible.
- Okay.
Can we just tell her the truth?
That what? She was hatched
in a government lab?
God, this whole time, I thought
that she was hiding who she was,
but clearly, she had no idea
she was a clone.
Did you see the way she reacted?
- What was that?
- Uh...
- Nothing.
- No, don't.
Don't...
Don't what?
- Thank God she's gone.
- Who's gone?
We gotta get out of here
before that fembot sounds the alarm.
Fembot?
Come on.
Okay, now concentrate on the target.
It's about focus and precision.
Like I need help
lighting things on fire.
Okay.
One, two...
Rory, could you focus on something
other than your stomach for a second?
Whatever.
I said just the target, you idiot!
- I'm the idiot?
- Yeah.
You're the one who doesn't eat
when you're hungry.
Maybe if you did,
you wouldn't be such a bitch!
What did you just say?
You heard me.
Whoa. What is going on?
Zari's training Rory.
Or killing him.
But now you're back on the ship,
we need to get out of Detroit
and back to work.
Uh... Nate is actually still
trying to convince Mari
not to be a vigilante,
and she is stubborn.
I wonder where she gets that from.
Kuasa, what are you doing here?
- I come with a peace offering.
- How did you get that?
Wait, where is Nate?
I gave him to the Darhks
in exchange for the totem.
- That wasn't the plan.
- What plan?
Nate thought it'd be better
not to tell you.
Because you're in love
with him, Nana Baa.
And that love is a threat
to both Mari and me.
- So you betrayed him?
- He's not my grandfather.
Every moment that you spend with him
is a threat
to our entire family's future.
How can you be so selfish?
You're the selfish one.
Our family's destruction
looms in 1992.
You promised you'd save us,
and yet, you continuously
search for ways
to abandon your family and Zambesi.
I have done everything in my power
to try to redeem you.
And in doing so, Mari got hurt.
She understands
that being a totem bearer
means protecting all people,
not just our own.
It's no wonder this totem
ended up with Mari and not you.
You're beyond redemption.
Mothership is this way.
Sara listen, I really need to confess
something to you.
- Can we do this later?
- No, listen.
I wasn't really visiting
my parents in Fresno.
I don't even know why I said that.
I never visit my parents.
- They're like strangers to me.
- You don't say.
When we broke up,
I actually called my ex in Vegas.
I'm so ashamed,
but it's worse than that, all right?
I created an Upswipz profile...
And, I actually went
really overboard on the swiping.
It really is more intuitive
to go up and down, but...
That's not even the point.
The point is,
I realized
that it's not for me, okay?
And, I know that we aren't
together anymore, Sara,
but I really just felt like
I needed to be honest with you.
Okay? Great. Now you all hate me.
Not that I can blame you, I just...
Can you, please, stop looking at me
like that? I can't take it.
Ava, look, it's not you...
It's them.
What the hell are those things
and why do they all look like me?
Uh... Well, short version,
you're a clone.
I'm a...
I'm a clone? From the future?
I'm a future clone thing?
Hey, Ava.
- Shh.
- It's okay, Director Sharpe.
- Gary will take care of everything.
- No.
She deserves to know.
I don't understand.
This can't be happening.
You're saying I'm one of them?
Hey, look, this might be
where you're from,
but it is not who you are.
Then who the hell am I?
You are the same person
that you have always been.
You are the woman who has
worked her way to the top
to becoming the head
of the Time Bureau.
- You are extraordinary.
- No.
My life, my memories,
they're all manufactured.
They're not real. I'm not even real.
Ava, you are real.
You are as real as I feel about you.
How can you say that when I'm
just like one of those things?
Because I know you.
And I know that you are a badass.
And you are different.
And now that we both know that,
I need you to act exactly
like one of those clones
if we wanna get out of here.
Go ahead, Darhk.
Make my day.
You asked for it, steel boy.
- Was that good?
- Really good, really good.
- Just a lit bit bigger this time.
- Okay.
Here we go.
Oh, no! My God!
There's blood everywhere.
There's so much blood.
You know better
than to play Mallus for a fool.
No, no, no. Honey, I can explain.
Such a waste of a good head of hair.
Hey, get your hands
off that hard body.
I'm sorry, that sounded
way better in my head.
What the hell?
Seems that you and Kuasa
have resolved your family squabble.
So much drama over a silly trinket.
Pathetic.
I wouldn't expect you to understand
anything about honor or legacy.
Amaya!
I've apprehended the intruders.
I'll escort them from the premises
and terminate them.
Move.
Don't move.
This one's a fake.
She's not one of us.
Step forward.
You are to be
reprocessed immediately.
That feel fake to you?
Stay close.
I don't wanna lose you in this crowd.
Is this as weird for you
as it is for me?
I've had messier breakups.
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
This is the second-worst
attack of the clones I've seen.
Please, please,
I don't wanna do this.
Gary.
Thank God. It's the real you.
Let's get back to the ship
before more show up.
Yeah.
You were right, Sara.
I'm never gonna be a mindless clone.
I'm keeping the suit.
Your totem
is still governed by my powers.
No.
What are you doing here?
I'm not here for you.
Get your ass up.
Nathaniel.
Love you, too.
Hardly seems like a fair fight.
Then I'd give up now.
I was talking about all of you.
If you cannot defeat me
in this vessel,
how will you stop me once
I've assumed my true form?
She's too strong. We have to leave.
I gave you life, Kuasa.
Offered you real power.
Family is true power.
I know you're in there
somewhere, Nora.
You have your father,
I have my grandmother.
We don't have to become our demons.
I like my demons.
Nana Baa.
Kuasa.
She should have known,
there's no running from Mallus.
- Amaya, we gotta get out of here.
- No!
- Amaya, we gotta go!
- Kuasa, no.
I'll do what you want,
just put me down.
Thanks.
No, it wasn't me, it was our totems.
Something's wrong.
It's Kuasa.
She's dead.
Yeah.
I need a drink.
Gary, you cannot tell anyone
about what you saw in 2213.
If you do,
I will straight up kill you.
But, I'm terrible at keeping secrets,
and every time I close my eyes,
all I see is you.
- I'll never get it out of my head.
- I wouldn't worry about it, Gary.
Gary, right this way.
I got a flasher with your name on it.
If I had known
that was gonna happen...
It's not your fault.
Still, I shouldn't have gone
behind your back.
And I shouldn't have tried
to outsmart the Darhks on my own.
You wanted me to have my totem back,
and now I do.
Come on, Amaya, just say it,
I got Kuasa killed.
I got my granddaughter killed.
You?
How?
By goading her
to be more like her sister.
Kuasa wanted to prove
that she was worthy of this.
She died proving
that I was wrong about her,
by saving the life of a man
who threatened her existence.
Exactly, and if
I didn't get captured,
- then Kuasa would have...
- Was doomed either way.
I mean, that's how time works.
Well, clearly,
time wants my family to suffer.
Amaya, you have to believe
you're in charge of your own destiny.
You know, there are times that I wish
I had never set foot on this ship.
If I'd never left 1942,
I would have returned to Zambesi
like I was supposed to.
With no idea of the tragedy
that awaited me.
I would have died an old woman.
Murdered by warlords.
And you and I never would have met.
Is that what you want, Amaya?
I don't know, Nathaniel.
Mmm.
I thought you couldn't eat.
Yeah, I told Gideon to tell me
when sundown would have been,
if I had been at home.
I mean, Ramadan's just a stupid
1,400-year-old tradition
to you, right?
So, why am I even talking about it?
Well, uh, how about
if I help you heat it up?
Try it, it's good for you.
You know,
I can't stop thinking about Kuasa.
I felt her die.
Well, me too.
Mind you, she did try
to kill us a couple times.
But she was a totem bearer
and Amaya's granddaughter.
And the totems supposedly
connect us to something larger.
Yeah, for better or worse.
You know, I think that's kind of
why I still fast.
When I was little,
my mom tried to get me to do it,
and I wouldn't, but she did make me
learn how to cook Iftar,
it's the meal we eat
to break the fast.
And while she cooked,
she would say that Ramadan's
not just a time for honoring God,
but a time
to honor tradition, family,
community.
So, whenever I fast or cook Iftar,
it makes me feel connected to my mom.
I'm hungry.
Still pork.
Still good.
You all right?
You know, maybe you should wipe
my memory, too.
How am I supposed
to face the Time Bureau now,
knowing what I know about myself?
The same way that I faced my team.
We don't have the luxury
of running away and hiding,
not with the fight we have
ahead of us.
Our team's gonna need us
to lead them through this.
You know, there must be some reason
that I don't remember anything
about 2213.
Anything about being a clone.
I'm sure there is.
Who recruited you for the Bureau?
Rip.
Well, I bet you that entire bottle,
he's the one who wiped your file
from the Bureau
and put 2213 off-limits.
- Why would he do that to me?
- I don't know.
But we're gonna find out.
Gideon, initialize the time drive
and set a course.
Traveling to this time period
is inadvisable.
I'm sure Captain Lance
would not allow it.
Please, Gideon.
I have to save my granddaughter.
I have to save my family.
And no one is going to stop me.
Now, lock in the coordinates.
Course set for the M'Changa Province
of Zambesi, 1992.