Vandal Savage.
An evil dictator
blessed with immortality.
He has achieved what no one
in human history ever has.
He has conquered the entire planet.
What's your name, son?
Jonas.
Your mother was brave.
Just as your father was foolish.
Which are you?
So, you take after your mother, huh?
Or not.
Caesar.
Hitler.
Per Degaton.
Rank amateurs compared to Savage.
His forces have already claimed
the lives of billions.
And if we possess the means
to stop him, and again,
do nothing,
then their blood is on our hands.
As a Time Master of long standing,
you seem to forget our responsibility
is to protect the timeline, not humanity.
You wish to engage in the very
sort of manipulation of time
that we are sworn to prevent.
And yet if we allow humanity
to perish at the hands of evil,
then what universe are we custodians of?
What if, in trying
to save the world from Savage,
you make it vulnerable
to another, more terrible, despot?
We are not warriors, Captain Hunter.
- We possess no army--
- And I'm not asking for one.
Just a single Timeship
and your permission to change history
before Vandal Savage puts an end to it.
I'm not appealing to you as Time Masters,
but as humans.
Please.
Grant me the authority to change
the timeline just this once.
How did the council meeting go,
Captain Hunter?
Exactly as expected, Gideon.
So we are proceeding?
Indeed.
Prepare the Waverider for takeoff.
Set a course.
United States, Star City, January, 2016.
Ah. The early
second-millennium A.D.
The golden age of gasoline
engines, online pornography,
and those silly little smart phones.
What are we going to retrieve, Captain?
Oh, not what. Who.
I need you to pull up some files, Gideon.
The eight men and women
who will be joining us
on our little crusade.
You usually prefer
to work alone, Captain.
This time, I'll need a team.
First recruit, Dr. Raymond Palmer.
Also known as the Atom.
This feels good.
Being back in the field.
Not that this is a field.
Ray, are you up for this?
Uh, too late to turn back now.
Huh. Someone removed
the central processing unit.
Are you sure?
I designed the computer's CPU,
so yeah, pretty sure.
Well, HIVE would only remove it
if they knew--
You had me shrink down and fly
into their secret computer lab.
My night's about to get
a whole lot worse, isn't it?
Oh, you can take them.
They have guns, you have a super-suit.
It's time to start growing.
This is gonna get a little rough.
Oh, I am not one of your adversaries.
Next recruit.
Sara Lance, former member
of the League of Assassins,
also formerly dead.
Miss Lance. Join me for a drink?
I have come quite a long way to meet you.
Firestorm. The merged superform
of one Jefferson Jackson
and Professor Martin Stein.
Caution, Jefferson.
83% of the chemicals
in this factory are combustible.
Yeah. Tell that to Rambo.
I thought I told you to be careful.
What's the use of sharing my intelligence
if you won't listen?
Stop bossing me around
like I'm one of your
snot-nosed undergrads.
- Excuse me.
- Who are you?
Kendra Saunders and Carter Hall.
The latest reincarnations
of Hawkman and Hawkgirl.
Kendra!
You, my love, almost got us killed.
Thank you.
Your flying is still clumsy,
like a bird just out of the nest.
Well, maybe that's because
up until two months ago,
I was a barista, not some
damn winged demi-goddess.
Have you two
considered couples counseling?
I hear it's quite popular in this century.
There seems to be an error,
Captain.
These candidates,
Leonard Snart and Mick Rory,
- are a pair of criminals.
- There's no error, Gideon.
Drop your weapons!
Fry, you little piggies!
A minivan? Really, Snart?
Cops'll never hassle a dad buying diapers
in the middle of the night.
- What the...
- Watch it!
What a headache.
Stein?
The hell are you doing here?
I'm as ignorant as you for once.
Where are we?
Why don't you ask the dude who
knocked us out and kidnapped us?
British dude with a flashy thing
ring any bells?
The name's Rip Hunter!
I'm from East London. Oh.
And the future.
Nice to meet you, Rip.
Uh, while you were incapacitated,
I may have tampered with your weapons.
I've assembled you all
because I need your help.
The future of the world is in peril
because of a man
by the name of Vandal Savage.
That can't be. We destroyed him.
Yeah. The Green Arrow and Flash
helped us do it.
And therein lay the problem.
Unless you or Mr. Hall
deliver the death blow,
Savage can be restored
from but a single cell.
The hell are you talking about?
Vandal is immortal.
Kendra and I reincarnate.
Yeah, I've done that.
What the hell does this
Randall guy gotta do with us?
Vandal.
In the future, he will employ
the evil he's perfected
over his long life,
and the power he's amassed
throughout history,
to finally conquer the world.
I've been tasked with assembling
an elite team to stop him.
How?
To travel through time,
to capture Savage before he grows into
the monster he becomes.
You got the wrong guy.
- "Hero" ain't on my resume.
- Or mine.
I know it's difficult
for you to fathom, but where...
When I'm from, the year 2166,
you and everyone on this roof
aren't just considered heroes.
You're legends.
Legends?
I, uh, hate to nitpick, but doesn't
a legend have to be dead?
Yeah. See, uh, that's a deal-breaker
for me, so I'm gonna pass.
It's dangerous for any of you to know
too much about your own futures,
but I am here because
each of you, as individuals,
is destined for greatness.
I could get behind that.
And because if you don't follow me,
this is what is in store for
your world, 150 years from now.
I could've chosen any time and any place.
Of all the people who ever lived,
I chose you eight.
I certainly hope that you
won't let me and the world down.
If your answer is yes, meet me
at this address in 36 hours.
- I had that.
- I know.
And it's fun to watch you kick
and punch and skewer bad guys,
but I need a minute of your time.
I'm sure Captain Hunter will
return me to the moment I left,
but I thought, you know, just in case,
someone should know I was gone.
We went up against Savage.
He does not go down easy.
That's why Hunter's recruited a team.
A team that includes
Leonard Snart and Mick Rory.
So what do you know about Captain Hunter?
He's a Time Master from the 22nd century.
He's a little hard to google.
So you know nothing,
and yet you trust him?
I'm as trusting as you are cynical.
Oh, I'm cynical and it's difficult
for me to trust anyone.
But that has kept me alive.
I died once.
At least the world thought I did.
And you know what happened?
Nothing.
All the money, all the buildings,
all the inventions,
the world didn't care.
My life ultimately didn't matter.
Rip has given me the chance
to help save the world.
I have to take it.
Keep your head on a swivel
while you're at it.
Two hundred and six times.
Savage has killed both of us 206 times--
Yeah, and I'm not too eager
about making it 207.
So, what?
You just gonna run away?
We've tried that before.
Look, I know you don't remember
your past lives yet,
but I remember so much of it.
God, if you only knew
how I loved you and how much...
How much it hurt every time
he took you away from me.
Have you ever stopped to think
that maybe,
just maybe, we can't actually beat him?
But this time,
we wouldn't be facing him alone.
And we almost defeated him
with help before.
Yeah, almost.
Kendra, this is our best chance
to stop him forever.
The woman I've loved for millennia
wouldn't be scared of this.
Look.
Past lives, we'd fight, argue.
A lot.
But we'd settle matters as warriors.
What, like I beat you
and you give up this plan
to follow Hunter?
Yeah.
Except you won't be able to beat me.
But you can absolutely try.
Winner gets to decide, little lady.
I remember when you told Mom and Dad
that you wanted to go to sleepaway camp.
This will be a little different.
Time travel.
I can't even believe
we're talking about it
like it's something real.
I know.
I think you should go.
Laurel...
I died.
I'm still picking up those pieces.
The Lazarus Pit brought me back,
but it left me with this need to take,
to kill.
I'm dangerous.
After you died,
I needed a channel for my grief.
I found it in becoming the Black Canary.
I found it in you.
For me, being the Canary
was never that positive.
Then don't be the Canary.
Do what Oliver's been doing.
Do what this Rip Hunter
is offering you the chance to do and...
Be a hero in the light.
Be the White Canary.
Where did you get this?
I have a resourceful friend named Cisco.
Where's the mask?
You don't need it anymore.
You've lived in the shadows long enough.
I can't believe you're thinking
of hooking up
with the Englishman.
We're thieves, crooks, criminals.
I have no desire to save the world.
Especially 100 years after I'm dead.
He said across time, Mick.
What about the years before?
Before fingerprints
and surveillance cameras
and DNA analysis.
Why did we become criminals?
Because we hate working and we love money.
We could steal the Mona Lisa
straight off da Vinci's easel,
snatch the Hope diamond
before it was discovered.
This is everything we got into
thieving for in the first place.
More than everything.
You want me in, I'm in.
But I'm not gonna be anyone's hero.
Jefferson, it's imperative
we remain together
for our powers to work.
In case you haven't noticed,
I'm still getting used to
the whole powers thing,
and now that you're adding
time travel to the mix--
Do you have any idea what
an extraordinary opportunity
we've been given?
A chance to get murdered
by an immortal psychopath.
No, thanks.
Look, I'm a 20-year-old
auto mechanic.
The world is better off
without me trying to save it.
I don't understand your decision.
But I respect it.
Perhaps I can persuade Mr. Hunter
that he needs my knowledge as a physicist
and not my abilities as Firestorm.
So I propose we have a toast.
To my grand and solo adventure.
To saving the world.
Knock yourself out.
You took the words right out of my mouth.
Professor!
This is the place.
I think we're being punked.
- Do people still say "punked"?
- No.
I see your buddy threw himself
a going-away party.
Yes. I believe he drank something
that didn't quite agree with him.
You don't look too happy to be here.
- Perceptive.
- Well.
I see you've all decided to come.
Well, then we can be on our way.
I ain't footing it anywhere.
A Time Master's sacred charge
is to do no harm to the timeline.
Can you imagine
what a Timeship would look like
in, say, Victorian England?
Holographic indigenous
camouflage projection.
Indeed.
It's called the Waverider.
It's been my ship for over a decade.
Shall we?
Excuse me. Would you mind, um...
Thank you.
Whoa.
I bet it uses ionic propulsion.
I doubt that very much, given
that even advanced technology
wouldn't be able to sustain
an ionic reaction.
It's possible if you stabilized
the quantum flux.
Yeah, we actually covered
this before, Professor Stein,
when I was your student many moons ago.
Perhaps you remember my paper
on subspace field mechanics.
- I don't remember you, Mr. Palmer.
- Oh.
Whatever you roofied him with,
I'd like some.
I did not roofie him.
Oh, I ain't judging.
I have never seen
anything like this before.
Neither have I.
And considering I have
4,000 years worth of memories,
that's saying something.
How does a vessel of this size
function without a crew?
I don't need one. I have Gideon.
Welcome aboard.
I am Gideon, an interactive
artificial consciousness
programmed to operate
this vessel's critical systems
and aid Captain Hunter in his mission.
"Captain"?
Gideon's been working on
helping me locate Vandal Savage.
I thought you said he's pretty
active in the 22nd century.
Perhaps engaging Savage
at the height of his powers
isn't the best stratagem.
Indeed.
Unfortunately, Savage has kept
his movements
hidden throughout history.
Not even Gideon can determine
where or when we can find him.
But I have the next best thing.
The man who can.
Professor Aldus Boardman.
Now, Professor Boardman
is the world's leading, well,
only expert on Vandal Savage.
We're going to pay him a little visit.
Course plotted for St. Roch,
New Orleans.
- St. Roch?
- October 17, 1975.
I suggest you all strap yourselves in.
Temporal navigation isn't something
one wants to be standing up for.
Time travel.
Cool.
Some of you may experience
some slight discomfort.
In very rare instances, there will be
some, uh, bleeding from the eyeballs.
I'm sorry, what?
The human body is used to
time unfolding linearly.
Oh, Jax, I'm so glad you're awake.
I didn't want you to miss this.
Miss what?
What the...
I wouldn't unfasten those if I were you.
Get me off this... Whatever this thing is!
Good luck explaining this.
I did him a favor.
He doesn't look all that grateful.
Just hang on and remain calm.
All of your worlds are about to change.
Whoa.
Seriously.
That was insanity.
Whoa. That is some serious
Darth Vader going on there.
Chronos to Command.
I am closing in
on Captain Hunter's position.
Hey, what you doing there, bro?
I am determining whether you are
integral to the timeline.
Okay.
You are not.
Oh, I should have mentioned it before,
nausea is one of the side effects
of time travel, along with--
Vertigo.
- I can't see.
- And temporary blindness.
It should only last a minute.
After all, that was a mere jaunt.
The further back in time you go,
the worse the side effects.
- Better?
- It's all relative.
Good.
I can't believe you kidnapped me.
Hey. I want to go home.
Good news, then.
2016 will be around in, uh, 41 years.
Now, you three, feel free
to make yourselves comfortable
back here on the ship,
while the rest of you are coming with me
to find Professor Boardman.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You're benching us?
I thought we were a team.
This mission doesn't require
your particular skill-set. Yet.
Meaning, you don't need anyone
killed, maimed, or robbed.
Precisely.
Sure it's a good idea to
leave these two unsupervised
on a time machine?
Hey, haircut.
Deafness wasn't one of the side effects.
We better hurry up. Professor Boardman
will die in less than 24 hours.
What's the point of cutting it so close?
Because if he's destined to die
then he doesn't have a timeline
for us to disrupt
and his impact on the future
will be minimal.
How brilliant.
And depressing.
How does he die?
He's found dead in his
university from unknown causes.
Come on.
- Are you coming?
- I'll stay put.
You'd rather stay with them?
They didn't drug me.
Point taken.
This is unbelievable. 1975.
Imagine all the wondrous applications
for this technology.
A chance to witness the
construction of the pyramids,
the end of the dinosaurs.
I've never been to 1975.
It's rather colorful.
So, where can we find Professor Boardman?
In his lecture hall.
Oh, no, we're too late.
I'm sorry.
You.
Both of you.
You know who we are?
I've been studying you my whole life.
Ever since, as a child,
I first heard the story
of Chay-Ara High Priestess
of Horus, the Hawk God,
and her lover, Prince Khufu.
I hoped and prayed this day might come.
Well, it looks like
we've come to the right place.
I'm sorry. Who are you?
A fellow historian,
here to discuss another passion of yours.
Vandal Savage.
There's no way of telling your story
without telling his also.
Why does this stupid station
play nothing but re-runs?
Don't even bother trying to explain.
Am I the only one on this ship
who could really use a drink?
I say, we go get weird in the '70s.
Excellent idea.
I got the perfect outfit.
Perhaps Captain Hunter
was unclear
with his instructions to remain onboard?
- Shut it, metal-mouth.
- Ooh.
You're not quite ready
to run with this crew.
Sorry, kid.
Wait, you're just gonna leave me here?
I said I'd take care of you.
Four thousand years ago,
Vandal Savage was an Egyptian priest,
secretly in love with a priestess.
You.
Or rather, you in your first life.
But you were in love with another.
Prince Khufu.
Savage, or Hath-Set, as he was then known,
learned of the affair and
was consumed with jealous rage.
You believe me yet?
Which drove him to murder you both.
And prayed for the Hawk God, Horus,
to damn the objects of his hate
for all eternity.
But Chay-Ara had a prayer of her own.
That Horus would protect them forever.
But another life was
bound to theirs by accident.
Savage's.
That's why he wants us both dead.
My theory is that the three of you
were exposed to the same
radiation by the meteorites.
We all share the same power.
And every time he kills you,
it passes to him.
That's what maintains his immortality.
That's impossible.
Unless the meteorites contained
a mutative element,
like the particle accelerator
that caused your powers.
But without evidence.
You're asking us to take you at your word.
It's not my word.
It's theirs.
But you still don't remember me, do you?
We knew you in our past lives?
You've told me your entire story,
stretching back through the ages.
But when I first knew you,
it was after World War I.
And your names were Joe and Edith.
Edith Boardman.
Wait, we were related?
I don't remember you.
I'm so sorry.
Don't be.
You always warned me,
that if I ran into you in your next life,
you might have forgotten me.
That's us.
At the world's fair.
You're just as beautiful
as I remember you.
Mother.
How old were you when...
You two were murdered?
Ten.
My whole life, you taught me
to be careful, keep moving
always one step ahead of Savage.
But after tracking you for
4,000 years, he'd gotten good.
He found us in the middle of the night,
at a fleabag motel in North Carolina.
You hid me in the closet,
made me promise that no matter
what I heard, I'd stay put.
And I did.
Sorry to interrupt your family time,
but we were hoping you could tell us
a bit more where to locate
Savage's present whereabouts.
He hides in the shadows,
never drawing too much attention.
But every lifetime placing
himself near the seat of power,
sowing seeds of destruction.
Who remembers the name of the man
who whispered in the ear
of Gavrilo Princip,
and convinced him to start World War I?
But why? What does he get out of that?
The more the world is focused
on destroying itself,
the less it notices an immortal
psychopath in its midst.
With the ultimate goal of
subjugating the entire planet.
He killed your parents,
Professor Boardman.
Something tells me you know
where to locate Vandal Savage.
I have an educated guess.
Ah, dollar beers?
You got to love the '70s.
Who wants to listen to
some Captain & Tennille?
My mother played it.
A lot.
Wow. You guys are really far out.
You wanna dance, Leonard?
You go right ahead.
I'll watch.
Suit yourself.
Can I help you?
How about you join me in the parking lot?
Mmm. Tempting. But you're not my type.
But your lady on the other hand,
she looks just my speed.
Maybe you didn't understand
my request, bitch.
Son of a...
I got this.
Now I could stand for a little help.
I love the '70s.
Gideon? That is your name, right?
How may I help you?
I assume this ship has
an auto-pilot or something?
You assume correctly.
Great. In that case, I'm gonna need you
to take me back to 2016.
See, me being here,
it's all a big mistake.
Captain Hunter told me
you'd try to do this.
And he also told me not to
listen to anything you say.
Whoa. You are a computer!
You have to listen to me!
You seem overwrought, Mr. Jackson.
If you'd like to go to the MedBay,
I'd be happy to prescribe you a sedative.
I do not need another roofie!
Whoa!
What was that?
A thermite grenade.
It seems someone is trying
to breach the hull.
His name is Chronos.
He's a temporal bounty hunter.
The ship is taking heavy fire.
I know! Aren't we supposed to be
invisible or something?
You need to get us out of here, now!
A lifetime of research on Vandal Savage
that all points in this direction.
This should help you find him.
And the vengeance that
has eluded me all these years.
Jefferson. Something is
happening to Jefferson.
We seem to have a little problem
back at the, uh, vessel.
There's an intruder.
We really must be going now.
Thank you for everything.
Wait. We can't just leave him here.
We have to get back now.
You said he's going to die in 24 hours.
And we can stop it--
Are either of you a Time Master?
I didn't think so.
I've spent years studying the implications
of chronological alteration.
Good for you.
But we're not going anywhere
unless our son's coming with us.
Why is Chronos attacking us?
Perhaps Captain Hunter is best
suited to answer that query.
Fire photon torpedoes or something!
Only Captain Hunter
is authorized--
Where is Captain Hunter?
Dr. Palmer, please tell me...
I didn't leave my exo-suit on the ship?
Okay, but I'd be lying.
Who the hell is this guy?
Is that a laser gun?
I gotta get back to the ship
and bond with Jefferson.
Cover me!
Cover me, too.
Oh, you crazy old man.
Thank you, Mr. Palmer.
Seriously? It's Dr. Palmer.
Get down!
Ah!
We need to merge!
We go out for one lousy drink
and you guys somehow manage
to pick a fight with Boba Fett.
- Aldus.
- We'll get you out of here.
Professor Boardman has
sustained severe internal injuries.
Prepare the MedBay
to receive Professor Boardman
and get us out of here.
- Course heading?
- Anywhere but here!
Our cloaking shield
and aft entrance
have been significantly
compromised, Captain.
Yes, I can see that, Gideon.
Station us in the temporal zone
while I work on repairs.
- Temporal zone?
- It's essentially a, uh, time limbo.
We can hide out there for a bit.
Another temporal jump would
risk revealing our position.
A time limbo. Astonishing.
Well, there's something you people
don't know about time travel.
Surprising, isn't it,
considering none of you
have ever time traveled before.
Bringing a family member
from the past onto a Timeship.
Breaking out
and carousing around the 1970s.
We've barely begun
and already this is the worst,
unmitigated disaster of my career.
I see why you've got the hots
for that one.
My son is hurt because of you.
Who attacked us?
That's something of a long story.
Better tell it fast, Rip.
'Cause it doesn't look like
the lady's in a patient mood.
And neither am I.
His name is Chronos.
He works for the Council of Time Masters.
My former employers.
I thought you were a Time Master.
As I've expressed,
time's not a linear thing.
At some point, I was, in fact,
a Time Master.
Will you people please stop hitting me?
Start telling the truth.
I relinquished my position
as a Time Master
when I commandeered the Waverider.
Chronos was clearly sent to bring me in.
- You lied to us.
- Of course I lied to you.
I needed your help and you
all barely said yes as it was.
What about the legends part?
You lied about that, too, didn't you?
I chose you all
because 100 years from now,
your lives have minimal effect
on the recorded timeline.
I needed your help without
disturbing the history of 2166.
So we're like the opposite of legends.
Give me one good reason
why we shouldn't kill you.
Ditto the arsonist.
Because Gideon wouldn't listen
to your commands
and you'd be stuck here forever.
Great. So, we're not
an elite team of heroes
on a sanctioned mission
sent to rid the future
of its most horrific bad guy.
Just a collection of nobodies
who time really doesn't give a damn about.
I didn't lie about the mission itself.
Or the brutality
and ruthlessness of Savage.
Or my need for your help.
I don't imagine you're the kind
of guy who quits his job
and takes on this kind of threat
for altruistic reasons.
So, Rip, why don't you tell us,
what did Vandal Savage do to you?
The Time Masters discourage marriage.
They urge against procreation even more.
A Time Master should be free
of any personal entanglements
that might compromise him.
But I fell in love.
And we had a child.
A boy.
Jonas.
Savage killed your family.
He slaughtered my family.
And thousands of other families.
And the body that I swore an oath to serve
turned a blind eye.
They continue to turn a blind eye.
I won't.
The last thing that
my child saw in this world
was that monster's face.
You can be damn well sure
that when Savage dies,
the last face he sees will be mine.
I understand, given the circumstances,
if you wish to return home.
We can make a jump
once the repairs are done,
if and when
Professor Boardman stabilizes.
I think we all need a little time
to consider our options.
Just get some rest.
There's something I wanted you to have.
It's around my neck.
It was my mother's.
Yours.
It's beautiful.
I remember it.
Thank you.
Rip wouldn't have allowed me
to bring Aldus onboard if you hadn't--
Of course.
Chay-Ara.
Sorry, Kendra.
No. It's okay.
Chay-Ara is fine.
It seems an apology is in order.
What I did was wrong.
I should never have forced you
to come along,
but for me, the opportunity
to travel through time,
see the mysteries
of the universe revealed,
notions I've spent my whole life studying.
Please do not geek out
on quantum physics right now.
Mr. Hunter was offering grand adventure.
And at my age, you never know
how many adventures you have left.
Hey.
I saw your 40-yard dash onto the ship
with that Chronos guy shooting at you.
I think you got plenty of adventures left.
Yes. Perhaps you're right.
Back home, as Firestorm.
And what if I don't want
to go home? Yet, I mean.
Why the change of heart?
You ever play football?
Yeah, I didn't think so.
Anyway...
The best feeling I ever got
from being on the field wasn't
when I made a great play,
or we won some game.
It was when one of my teammates
took a tackle for me,
and I knew they were
gonna make sure I was safe,
that nobody got to me.
Watching all of you rush back
to this ship,
even those two knuckleheads,
to take on Chronos,
made me feel the same way.
I like being part of a team, man.
Me, too.
Watch it!
Sorry.
What's the point of us even
giving this a second thought?
Rip has already seen the future,
he knows exactly
what's in store for each of us.
Might as well have stayed dead.
'Cause the world doesn't need any of us.
You're just a lost assassin,
you're just a pair
of good-for-nothing criminals.
I can live with that.
Well, I can't.
I can't live with somebody
putting a cap on my destiny.
I've spent my whole life
working to be something greater
by becoming something smaller.
And then some guy comes along
and tells me
that being the Atom is as
insignificant as an actual atom.
That's not what he said.
Rip said that in his future,
we're nobodies.
But this mission
is about changing the future.
If we have the power to change the world,
don't you think we have the power
to change our own fate?
For better or for worse.
That's a very good point.
What do you think, Gideon?
I calculate
a less than 6% likelihood
that they decide to go on
with the mission.
I meant about the repairs.
And there has been another
unfortunate consequence
of Chronos' attack.
- Care to hear about it?
- Not really.
He's gone.
Our son.
Or our son from a previous life.
It's all too confusing.
I'm very sorry.
Actually, you don't get
the blame for this.
This was my fault.
If I hadn't insisted
on bringing him back here,
he might've died peacefully.
In his sleep, maybe.
Don't torture yourself
with recriminations.
One of the great lessons
of time travel is that
many things cannot be changed.
Time wants to happen.
Chronos, even Vandal,
won't be the only enemy we face.
Very often, it will be time itself.
Whether it wants to happen
or not, we're gonna change time,
erase Savage's future
and earn our rightful place in history.
Dr. Palmer is correct.
We may not be legends
in your time, Captain,
but we are going to decide our own fates.
I don't give a damn about being a legend,
as long as we end Savage
once and for all.
I can get down with that.
And our malcontents?
I like killing people.
We're in. For now.
So how do we find this guy?
Professor Boardman
had a theory about that.
I've already had Gideon plot a course.
Do you know what this is?
An instrument to
make this world a better place.
History teaches us
that the cause of humanity
is only advanced through strife.
There is no Renaissance
without the Dark Ages.
Man had no interest in splitting
the atom until World War II.
I am just trying to make
this world a better place,
one war at a time.
English - SDH