My name is Sara Lance.
Last year, a former Time Master
named Rip Hunter
recruited a team of heroes
and villains to save the world,
and we did.
But in the process,
we destroyed the Time Masters.
Now, we've taken up their mantle
of protecting the timeline
from time criminals.
We are no longer saving the world.
We are saving history.
But don't call us heroes.
We are legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Heywood. Dr. Nate Heywood.
I need to talk to you about
Sara Lance, Ray Palmer
and the rest of the Legends.
I think they're all in trouble.
I am piloting us on a collision
course with a torpedo.
Gideon.
I'm here, Captain.
Where's Captain Hunter?
I would be happy to play
his final message for you all.
Together, you are the best crew.
The best team a captain
could ever hope for.
Good luck.
What do you guys say
we get out of 1942?
Not until you answer a few questions.
We're the Justice Society of America.
And you're coming with us.
Oh, my God.
You're Commander Steel.
Who the hell are you?
Whoa, whoa. Just relax.
We're all friends here.
Rex Tyler told us about the JSA.
You guys are awesome.
Hey. The name's Jax.
Rex never mentioned any of you.
Mind telling us what you were doing
impersonating OSS agents?
It's quite simple, actually.
We were protecting Albert Einstein
from Nazi agents
who were attempting to kidnap him
and force him to build an atomic bomb
in the future.
Time travel.
It's... it's hard to explain.
You can take all the time you need.
In custody.
Whoa, take it easy.
Let's talk for a minute.
I mean, after all, you're my...
Obsidian, shut off the lights!
Wow, that's pretty neat.
She's trying to kill us!
No, she's just flirting.
We don't want to fight!
You win!
You just had to mention time travel,
didn't you?
Yeah, well, at least
he didn't throw the first punch.
I'm perfectly capable
of defending myself, Raymond.
I'm pretty sure that you got
knocked out
by a teenager
in a star-spangled leotard.
Her name's Stargirl.
Did anybody catch her
regular-person name?
I'm surprised you didn't ask
for her number.
Oh, so it's my fault that
we got our asses handed to us?
Look, they're just better
coordinated than us.
You guys,
just listen to me for two...
Pretty, shut up.
If I recall, you were late coming
to the party.
Oh, is that right?
How did you see that?
Never laid eyes on them
before in my life.
They seemed quite adamant
that they knew you.
Believe me, if I'd met this bunch...
pretty sure I'd remember.
What do you propose we do with them?
If I may be so bold, sir...
I say we find the darkest hole in
Leavenworth and throw away the key.
I say we ship them to the boys
in Bellevue Mental Hospital.
I suppose before we do anything...
we ought to question them.
So far up Mr. Goggle's...
If we can even manage
to get a word in.
I don't understand why they were
tracking us in the first place.
Because they're the Justice Society
of America.
The single greatest secret force
this country has ever known.
If it's so secret,
how do you know about them?
Because his Nazi handlers
have briefed him, no doubt.
Look, I'm not a Nazi.
I'm a historian.
Here we go with the time travel
nonsense again.
070233.
What?
Those are numbers on your dog tags.
They're not disclosed on any
documents, military or otherwise.
How do you know that?
You gave these to your wife
after the birth of your son in 1955.
The dent in the front was
from an assassin's bullet
when you saved
President Roosevelt in 1939.
Your son passed them down
to his son...
me.
You are late, Herr Thawne.
You'll find that I have an entirely
different concept of time than most.
Did you locate the item?
It's in Berlin.
The Fuehrerrefuses to part with it.
I have something much
more valuable to offer him.
The JSA are basically a group
of super-soldiers.
To win,
the Reichwill need their own.
This is just a taste.
Enough to dose one person.
Proof of concept.
Give me what I want...
and your Fuehrerwill be planting his
flag on the White House lawn
within a matter of months.
Do we have an accord?
Mr. Tyler.
See? Rex Tyler.
Told you we knew the guy.
I don't know you.
Any of you.
Tell me what the heck is going
on here.
Well, we tried explaining...
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I was addressing the team leader.
Uh, oh...
Oh, well, simply put,
we've come here as time travelers
to identify aberrations in history
and correct them.
We're superheroes, like you guys.
You think you're just like us?
What are your qualifications?
Well, I used my personal fortune
to create an advanced exo-skeleton,
which is powered by dwarf star alloy.
And I'm nothing like you.
I'm a criminal.
Are there any other
felons on your team?
- No, no...
- Yes.
She's an assassin,
but never convicted, right?
We're protecting history.
It's pretty important.
In the future, you risk your own life
to save us, Mr. Tyler.
How do you know my name?
Because you told us your name
in 2016.
My name is Rex Tyler.
And I'm a member of the Justice
Society of America.
Never heard of them, pal.
That's because I'm from 1942.
The same year in which
all of you will...
Bite the bullet?
So if we don't go back to 1942,
we're safe, right?
Not to be rude,
but how... how do we know you are
who you say you are?
You all have no idea
what you're up against.
If you return to 1942,
the consequences
will be catastrophic.
That was weird.
So I crashed your ship,
told you some bunk
about not staying in 1942
and then I just disappeared?
It was more like "fritzing" out.
You might've been on to something
with the Bellevue idea.
Yes, Mr. President, sir?
FDR?
Oh, tell him I'm a big fan
of the New Deal.
Hey, uh, I'm sorry about earlier.
I just, uh...
I never imagined meeting you
like this.
I actually never imagined meeting you
at all because you're dead.
I mean, where I come from, you're...
you're dead.
My dad used to tell me
bedtime stories about you.
All the battles you fought.
You're a hero to me.
I'm a hero to a lot of people.
That's the job.
Of course. All right.
You can count on us, sir.
All right, we have to move out.
Baron Krieger's been spotted
in Paris.
If it's permissible, sir...
I'll fly ahead and record
Krieger's movements.
Sensible, as always.
We could help you out with that.
Fighting Nazis is kind of our thing.
Yeah. Last time we tried,
we ended up at the bottom
of the Atlantic Ocean.
We can handle Adolf's buddies.
I think it's best
for the 20th century if...
For us to leave it?
And that's why you're team leader.
Well, I guess
we'll be on our way, then.
Can you believe what we just saw
with our own eyes?
The actual JSA.
And Hourman? That guy's amazing.
Aw, haircut's in love.
Come on.
Those guys were precise,
professional, in constant agreement.
We can't even agree on
whose turn it is to make dinner.
Not it.
I can't argue with you, man.
They got some serious skills.
Big deal.
Apart from the fancy headquarters,
discipline
and calls from
the White House...
I mean, what do they have
that we don't?
An actual leader.
Rip's gone.
And who knows when
or if we'll ever find him.
In the meantime, we need someone
who can make the tough calls.
Let me guess, you're volunteering?
With all due respect, Raymond,
I think there's a reason
Mr. Tyler just naturally assumed
I was in charge.
Yeah, because Mr. Tyler is from 1942
and you're some old white dude.
"Old," meaning experienced.
- What about...
- Martin's right.
With Rip gone, we could use
some adult supervision.
Congratulations, Captain.
Well, then.
Thank you all for your support.
Now, I believe our first order
of business concerns Dr. Heywood.
Is that Grandpa?
Yeah.
Pictures of him are hard to find.
You just got to know where to look.
Well, that must've been something,
getting the chance to meet him.
You would think so, right? But...
I don't know.
Felt empty somehow.
Well, meeting your idols
usually does.
Think of it this way.
You are gonna have one hell
of a story to tell your friends
when you get back home.
Back home? 2016 back home?
You can't cut me from the team.
Well, you're right,
because you're not a member of it.
And even if you were,
history can be dangerous,
and it's no place for a...
A historian? I'm more than...
that's weird.
It's really not so weird.
You don't have any superpowers.
You don't even have training...
Not that. My grandfather's dog tags.
They aren't around my neck.
So?
So I haven't taken them off
since I was a kid.
They were here a minute ago,
and now they've...
Vanished.
What does that mean?
That history has changed.
What are you doing?
Reviewing my notes on the JSA.
We have to go back to 1942.
Nate, the JSA was pretty explicit
on us not going back to 1942.
That mission the JSA went on to
track down Baron Krieger in Paris?
They're all gonna die there tomorrow.
My grandfather too.
And this is where
the JSA's gonna die?
Not unless we save them,
including my grandfather.
Well, first we got to find them.
Fortunately, we know they're looking
for a Nazi named Krieger.
A Nazi named Krieger...
Can someone please help me
operate this thing?
Oh, God.
Thank you.
Krieger and his men
frequent Folies-Bergère.
We find Krieger, we find the JSA.
So how do we sneak
into a Nazi nightclub?
I have a plan.
Are any of you familiar
with Max Suelzenfuss,
better known by his stage name,
Max Lorenz?
He was Hitler's favorite singer
and fortunately, bears a passing
resemblance to moi.
That's French.
Grey. Are you sure about this?
Because bluffing at a card game
isn't exactly the same
as bluffing Nazis.
You disapprove of my plan?
I'm just saying, we're dropping
into the middle of World War II here
and you're not exactly
a wartime consigliere.
- And let me guess, you are?
- I...
Or perhaps you would prefer
the arsonist, the assassin
or the incredible shrinking man?
I'm just saying, you're smart
and analytical and stuff,
and real deliberate.
But when bullets start flying,
analytical is not gonna cut it.
Well, thank you for pointing
out my inadequacies.
- Come on, Grey.
- It's Captain Grey, now.
Well, I'm glad it hasn't gone
to your head.
Ouch. Where'd you get that?
It must have happened when I fell
after my grandfather decked me.
Hey, that fabrication room's
pretty cool.
Can it really make clothes
from any era?
Yeah, you know,
we may not have trophies
or framed letters
from former presidents
but we've got a few cool toys.
Including ingestible translator.
Swallow this, you'll be able to speak
and understand any language
spoken to you.
That's cool.
But I already speak German, French,
Japanese, Italian, and Latin.
What?
You speak six different languages,
you have a tendency
to run towards danger.
And you're related to a member
of the JSA.
Why did you become a historian?
It's a long story.
Hey, where do I go to get a gun?
You ever shoot someone before?
I mean, I may not be trained
by the League of Assassins
but I can take care of myself.
Not out here, you can't.
Out here, even the strongest
and the bravest of us die.
Like Captain Hunter?
I'm just trying to make sure
you get home safe and sound.
So the lady does have a heart.
Don't tell anyone.
Excuse me...
The club is closed tonight
for a private function.
Do you have any idea who I am?
I am Max Lorenz.
- Did you say Max Lorenz?
- Yes.
And I have never been treated
with such rudeness.
Of course not.
You're more than welcome here,
Herr Max.
Thank you.
No sign of Krieger or the JSA.
Canvass the area
and stay on the comms.
Think I got something.
The lady with the animal powers.
But she looks different.
You mean hot.
May I?
What are you doing?
I'm on a covert mission.
Not for long.
You and your team are all
24 hours away from being killed.
What are you talking about?
I'm a time traveler, remember?
Something changes in the future,
and you all die.
But if we do, how do you know
it's not because of your team?
Hadn't thought of that.
Look who I found, and she's thrilled
we've offered our help.
Herr Lorenz, I must introduce you
to General Gerd von Rundstedt.
He's a huge fan.
Oh, lovely to meet you, General.
You are Max Lorenz?
Lorenz is well over 6ft tall.
Ah.
My towering voice often causes people
to overestimate my height.
Perhaps, you will treat us to a song,
Mr. Lorenz?
Maxie has a concert tomorrow night
and needs to rest his pipes.
I insist, Fraulein.
And, please...
no Negro music.
I swa...
not worth it.
It'd be a little worth it.
Heads up. Baron Krieger just arrived.
Is this on?
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
My name is Max Lorenz,
and this little waltz...
I am about to sing for you
is an original song.
Uh, very popular in Austria
where... where the hills are alive
with the sound of music.
Key of A.
Watch me for the changes
and try to keep up.
One, two, three.
Edelweiss
Every morning
You greet me
Small and white
Clean and bright
You look happy to meet me
No, no, Herr Krieger, please.
The Askaran Amulet is
not degenerate artwork.
It is a masterpiece.
Which you will help my men transport
to the exchange tomorrow at 01000.
Refusing would meet
with the Fuehrer'sdisapproval.
Edelweiss
I know the Baron's plan.
Let's get out of here.
- Hey.
- Edelweiss
Bless my homeland
Forever
Heil Hitler!
You did not salute the Fuehrer.
Oh, yeah. Sure, I did.
I'm all about saluting the Fuehrer.
You're lying.
I was watching you the entire time.
You know what? I... I just...
I have a little crick in my neck.
And it's really hard for me
to straighten my arm.
Heil Hitler.
Heil Hitler!
Ha...
Ha... aw, hell.
Why do you get to punch him?
Protect Max Lorenz!
What the hell are you doing here?
We came back to...
to rescue you.
If we're meant to be impressed
by all this technology...
it has the opposite effect.
It only makes you
that much more dangerous.
Well, and there's evidence
to support that,
but I think what's important now
is for all us to stop arguing.
Does your team ever stop arguing?
Fair point.
I think what Martin is trying to say
we're gonna help you
whether you like it or not.
You're going after Krieger.
We know where he's going next.
And given the laws
of temporal mechanics, if you die...
your grandson ceases to exist.
Well, I don't pretend to understand
any of this time travel bunk
but, these fellas do have a timeship.
Might come in handy.
And having them as our back-up
might be the only way
to keep them out of trouble.
Let's put it to a vote, then.
The ayes have it.
Did your reconnaissance at the club
yield any usable intel?
Only to map the area.
Bringing one online now.
- What was that?
- AI.
A talking computer.
What's a computer?
There. The Fontainebleau Forest.
Now, I saw a few of Krieger's
men studying a map of it.
That must be where Krieger's
planning on making the exchange.
Nate overheard Krieger talking about
making a trade for something
called an Askaran Amulet.
Hitler has long amassed
ancient artifacts such as this one.
He may want the amulet because
it conveys some sort of occult power.
Our objective should be
to take out the Baron
and stop this exchange at all costs.
I propose we survey all military
activity in the area
to learn what we're up against.
We don't have time for that.
I concur.
We should have both teams gear up
while Dr. Stein and I finalize
the details.
Be ready to go at first light.
How are things with your grandfather?
You know? I think he's avoiding me
for some reason.
Well, it's hard for people
to look at their future.
Maybe.
Oh, one of the Nazis
at the club had a knife.
Well, that should have
stopped bleeding by now.
I'm just gonna get a new bandage.
To go with your bruise?
Well, you know how fragile
we historians can be.
This isn't fragility.
I know my cuts and bruises.
You're a hemophiliac.
Your blood doesn't clot,
wounds can't heal.
And if it's bad,
you can bleed to death.
Yeah, well, you don't have
to worry about that.
Too late. You could've died tonight.
But I didn't.
In fact, it was the opposite.
I never felt more alive.
Look, when I was five years old,
I cut my knee
and my mother wouldn't let me
out of the house till I was 16.
I'm a grown man.
I can make my own decisions.
- Not on this ship, you can't.
- Sara.
Look, I cannot let you
go out there tomorrow,
knowing that you could get killed.
I have enough deaths
on my conscience as it is.
Look, I know you don't think
I can add anything to this team.
But out there? Out there is history.
And nobody knows more about it
than me.
Well, we've been managing
just fine without you.
Mostly fine.
Your suit looks a bit cumbersome.
Oh, actually,
I made it to fit me perfectly.
It's constructed out
of a proprietary alloy
and it's been battle-tested
quite a bit.
I even wore it in space once.
Personal highlight.
So your superpower
is wearing the suit?
Yeah, I guess so.
It's a little more complicated
than that... but yeah.
You're still mad at me for punching
out that Nazi in the club, huh?
I'm mad because you blew my cover.
I'll never be able to go undercover
in Paris ever again.
Yeah, sorry.
I didn't think about that.
I imagine that's a pattern
with you and your group.
But I can't dwell on it.
Getting stuck on past mistakes
only takes focus off
the primary goal at hand.
Well, I got to admit.
Watching your team work
like a well-oiled machine
kind of makes me feel like I'm doing
this whole hero thing wrong.
If it's any consolation, Dr. Palmer,
you're not really a hero.
We better get ready.
We've spotted the Baron's caravan.
ETA five minutes.
I've got eyes on the Baron.
What the hell's going on down there?
Animal Girl and I are going
after Krieger.
In the field, I'm called Vixen.
Negative, Raymond.
Our target is the convoy.
We've got the convoy covered.
Pursue the Baron.
The mission is the amulet.
Our mission is Krieger.
We don't have time for this.
Give me a moment. I... I... I...
I need to assess the situation.
Krieger's getting away, man.
What the hell was that?
We're under attack.
It's Krieger! He turned into a...
We need backup!
Dr. Palmer? Vixen?
Do you read?
Their comms are down.
Oh, my God.
- I've got the amulet.
- Good work.
Dr. Mid-Nite, Stargirl,
Vixen and Dr. Palmer need assistance.
Copy that.
But I think we have a new problem.
Grey, you got to get them out
of there!
I just need a minute.
Come on, Grey! Do something!
Uh...
Fall back. Get Obsidian.
Mick, lay down fire
to cover our retreat.
Now you're talking.
Mick! Come on!
Commander Steel,
do... do you still have the amulet?
Yes, sir! En route to your position.
What about Ray and Amaya?
You just can't leave them there.
Nor can we engage this super-Nazi.
Not without compiling
more information first.
This is not a science debate, Grey!
Damn it! Jefferson, I know that!
But for now, they're on their own.
I must admit,
it's a feat of engineering.
Far beyond anything
I have ever seen
or expected from you Americans.
Well, maybe you Germans should
just stick to your luxury cars.
Why should I fear a robot suit
when I have becomeder Ubermensch?
You really think a single case of
'roid rage is gonna win you the war?
Yeah.
Once I have replicated
the super-serum
for the entire Wehrmacht.
But you haven't replicated the...
What'd you call it? Super-serum?
Kind of on the nose, don't you think?
If all this is just a preamble
to you killing us, get it over with.
I was hoping to torture you
a little bit first.
But since you're in such a rush,
I will be glad to accommodate you
with your schedule.
Wait, wait. I'm a scientist.
That exo-suit? I invented it.
I can help you with your little
supply and demand problem.
I'll even improve it.
Just don't shoot her.
I hope you are as smart
as you say you are...
for her sake.
You know he's gonna kill us both
even if you help him.
I have a plan.
That's what I'm afraid of.
We have the amulet. Now what?
First priority is making sure
Ray and Amaya are alive.
And then, getting them out
of the bunker
where the Nazis are holding them.
Actually, our first priority
is destroying the Baron
and whatever serum
is making him indestructible.
Perhaps we could propose a trade.
Their lives for the Amulet.
Unfortunately,
the amulet's not ours to barter with.
We need an extraction plan.
We need to eliminate the threat.
Now, Professor Stein,
please, tell us,
what is your plan of action?
How... how am I supposed
to come up with a plan
when I can't even hear myself think?
Would... would you please
all just leave?
I... I... I need a moment
to collect my thoughts.
What the hell, Grey?
I can practically feel you
going crazy inside my head.
I'm fine.
Jefferson, I'm trying to determine
the best course of action.
I wouldn't believe that even if we
didn't have a psychic connection
which hold on... we do.
I just don't know how
Rip was able to do all this.
So many decisions to make,
consequences to manage,
opinions to consider.
Trying to reach a consensus
with this team
is like something akin
to chaos theory.
That's the thing, Grey.
We don't need someone
to reach a consensus.
We just need someone
who can call the shots.
Then you should have put a tactician,
not a theoretician, in charge.
You were right, Jefferson.
I'm not a wartime consigliere.
Are they gonna be okay?
They'll live to fight another day.
It's what we do.
I used to fantasize
about meeting you.
Trading stories or having a beer.
Or just making eye contact.
I'm sorry, I...
I guess back at headquarters...
I was afraid to get too close to you.
Why? You're my grandfather.
You're... you're more than that.
You're a hero to me.
I don't want to be anyone's hero.
That look you gave me
when we first met?
I've seen it before.
When people look up to me,
decide that they have to act
a certain way,
a way that's likely
to get them killed.
I do what I do.
So that others don't have to.
So you wouldn't have to.
My whole life, people have been
trying to shield me from the world,
your son included.
Meanwhile, all I ever wanted
to be was a soldier, like you.
It's a parent's job
to protect their child.
But it's a child's obligation
to themselves to live their own life.
You can and should do whatever
you set your mind to.
But you should know...
you don't have to be a soldier
to be a hero.
And we approach
from the southwest,
destroy the weapons lab
and the Baron in one move.
Except for the last time
we faced him,
he took out both of our teams.
The last time, we weren't being
backed by a squadron of B-17s.
Then how do we get Ray and Amaya
out before the bombs start falling?
We don't.
This conflict is bigger
than any one of us.
If it means ending the war
one day sooner,
Amaya would happily make
that sacrifice.
But she doesn't have to.
Look, I know you and your team think,
we're a group of irresponsible
losers.
But I know Ray Palmer
and he has a plan
to get out of that bunker.
We just need to give him time...
Which means giving the Nazis time.
I'm calling in the strike.
I can't let you do that.
You don't have the authority.
Yes, she does.
Miss Lance speaks for all of us.
I have watched her become the beating
heart and steady hand of this team.
She is the proper person to lead us.
And if she says that we are
going to rescue our people...
that is what we are going to do.
This would go a lot faster
if I wasn't handcuffed.
I mean, what do you think,
I'm gonna escape using a microscope?
Are you going to
make more serum...
or is your friend going to die?
First off, it's not a serum.
It's a biomolecular enhancer.
By the way, who gave you this?
Because, from an engineering
standpoint, it's really rather ama...
Yes. I can make more.
Ray, don't do it.
Don't help him.
Back to work.
Watch them.
How can you do this?
No member of the JSA
would ever help the Nazis.
Neither would a Legend.
Damn, I really wanted to do it
with just the microscope.
Get the handcuff keys.
Alpha-stabilizer's damaged.
Suit's not gonna work.
They took my amulet.
And without it,
I'm guessing you're just...
A fifth-degree black belt
with training in edged weapons
combat.
Nice, but I think we'll need more
than that to get past super-Krieger.
What are you doing?
I told you I had a plan.
It was to get my hands on this
and enhance it, but not for them.
I'm not only a man in a metal suit.
At least not after this.
We are under attack.
Baron Krieger has ordered us
to transport you
to a more secure location.
Who's attacking you?
Sir, the sentries are reporting
a man made of fire flying
through the forest.
Lock down the base. Now.
Firestorm is drawing the troops away
from the bunker.
Copy that. We still need to find
Ray and Amaya.
Mick, look out!
Thanks, Haircut.
I believe this belongs to you.
Steel, Mid-Nite, we've recovered
the rest of the team.
I suggest you save
the teary reunion for later.
Hourman ordered
the bombers to strike.
They're five minutes out.
But, Herr Krieger is here right now!
Come on, you Nazi bastard.
- Get on!
- What are you doing here?
Saving you! Get on!
Bombing run about to commence.
All points, get clear.
Working on it!
What was that?
He's dead.
You did it. You saved us!
I'm afraid Mr. Heywood's
vitals are dropping.
There's got to be something on board
this tub to get him back on his feet.
You people are from the future,
for God's sake!
The bomb blast caused
massive internal bleeding.
And because his body lacks
the normal clotting factor,
there's only so much Gideon can do!
Were you two close?
No, not really.
But if it wasn't for Nate, I'd still
be trapped in the Cretaceous period
being chased by a T. Rex.
I'm sorry.
This is our fight, not yours.
- The Nazis are not...
- Nazis.
Nazis.
You kept the serum?
There may be enough.
I think I can save him, with this.
Is that the Nazi serum that created
that hideous berserker?
Are you mad?
I did a little tinkering
to the formula, so...
So, what will it do now?
With any luck, save his life.
How do we know if it's working?
He's not dead yet,
so that's a good sign.
And he's not turning
into a Nazi berserker.
His vitals are improving.
He's stabilizing.
What'd the Nazis want with
a piece of jewelry anyway?
No idea.
Hitler's known to be obsessed
with the strange.
We'll keep it safe, in any case.
I guess that's your way
of saying thanks.
Right. Well, I think it's time
we got out of 1942.
This was fun.
It was... unusual.
Hey, I wanted to apologize
for what I said.
About me not being a hero?
You're not a superhero.
But, what you did for Nate...
giving him the serum, giving up
your chance at real powers...
that was heroic.
Oh, it's about time, Sleeping Beauty.
I was afraid you wouldn't wake up
in time for me to say good-bye.
And here I was afraid
I wasn't gonna wake up at all.
I was afraid of that, too.
I'm sorry if I didn't live up to
the version of Commander Steel
you dreamt of meeting.
No, I like the real version better.
Well, I'll be damned.
Guess this means
we're both gonna make it.
Not bad for a historian.
Not bad for a hero.
- Hello, Rex.
- Who are you?
Oh, we've met before.
Quite a number of times, actually.
In fact, after our last go,
you discovered my plan
and then traveled
through time yourself
to stop the Legends from coming here.
They... they said I disappeared.
Not disappeared.
No.
Erased from the timeline.
Like this.
No.
Rex?
Rex.
Rex, no.
Time...
time traveler.
No.
Rex.