[sighs] Okay.
All of Sara's favorite things,
double espresso,
bacon not-too-crispy...
Hang on. Greek finishing salt.
Did a grocery run
to the agora in ancient Athens.
Nice.
- Just heard her alarm. It's go time.
- [Agent Sharpe] Okay.
- [sighs]
- [Behrad] Not yet.
Can't skip the garnish.
We eat with our eyes first.
- Is that all of it? Okay.
- Ava, wait.
Passion Dragon Ash.
Enhances vitality and endurance.
Sara really doesn't like smoothies,
but... Ooh, nice flourish, Nate.
[Nate] Mmm-hmm.
[Mick snoring]
We didn't forget about you, gorgeous.
Seriously, Mick,
thank you so, so much for everything.
[Zari] Here. Recovery Dragon Ash,
usually for hangovers,
but also probably good
if you've been lost in space.
And A5 Kobe beef.
I dry-aged it
for 15 years this morning.
Yeah, we seriously need to talk
about your portal use.
So, the rest of the team is hooking up
the gizmo we jacked from Kayla's ship.
Okay, once that happens,
Gideon can help us
pinpoint the rest of the alien pods.
And we will find the perfect mish
to welcome the captain back.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Ava, relax.
I know we've been through a lot,
but things are finally back to normal.
- Are they?
- Talk, talk, talk.
Can't a man just eat in peace?
See?
If you don't hold it,
I won't be able to connect the wire.
[straining] If I keep holding it,
I won't be able to feel my arms.
Could you keep it down out there?
I am trying to study magic, but I cannot
concentrate over your constant toiling.
Okay, how about you
memorize your nursery rhymes
when we're done with
the real work over here?
Tua curtis fiat ignite!
[groans]
- What the hell was that supposed to do?
- Must have the pronunciation wrong.
All right. Let's get back at it. And...
Gary, my alien chum,
let's have a chat, eh?
Is this about us parking
Kayla's ship at your place?
- Because we were kind of in a hurry.
- Not that.
What do you know about
the Fountain of Imperium?
- Where'd you hear about that?
- [thuds]
I... I mean, no. The fountain of what?
- All right. Just let him be.
- Thank you, Spooner.
No, it's just that when you're stressed,
I got to feel it too.
Okay? This whole alien empath thing
was hard enough
before we had an actual alien
on the ship.
- Back to the books, then.
- [Gary] Good luck.
All right. Come on,
let's get back at it. Come on.
And quieter this time. Thanks.
[yawns]
God, this is so much better
than waking up on an alien planet.
Right?
- Here you go, my love.
- Thanks.
And I'm just going to say this, okay?
Whenever you're ready to talk about
what happened out there, I am here.
Who wants to talk about space when
we have Legends gossip to catch up on?
Oh! Hot and juicy. Okay.
Um... So, Spooner is great.
Well, once she put away her rail gun.
- Sounds like my kind of girl.
- Yes.
Um, oh, and I was a binder, and actually
I think I turned into a cartoon.
- That's a new one.
- Yeah.
Babe, something wrong with the food?
Come on.
Oh, babe, no.
The food, it looks amazing.
I just think I'm jet lagged.
- I get it.
- But what's with the smoothie?
That is from Zari.
It's for passion, which...
Why are we wasting time
talking about gossip and aliens
when we could be focusing on you and me?
I'm an alien-human hybrid clone.
[laughs] What?
[theme music playing]
[Agent Sharpe sighs]
So, you're an alien-human
hybrid clone who can regenerate?
[sighs] Babe, it sounds so crazy.
No. I mean, yes, obviously, but...
Okay, babe... You're Sara Lance.
You're still the same
beautiful, tough, and, yes,
sometimes very surprising woman
that I fell in love with.
And you're here with me.
Okay? So, that's all that matters.
[Gideon] Captains, you're needed on the
bridge. An alien pod has been detected.
We have to go.
Babe, wait. Can we just maybe not
tell the team about
the whole hybrid thing?
Just for the first mission back,
I kind of want to feel normal.
Yeah, I get it. And you know what?
After everything we've been through,
they could use a little normalcy, too.
- Yeah, okay. Yeah.
- We have to go though.
[sighs]
[all cheering]
All right, all right, all right.
That's enough.
Okay, we get it, we get it.
- Gideon, what have we got?
- Welcome back, Captain.
I've detected a pod
in the Oklahoma territory, 1891,
near an encampment known as Fist City.
[Nate] Oof, that can't be good.
The outpost at Fist City
was the wildest of the West.
Countless outlaws passed through.
Butch Cassidy, Belle Starr, Wild Bill.
Sounds like a bad scene
on its best days.
Hate to see the kind of havoc
an alien could wreak out there.
Hey, Spoons, you okay?
Yeah, just alien mind meld's
been flaring up
since the space cadets got back.
- It's coming from...
- Gary, obviously.
If my read is right,
Gary is hiding something big from us.
That's okay, whatever it is, right?
I mean, Gary, you're an alien,
but you're also one of us,
and I think we should all be
more accepting of Gary.
Okay, but now my read says
Gary wants to jump Ava's bones.
- [Astra] That sounds about right.
- What? No. I do not...
Okay, well, I feel like
getting back in the saddle.
Who's coming with me?
[imitates gunfire]
Hey, Nate. Just with everything
Sara's been through,
I think she could use
a nice, smooth mission, okay?
- So, a classic Legends romp. On it.
- Yeah, but easy.
All right, gang, be on watch.
The pod has already landed.
So, the alien could be anywhere.
Try to keep a low profile.
I don't know what's more dangerous,
the alien or the locals.
- Sounds like my kind of place.
- Yeah, mine too.
My dad put me through
a cowboy phase as a kid
when he was trying to lean
into American culture.
- Some of it stuck.
- Cute.
But I was talking about the lawlessness.
Hell, I might know some of these people
from... Hell.
You want to talk line dancing
or lassos, try Spooner.
I was raised in Texas, not Hee Haw.
I don't know what that is, but it looks
like your hat does, partner.
Well, I had to put this back on
to dim my alien radar.
So far, getting nothing but Gary.
[Zari clears throat]
Couldn't help but notice you
flirting with Astra.
I wasn't flirting.
I was just trying to connect,
person-to-person, soul-to-soul.
Yeah, that's called flirting.
Listen, I know it's hard to have
a social life on a time ship.
So, I wanted to offer my help
as someone who has recently learned
how to balance work
with a healthy and fulfilling love life.
Oh, don't need to hear about that.
And if this is your way
of finding another test subject
for your passion smoothies, I'm good.
Hey, I promised Ava
a classic Legends romp, okay?
So, no getting captured.
No personal drama.
Bet we'd find the alien quicker
if Spooner wasn't afraid of her brain.
You mean you can't find it
by bungling some Latin phrase?
Okay, tension. Got it.
You know what this calls for?
The buddy system.
You two, starting now, are buddies.
By the end of the mission,
you will be friends, okay?
Big smiles.
[saloon piano playing]
[music stops]
Remember, don't make waves.
They won't take kind
to outsiders around here.
Can you just find this alien
so we can get out of here?
Getting nothing new.
And you're not going to
if you keep wearing this thing.
- Guys!
- [man] Whoa.
[Nate] Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, partner, let us...
Let us get you another.
Yeah, that ain't happenin'.
Look, we really don't want no trouble.
Aw, shucks! Come on, neither do I.
'Cause I should be the one treatin' you.
Barkeep, may I please have a round
for our new guests?
Guys, is that a swear jar?
- Is this root beer?
- Yup.
What'd you say about
this place being dangerous?
Well, folks,
seems by my sights, we have outsiders
come into our modest municipal.
So, how about we make
these newcomers neighbors
by letting them in
on our ways around here?
[singing]
Well, other towns get you down
I don't know where to start
There's rifle play
And fights all day
It breaks my cowboy heart
But don't you fear 'cause over here
We offer the reverse
Yes, welcome to Fist City
The gladdest place on Earth
Welcome to Fist City
[all cheering]
I've seen weird before,
but this is weird.
Gary, mate, I found something
that might jog your memory.
This fountain, it's an ancient
alien artifact said to amp up magic.
Are you sure you haven't heard
anything about it?
Why would you need this?
You're already the most powerful
magician there is.
Yeah, see, that's the thing.
While you were away,
the Legends got into a bit of a scrape,
and in order to set it right...
I had to surrender my power.
You lost your magic?
All right, all right,
don't cry about it.
But you can help me.
This Fountain of Imperium,
it's my one shot
at getting my magic back.
[Gary] Fountain...
Right, right, right, right. Imperium.
Yes, yes. I have heard of it.
It's a total myth. I'm sorry.
There's just nothing out there.
You should give it up.
I'm telling you, these people should be
low-down, dirty,
probably diseased sons of...
- Ma'am.
- [Behrad] Happy trails.
- [man] Good day.
- Something big must have happened
to turn this place
from Deadwood to Disneyland.
Yeah, it must be our alien.
Or gentrification.
Either way, we should stop it.
Let's blend in, spread out,
figure out exactly when things changed.
Okay.
I'd thank you for another soda, my lady.
Deal me in.
Is this your way of nabbing the alien?
No, this is my way of nabbing
that jerk's gold.
But you're right. It could be the alien.
So, could you sense what cards he has?
I can barely control my powers as it is.
I ain't gonna tap into 'em
just to help you cheat at cards.
The game's Go Fish.
- You know it?
- What's your wager?
Ain't no gambling around here.
That just leads to bad blood.
Besides, we'd be breaking
rule number three.
So, got any jacks?
Maybe we should check out
the card tables.
Okay. I'm sorry. I cannot let you
make the same mistake again.
You always go for the bad girls.
What we need is to find you a woman
who appreciates you
for the nice, sweet boy you are.
I don't only go out for the bad girls,
and I don't need a matchmaker.
See, she looks nice.
Oh, no, bro, bro, bro.
This is a saloon.
It is her profession
to be interested in you.
No. We don't offer
that sort of business.
It's one of the rules.
[Behrad]
What has gotten into these people?
[woman clears throat]
- You're new in town, ain't ya?
- Reckon I am.
That just means I need someone
to show me around.
Say, what's with all these here rules?
Ugh, Sheriff's got lots of
dos and don'ts.
There ain't no rule against
playing a girl a tune.
Forgive my forward nature.
I'm Irma Rose.
Why, if that ain't the sweetest
sounding name in the whole wide world.
You got a song in mind?
Something to put a smile on my face.
- Think you can manage that?
- You think you can manage that?
I guess we'll find out.
[exhales]
[playing upbeat music]
[sighs]
Hey, uh, barkeep, have you noticed
anything weird around here lately?
Weird? Not at all.
Now, what can I get you ladies?
Got sarsaparilla, phosphates,
milkshakes.
- Make it a milkshake, extra cherries.
- [bartender] Yes, ma'am.
Another one?
[Sara] Well...
Guess I'm finally
getting my appetite back.
[Nate] Over here.
I ain't never seen no one
down 'em like that.
[Nate] "Bass Reeves."
Reeves was the first Black deputy
marshal west of the Mississippi.
He's a hero, not a wanted man.
The alien's changing history.
"Contact Sheriff Levi Stapleton."
Hmm.
Oh, I know that name.
Stapleton was a criminal famous
for terrorizing the Oklahoma territory.
But how did a outlaw end up a sheriff,
and how did a marshal end up an outlaw?
Hey, barkeep, what can you tell me
about Levi Stapleton?
Well, just that he's about
the finest law man around.
[eagle screeches]
I heard we had some visitors come in.
[guitar playing]
[singing] Oh, Stapleton
Stapleton fills us with awe
Restoring us order and laying down law
The Sheriff of sheriffs
He's fair and he's firm
Brings peace to our streets
And we hail him in turn
I'd say "Let me be the first
to bid you welcome,"
but I see my fine citizenry's
beat me to it.
It is a fine town y'all have here.
In fact, we was just wondering...
How you made this place such a haven.
Now, don't you worry about that.
You just enjoy yourself.
Oh, barkeep, fill our guests
some drink and vittles
so they can be on their way.
Guess we know who scared
this town straight.
Think he's our alien?
We'll have Spooner get a read.
Speaking of...
Where are Spooner and Astra?
Spoons?
[whistling]
If you won't let me win your gold,
then tell me where you got it.
[Spooner] Sorry.
She gets hot under the collar.
You know? But what we do have a question
about what's happening around here.
I don't know what you're aiming at,
but you'd be wise to stop asking
and get like a good little girl.
[groans]
[rumbling]
What is that?
Fight's going outside!
[people clamoring]
Okay, Astra, it's getting closer.
Not now, Spooner.
And even if I was gonna say
where I got my gold,
the last one I'd tell is a girl
with the looks of you.
[Astra] Don't try me.
- Hell if I let you touch me!
- Look out!
[screeching]
[dissonant whistling]
[dissonant whistling continues]
Shame to see.
But let that remind y'all
why we keep our tempers in check here.
So, how about you all go back inside
and get back to having a good time?
Go on, get.
As for you...
I think you've seen
just about enough of Fist City.
So, y'all don't come back now, you hear?
[Sara] Hey, Gary.
Do you know any alien species
that live underground,
look like a worm
and swallow people whole?
Oh.
That sounds like a Haverack.
Haverack translates into "rage eater."
It's drawn to the chemicals
we release when we're angry
and then it eats us.
That's why I felt it gaining
when that guy got all riled up.
Its outer shell is impenetrable, so
the only way to stop it is to tame it.
There's this whistle...
Yeah, that's the thing Stapleton used.
It must have been loaded with the pod.
So we get the sheriff to give it up.
Great. I was looking for a reason
to wipe that smile off his face.
Whoa, but we need to avoid a fight,
especially if the worm's drawn to anger.
So we gotta sneak it off Stapleton.
And I know the perfect way
to get close to him.
Square dancing contest. High noon.
Yeah. There is no way
I'm square dancing.
Yeah, we can't have
you two triggering the worm again.
Are you benching us?
Do you even have that authority?
I don't know.
It did feel weird.
But he's right. If this thing
is attracted to hot tempers,
then you two
are definitely staying here,
while the rest of us... dance.
All right, everybody, find the whistle.
[whoops] Everybody, elbow swing!
Square up!
Hey, babe, this is our first dance
since we've been engaged.
Oh, yeah.
I didn't expect it to have
so much fiddle, but I'm into it.
[caller] And tunnel going,
one more time!
I might just go grab another milkshake.
- Again?
- Yeah.
- Is that okay?
- Yeah, it's just you've already had...
Ava, I've missed this.
- I've missed us.
- Yeah.
So, this might be
a really weird question,
but is there any species of alien
that loves cherries?
[Gary] Ooh. It could be a Wafter.
You're worried about sharing
the ship with an alien.
- [Agent Sharpe] That's not what I said...
- [Gary] No, don't worry.
I haven't wanted to eat
a human in years.
Okay. Well, thank you, Gary.
Appreciate it.
[singing] Grab your partner
Right hand through
Travel over, by two-by-two
[gasps]
John.
I've missed this. I've missed us.
- Have you, Gary?
- Yeah.
Well, you can see why I'm struggling
to believe a word you say
after you lied to me all those years
about being a human being.
Well, you know, those days are over now.
Yeah, are they?
So, you're telling me the whole truth
about the Fountain of Imperium then?
[caller] Everybody, change partner!
Oh! Listen to that, I gotta go.
[caller] Come on down.
Let's shoot the stars!
I'm almost in position
to grab the whistle.
And I'm almost in position
to make my move with Irma Rose.
Listen, I believe
long-distance relationships can work,
but the 1800's?
That's a bit of a stretch.
Two hands up, make lines on the side!
[Zari] I'm going in.
Everybody, two-hand balance.
Strange, y'all don't strike me
as the square-dancing type.
No?
I thought I told y'all to get.
But, Sheriff,
we just love dancing so much.
Don't think I'm unaware
as why you're all really here,
but that worm is mine.
- You're hurting my arm.
- Take your hands off her, you bastard.
Is this one yours?
Rude!
[rumbling]
It's coming.
Well, go on.
You know you want to get a good hit in.
- Stop, stop, stop.
- [Sara] Hey! Stapleton!
[hocking]
[people gasping]
[laughs]
You just broke rule number six.
Well, I don't give a damn
about your rules.
And your reign here is about to end.
I challenge you to a duel.
Winner gets your whistle.
Loser gets out of town.
You want to fight?
You got it.
Are you sure about this?
The Sheriff's one thing,
- but we've seen what that worm can do.
- Babe.
I'm Sara Lance. I always keep my cool.
[Spooner]
You passed this spot twice already.
But then, I can see
your navigation skill's ain't for much.
Wait, you're following me?
I knew you wouldn't last a minute
out here alone.
What the hell are you doing hiking
in alien-infested territories?
Prospecting.
I'm going to find that gold.
Okay. Well, if it's gold you're after,
you should follow the waterflow.
Why don't you just concentrate
on using your radar
in case that thing decides
to attack again?
Yeah, well, I ain't your tool.
And, you know, I'm pretty sure
the ship can make all the gold you want.
It's not about the gold.
Or not just about the gold.
It's about showing everyone
in that town that I get what I want.
Ugh, seems like a lot of work
just to prove a point.
Yeah, well, it figures you'd say that,
but I've had to fight
for every bit of power that I have.
And you think I've had it easy?
I think you've spent your life
creating your own kind of hell.
Hiding and alone,
letting aliens mess with your head
when you could harness that power.
Yeah, well, I wasn't hiding.
I was keeping my head down.
And, you know,
I wasn't always alone either.
You know, when I lost my mom,
they put me in foster care.
Your mom?
Yeah. You know, people tried
their best with me,
but some kid who, you know, hears aliens
all the time, they couldn't deal.
Well, where I'm from,
you have to use whatever power you have
to tip the scales in your favor.
You know, we're not in Hell anymore.
And you're not in Texas.
So, which way do we go?
[leaves rustling]
What's up, babe?
You know I've never lost a shootout.
Yes, I know.
And I would tell you if I didn't feel
up for this. It's like you said.
Nothing's changed.
And I meant it.
But with everything
that you've been through...
With everything I've been through,
a Wild West shootout
is exactly what I need.
All right.
Let's go win ourselves
a standoff, shall we?
[singing] We don't know
Where she came from
But know that she ain't going back
'Cause there ain't no one faces
Stapleton's guns
And walks away looking intact
If she shoots, the worm will eat her
If she don't
She'll fall from his lead
You can do what you can
To prove you're a man...
Can it, cowboy.
Godspeed, Sara Lance
[Sara] You done playing with
your pistol yet?
[chuckles] Mmm.
Ten paces.
Then we draw.
One, two...
- Gary!
- [Nate] Would you shut up?
[mouthing]
- Sara!
- Hold on, hold on.
[chuckles]
[exhales]
What the bloody hell happened
on that planet, hey?
That... That ain't normal.
You must be some kind of monster.
No, not a monster.
But you're right about the other thing.
I'm definitely not normal.
The deal is off.
You ain't getting this.
[rumbling]
[Stapleton] Why...
Won't...
You...
Die!
[screeching]
[dissonant whistling]
Oh!
[dissonant whistling continues]
[Irma Rose] Would you look at that?
Looks like y'all did it.
I guess we did.
We found it. Not bad, Spooner.
What? Is the alien nearby?
Yeah.
And I'm looking at it.
Looks like we both found
what we were looking for.
Did gold just come out of that alien's...
But if that's the deposit, then...
That guy,
he's not just protecting the gold.
He's protecting the alien.
Well, y'all figured it out.
That there worm
made Fist City a boomtown,
but don't come between
those folks and their gold.
Deputy Marshal.
Bass Reeves.
We'll take it from here, my lady.
Like hell you will.
Ain't nobody taking our little worm.
That thing's a literal goldmine,
you know? [gasps]
[exhales]
And the thing about us
shooting y'all, well...
Actually, we're happy to do it.
[laughing]
[laughs] What's that?
[gunshots ringing out]
[exclaims in frustration]
What happened out there?
Okay. So, maybe not everything
is back to normal.
[exhales]
[Irma Rose yelling]
Ain't no hiding!
Come on out now!
Don't want the worm coming for you.
Besides, they ain't gonna be
cooping up in there too long
before they lose it.
Once they do... [chuckles]
- Worm will get 'em.
- [sighs]
So you're bulletproof now?
Yeah.
Welcome to the club.
Okay, it's a long story.
I was going to tell you guys,
I just...
I wanted to have a normal mission first.
And on a normal mission,
I would be out there fighting.
If we fight, we attract the worm,
and I cannot see you
take another bullet.
Babe, I don't know
what you want me to do.
Look, I'm sorry,
but this is who I am now.
All right, so let's focus
on getting the whistle
so we can squash this worm for good.
Ooh, I have an idea.
How about Behrad
just flirts it away from his girlfriend?
Hey, just because she's evil
doesn't mean she's not into me, okay?
[Zari] You are dumb.
You know, magic would be
really useful about now.
Guess I'm not getting that back
any time soon, am I, Gary?
[rumbling]
Oh! Milkshakes are ten cents.
Look, we'll come up with a new plan.
The important thing
is that we keep our cool.
Gang, remember, we're romping.
Huh?
[piano key plinks]
[Nate] All right,
we cannot stay in here forever.
So, let's brainstorm.
No bad ideas.
I don't need to hear
your "I told you so's."
Listen, I wish you crazy kids
could have worked things out,
but, I don't know,
maybe there's a lesson here.
You pick these unattainable girls,
you pine away silently for years,
when maybe that's easier
than being in a real relationship.
I know you assume
everybody needs your lifestyle advice,
but I'm actually good.
Fine. Ignore me like you always do.
Even though, I don't know,
maybe as the older sibling,
I would have some wisdom to offer.
It's fine.
You know what we need?
We need... We need a sing-along.
You guys remember "Sweet Baby James"?
"Thong Song"?
We love the "Thong Song."
[Constantine] Oi, Gary.
Take a seat.
Look, I know that
the Fountain is real, mate.
Come on, old son. Give it up.
Okay.
Aliens have known
about the Fountain for ages.
Once I even found a lead
in your library, but, um...
Anyone who's gone after it
has ended in ruin.
You know, so I only lied to you
because it's too dangerous,
especially without your magic.
I don't need the likes of you
to protect me, even without my magic.
Just... Just tell me
where to find it, Gary.
Okay.
There's a, uh, map to
the Fountain of Imperium out there,
and, um, humans could never really
figure out how to read it
'cause they thought
it was a map of the heavens.
But aliens...
we know it's a map of your planet.
So you're telling me
that I could be out there right now
searching for this map,
but thanks to you,
I'm stuck in a bloody saloon!
[rumbling]
[screeching]
[Astra] Oh, no. That can't be good.
Wait, the town's that way.
I know a way we can cut 'em off.
Follow me.
Hey, speaking of magic,
you guys like card tricks?
That... That sounds like fun.
[chuckling]
[all chuckling]
No.
Babe, look, I know that was hard
for you to watch, but look at me now.
All right, look, I'm fine.
I know you're still you,
but seeing it in action, I don't know,
it made me realize we can't just pretend
that everything's normal.
- You know, I was talking to Gary...
- Yeah, obviously...
Why are you talking to Gary about this
before you're talking to me?
- I wasn't talking...
- Guys, have a drink.
God, what is with the cherries?
I don't know, okay?
Stay out of it.
[Nate] Guys? Guys?
[grunts]
First, you're mad I'm lying,
now you're mad I'm telling the truth?
- [all arguing]
- [rumbling]
[glasses rattling]
[vase smashes]
How annoying!
[Behrad] I was six!
[all continue arguing]
Enough!
Can't you just hold it together
till we get the job done?
I mean, I don't know what's harder.
Fighting the alien or keeping the peace
between you people.
Um, Nate, the worm, remember?
Just...
You might wanna simmer it down.
[rumbling stops]
You know what?
I won't simmer down.
I've been having
a lot of big feelings too lately,
and now is the exact right time
to share them.
[objects rattling]
When Mick left the ship,
it wasn't easy being the O-est G,
but did any of you check in
on my existential crisis?
No, because Nate's so chill, isn't he?
Dude, you're right. We should talk,
but maybe not while the worm's coming.
I used to have Zari to talk to, right?
And while all of you are hooking up,
getting engaged,
I guess she's just
stuck in the totem forever.
No offense. I think you're great.
It's not really
an either/or type of thing.
And don't get me started
about life on the ship!
Six roommates, and I'm the only one
that replaces the cartridges
in the fabricators?
I didn't know they took cartridges.
Well, they do, genius. They do.
And I know one of you
changes the thermostat every night,
so don't blame it on Gideon.
Well, since none of you
can hold it together,
guess I'll draw the worm to me
so you don't get eaten alive
because I'm so chill.
So come and get me, you alien slug.
I got your romp right here!
That white boy's a goner.
Spooner, you have to do something.
You don't know what it feels like
when they get in my head.
So get into theirs.
Let them feel what you're feeling.
Don't do it for me or for Nate.
Do it for you.
And another thing!
I asked for a chair
at the Hall of Justice.
Big surprise, no response!
[cracking]
[screeching]
And this is where my plan stops.
[snarls]
Stop!
[high-pitched ringing]
That's right. It's my power now.
[gun cocks]
It's Reeves!
[shots firing]
Dig?
Yes, ma'am, I definitely do dig.
Bass Reeves.
I'm glad to see
you can join the fight.
[worm screeching]
[roaring]
[high-pitched ringing fading]
I can't...
I can't hold it much longer.
[screeching]
[Astra] I got you.
Tua cutis fiat ignite!
[worm groaning]
[both panting]
[sighs]
No.
I feel so much better.
Me too.
[Nate] Eh?
[all] Yay!
- [Agent Sharpe] Gary!
- Whoo!
[ragtime piano music playing]
Now that is better.
[Spooner] This whole place looks better.
How are you even able
to keep your head down here?
Worm would have gotten me in a minute
if I was stuck with these people.
Well, I was plenty angry.
But I decided if these folks
want to underestimate me,
well, I'll just use it against them.
That's how I put
most of these bastards away.
You made it your power.
See? This one gets it.
[soft guitar music playing]
You're probably wondering what happened
to that band of outsiders.
Well, from what I heard tell...
[singing] They cleaned up the town
Got it back to itself
There was beer at the bar
And poker hands dealt
They got on their ship
Bein' sure no one's seen 'em
The only fights left
Were the ones between 'em
You here to shower me with pity,
Gary Green?
No. I, uh...
I know how you can
get a map to the Fountain.
Shouldn't be much trouble actually,
'cause the man who found it
lives in your attic.
Aleister Crowley.
If anyone can find that Fountain
and live to tell of it, it's you.
So I'll be seeing you, John Constantine.
Well, the magic man's
Heading off for the unknown
Bid his lady goodbye
Then he set off alone
She told him she trusted
That he'd dodge any doom
Now, what of the captains
Let's cut to their room
- [sighs]
- [Agent Sharpe] Hey.
Hey, babe.
- Made you something.
- Thank you.
I think my normal appetite
is finally starting to come back.
- Good.
- But this does look good.
Well, dig in.
Mmm! Mmm-hmm.
You know what? I...
I think I've been trying
way too hard to pretend
that things around here could be normal.
Babe, we both were.
Right? Ugh.
I wanted so badly for everything
to just feel like it was before.
But after everything we've been through,
there's no going back.
But does that have to be a bad thing?
Maybe we can be something new,
something better.
I mean, let's be honest,
we were never normal to begin with.
So why start now?
[inhales sharply] Whew!
What?
- Was that...
- I've no idea what you're talking about.
- Passion Dragon Ash?
- Yes!
- Mmm-hmm.
- [Agent Sharpe giggling]
[bluegrass music playing]
I saw John on his way out.
- [clears throat]
- You doing okay?
Yeah. Trying.
Well, I'm here if you need me,
but I know you'll be fine.
You are the wise one, after all.
Okay, look, I know I can be
a bit overbearing at times, but...
I just want you to be happy.
Hey.
I actually know
who could use both our help.
Can I, uh, borrow your totem?
[Behrad] Yo, yo.
Hey, man. You want a doughnut?
Uh, thanks, dude,
but I actually came
to give you something.
What? No, no, no.
No, I cannot be a totem master.
Maybe with some training.
- But at this point...
- No, no, no.
It's so you can visit her.
So you can see Zari.
That's possible?
I'm sure it's been tough,
and I should've noticed.
But now you can
take a totem trip to her,
and do what you do together.
[inhales sharply]
Just, uh, let me know when you're done.
[bluegrass music continues playing]
Now the Guy of Steel's
Off to see his girl
Sure it's weird
But then so is the world
So I leave you now with this takeaway
That there might not be a normal
But that might be okay
[music ends]
[sighs] I told you guys,
we can't keep the cowboy narrator.
Sorry, sorry.
Hey, man, we'll drop you off.
Happy trails, Legends.
[guitar strings twang]
[theme music playing]