JAX: Time travel is real,
and all of history
is vulnerable to attack,
which is why we must travel
through time to stop the spread of
these so-called Time Aberrations
and to erase their damage to history.
We are a team of outcasts and misfits,
so please don't call us heroes.
We're something else.
We're legends.
PROFESSOR STEIN:
Previously, on Legends of Tomorrow...
I had forgotten how handsome I was.
Hi. I'm Marty.
PROFESSOR STEIN: Have a wonderful life, Martin.
RORY: This belonged
to the greatest outsider I ever knew.
I'm looking for a partner.
- Hello, Rex.
- (REX SCREAMS)
With his last words,
he told me his killer was a time traveler.
Damien Darhk murdered my sister.
- If I take him out here...
- You save her.
We gotta let him go.
DRUG DEALER: So, it's all here, then?
Every sweet-smelling speck of it.
As for my compensation?
A strange form of payment.
Why this and not cash?
Everyone has a hobby.
Some men collect stamps.
I collect relics.
This "thing" is called a faeces.
A ceremonial ax carried
by the bodyguard of Emperor Nero,
from which the term "fascism" derived.
No?
A form of rule, which in my opinion,
is getting a bit of a bad rap lately.
- DEA! Get your hands in the air! Now!
- (GUNS CLICKING)
- (WHOOSHING)
- (MEN GROANING)
(SIGHS)
You know, I had this under control.
My way is faster.
Speed isn't everything, Mr. Thawne.
You should have learned
that lesson by now.
What's it been,
45 years since you hired me
to nuke New York?
Forty-five years for you, maybe.
But for me...
- Huh.
- Good seeing you again, old friend.
"Old"? That's fair.
"Friend"? Now that's something
that has to be earned.
Lovely piece.
What is this, first century AD,
if I'm not mistaken?
What is it that you want?
A partner.
Pass. I prefer to work alone.
Ah, yeah. Gathering your hive
of followers? Building your empire?
Designing your ark?
Yeah, I know what you're planning,
and how it works out.
You want to reshape the world?
Try reshaping history,
try rewriting destiny...
Try putting our partnership
into concrete terms, as in...
What's in it for me?
Well, perhaps you're content
collecting symbols of power,
but I can give you actual power.
We have the tools to make a difference.
We can make history better.
Even if we act
with the best of intentions,
these changes can ripple throughout time.
A temporal domino effect
with disastrous consequences.
So, we start small,
make changes we can control.
What you're talking about can't be done.
It's like playing God,
and it goes against everything
we're trying to do.
I thought we were trying to help people.
We're helping by fixing Aberrations,
not creating them.
You're not thinking fourth-dimensionally.
Did you really just use Doc Brown on me?
Who the hell is that?
Sara, come on.
You can't be Switzerland on this one.
In my heart, I agree with you.
But that's not what
Rip entrusted us to do.
Our job is to protect history.
You mean clean it up
after somebody else makes a mess of it.
Time janitors, that's all we are.
(SIGHS)
(WEAPON POWERING UP)
Easy. Point and shoot.
You're up.
All right, then. Point and shoot.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(PANTING)
You killed my beers.
Come on. The trigger's really sensitive.
And these goggles make everything
look blue.
(SIGHS)
You know, it'd be really easy for me
to improve this whole set-up
by just iterating the power source...
There's nothing wrong with the gun.
You just gotta be cool. Like Snart.
Yeah. I can be cool.
What are you doing?
Trying to be cool.
Maybe this was a bad idea.
You know, this may shock you,
but I was considered extremely cool
when I left my cushy, six-figure
Silicon Valley job
and started my own tech company.
Ladies were lining up.
Listen, Haircut.
If you wanna fit into Snart's shoes,
you gotta find the pain,
the darkness, the anger.
You got it in you.
Call me Haircut again, and I'll ice you.
Not bad.
Hey.
What are you doing?
A little side project I've been working on
with Ray and the Professor.
Hmm.
They said that Temporal Aberrations
cause these things called timequakes.
So I started thinking,
if there was a way
of locating their epicenters,
maybe we'll be able to fix the Aberrations
before they happen.
Like a time seismograph.
That's an awesome name,
and I'm totally gonna steal that.
If the JSA could get even
a glimpse of all this, they would...
They'd what?
Never mind.
Hey, wait.
We've barely had half a conversation
since you came on board.
You were friends with my grandfather.
Talk to me. What was he like as a person?
Your grandfather was a great man.
That's it? He's a great man?
Is it because
your missions were classified?
Or is it because you really
didn't know him well as a person?
It's because the JSA didn't encourage
its members to fraternize.
It's something
you and your team should consider.
(MACHINE BEEPING)
It worked?
Oh, it worked all right.
SARA: Where's it coming from?
Washington D.C., December 7th, 1987.
1600 Pennsylvania Ave.
- So?
- Dude, that's the White House.
So what?
December 7th was the day before
Reagan and Gorbachev
signed the INF Treaty,
reducing both countries' nuclear arsenals
and paving the way
for the end of the Cold War.
How do you know all that?
Because I was in the capital
for that very summit.
The Reagan Administration would call upon
the top nuclear physicists
to act as technical advisors.
You think someone might have
traveled back in time
to stop the treaty from being signed?
That or worse. Think about it.
Reagan and Gorbachev under the same roof
at one of the most volatile moments
in history?
The JSA has a training academy in D.C.
I could reach out
to the current membership,
see if they have any intel
or resources we could use.
Good idea, but you shouldn't go alone.
1987 is a long way from 1942,
and it's dangerous to know
too much about the future.
I can handle myself.
- I'll go with her.
- SARA: Great.
You two reach out to the JSA,
while the rest of us break into
the most secure residence in the country.
And how exactly do we do that?
Welcome to the White House.
This is Cross Hall,
a magnificent space that connects
the State Dining Room with the East Room.
All right. Fan out, but stay on the comms
and report if anything seems out of place.
Women actually wore these things
in the '80s?
Shoulder pads? Yeah.
They were supposed to make women
more imposing, more... I don't know.
- Manly?
- Yeah.
I'd hoped that by this decade,
women wouldn't need to use clothing
to compensate for their status.
Surely by now,
men and women are considered equals?
Never lose that optimism.
This is it.
This is the JSA Academy?
Inside a crummy warehouse?
The JSA Academy is hidden
inside a crummy warehouse.
Prepare to see the most elite
training facility in all of history.
Maybe "elite" means something different
in 1987?
When I was recruited,
this is where I was brought to train.
What happened to the JSA?
No clue.
But a lot can change in 45 years.
I thought you said you were a historian.
How can you not know?
Hey, every memo, every executive action
relating to the JSA is top secret.
I only pieced together
their World War II activities
from my father's bedtime stories,
witness testimonies and government leaks.
I never should have left 1942.
Look, Amaya, whatever happened to them,
that's not your fault.
You don't know that.
Like you said, you don't know
what happened to them.
1987, the halcyon days of
Whitney Houston
and Star Trek: The Next Generation.
I can remember this year
as if it were yesterday.
Looks like there's something
you forgot about.
Mr. Stein, pleasure to meet you.
Uh-oh.
That's me.
Go, go.
(EXHALES)
I thought you said you were
stuck in meetings on the Hill all clay.
I was. I never stepped foot
inside the White House.
The Aberration must have caused
infinitesimal ripples
that affected
the movements of my younger self.
The temporal domino effect.
This is why
we should never interfere with history.
We'll agree to disagree.
But one thing's for sure,
we cannot let him see you.
Indeed. The last time he and I interacted,
nearly erased our marriage from existence.
(RAY SIGHS)
Those are jelly beans.
I can see that.
Those are President Reagan's jelly beans.
So what? Eat 'em.
What? I'm pretty sure
that's against the rules.
We don't follow rules, remember?
Oh. Right.
(CHUCKLES)
Reagan wasn't even
one of my top-three favorite presidents.
- Want some?
- Yeah.
Oh, it'll take some massaging,
but I believe we can get the Soviets
to agree to eliminating
all nuclear ground-launched
ballistic and cruise missiles.
I'll even make them believe
it was their idea.
I don't know
what we'd do without you, Mr. Darhk.
You'd manage.
But winning is always better.
(CHUCKLES)
I think we found our Aberration.
RAY: (ON RADIO) Damien Darhk is here.
PROFESSOR STEIN:
Sara, don't do anything rash.
- Sara? Sara? Are you...
- (CLICKS)
Here's another diplomatic cable from 1956
from the British ambassador
warning the JSA
about Soviet spies in their midst.
I thought fighting Hitler would unite
the US and the Soviet Union.
Oh, we have so much Cold War history
to catch you up on.
(POWERING DOWN)
Okay, what's this?
(EAGLE SCREAMS)
(SHOUTS)
Todd?
Why?
Why did you abandon us?
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
(PANTING)
Who is that?
AMAYA: It's Obsidian.
From the JSA?
Oh...
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(GUN CLICKS)
Ma'am, I'm gonna need you
to drop the weapon.
Drop the knife,
and place your hands behind your head.
We've got a situation in the East Wing.
I know you want vengeance for Laurel,
but it's not that simple.
Get out of my way.
Don't move!
Stay where you are!
Damn it!
We gonna fight or leave?
- Fight.
- (WEAPON POWERING UP)
(MEN SHOUTING)
All right. Get out of here, I got this.
- No, you go. I got this.
- I said go!
(BOTH GROAN)
What do I say about crossing streams?
- You said we don't follow the rules.
- That's the one rule!
One rule we follow!
Go!
We interrupt this broadcast
with breaking news.
Just a day before President Reagan is set
to welcome General Secretary Gorbachev
to the White House to sign the INF Treaty,
a White House tour ends in violence
and what witnesses describe
as a "rocket man."
Was this an act of terrorism?
Please turn it off, Gideon,
I can't bear it.
So, your thirst for vengeance
nearly landed the entire team in prison.
I guess it's only okay to change history
if it suits your personal vendetta.
Wasn't all Blondie's fault.
Haircut screwed up as well.
(SPLUTTERS) If you would just
let me tinker with the cold gun,
I told you I could figure it out,
the whole crossing the streams problem.
There's nothing wrong with the cold gun.
It's you, you goof.
RAY: The bigger question is,
why did Damien Darhk become
an advisor to Reagan's White House
on the eve of a nuclear treaty
with the USSR?
If his involvement with the Nazis in 1942
is any indication,
he's working
with our time-traveling nemesis.
It's the same person that killed Hourman.
Amaya needs to hear about this.
So she can also lose focus,
risking everything
in a selfish pursuit of revenge?
Do you have something
you'd like to say to me, Martin?
Yes.
That killing Damien Darhk almost 30 years
before his actual death
will have countless,
unforeseeable effects on the history
that we are charged with protecting.
But what about protecting my sister?
She brought me back from the dead.
She risked everything for me.
How could I not do the same for her?
Because you answer
to a higher calling, Sara.
I'm sorry, but we cannot stray
from our guiding principle.
Well, I'm sorry, too.
Sounds like
you've never really cared about anyone.
(WHISPERING) You think I killed him?
I hope I didn't kill him.
He's gotta be in his late 70s, at least.
Maybe he couldn't take the hit.
Oh, my God. I just killed a member
of the Justice Society.
Why are you whispering?
In case he's not dead,
he could probably use the nap.
- I'm not an invalid.
- (SIGHS)
Just old.
And you.
You haven't aged a day.
It's one of
the few benefits of time travel.
So, you left us
to join the lovable losers?
I was trying to find Rex's killer.
And you never thought to tell me?
I found Rex dying.
His last words were "time traveler."
I didn't think, I just acted.
What happened to them, Todd?
After the war, our friendship
with the Soviet Union ended.
And we continued fighting
as what was known as the Iron Curtain
descended over Central and Eastern Europe.
Does "we" include my grandfather?
Right to the end.
In 1956, President Eisenhower
sent the team on a mission to Leipzig.
They never made it back.
Why didn't you go?
'56 was a charged time.
They were concerned
that I couldn't be trusted.
- Why not?
- Leave it be, Nathaniel.
SARA: Nate, Amaya.
Report back to the Waverider.
I promise you, Todd, I will fix this.
What's done is done, Amaya.
Not when you have a time machine.
I'm sorry for leaving, Todd.
I truly am.
Rex's killer is here?
In 1987?
Potentially, if Damien Darhk
is still working with him.
No way. Damien Darhk
joined the Reagan Administration
as an advisor at the Reykjavik Summit?
And after the collapse of the summit,
Darhk was credited
with reviving the disarmament talks?
Darhk prefers stockpiling nukes,
not getting rid of them.
The nuclear treaty must be a cover.
- For what purpose?
- SARA: That's what we need to find out.
Gideon, where is Damien Darhk now?
GIDEON: I'm accessing the calendar
on his secretary's IBM personal computer.
Mr. Darhk has a meeting in Georgetown Park
at 8:00 p.m.
Late-night meeting in the park.
That's not suspicious.
Ray, take Mick. Find out
who Darhk is meeting with and why.
Wait. Just us?
(SIGHS)
Look, it's not a good idea for me to be
anywhere near Damien Darhk right now.
Right. I agree.
(GRUNTS) Okay, we're a go on audio.
RORY: We're cutting it close, Haircut.
That's Snart's jacket.
Thought it'd help me get into character.
- I'm Colonel Cold.
- The hell you are.
You're not gonna
give yourself a promotion.
Fine.
What are you doing?
We're on a stakeout. I brought snacks.
Apple slice?
I guess you're still upset
about the White House.
Look, I can be more careful.
I can be more meticulous, more like Snart.
I don't want you to be like Snart.
What?
You gave me his gun. You told me
I had to try to fill his shoes.
I was wrong.
(PANTING)
You keep reminding me of my dead friend.
It's bringing up...
- Feelings?
- Yes.
So, just stop and be you.
Well, that's a little difficult.
Considering I lost my suit,
my company, my powers.
Is this what
an existential crisis feels like?
RORY: Shut up.
Just shut up.
(SOFT ROCK MUSIC ON RADIO)
- I hate the '80s!
- (RADIO BREAKS)
ls there any sign
of who Darhk's meeting with?
RORY: Not yet.
Clandestine meeting in a D.C. park.
It feels like the beginning
of a John le Carré spy novel.
I'm more of an Ian Fleming guy.
Mmm. More explosions, less clothing.
What if Darhk is meeting
with Rex's killer?
- Then we don't let either of them leave.
- RAY: We've got movement.
A man just entered the park.
- SARA: Ray, we need audio.
- Yup.
Way ahead of you, Cap.
Thankfully, there was
a Tech Village nearby. Heh.
You wouldn't believe
what you can hack together
with a few household items. (GRUNTS)
(BORIS GREETS IN RUSSIAN)
Mr. Darhk.
Sounds like he's meeting with a member
of the Soviet delegation.
Not Rex's killer.
The package is procured.
Excellent news, Boris.
That is your name, isn't it? Boris?
Or is it Igor?
I find it's always one or the other
with you KGB agents.
Anyhoo, once the treaty is signed,
during the State Dinner,
you'll deliver the package.
And you will uphold
your half of the bargain.
As agreed.
But first, a toast,
to peace between our two nations.
Darhk was never interested
in the nuclear treaty.
He's working a side deal with the KGB.
Uh-oh.
Mayday.
(STUTTERING) My name is Martin Stein.
You must have heard of me.
You may have heard of me.
Marty, younger you just entered the park.
(STUTTERS) But that's impossible.
Today is December 7th,
Clarissa's birthday.
I distinctly remember
we had a dinner reservation for this
evening which took me months to procure.
- Well, you must've blown her off.
- This ought to be good.
Should we stop him?
PROFESSOR STEIN: Stop what? What am I doing?
(STAMMERING) Mr. Darhk,
allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Martin Stein,
you may have heard of me.
I'm on the negotiating team
and was recently nominated for my sixth
Carlin Award in physics. (CHUCKLES)
- Congratulations.
- Thank you. (CHUCKLES)
- Did you follow me here?
- I did. (CHUCKLES)
You see, I'm working
on a transmutation project
that is vital to national security.
I was hoping you might pass the proposal
on to the President.
Excuse me, I can't help but notice
you're wearing a Komandirskie watch,
typically supplied
to the Soviet Ministry of Defense.
Meeting with a Soviet outside
of the official negotiation schedule?
(STAMMERS) That is highly irregular.
(SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN)
Ray, Mick, get in there, now!
Okay. (CHUCKLES)
Clearly, there's been
some kind of misunderstanding.
I'll just leave
and pretend these last five minutes
didn't happen. (CHUCKLES)
Unfortunately, my imagination
isn't quite that vivid.
- (GROANS)
- Martin!
- Grey!
(COUGHS)
(SIGHS)
(WHISTLING)
Ray, what happened?
RAY: Darhk just stabbed
Marty's younger self.
Where's Darhk?
RORY: We lost him.
RAY: It's gonna be okay.
We'll get you back.
Where is he?
He's on his way now.
Don't worry. You're gonna be fine.
You again?
By that I mean me again.
SARA: Guess who figured it out.
How did this happen?
I'm too young to die,
too brilliant to die.
Will one of you please shut me up?
- Gladly.
- SARA: Gideon.
GIDEON: I am cauterizing
the younger Martin's wound.
I am afraid it will leave both patients
with a rather nasty scar.
You should've let me punch him.
This is about time travel, isn't it?
That's why Special Advisor Darhk
stabbed me.
He wouldn't have stabbed you
if you had been having dinner
with Clarissa
- at L'Auberge as previously planned.
- Good God!
Clarissa. She's waiting
for me at the hotel.
How could you've left her alone
on her birthday?
She ordered room service.
- You are a careless, self-centered idiot.
- JAX: Grey. Grey.
Look, I'll go to the hotel,
and I'll tell Clarissa
that her husband's working late.
Okay? Just relax.
(PANTING)
Martin, what on Earth were you thinking?
Hubba hubba. Who's that?
Professor Stein's wife.
Jax is at her hotel explaining
why she has to spend her birthday alone.
Wait a minute. If you use everyone's
favorite talking computer to find her...
Gideon, do you have the location
on Damien Darhk?
GIDEON: Unfortunately, I have no intel
on his current whereabouts.
But we know where he's gonna be.
His little side deal with the Soviets
is going down at the State Dinner
tomorrow night.
GIDEON: Which is probably the most
heavily guarded dinner in history.
I think we know someone
who may be able to help.
- GIDEON: Is that so?
- One of Amaya's old JSA buddies.
And by "old" I mean old.
He may still have some government contacts
we can exploit.
TODD: Absolutely not.
Whatever Darhk is planning to exchange
with the Soviets, it can't be good.
All right, I'll contact the FBI.
You don't have to worry about it.
Except we do.
Darhk's working with a time traveler.
That's way out of the Bureau's league.
I believe this time traveler killed Rex.
All the more reason
to stay clear of that State Dinner.
You can't remain professional.
Are you kidding me?
She's nothing but professional.
She's all about being professional.
The only reason
I could ever see her not being...
Oh, my God!
You and Rex Tyler were together!
- No.
- They were together, weren't they?
- This makes total sense.
- We weren't together.
Like I said before, fraternization
among teammates is unprofessional.
Rex and I were going to leave the JSA
after the war.
Try and start a new life with each other.
And then he was cut down.
That's why I left the team.
And that's why I wouldn't talk to you
about them.
It's too hard.
And this is why I'm reluctant to help you.
Because your emotions
are clouding your judgment.
She won't be facing Darhk alone.
AMAYA: We need your help.
I know you feel like I abandoned you,
but please don't abandon me.
Hey, how're you doing?
I'm all right.
The truth is this young man
is like a stranger to me.
Every time I encounter him,
I can't imagine I was ever that person.
I think anyone would feel that way
about meeting their younger self.
I don't recognize my current self.
Mick told me I need to be more like me.
And he's right, which is rare.
Mmm. Indeed.
Problem is I don't know
what being me means right now.
- I don't know if that makes any sense.
- Of course it does.
I think everyone struggles,
at least on occasion,
with who they are and
what their place is in the world.
So, what's the answer?
(CHUCKLES) I have no idea.
But I suppose it's just to live.
It's all any of us can really do.
And then hopefully, through the act of
living, we discover who we truly are
and learn to grow from that.
Amaya got us invites to the State Dinner.
- Are you feeling up to it?
- Yes. I'm feeling much better.
Are you feeling up to it?
I think what he means is,
are you gonna create a diplomatic crisis
and risk unknown damage to history
by killing Damien Darhk?
I know what he means, Ray.
Earlier, you accused me
of not ever caring for anyone,
but you know that's not true.
I care very much about you.
And I'm less concerned about history
than I am about your conscience.
You're no longer an assassin, Sara.
You're our captain.
Well, let's hope I remember that
when the time comes.
Now, let's do this.
Thank you for helping us get in.
Feels good to be back in the game.
I don't see Damien Darhk anywhere.
He'll be here.
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
Oh, my God, what is she doing here?
Probably looking for her husband,
no doubt.
- She's coming this way. What should I do?
- Just talk to her.
Mr. Jackson, I expected
to meet my husband here.
- Have you seen him yet?
- I'm sorry. No, I haven't.
I'd be worried,
but it's just like Martin
to lose track of time.
(CHUCKLES) Well, I'm sure wherever he is,
you are foremost in his mind.
Who are you?
Uh, I'm a colleague of his.
My name is also Martin.
He never mentioned you.
Well, I'm sure he has more important
things to talk about.
(JAZZ MUSIC ON SPEAKERS)
Oh, uh, would you care to dance?
I never seem to take the time
to enjoy these State Dinners.
Sure.
You all right? You seem tense.
When you find Rex's killer,
what are you gonna do to him?
Arrest him.
What else is there?
You could kill him.
I'm a member of the Justice Society.
Or at least I was when it existed.
I'm not some vigilante.
I'm sorry, I don't mean to pry,
but you don't seem too happy to be here.
It's just...
Martin invited me on this trip
for my birthday,
and I've spent
the better part of it alone.
Perhaps you should talk to him.
I've tried.
But Martin's love for nuclear science,
it's irrepressible.
Sometimes my husband has tunnel vision.
Well, Martin is a fool.
But, believe me, he loves you.
You're far more important to him
than any of his scientific achievements.
I have the strangest feeling,
like we've danced before.
Sara, Darhk is in the hallway.
Mick, Ray, guard the exits.
Everybody else, get ready to move.
Now that our governments
are waging peace upstairs,
what do you say
we get down to the real business?
You have brought us the codes?
It's called a CD-ROM, the latest
in Defense Department technology.
As for my half of the exchange?
(LAUGHING)
- Hand over the box!
- (GUNS CLICKING)
And the kickass CD-ROM.
What is this?
- He thinks we're working with Darhk.
- Never.
No one has to get hurt.
It's not really my style.
Now, we can waste time chit-chatting,
or you can deal with the explosive
my people have secreted
inside the state dining room.
See, in about six minutes,
Reagan, Gorbachev,
and every hope for peace goes kaboom.
- Ray?
- RAY: We're on it.
I am sorry. Inconvenient, I know.
But try being me.
(ALL GRUNTING)
Todd!
RAY: We're on the move to find the bomb.
PROFESSOR STEM: The bomb?
We must save Clarissa.
(CLANGS)
I got this, Sara. Go stop Darhk.
- (CLANGS)
- Huh?
That's cool, man. Mary Todd's hope chest.
Aw! You have gone too far!
Everyone, get the hell out of here
right now.
(ALL MURMURING)
Now that we have your attention.
Would you please
leave the dining room immediately?
We believe there's a bomb on the premises.
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
(CLATTERING)
(BEEPING)
You okay?
Who are you?
A friend of your husband's.
Good news, we found the bomb.
Bad news,
this type of firing system is obsolete.
I have no idea how to disarm
such a crude weapon.
(GROANS) Figure it out, Ray.
I'm a little busy.
(GRUNTING)
- There's nothing I can do.
- RORY: Yes, there is.
I was wrong trying to make you like Snart.
You're Ray Palmer.
You can science your way out of anything.
I'm Ray Palmer. I'm Ray Palmer.
I can science my way out of anything.
I can...
If I can send an electrical pulse
from an outside power source,
I might be able to overload
the bomb's incendiary trigger.
But I'd have to dismantle the cold gun.
Less talking, more doing.
Huh.
No!
(DARHK CHUCKLING)
(GROANS)
Ray, tell me the bomb is disarmed.
(GRUNTING) That would be a lie.
Well, 10 seconds to live.
There are worse ways of dying.
- (ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
{GROANS)
(PANTING)
RAY: I did it.
I did it.
Good.
Hold on, Todd.
Okay? Just hold on.
You and I have met before.
New York City, 1942.
You haven't aged a bit. Lazarus Pit?
Oh. A woman of mystery.
I know that look in your eye, though.
That's the look of someone
that I've taken everything from.
Not everything.
You haven't taken my soul,
which I've already lost
and I'm not eager to do again.
And that's why I'm sparing your life.
How merciful of you.
I'm sparing you to prolong your suffering.
'Cause I'm from the future, Damien.
And I know how this all ends.
Your ark,
your grand vision,
just as you're about to accomplish
everything you desire,
your wife is murdered.
The love of your life.
And in total despair, you even try
to kill your own daughter.
An entire city rises up against you.
And then you die.
Defeated and alone.
(WHOOSHES)
What happened? Where's Darhk?
He took him.
The time traveler working against us...
He's a speedster.
Like the Flash?
Faster.
So, the speedster and Darhk, they have
whatever the KGB gave Darhk?
Unless...
Unless?
I swiped it off Darhk.
- Shut up.
- (SNORTS)
Can I hug you? Do we hug?
- Okay, just this once.
- There's gonna be more.
Yeah!
You took a bullet for me.
For a fellow member of the JSA,
it was nothing.
Astonishing to be back here again.
A ship that can travel through time
and heal any wound.
Think of the possibilities.
Let me remind you,
it's imperative that you carry on
as if you never saw me
or anything else from the future.
That you would pass up
the chance to show me
even the barest glimpse of that future,
catapulting our transmutation research
into the 21st century.
I had no idea I could ever be so selfish.
Interesting, considering that's
exactly how you've been to Clarissa.
She nearly died last night because of
your blind devotion to your work.
You of all people understand
the importance of our research...
I understand the importance
of one thing, and one thing only.
After everything I've accomplished,
all the awards I've won...
Did we win the sixth Carlin?
The only thing that brings
meaning to my life is Clarissa.
Yes, Martin, our wife.
Who you've spent
the last two days ignoring.
But I love Clarissa.
Then cherish her, Martin.
Because I promise you,
she is the only thing
you'll care to remember.
And I promise you,
I'll make sure she knows I love her.
I pray that you do.
- (BEEPING)
- (WHIRRING)
(SIGHS)
Are you sure you won't come with us?
Rex's killer is still out there.
We could find him together.
I think last night proved
my fighting days are over.
- You were amazing out there.
- (CHUCKLES)
It felt like old times.
But there's something keeping you
here in 1987, isn't there?
After the JSA disbanded,
I spent a lot of lonely years.
Until I finally met someone, Amaya.
And he's waiting for me at home.
(CHUCKLES)
GIDEON: I have ameliorated
Mr. Rice's injuries.
TODD: That's incredible.
Wow.
A word of advice from an old man,
who's lived long enough
to see the world change,
and mostly for the better.
If you're lucky enough to find love again,
embrace it.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Are you leaving already?
I was hoping we'd have a beer.
Uh, unlike you, my time is limited.
And I don't need the carbs.
Good-bye, Todd.
- Well, I guess I'll just, uh...
- He loved to sing.
Henry.
Your grandfather.
He had a beautiful voice.
During long convoys or stakeouts,
he would serenade the team.
He made it his personal mission
to get me to sing along,
but he never succeeded.
But when the chips were down
and all hope seemed lost,
we could always count on Henry
to lift our spirits.
That's the kind of man
your grandfather was.
Then take me back there now.
I will get your item back for you.
The Legends have left 1987.
The item is beyond your reach.
That blonde woman,
she's a time traveler like you.
She knows what happens to me
in the future.
- I'm sure she does.
- Then take me with you.
I need to change my destiny.
Tell you what.
Why don't we work together
to change both of our destinies?
Step inside.
Whoa.