Last season
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
I'm no longer the captain. You are.
Permission to depart, Captain Lance.
I know that I'm supposed
to go back to 1942.
I have to believe that time
is stronger than that.
It's a timequake.
The result of us
interacting with ourselves.
And whose bright idea was it
to do the one thing
that could jeopardize all of time?
Yours.
Guys.
I think we broke time.
I guess this means
we're not going to Aruba.
You said you broke time.
No, I said we broke time.
Yep, but it was your idea.
No, my idea was to save
reality and save Amaya.
By violating the first rule
of time travel.
Never visit the same time
and place twice,
thereby breaking time.
Perhaps we should continue
this argument
somewhere there aren't dinosaurs.
Whoa. Big Ben.
So what?
- Guys.
- I always wanted to visit it.
Guys!
Amaya, talk to it.
- She can talk dinosaur?
- Like you wouldn't believe.
Please speed up that conversation...
Y'all just saw that, right?
And that.
Well, you really have
buggered everything up this time.
Her idea.
No matter. As you can see,
my agents are already hard at work
dealing with these Anachronisms.
Anachronisms?
People, places, and things
displaced from
their native time periods.
I told you. I was leaving to create
an organization to replace
the Time Masters.
- 15 minutes ago.
- For you.
Forming the Time Bureau
has been the work
of the last five years of my life.
I've gotten quite good at it,
I'd have to say.
You mean, you have
Time Agents at work
in the Cretaceous Period as we speak?
Indeed, and throughout
Los Angeles, making sure
no one retains any memory of this...
unfortunate incident.
Which is why your services
are no longer required.
Whoa. What?
It seems only fitting,
since I was the one
who brought this team together
that I should be
the one to disband it.
So...
On behalf of the Time Bureau,
I hereby relieve
the Legends from duty.
This isn't auditions
for "American Ninja Warrior",
you know.
And how many times have I told you
not to play with the merchandise?
Oh, I know that look.
It's the look of someone who thinks
they could have gotten a better job.
Well, let me tell you
something, freckles.
You're lucky I even hired someone
who had been reported dead...
twice.
Especially in this economy.
What?
No thank you?
Thank you.
That's better.
Now get over to Health and Beauty.
Somebody just spilled
a whole mess of conditioner.
Alan...
Alan, I've had a breakthrough.
I have told you not to interrupt me
when I'm plugged in.
Yes. No, I know
that's very important to you, but,
Alan, I've been working
on this side project.
Not only have I managed
to shrink organic matter
but I've also streamlined
the technology
so that you can wear...
I'm not interested, brah.
Look, I... I get it.
Once upon a time,
you were "Ray Palmer, tech mogul".
But when you give your
company to a woman
who runs it into the ground,
you lose all side-project privileges.
Great news for you, though.
What we're doing here at Upswipz
is trying to change the world.
Upswipz is a dating app.
Just like Tinder, except you
swipe up-down instead of left-right.
Which is far more intuitive.
And Upswipz isn't a dating app.
- It's a holistic social networking
- Social networking platform.
Oh, but, Alan...
my miniaturization technology
has the potential to actually
make the world a better place.
If that were true,
it'd be an app.
If it doesn't live in a phone...
it's not the future, Ray.
Well, I've actually been
to the future.
Like, three times.
Damn it, Wally.
What did I say?
Oh, I was supposed to save
some of the bad guys for you.
Just a few.
You know what?
I'll make it up to you.
The first round is on me.
No. Thanks, man, we're good.
I actually
have a girl waiting for me.
Next time.
Hey.
Sorry I'm late. There was a...
kind of a work thing.
It's okay.
I know a really great coffee place...
Alana.
- Hey, girl.
- Hi.
Hey, idiot.
Either refill my margarita
or get out of my light.
This is a private beach.
Listen, pal, what did I...
And who the hell
are you supposed to be?
I am Gaius Julius Caesar
of Rome.
Thought I recognized you.
I knocked off one of your casinos
in Vegas.
I am here to conquer
all the known world.
Right.
Wait a sec.
How did you get here?
I imagine through the mischief
of the goddess Ate.
But it matters
not the land I find myself in.
It is but a matter of time
before my banner flies over it.
Is that a fact?
Yeah?
Boss.
- Rory?
- I got a situation.
I think I bumped into one of those
mechanisms...
- Mechanism?
- A nagging-ism.
- Anachronism?
- Yes.
Julius Caesar...
is in Aruba.
- Seriously?
- Seriously.
I got him tied up in my casita.
What do you want me to do?
Just sit tight and keep him safe.
If you screw up history,
the Bureau will be on your ass
before you can say...
Son of a bitch.
Are you taking a personal call
- during peak consumer traffic?
- No.
'Cause I quit.
All right.
What's so important
to make you catch a train
to Central City?
Where's Amaya?
We kind of broke up.
- What?
- It's not a big deal.
So what's going on?
Rory found an Anachronism.
Apparently, Julius Caesar
just wound up in Aruba.
Mick's got him all tied up.
Look, this is our chance
to get the Time Bureau
to deal us back in.
Look, if we pull this off,
Rip might give us
our old ship back.
Wow, I had no idea
you were so unhappy
with your new life.
Are you kidding me?
I'm... I'm... I'm loving it.
I'm doing really good work.
It says you work at
Sink, Shower & Stuff.
Yeah, well...
even vigilantes
have to pay their bills.
What are you guys
so content with, huh?
What are you doing?
I'm doing pretty good.
Thanks for asking.
I am...
The second most popular
superhero in Central City.
So that's... pretty good.
Well, I am the first
most popular in Silicon Valley
when I'm not changing
the world with a...
holistic social networking platform.
- Let's go.
- Thank God.
You sure this is where they're at?
I bumped into one of Rip's
Time Agents a while back.
He may have left his badge
at my place.
He left it at your place?
All right,
maybe I lifted it off of him
in the morning.
- Freeze!
- Hands in the air!
Eyes on, eyes on!
Hey, don't move!
Stay right there!
Hello, everyone.
Welcome.
On the floor.
Hands behind your heads.
Oh, sorry, there must be
some kind of mistake.
We're the... we're the...
Legends!
Oh, we know exactly
who you losers are.
Wow. This floor is,
like, super clean.
Lady, why are you so mean?
Maybe it's that poly-blend pantsuit
that's got her so grumpy.
I didn't know Men's Wearhouse
gave group discounts.
What's wrong with you people?
Do you want to get shot?
Totally rather get shot
than look like a Sears model.
Hold your fire!
Stand down! All of you.
Excuse me.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
Hello. So good to see you all.
Next time, just call ahead.
You son of a bitch.
Eyes on, eyes on!
There's been a slight
misunderstanding,
- Dr. Heywood.
- Nate, what are you doing?
I want to hear Rip say it.
You told Amaya to go back to 1942.
Amaya went back to 1942?
It was her idea.
She wanted to go back home
to Zambesi.
What'd you say?
It was Amaya's idea
to go back to Zambesi.
No, I heard him, Ray.
I was just being rhetorical.
All right. This is just awkward.
So...
what brings the rest of you
to the Time Bureau?
We found an Anachronism.
I wasn't aware any of you
were searching for Anachronisms.
We weren't.
Rory was on a bender
when Julius Caesar showed up.
Agent Sharp, have we seen
any activity that would match
such a massive historical
displacement?
Absolutely not, sir.
Well, I guess you must have
missed one then.
I find that very hard to
believe, and you know what...
Ready a go-team...
and we will meet you
at the Op-Center.
Sir.
In the meantime...
Who fancies a tour?
Guess they're not used to seeing
famous people.
Yeah, kind of like
we're the Founding Fathers
of the Time Bureau.
In a way.
I suppose if you lot hadn't created
the greatest time paradox
the world had ever known...
all of these people
would have nothing to do.
- Unhand me, you knave!
- Is that...
Oh, yeah. King Arthur.
His displacement
into the Spanish Civil War
caused quite the Anachronism.
Oh, evil sorcerer!
I might have known you
were responsible for all of this.
Now when he's returned
to his original time,
he will have no memory
of his displacement.
All humility aside,
we are the most important
security organization...
That no one's ever heard of.
Who somehow missed
the fact that Julius Caesar
is down in Aruba working on his tan.
I'm sure, our detection system
would have picked up
on his displacement.
Yeah, and we get that.
But all we're saying is,
if you wanted to give us
the old Waverider back,
we would be happy
to go down there
and take care of it for you.
Yeah, you know, for...
for old time's sake?
I'm sorry, but our old ship
has been put to new use.
You turned our ship
into a simulator?
The Command Module is heading
toward a meteoroid belt.
Apollo 13 astronauts will die
unless we do something.
Oh, that's cool, man.
They're teaching one
of our old missions.
I've got an idea.
Why don't we swing around
and use our ship as a shield?
- Boom.
- Kidding.
I'm not a total idiot.
Target the Command Module's
oxygen tank with our photons
and fire.
Yes! The ruptured tank
propelled their capsule
out of harm's way, Captain.
Well done, class.
See you all tomorrow.
We'll see how you do
trying to stop an atomic torpedo
from blowing up New York City.
What are they doing here?
We are here to help you.
That's very gracious of you.
But whatever it is,
we have professionals
who can handle the matter.
Along with whatever damage
Mr. Rory causes.
Your salad sucks.
You should know
this is not the first time
I've been taken captive.
Oh, great, a story.
Once, when I was a young man...
I was kidnapped by pirates.
They ransomed me for 50 talents
of silver, a fortune.
My family paid the money, of course.
But I told my captors
they would be better off killing me.
Because if they did let me go...
I promised to come back one day...
and not only to take my silver...
but to crucify
the pirates one by one.
And that's exactly what I did.
You saying I should kill you?
You should believe me
when I make a promise.
The gold in this satchel...
is yours.
Gold?
But I swear by my household gods...
it will cost you your life.
Do we have a location on Mr. Rory?
We followed a trail
of petty larceny reports.
He's been holed up on the beach...
running up a room service tab
and a serious collection of STDs.
- That's our Mick.
- He's been busy.
Locking in on coordinates now.
Is the go-team ready?
Locked and loaded, sir.
Opening a portal.
You broke my nose.
Out of my way!
- Our team is under attack.
- Definitely Rory.
Alpha team,
do you have eyes on Caesar?
He's got the target.
What do you want us to do,
Command?
Get the hell out of there
before Mr. Rory causes
any more mayhem.
Roger that. Initiating extraction.
Get off me, you damn missionaries!
Get the hell off me, dude.
This is Julius Caesar?
Dude, my dad's a lawyer.
I'm going to totally sue
all of your asses.
What is this place?
An institution you will never
step foot in again, Mr. Rory.
Get them out of here!
Rip, look. I'm sorry.
- I thought that this...
- The Legends would change?
Since when do we need to change?
When you left our team, you said
you had nothing left to teach me.
Yes, well,
unfortunately all of history
suddenly came unglued
moments after
I'd uttered those words.
Look, I miss the good
old days too, Sara.
But times have changed.
Yeah, and you don't think
you need us anymore.
Look, Rip.
This is our mess.
You have to let us fix it.
Using your team to fix anything...
is like doing brain surgery
with a chainsaw.
Whoa. You can't leave yet.
Not without parking validation.
Son of a bitch stole my money.
This is a genuine Roman aureus.
This is first century B.C.
That means Rory really
saw Julius Caesar.
- Duh.
- We've got to tell Rip
that he's got the wrong guy.
- Yeah, like he'll listen to us.
- He's right.
We've got to grab Caesar
ourselves.
And prove to Rip
that we got the right stuff.
Sara.
Exit's this way.
Our ship's this way.
We're gonna steal the Waverider?
We're gonna fix our mistakes.
Oh, damn it! I mean, darn it.
There's a class in session.
Listen up, punks.
Class dismissed. Get out of here.
This must be a part
of the training exercise.
Our ship has been boarded
by a Time Pirate.
On behalf of The Time Bureau,
and in accordance
to Article 15.6, Section B,
concerning the unlawful seizure
of Time Ships...
Anyone else?
Gideon's been in sleep mode
for five years.
But if I can divert her power
back to the core...
Hello, Legends. What did I miss?
Well, we're about to
steal the ship...
go grab Julius Caesar in Aruba...
all before history
completely collapses.
So it's business as usual, then.
Exactly.
Gideon, engines to power.
Turbines to speed.
Right away, Captain.
Sounds like this old boat
needs a lube job.
What in the hell
do they think they're doing?
The hangar's sealed.
There's no way out of here.
Yep, well, I'm afraid the Legends
have never permitted
something like logic
to stop them.
I hope you know what
you're doing, Ms. Lance.
Gideon, time-jump us out of here.
Oh, are you sure we can
time-jump inside the building?
We're about to find out.
Gideon, when are we?
I was only able to time-jump us
three minutes into the future.
We're still in Star City.
If you haven't noticed,
the ship is in desperate need
of maintenance.
Yeah, there's no way
we're gonna make it to Aruba.
Can we make it to Central City?
I know a good mechanic there.
Jefferson.
What a... what a nice surprise.
Lily also dropped by
with some rather exciting news.
Oh, well, if it's a bad time,
I can always just...
Wait, wait. What is it?
Something's wrong. I can feel it.
We may only see each other
once a week
for our bonding sessions
but we still share
a psychic connection.
I dropped out of school.
Why would you do that?
You could have your
master's in... in two years.
Yeah, I know, it's just...
Learning about engineering
is not half as fun
as actually, you know,
being an engineer...
on a time ship.
Oh, hey, Jax.
Lily, you're... you're...
What? I'm what?
Oh, you... you look...
you look healthy.
I'm kidding. I'm pregnant.
- Oh, my God. Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Yeah, I was on sabbatical
in Rome with my boyfriend and...
She means her future husband.
And we decided
we wanted to come home
and break the big news in person.
Oh, I've got to put
the osso buco in the oven.
But you should totally stay
for dinner...
right, daddy?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Dude. What?
My heart still melts
when she says that word.
It's crazy. It's...
Oh, my God.
Is that what I think it is?
Come on, Grey.
A chance to meet Julius Caesar
and fix history.
Look, we have a time ship.
We can get you home
in time for dessert.
That's what I told
Clarissa the last time I left.
And when you came home
you had a surprise daughter.
Your point?
The point is, sometimes...
we screw things up for the better.
That's a good motto.
We should use that.
Fine, whatever.
- I'll... I'll come.
- Great.
Now all we need is Amaya
and we can get the band
back together.
That's not happening.
Whoa, did I miss something?
Amaya dumped him.
- Went back to 1942.
- She didn't dump me.
She didn't dump me.
Amaya went back to Zambesi
because Rip told her
she has some
sort of destiny to fulfill
back in 1942. That's it.
Unlike the rest of us
who don't have crap
waiting for us in the real world.
Speak for yourself, numb nuts.
I don't know about you all,
but I was destined
for greater
things than folding towels.
And Rip thinks he doesn't need us
because he's got the Time Bureau.
Ray's right.
We're the ones who broke history.
We should be the ones that fix it.
But instead of operating
on history with a chainsaw...
this time, we are gonna be
the scalpel.
Is this your idea of subtle?
Just try to blend in, okay?
No problem.
Great Caesar's ghost.
That's him.
So what I have to say
to you is this...
are you willing to fight with me?
Yeah!
And claim this savage land
for Rome?
Yeah!
What, did you teach Caesar English?
Nope. Just showed up speaking fancy.
Temporal linguistic dysplasia...
- What?
- A side-effect
of historical displacement.
Astonishing!
You know, cowards die
many times before their deaths.
The valiant never taste death
but once!
- Yeah!
- And Delta Nu Phi sucks!
Delta Nu Phi sucks!
Alpha Psi Gamma sucks!
Can we not agree they all suck?
Alright.
Let's shut this toga party down
before things really get out of hand.
No powers.
It can make
the Anachronism worse.
Right, be the scalpel.
Because I saw in you...
I've got an idea.
The makings of a legion.
Come on, man. Are you really
trying to hook up now?
No, I'm creating a dating profile
on our new UpSwipz app.
Gideon, I need you to hit
every phone on the beach
with a match.
"Exotic beauty looking for
casual sex with young frat stud?"
- That might work.
- Yeah.
Now all I need is a profile picture.
I believe I've got that covered.
Not bad.
- For Mars!
- Yeah!
- For Rome!
Death... or glory!
All right, JC. Party's over.
You're coming with us.
I'd rather fall on my sword
than surrender it to a woman.
Well, then today is your lucky day.
Oh, shouldn't we help her?
It's him I'm worried about.
Yep, I'd say our work here is done.
And to quote the great
conqueror himself,
"We came, we saw..."
We kicked Caesar's ass!
Oh, man.
- Suckers.
- Nice work.
I'd have done it faster.
Oh, I'm sorry.
- Did that hurt?
- Easy, Mick.
He broke my nose.
My best feature.
Still... we have to get him
back to his time in one piece.
Or he doesn't go on
to conquer the world
and help create the greatest empire
history has ever known.
We need to get moving.
It's not gonna take Rip long
to track down a stolen time ship.
Quite so, Ms. Lance.
It appears that you've captured
the real Julius Caesar. Well done.
Now, if you'll just return him to us,
we'll be happy to handle his
reinsertion back into history.
You don't think we can handle it?
It's not that.
Maybe it is that.
But, the fact remains
that you have hijacked our property.
And if you would return it to us
along with our anachronistic guest...
all will be forgiven.
I trust you'll use
your best judgment.
Does he not know this team?
Shouldn't we entrust Caesar's return
to people who do that sort
of thing professionally?
I thought this
was our chance to prove
that we were professional... ish.
Your call, Captain.
Gideon...
plot a course for the Time Bureau.
I'm afraid that won't be possible
without additional repairs.
Of course.
Et tu, Sara?
I'm using my best judgment.
You know, I've taken
these engines apart
so many times, feels like
this ship is a part of me.
It is a part of you
that you can take on
whatever adventure
life offers you next.
What adventure could be better
than this one?
I mean, I got to be a superhero
who traveled through time...
changing history.
Yes, I know.
Look, I know you want to do
the whole granddad thing.
Smoke a pipe by the fire, but...
I got a whole lot of life left...
and I have no idea how to fill it.
Jefferson, you are, hands down...
the most gifted, capable...
driven young man I've ever known.
You can do anything you want to do.
Well, that's all well and good.
But what I want to do is be half
of a nuclear-powered superhero.
And I can't do that
if you don't want to.
Have you come to gloat?
Or to grant me the mercy
of taking my own life?
Getting beaten by a woman
bothers you that much?
Yes.
If your intention is neither
boasting nor mercy...
to what do I owe the honor
of this visit?
You doubt your present
course of action
and seem to believe that Caesar
holds the key to resolving it.
There's nothing to resolve.
My course of action isn't up to me.
So you believe your future
lies in the hands
of the Three Fates?
No.
It lies in the hands of a group
called the Time Bureau.
And if I go against them now,
they'll take my ship.
And if I screw this up...
then I lose everything.
And that's all you're willing
to wager for greatness?
Pompey said
he would have my head
for going against the Senate...
but when I lead my army
across the Rubicon...
Rome will welcome me as a god.
Well, I wish
I shared your confidence.
It cost me eight years
and countless centurions
to conquer Gaul.
But with an Amazonian queen
like you by my side...
I could make short work
of the rest of the world.
Conquering the world
does sound nice...
But I don't need you to do it.
Ship's fixed, Cap.
Fixed enough to get us back
to the Time Bureau?
How about ancient Rome?
Only one way to find out.
According to Gideon,
Caesar disappeared
the night before
his famous march on Rome.
Yeah, no crossing the Rubicon
means no civil war.
No civil war means no Ides of March.
No Ides of March means...
No Roman Empire.
What happens on the Ides of March?
Well, that's when your friends,
who really aren't your friends,
stab you in the back
to stop your rise to power.
Not that you'll remember any of this.
Check it out.
History is back to normal.
And now a little something
for the Heywood scrapbook.
Oh, man. That's a keeper.
Enjoy conquering the world.
Perhaps my eyes deceive me,
but that does not look
like the Time Bureau to me.
No, it says here we landed
in 49 B.C.
Relax, because
we just dropped off JC
back where he belongs.
So, history has been restored
and we can go home.
I'm afraid that's not possible.
Why? Something wrong with the ship?
No, but your home no longer exists.
Here is a map of what
was formally known
as the United States, circa 2017.
I thought you said
that history has been restored.
Does that look restored to you?
What does "Magna Hesperia" mean?
It means Caesar went on
to conquer the known world
and then, the unknown world.
One of you fools
must have entrusted him
with future knowledge,
something that allowed him
to alter the course of history.
No, no. I mean, Sara hit him
with Rip's flashy...
- Flashy thing.
- Thing.
Oh, my God.
What?
My book.
What book?
Change of plans.
We're not marching on Rome, sir?
No, we're still marching.
But when we get there,
we're going to visit
a few old friends...
starting with Brutus and Cassius.
I cannot believe you let Caesar
steal the answers to the test.
Why are you all looking at me?
It's not my fault.
How did mop-head even know
there would be a test?
It's a figure of speech.
Caesar knew how to alter history
because he already knew
how it would unfold.
Okay, so, all we got to do
is get back out there
and refold history.
Or contact Mr. Hunter
and let the Time Bureau handle it.
No, no, no, no.
We do not let those time-turds
have the satisfaction
of knowing that we...
That you lost the book?
Stop blaming me, okay?
Caesar must have swiped it
when I wasn't looking.
- Nate's right.
- Thank you.
Not about it not being your fault...
about The Time Bureau.
They're 2,000 years away.
- We can fix this before they even...
- Too late.
Ms. Lance, a word.
Yeah.
Look, I know what you're gonna say
but we are gonna fix this.
You shall do nothing of the sort.
My agents
will clear this mess in no time.
And what if something
goes sideways?
None of these guys are field agents.
Admit it, Rip. You need us.
No, Sara. You need this.
But just because you all found
life outside this ship boring
doesn't mean you get
your old jobs back.
Because the Time Bureau is capable
of getting the job done...
Without the mess.
Status?
We've got eyes on the target.
Go-team is hot.
Yes, you are.
Watch and learn, Ms. Lance.
Execute.
Asset acquired.
Proceed to the target to commence
memory erasure protocol.
Wait, I've seen this play before.
Leave the merchandise unattended...
draw the target out...
League of Assassins strategy?
No. It's Sink, Shower & Stuff.
We use it to catch shoplift...
it's a trap!
You've got to pull your team out
of there.
Agent Sharpe, initiate extraction.
Extract.
Oh, Agent Sharpe has been...
apprehended.
We were caught unprepared.
But we'll go back in, and we...
And screw things up
worse than you already have?
Boss is right.
We need to go
and rescue Agent Hotcakes.
Oh, please. This entire situation
is happening because of you idiots...
Idiots?
Idiots with special abilities.
We know how to handle ourselves.
Not against Julius Caesar
who has an entire legion
at his command.
We're pretty good
at taking down legions.
You're damn straight.
I'm assuming the answer is no,
but do any of you happen
to have a plan?
We're about to rejoin my army.
Be grateful.
Not only am I letting you live.
I'm permitting you to witness
the rise of the Roman Empire.
The Time Bureau will never
permit you to alter history.
Caesar does not alter history.
He makes it.
Surrender your prisoner
in the name of Ares...
the god of war!
Mars is the Roman god
of war, Jefferson.
Yeah, whatever.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Rescuing you.
I can take care of myself.
Howdy.
Dormi strictum amicus.
What did you say to him?
Oh, "sleep tight, buddy"?
I guess. Maybe.
I think this deserves a bro hug.
Bring it.
Damn, Ray.
You ruined my vacation...
and my nose.
Now we're even.
See? Problem solved.
I've got to say, Ms. Lance.
Now that I've seen your team
in action with my own eyes...
you are even worse than I imagined.
You're welcome.
Well, like Nate said...
sometimes we screw things up
for the better.
I fail to see how
that's true in this case.
It's our new motto.
New motto?
Right, does that mean
that you all plan to continue
swashbuckling your way
through history?
With the Time Bureau's
permission, of course.
And if I deny you permission?
- We'll do it anyways.
- Yeah.
Sir, the go-team has erased the
memories of Caesar and his forces.
Good.
We'd best take our leave, then.
Sara. Mr. Rory.
Do your best to stay out of trouble.
What's that?
It's a portal thingy.
Communications thing...
and a... yes...
a memory thing.
So I guess that means you're staying.
Well, I kind of have to.
You'd be dead without me.
Cheers.
They are irresponsible,
undependable, unpredictable,
dangerous...
And yet effective.
At least on occasion.
Is that the reason
they're not warming a cell
back at headquarters as we speak?
They're not warming a cell,
Agent Sharpe.
Because they might just be
our best hope
of defeating what's coming.
They are the reason
Mallus is a threat.
Indeed.
But there might just come a day
when we need the Legends
to do what they do best...
Which is what, exactly?
Be the chainsaw.
Would you open a portal
back to headquarters?
I seem to have...
misplaced my Time Courier.
How's she running?
Lousy.
Rip's monkeys really
screwed up the works.
It's gonna take Ray months
to figure this out.
Why Raymond?
Well, I told Sara
to take us back home.
Oh, that's... that's
unfortunate, considering...
I have decided to stay aboard.
Whoa, wait, wait, what?
I shanghaied you
into our first voyage.
I forced this life upon you.
I could hardly ask you
to give it up now.
But your life, your family...
I'll make it home
for the birth of my first grandchild.
As for my family...
They're on this ship as well.
- Yeah.
You doing okay?
Well, nothing says "doing okay" like
pining over files of your ex.
Yeah, I was just thinking...
About her?
Yeah, about her, and...
and this place.
I miss being on the ship.
Yeah, of course you do.
It's your home.
And, she's back home too.
If she's happy, I'm happy.
She's happy, right?
Yeah. Totally.
This is the village.
Get out of our way, woman.
Actually, that's what
I was gonna tell you.
We have business here.
If you call poaching
and raping "business".
Zambesi is under my protection.
No! No, please don't!