RIP: In 2166,
an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan
is opposed by the body
I had sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered
as legends.
Previously, on
Legends of Tomorrow...
I was her.
Tragedy or heartbreak,
that's how it always ends
if the man's not Carter.
Time Master Druce?
You and your band of rogues have
run rampant throughout history.
This is why we work alone, Rip.
A team is a liability.
The Time Masters have issued
Omega Protocols on all of us.
They've sent the Pilgrim.
Who's the Pilgrim?
The Pilgrim is the Time Masters'
most deadly assassin.
She's hunting
our younger selves.
Kaylex Druzan.
You have been found guilty of
time piracy in the first degree
and sentenced to death
via Omega Protocol.
The Pilgrim has made contact
with your younger self.
(GASPING)
This will all be over quickly.
(CHOKING)
(SIZZLING)
Well done.
Here's your next assignment.
These individuals have
manipulated the timeline
without authorization
on multiple occasions.
You are hereby ordered
to hunt down these individuals'
younger selves,
and eliminate them.
- This isn't my element.
- (GRUNTS) It's mine.
Just keep a weather eye open
for the Pilgrim.
Gideon calculates a 97% chance
that she will attack
your younger self
in this exact time and place.
Got it.
(SIREN WAILING)
(COUGHING)
Young Rory is not in there.
But we found his parents,
they're dead.
All right, where the hell is he?
(GUN LOADING)
(STATIC FLASHING)
Come with me
if you want to live.
(CHUCKLES) I've always wanted to say that.
- JAX: That's younger you?
- RORY: What did you tell him?
That we work for a secret agency
called A.R.G.U.S.
I think he bought it.
Of course, he did.
He's an idiot.
Hey, no offense,
but do you really think
it's a good idea
to leave him unsupervised?
You're right, have fun.
- You seem calm.
- You mean considering
a temporal bounty hunter
is trying
to murder our younger selves?
I was gonna put it a little more
delicately than that, but yeah.
I think at some point,
you just learn
to live with a sword
over your head.
(CLANGING)
Either you're getting better,
or I'm getting lazy.
(SCOFFS)
So, it seems like
you decided to ignore
the advice from Old-West-you,
about not being with Ray.
Ignoring her advice about Ray
was your advice. Remember?
Don't listen to my advice.
So, did you tell him
what she said?
Oh, sure.
"Hey, Ray, by the way,
the women I met in 1871 was me.
"And she told me
our love was doomed
"to fail
because you're not Carter."
So, that was a "no"?
Look, Ray and I
are happy together.
We should be able to enjoy that
before I have to drop
the whole doomed-love-affair
thing on his head.
Yeah, I mean,
who wants a relationship
based on honesty
and communication? (GAGS)
Believe me, a relationship based
on an ancient Egyptian curse
doesn't work much better.
(CLANGING)
Mr. Rory, how are you feeling?
I mean, your younger self.
Jax is watching him.
That young man, you,
just lost his family,
you might want
a shoulder to cry on.
I don't cry, Professor. Oh, and,
Haircut, thanks for saving me.
You're welcome.
You know what I don't get is,
why doesn't the Pilgrim
just go back a week earlier
and kill younger Rory then?
Because the Omega Protocol
calls for precision.
Multiple attempts
from the Pilgrim
could do irreparable
temporal damage.
Which means
she's only got one shot
at killing each
and every one of us.
And we only have
one shot to extract
your younger selves
from the timeline
before she pulls the trigger.
Sir, based on the temporal wake
generated by the
Pilgrim's Timeship,
I calculate a 96% likelihood
that she's headed to
Starling City, circa 2007.
Pilgrim is targeting Ms. Lance.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- COP1: Name?
- Lance. Sara Lance.
This is ridiculous.
(LAUGHS) Come on, I thought it was
"Take your daughter
to work" day.
Yeah, If I was in grade school.
"Daddy, I'm doing a paper
on the Criminal Justice System,
"I wanna see what it looks like
on the inside."
Well, I didn't mean
inside a jail cell.
Too bad, 'cause that's the
next stop on our little tour.
I think you're enjoying this
a little too much.
Honey, it's the dream
of every father
to keep their daughters
locked up until they are 30.
Maybe even 40.
(GRUNTING)
What the...
(COMMOTION ENSUES)
(GRUNTS)
- (ZAPPING)
- (YELLING)
(GRUNTING AND GROANING)
(YELLS) Daddy!
(GRUNTS)
Get out of here!
Get out of here! Go! Go! Go!
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTING)
- (LASER GUN LOADING)
- (WINCES)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
Oh, my God, she's--
Quite the badass.
(GRUNTING)
(GUN LOADING)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
(SIGHS)
I put her in the cargo bay
with mini you.
Told them both to stay put.
The less they know
what's going on, the better.
You sure you wanna leave
daddy's little girl
with that punk?
Even before
the League of Assassins,
I knew how to handle
guys like you.
Has Gideon figured out
the Pilgrim's next target yet?
- That's peculiar.
- Peculiar or bad?
Gideon, run another scan for the
whereabouts of the Pilgrim.
GIDEON: I'm sorry, sir, the timeline
shows no temporal distortions.
I seem to be unable
to track the Pilgrim.
- That doesn't sound good.
- No. It's quite the opposite.
Without a way to track
the whereabouts of the Pilgrim,
she could target any one of you
at any point in time.
Gideon was tracking
the Pilgrim's temporal wake.
I didn't think it was possible
to conceal one's movements
through time.
Well, it is if the Time Masters
are on your side.
How does this all work?
She can travel to any place,
any time?
She could be killing any of us
right now.
- And if we die in the past--
- You die in the present.
RAY: Wow, this is so interesting.
How long does it take
for what happens in the past
to affect the present?
Could I be dead right now
and not know it?
Maybe I am dead right now.
RAY: Hello?
- Can anybody hear me?
- No.
Look, the important thing
is not to panic.
Somebody is playing
Russian roulette
with our younger selves,
why would we panic?
Well, there are
a few exceptions.
Kendra's ability to reincarnate
means that it would the Pilgrim
no good to target her.
And, as a former Time Master,
to remove me from history
would be quite dangerous
to the timeline.
Well, that's convenient.
And what's that
supposed to mean?
Nothing. It just occurs to me,
you've never told us
about your past, Rip.
And I don't trust a man
with secrets.
Look, the less information
you have to offer on me,
the less valuable you are
to our now numerous enemies.
- Like I said, convenient.
- Are they fighting?
This is not a fight, it's merely
an exchange of ideas.
No, not you. Them!
(CHUCKLES)
She slapped me.
The little weirdo said that
he liked the way that I smell.
I'm usually a lot smoother,
but I'm sort of freaking out
right now.
You, hands to yourself.
And next time,
hit with a flat palm.
And, you...
You're not her type. Now,
do I need to separate you two?
No.
Hey, when do I get to go home?
You're safer here, trust me.
Well, where is here?
And why do you look like me?
Please, will you just tell me
what the hell is going on?
Look, it's safer for you
if I don't.
And we look alike because...
Because we're like family,
and I need you to trust me.
Look, my dad,
he's gonna be freaking out.
- If he ever lost me--
- He won't lose you.
Ever.
I promise.
Hey.
Did you know that
Rip has a secret stash
of vintage cereals?
Fruit Brute
was always my favorite.
Are you okay?
I'm a little on edge.
You know, we've been
through a lot together
and you've never quite resorted
to eating sugary cereals.
RAY: Look...
I've spent a lot of my life
thinking about the future.
And now, I have to think
about the past,
just sometimes
the present and...
The point is, do you know where
I go to when things get crazy?
Which, for us, is always.
I go to those two years
in Hub City
when it was just you and me.
And it felt like we had forever.
Yeah.
That's what kept me grounded.
In fact, seconds before
Rip and the team came back,
I was about-- (GROANS)
KENDRA: Ray!
- My God!
- (CHOKING)
What's wrong?
Oh, my God!
Gideon, we need help! Ray...
(RAY GRUNTING)
What's happening to him?
GIDEON: He is suffering
from severe internal injuries.
(GROANS)
Who's doing this?
GIDEON: A deep scan
of Mr. Palmer's timeline
reveals a temporal anomaly
on December 19th, 2014.
In the vicinity
of Palmer Technologies.
The Pilgrim. Gideon,
get us to that location now!
- (GRUNTS)
- (CLAMORING)
Who are you?
I'm no one.
We have that in common.
(GUN LOADING)
(PULSE SUSTAINING)
- (GASPS)
- We need to get you to cover.
(GROANS) What is that thing?
Who is she? Who are you?
No time to explain!
(YELLING)
(COUGHS)
Rip and the team
are saving you in the past,
and I'm here now.
However long we have,
I wanna spend it with you.
RAY: My suit.
It works.
(BEEPING)
GIDEON: Mr. Palmer's vitals
are stabilizing.
They did it.
(STRAINING) Actually, I think
you get most of the credit.
Couldn't miss spending
the rest of our lives together.
(CHUCKLES)
I meant it, Ray.
I love you.
I guess you found the ring.
The ring?
Kind of a strange way
to get engaged, but
I'll take it.
(EXHALES)
What the Pilgrim did,
the way she turned our attacks
back on us.
It's as if she
was reversing time.
It's called,
"Temporal Micro Manipulation."
The ability to control time
in one's immediate vicinity.
We are lucky
to have saved Dr. Palmer.
So, basically, we have no idea
who she's going after next.
We know it's not Rip,
because he doesn't have a past
to go back to.
Gideon, prepare
for multiple time jumps.
Plot points here, here and here.
(BEEPING)
My birthday? Why are we--
The only way to ensure you
are not harmed in your past--
Is to abduct ourselves
as newborns.
Thus removing ourselves
from our future timelines.
- It's brilliant.
- It's morally questionable.
It's suicidal.
If we take too long
in getting them home--
Then history is altered.
There won't be a home
to go back to.
You'll disappear from the minds
of everyone
who's ever known you.
You mean, my own mom
wouldn't even know me?
My wife.
Yeah. And my...
Oh yeah, I don't have anyone.
Sure as hell beats dying.
- Hey.
How's Ray?
Fine, um, his younger self
is in the hospital,
so, our Ray
is healing rather quickly.
Though, you don't seem
too happy about it.
I'm not unhappy, I'm...
I'm engaged.
What?
Yeah. Ray proposed to me
while he was...
You know what?
It's a long story.
But you said, "Yes."
At the time.
(LAUGHS)
I never thought about marriage,
I didn't think I was able
to think about marriage.
KENDRA: I don't know what to do.
That's hard.
Do you like babies?
Yeah, but that sounds like
doubling down to me.
I need your help and then
I'll help you figure out
what you should say to Ray.
Okay.
Let's go.
All right, this is just like
any other mission.
The mark may be a newborn,
but it might as well be
a diamond or a microchip.
You know, you're starting
to sound like Snart.
- (GRUNTS)
- (BABIES CRYING)
Okay. Which one is Snart?
Look for the one with horns.
Found him.
Great. Grab him, let's go.
KENDRA: Hello, baby Snart.
Oh! Look at you.
Kendra, come on,
we don't have time for this.
KENDRA: Look.
- Look at those cheeks.
- (LAUGHS)
Oh! You're the cutest little baby
in the world.
(SHUSHING)
KENDRA: Poor kid.
He's gonna have a rough life
ahead of him.
Good thing we're kidnapping him.
- What are you doing?
- I'm getting us out of here.
We don't even know
where here is.
GIDEON: Identity confirmed. Sara Lance.
YOUNG RORY: Let's go!
Where do you think you're going?
- Give me that! Inside!
- (BABY CRIES)
Is that a baby?
Yes, and you guys
are in charge of him.
Wait, I--
Made five grand last summer,
babysitting. You'll be fine.
- No, I don't do babies.
- KENDRA: You do now.
Think of it as a "thank you"
for saving your life.
You better not drop
my future criminal partner.
Otherwise you are in trouble.
Comprende?
(GROWLS)
We've got Mr. Snart's
younger self.
Next up is you, Professor,
and you, Mr. Jackson.
How strange to imagine
holding one's infant self.
Actually, none of you
should participate
in your own abductions.
Let's call it
paradox prevention.
It's almost worth the risk.
To experience
how our own fathers
must have felt
the day we were born.
Yeah, well, not my dad.
He shipped out
before my mom went into labor.
He died two weeks later
in Somalia, so...
I'm so sorry.
Yeah.
(STRAINING IN LABOR)
I think I see the head.
- (GROANING)
- (BABY CRIES)
- (GASPING)
- (SIREN WAILING)
Look at that.
(BABY CRYING)
What do you think
of "Jeremy" as a name?
RIP: I think he looks
more like a "Martin."
You guys asked
for a doctor, right?
Yeah, how would we?
Uh... He means that we were
on our way to the hospital
and we saw your automobile.
Yeah, this little munchkin
needs a checkup.
Pre-natal care.
It's very important.
He means "post-natal."
We'll take him straight to the
hospital. We'll meet you there.
What about my wife?
It's somewhat disconcerting
that my father would give me up
so willingly
to two complete strangers.
Well, the 1950s
was a much more trusting time.
Trust me, I lived then. (SCOFFS)
- PROFESSOR STEIN: He's not in Somalia.
- RAY: What?
We need to hold off
on taking baby Jefferson.
I need to find grown Jefferson.
But Rip said that we...
I doubt very much
that giving the boy a moment
with his soon-to-be-dead father
will do the universe any harm.
What are you doing, Grey?
Trust me, Jefferson,
there's someone here
I really think you should meet.
Go talk to him.
And say what?
Speak from your heart.
- (EXHALES)
- Go.
JAX: You were supposed
to be shipping out.
- How do you know that?
- (BABY CRYING)
(SCOFFS) Right. My transport got delayed.
Told my CO,
my wife's giving birth.
He got me a pass and a jeep.
And I made it. I saw him.
My boy.
Which one's yours?
Oh no, I'm not a dad. I just...
I'm here for my family.
Well, I hope you get
to experience this
for yourself one day.
Imagining all the things
my boy's gonna be
when he grows up.
How do you know?
'Cause he's my son.
Jefferson Jackson,
remember that name.
He's destined for great things.
(SIGHS) I gotta go.
Will you give the nurse
a message for my wife?
You're leaving already?
Yeah, well, if I don't...
I just want her to know
that I saw my son,
and that I couldn't be
more proud and happy.
And tell her I'll be home
as soon as I can.
Can you do that?
Wait!
I gotta tell you something.
(CHUCKLES)
Congratulations.
Thanks. Appreciate that.
(SIGHS)
(BABIES CRYING)
We're here.
Where is here?
Come, I'll show you.
Again, where is here?
We need a safe harbor
to keep your younger selves.
I've been waiting.
It's good to see you.
It is good to see you,
too, Mother.
MARY: Don't forget to take
your boots off
before you come back in!
Ah!
Oi!
Out you go.
So, this is where Rip plans on
keeping our baby selves.
If all goes according to plan,
we'll only be here
for a few minutes,
then, presumably,
never remember.
When's the last time
anything went according to plan?
I don't think
there was a last time.
I really would sit up
if I were you.
She'll kill you
if she catches you slouching.
Don't be fooled by appearances.
That woman is as tough as nails.
Funny how you never mentioned
having a mother.
Adoptive mother.
Now, can I interest any of you
in some more tea?
- Thank you.
- So, Michael...
- "Michael"?
- That's me. My birth name.
The Time Masters insist on
the adoption of new identities
for their protection.
How do you know so much
about the Time Masters?
I work for them.
MARY: Oh, don't worry.
My true loyalty
is to my children.
Thank you. The Time Masters
fill their ranks with children.
Orphans pulled from throughout
the course of history.
MARY: When Michael arrived
at the refuge,
he had nothing
but the clothes on his back.
There's a reason
it's called "the refuge."
And a reason that it exists
in a secret location in history.
The Time Masters will never
think to look for you here.
Thank you for your assistance.
Look, I know I make
a gorgeous baby,
but I should warn you,
you've got your hands full
with me.
MARY: I assure you.
You're not the first tough case
to arrive at my door.
Hmm.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Where'd you find the match?
You can always find one.
RORY: Beautiful, isn't it?
Not as beautiful
as a whole house
going up in flames, though.
- It was an accident.
- Sure, it was.
You don't know me.
You think I wanted
to kill my family?
I think you fell in love
with your dad's lighter fluid.
I think you fell in love with
the flames dancing around.
But then you realized
you couldn't control them,
and you ran,
without waking your family.
The only thing
you were concerned about
was your own skin.
Now, while I'm gone, there
better not be any accidents.
If there is,
I'm gonna come looking for you.
I'm gonna kill you.
You sound just like my dad.
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
CHILD 1: Wait for me!
(LAUGHING AND CHATTERING)
I couldn't quite bring myself
to leave this place just yet.
I've made you
something for your travels.
Some mince pies
for your friends.
My friends.
Yeah, the people
whose relationships
with their friends and family
I've put at risk
to save my family.
You think you've been selfish?
- I do, yes.
- What a load of old codswallop.
I've always known that you
were brought to me
for a reason, Michael.
That you were ready
for great things.
But you won't accomplish
anything by wallowing.
So, for goodness sake,
pull yourself out of it
and get the job done.
What about you?
I've put you in terrible danger.
You don't honestly think
I'd let you go away
with my best serving dish
if I didn't think
I'd see you again, do you?
I can manage quite happily
with a house full of
10-year-old Time Masters.
So, I think I can perfectly deal
with the adult version.
- Go on.
- Yes, yes, yes. Thank you.
- PROFESSOR STEIN: Jefferson?
- (SNIFFLES)
Hey. What's up, man? You good?
Please, we share
a psychic connection.
I know how you're feeling
and I'm sorry.
I thought affording you time
with your father
would lift your spirits.
Yeah. I...
I thought so, too.
I just...
I should have said something.
I should have told him about
what happens to him
in Mogadishu.
- I could have saved him.
- You don't know that.
It's highly unlikely
you could have said
anything that would have
changed his fate.
My whole life,
everything good I ever did,
every report card,
every touchdown,
in the back of my mind,
I always wondered,
"What would my dad
think about this?"
- Hey.
I was just on my way
to the bridge.
No, wait, wait, please.
I didn't mean to be a lurker,
but I heard you
and Sara talking.
And I get it.
You thought I was dying.
You told me
what I needed to hear.
And it worked.
So, if you need a reason,
a way to let me down easy--
Ray, no, I want to be with you.
It's just that
I know that we can't last.
Says who?
Me.
The woman I met in 1871
was me.
And she warned me
that it would end in heartbreak
if I ever tried to be
with someone--
Other than Carter.
(SNIFFLES) God, this is just
too complicated.
No, it isn't, really.
I mean, if I make you happy,
if being with me
makes you happy,
then you can be happy.
Or you can choose to listen to
some former version of yourself
who believes in curses.
When you decide, let me know.
RIP: Everyone, please report
to the main deck immediately.
What's going on?
Gideon has intercepted
a transchronal beacon.
Gideon, show them.
PILGRIM: This message
is for Rip Hunter.
I'm going to make this
very quick and very simple.
If I can't find you...
I can find those you love.
Anna.
Dad!
All of them will suffer and die
because of you.
PILGRIM: Your family, friends,
anyone you've ever cared about.
Unless you surrender
your younger selves to me.
So she can erase you all
from history.
If it's of any comfort,
you won't feel a thing.
As for your loved ones,
I cannot promise the same thing.
Gideon, I take it that
the Pilgrim's transmission
included a carrier frequency
through which
she can be contacted.
GIDEON: Yes, Captain.
Hail her, please.
What are you planning to do?
- PILGRIM: Captain Hunter--
- Look, I'm gonna make this easy.
I already have.
The lives of your team's
nearest and dearest
for their younger selves.
And I'm gonna counter
that demand
with an offer of my own.
I will surrender myself
if you spare the lives of
my crew and their loved ones.
PILGRIM: A noble gesture.
But worthless.
My directive is to eliminate
your entire team.
Not just you.
Yes, well,
I'm not talking about me now.
I'm offering you me in the past.
Rip Hunter before he became
a Time Master.
Eliminate him,
and this team
will never have been.
If this is some kind of trick--
It's no trick.
Enough people
have died at my expense.
Gideon will send you
the location.
And, Mr. Snart,
your wish is about to come true.
You're going to meet
my younger self.
- JAX: What is this place?
- RIP: Neutral ground.
It's a defunct
Time Masters outpost.
I thought we were supposed to be
picking up your younger self.
He's being brought
to us, actually.
That little boy
was at the refuge.
He's you.
You got my message.
I don't approve
of what you're planning.
Not that
it ever stopped you before.
Your younger selves
are all still safe and sound.
Thank you.
- You're a naughty one.
- That's right.
I think it's probably about time
that you left.
Give her hell.
Where's my dad?
Onboard my ship,
along with the rest.
PILGRIM: All in perfect condition.
As long as your captain honors
his end of our bargain.
You'd murder a child?
I'd murder as many children
as is necessary
to accomplish my mission.
Do you know what this will do
to the timeline?
Killing a Time Master?
In case you've forgotten, I am
sanctioned by the Time Masters
to do what my former colleague
Chronos, here, failed to do.
Enough of that!
Let's get down to business.
Where's the rest of your group?
They're around.
I'll be taking the boy.
Before you do that,
we don't believe for a second
their loved ones
are on your ship.
A show of good faith, then.
A prisoner exchange.
Send the boy,
and I'll send the father.
PILGRIM: Once I have the future
Captain Hunter
in my possession,
then I'll release the rest.
- What the hell's going on?
- You don't need to understand.
- (GRUNTS)
- Only walk.
You are going to be
absolutely fine. I promise.
As soon as my dad's in
the clear, let's light this up.
Remember, we wait for Ray's cue.
ATOM: I'm in position.
YOUNG RIP: You wanted to see me?
Have I done
something wrong, miss?
Not yet.
RIP: Now!
Fool me once...
(GRUNTS)
(LOADING)
Now, Kendra!
I was willing to proceed
in good faith.
Now, you'll watch
those closest to you die.
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
Thought you could snuff me out?
You don't know me at all, miss.
(SCREAMING)
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
Hey, are you okay?
Not really.
Yeah, let me explain.
- You poor boy.
- (GRUNTS)
I'll take you. You all right?
That's you?
Yeah.
I was a cut-purse
from the age of five.
I starved more than I ate.
I knew what I'd do
if she tried to harm me.
Lucky for us
you didn't forget your roots.
Believe me, Mr. Snart,
I've tried.
MARY: There you are. (CHUCKLES)
The Pilgrim
may have been dealt with,
but the Omega Protocol
is still in effect.
I'll look after your friends,
don't worry.
I know you will, Mom.
You did the same for me.
Must be strange for you
to see yourself as you were.
Hmm.
Do you remember
the first day you were here?
Yes, I think I tried
to steal your purse.
God, I was a mean
little bastard.
- You were tough.
- I was selfish.
You were surviving.
I was home.
Which is why I know
you'll be back.
Here to give me another
don't-burn-down-the-house
speech?
You think by hurting yourself,
it's gonna make you feel better
about the fire.
You don't know anything
about me, man.
Guess again, kid.
- I'm you.
- YOUNG RORY: What?
RORY: That's right.
You're too young to understand.
But understand this.
It wasn't your fault.
I let that flame
get out of control.
YOUNG RORY: Like you said.
I ran out, without waking
anybody, like you said.
I was just so afraid.
You were just a kid.
I spent my whole life
blaming you.
Hating you.
For something
you didn't mean to do.
Why are you telling me this?
You can't change
the things you did.
But you can change
what you become.
Don't be like me.
Be better.
Clarissa, it's me, Martin.
I'm sorry, you look so familiar,
but I just can't place you.
Spaceship.
- What next? Martians?
- No.
- Actually, amnesia pill.
- Oh, yeah. (SCOFFS)
This will just wipe
your short-term memory.
Of course, it's up to you,
but we don't wanna mess
with time too much.
Hmmm.
I always knew that you'd end up
caring for people.
Protecting people.
Well, I learned it from my dad.
Proud of you, honey.
Is everything all right?
My wife doesn't seem
to remember me.
Because until we return your
younger selves to the timeline,
you, none of you,
will have ever existed.
But we will return you.
When we left 2016,
I just assumed I would return
to the exact moment I left.
That Clarissa wouldn't even know
I was gone.
So, I didn't say goodbye.
And, now, I fear
I will never have that chance.
You will.
Look, I've told you before
that I am not going
to risk your marriage
in order to save my wife.
I promise you, Martin.
Thank you.
Not even gonna pretend
to understand any of this.
(CHUCKLES) Yes. Pretty crazy.
Huh?
(SIGHS)
That was you.
In the hospital,
on the day you were born.
And, earlier, on fire.
Amazing.
- Where'd you learn those moves?
- (LAUGHS)
From my dad.
You know, the day you were born,
in the hospital,
I've never been so scared.
I mean, even in combat.
But now, I know,
for you to be
the man I see standing here,
I must do something right.
I can't wait to be there
to watch it happen.
(EXHALES)
Dad, listen.
On September 26th,
you're gonna be deployed
along the K4 circle.
Keep your head on the swivel
for an IED.
You know this because...
You're from the future.
Please, promise me
you'll be careful.
(SNIFFLES)
I'll be back soon, okay?
- Hey.
- KENDRA: Hey.
Hope you don't mind,
my fiancée...
My other fiancée is
- in our quarters, resting.
- Yeah, no, that's...
That's fine.
- Hey, I'm sorry--
- No, really, it's fine.
No, I mean,
being at death's door
is not the right time
to pop the question.
Look, when you proposed,
I was so afraid of losing you.
And then facing the Pilgrim,
I realized, there is never going
to be a right time for this.
So, we should stop waiting
for the right time.
Uh...
I don't understand.
I wanna marry you, Ray.
I mean it.
How's your sister?
She's a tough kid.
How's your dad?
Sleeping off that amnesia pill
from Rip.
Hey.
I might have just stopped my dad
from getting killed
at Mogadishu.
I just thought
I should tell you in case
there's a time paradox,
or whatever.
Well, as I've been saying,
Mr. Jackson,
- time wants to happen.
- Yeah, I know, but...
- I had to try.
- And perhaps,
what time wants is to see
you and your father
back together.
(GRUNTS)
Just pulled younger me's head
from out of his ass.
- I'm not sure it stuck.
- Me either.
But I saw younger Rip change,
and I thought
why not give it a shot.
Surprised you didn't advise
your teenage self
to not get on a certain boat.
Yeah, me, too.
(EXCLAIMING) I thought
we were on a clock here.
Indeed, we are. Um...
Time, the history from which
your younger selves were removed
is beginning to set.
RIP: As is evidenced by
the change in Clarissa's memory.
Okay, so how long do we have
till these changes stick?
No one knows.
RIP: Which is why
we need to move swiftly
to locate Vandal Savage
if any of your lives
are to be restored to normal.
So how long will it take
to determine a new location
for Savage?
Longer than we have.
Fortunately,
there is one place in time
that we know Savage to be.
You said he conquered
the world in 2166.
PROFESSOR STEIN: You also said
it was too dangerous
to strike at Savage
while he was at the height
of his powers.
That, it is.
But with your younger selves
removed from history,
we have, quite literally,
run out of time.
English - SDH