How will we be remembered?
Will it be
for saving the world twice?
Nope, we're the team who broke time.
That's right. History
has been torn to shreds.
Which means, it's up to us
to put it back together again
piece by piece,
fixing these so-called anachronisms
before we get torn to shreds.
So please, don't call us heroes.
We're Legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
I told you, I was leaving
to create an organization
to replace the Time Masters.
- Fifteen minutes ago.
- For you.
Forming the Time Bureau
has been the work
of the last five years of my life.
They are undependable,
unpredictable, dangerous.
Yeah.
My decision to leave
had nothing to do with you.
I could feel myself losing control.
The animal was in charge, not me.
Tell me what we're facing here.
That information is need-to-know.
Welcome back, Kuasa.
This is A.R.G.U.S.
Anti-meta-human curfew is in effect.
Citizens, please stay in your homes.
HQ, this is Transport X-17.
En route to facility.
Copy, X-17.
Standing by to receive prisoner.
What the hell?
Hey!
Code 99.
We have a code 99!
So there's this theory
that the phrase
"bring home the bacon"
started in a town in Old England.
Bacon was awarded to any man
who can truthfully say
he and his wife had not argued
that past year.
The same cannot be said
of you and Ms. Jiwe, however.
No, because I'm eating bacon.
- But since you asked...
- I didn't.
Hey, it is a little awkward.
I mean, I am a little resentful...
Please, if you need
to discuss this with someone,
I would suggest Amaya.
Yeah, I know.
We should talk things out, but...
Amaya.
Acute arachnoid somnambulism.
Now, this really is fascinating.
Oh, my God.
She's having a dream she's a spider.
We gotta wake her up
before she crawls into the engine.
- Amaya!
- You're not supposed
to wake a sleepwalker,
especially when they're stuck
to the ceiling.
Why not? Amaya!
That's why.
Are you okay?
I... I was, I was having a nightmare.
And in the process,
summoned the ashe of a spider.
- Astonishing!
- No, Martin. It isn't.
What if I summoned a rhino
and I crashed through the hull
of the ship?
Or a lion and I mauled someone?
Well, if the victim was Mr. Rory,
I can imagine...
It's gonna be okay.
We're gonna figure out what's going
on with you and your totem.
What do you think
I've been trying to do
for the past six months?
In my experience, there is no problem
that cannot be solved
by the rigorous application
of science.
It's a mystical totem, Martin.
I believe we should start
in the med bay.
Please, please.
Come with me. Come with me.
Code 99.
This is Agent Gary Green.
Seattle, Washington, 2042.
I just witnessed a female meta
of unknown origin.
She killed everyone.
Hey. What's going on?
We intercepted a distress call
from one of Rip's Time Bureau agents.
Why? Actually, forget it.
- I don't care.
- It's the dweeby one, Gary.
Still don't care.
Yeah, I gotta go
with Mick on this one.
Why would we help those ass clowns?
I mean, that's not our job.
Hopefully, that little time
dweeb learns his lesson.
Agreed, but last time I checked,
we help people who are in trouble.
I don't.
Something feels off about this place.
Yeah. Like, where is everybody?
Martial law. It's a police state.
- How do you know?
- I can smell pigs.
He's right.
All the cars on the street
are military.
More pigs! Get down! Get down!
That's A.R.G.U.S., covert
paramilitary organization.
Yeah, but it seems they've
forgotten how to be covert.
The signal we intercepted
came from over there.
Should be here somewhere.
Gary!
- Gary!
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
She's gonna kill me.
The chick from your distress call?
Agent Sharpe.
She hates you guys.
Well, feeling's mutual.
Look, you said there was
a female meta killing everyone.
- What's going on?
- No, this is classified
Time Bureau business.
Open your mouth and say some words.
Guess you're gonna have to decide
who you're more afraid of,
Agent Sharpe or Mick here.
The Bureau got a ping
on some unregulated time travel.
But when I got here, the person
I was supposed to arrest...
Was a meta-human
who had no problem murdering people?
Her powers let her control water.
A human squirt gun. Big deal.
No, you guys really have no idea
how dangerous this woman is.
Dweeb's right.
That chick's dangerous.
She just blew through
those pigs like it was nothing.
Actually, I fought someone
with water powers like this
a few years ago.
It was not very pleasant.
Well, why would
a time-traveling meta-human
come to 2042 to kill
a bunch of A.R.G.U.S. agents?
She didn't.
She came here to kill their prisoner.
Well, it looks like she struck out.
Something tells me our assassin
doesn't give up so easily.
- You got a plan, Captain?
- Why?
We saved Four-eyes.
Mission accomplished.
And Four-Eyes' mission
was to prevent the anachronism.
You mean stop the water witch
before she kills whoever
was in the back of that truck?
Gideon, scan A.R.G.U.S.' logs.
See if you can ID the prisoner.
I can do better than that, Captain.
I can project the prisoner's
most likely destination.
Even better.
Zari Tomaz?
Come with us if you want to live.
Yeah, I used that one once.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Yeah, I don't know who you are
or what you're doing
but you're gonna lead A.R.G.U.S.
right here.
No, don't worry.
We can protect you.
Who's gonna protect you?
This is A.R.G.U.S.
Sara Lance, Nathaniel Heywood,
Raymond Palmer, and Mick Rory,
you are listed
in the Meta-human Registry
as missing.
You are hereby under arrest
for violating
the Anti-Meta-human Act.
Anti-Meta-human?
Yeah, meta-humans
have been illegal since 2021.
- Didn't you guys get the memo?
- No.
Well, nice to meet you. I'm out.
Wait, your life is still in danger!
- Remain where you are.
- Ditto. Bye.
Detainment units have been notified.
Hate to destroy
futuristic technology, but...
Stand down!
Go! Go!
You are surrounded.
Under the Meta-human Act of 2021,
you are under arrest.
On the ground!
Hands behind your head!
Final warning!
Do as they say.
You gotta be kidding me.
That's an order.
Don't suppose
I get to call my lawyer.
- What?
- I wanted to shoot someone.
All right, let's get back
to the Waverider,
see if we can get a line on Tomaz.
Why?
Pretty sure she just told us
to screw off.
Doesn't change the fact
that there's a rogue time traveler
trying to kill her.
- I can see why.
- Let's go.
There's nothing to worry about.
Gideon can't find anything
medically wrong with you.
I told you, Martin.
My problem is mystical.
It's not scientific.
Believe me, mysticism
is merely science
that hasn't been understood yet.
Hey! Did you figure out
what's wrong with her?
I'm sitting right here, Nathaniel.
I suggest we consider
a new battery of tests...
- I don't think there's...
- To check on an overactive
hippocampus,
latent chromosomal imbalance,
not to mention temporal dysplasia.
I'll ask Jax to adjust
Gideon's diagnostic algorithm.
There's no algorithm
for what's wrong with me.
It's my totem.
It's the legacy of my ancestors.
Great, so let's go talk
to your ancestors.
We're on a time ship.
This totem means
I protect my village,
not mess with its history.
What is her problem?
Side effect of temporal dysplasia,
I suspect.
Hey, how you feeling?
Like I just understood
what you meant
by the term "mansplaining".
I take it from Nathaniel's
premature return.
You didn't have much luck
with Ms. Tomaz.
Well, that was interesting.
Turns out Zari's a bit of a,
not very nice person.
Apparently, it's illegal
to be a meta-human in 2042.
You know what I don't get? A.R.G.U.S.
- In 2016, they weren't...
- Idiots.
Well, I was gonna say
they weren't trying to control
the city with killer drones, but...
Any authoritarian organization
always goes bad, always.
Which means
it's only a matter of time
before Rip and his Time Bureau
turn into the Time Gestapo.
In case you've forgotten,
the Time Bureau only exists
to clean up your time mess.
Which now includes
an at-large time assassin
and a fugitive hacker!
Is that your way of thanking us
for rescuing you?
Gideon, do we have
a location on Zari yet?
Negative, Captain.
I'm afraid Ms. Tomaz
has stepped up her efforts
to remain undetected.
Damn, I can see why.
Look at this rap sheet.
Burglary, larceny,
grand larceny, identity theft,
trespassing, digital trespassing,
meta-human smuggling, conspiracy...
Impressive.
Multiple religious infractions.
- What do you mean?
- Zari's Muslim.
And apparently religion
is illegal in 2042.
Rory, if you had this much heat
on you, where would you go?
My bar.
What have they done to my bar?
Too much, Ray, too much.
What? I look like
I just robbed a bank.
Or a costume store.
There she is.
You run, scream,
or sic one of those drones on us,
I'll light you up.
You got that, missy?
Are you guys stalking me?
Not me, but for some reason,
my boss has a bee in her bonnet
about protecting you
from that water bitch.
Not you, sweetheart.
Yeah, I can take care of myself.
Is that right?
Is that why you're in this bar?
Looking to hire muscle?
Look, you can trust us, okay?
We're the good guys.
Oh, don't be fooled by our disguises.
Good guy!
It's her.
Let's get out of here. Come on.
Oh, a pool party.
Cute tricks.
Get her to the ship!
You guys have a ship?
Is it a big ship?
How about a diversion, Rory?
Who wants to fight?
Go!
Okay, this is almost amazing.
What do you mean, "almost"?
Don't worry. You'll be safe here.
Who's the woman that's after you?
No idea.
Any idea of why someone
would want to kill you?
Yeah, I can think
of quite a few, actually.
Look, if we're gonna help you,
you need to start being
more straightforward.
What is she doing here?
Water woman was trying to kill her,
so we're, protecting her.
No, this is technology
you are not allowed to see.
Civilians are not allowed
to know about time travel.
Wait, you guys are time travelers?
Nice one, Gary.
Okay, that's on me.
But still, our job is to prevent
the anachronism.
Which means, capturing
the assassin, not the target.
I can't believe...
You guys are time-traveling
superheroes?
Yeah, we've actually
saved the world, twice.
Not that we're counting.
Really? You saved the world.
- Twice!
- Then why does it still suck?
Just for the record...
dealing with that messed-up
police state of yours?
That's on our to-do list, so...
But after we capture the person
trying to kill you.
And we need your help to do it.
Oh, I get it.
Since you have no way
of tracking this water psycho,
you plan to use me as bait, right?
Right.
Okay, I'll help you,
on one condition.
You help me break my brother
out of the A.R.G.U.S. facility
where they're holding him.
Prison break.
- I'm in.
- No, no.
No, no, no, no, no,
they're not helping you,
because they're still helping me.
Guys, this mission has gone
way off-the-rails as it is.
Zari's brother is not the priority.
If you really want my help,
then that's my price.
Guess we're breaking
into an A.R.G.U.S. prison.
Okay, so I've been
doing some research.
Turns out there's a root
from your region of Zambesi
that's known for its spiritual
healing properties.
- The Lyoga root?
- That's the one.
It's a powerful hallucinogen.
Yes, and people use it
to go on vision quests.
Oh, so you admit that my problem
might be mystical in nature?
Well, if you say it's mystical,
then it's mystical.
Anyways, I was having
a chat with Gideon.
And it turns out, our favorite
talking supercomputer
is really great at synthesizing
pretty much anything.
No.
Please tell me you didn't.
We re-created the Lyoga root
extract right here on the ship.
I mean, Gideon did most of the work.
I pushed, like, seven buttons.
Nate, this is a really bad idea.
A single miscalculation
could be lethal.
Which is why I did a quality
control test on myself first.
What?
- You already took it?
- Yeah.
I just had to make sure it was safe.
So far, pretty good.
The tongue, getting a little numb.
But, you should drink it now
so we peak at the same time, please.
Okay.
Right, we should be
sitting down for this.
The room should be dark.
Gideon?
Okay.
So what do we do now?
Believe it or not,
this is my first vision quest.
Do we chant?
- No.
We stop talking.
Close your eyes and just breathe.
Breathing in.
Breathing out. Breathing in again...
Nate.
Sorry.
- Rory, don't.
- Just a little.
Maybe later.
Which way?
My brother's in the east wing annex.
The blueprints Gideon downloaded
said the control panel's this way.
You guys open the cell.
Let's go talk to your brother.
Now.
Hey! How's it going?
There's no maintenance
scheduled here till tomorrow.
Really? We got a call that,
something was broken.
- Yeah? What?
- Your nose.
Says here my brother's
being held in cell 4587.
You guys got a location
on the other security console?
Yep, all clear.
All right, which cell do
we need to open?
It's room 4587.
Okay, I'm on it.
Wait a minute.
You mean everybody
locked up in here is a meta?
Yeah. Looks like A.R.G.U.S.
is conducting experiments on them.
Guys, open the cell, now.
I can do a lot better than that.
What are you doing?
What does it look like?
Hurry! This way. Come on.
Let's go!
I thought you were just
gonna open her brother's cell.
You didn't see
what we saw on the monitors.
A.R.G.U.S. is experimenting
on these prisoners.
Hey, where's Zari?
What the hell is going on?
I thought this was just
about grabbing your brother.
Yeah, about that? Sorry.
- Sorry for what?
- There is no brother.
There is no prison break.
It's a heist.
You used us.
We bent over backwards to help you.
As lies go,
this was a pretty white one.
This used to be my brother's.
Now it's mine.
Oh, my God.
- Nate?
- Not supposed to talk.
Nate, look.
Not supposed
to open your eyes either.
Oh! I think I'm starting to peak.
Amaya, you okay?
Oh, boy.
Where's Zari?
Go! Go!
Oh, man!
Knock yourself out.
About time.
Nate, buddy?
We need you to bring
the Waverider to us, now.
Stay.
Okay...
Yeah, I can...
I can do that.
My face! My face!
This room is huge!
Pulling up the anchor!
Raising the sails!
Full speed ahead!
That's enough, Zari!
You're not going anywhere without us.
Is that right?
That's a cool getaway.
Don't worry. I'll follow her.
Where's Pretty?
Nate, how are we doing
with that rescue?
I'm giving her all she's got,
Captain!
The ship can't take
much more of this!
Actually, Dr. Heywood,
the engines are still idling.
Then why does it feel like
my face is peeling off?
Yo, are you high or something, man?
You have no idea.
Gideon, take command of the ship.
I'll arrange a rendezvous point.
Let's get out of here.
Where's Stein anyway?
I believe he's checking on Ms. Giwe.
She seems to be experiencing
a, well, unusual side effect.
And as for Mr. Heywood, he's in...
We got bigger fish to fry.
Ray, you have eyes on Zari?
Yep, I'm on her tail, not literally.
I'm following her posterior
from a respectable distance.
I can't believe
she played us like that.
The whole sob story
about her brother,
just an excuse to get her hands
on some magical necklace.
When we find that chick,
I am gonna kill her.
I like her.
When you say kill her,
what you really mean is...
Kill her. And slowly.
No, no, no, no, no, no,
we have to restore the timeline.
Which means, getting Ms. Tomaz
back to the A.R.G.U.S. black site
where she belongs
and tracking down your time assassin.
Oh, and cleaning up
the prison debacle!
Don't worry, Gary. We got this.
Jeez Louise, this disaster
keeps getting bigger
and bigger and bigger.
What are you doing?
Well, I hate to say it,
but Gary's right.
We gotta put Zari back in the bottle.
Look, she's not exactly
my favorite person either right now.
But...
you didn't see how it was back there.
The way A.R.G.U.S.
was treating those people?
She played us, Jax.
We're lucky that it's not us
in that prison instead.
She had a water witch travel
through time to hunt her down.
I mean, did Zari really act
any differently
than you would've in that situation?
I'm just saying, do we really
want to be the people
who put her back in a meta prison?
Is that who we are?
I can see through my hand.
Are you on drugs?
Your face.
I want your face.
Okay, buddy.
Not a good idea.
- Gideon!
- As I was trying to tell you,
Mr. Heywood is under the influence
of a hallucinogenic compound.
To help Amaya with her totem problem.
Okay? It's totally safe.
People in her village do it
all the...
It's safe, I think.
As for Ms. Giwe,
Professor Stein helped her
to the medical bay.
Get him to his quarters now!
Give him some water
and maybe his fidget spinner.
I told you, bro.
Let's go. Come on now.
Cobra!
All right, all right. Just...
Amaya.
What is this place?
You are in the world between worlds.
Who are you?
I am your blood.
I am all who have come before you.
I can feel the fear inside you.
It is a burden that weighs
heavy on your heart.
My totem, I can feel it
growing stronger.
I fear that I'm losing
control over it.
You can't stop the
forces of nature...
no more than you can stop
a charging stallion.
You must learn to run beside it.
But why is it getting stronger?
The totem's strength grows
when the threats that you must
face become more powerful.
But you cannot face
this new threat alone.
You must find the girl.
She needs your protection.
Do not fail this new totem-bearer.
Do not resist your power.
Trust in it.
Zari.
Look, I don't want to fight,
but we gotta go.
We can't stay here. It's not safe.
I don't understand.
They're not here.
Nobody's here.
They were supposed to meet me here.
This was supposed to be our Jannah.
Jannah?
It means "sanctuary" in Arabic.
My brother had powers
because he wielded this.
He fought against A.R.G.U.S.'
injustices, so he was hunted.
We all were.
The night we were leaving,
A.R.G.U.S. raided our house.
Killed my brother...
and took the only part
that's left of him.
And that's how you got caught,
trying to steal it the first time?
Yeah, I couldn't let
A.R.G.U.S. keep it.
With my brother gone,
I needed its power
to help me protect my parents, but...
- Maybe they got away.
- Where?
Can't you see
there's nowhere left to go?
This was our last hope.
Zari, I'm sorry about everything
that's happened to your family,
but we really have to...
Sara, the water woman
just showed up,
and she looks pretty grumpy.
Like "kill anyone that gets
in her way" grumpy.
Send us your coordinates.
We're on our way.
What's going on now?
Unidentified ship
approaching, Captain.
- A.R.G.U.S.?
- No, Captain.
It's the Time Bureau.
I don't understand.
How does the Time Bureau
know where we were?
Gary!
I'm sorry, I know you said
you could handle it.
But you guys can't handle anything!
I should go.
Sara Lance.
I see that you and your team
have managed
to get yourselves
in over your heads, again.
- Chill, lady.
- We were just trying to help.
By starting a prison riot
at the A.R.G.U.S. facility?
When are you going
to learn that the Legends
should not be interfering
with Bureau affairs?
Maybe when you stop
screwing things up.
Perhaps it's best not
to antagonize someone
on such a large time ship.
I don't care what Gary says.
We don't need backup.
Sara! I need backup!
Sara!
Where are you guys?
Interesting, sounds like
one of your team members
has stumbled sideways
into finding our assassin.
Yes, that's rather our style.
Just give us his coordinates.
We would be happy
to save him for you.
You know these guys
are just gonna hand Zari back
to those A.R.G.U.S. bastards,
who are gonna do
God knows what to her.
And if you don't comply,
we would also be happy
to scatter you all into space.
Did you just shoot at us?
I am not screwing around.
Give us those coordinates.
The next one will not
be a warning, Ms. Lance.
I knew we shouldn't have trusted
that time dweeb.
Just give her what she wants.
Fine.
I'll uplink their coordinates
to you now.
You gotta be kidding me.
- Ready?
- Ready to receive.
- They're gone.
- I can see that, Gary.
Track their signature
and follow them.
That was easier
than I thought it'd be.
Is this what you're looking for?
So you do have it.
But are you capable of using it?
What are you offering for the totem?
I can give you
what you really want, Zari.
What you want more
than that little trinket.
I can give you revenge.
Revenge on A.R.G.U.S.
They targeted you and your family.
Turned you all
into fugitives and criminals.
They should die.
In exchange for your help,
I give you this?
You can't control this power.
It wasn't meant for you.
I can free you from this burden
and help you get justice
for your family.
Maybe picking a fight
with the Time Bureau
wasn't the best strategy.
Yep, well, they fired on us first.
And if they continue to do so,
we will sustain critical damage
in less than five minutes.
Four minutes.
Well?
I... I guess I have to say...
Sorry.
Come on, Ray. She's too much for us.
- We gotta move.
- And she tastes terrible!
- What's happening?
- Time pukes are shooting at us.
At least you seem to be
feeling better, Ms. Ziwe.
Yeah, Nathaniel's plan,
while ill-advised, was beneficial.
Quiet! The marshmallows are talking.
Get to the jump ship!
Get a fix on Ray's position
while Stein and I keep
our Time Bureau friends busy.
Not you, space ranger. Sit!
I really love this show.
Gideon, status.
The jump ship has been deployed.
I don't believe our pursuers noticed.
Oh, dear!
I'm afraid our rear deflectors
have been completely lost, Captain.
Sara, please.
We still have enough time to arrange
a détente with the Time Bureau.
A compromise, if you will.
Sorry, Martin. I don't compromise.
Would you please help me
talk some sense into her?
I like broccoli!
Gideon, divert everything
to our forward shields.
You guys might want to hold on.
Gideon, hail the Time Bureau.
- What are you doing?
- Being true to who we are.
My team doesn't roll over
on their own.
Zari Tomaz is not one of your own.
Either way, we're not gonna let you,
A.R.G.U.S., or anyone else
put her behind bars for who she is.
So you'd rather kill
your team and mine?
Collision in ten seconds, Captain.
Last chance, Ms. Lance!
Sara, this is madness!
Change your course!
I'm good.
Impact in three, two, one.
Are we dead?
Did... did we die?
The Time Bureau vessel jumped away.
Gideon, make sure
they're not following us.
Professor, you all right?
Nothing that a cup of tea won't fix.
One cup of Lyoga root tea
for the professor coming up,
'cause you're my best friend!
What made you change your mind?
Thought about what my brother
would want me to do.
Weren't your friends supposed
to be coming to rescue us?
Good point.
You had your chance.
I was willing to offer you
a compromise.
But now I have to kill you.
I'm afraid we can't let you do that!
If anyone's gonna kill Haircut,
it's me, lady.
- Thanks, Mick.
- Pleasure.
You think you could stop me?
Trust in it.
What are you doing?
Trusting it.
How?
Stay down.
I can do this all day.
I would kill you.
But I'd just be killing myself.
All right, Gideon.
How are we doing?
Our time jump from Jannah
remained undetected, Captain.
I think we can safely say
our Time Bureau problem is...
Oh, bollocks.
- Perhaps I spoke too soon.
- What is it?
Incoming transmission
from Agent Sharpe.
Put her on.
Oh. Hey, Ava.
How was your day?
You do realize that
that little stunt of yours
could've destroyed us both.
You tried to kill us first.
No, I tried to warn you first.
But you don't take warnings, do you?
Now you're starting to get it.
Well, this isn't a warning.
It's a promise.
If I ever track you down again,
you and your band of idiots
will be exiled to the dawn of time.
Whatever leniency
Hunter gave you is over.
What a bitch.
You took the words right out
of my mouth, Gideon.
Plot a course to 2042.
Hey, how do you feel?
Yeah, much better.
And you?
I thought the hangover
I got drinking with P.T. Barnum
was bad, oof.
Hey, I wanted to thank you.
I've gotten a handle
on my totem again.
That's great.
You can at least try not
to sound so disappointed.
It's cool.
I just thought you were staying
on the ship
because your totem was out of whack,
and now that it's back in whack...
I can't go.
This whole experience
has made me realize
that my fate is entwined
with someone else's.
Zari's.
Well...
Sara said we're dropping her
back off in 2042.
We could've dropped you off anywhere.
Why this dump?
With Jannah gone, this is home.
Oh. Well, you got a lot
of heat on you.
I can handle heat.
Thanks.
Wait!
It's not safe for you here.
There's no reason to suggest
that sorceress won't return for you.
Well, it's not like
I have any other options.
That amulet, it's not an amulet.
It's a totem, like mine.
We're bound together somehow...
in a way that I have yet
to understand.
Come with us.
That's all nice and weird, but...
Totems, they guide us
in strange ways.
What if yours guided you to us?
What would you rather do?
Hide from A.R.G.U.S. your whole life
or do something really stupid,
like time travel?
I'm not a superhero.
Neither am I.
Good.
You can't pedal forever,
you little nerd!
Come on! Come on!
Where are you, nerd?
I think he went down this way!
Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
He went down here! Down here!
Hello?
Hi, what's your name?
Mine's Ray Palmer.