My name is Damien Darhk.
- (DARHK GRUNTS)
- In 2016
I was murdered by the Green Arrow.
But I was removed from the timeline
31 years before my death
by a speedster from the future
named Eobard Thawne.
Together with Malcolm Merlyn, the former
head of the League of Assassins,
the three of us are going to locate
the Spear of Destiny,
a mystical object
which can rewrite reality itself.
With the Spear in our possession,
we will change our past and our future
and the world as you know it.
RIP: Previously, on
Legends of Tomorrow...
GIDEON: A deep scan reveals that.
Captain Hunter's neural architecture
has been reprogrammed
with a new identity.
The Longinus Medallion.
(ALL GRUNTING)
WHITE CANARY: Rip!
EOBARD: I know that you're one of
the protectors of the Spear of Destiny.
And I know that you know
where the other pieces are hidden.
You're gonna torture me, aren't you?
I'm not going to torture you.
They are.
(SIRENS WAILING)
REPORTER: (ON TV) Damien Darhk, the man
behind tonight's siege of Star City,
was killed by the masked vigilante
known as the Green Arrow.
Amateur cell phone video
captured his final moments,
putting an end to the chaos
that has gripped the city.
(SIGHS)
(DARHK CHUCKLES)
This is the great Malcolm Merlyn?
I am unimpressed.
EOBARD: Well, he's fallen on hard times.
But this man used to be Ra's al Ghul.
We haven't met. I'm Eobard Thawne.
I'm from the future.
What the hell is going on here?
Excellent question. Here's another.
Do you believe in second chances?
I just watched you die.
Yeah, I hear 2016's not my best year,
but I plan on fixing that.
EOBARD: But the question for you, Malcolm,
is do you wish to see your fortunes
similarly reversed?
By time travel?
No. No.
Something much better.
(DOOR OPENS)
- Well?
- No luck so far.
It's not that
Captain Hunter's uncooperative,
it's that he's not fully in possession
of his marbles.
So he won't tell us where
the rest of the Spear of Destiny is.
Eh, It's more like "can't."
Which wouldn't be such a problem
if you two idiots hadn't lost
the Longinus Medallion.
(STAMMERS) I seem to remember
you being there as well.
Until you weren't.
(EXCLAIMS)
I hate when he does that.
If you have something
to say to me, Malcolm,
I suggest you keep it to yourself.
I'm sorry.
Am I supposed to be afraid of you?
Oh, I would be.
Considering I can kill you
before you even knew I was doing it.
Ah, yes.
But then you wouldn't get what you want.
You brought me and Damien
into your little quest for a reason.
Without the Medallion,
Hunter is our only way
to get the rest of the Spear.
You need me to get it out of him.
We already tried torture.
MALCOLM: I'm not talking about torture.
I'm talking about hypnosis.
Regression therapy.
(GRUNTS)
Hunter's mind is locked away.
I've got the key.
(PANTING)
Is this some technique you picked up
with the League of Assassins?
The League didn't call me
"the Magician" for nothing.
- EOBARD: Well, be quick about it.
- (GROANS)
Speedsters aren't known
for their patience.
What's to keep Hunter's crew
from finding the rest of the Spear
before Merlyn finishes
unscrambling Hunter's brain?
The workings of the Medallion
are lost to history.
Trying to get it to reveal
its secrets will prove difficult.
Plus, we have
an additional advantage over them.
Enlighten me.
They're idiots.
- You're all idiots.
- AMAYA: Excuse me?
Pot, meet kettle.
Yeah, Mick, given your glass house,
you shouldn't throw stones.
Mixing metaphors isn't going
to solve anything.
How about instead of bickering,
we figure out our next move
against the speedster and his allies?
"Legion of Doom" has a sexier ring to it.
I'm not calling them that.
And we need to figure out
a way to rescue Rip.
All you got to do is trade the amulet
or the Medallion for the Englishman.
It's really simple.
The only thing is
I don't know how it works.
Mmm, you're an idiot.
You want to put an artifact
that can rewrite reality
into the hands of the enemy
- and we're the idiots?
- Mmm-hmm.
Our priority has to be
identifying this speedster.
Of course you'd say that.
I mean, he is the one
that killed your boyfriend, so...
He's at the center of this
and you can't defeat an enemy
that you don't know.
Look, Amaya's right.
And, I hate to say it, but so is Mick.
BOTH: I'm not an idiot.
Not about being idiots.
About using the Medallion as leverage.
But first, we need to figure out
how it works.
Well, in my defense,
it's a mystical object.
It doesn't come
with a set of instructions.
Maybe that's been the problem.
Approaching it from a mystical vantage
instead of leaning into our strengths
which are...
- Technological.
- Exactly.
And, as it happens,
I have a colleague in Central City
whose knowledge
might prove to be advantageous.
Gideon, set a course
for Central City, 2017.
Jax, stick with Martin.
And let's work on
putting a name to our speedster.
(DOOR OPENING)
Aw! Here comes a man
who looks like he just struck out.
Don't get smug with me, Damien.
I may not have all my prior resources,
but at least I'm not dead.
Look, I couldn't get Hunter to remember
because his memories
aren't buried or locked away.
They're gone.
It's like his old self didn't exist.
Are you sure about that?
Do you think you can do any better?
You are welcome to try.
We already tried torture.
You know what I love about torture?
I'm not sure if we have enough time
for me to list all the reasons,
but mainly it's because
there's always another gear to find.
(SIGHS)
This is what I get for relying
on a washout and a dead man.
I don't like that guy.
- Hmm. You know, I'll be honest.
- (KNIFE SWISHES)
Which, I have to admit,
I don't have much practice in.
I don't like this situation.
Not one bit.
For one thing,
Mr. Thawne has this habit
of treating me like a henchman.
Do you know what all henchmen
have in common, Captain Hunter?
No thoughts on this one?
The thing that all henchmen have in common
is that they all end up dead.
A fate that I am fastidiously
trying to avoid.
Maybe it's that I just hate taking orders
or being threatened.
You don't like being threatened, do you?
Hmm?
What's that? Oh, sorry.
(CHUCKLES)
- Oh, God. No.
- Yeah, neither do I.
Which is why I need your cooperation
to end Mr. Thawne's tedious threats.
Look, I...
I don't know anything. I swear...
Shh!
I can't take your word for it.
But don't worry.
I'll start you off with an easy question.
Right eye or left eye?
Please. Please. Don't. I'll do anything!
I'll tell you anything you want to know
even if I don't know.
- Please don't!
- Shh.
Second question,
when was the last time
you had any dental work done?
What? No. No, God.
(RIP SCREAMING)
It may not be in the best condition,
but then again,
Captain Hunter is British.
You pulled out his tooth.
As torture goes,
isn't that kind of bush league?
Look closer.
Thank you, but no.
There's some markings on here
like a bar code.
Account information.
From a security deposit box
in Switzerland.
Who puts that kind of information
on a tooth?
A Time Master.
That's no ordinary security box.
My thinking exactly.
Now, it's possible the box could contain
his son's birth certificate and the like.
But given the exotic nature of the care
that's been taken here,
- I would have to assume...
- It's the rest of the Spear.
- When was it last accessed?
- January, 2025.
(WATCH BEEPING)
Oh, you got somewhere to go?
Funny. Just like clockwork.
Take the Time Sphere back to 2025
and secure the rest of the Spear.
The next one of you who screws up
will lose more than just a tooth.
(MALCOLM GROANS)
Well, I'd hate to see you
lose another hand, Malcolm.
(DARHK LAUGHS)
JAX: Seriously, Grey?
I know you didn't bring me to 2017
just so we could get lattes
and Frappuccinos, man.
Of course not.
It's just my colleague merely frequents
this establishment at this hour.
(GROANS)
Sorry, Jefferson.
You should go back to the Waverider.
I can handle things from here.
What the hell is going on with you, man?
- LILY: Dad?
- (GASPS)
I didn't know you were coming to town.
"Dad"?
- Well, I wanted to surprise you.
- LILY: Oh.
Wait, your colleague is your daughter?
Lily, this is my friend Jefferson.
Jefferson, this is my daughter.
Nice to meet you.
Hi.
- Shall we sit down?
- Yeah.
- Over here.
- This is so weird.
Because I didn't think
I'd get the chance to meet you.
Like, ever, but, uh, here we are.
Uh, I was explaining to Jefferson
how you might be able
to assist us with the, um...
Research project.
Sort of like Indiana Jones.
- Yeah, sort of.
- Mmm-hmm.
You brought it to a coffee shop?
- Oh, well, for one thing,
- (DEVICE BEEPING)
it's throwing off
low levels of ionic radiation.
Is that an ionic transmographer?
I've never seen one smaller than a house.
Yeah, I had an idea
for hyperminiaturization
when I was in Tahiti.
I don't vacation well.
You know, I'm thinking
a shortwave ionic pulse might...
(DEVICE WHIRS)
(PROFESSOR STEIN EXCLAIMS)
Hey.
Perhaps we should, uh,
take our little research project
somewhere a bit more private.
(LILY GASPS)
A temporal navigation vessel. L...
I absolutely cannot believe it.
Urn, hello, who are you?
Oh, hi, I'm Lily. I'm Martin's daughter.
We didn't know Martin had a daughter.
Yeah, you told me you didn't have kids.
Well, I like to keep
my private life private.
There's private and there's lying.
Sara, did you know about this?
Oh, I know all about this.
(HUMS)
What are you doing?
I'm trying to make up my mind.
I mean, Eobard has such a delicious
selection of killing devices.
We can't just storm into the bank
and demand to see the deposit box.
We absolutely can.
We're former members
of the League of Assassins.
This operation requires subtlety,
not a bloodbath.
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm not up
on current events,
but might this squeamishness
that I'm witnessing
be the cause of your downfall?
Hunter is an asset,
one that we can use
to gain access to our objective.
To not use him is foolish.
Oh. Well, in that case
I would have to defer
to your superior expertise in foolishness.
But if your plan goes south,
it's not our speedster friend
you need to worry about.
One thing I hate more
than taking orders from him
is being threatened by you.
Luckily, Damien,
I don't find you threatening.
Hmm.
What's the big deal?
The professor didn't have a kid
and now he does.
- Mazel tov.
- Thank you.
The big deal is Lily is a Time Aberration,
which was all well and good
until you plucked her out of 2017
and showed her a Timeship,
which could cause more Aberrations.
- Hey, what are you looking at me for?
- Because you were with him.
I, quite simply, missed my daughter.
If Lily's presence on the Waverider
posed any temporal issues,
I'm sure Gideon would have detected them.
Plus, Grey said Lily could
hook the Medallion up with Gideon so...
Wait, she wants to try networking
the ancient amulet
with an advanced Al system?
(CHUCKLES)
I'm totally helping.
Fine. Then I would appreciate it if you...
If none of you would reveal to her
that she's an Aberration.
Why are you looking at me?
So where are we
on identifying the speedster?
I think the technical term is "nowhere".
All the speedsters that Flash faced
are either dead or his friends.
Or people he thought were his friends,
and are now dead.
SARA: Okay, we will figure this out.
And in the meantime,
you and Lily keep working with the amulet
to figure out where
the rest of the Spear is.
Who's to say he won't kill us anyway,
even after we've gotten
his precious Spear?
Oh, forget it. Why am I asking you?
I don't know, man. I don't know anything.
I don't even know why you're getting me
to wear this... This... This...
This monkey suit.
- And my mouth is so sore...
- Quit whining.
Fact of the matter
is we have something in common, Rip.
- My name is Phil.
- Whatever.
We are both dealing
with unstable individuals.
And that is not something I enjoy.
Hey, this is not exactly
a walk in the park for me either.
Which is why
you will do exactly as I say.
Then maybe, just maybe,
you'll make it through this alive.
Cool. All right. Um...
What... What is it you want me to...
To do?
Tell me, Phil,
have you ever been to Switzerland?
MALCOLM: Put this in your ear.
- What is it'?
- Communication device.
Really? It's so small.
Do it or I'll shove it down your throat.
MALCOLM: It will allow us to monitor you.
This is very simple.
You go to the bank associate
and you tell them
you want to access security box 4587.
4587, right. What do I do then?
Bring the contents of said box back to us.
If you don't, you'll be killed.
- Really?
- What?
I'm motivating him.
In and out.
Take no longer than five minutes.
You will be fine.
I'll be fine.
I'll be fine. Okay.
This would be easier
if we just killed everybody.
(SIGHS)
Hi, how are you?
I'd like box 4587, please.
Sure. Have a seat.
MALCOLM: What do you think
is going on with him?
It's simple. His mind is pudding.
Not Hunter. Thawne.
It's strange how he never stays
in one place for very long.
Perhaps that's why they refer to them
as "speedsters".
What, you think he left us behind
in 1967, Los Angeles,
because he had a more pressing engagement?
What about what he said to us earlier?
That he wanted to kill one of us?
No. That he didn't know
why he was relying on us.
I mean, fair question.
Why does a time-traveling speedster
need to rely on anyone?
Thawne's hiding something.
Wouldn't you like to know what it is?
(CHUCKLES)
Thawne said we knew each other
back in 2016.
Do I really become so stupid
that you think
these mind tricks will work on me?
I am not trying...
A trio such as ours
turning one against each other
for your own benefit
is not only obvious but cliché.
Thawne does not treat us as equals to him.
And until he does,
neither of us is getting what he wants.
All right, let's go over this again.
- I've already been over it, Sara.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Again and again.
- And again.
We're obviously dealing with a new player.
Whoever this speedster is,
it's someone you and your friends
haven't encountered before.
Which means this speedster
is from the future which makes sense
because speedsters can time travel.
Then what would the speedster
need the Spear of Destiny for?
He could just go back
and change history himself.
But not reality.
That's why he needs the Spear.
Question is,
what is this speedster trying to change?
Or fix.
That's the question.
He knows what we want to do
with the Spear of Destiny,
but he's being very coy about his plans.
(DOOR BEEPING)
Here you are, Mr. Hunter.
Please lean towards the panel,
if you would.
- Excuse me?
- A retinal scan.
- Rectal scanner?
- What?
MALCOLM: (OVER COMMS)
It's an eye scan.
Part of the bank's security.
(CHUCKLES) You know,
this whole situation sucks,
but man, I love being in the future.
- What?
Retinal scan. Right.
(BEEPING)
(RIP SIGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
Why, uh... Why is it not working?
Voice ID is next.
You need to speak your access code.
"Access code"?
Oh, boy.
Yes, sir. The one you set
when you opened your account.
Uh...
- MALCOLM: Get out of there now.
- Yeah.
No. Don't.
MALCOLM: Go. Move.
DARHK: Don't.
- This was your plan.
- Which I am trying to execute.
And failing spectacularly per usual.
We can't just let them call security.
I'm calling security.
Great idea, security... No...
Security is awesome.
- (GUN FIRES)
- (EXCLAIMS)
(GRUNTS)
You weren't planning on going rogue
on us now, were you, Rip?
I have told you, my name is Phil!
All right, Phil.
It was lovely knowing you.
Don't! We still need him.
He's useless to us.
- Hey, I can be more useful.
- (ALARM BLARING)
Damn it. Security's gonna be
on top of us at any moment.
Might I suggest you kill them instead?
Try and run and I will find you
and feed you your testicles.
Okay.
(VOICE TREMBLING)
Oh, my God.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Reinforcements are on their way.
Let's get the hell out of here.
(SIRENS WAILING)
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
LILY: Okay. That should just about do it.
RAY: Now we just have to
activate the Medallion,
- and see if Gideon can access its data.
- Okay.
So, what are we waiting for?
Nothing.
It's just... If we've underestimated
the size of the artifact's data-stream...
We'll fry the ship's CPU
and we'll all spend the rest of our lives
stranded in the Temporal Zone?
(GIDEON CLEARS THROAT)
The ship's CPU has a name.
Sorry, Gideon.
Can we at least talk about this
before you connect...
(ENERGY SURGES)
(CIRCUITS SCRAMBLING)
(GIDEON SHUTS DOWN)
Gideon?
You still there?
- Oh, my God, we killed her.
- Oh...
Artificial intelligences cannot,
by definition, be killed, Dr. Palmer.
- Yes, I know.
- It's pretty remarkable
considering we just mainlined
1.2 zettabytes directly into her brain.
Yeah.
I'm processing the Medallion's
temporal output as we speak.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
- Ah! Nice work, Doctor.
- Doctor.
You don't happen to have
any champagne on this ship, do you?
Ah, 1998 Blanc de Noirs.
- Mmm.
- But I like beer.
Gets me drunk.
To Lily.
- To Gideon.
- Hmm.
Wow. That tastes real!
It's completely synthetic.
The food fabricator can make anything.
Except American cheese,
which is pretty much
synthetic to begin with.
Beluga caviar?
Fake food never tasted so good.
Fake food for a fake person.
(CHUCKLES)
What did you say?
(STAMMERS) He didn't say anything.
Everyone has been looking at me weird
ever since I came on board the ship.
What are you not telling me?
(RORY CLEARS THROAT)
Cat's out of the bag, Haircut.
You may as well tell her.
Tell me what?
Sweetheart, I don't wanna
rain on your parade, but you're a, uh...
How would the professor put it?
An abrasion. No, that's not it. Um...
Asphyxiation.
Aberration. You're a Time Aberration.
You're a Time Aberration.
Ray?
What is a Time Aberration?
Um...
I think maybe you should talk to your dad.
(MALCOLM SIGHS)
Perhaps we could all just talk about
- what went wrong.
- Shh.
Oh, I know what went wrong.
I listened to him.
If you'd have listened to me,
we would have walked out of that bank
instead of being chased out.
Either way, we came out empty-handed.
I seem to remember Eobard mentioning
how he was going to punish your failure.
If anyone's a failure, it's you.
You were the one who learned
about Hunter's secret account,
yet seemed not to know about a passcode.
Sloppy, Damien.
No wonder they passed you over for Ra's.
You see this is where he reminds me
that he was Ra's al Ghul.
Poor Malcolm, always living in the past.
This is when I remind you
about your future.
Aw...
That's right. I've been there.
I've seen how pathetic you are.
In this future that you're from,
do I at least have two hands?
Either way, I intend to change my future,
but look at you now. You're pathetic.
I don't even know why Thawne recruited you
in the first place.
We could argue all night, Damien,
but I don't want to bore our guest here
with your impotent insults
and recriminations.
What are you suggesting?
You recall how we resolve disputes
within the League?
Mmm-hmm.
Now...
I suggest you choose a blade
that matches that sharp tongue of yours.
(WHISPERS) Excuse me for a second.
Gladly.
PROFESSOR STEIN:
You did it, my darling!
You created an interface
between a mystical relic
from the first century
and a 22nd-century supercomputer.
Only a Stein could be so brilliant.
What is a Time Aberration?
- I'm sorry, what?
- You heard me, Dad.
An Aberration is an unnatural alteration
of history as a result of time travel.
Dad?
Am I...
Am I an Aberration?
That word could never describe who you are
or how much you mean to me.
- So it's true.
- Please let me explain.
That's why you were acting so weird
when you visited Central City
the first time.
The reason you were treating me
like a stranger...
Was because you didn't even exist
the last time I boarded this ship
and left 2016.
But now you do exist.
And that's all that matters.
(SOBS) How could this be happening?
Well, it's really quite simple.
You see, I interacted
with my younger self back in 1987,
who then interacted
with your mother's former self,
and when two former selves
love each other...
Okay, Dad, we've already had
the birds-and-bees talk.
I was 10.
Or did we?
That's a very interesting point.
I mean, who's to say
which of our realities is real
and which one is aberrant?
It's really a matter of perspective.
Actually, it's quite fascinating...
This is not fascinating, Dad!
This is a nightmare.
Lily, I'm so sorry.
This is not how I wanted you to find out.
No. No, I get it.
You didn't want kids
when you first came on board this Timeship.
But now you have me.
(BLADES CLANKING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
You just reminded me of something.
Which is?
How much I've missed this.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(CLATTERING)
(MALCOLM YELLS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Okay, stop, stop! Time-out! Time-out!
Can't you see
that this is what your boss wants?
For his underlings
to be at one another's throats?
Like, literally?
He is not our boss.
Did he call us "underlings"?
Oh, I'm sorry. Uh...
"Henchmen"?
Try again.
Wait, wait, wait. What if he's right?
You actually care what this
pudding-brained hippie has to say?
It's just like the movie,
The Good, the Bad and the Ugly.
Three bad guys, no one knows who to trust,
so they all end up
screwing each other over.
It's an interesting theory.
- Which one are we?
- The point is
that neither of you are Clint Eastwood,
and so neither of you
end up going home with the gold.
We're not after the gold.
I know, I know. I know what you're after.
You, you want to change your past.
And you, you want to change your future.
And the fast guy is the only one
who can make those two things happen.
I told you.
Thawne doesn't treat us as equals.
Even the hippie knows it.
And he also knows
that the only way to stop Thawne
from screwing us over
is for us to work together.
Two former members
of the League of Assassins
versus a speedster.
I am liking those odds.
- Dude. What is going on with you?
- What do you mean?
And don't call me "dude".
I've gotten used
to sharing a brain with you,
but this, whatever this is,
this is something new.
Just enjoying a cup of Earl Grey.
Is that whiskey?
Of course it's not whiskey!
It's brandy.
What do you take me for, a sailor?
Okay, let's start this over. Hmm?
(PROFESSOR STEIN SIGHS)
Come on.
(SIGHS)
Fine.
I made a terrible mistake.
I should never have brought Lily
on board this ship.
(SIGHS) She found out.
She knows she is an Aberration.
Sir Rory spilled the beans, as predicted.
So what you gonna do?
What can I do?
Just tell her how you feel.
She knows how I feel.
It goes without saying.
Yeah, for us it does.
We have a psychic connection, but for her?
She just hears whatever comes out
of that big brain of yours.
Just tell her you love her.
That's what dads do.
Clearly, you never met my father.
You know, the...
The reason Clarissa and I chose
not to have children
the first time around was because...
I feared that history would repeat itself,
that I would be
the kind of father that he was.
We're Legends, Grey.
Changing history is what we do.
Why would a speedster
need to change reality?
(SIGHS) How many times
are you gonna ask that question?
Until we have an answer.
She's right.
Speedsters can time travel,
so what's stopping him
from changing history
even without the Spear?
Unless he doesn't exist.
Okay, so what, he's a ghost?
What if he's a Temporal Aberration
just like...
Excuse me,
have any of you have seen my daughter?
- One second, Professor.
- Sorry, this is quite urgent.
Look, what if instead of creating a person
like you did with Lily,
our mystery speedster
erased himself from history?
- Why would he want to do that?
- I don't know.
But it would explain why we don't have
any evidence of his existence.
Okay, so we just need to ID
someone who doesn't exist.
Eobard Thawne.
- Um, is... Is he okay?
- I'm fine.
Eobard Thawne is a name.
The name of a speedster who...
Who what?
PROFESSOR STEIN: Thawne was erased
from existence when his progenitor,
Eddie Thawne, committed suicide
in order to stop him.
Which would explain why the Time Masters
didn't have a file on him.
But if Thawne doesn't exist then how...
He was protected from his ancestor's death
because he was a member
of the Speed Force.
- (SIGHS) It's a little complicated.
- A little.
(GUNS FIRING)
(BODIES THUDDING)
Oh, and for the record,
this is how I wanted
to approach things in the first place.
Only because you enjoy
killing a lot of people.
DARHK: As if you don't.
(BEEPS)
All right,
that's pretty impressive, Malcolm,
but how did you get Hunter's passcode?
It's not Hunter's.
It's the bank manager's
security override code.
- It only cost him three fingers.
- Ah. (CHUCKLES)
(STRAINING)
Yes.
Ow!
(GASPS)
Going somewhere?
No.
Yes. What do you expect me to do?
Your partners just left me here
all tied up.
Where are they?
They told me not to tell you.
The bank, they're... They're at the bank.
Look, you could help yourself
to whatever is in that safe deposit box.
But please, please just let me go, man.
Let me go.
(WHIMPERS)
Does this look like a Spear to you?
It most certainly does not.
It's a mnemonic archive.
I'm sorry.
Are we supposed to know what that means?
Since it won't be invented
for a century, no.
This device is designed to store memories.
Rip Hunter's, I'd assume.
Guys, I think I just figured it out,
why a seemingly invincible speedster
would need to take on partners.
By all means, Dr. Heywood,
please enlighten us.
Okay, what if Thawne
isn't just chasing us?
What if he's running from something?
But running from what?
- Time.
- And time takes time to harden.
And if Thawne ceased to exist the moment
his great-great whatever killed himself,
then maybe he has to keep moving
in order for his own nonexistence
not to catch up with him.
(SOFTLY) Boom.
That doesn't even begin to make
any kind of sense.
I don't know. It could work.
Professor, what do you think?
Per the scientific method,
there's only one way to prove it.
You'd have to trap Thawne in one place
and then see what happens.
(DOOR LOCKS)
What do you think you're doing?
Renegotiating the terms
of our partnership.
And it is going to be a partnership.
We need a bit more of a guarantee
that you're going to uphold
your end of our bargain.
- (LAUGHING)
- (DARHK CHUCKLES SARCASTICALLY)
I'll guarantee you one thing.
If you don't open that door,
- I'll kill you.
Yes, but I'm the only one
who knows the code to open it.
Perhaps you can persuade
our friend to cooperate.
Me? No. I'd rather see how this plays out.
(EXHALES) Oh...
It seems you two have formed an alliance.
There's just one problem.
That you're the only one who can
give us what we want. Yes, we know.
You're always so quick to remind us
how much we need you, Eobard.
But, clearly, you need us.
You could have gotten in this vault
all by yourself. Why didn't you?
(WATCH BEEPING)
And for that matter,
why would a man who can travel
through time always be in such a hurry?
We don't have time for this.
Oh, I've got all the time in the world.
(WATCH BEEPS)
Okay! Okay. You two have made your point.
I need you as much
as you need me, all right?
But if you do not open that door,
he is going to kill us!
He is coming for me!
- Who's coming for you?
- It's not a who.
It's a... It's a... A what.
- A thing.
- What thing?
Can you be a little more specific?
My ancestor kills himself
in an effort to erase my very existence.
Well, you look pretty spry despite it.
The Flash pulled me from the timeline.
He held me captive for months.
And when I finally got loose,
I found myself pursued by something.
I thought it was a time wraith,
the monsters that hunt speedsters
who mess with time.
But whatever is hunting me
is far worse than a time wraith.
(SHRIEKING)
It can sense the Speed Force.
And it's trying to kill me.
Interesting. So that's why
you keep running out on us.
Huh. So you're kind of like a shark
who'll die if you stay in one place.
We are all going to die if you don't...
(DISTANT SHRIEK)
It's too late.
It's here.
Well, the good news is
you two finally got what you wanted,
you managed to balance
our partnership.
We're now all equally dead.
Oh, I wouldn't worry about that.
This isn't the first scary speedster
that we had to put in its place.
MALCOLM: We're gonna get you
out of this bank vault, Eobard.
But on one condition.
You stop treating us like lackeys.
(SIGHS)
You think you can stop that? Good luck.
Was that a yes?
- Yes.
- Great. Let's go to work.
All right, so you say this thing
is attracted to the Speed Force?
What if you don't use it?
What are you suggesting?
That you stop running.
(SHRIEKING)
(BREATH SHUDDERING)
It knows I'm here.
MALCOLM: (OVER COMMS) Good.
'Cause we've only got one shot at this.
(SNARLS)
(ROARS)
Remember, as long as you stay still,
he can't sense you.
(GROWLING)
(SNIFFS)
(SHRIEKS)
Easy, Eobard.
(ROARS)
(WHISPERING) Easy.
(SNARLING)
(ROARING)
It won't stay trapped for long.
We have to go.
"We?"
- We.
- (BANGING FROM VAULT)
Partners.
Better.
LILY: Gideon, can you please
take the ship back to Central City?
GIDEON: If your goal is to return to 2017,
I'm afraid your father has instructed me
not to permit you to leave the ship.
Well, considering he never wanted
to be my father,
that should draw his parental dictates
into question, wouldn't it?
You share my fondness for erudition.
(CHUCKLES)
You truly are my daughter.
Well, I am sorry about that.
No, I'm... I'm the one who's sorry.
(SCOFFS) For what?
It's not your fault I'm a mistake.
I've made many mistakes in my life, Lily,
but you most certainly
are not one of them.
The apology that I owe you
is for not telling you
about the unique circumstances
of your conception.
You didn't want me to know
that you didn't want me.
No.
- You're right, I...
- (LILY SIGHS)
I didn't want children.
But if there's one thing my travels
aboard the Waverider have taught me,
it's that time often doesn't provide us
with what we want.
But it's quite adept
at giving us what we need.
And I needed you in my life.
In ways that I could
never even dare to imagine.
(LILY CHUCKLES)
I just don't want there to be
any more secrets between us.
Well, in that spirit,
I suppose I should tell you
that I am one-half of a nuclear-powered
superhero called Firestorm.
(LAUGHS)
That is so not funny, Dad.
(CHUCKLES)
Anyway, as fun as this was,
I probably should be getting home.
You're sure you can't stay?
I... I would, I just...
I'm working on a series
of synthetic proteins
that are not going to
fold themselves, so...
So, then I guess this is goodbye.
(SIGHS)
Good luck folding those proteins.
- Good luck rescuing your friend Rip.
- Hmm.
Bye, Dad.
DARHK: Feel no pressure to tell us
what all this techno-crap is about.
- I'm sure we can figure it out ourselves.
- (CHUCKLES)
This, uh, techno-crap,
as you so eloquently put it,
is Captain Hunter's memories.
Including the locations
of the other pieces of the Spear, I hope.
That is my working assumption, yes.
All we have to do now is upload
his memories to his cerebral cortex.
And that's not happening now because...
Well, we'd hardly be doing
Captain Hunter any favors
if we just restored the memories
without taking the liberty
to redress some of his shortcomings.
What, like stopping him biting his nails?
(LAUGHS)
Not exactly.
(MAN SHOUTING ORDERS)
Can I help you with something, soldier?
Uh, no, General Washington. I'm fine.
You, on the other hand...