Previously on Legends Of Tomorrow...
We can't change history.
If that happens, the Darhks
will be able to free their demon.
Do not let him
take you away from me.
We can save Nora and stop Mallus
from being freed together.
We have the six Totems.
What if the only way to kill Mallus
is to let him out?
We are here to help you
create the anachronism
so we can release Mallus
and then we can kill him.
I'll find you. Go!
No.
Nora.
Mallus is taller than I thought.
My name is Malice, you fools.
- "Malice"?
- Oh!
I knew it. It sounds way cooler.
Hand over the totems,
or I will lay waste to your world.
You want the totems?
Come and get them.
Amaya!
All right, everyone, fall back.
Rip, we're gonna need an evac.
We're in over our heads here.
If my read
of the situation is correct,
what you need is a miracle.
I'm going to buy you some time.
- Wally, create a distraction.
- Got it.
I'm starting to think letting Malice
out of his cage was a bad idea.
The Waverider's time drive
is highly unstable.
- Removing it...
- May very well be the only way
to hold our adversary at bay.
I believe I know
what you're planning.
It is extremely reckless
with a low likelihood of success.
Well, then, seems like I've finally
learned to think like a Legend.
- The odds of survival are 0.00...
- I know.
I will miss you, Gideon.
- Truly.
- No more than I'll miss you, Rip.
Guys, I can't hold him off
much longer.
I'm gonna get her to the MedBay.
Wally, I need you
back on the ship now.
So you're saying you don't fit in?
You're an outcast.
A misfit.
Let's assume.
Sounds to me like you're a Legend.
Together, you are the best crew,
the best team a captain
could ever hope for.
Love changes everything.
Daddy.
Gideon, give me eyes on Rip.
I have a visual, Captain.
What the hell is he doing?
Rip disengaged the time drive,
making it unstable.
When it reaches critical mass,
it will consume Mallus.
And Rip.
Gideon, time jump us out of here.
She can't.
Rip has our time drive.
Yes, but there is another one.
From the Jumpship.
Wally.
Gideon, put me through to Rip.
Rip.
A little busy at the moment, Sara.
Look, you didn't tell us that
you were buying us time with your life.
Listen carefully.
This gambit will not kill Mallus.
It will only delay him long enough
for you to make an escape.
There has to be another way.
No, there isn't.
It's all right, Sara.
I should very much
like to see my wife and son again.
I will miss you, Captain Lance,
you and the rest of the Legends.
My one hope is that
you all live up to that name.
Captain Lance, the time drive
is reaching critical mass.
Can we jump?
Ms. Tomaz has finished
making repairs.
We have 15 seconds.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, Captain.
Gideon, get us out of here.
Ironic, isn't it?
A time demon who's run out of time.
You don't drink.
Yeah, well, we lost Rip.
Okay, somebody's got to say it,
so I'm gonna say it.
This is all our fault.
Apparently I'm not gonna say it,
but, yeah, we let Mallus out.
Well, whose stupid idea
was it to fight him
with some magic necklaces?
It wasn't the totems that failed.
It was us.
Yeah, we might wanna
rethink that whole
"we screw up things
for the better" motto.
Okay, so what's the plan, Captain?
All I know is that Rip gave his life
so that we could take
the totems somewhere
that Mallus can't find them.
So that's what we're gonna do.
And where is that?
The Old West.
Salvation, North Dakota.
It's basically a temporal blind spot.
Wait a sec, we just
unleashed an ancient time demon
who's about to
lay waste to all of history,
and our plan is to hide?
Yes, it is.
Gideon, plot a course.
Well, I hope you're here to make
good on your promise and kill me,
which would work out
for both of us, be a real win-win.
Mercy killing is not my style.
Even if it was,
you don't deserve my mercy.
You deserve to live out
the rest of your days
knowing that you
destroyed your own daughter.
What are you doing here?
Uh, it's my lab.
Don't do anything stupid.
Captain, we've arrived
in the Wild West.
Thank you, Gideon. Have everyone
meet me in the fabrication room.
Ray?
Nothing stupid.
Is she right? Are you
really planning something stupid?
Maybe.
Probably. Most likely.
But it could fix this whole thing.
And get Nora back.
Yo, this is tight.
I know everyone's dead,
I know time is broken,
but can we just
take a second to acknowledge this?
You know, as much as
I enjoy this getup,
and actually really do,
Mallus is still out there.
And we'll deal with him, but first,
we need to get our heads on straight.
How long is that gonna take?
- Depends.
- On what?
How strong the whiskey is.
All right, I think it's working.
I am on the edges of a plan.
Great. Let's hear it.
So we know that the six totems are
the only thing that can stop Mallus.
They weren't much
use to us last time.
"Us" being the keyword.
You and Amaya were born
to wield the totems,
- and the rest of us are just...
- Losers.
That's why Rip picked us,
Snart, the Professor,
stupid hawk, flying chicken people.
We're all expendable.
Not that any of these
unwashed hayseeds
look like righteous totem bearers.
Who you calling a hayseed?
Jonah Hex.
You know this guy?
Me and these ruffians go way back.
Wally, Zari, this is Jonah Hex.
Nice hat.
Thank you, ma'am.
Obviously joking.
So, who died and made you sheriff?
- That'd be the old sheriff.
- Oh.
Now, it's my job
to keep the peace around here.
So you can't be causing any trouble.
We are not here to cause trouble.
We're here to avoid it.
This the trouble
you aiming to avoid?
Not exactly.
Looks like Fallus.
- Malice.
- Mallus.
Has brought back our old buddies.
I thought Mallus wasn't supposed
to be able to find us here.
Fools.
Mallus sees all,
knows all.
Then why did he bring back
you germs to do his business?
Because he's probably
still recovering
from that beatdown Rip gave him.
Oh, now do not confuse Mallus' clemency
with weakness, my hearties.
Mallus will spare your lives...
It's actually Malice.
It's actually Mallus.
- No, Malice.
- Mallus!
Guys, it doesn't matter.
If you surrender the six totems.
Yeah, sorry, we only brought two,
and mine's kind of
a family heirloom, so...
Then we have no choice,
but to march our army on your town,
and kill every fool
who has given you shelter.
You leave my town out of this.
You have been warned.
We'll be back to collect the totems,
shall we say, high noon tomorrow?
Toodles.
Well, so much for hiding out.
Guys, if you can hear me, I need you
to put the Waverider on lockdown.
You know I'm only doing this
because of my daughter.
- Wow.
- Well, if this works, we can save her.
Going somewhere, Raymond?
Uh...
Ha! No, no, of course not.
Zari rerouted the time drive, so...
Yeah, Gideon just said
someone re-rerouted it.
- What are you doing?
- Sara wanted the ship on lockdown.
- So...
- So you decided to
load Damien Darhk into the Jumpship?
- Hey, Nate.
- Don't wave.
Have you lost your complete mind?
I know this looks bad.
- Yeah.
- But there's a...
There's a completely
rational explanation.
I'm listening.
Me, too.
- Sorry.
- Oh, my nose!
Ray, what are you doing?
You know, not that I couldn't watch
Pompadour get punched out all day,
but you could've just
told him where we're going.
- Ray, open the door.
- Where are we going?
To right before
Mallus took over Nora.
And I can't tell anybody
because we're not supposed to travel
to events in which we participated.
I will punch through this door!
- And no one on your team trusts me.
- Damn it, Ray.
That goes without saying.
Whoa!
Didn't you hear me over comms?
Ray punched me in the face
with his giant banana hands,
and took off with Damien Darhk.
What are you doing?
Lyoga root?
Do you really think
this is the best time
to go on a psychedelic vision quest?
Who am I kidding?
It's never a bad time to go.
You can't come with me, Nathaniel.
I'm going all the way
back to the beginning.
To meet with my ancestors,
the original totem bearers.
Why?
Sara thinks we're not cut out
to wield the totems.
But I believe the reason we
didn't defeat Mallus the first time
is because we didn't know how.
So you wanna talk
to the original bearers
so they can teach you
the totem user manual.
- I am definitely coming with you.
- No.
It was my decision
to save my village.
I shattered history
and allowed the demon to escape.
It's up to me to
find a way to stop him.
Amaya.
Amaya, look at me.
We decided to save your village.
Now if you're gonna go on
some crazy drug trip,
you better believe
I'm coming with you.
No, Nathaniel.
You're only supposed to
take a sip of that.
Really?
I'll see you on the other side.
Nate?
Nate, open your eyes.
Totem bearers.
What are they doing?
Oh, snap! They got lasers.
Nathaniel.
Wake up.
They beat him
with the Care Bear stare.
No.
They stopped Mallus together.
That is the only way to defeat him.
Together. Together.
What gives, Gideon?
You have a visitor.
Begging your pardons, ma'am.
Captain Lance thought
that you might need a hand.
Yeah, I think she was
just trying to get rid of you.
What in tarnation is that?
It's a computer program I designed
to act as a temporal beacon.
Like a smoke signal.
Sara wants us to
find new totem bearers,
but we're a little short on allies.
Well, the Legends,
they may be an unorthodox lot,
but they got a knack
for making friends.
Like you?
I don't take a shine to most folks.
Me neither.
Hmm.
Well, you're sending out
a smoke signal.
I'll bet you a greenback
you'll get a response.
I'll take that bet.
Sheriff.
Now, you can call me Jonah.
Ma'am.
Hello, this is
Nathaniel Heywood speaking.
And we have a Code 113.
Repeat, a Code 113.
If the code is 113, it's off
to the bridge for you and me.
You memorized Ray's song?
He sings it often enough.
Nathaniel and I shared
a cup of Lyoga root tea
to access the memories
of the original totem bearers.
- Ay.
- Oh, you're still high.
Now the reason the totems
haven't been working for us
is not because we're unworthy.
It's because we've been
using them wrong.
The totems were not
designed to be used individually.
Individually.
- Individually.
- Shut up.
Their elemental powers
combine to create
a perfect being of light
to fight Mallus with.
- Like Voltron.
- "Like Voltron"?
Defender of the Universe.
Right, well,
weren't all of the original
totem bearers actually from Zambesi?
But you all wield them now. I mean,
do you think that was an accident?
Yes, I do.
Mick, the chances of you
running into your father
in Vietnam are next to zero.
And yet, you did.
You came out a better man for it.
Zari, you remember the way your totem
called mine the moment you put it on?
It wanted you to stay with us.
So maybe it wasn't
a coincidence that I joined the team.
No.
That was just another one
of the Englishman's crazy ideas.
- Sara...
- Mmm-hmm.
Please.
We have to try.
- Fine.
- Sick! Yes!
Because no coincidences.
All right, Amaya.
It's your show. How do we
create this magical light being?
All right, everyone, over here.
Make a circle.
Mick, your fire is gonna provide
our champion with its spark.
Zari, use your air to give it breath.
Wally, use water to flow
life's blood through its veins.
- Nate...
- I will use the Earth Totem
to give Voltron flesh.
You gotta stop calling it that.
I will never stop calling it that.
I'm gonna use my spirit
to provide it with a soul.
But, without the final totem,
our champion will be incomplete.
No, it's not happening.
Without the Death Totem, the other
five totems can only imprison Mallus.
We need Death to kill him.
Once and for all.
Don't worry, if you turn
into a witch bitch, I'll kill you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
All right.
Let's do it.
We're good.
Okay, hold hands.
Come on, come on.
Clear your minds,
and focus on your breath.
Imagine a perfect warrior
of justice, mercy and light.
Why does Pretty have
such girly hands?
Damn, this Lyoga root is strong.
Concentrate, Nate, think about
Voltron, Defender of the Universe.
I kinda pictured myself
wielding something cool
like a Lightning Totem.
Am I crazy or is Jonah Hex hot?
Eh, you could do worse than Hex.
Wait, you can hear me?
We can all hear each other.
Even what I said
about Pretty's girly hands?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Please. We need to clear our minds.
- Whoa.
- It's working.
Are we making a baby?
Guys, we have to focus.
You telling us to focus is
making it harder to focus.
All right, look, this is why
we're not worthy of the totems.
Seriously, are we making a baby?
Everyone, just shut up.
Whoa! Whoa!
A Cronen-baby.
Is it supposed to be gooey?
- Mick!
- What?
I'm just putting this slop
out of its misery.
Aw. Voltron.
Right. We need to try again.
No, what we need to do,
is find some people that are
worthy of using these totems.
If that's not an entrance line,
I don't know what is.
I got your message.
We all did.
You guys just can't seem to
keep yourselves
out of trouble, can you?
Whoa! Sounds like I'm really
giving you the business in there.
- Yeah, still hurts.
- Sorry.
Okay, so here's the plan.
We have to knock Nora out.
Gently because I know
she's still your daughter.
And we probably have to
keep her unconscious
until we figure out
a way to de-demonize her.
We better move quickly.
I can't believe you were
ever this young, Nana Baa.
I can't believe you came to my aid.
If you only knew
the odds against that happening.
Odds?
I've been given
a chance to fight alongside
the woman who saved Zambesi.
What was I supposed to say, no?
Am I still high?
Or is the water witch a pal,
Helen of Troy a warrior princess
and Jax is wearing a wedding ring.
I believe you owe me a greenback.
Not to look a gift horse
in the mouth,
but I was hoping for
some real soldiers.
I'm Helen. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, little lady.
Well, it's really good
seeing you again, Jax.
I just wish
it was under better circumstances.
Hey, listen, I'm just glad that
we got Zari's beacon in time.
I mean, going up
against three armies,
y'all are gonna need
all the help you can get.
Hey, what happened to Ray?
You do not wanna know.
Come on, do it now.
Before it's too late. Go!
Oh, man, you really
shouldn't hit your daughter.
You stole my nanite gun?
But that'll kill her.
Sorry, honey.
Nora.
Dad, why?
'Cause I love you.
And I couldn't watch you
become a monster
like me.
You fool.
You thought destroying this vessel
would thwart my return?
I'll gladly take you instead.
I was counting on that.
Goodbye, Nora.
- Go, go.
- No.
Get her out of here.
- Go!
- No!
Dad!
Is it weird that I keep
expecting your granddaughter
to use that thing
to try to drown me again?
This Kuasa never suffered in the war.
She never worked for the Darhks.
She's a good person
who's led a good life.
And she and Mari shared the totem.
It worked.
I can't believe it.
I can.
You told us
the universe was guiding us,
prepping us for this fight.
You listened to your heart,
and it drove you to do a really
good/super-messy thing.
Since when did you
have time to have a baby?
You've only been gone
a couple of months.
Well, I mean,
that's how it is for you guys.
But for me, it's been five years.
Here, look.
Her name's Martina.
And her and her mom
are the light of my life, man.
Well.
Mazel tov!
- Okay. Yeah.
- Cheers.
Okay, stay with me, Nora.
Okay, you're safe.
My dad, my dad.
He traded places with you
as Malice's vessel to save you.
How could you let him do that?
- Why didn't you stop him?
- It's okay.
No, no, Dad!
Just point, and shoot.
Damn, girl.
Damn, where did you
learn to shoot like that?
I learned to fight in Themyscira.
But the Legends were
the ones that inspired me.
They gave me the gift of a new life.
It is an honor to be here
to help you save yours.
Thank you, but we need to be
teaching you to use the totems.
And I'm pretty sure you didn't
learn that in Themyscira.
It's not why we're here, Sara.
We're here to help you,
not replace you.
Look, we've already tried twice,
and we failed miserably.
You still don't see it, do you, Sara?
You guys made Kuasa
and Helen's life better,
and that is just
the tip of the iceberg.
We are all here
to support the Legends,
and what, you're gonna
stand there and tell me
that you aren't the exact people to
wield the totems against Mallus now?
Good speech.
Thank you.
And, uh, it's a good point.
By the way,
I wanted to ask you, did you
mean what you said the last time
we saw each other?
When I told you to run?
No, before that.
Oh!
Oh, you mean,
when I told you I loved you.
Yeah.
What do you think?
I, uh, think that...
Howdy, partners.
What did I miss?
Where's Darhk?
- Um...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Wrong Darhk, wrong Darhk!
No, no, look, look, look. She's...
She's been de-Mallused.
She's no longer a demon.
So we don't have to
fight Mallus anymore?
Uh... Not exactly.
And what about Damien Darhk?
Long story short,
um, he sacrificed himself for Nora,
and now, he's Mallus' vessel. So...
What's new in the Old West?
Well, Caesar, Blackbeard,
and Leif Erikson's crazy sister
are demon pawns.
They gave us an ultimatum
to hand over the totems.
How long do we have?
Oh.
All right.
We're facing an army
of Romans, Vikings and pirates.
But you know what today is?
Today is the day
that we prove that Rip
did not sacrifice his life in vain.
And today
is the day that we prove
that we are not losers.
And today
is the day that we earn
the name Legends.
- Yeah.
All right, all right.
Now, how do we sneak out the back?
Nice of you to bring your fan club.
So...
About that ultimatum.
There is honor
in surrender, Captain Lance.
Our new god may grant you mercy.
Yes, be a good girl,
and hand us over your magic baubles.
I changed my mind.
New terms.
Get out of town,
or get hurt.
Attack!
Can you believe this is
my first time on a horse?
Haven't you ever learned
never to turn your back
on your enemies?
Caesar.
That's a Roman nose.
I should've known.
It was just a tall tale.
You're not the Dread Pirate Jiwe.
No, her name is Amaya Jiwe
of the great tribe of Zambesi.
Toodles.
Dynamite?
Are you sure about this?
No, but it's too late
for second-guessing.
Do it now.
So, we should probably
get back to fighting.
Aye.
Well, next round's on me.
Uh, not to be a buzzkill,
but this doesn't look good.
It's Mallus.
Go, make good your preparations.
The rest of us shall buy you time.
All right, you heard the lady.
Hopefully, this goes
better than last time.
Right. We have to believe
in the totems,
that they've chosen each of us.
Well, if this really
is the end of the world,
then I choose to surround myself
with you guys.
Come on.
Whoa. You feel that?
It's working.
All right, now imagine
a powerful light of pure goodness.
Something's forming.
Can I peek? I'm gonna peek.
- Oh, God.
- "Oh, God"?
- What, "Oh, God"?
- Everyone, focus!
Wait.
Is somebody thinking of...
I'm sorry, you said
think of something pure,
- and I thought...
- No, you didn't.
Again, I said I'm sorry.
Yeah, I can't stop
thinking about him either.
Guys, whatever you've got to...
What in the Sam Hill is going on?
I think this is part of Sara's plan.
I Io-Io-love you.
The Blue God, he has returned.
That is your captain's plan?
Where in the hell
are Sara and the others?
- That is Sara and the others.
- What?
Beebo hungry.
Man, have I missed you guys.
Let the gods of
Olympus make manifest.
Oh! Hey, I know you're
not gonna take that, Beebo.
- Nana Baa.
- Come on, guys, you got this.
Beebo can't breathe.
Don't you dare give up on me, Lance.
Beebo!
- Oh!
- Yeah, come on, that's it.
Kick his ass!
- Yes!
Hmm.
Not even the six can stop me now.
Beebo want cuddles.
No!
Whee!
Guys? Guys!
Are you all right?
Guys, we did it.
The totems united to
create a single, furry lovechild.
Worst orgy ever.
Dad.
Ah. I'm sorry, Nora.
He died a good man.
Damnation.
Now I've just seen about everything.
So wait, what, that's it?
You destroyed the demon?
I'm just glad the ancestors
aren't here to see this.
Yeah, but Rip would be proud.
Yes!
- Whoo!
- We did it, Mick!
Get off me!
The totems came together
when the world needed them most.
Now it's time for them
to find new bearers.
I trust you'll keep them
safe until they do, Nana.
Are you sure you don't
want the power to move earth,
call on the dead?
No, I'm good with just steel.
And I prefer being
a Speedster over a water wizard.
Too old for jewelry.
Nana Baa.
Unhand me, you fiend!
You shall pay dearly for this.
He saved us.
Beebo is our one true god.
The bonny ones
always be the craziest.
Well, I guess we better get to
mind-wiping Mallus' three amigos.
Guys, you think this is crazy,
try having a kid.
Oh, no, thank you.
I bet you're damn good at it.
I'll be seeing you, Ms. Lance.
Well, you can count on it,
Ms. Sharpe.
Come on.
- No.
- Oh.
Seeing as though this is the last time
we see one another.
Something to remember me by.
Oh, your dirty hat.
That's weird.
Sweet.
Hey.
Stop, I need to... I need to
talk to her for, like, two seconds.
Alone, please.
I lied.
It'll be more like 20 seconds.
So, I found something
on the ship that was your dad's.
And I thought maybe you'd
want something to remember him by.
As I spend the rest of my life
rotting in a Time Bureau prison?
That's my father's time stone.
He died to give you a second chance.
Don't waste it.
Are you glad I picked you up
in Zambesi six months ago?
I think the words you used were,
"Just one more mission."
It's better than the line
they used on me.
"Come with us if you wanna live."
I almost die every week on the ship.
But you found a home.
I did.
And as much fun as this has been,
it's time for me to go home.
Amaya, you can't
leave me and Sara, and...
You guys are my family.
Always will be.
But I have another family
waiting for me in the years to come.
And they need me more.
Well, you will always
have a home on the Waverider.
I'm gonna miss you guys.
- Um... Is that Jonah Hex's hat?
- Shut up.
- Is there...
- I can't.
- Do they...
- Stop, please.
- I'll miss that.
- Is this...
Yeah.
I guess this place is all right,
if you like untouched nature,
and beautiful views.
I do love it here.
But there are a lot
of things I'm gonna miss.
Like cheese puffs, and sports bras.
Mmm-hmm.
And you, Nathaniel.
You aren't gonna miss
any of those things.
Because you're not
gonna remember them.
I don't wanna forget.
Because if I do,
I would have lost the only
part of you that I'm allowed to keep.
Goodbye, Amaya.
Don't turn around.
Good call, Mick.
When I said Aruba, I meant me.
Not all of you.
Still, nothing helps
a broken heart like a good tan.
Should've invited Ava.
Oh, we've got plans.
And until then, she's busy fixing
all those pesky anachronisms
we left behind.
Well, that's the thing about
defeating an ancient time demon.
Everything else seems boring.
I'm good with boring.
Hey, idiot. Get out of here.
This is a private beach.
Fancy meeting you lot out here.
Constantine?
Did you really think I was him?
It's me.
Gary, Ray obviously
has been day-drinking.
The wig's too much, right?
No, it's very presidential.
Gary, what do you want?
He's been with me, love.
Oh, I need a word with you sorry lot.
Now...
Whose brilliant idea was it
to let an ancient demon
out of his bloody cage?
Sara's.
Well, you opened a door, love.
And Mallus wasn't
the only thing that got out.