[Nate] Previously on
Legends Of Tomorrow...
You and I dating would be totally weird.
Totally weird.
Hank is running some secret project.
[Hank] A man came to me.
Neron.
He offered me a deal.
Don't tell me
you're having second thoughts.
I have a new partner now. My son.
I don't need you anymore.
[Neron]
I don't need you anymore, either.
[Nate] Dad?
I'm sorry.
I didn't kill Nate's dad.
[Agent Sharpe] Sara, you're asking me
to risk everything.
For some conspiracy theory?
For a bunch of monsters?
- Ava, don't do this.
- I'm done.
[Sara] Ava and I didn'tjust get into
an argument. She asked me to leave.
- [door closes]
- [sobbing]
[knocking at door]
[Sara] Come on, Ava. Open up.
Look, I miss you.
I'm sorry things went down
the way they did,
but please, just open the door.
You know, technically,
- this is still our apartment.
- [lock clicking]
Ava.
[man] Have a safe return.
Nora, what are you doing here?
Uh, I can explain.
I can explain. I didn't kill Hank.
It was a demon.
[Constantine] Yeah, I know.
His name is Neron, and he's wearing
Desmond as a bleeding suit.
- [Sara] Ray.
- [Ray] Sara, great news!
Hank was killed by a demon.
"Great" was not the word
he was looking for.
- Poor Nate.
- Look, Ava's missing.
- Missing?
- I should've checked on her sooner.
It's Neron. He has his sights set on
the Time Bureau and the creatures.
And if he got to Hank,
then ding dongs to donuts, Ava was next.
She is not dead.
Listen, when Neron was at the Bureau,
he and I shared a connection.
If you can take me to Ava's place, I
might be able to know where he took her.
[Constantine] Demons communicate.
He'll know your past,
how susceptible you are.
You're a liability.
She's not a liability, she's a survivor.
Unlike you, she's turned her dark
experiences into a source of strength.
Not an excuse
for alcoholism or chain-smoking.
She also saved your life.
- Sorry. Would you like to add anything?
- No. That about covers it.
I don't care if she's a liability.
If Neron has Ava, then I need all
the magical firepower that we've got.
You two, with me. Woman the ship.
This is from two weeks ago.
[sniffs] Oh.
She's been gone a tick. That's not good.
Yeah. Thanks.
[grunts]
There.
What? What do you see?
He had her... here.
[distorted screaming]
- Ava.
- That doesn't mean she's dead.
Doesn't mean she's alive, either.
[sighs]
I know where she is.
[Gary]
Conspiracies, embezzling, paper trails.
I feel like Julia Roberts
in Erin Brockovich.
We're more Pacific Gas and Electric,
Gary.
Wait. We're the bad guys?
I don't know who we are, Gary.
All right?
We're the guys trying to keep
my dad's cracked-out idea
of Jur-magic Park
from tanking the Time Bureau.
All right? So, anything that has to do
with Heyworld, get rid of it!
How am I gonna explain all this
to Director Sharpe?
Actually, Ava's missing.
[Gary] I knew it.
I knew it! You know,
I had a dream about her
where she was driving
and I was in a car seat in the back.
- We were headed to Schul...
- Gary.
She needs me. [breathing heavily]
I can't... I gotta...
Sara, Constantine and Nora
are looking for her.
Nora?
- Look, she didn't kill Hank.
- Come on, man.
[Ray] Just listen, okay?
Your dad made a deal
with a demon named Neron.
I guess something went wrong,
and the demon killed him.
I'm sorry, buddy.
[sighs deeply]
My dad made a deal with a demon
to open a theme park.
Oh, Ray. I don't know
how much more of this I can take, man.
[cell phone buzzing]
- Is that you?
- No.
If this is my dad's mistress,
I'm gonna jump out a window.
- Hello?
- [Mikey] Yo, Mr. H. It's Mikey T.
Listen. Got a question for you
about the dragon lair.
I could sure use your eyes down here.
[clearing throat]
- [in deep voice] Down where?
- [Mikey] What? Here, at the site.
- Uh, Buckwood Downs?
- [Mikey] Uh, yeah. Where else?
Talk to you later.
Who was it?
[in normal voice]
I don't know. He sounded like a Soprano.
But apparently, my dad started
building this theme park.
[clicks fingers]
The guys who were working with him.
Maybe they know something about
this Neron, and why he killed my dad.
Come on!
I'm Steel, you're The Atom.
There's nothing we cannot handle.
[chuckles]
This one.
Ava!
Hey. Ava!
She's alive!
- What did he do to her?
- He's preparing her.
Neron must be looking for a new vessel.
It only makes sense, going after Ava,
especially if he wants control
over the Time Bureau.
And when a demon possesses someone,
the body has to be willing.
And if it's not,
the demon has to force his way in
by sending the soul to purgatory.
That's where the real fight begins.
How do we save her?
Some souls go up, and some go down.
But if she's been there
as long as she has,
then she's not coming back, Sara.
I'm not giving up on her, John.
You're gonna send me to purgatory
to get her.
If I send you down there with her,
there's nothing that I can do
to protect you.
I'll take my chances.
This isn't something that you can just
fight your way through, love.
John, please!
Fine.
[grunts]
Lay down.
Our purgatory is designed
to drive the soul to breaking point.
It's tailored to drive the captive mad.
Now, where you're going,
that's Ava's personal nightmare.
I've died, lost my soul,
and escaped a demon realm.
I'm pretty sure
I can handle Ava's purgatory.
Well, prepare for the worst, Sara Lance.
[sighs]
[Constantine chanting]
- [clerk] Welcome.
- [gasps]
Do you need a bag?
[indistinct chatter]
I gotta get out of here.
I can't do this anymore.
I just gotta get out of here.
Ava!
[panting] Hey. Hey.
- Oh, thank God!
- Oh, my God!
Sara, is that really you?
It's me. I got you.
What the hell happened? Am I dead?
You were kidnapped by a demon.
And he's trying to take over your body,
so he trapped your soul here,
in your own personal purgatory.
But, Ava, if you check out, you die!
That's kind of on the nose, isn't it?
Wait. Does that mean he got you, too?
No! I'm taking you home.
I've got it! Natari!
I'm gonna regret asking this,
but what's that?
It's your couple's name!
Nat for "Nate,"
and of course, Ari is for you!
You know I'm a superhero, right?
With a flick of my wrist,
I can blast you with my wind powers.
Being honest,
wind powers, just not that scary.
Yeah. You're like a magical hairdryer.
What is this,
Legends Eye for the Straight Guy?
You're straight?
[Mick] Where's Sara?
Uh, she's with Constantine and Nora,
trying to find Ava.
[Gideon] Actually, they've just returned
and Mr. Constantine has called
a team meeting in the lab.
- He can do that?
- No.
[sighs] Let's go, dummies.
[grunts]
Ava's in hell?
She's not in hell.
Her soul is trapped in limbo.
And I am right there with her.
Oh, Gary.
Emotionally. Poor Director Sharpe.
I've sent Sara down there
to try and pull her out.
- I thought that they broke up.
- She still loves her.
- What can we do?
- Sara chose to go in after her, so...
Unless praying is your thing,
then the best thing you can do is wait.
You don't have to worry.
- [Gary panting]
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- He's on it.
- I'll take good care of her.
Them!
- All right. Charlie, you're with me.
- This should be interesting.
Let's go find out what this demon wants,
shall we?
- You're up for it?
- Mmm-hmm.
All right, then. Let's raise some hell.
[indistinct yelling]
Oh, how you doing? Can I help you guys?
Yeah. We're looking for Mr...
- Mr. T.
- Who's asking?
'Cause no one's allowed
on this site, unless...
Hey, I know you.
I'd recognize
that Heywood jawline anywhere.
[chuckles] You must be "& Son."
Are you kidding me?
Hank is always going on about you.
Where is he?
Hank passed.
What? Jeez. I'm sorry to hear that.
- You mind if we take a look around?
- Hey,
- it's all yours now, kid. [scoffs]
- [Nate] Question.
Did my dad ever mention a man
by the name of Neron?
Neron? What is that, Greek?
No, it's demonic.
I mean, Danish, actually.
No. Never heard of the guy.
Actually, to be honest with you,
Hank didn't really tell me a lot.
All he gave me was this.
We're building that right now.
A unicorn rodeo.
Can you imagine? Two unicorns jousting.
[both laughing]
I'd rather not.
Hey. Come here, come here.
This... This is what
I was calling you guys about.
- About the...
- Dragon lair.
Yeah, I know. I drew it.
I drew all of this.
[Mikey]
Great, tell me something. Look at this.
See this here? What is this?
Is this supposed to be real flame
or were you thinking, like, plexi?
'Cause I got a guy that can do fire,
like forget about it.
I can't believe he did it.
[Ray]
I know you and your dad struggled.
And even if you got your wires crossed,
you never stopped trying to connect.
- I just hope my dad knew I loved him.
- He knew.
Look at this place.
You know, I just wish
he would've found a better way
to tell me he loved me.
One that didn't involve
teaming up with a demon
and embezzling money
from the government.
It's a bit much.
Mikey T! Mikey T!
Change of plans.
Tear it down.
The dragon lair?
The whole thing.
[clears throat]
Waiting sucks.
Ooh! Sexting Nate?
- Boundaries, Mona.
- I need vicarious feels.
[sighs] There are more important things
to focus on right now.
And Nate's got a lot going on.
It's not the right time.
[Mona] What are you typing?
- "Hey, what's up?"
- [grunts]
Wait, I don't even know
why I'm talking to you two about it.
You don't even date humans.
Love is love.
[Zari sighs]
Whatever you need, I'm here.
- Why is Gary in your subconscious?
- [sighs]
I may have some Gary issues
that need working out.
Okay, we just need to find the door
that you came in.
Does any of this look familiar?
No. It all looks exactly the same.
Why don't we just try to follow
the arrows back?
Maybe they'll take us to the entrance.
[woman on PA] Reminder, shoppers,
the store will be closing in one hour.
Constantine didn't say
anything about that.
What does it mean?
It means we take shortcuts. Come on.
Hello again, ladies.
- Damn it!
- [Agent Sharpe sighs]
Okay. This way.
No. Or we could just ask Gary.
How do we get to the entrance?
Oh...
We're not really allowed
to give that kind of advice.
Come on.
But the ERGRIK wardrobe might be
just the thing you're looking for.
[Sara] Looks like the wardrobe section.
[Agent Sharpe] No.
[Sara scoffs]
Now what?
I think we're supposed
to put it together.
No sweat.
Here.
Wait, wait, wait.
Step one, insert the dowel.
- Here, babe.
- I got this.
[screws rattling]
[boy] Shut up, man.
- [grunting]
- [whistling "Pop Goes the Weasel"]
[cars crashing]
[man yelling] You kidding me?
What are you, brain-damaged?
- [Neron as Desmond] Papa's home.
- [door closes]
Miss me? I missed you.
We'll be together soon, my pet.
[Charlie as Agent Sharpe]
Not bloody likely!
[Neron] Oh, Nora.
[grunts]
[groaning]
- [gasping for breath]
- [Constantine chanting]
[writing with chalk]
[chanting]
There's nowhere for you to run now,
you bile bladder.
Me, run? You're the one who ran.
All I had to do was say,
"I'm coming for you, Johnny."
And you left 2018 to me.
It's delicious
how easily humans are corrupted.
Especially here in D.C.
So, that's your game?
You inflict fear and anger on humanity?
I merely fan the flames.
People are primed
to give into what they fear most.
You know what, man?
I am gonna send your ass
straight back to hell.
- John, this isn't the plan.
- Nora, we finally get to talk.
Hope you've enjoyed
your little dalliances inside my mind.
[Neron, telepathically]
But it's not a one-way street.
- Is it, Nora?
- [groans]
I knew you were a liability.
We should be off with him.
You're playing right into his hands,
John.
You're the one who can't handle this.
Yes, says Miss Lock-herself-up-because-
she-can't-handle-her-own-demons.
This is me handling mine, all right?
[takes deep breath]
[chanting]
Out!
[laughs]
He's getting to you.
- What, he's getting to me?
- Yeah.
He's inside your head.
What, you don't think
I haven't seen you struggling?
Humanity hasn't exactly been kind
to you, has it, Nora?
You're addicted to this kind of power,
and believe me, it doesn't go away.
No, it doesn't. And it hasn't been easy.
But if I can trust myself,
I don't think it's too much
to ask for you to try, too.
Oh, it's killing you
to look at his face.
I know how hard it is to watch
someone you love become a demon.
Yeah, too bad there aren't any Beebos
around to hug you to death!
[Neron whistling "Pop Goes the Weasel"]
[both sigh]
We can't just keep him locked up
in there, driving us all mad.
Yeah. I think between the two of us,
we can figure something out.
[Sara] Ta-da!
Damn it!
What a surprise, you followed none
of the instructions, and it didn't work.
I am sensing
that this isn't about the dresser.
No, this is what you always do.
Just bulldoze your way through.
- I do not always do this.
- Like lying to me about the Kaupe?
You were defending torturing creatures.
Defending? I wasn't defending it.
I was defending myself.
Of course I don't believe
that we should be intentionally hurting
anything or anyone,
but when we fight, Sara,
I get really scared.
And I just go to my corner.
Look, it's just fight or flight.
That couldn't be any more human.
I just really need to know
that you're on my team.
I am always on your team,
even when we disagree.
Now,
should we give it another go?
Thank you.
- Uh-huh?
- Uh-huh.
See? Following instructions
is not that bad.
- Oh, don't gloat.
- [sighs] Let's get out of here.
[door rattling]
Something's wrong.
- Did we miss a screw, or something?
- No.
[sighs]
We missed this.
How the hell did we possibly miss this?
Damn it.
Hey, look.
It's not perfect, but it's ours.
Can you live with that?
Hey, don't go in your corner.
- Yeah, I can live with it.
- [door clicking]
Hell, yeah, let's go to Narnia.
Are we out?
[Sara] Out of the closet,
but not the store.
[Agent Sharpe] Touché.
Welcome to our mattress showroom!
If you'll follow me...
The mattress you choose will be the most
important decision of your life.
Wait,
you're showing them the mattresses?
We need everyone out
before Tabitha gets here.
Who the hell is Tabitha?
You don't want to know Tabitha.
Best of luck in your mattress choice.
- [Sara] Gary, don't...
- [Agent Sharpe] Wait. We need to...
This is starting to feel like
that escape room we did.
Okay, so, subconscious Gary said
that this would be
the most important choice of our life.
What do you think that means?
That even subconscious Gary
needs to get a life.
No, it's a puzzle.
What does it mean?
Do you think we need to...
It means we need to pick a mattress.
- How about this one?
- What?
Whoa! 600 bucks.
- That is...
- Three-year warranty?
- That's really...
- ...ridiculously expensive, right?
I was thinking, like, $250.
Are you kidding?
It would be saggy in like a year.
So, you just flip it over.
You just flip it over? Is that
what you do when things get saggy?
You just flip them over,
so you don't have to look
at their saggy faces?
Okay.
[exhaling]
How about this one? Fifteen years.
Well, that's better.
Oh.
When did you start going gray?
Whoa!
This place has been really stressful.
Yeah.
[gasping in horror]
I think it's the mattress.
Apparently, your purgatory
is your anxieties.
One of which must be getting old.
I'm not worried about getting old, Sara.
I'm worried about getting old with you.
[sighs]
So, we're talking about marriage.
[Agent Sharpe sighs]
Wow.
You look... still really hot, but...
You, too.
[scoffs softly]
Fifty years is a long time
sleeping on one mattress.
Sure is.
Look, I know it's a lot.
Fifty years with just one person.
It's not the one person thing, I just...
Look, I've never really thought
that much past tomorrow.
Ava, with my past,
planning anything for the future
is just... Feels like tempting fate.
And I convinced myself
that I like it that way.
Until you came along.
You just freaking came to purgatory
for me.
How's that for giving
a middle finger to fate?
Look, you're allowed to want things
sometimes, Sara.
But what if I can't be
the person that you need?
Let's be honest,
neither of us needs anybody, right?
But you are who I want.
I bet you there's some
good liquor in Ava's office.
I mean, my dad's old office.
Oh, man. Things are bleak.
Hey, Ray.
Thanks for sticking around here.
Yeah, buddy, of course.
That's what friends are for.
I just wish I wasn't such an idiot
at my dad's funeral.
I had a chance to talk to him,
but I blew it.
But now I'll never know what happened.
[Ray] Well, maybe Constantine
can get you some answers.
Looks like they caught Neron.
Son of a bitch!
Is that the demon who killed my dad?
Whoa, there, squire.
You take it easy, all right?
[Nora] Nate, you don't want to
go in there. Just walk away.
- No, not a chance.
- Nate!
Wait! Wait!
Hello, Nathaniel.
I've heard so much about you.
So predictable. The son who, in life,
could never connect with the father,
here now, seeking the truth.
Well, here it is.
Hank was an unfortunate snag in my plan.
So, I...
- You evil bastard.
- Yeah.
Demon.
[grunts] Nate's already angry,
makes him prime pickings for Neron.
He'll be all right, as long as
he doesn't cross that bloody barrier.
[groans]
Why? He built your theme park
just like you wanted.
You think I wanted a theme park?
I gave Hank power, and in return,
he was to supply me
with fear-mongering magical creatures
to terrorize people
into giving up their souls.
Instead, he went behind my back
and built some deranged zoo.
He betrayed me. Because of you.
No...
If you'd have just stayed
out of our way,
maybe your old man would still be alive.
[door beeps]
- [Ray] Nate! No!
- Don't push...
[groans]
[laughing]
Ray, I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry about...
- It's okay, buddy.
I know it wasn't you.
[whistling "Pop Goes the Weasel"]
Oh.
- [Sara gasps]
- [Agent Sharpe] What are...
[sighs] It's locked.
[sighs]
- Uh... There's nothing to build.
- No furniture to choose.
Dishes.
Piece of cake. Go, go, go.
You know, this seems more like
one of your fantasies than your fears,
watching me do dishes.
Please, if it were up to you,
we would only have paper plates. Here.
- You on that?
- Got it.
[Agent Sharpe grunts]
[crackles]
I'm on it.
It never ends. [sighs]
[Mona] Did you send it?
Honestly, mate, whatever happened
to just talking to someone?
Emojis are way more fun
and if he's not that into it,
you can pretend like
you were talking about something else.
Right. Nate's going to think I was dying
to tell him about a dancing lady
carrying a burning eggplant.
Here. Use words.
It's erotic, but vulnerable.
Okay, let me see it. [clears throat]
I'm not saying "bulge."
Sula the Wolf Witch talked about
smothering a demon.
Does that make sense to you?
When Mallus was a part of me,
I could feel his fear.
Like he was vulnerable here on Earth.
It made him nervous.
So, if we can separate the demon
from his earthly vessel,
it will suffocate him,
just like a fish out of water.
[Neron, telepathically] Why are you
even working with that arrogant dick?
He'll never value your true power.
Not like I will...
- You all right there, love?
- Yeah.
I just need some coffee. I'm fine.
And I'm sober.
Hey, are you okay?
[sighs] I'm all right. Thanks.
You best let her alone, squire.
This is all your mail! You deal with it.
[both sigh]
It's not like you have an address
to even get mail, so...
We both talked about it and agreed
that now wasn't the right time
for me to move in with you.
- But we're making it work.
- Are we?
Because how I see it, we're living
completely separate lives. So...
Ava, I want this.
Just when the time is right.
Timing doesn't just happen, Sara, okay?
You have to make a choice.
So, what?
What, this? This is what you want?
No. Of course, nobody just wants
dirty dishes, but, yes.
Ava, we're time-traveling superheroes.
Okay, fine. But I am not just my job.
I want some hobbies,
I want a life with you.
And sometimes, life is just this.
Okay? It's boring.
What then?
You off to the next adventure?
No. But I can't just decide
every single moment of forever,
right this instant.
So, please, just tell me what
you want me to say, and I'll say it,
and we can get out of here.
I can't tell you what to say, Sara,
because then it wouldn't mean anything.
Okay. Well...
[sighs]
Let's just move to the suburbs
and we'll just recycle until we die.
Can we go now?
[door opens]
Oh, no.
[gasps]
[door beeps]
It's just me. Let's talk.
I've admired your... power
for a long time, Nora.
I don't take compliments from people
who frame me for murder.
All in the interest
of self-preservation. You understand.
Do they even know
what you're capable of?
They have no idea.
Then why waste your time
with that arrogant bastard
and his pathetic delusion
that the world needs him to save it.
When I met John, I was just a kid.
He was kind.
Mallus wanted me, but I wasn't ready.
But I'll tell you this,
John did everything he could to save me.
[Constantine chanting]
[grunting]
But when he failed, he abandoned me.
[screaming]
John knew what the Order were doing
to me, and he just let them.
And he's the one who decides
who to send to hell. [chuckles]
Cocky cowboy, wearing his hangover
like a 10-gallon hat.
He might have won that last battle,
but the war is mine.
My Tabitha will be free soon,
and when she is,
we're gonna put John away for good.
[Nora] Tabitha?
That's why you needed Ava as a vessel.
[Gary] There's a model for everyone.
Are you looking for one to clean,
one to keep you safe, one to...
please you?
No, you creep.
I'm looking for Ava.
- They're all Ava.
- No. They're not.
[scoffs]
[Gary] Just remember, pick quickly.
Tabitha will be here soon,
and once she's here...
- [lights clunking off]
- [roaring]
[screeching]
Oh, no.
Once she's here, what?
[woman on PA] Attention. The store
will be closing in five minutes.
I can't believe I got my dad killed.
No. It was Hank's choice
to make a deal with a demon,
that is not your fault.
You spending time with him
inspired him, made him happy.
I don't think you doomed him.
I think you saved him.
[Ray clearing throat]
Here's to the man
you helped your dad become.
You know what, Ray?
You're right. I shouldn't
be embarrassed, I should be proud.
Yeah, my dad was a little wacky,
but most of the good ones are.
He was a legend,
and he should be remembered that way.
[gasps]
[coughs] Mikey T. I gotta stop him.
Sara will never let you take Ava.
If not her, I'll find someone else.
You know, I can bring back other people.
Damien misses you so much.
- You can bring my father...
- Of course.
Now, be a lamb and let me out,
Nora Darhk.
[takes deep breath]
You know,
you can't just walk out of here.
Constantine will never let you do that.
Maybe as Desmond.
But if you let me in,
you, with my power,
nobody could stop us.
The monitors were wonky,
are you all right?
Of course, you shut them down.
I should have never trusted you.
[groaning]
Shut up, John.
[groans]
[woman on PA] Attention, the store
will be closing in two minutes.
Where is she?
None of these are Ava!
I'm not leaving without her.
Ava.
But you could've chosen
any one of those other women.
[scoffs]
I don't want other women.
But I'm...
[sniffles]
[gasping]
- Hey. Hey.
- Oh.
You did it.
No. We did it.
[Gary] We did it!
[both exclaiming]
Let's do this.
[beeping]
Nora?
[screaming]
Now!
[screeching]
"Vessel."
What a pretty word for "victim."
Oh, I don't need your power, Neron.
I have my own.
We've got him. Just a few minutes more.
Nora!
Ray, no!
[screeching]
[gasps]
[groans]
Des, Des? Des. Des, hey, hey, hey.
It's okay, mate.
It's all right.
- Where am I?
- Safe.
Nora?
[gasps]
Nora.
[Mona] Eggplant's a little obvious.
I say you go with mushroom.
- Mushroom...
- [all gasping]
Ava! You're back from the dead!
- Gently.
- Do it gently.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Nice job, boss.
- Okay, serious. Which emoji is like...
- All right. Enough with the emojis.
Just leave while you can.
- You should just...
- Let's go.
- [Agent Sharpe] Okay.
- [Mona] Maybe...
We should probably talk
about whether or not we want kids.
Let's wait until the other eight
are old enough to handle the news.
I don't even know
what this text means anymore.
"You up? Hot dog, donut, thumbs up."
Well, you wanna snog him, yeah?
Or do you want him to get diabetes?
[chuckles]
Okay, this doesn't sound like me at all.
You like him and he likes you.
Just tell him that.
[clicks tongue]
Okay.
"Want to go out sometime..."
[clearing throat]
"...on a date?"
[Charlie and Mona gasp]
- [beeps]
- [all chuckling]
Yeah, see? That wasn't so bad.
- Now, it's all on Nate.
- [sighs]
Oh, God. Oh, God, what did I do?
[cell phone ringing]
[man] Give me a hand with that.
Mikey, pick up. Mikey, pick up.
[man] You can just drop that down.
You're not gonna need it.
[loud rock music playing]
No.
- [loud rock music continues]
- Mikey! No! Mikey!
Mikey, stop!
[cell phone beeps]
Zari?
[gasping and panting]
[sighs]
Is that you, "& Son"?
I changed my mind!
What are you doing?
You should've just called.
[grunts in frustration]
I knew I should have synced
to the stupid cloud.
Nate.
- Hey.
- Hi. Uh...
So, about... [clears throat]
About that text...
Yeah, my phone had an unfortunate run-in
with a wrecking ball, so...
[laughing] Oh, my God. That sucks.
What did you wanna talk about?
[stammering] I just wanted to let you
know that Sara and Ava, they're good.
- That's great!
- Yeah.
Anything else you wanna talk about?
No. No, not that I can think of.
Okay. Cool, cool, cool.
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
- Zari.
[Desmond] Hello?
Is there anyone here
who can call me a cab?
Anything you need, mate.
I can get you a flight to New Orleans,
anywhere in the world. You name it.
No. I don't want anything from you.
I'm not asking you for forgiveness, Des.
- Good.
- Just wait.
[sighs]
You saved me, Johnny.
I'm grateful for that.
But it doesn't change anything.
I know.
You know, I can make it all go away,
Des. This'll make you forget.
No.
You sent me to hell.
That's something
we're both gonna have to live with.
[elevator dings]
[machine beeping]
[Constantine]
How's she holding up, old son?
She's stable, but unresponsive.
Well, that's better
than the alternative.
I couldn't let her get hurt again.
Yeah, right,
you just rode straight in there,
like a knight in shinin' armor
and nearly got her killed.
I didn't mean to.
Yeah, I know.
She's a brave lass.
Nearly cost her her life.
She killed that bloody demon.
She's amazing.
[Constantine]
We'll get you out of this one, Nora.
I'm not gonna abandon you again.
[sighing]
[barking]
It's okay, boy! Dogs usually love me!
[whistling "Pop Goes the Weasel"]
[theme music playing]