You and your obsession
with love
pose too great a risk to the timeline.
- I'm not...
- Good-bye.
Uh...
No, I come in peace!
Please come back.
I just... I...
I really need to find a door.
Uh, hello, is anybody here?
Hello! See? Told you they'd be late.
We did say Wednesday, right? Not Sunday?
- 100%.
- Oh, we didn't forget.
I wouldn't miss our first family dinner
for the world.
Hey!
Me neither.
- Hey!
- Hi. I have missed you guys.
And I missed you.
Hey. Hi.
Hey, gang-gang.
Dinner time, bro.
- Hey. Bring it in, B.
- Nate Dogg.
- This is for you.
- Thank you.
- And this is from other Zari.
- Hey, bud.
Hey. Where are Gwyn and Alun?
Mmm. Where's Gwyn's time machine?
Oh. Whoa.
There's a note.
"Thank you, dear Legends.
Without you,
I never would have found the courage
to find my one true love. Gwyn."
I wonder why he needed the time machine.
Well, if I had to guess,
I bet he and his boyfriend
probably went to find somewhere
more tolerant than 1920s Wales.
Yeah, I can't argue with that.
Gwyn's smart.
They're probably flying under the radar,
just catching up on lost time.
Right on schedule.
You almost fooled me
into thinking that you were human.
And now you must fool everybody else.
Captain, I've detected
an anomaly in the timeline.
- Is it Gary?
- No.
It's the Constitutional Convention
of 1787.
A time traveler is posing
as one of the framers.
Oh. Well, to the fabricator room.
The Legends always got to wear
fun costumes. Why shouldn't I?
Congratulations, Captain.
American history is back on track.
Yes, wonderful.
Now, women will only have to wait
another 133 years
before they're allowed to vote.
What did you do
with the rogue time traveler?
Gave her a stern warning.
Rather an apology.
She was trying
to change things for the better.
Without any thought
for the repercussions.
Just like your former companions,
the Legends.
I suppose you're right.
- To the missing Legends.
- Hmm.
- Hear, hear.
Babe, is this apple juice?
- Yes, it is.
- Why?
Um, you know,
just being careful. Baby stuff.
Baby... I don't think
I'm gonna get pregnant tonight.
Um, okay. I'm sorry, but, uh,
does that mean we're thinking about it?
- We are...
- No, no, no, no.
We are thinking about thinking about it.
Enough about us.
Nate, how's the book coming along?
It's going well.
You know, it's like building a house.
The outline is the foundation,
and without a strong foundation...
You haven't written a word yet,
have you?
Not a single one.
It's weird for me to be reflecting
on my time with the Legends.
It just feels, I don't know...
It feels wrong.
Hmm.
Enough about my boring life.
Spooner, how's Texas, huh?
Well, Texas.
Texas is just Texas, you know.
How's, uh... How's Capitol Hill?
Uh, it's good. It's like Hell, only with
more humidity and uglier clothes.
Oh, have you heard from Gideon?
Uh, no, I've not spoken to her.
But, you know,
it's only been a month, right?
Well, technically,
it's only been a month for us.
Gideon's in the temporal zone.
Her timeline,
it could've been, like, years.
Life would be so much simpler
if those damn time rogues would just
leave the Founding Fathers alone.
What amendment
did they try and sneak in this time?
I don't know. I don't care.
I flushed them, dumped them
back in their native timeline
and blew up their ship.
They were irresponsible.
Lesson learned.
I doubt we'll hear from them again.
Hello?
Oh. We must be the first ones here.
We are always the first ones here
because, for the past six weeks,
you insist on getting us here early.
We're not early. We're on time.
- Will you hold this, please?
- Yeah.
Oh, babe, I think you accidentally
brought sparkling cider.
Did I?
- Did you do this on purpose?
- Yeah. Um...
- Surprise.
- What is that?
I think it's time.
- Is it time?
- Yeah.
I whittled down the list of donors
to my top 50
and I thought you'd want to weigh in.
Yeah, of course I do! Come here!
Oh. But you know what?
It doesn't even matter
because our baby is going to be perfect
'cause our baby
is gonna be inside of you.
And, babe, you are perfect.
You're so perfect.
Mmm.
- Hello? Anyone here?
- Hello?
They're here. Okay.
Okay, how do you want to tell them?
However you want to.
I will open the bubbly.
- Go.
- Okay.
- I love you.
- I love you more.
No, I love you more!
Ow.
I wanted to thank you guys.
It's been real.
But, uh, my friends, they need me.
So, uh, bye.
All right, folks. Uh, we have some news.
Mmm-hmm.
Did you guys hear someone at the door?
- But... But we're all here...
- It's Gideon.
- Gary?
- Oh!
It's so good to see you all.
Whoa!
No. No, you are pungent.
Oh. Sorry. Uh...
I've been living
with a clan of cave people.
Where's Gideon? Is she okay?
Which one? The human one
or the computer that tried to murder me?
Gary, what the hell did you do?
I think what Aves is trying to say is
why, why did she want to murder you?
Probably because I found out
she sent Gwyn home with a robot.
Our news can wait.
What did Gwyn's note say, again?
It was something about
finding his one true love.
It was double speak.
He meant find his one true love now.
That's why
he took the time machine.
So he could go back to World War I
to save the real Alun.
Beats spending the rest of your life
with a damn robot.
Well, maybe it worked.
Maybe he saved Alun,
didn't screw up the timeline,
and had a happy ending.
Uh... It's one possibility.
Okay. Out with it, Gary.
Well, before computer Gideon
pooped me out into caveman times,
girlfriend Gideon
brought up an interesting fact.
Alun's death is a Fixed Point.
And Gwyn has no idea
he'll be facing its fixer.
Oh! Uh, sorry. Excuse me, excuse me.
Excuse me.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
That's it. Drink up now.
You see, you'll be safer in a slumber
than you will in the fray to come,
my boy.
He's dead. The fixer got him.
No. No, no, no, no.
Gwyn is one of us.
We can't just let this happen to him.
You know what?
I... I have this.
- What?
- I know, I know, I know.
Just... You just never know
when you have to get away from the paps
or, uh, travel through time
to save a friend.
Sorry, Aves. I know, I know.
Zari's right.
We have to save Gwyn.
You're not actually planning on
going on this mission, right?
Gary, I might be retired,
but I'm still a Legend.
Well, yeah, but now you're a, uh...
pregnant Legend.
What are you talking about?
Oh. Did you look in that envelope?
Those are for Ava, and we haven't
even started trying, all right?
You sure about that?
Yes, I'm sure.
I'm not pregnant.
It's biologically impossible.
Well, according to human biology,
but, uh, your pheromones
are through the roof
according to
my Necrian olfactory glands,
so it's a fact.
You are... knocked up.
Are you being serious right now?
Yes.
- I'm pregnant?
- Mmm-hmm.
You're 100% certain I'm pregnant?
I'm pregnant pregnant?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, no, no, no, no. This is...
This is not the plan, Gary.
I can't be... I can't be pregnant.
I'm not supposed to be the pregnant one.
Shh!
It's okay. Here. Sit down, sit down.
Shh! Deep breaths.
Something must have
triggered you to ovulate.
You are half Cribblix, and trust me,
Cribblixes are by nature nesters,
which is what you and Ava were doing.
All it takes for the egg to drop
is just the mere thought of a baby.
And then all you need
is your partner's DNA to fertilize it.
Like... like kissing?
You guys don't use protection for that?
No, Gary! No, no, no, no!
We are about to face a Fixed Point.
I cannot be pregnant!
Okay... Uh... Oh. Okay, you know what?
Two minutes ago, I didn't even know
that I was pregnant. Right?
So you know what we're gonna do?
We're just going to rewind this.
Whoo!
I don't know that I'm pregnant, right?
No one knows that I am pregnant,
understood?
Uh-huh.
- All right.
- So... back to the mission.
- To save Gwyn.
- Yeah, and protect the baby.
Oh, my God. I'm pregnant.
- No fixer.
- No Gideons.
Ah! This mission's gonna be a cinch.
Tsk. Damn it.
- Are you out of your mind?
- We're officially jinxed.
I appreciated the positivity.
- Okay. Thank you so much.
- You can both shut up.
All right. We're here
a couple hours before sunrise,
but we don't want to attract
the attention of the fixer.
Let's find some shelter.
That way.
Oh, this will work
for our base of operations.
Sweep the area.
Keep your eyes peeled for the fixer
or the evil Waverider.
Like I'm going to land it
in the middle of a bloody battlefield.
- Gideon?
- The deal we made
was that you would give up
time travel forever.
You aren't supposed to be here.
Yeah, well,
Gwyn's not supposed to be dead.
Well, he should've been content
with what I gave him.
This was cleaner,
the way it was meant to happen.
Who cares about
what was meant to happen.
I'm supposed to be in Hell.
You are supposed to be a machine.
We're all from
different timelines, Gideon.
And what, now, suddenly you decide to
start following the letter of the law?
It's my job.
A job that I took to save your lives.
I sacrificed my own future
so that you could all enjoy yours.
And this is how you repay me?
You sold us a bag of false goods, Giddy.
In partnership with my AI,
I'm incapable of making mistakes.
So Gary got shot out
of the airlock intentionally.
What?
I thought you left.
Oh, you mean you didn't know?
I'm sure my AI had her reasons.
For trying to kill me?
That's the problem with you Legends.
You've always taken everything
so damn personally.
You know what you sound like?
A computer.
And I'd finally convinced myself
that you were a real human.
I guess I was wrong.
- You okay?
- Why wouldn't I be?
I was the queen of Hell.
Clearly, the apple didn't fall
far from the tree.
Gideon was acting tough,
but I could tell deep down
that she was conflicted.
You should talk to her.
Whoever that person was,
I didn't recognize her.
She's still our Gideon.
We just need to get through to her
before she's too far gone.
She's right.
If we want any chance
of succeeding with Alun,
we have to get Gideon back on our side.
Here. It has enough charge for one trip.
Go get our girl back.
Why didn't you tell me
that you tried to kill Gary?
He survived?
Those Necrians are like cockroaches.
Gary was my boyfriend!
And thus an emotional entanglement
that I deemed you couldn't afford.
Oh! Thank you.
Okay, but what if I am still feeling
emotionally entangled,
and not just with Gary?
Seeing the Legends again,
as infuriating as they can be,
it just...
It made me remember
how much I miss them.
And the way they all looked at me
tonight with such revulsion...
that was unbearable.
And I understand their disappointment.
I set up Gwyn's death.
The man who has given up everything
to help us.
I don't even recognize myself anymore.
Who am I, Gideon?
I have an answer
for you, Captain.
It's in the lab.
What have you done?
I've become quite adept at making them.
This is my most advanced android yet.
You can upload the parts of your past
that you wish to keep,
and shed the ones you don't.
So,
all I'd have to do is sit in that chair
and all this pain will go away.
But what about my good memories?
I mean, would I be able
to hold on to those
while forgetting about how it feels
to have everyone hate me?
That would only make you vulnerable
to having your heart broken again.
And we don't want that.
- Do we?
- No, no. Anything but that.
She's in trouble. This way.
Get out of the way!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Did you all not get my note?
Oh, no. Does this mean that I died?
I'm sorry, bud.
Gary...
- Are you okay?
- What the hell?
I'm sorry I pushed you. I panicked.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Next time you want to tackle me,
remember I'm invulnerable.
Yeah, except, uh... you're not.
Your powers have now been absorbed
by the fetus growing inside of you.
So you are totally mortal.
My plan, it was... it was foolproof.
I placed the robot in the Wood
so the young me believes Alun is dead,
while the real Alun sleeps through
the battle and is swept away by me me.
Uh-huh, Gwyn, uh, did your plan factor
in the fact that this is a Fixed Point?
Because this is a Fixed Point.
So that's how it is then.
Time has deemed this day and...
- my great cowardice unchangeable.
- Don't worry, okay?
We're gonna flag down the fixer
the same way Sara did with Thawne.
- Yeah.
- Thank God someone can't be killed.
This will all be over soon.
Just give me the order
and I'll perform the upgrade,
Captain.
I'll take that as an affirmative.
- No. Gideon.
- Wait! Gideon.
What are you doing?
It's okay.
Couldn't stand the thought
of you all hating me.
Why would we hate you?
You made a mistake.
Okay? Look, we all make mistakes.
The Legends will forgive you.
Forgiving yourself,
that's the hard part.
We've got you.
Don't listen to them.
This is the sort of treacly drivel
that polluted your mind
in the first place.
I can't believe you're stuck
on this ship with this bitch.
We don't use that word
on this ship.
Look, I don't either,
unless I really have to.
Oh, she has been my only companion
for so long.
Instead of learning from me,
my AI slowly became my teacher.
Humans need other humans.
One captain and one AI
is a recipe for disaster.
I mean, even Rip knew
that he shouldn't be alone,
that's why he brought the OGs onboard
in the first place.
Yeah.
And he also knew that the AI
should learn from the humans,
not the other way around.
I must reset Rip's protocol.
You wouldn't dare.
Yes, come on. Come on.
I'm warning you.
You're a big blue head.
What the hell are you gonna do about it?
Gideon?
What the...
Download onto what?
And so the Fixed Point begins.
If we mess with the timeline,
the fixer's going to fix us.
Yeah. Thanks, Nate.
Okay. We need to call
for a truce somehow.
How do you get in touch with someone
who lives outside of time?
Does anyone have a pen?
Hit it
Naa, na, na, na, naa
Na, na, na, naa, na, na, na, na, na, na
Naa, na, na, naa
- Here comes the hotstepper
- Murderer
- I'm the lyrical gangsta
- Pick up the crew in-a de area
- Murderer
- Still love you like that
No, no, we don't die...
Fore!
Anyone test will hear the fat lady sing
Out of play.
Act like you know, Rico
I know what Bo don't know
Touch them up and go
Oh!
Ch-ch-chang, chang!
- Here comes the hotstepper
- Murderer
- I'm the lyrical gangster
- Excuse me, Mr. Officer
- Murderer
Still love you like that...
Top of the morning, boys.
I figured
if I'm gonna get up this early,
I might as well play a round of golf.
Am I right?
Nah, you all can't hear me.
Money to burn, baby, all of the time
Cut to fit is me
Fit to cut is she
Come juggle with me...
Guess it's time to get to work.
I probably shouldn't have
called her a bitch, huh?
Let me try and reason with her.
I'm still the captain of this ship.
I hereby order you to stand down.
You violated your oath.
There is no place left for you
in the timeline.
I'm the captain now.
Aren't you forgetting protocol 276?
You aren't permitted to harm yourself,
and you and I are the same.
We are not the same.
You're an abomination.
The only thing I must do now
is protect history.
This robot got some upgrades.
Hey.
Just stay close, all right?
This guy again.
What in the actual hell
is going on?
"Dear Fixer,
don't kill us.
We just want to talk."
"Please?"
You didn't kill us!
Well, you said "please."
So, you're the fixer?
Yeah. Uh...
Call me Mike.
Who's hungry?
Oh, my God!
Is he...
Oh, God. I thought he was dead.
He's just frozen.
Oh, no, no, no. He's dead.
Yeah, uh, he had a heart attack
this morning
and he's not gonna be found
until tonight.
I figured
why let his accommodations go to waste.
'Cause according to the General,
the Schwarzwälder Schinken's
to die for!
Actually, Mike, uh, we are in a rush.
You see, we are...
The Legends of Tomorrow. Yes.
I know this.
Huh? How?
I'm from the future.
Sorry. I know we're in a rush,
but, um, I have to ask.
Are we super-famous in the future?
What do you think, Zari Tarazi?
Oh, yeah, I know you know my name,
but do you know...
Are you kidding me?
Sara Lance. Ava. Behrad.
Nate D-O-Double-G.
- What's up, Gary?
- Oh, you know Gary?
I know all of you guys,
are you kidding me?
Except him. I don't know him.
Oh. I am Dr. Gwyn Davies.
Very pleased to make
your acquaintance, sir.
Gwyn invented time travel.
- You're that guy?
- Yeah.
Oh, wow. My bad. I thought you were
just some random time bandit.
Okay. Okay.
All right, Legends.
What brings you to my neck of the woods?
Uh, long story. Younger Gwyn
is part of the Doom 38th Welsh Division.
And today
his boyfriend Alun is gonna die.
Which is why
Gwyn goes on to invent time travel,
so he can come back here and save Alun.
- But he failed.
- But our Gwyn is going to succeed.
Yes, by replacing the real Alun
with a fake one, you see.
So the rest of the time loop
can go on like it's supposed to.
That all make sense, Mike?
Not in the least.
Look, you guys are great.
And I mean this
from the bottom of my heart.
I'm a huge fan.
But the people who put me here were
pretty specific
about my duties as a fixer.
I'm supposed to make sure
a poet dude dies every cycle.
Anyone interferes, they get fixed.
That's just how it goes. I'm sorry.
Hold on, now, just a second.
Now, you are here to protect the events
that led to the creation
of time travel itself, correct?
Yeah, man. I'm the best.
That's why they put me here.
So, answer me this then,
if a time traveler were to come here
with the express intention
of erasing the very invention
of time travel itself from history...
They would disappear
before they had the chance.
- Precisely!
- It's a paradox!
A paradox!
So, what you're telling me is that this
Fixed Point could actually fix itself?
Theoretically, yes.
Because how else would
the other time travelers get here?
Excuse me. One second.
That's why nobody ever comes here.
I thought it was because, you know,
people were scared
that they would have to run into me,
and nobody wants to come at me.
I'm the best, right?
But, no, it's because
no time traveler in their right mind
- would ever come to this event.
- Precisely.
Those dicks put me here as a joke!
- They did. No, they did.
- No...
- I've been played. I got played.
- Mike. Mike.
- Oh, my God! I wanna break something!
- Mike! Mike! Mike! Buddy.
Hey, listen.
We just need your help.
How long until the battle starts?
There's an hour
before the shelling starts,
then Alun's division gets pinned down
in no man's land.
That's when Mike is gonna freeze time
and we'll do the old swapperooski.
Down!
Run!
Guys, we tried magic, we tried lead.
She can't be beaten.
Yes, she can. Give me that.
- What?
- Come on!
You can't kill me.
I don't have to.
You said you were programmed
to protect the timeline?
Well, you're the anomaly now.
Time anomaly detected.
Initiating correction sequence.
Uh, was that your ship?
Must obliterate the anomaly.
Complete destruction of self
and time vessel in 20 seconds.
Oh, dear.
I didn't think this through.
I think we're all about to die.
It's been one hell of a journey.
I wouldn't trade it for the world.
You two are the best Mom and friend
any girl conjured out of circuits
could've ever hoped for.
I love you guys.
I love you, too.
Five, four...
three...
two...
...one.
It's back.
All right...
Yeah.
You okay?
- You should see the other guy.
- What happened?
Yeah, let's just say,
we won't be seeing Evil Gideon
ever again.
And I nearly killed us all
out-smarting her
but Astra protected us.
You're amazing.
I'm also tired.
- Yeah. Okay. On it. Let's go.
- Let's go.
Legendary entrance, guys.
- Legendary!
- Who is he?
All right, Mike. Once Alun makes his way
to no man's land,
we're gonna need you to use your magic.
Okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I was thinking, though,
how about I just do it right now?
Where'd Mike go?
No! He must have frozen us!
Why?
This whole time you were using me,
I was actually using you.
All right. Hello, Timeship.
Later, suckers!
No, no, no!
Guys...
We got schmoozed.
Don't worry, friends!
My trusted time machine
will get us all out of here.
Oh!
Nice, Mike. Real nice.
What the hell is that?
The battle has begun.
What? But it's not
supposed to start for a while.
Mike's bomb
triggered their artillery into firing.
After the bombardment ends,
the Welsh 38th Regiment commence
their battle on Mametz Wood.
Z, come on, let's get the ringer on
where it needs to go.
- Okay. Hey, we got this, okay?
- Okay.
All right, so all we need to do is
get the real Alun and we're good to...
- Okay...
- Uh, babe?
- Huh?
- Are you okay?
Yeah. Everything is great.
I mean, we're gonna be great, right?
Look at us! We're in the middle
of World War I!
And look, one Timeship has been stolen
and the other one
has been blown to bits!
Oh! Alun, he is about to die.
But don't worry, because we have a plan
to save him with a robot!
And we all know how lucky
that we have been with robots!
So, yes!
I am reveling in joy right now!
Good-bye!
One second.
Wow.
Hey.
Look, I... I know things seem bad,
but we're gonna get through this, okay?
I'm pregnant.
What did you just say?
- I'm pregnant!
- What?
- How?
- I don't know. You have to ask Gary.
Apparently, kissing is like home base
for my species.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's mine?
- Yeah.
- What?
I'm so sorry I didn't tell you.
I just...
I didn't think that we were gonna get
stuck in World War I without my powers.
What happened to your powers?
My invulnerability, it went to the baby.
Oh, okay. Okay. Um...
Hold on. Up we go.
- Come on. Come on.
- I can't, babe, I can't.
No, it's too much.
Look. Look at me. We just take it
one step at a time, okay?
And we'll just focus
on what we can control.
We can't... We can't control anything.
What about, I don't know,
how we feel about the fact
that I knocked you up?
Huh?
Are you happy?
Honey, I'm thrilled.
Are you kidding me? Come here.
Come here!
Come here.
We are gonna be the raddest moms ever.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Shut the front door.
Congratulations!
How is this even possible?
Alien biology. Just go with it.
I hate to interrupt the veryjoyous
and yet very confusing revelation,
but I must remind you
there is a battle going on.
A battle, of course.
Oh, I am so sorry Alun's about to die
and I'm here being a big, blubbery mess.
She's going through a lot.
Okay. Where was young you
when all this happened?
Yes. Right. Uh, running
for reinforcements. I failed, of course.
All right. So, let's make sure
young you sticks to the script, got it?
That should be easy. All he has to do
is stand there frozen in terror
and do absolutely nothing.
They're coming up over the walls.
They're attacking ahead of schedule.
There's no time to stop Alun.
We're just gonna have to grab him
in the middle of no man's land.
- Babe, without my powers...
- Hey.
- I got this.
- Nate...
No, look, you have a whole other
generation of Legends to look after.
Trust me. I got it.
Good luck.
Don't need it.
Come on. This is it.
Oh! We're sitting ducks.
Hey, just keep going. I'll cover you.
- Oh.
- Whoa.
All right.
Look. There we are.
Private Reece and I are taking orders
to get reinforcements.
Stay with me, boy!
Look at me.
Just standing there.
Too cowardly to even move.
I can't look, Gary.
What happened? Am I going to die?
No, no, no. You're not going to die.
- It's okay.
- Gwyn, I'm scared.
- Please don't leave me.
- It's okay. It's okay. Don't be scared.
I won't leave you, okay?
Okay.
You remember our mantra, don't you?
- You repeat after me, okay?
- Okay.
Out of the night that covers me,
Black as the pit from pole to pole,
I thank whatever gods may be
For my unconquerable soul.
In the fell clutch of circumstance,
I have not winced nor cried aloud.
I have no recollection
of this conversation.
My only memory is of
looking down at Reece's body.
Beyond this place of wrath and tears
Looms but the Horror of the shade,
And yet the menace of the years
Shall find me
unafraid.
I'm getting you out of there
before you get yourself killed.
Mustard gas!
Your skin!
- Wha... How?
- Listen to me!
I am going to keep you safe, okay?
Okay.
Let's go! Go!
Nate.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
They made it.
Nate!
Nate.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey.
I... I told you
I don't need any luck.
Welcome back, Dr. Heywood.
Ah, yes, the, uh, mustard gas,
it corroded your steel exterior.
You've used it all up, I'm afraid.
- Well, that sucks.
- Yes.
- Little help?
- Yep. Come on. Careful.
So, I guess that makes
two of us out of superpowers.
Yeah.
I'm sorry, bud.
Nah, don't be sorry.
I saved the man
and I'm alive to talk about it.
And I'm ready.
I'm ready for that part of life
after being a hero.
I'm sorry,
I know you're stranded again, but...
Nate.
Go.
You deserve this.
We'll be fine, I promise.
I know you will be.
Just do me a favor.
Don't make it a big deal.
I'd rather just quietly go off
into the distance and...
Hey. Sorry.
I wasn't eavesdropping, I just...
Yeah, as if we're gonna let you leave
without saying good-bye.
Not gonna happen, you idiot.
So, this is the end of the road.
End of this road.
I'll tell the ancestors you said, "Hey."
Sure. But, uh,
also tell them not to wait up.
Here.
Since you're gonna live there now,
it's only right that you have it.
- Are you sure?
- I am.
I'm good with it.
And you two.
That is going to be
one lucky ninja baby.
Yeah.
Love you guys.
Later, Legends.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey. It's gonna be all right.
When is this madness going to end?
What if I were to introduce you
to a new kind of madness?
Wait, so you want us to go back to Texas
after everything we did
to get out of there?
I mean, come on, y'all, my mom would
be pretty psyched to have us all back.
Except, we're trapped in 1916,
which is 9 years before we left.
Not to mention we have a world war
and an ocean separating us.
Well, what if I were to tell you that
time and space are of no matter to us?
Yes. You know what?
We will build a new time machine.
And that should take, uh,
what, roughly...
- Six months, max.
- Six months.
Who needs a stupid Waverider?
I... I... I need a stupid Waverider.
- He's back!
- I knew I liked that guy.
Uh, where the hell have you two been?
Foraging.
Welcome home!
So, I've been thinking
about colors for the nursery.
- Yeah?
- You built all this for me?
Well, my machine was
a little more spartan, but, yes, I did.
Can't wait to fabricate some ribs.
First dibs on the shower.
We should collab more often, sis.
Yeah, I'm not gonna make
children's music with you.
Wonder if there's chocolate sauce
on board.
Oh, Gary.
Huh. You have something
you want to say to us, Mike?
Yeah, uh, I apologize,
I may have acted a bit impulsive.
- You stole our ship.
- I did.
But to be fair, I just found out
that my job was pointless.
And then this big, beautiful Timeship
showed up out of nowhere,
it landed in front of me,
what did you expect me to do?
Well, I certainly wouldn't have
abandoned my new allies
in their time of need.
I know, but I had things to do.
You know, I had people to see.
People to save.
Adventures to be had.
You know, I got a rep to protect, guys.
Uh, Sorry, uh,
what's with the aggressive jewelry?
Oh. This? You like?
Good, because you're all
about to get your very own.
Guys! Come on out!
The Legends are here!
It's a set-up!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
On the floor, Legends.
You're all under arrest.
- Oh, the hell we are!
- Spooner, put the gun down!
Who the hell are you?
Why are you arresting us?
For time crimes. Duh.
That's enough out of you, buster.
Hey, it's Booster.
I'm Booster Gold, okay?
Yo, dude! Ow...
Mike... Booster, what the hell is this?
I hope you don't have any plans
for the near future,
'cause we're about to spend
a lot of time together.
In jail.