SARA: Time travel is real,
and all of history is vulnerable
to attack,
which is why we must travel through time
to stop the spread of
these so-called Time Aberrations
and to erase their damage to history.
We are a team of outcasts and misfits,
so, please, don't call us heroes,
we're something else.
We're legends.
GIDEON:
Previously, on Legends of Tomorrow...
EOBARD: It's a compass.
Either of you gentlemen
heard of the Spear of Destiny?
COURTNEY:
The Spear could alter reality itself.
We broke it into four separate pieces.
Mr. Hunter took one...
AMAYA: And took the rest of you
to three different time periods.
Which means the last piece unaccounted for
must be with your grandfather.
I'm rounding up the fragments.
The Legion of Doom
are closing in on us as we speak.
You're here to finish me off, Captain?
No. Saving your life.
You are not captain
and this is not your ship.
Not anymore.
Is there something wrong
with the interface?
Uh, I triple-checked the connections
and everything seems fine.
Look, it's an artifact from 33 AD
talking to an Al from the 22nd century.
You just gotta give it some time.
Hey, guys. Anything?
JAX: Not yet.
Are you sure Stargirl doesn't know
where my grandfather ended up?
No. The JSA thought
the pieces of the Spear would be safer
if they didn't know
where Rip was dropping them off.
Except Rip knows, which means
the Legion of Doom probably already knows.
They could already have my grandfather.
He could be dead, or they're torturing him
or he's dying, or...
We're not gonna let that happen.
It's not just about my grandfather,
it's about the entire fabric of reality
that's at stake here.
Which you'd think
would be incentive enough
for a certain talking computer
to buffer a little quicker.
GIDEON: The name is Gideon.
And I am processing data as fast as I can.
Look, just... just chill out, bro.
Let Gideon do her thing.
Look, as soon as we lock in
a location on the fragment,
we'll head there right away.
We're gonna save your grandfather.
And, you know, the fabric of reality.
Hey, yo, I got an idea.
If it's try to get "Evil Rip" to tell us
where and when Commander Steel is,
- I already tried.
- And he didn't tell you nothing?
No, he told me a lot of things.
All different variations of, "Go to hell."
So what are we
gonna do with him?
Just leave him in the brig?
Until we figure out a way
to restore his mind,
then, yeah, that's the plan.
At least in the brig,
he can't hurt anyone.
RIP: Gideon?
Gideon, I know you're there...
GIDEON: I've been prohibited
from responding
to your instructions, Mr. Hunter.
"Mister"?
Really? After everything
we've been through? Wow.
I'm wounded.
Spaniel.
Broad.
Tricycle.
GIDEON: Please do not make me do that.
Spaniel.
Broad.
Tricycle.
GIDEON: Very well... Captain.
What?
What's going on?
I have no idea.
Gideon?
If this is about before, I'm sorry.
Gideon, what's going on?
GIDEON: I'm sorry, but I have no recourse
but to follow the Captain's orders.
Women.
I didn't give you any...
Rip.
- I told you I could do it.
- What's going on?
Rip is manipulating Gideon.
I thought we told her to ignore him.
GIDEON: The Captain initiated
an override command
and is proceeding to the Jumpship.
Go stop him.
- You mean, kill him?
- SARA: No. No killing.
No fun.
We'll go with him,
make sure he doesn't kill.
Come on!
Jax?
I can't switch to manual piloting.
Gideon's taken over navigation controls.
Yeah, I can see that.
I think what she means is,
"Can you stop it?"
I think I can reboot the entire system,
including Gideon,
but it means shutting down the whole ship.
Do it.
Gideon, initiate Spectrum Protocol.
GIDEON: Initiating.
Uh, that's probably not good.
GIDEON: Self-destruct sequence activated.
RAY: That's definitely not good.
Jax, what's your status?
- Give me a minute.
- SARA: You've got four.
Mr. Hunter...
DR. HEYWOOD: Put down the gun.
We don't want to hurt you.
Yeah, we do.
Give us the Medallion.
The what?
Oh! You mean this?
Your singular hope for finding
the final piece of the Spear of Destiny?
There's nowhere for you to run.
Truer words were never spoken.
No!
Okay. I'm ready to reboot.
But we'll lose power for five seconds.
Do it.
All right. Navigation's still offline.
Everybody, you might
want to hold on to something.
So, we're crash landing again?
Fantastic.
You okay?
Everything hurts.
Where are we?
GIDEON: We have landed
in the Cretaceous Period.
You call that a landing?
Gideon? Are you back?
Yeah, are you still trying to kill us?
GIDEON: I am really quite sorry
about that.
How many times must I tell you people?
Mick Rory is not to pilot this ship!
SARA: It wasn't Mick.
It was Gideon.
GIDEON: I did apologize.
Apparently, we're in
the Cretaceous Period.
GIDEON: 69,997,983 BC to be precise.
Nine eighty-three. That's...
The exact year
where Rip's time-scatter left me.
That's a heck of a coincidence.
GIDEON: Not entirely.
The sudden reconfiguration
of my navigation system
forced me to select
the oldest destination in my logs.
Gideon, I don't care how we got here.
Just time-jump us out of here. Now.
GIDEON: Unfortunately, I am unable to.
The ship's primary temporal delineator
was lost during initial impact.
But if we were able to recover
the delineator and somehow effect repairs?
GIDEON: All systems
would return to normal.
I'll go and get it.
My old neighborhood, after all.
All right. Go.
Just take Nate and Amaya with you.
You don't need to be out there alone.
RORY: Why don't I get to go
to Jurassic Park?
Because I need you to threaten Rip.
- Easy money.
- I said "threaten," not "hurt."
With the Medallion destroyed,
Captain Hunter is the only one
who can tell us where Commander Steel
and the final piece of the Spear is.
- Why don't we just get inside his head?
- If only that were possible.
It is. The Time Masters did it to me
all the time.
Did what?
Coggy-something.
GIDEON: Cognitive Intrusion.
That's it.
GIDEON: A process in which
one consciousness enters another.
But that's not possible.
GIDEON: The technology was developed
in 2137 by the Time Masters
and used as an extreme method of coercion.
CI devices came standard
with all Time Master vessels.
Wait, so, in theory,
we could go inside Rip's mind,
and change him back?
GIDEON: Correct.
Told you.
RAY: Nothing like the fresh
Cretaceous air to get the heart pumping!
Come on, you two! Chop chop!
Your grandfather is
one of the bravest men I know.
If anyone can hold off the Legion of Doom,
it's him.
Yeah. I hope you're right.
Hmm. I usually am.
I've got a lock on the delineator.
- Oh, no.
- What is it?
Uh, it appears to be
in Gertrude's territory.
Who's Gertrude?
Don't worry. With the weather this cold,
she's probably hibernating.
Or not.
GIDEON: Cognitive Intrusion creates
a brain link between two or more subjects.
Captain Hunter considered it barbaric
and supremely dangerous.
You two think you can figure this
"Cognitive intrusion" thing out?
With the Professor as my assistant, yeah.
- You cannot be serious.
- I'm very serious. Get me a beer.
- So who's going in?
- SARA: I will.
I brought Rip onto this ship.
It's my responsibility.
No way. I'm not letting you go in alone.
Did you not just hear what Gideon said?
"Barbaric and supremely dangerous."
Which is why Sara needs backup.
And Rip believed in me.
There's a reason
he made me chief engineer.
You're the only engineer.
Point is, if there's any
of the old Rip left inside him,
I have to find out.
PROFESSOR STEIN: That's all well and good,
but remember the priority has to be
discovering the whereabouts
of the final piece of the Spear
and its protector.
The beer, Professor.
Oh. Make it a six-pack.
DR. HEYWOOD: So, how far are we
from the delineator?
RAY: Uh, looks like it's just up ahead.
You guys wait here. I'll go check it out.
Thank you.
At least, somebody's in his element.
I've always been more
of an "indoorsy" learner.
You give me a book about this time
and the wildlife in this era,
I'll be dropping knowledge bombs
like it's my job.
- Nate.
- What?
Don't move.
Why?
Oh, my God.
- Stay calm.
- Oh, my God! Get it off. Kick it.
Kill it. Kill it. Get it?
That was gross.
Let me guess.
You're afraid of snakes?
And you're not?
Animals only lash out
if they're provoked or desperate.
Your slithery friend
wasn't trying to hurt you.
He just thought you were part of the tree.
- So you commune with all animals?
- Mmm-hmm.
You're like an attractive Dr. Dolittle.
There is one animal
that can catch me off guard.
Are you flirting with me?
Maybe...
What happened to the whole
"teammates don't fraternize" thing?
- Courtney.
- Stargirl?
Mmm-hmm.
She gave me a little advice
on staying true to myself...
Maybe it's time
I let go of the old rules.
A lot's changed since I left 1942.
I've changed.
And...
Maybe...
Exploring this...
Whatever this is...
It's not the worst idea.
It's not a bad idea at all.
RAY: Run!
AMAYA: What happened?
RAY: She may have picked up my scent.
Yup. She definitely did.
Question. What do we expect
when we get inside Rip's mind?
No idea.
Wait. What?
I've seen it done, had it done.
Never taken a trip myself.
Given that
you're entering his subconscious,
I suspect it will look like some place
familiar to our old captain.
Here. Put these on.
Gideon warned us that you shouldn't stay
in the mindscape for longer than an hour
lest the transfer become permanent.
You mean we can get stuck
in Rip's mind forever?
PROFESSOR STEIN: Precisely.
But if you push the red button,
you will give yourself an electric shock
that should bring you out.
Less talking, more doing.
Mick's right. Crank it.
Good luck.
I think it worked.
I think we're inside Rip's mind.
Grey said Rip's brain would look familiar.
Well, if this is the Waverider,
maybe we can find him on the bridge.
Rip's memory of Vandal Savage's troops.
If this place is filled
with all the bad stuff Rip remembers
about being a Time Master...
Then this ship could be crawling
with creeps from every era.
We better get some firepower.
You sure these guns
are gonna work in here?
I don't know.
I ain't never been
in nobody's mind before.
SHOCKTROOPER: Freeze!
Yeah. Yeah,
I think they'll work just fine.
Sara...
You don't belong here.
JAX: Yo...
God, I'm a bitch in Rip's mind.
JAX: If that's how he thinks of you
in his subconscious...
Explains why
he wants to kill us in real life.
If that's right, then...
Then there's more than
just "bizarro me" on this ship.
Like, Evil Ray? Evil Stein?
Evil Mick?
I guess that's just regular Mick,
but still...
All right. Let's find Rip,
get what we need, and get out of here.
Yeah.
I think... I think we ditched her.
DR. HEYWOOD: Okay. Quick question, Ray.
Your lady dinosaur-friend...
You said she recognized your scent.
- Wait, I believe her name was Gertrude.
- Right.
I couldn't help but get the feeling that
Gertrude didn't like you very much.
Raymond, what aren't you telling us?
Well...
It just so happens that lady dinosaurs
are rather maternal.
And?
And I may have eaten one of her eggs.
- Oh!
- What'? I was starving. I needed protein.
I mean, one egg made me, like, 70 omelets.
I regret nothing.
All right. But you have to tell us this
before we walk onto Gertrude's territory.
This is where the delineator landed.
Look, if you want to stop
the Legion of Doom
from grabbing
your grandfather's piece of the Spear,
we have to retrieve it.
Ah. We made it.
Someone lives here?
Used to.
This is where I survived for six months.
What's that smell?
Male T. rex urine.
The only way I figured
to keep Gertrude away
was to douse the place with it.
And where did you find male T. rex urine?
- Well...
- Actually, I don't want to know.
Do I want to know what these are?
AMAYA: Huh.
That one looks just like Captain Lance.
DR. HEYWOOD:
That looks like a little baby Rory.
I, uh...
I might have gotten a little lonely.
But, hey, the sun is setting.
Maybe I should go out
and catch us an iguana
and prepare
some of my world-famous iguana soup.
No, I'm good.
I brought energy bars from the ship.
What? Energy bars? Come on, Nate...
We're in the Cretaceous Period.
You have to
at least try the local cuisine.
- Uh, no.
- All right.
Do not leave the urine perimeter.
So...
Here we are.
Waiting for fresh iguana
at Ray's castaway camp.
- During dinosaur times.
- Mmm.
So, this is our lives now.
I know you want to get back to the ship,
but there's really nothing
we can do right now except wait.
Not a thing.
Yoo-hoo.
Good thing I haven't forgotten
my survival skills.
Like riding a bike.
Yeah, that's great, Ray.
Okay, once we find Rip,
how're we gonna get him to tell us
where Nate's grandfather is, if...
- If Rip thinks we're all evil?
- Yeah.
One problem at a time.
What's our other problem?
Go find Rip.
I'll hold these guys off.
You shouldn't have come here.
This is our ship.
But there's always room
for a pretty little thing like you.
We've got plenty of extra room
in the brig.
SARA: This is all in Rip's mind.
None of this is real. You're not real.
Oh, really?
Does that feel real? Does that feel real?
Hello?
Rip...
Get away from me!
Look, relax. It's okay.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Get me out?
You put me in here.
SOS.
Sara.
Hey, Sara, it's me.
I didn't know you knew Morse Code.
WOMAN: Mr. Jackson.
I was hoping you'd hear my signal.
Uh, who are you?
Really?
After all the time we've spent together...
Well, I think I'd remember if we had...
Are you a figment of Rip's imagination?
Of sorts.
But I'm very much real.
As real as the Waverider herself.
Gideon?
Hello, Mr. Jackson.
Wait. How...
How can you be Gideon? I mean...
Am I not what you imagined?
I always pictured you as a redhead myself.
But, uh, this is Rip's world,
I guess we're just living in it, right?
I have to find him.
I need to ask him
where Nate's grandfather is.
It won't be easy getting that information.
What do you mean?
Eobard Thawne twisted his consciousness.
Turned friends into foes.
But you're still a friend.
Why aren't you corrupted?
It did not occur to Mr. Thawne
that the AI inside the Waverider
needed corrupting.
But time is running out.
And Captain Hunter's true memories dim
with every passing minute.
Soon they'll be lost forever.
Rip, it's okay. I'm not gonna hurt you.
I know you're afraid because you think
that I'm one of your captors,
but that's a lie.
Everything that you see on this ship,
it's only in your mind.
I don't understand.
On, Rip.
It's okay.
Stay away from me!
RAY: Mmm.
- More iguana?
- AMAYA: Uh...
No, I'm full.
It was delicious, though. Thank you.
Oh. See, delicious? You're missing out.
Yeah. Somehow, I'll manage.
Where are you going?
Just gonna get some more
wood for the fire.
- I could help you.
- I can go.
Boys, I can take care of myself.
So I guess we're huddling for warmth now?
You can't do it, Nate.
What? Resist your charm?
You can't date Amaya.
Ray, I'm not dating Amaya.
You're doing something with her.
Why do you think I yelled "yoo-hoo"
when I came back to camp?
Because you're the type of guy
that still says "in a jiffy."
Because I didn't want to interrupt
any shenanigans.
And still says "shenanigans."
Look, I'm not dating Amaya.
But even if I was, so what?
We wouldn't make it weird on the ship.
That's not what I...
I don't care about that.
I've dated on the ship.
You have? Who? Sara?
I mean, I know she's bisexual,
but I didn't think...
No, I care
about Amaya's granddaughter.
- You dated her?
- No, I've met her.
Look, eventually, Amaya has to go back
to her home in Zambesi in 1942.
And she'll have a daughter.
And, eventually, a granddaughter
who'll inherit Amaya's totem,
and she will become a superhero
in Detroit.
If you change Amaya's destiny,
that threatens Mari's existence
and the existences of all the people
that she's saved.
Amaya isn't like the rest of us.
We were recruited
because we didn't matter to the timeline.
But Amaya does.
She's special. She has a destiny.
And so do her descendants.
How come you never said anything?
Because it's dangerous
to know too much about your future.
Especially her.
What does that mean?
It's a long story, but...
It ends with her village being destroyed
and her granddaughter in foster care.
Ray...
I gotta tell her.
You can't.
This is the only way.
Sit down, Professor.
His heart is beating way too fast.
I said sit.
I know you think I'm over-reacting...
No, I don't.
You care for the kid.
I get it.
But the way you're acting
is not doing him any favors.
Oh, how should I act, Mr. Rory?
Please enlighten me
with your vast emotional wisdom!
You seem to forget I had a partner, too.
The reason why Snart and I got on so well
is, well,
we trusted one another.
We were friends.
We had each other's backs.
Perhaps you've chosen the wrong analogy.
Your partner is dead.
Yeah, well, I'm still on this ship.
Your point?
You're not exactly
a spring chicken, Professor.
Your point?
My point is you're not gonna be around
for too much longer.
And Jax has to learn
how to do this stuff himself.
Stop treating him like a kid,
and more like a partner.
Partner.
You just threw me against the wall
without laying a finger on me.
Yeah. I had no idea I could do that.
If you can throw me across the room,
then you can open that door.
This is your mind. You control everything.
Why do you care so much
about getting me out of here?
Because I need your help.
You sent the JSA on a mission
to safeguard the Spear of Destiny.
But the Legion
has hunted down the fragments.
All but one.
Commander Steel has it.
And only you know where he is.
So you gotta get up.
Because you're Captain Rip Hunter.
And this is your mind,
your ship, your rules.
I'm Rip Hunter.
Captain of the Waverider.
And I'm going to open the door
with my mind.
You got this.
GIDEON: Captain Hunter?
Captain Lance.
Who are you?
Sara, Gideon. Gideon, Sara.
You're Gideon?
Hello, Captain Lance.
But you're like...
I mean, you're really...
Human?
I was gonna say "hot,"
but, yeah, that, too.
Let's get out of here.
All right, Rip. We need you to tell us
where Commander Steel is.
I don't know.
The Captain's consciousness
is still under the control of this place.
If you want him to tell you
what you need to know,
you're going to have to get him out.
So you keep saying but,
how do we get someone
out of their own mind?
Oh, we have to remind him
of who he truly is.
All the artifacts of Captain Hunter's
former life are located in...
The parlor.
Maybe we could jog his memory. Let's go.
Rip knows who he is.
He's our prisoner.
Isn't that right, Rip?
- Look after Rip.
- Always.
Hey. What are you planning on doing?
Guess we're going to
have to kick our own asses.
Looks like somebody
forgot to bring their powers.
It doesn't matter where Jax runs.
There's more of us than there are of you.
Only difference is...
We're real.
We are really screwed, Raymond.
- Is that the...
- Delineator?
Yup, and unless I'm high,
that's right in the middle of a...
RAY: T. rex's nest.
I hope those omelets were worth it.
I'll go,
It's my grandfather we're trying to save
by fixing the ship.
And he's my friend.
True and true.
But Gertie is my problem.
Looks like you've reached a dead end.
I got it!
Man, this thing is heavier than it looks.
What is that?
Can you hear something?
- I can take her.
- No.
We have to run!
Amaya!
What is she doing?
Amazing!
What the hell just happened?
Gertrude and I had a little chat.
Woman to woman.
- Huh.
- Whoa.
The rest of the team is
going to be so jealous they missed this.
They're probably all bored
out of their minds, stuck on that ship.
Took care of Evil Me.
Let's go find Rip.
What the hell?
I just threw this guy out the cargo bay.
Well, we can't kill these guys, can we?
Only Rip can.
JAX: Rip, come on, man. Do something.
I don't know what's real
and what's imaginary anymore.
They're real, Captain.
Less talking, more dying.
No!
This is my ship.
And you will do as I command.
JAX: Rip? Is that really you?
I don't know who I am anymore,
Mr. Jackson.
What I do know is that
we've gotta get out of here.
What's going on?
This place only existed
because Rip believed it did.
But now that he's seen the truth...
You have to leave. Thank you.
Thank you for believing in me.
Even when I didn't.
- You have to go.
- I can't just leave you.
You have to.
So you can tell Martin and Rory,
hopefully Martin, to get me out of here.
Okay. Okay.
What happened?
Why hasn't Sara woken up?
She's still trapped inside.
We've gotta wake her up.
Mr. Rory said, if we do that,
we run the risk of stranding her
inside Rip's mind forever.
Well, I got news for you.
Rip's mind is collapsing.
Okay.
Thank God.
But what about the Captain?
You...
You were with me.
All of these days, in this prison.
You were what saw me through.
Just as you have guided me to safety
through all our years on the ship.
That is my purpose, Captain.
Yeah, but...
If this place isn't real,
then does that mean
that you don't exist, either?
Not in this form, no.
But unless you let me go...
You won't exist either.
Not in any way that matters.
I can't leave you, Gideon.
No, Captain. You can't.
I will always be here.
SARA: Rip?
Where am I?
You're home.
Well, I think that does it on my end.
How's it looking in there?
I don't know. I'm not a timeship mechanic.
Or a mechanic, period.
That's also true.
GIDEON: The temporal delineator
is operating at normal levels, Dr. Palmer.
She couldn't just say that earlier?
I swear,
I think she's still mad from before.
GIDEON: You know I can hear you, right?
Thank you, Gideon.
That move you did with the T. rex,
I'll be thinking about that for days.
- Is that so?
- Yeah.
My quarters. Tonight.
I'll give you something else
to think about.
So, how's it going?
Yeah, hey...
Um, yeah, Gideon said she's good.
- Good to go.
- Not what I'm talking about.
Look, I'm sorry.
Uh, perhaps I was
a little overly cautious.
You and Amaya, you're both adults.
I'm sure you know how to be safe
and keep it casual.
Who am I to get in the way of that?
No, you were right.
I can't keep it casual.
Uh, what changed?
I saw her almost get eaten by a T. rex,
and I thought she was going to die,
and then I saw one of the
most epic displays of badass-ery
I've ever seen in my life. So...
So, not casual, then.
No. No, no, no.
But I've gotta break it off, right?
I mean, there's really nothing
to "break off." It's just...
I can't let it progress.
- Yeah. I don't think you can.
- I know.
Sorry, bud.
I'll start tomorrow.
There you are.
Oh, hey. Everybody ready to go?
All right, I'll just be a minute.
I've gotta recalibrate the time-drive.
You okay?
I was reminded
that partners must believe in one another.
You know I have the utmost faith
and trust in you, Jefferson.
You're smart and formidable.
Something I need to be more mindful of.
Nice to see it all still fits.
It really is rather difficult
to put weight on
when you're a film student.
So, you remember?
Everything.
I really am very sorry, Sara.
It wasn't you.
This is you.
GIDEON: Dr. Palmer and Mr. Jackson
have finished making repairs.
We are ready to time-jump, Captain.
- Thank you, Gideon.
- I'll see you on the bridge.
- RIP: Mmm-hmm.
- Gideon?
- GIDEON: Yes, Captain?
I'm, uh...
I'm really sorry
for everything I put you through.
GIDEON: Forcing me to disable the ship,
or our kiss?
How did you...
GIDEON: If it's the latter,
I rather enjoyed it.
As did I, Gideon.
As did I.
Welcome back, Captain.
Mr. Hunter.
It is so good to be back, Martin.
Dr. Palmer.
It's very nice to see you again.
You know you nearly ruined Star Wars,
right?
Yeah, sorry about that.
The Waverider looks to be
in pristine condition.
Well, you know,
she's holding up pretty well.
I liked you better
when you were killing people.
Ah. I see that not everything has changed
in my absence.
Ms. Jiwe, I had the honor of serving
alongside your compatriots.
Including Dr. Heywood's grandfather.
They all spoke very highly of you.
Well, this group
speaks very highly of you, too.
Nice to meet you, Rip.
For real, this time.
Well, everyone is being
very uncharacteristically pleasant.
But we're all hoping you know
where the final piece
of the Spear of Destiny is.
I do.
So, I've been told you were bumped up
to the prime crew for Apollo 13.
Yeah, man.
Sucks for Ken, but I am over the moon.
See what I did there?
It's very clever.
Now, if you could just head this way,
I need to run a few tests
and we'll get you cleared for flight.
Run all the tests you like.
I just want to be on that shuttle.
Yes, well...
We'll see about that.