Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
I couldn't send Neron into hell
without sending Dez down with him.
I killed the man I loved,
and for what?
John, you have to stop this.
If Desmond isn't dragged to hell
and you don't join the Legends,
the effects could be cataclysmic.
History be bloody damned.
I really care about you.
This thing between us, it isn't real.
It never was.
- What's that?
- I think John just broke time.
Oy, see, check this out.
I got my powers back.
Zari.
Constantine did it.
He changed the timeline
back in New Orleans.
He saved old Dez.
Unfortunately, I have no idea
why you're a cat, Z.
Oh, quit your whinging.
I know it's a pretty raw deal
for you.
Especially 'cause...
well, who knows
what they put in cat food.
On the plus side
you are cute as hell.
Z, it has been an experience.
Now, I'm gonna set the autopilot
to take you back to the Waverider,
but first we're gonna drop me
off somewhere fabulous.
Hope y'all are thirsty for champagne.
Because I'm feeling a little bubbly.
Hello, Red.
Ms. Monroe.
How's lady luck treating you?
Red, it's me. Charlie.
Shape-shifter.
Cheers to Saint Patrick.
What are you doing here?
I haven't seen you
since we escaped from that prison.
Yeah. Hey listen, mate.
You got to stop doing
your leprechaun magic
so out in the open like this,
all right?
I do this all the time.
These humans,
they don't notice anything.
Watch.
Lucky 11. Winner!
Quit doing that.
But I'm just having a little fun.
What's got you so worried?
The Magic Police?
They're called the Legends
and I'm just trying
to stay off their radar
for a little while.
Sounds to me like you're scared.
What, of them?
No, no, no, they're not dangerous.
They're just annoying little
boy scouts, you know?
Reach for the sky,
you filthy animals.
Pretty please.
He asked nicely.
Greetings, gentlemen.
The leprechaun.
You fellas play?
No.
Oh, my God.
Why did you do that?
Marilyn Monroe.
I am killing it
at historical figure bingo.
All right, everyone, calm down.
We just saved your butts
from a very dangerous
magical creature.
Who are you guys?
Hi, Nate Heywood. Monster hunter.
Just wanted you ladies
to know you're in good hands.
Man, Garima is gonna flip
when she hears we met Marilyn Monroe.
Do you think a murderous alien queen
that sprang to life from Mick's
fantasies is into Marilyn?
Yes.
What is up with these guys?
Gideon, any messages
while we were gone?
You missed calls from Barry Allen,
Oliver Queen, and Kara Zor-El.
Sounds like the annual crossover.
Yeah, that's gonna be a hard pass.
Did I tell you Oliver owes me money?
I bet this year
they'll swap costumes.
Oh, Zari.
Well, I'm glad to see that you
made it back to the ship okay.
Okay, I hear you.
You're still mad at me.
Listen, I really need your help.
All right, yeah,
I can see that being a cat
is your main concern right now,
but I still don't know
why you're a cat.
Ms. Tomaz was turned into a cat
during the team's encounter
with a Fairy Godmother.
Gideon, your latest upgrade, smoking.
Thank you, Miss Jiwe.
Amaya Jiwe, yup, that's me.
And may I say your new upgrade
and accent are also smoking.
Oh, yeah.
You know, I'm just trying
something out.
Yeah, okay, one last question.
Why are the Legends homicidal
wankers now?
If you're referring to the Custodians
of the Chronology,
their policy towards
magical creatures
has been shoot on sight
since their disastrous encounter
at Woodstock.
Right. Thanks, Gideon.
Must be fallout from Constantine
altering the timeline.
Right, this zero tolerance
bollocks ends now.
Hey, people!
I have an announcement to make.
Please, gather around.
Come listen.
So, I know our shoot-first,
ask-questions-never policy
has lead to some interesting
decorations,
but it's time to change.
From now on we are going
to capture the magical creatures
and bring them to the Bureau
like we are supposed to.
Why are you looking at me weird?
Well, just seems like a shame
to change our policy now.
Considering we're so close
to capturing our white whale.
That's a Moby Dickreference.
And what is your white whale?
The only creature
we haven't been able to capture
because it's quite elusive.
Maybe because it has the ability
to change shape.
Shape-shifter!
How dare you step on this ship
and pretend to be our dead captain.
What?
Wait, Sara's dead?
Yeah, that's why we know
you're not Sara.
Is that why you guys are like this?
Like what?
Hunting down magical creatures
like it's a...
Yes!
Damn it, Garima.
I called dibs on killing
shape-shifter last week.
You know what? He did.
You remember when we were roasting
that little baby Gryphon,
which was delicious, by the way,
but you guys got into an argument
about who actually killed it,
so then Ray got upset
and he was like, "Hey,
I wanna kill the shape- shifter."
Oh, it heals itself
and turns into Amaya.
This is not good.
- Kill her again!
- I get to kill her this time.
After her!
Zari. Oh, bollocks.
Go, go! Come on, Ray!
Hey, hey...
Make sure she doesn't steal anything!
They've become maniacs.
Okay, this is bad.
What, Constantine?
Yes, this is his fault.
He needs to help us fix this,
but where is he?
Nice work, Zari cat.
I can't very well walk around here
looking like this.
Oh, hush, it's still me
despite the insane grin on my face.
I don't remember there being
a memorial here.
Sara Lance struck down by unicorn.
Bollocks.
Gary, you're late.
Sorry, Mr. Heywood,
my cat-sitter quit on me, so...
This place is going to hell
in a hand basket.
Yeah, it's my bad, sir.
Look, the Custodians
of the Chronology
just destroyed a freaking leprechaun.
All right, you know what?
If you see them, tell them they're
getting a scream-down from me.
Oh, one more thing, Mr. Heywood.
Have you seen
John Constantine around?
Is that a joke?
He's been in confinement for months.
You put him there.
- Idiots.
- Right.
This isn't the when,
when I'm supposed to be.
Johnny? Johnny?
No, the truth is not the truth!
All right, this is not the when,
when I'm supposed to be.
You should go.
This was real charming.
Reality is fractured, but the pieces,
they speak to each other like light
between broken mirrors.
John Constantine.
Confined for becoming
dangerously unstable
after suspected time crimes.
Are you real? Do you exist?
Because it's really hard
to tell these days.
Yup, bloke's gone cuckoo.
I sense a familiar face.
Who is that?
Z? Z, Is that you?
Why the transmogrification?
Let's get this sorted out.
Yeah, all right, I'm sorry,
but this is the only way
that you will know your true self.
Oh, finally.
Hairball.
Because of you dicks,
I have been a cat for so long.
Do you know
where this tongue has been?
Places.
I wasn't sure that reversal
was gonna work
because I've been feeling a little,
you know, insane lately.
Yeah, well, you only have
yourself to blame.
Wait, what?
You created a time wave
when you changed your past
with Desmond.
Because you're the epicenter,
your experience of this timeline and
that one both exist in your brain.
Just give me a break here.
All right, what you're trying
to say is that I broke time?
Yes, back in New Orleans.
Sure, you don't have to live
with the guilt of damning Desmond,
but you also never joined
the Legends.
Without John's help
with the unicorn at Woodstock,
Sara died, which made
the Legends into killers.
Well, there's only one way
to fix this.
We go to back to Woodstock
and we save Sara.
- Yeah.
- No!
Guys, you're not listening to me.
You have to go to New Orleans
and set history back on track.
Whoa, whoa, Z.
You're suggesting a total reset
of the timeline.
What we need is a surgical strike.
Now, if we save Sara,
then the Custodians
of the Chronology never exist.
I keep my powers,
Dez is de-demoned, Bob's your uncle.
I'm sorry, guys.
I have to stop you before you
before you make this any worse.
All right, then.
I'm sorry, love.
Until you can learn
to stay out of my way, then you...
are a cat.
- In the mood for a prison break?
- Oh, yes I am.
Is the coast clear?
How much of that did you hear?
Nothing at all.
Nothing about breaking out
or hacking history.
Please don't turn me into a cat.
Well, I didn't turn her into cat.
I returned her to being a cat,
which is considerably easier,
believe me.
But if you gotta,
maybe a Calico and real fluffy.
Okay, I'm ready. Do it.
- What are we gonna do with her?
- I have no idea.
You don't have to do anything.
I wanna help.
You do?
The Custodians of the Chronology
must be stopped.
They turned my Kaupe friend
into a rug.
So, if you're trying to defeat them,
I want in.
Watch the bumps, yeah?
- Oi!
- Someone might hear you.
Red Alert, the Waverider
is landing. Red Alert.
Oh, man, the Custodians are here.
Could things get any worse?
Wait, stop right there.
Are you me?
Yes.
From the future.
Do I ever find love,
or at least my sunglasses?
They might be in my other pants.
Yes, Gary, all that and more.
It's the Custodians!
Notify Mr. Heywood.
But right now, I need you
to delay the Custodians.
Okay. Oh, but be careful.
There's been reports
of a shape-shifter on the loose.
Yeah, I know that already.
Because I'm you
from the future, dummy.
Okay. Okay.
Come on.
We gotta find a place to hide.
Knock, knock, anybody home?
There's a letter on the desktop
Come on, hurry up!
Let me out of this thing.
Oh, God.
Where are we?
This is Ava's office, but she's gone.
Gone, gone?
I'm right here, you idiots.
Dad, we tracked a shape-shifter here,
so we're gonna need you to stand down
and let us do our job
and bag it for you.
Your job, son,
is to bring the creatures
back to the Bureau alive.
Not leave their insides
strewn through history.
It's called payback
for what they did to Sara,
and don't get in our way.
Sharpie? What happened to you?
I'm allowed to grieve in my own way.
Why the hell are you
out of your cell?
Well, plans change, luv.
Are you sure you're okay,
Director Sharpe?
I'm fine!
Okay, I'm just taking some time
to get my head together
after Sara was unicorned.
I'm really sorry about that.
Things are not as they seem.
- Amaya?
- No.
Well, it's a long story,
but time is, well, broken.
- What are you talking about?
- Well, you see,
you're living in a timeline
that doesn't exist,
and we are from a timeline
where your hair is still blonde.
Okay, I don't have time
for this timey-wimey crap.
No, no, this is the truth.
Now, listen.
The Custodians of the Chronology
are actually the Legends of Tomorrow
and they're the good guys, mostly.
Yeah, and the kicker is Sara
is supposed to be alive.
Did you say Sara's alive?
- Yeah.
- I knew it!
I knew something was wrong.
I mean, I like the Indigo Girls,
but they should not be a way of life.
Then let's help them
set things right.
What do you guys need from me?
Well, well, well, look
who's helping our magical fugitive.
Smith! Take position.
We were looking for you.
Got eyes on suspects.
Thought you might want
to have some fun.
I got 12 gauges of fun right here.
That's it.
I'm placing you all under arrest.
Shut your mouth, pops.
Go!
Take cover!
Get them out of here!
I'll cover you. Go save Sara.
Did they really all
just kill each other?
Don't think about it.
And we'll go back in time
and we'll fix things.
We have to.
Target ahead.
Arming the weapons now.
Is that what I think it is?
Twilight Sparkle come to life.
We didn't screw things up
for the better this year.
We screwed things up
for the more magical.
- Yes!
- Nice shot!
Who the hell's in the jump ship?
Who cares? Mission accomplished.
And you guys thought
we needed Constantine.
Yeah, we saved Sara's life.
Now that should fix everything.
The Custodians should be back
to being the Legends,
and Zari should no longer be a cat.
All right, this might be
a crossed wired thing
in my brain, but that is still
a cat sitting there, isn't it?
Killing the unicorn
didn't solve the problem.
No, Zari, we're not going
back to New Orleans.
We need to find out what's wrong
with this timeline and fix it.
All right, we go back to the Bureau,
figure out our next step.
Charlie, come on. Talk to me, love.
What's happening?
Is everything normal?
No.
In fact, things are pretty far
from normal.
No reason to panic.
We still got this.
Right, we'll find out
how the boys died in this timeline,
then we'll go back and save them,
and hopefully when they return
they won't be magical
creature murderers.
Right, sounds so simple.
Hey, watch it.
Out of the way, suckers.
Make way for S.O.S.
What the hell is S.O.S.?
Good morning, Sirens.
Good morning, Hank.
Well, I hope you're ready
to go to work today
because we have one hell
of a case on our hands.
If anyone knows what happened
to the guys, it'll be them.
Hang tight on the ship.
Looks like I'm joining the S.O.S.
All right, ladies.
Weapons check.
Way ahead of you, babe.
My pistol's hot and ready.
Hey, girls. Save some fun for me.
Amaya, what are you doing here?
We thought you went back to 1942.
I did, but then I heard
about your monster problem,
and, well, I couldn't stay away.
It's perfect timing.
We are up to our peaches
with magical creatures
and about to kick some ass.
I'm in.
Johnny, just be honest with me.
This thing between us, it isn't real.
It never was. It doesn't exist.
Get it together, John.
Come on. Get your head together.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I know what you're thinking.
You want me to put things
back the way they were,
but that's not gonna bloody happen.
No, I'm not all right to be honest.
So, what kind of fun costumes
are we gonna need for this mission?
We don't do costumes anymore.
Yeah, we stopped
so we could streamline missions.
Yeah, why get all dressed up
if we're just wasting
these magical creatures
straight away.
I mean, please tell me you don't keep
a trophy room of their skulls.
What do we look like? Barbarians?
- No, we just toss them.
- You what?
Yeah, ever since
that Fairy Godmother killed
Nate, Ray, and Rory
we just waste any magical creature
that comes in our path.
No questions asked.
Well, they can't all be bad.
We haven't met a good one.
Hey, how is Zambesi?
- Who?
- Zambesi.
Where you're from.
It's great. Yeah, it's, like, chill.
Super chill.
If I do what you ask,
I'd be sending Desmond to hell.
Yeah, I know, maybe
I deserve this insanity.
Oh, you're all soft.
Oy, wake up, losers.
I know how to fix it.
Right, we got to take care
of the Fairy Godmother in Salem.
Fire up the ship.
I'm heading up there now.
Cor blimey.
No more tea and crumpets
for this dodgy doppelganger.
Hard Drive here knew
you weren't really Amaya all along.
I'm equipped to detect
shape-shifter pheromones.
How fortunate our white whale
swam right into our net.
What is with you guys
and white whales?
Oh, you really think
you three can take me?
Oh, I can take you alone.
Damn it. Get back here!
Oh, hey.
How were the Sirens in Space-Time?
Well, they're not the Custodians.
They may actually be worse.
Now, let's go save the lads.
The three of you have been
so rude with your nasty attitude.
It will be ever so sublime
To slowly choke you up with vines
Whatever you're gonna do, Charlie,
you better make it fast.
I got this.
A peach or a cherry
Any good thing to make us so merry
Prudence.
Fairy Godmother, are you finished?
That was fast.
Yes, and I was thinking,
if I'm to be your Fairy Godmother,
you must start behaving
like a proper young lady.
How do you mean?
Oh, nothing dreadful
or out of the ordinary.
Just chores, daily baths,
church service each morning,
and you must start eating broccoli.
But I don't want all that.
Well, until our bond is severed,
I'm afraid that's the way it must be.
Now, eat the broccoli.
Fairy Godmother, I relinquish you.
That's cool.
I alone may become satiated
When you're all asphyxiated
My bond with Prudence
has been severed.
Oh, fiddlesticks.
You know, I hate to jinx us,
but I really think
we nailed it this time.
I just hope you guys are right.
What's wrong?
What are you looking at?
There something on my nose?
Bollocks.
- Anything yet?
- Don't rush me, luv.
Who knows what surprises wait
for us in here.
Looks like there's reptilians
in the Renaissance.
Sounds like a team meeting.
I'll just pop in
and say hello, shall I?
So, put on your
period-appropriate boots
because we are going lizard stomping.
Oh, hey, everybody, look.
It's our good friend,
John Constantine.
Yay.
What the...
Flying through history
Solving some mysteries
We give bad guys the boot
In super hero suits
We'll win our victory
By stopping witchery
So they've got magic
Well we've got heart and fabric
Puppets of Tomorrow
Puppets of Tomorrow today
Welcome to
DC's Puppets Of Tomorrow.
"Fraggle Rock" is going on here?
Well, today we learned about
the importance of cooperating.
And about the number three.
And about a famous man
from history named Napoleon.
I think I need a drink.
We can help.
When you're thirsty for a drink
And you just can't reach a sink
You gotta ask for a help
No, stop.
All right, please, please.
No more singing.
Just tell me, why are you puppets?
Because Rory called us a bunch
of Time Bureau puppets.
Yeah, and then he ran off
with his new partner in crime.
So, did you figure out
how I turned into a damn puppet?
Yeah, it's worse than I thought.
After we managed to separate
the Fairy Godmother from Prudence,
she somehow glommed onto Rory.
You can probably figure out the rest.
Well, we're just gonna have
to keep fixing what's broken
until we get it right.
Yeah.
Damn it.
Nope.
No plaques.
No plaques. No plaques.
We did it. I'm shocked to bits.
Everyone's alive, Zari's human again,
and I still have my powers.
That's smashing news, luv.
Yeah, I mean, sure,
it's got a few cracks,
but fixed the timeline.
See that, Zari.
John, are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, it's, never better.
John.
- What happened?
- Passed out, mate.
He didn't just pass out.
His brain can't handle
this wad of bandages
you call a timeline.
I can take the pain, luv.
What if you can't?
What if you die, John?
What happens to all the people
who need you alive and Constantine-y?
Yeah, well, you can leave
that to the real heroes, all right,
because I'm done giving a damn.
Oh, I see.
This is isn't about saving
Desmond anymore.
It's an excuse for you
to give up on yourself.
Just leave him alone, will you?
You think because there's no plaques
the world is fixed?
I promise you,
it's just as messed up out there
as it is in John's brain.
I know you don't want
to send Desmond to hell,
but that doesn't have to be
the end of the story.
You of all people can find a way
to keep fighting for him.
Go to New Orleans
and set things right.
Don't listen to her.
Come on, John. It's you and me.
We can make this timeline work.
No, Charlie.
We've tried over, and over, and over
to get what we wanted
and it hasn't worked.
Well, Zari's right.
There's still hope for Desmond,
and maybe there's still hope
for your powers too.
Hope?
My powers aren't some magic trick.
They're who I am.
I'm not gonna just sit around
and hope that they come back.
I'll fight for them.
This ain't over.
Not by a long shot.
Ava, I wasn't expecting
to see you here.
Yeah, the Bureau got
an emergency alert
about a magical presence
in New Orleans, 2018.
I thought maybe
we could check it out together.
- Let's get to work.
- Cool.
Jeez.
I didn't live this specific moment,
but I remember it.
It's all part of jumbled,
bloody memory.
By the way, only about ten percent
of what you're saying
makes any sense,
but by all means continue.
Right, so the earliest me
just left for the market.
The other one is upstairs
breaking up with Dez right now,
and when Dez leaves upset,
I stop him.
Put things back to normal.
All right, good luck.
Blimey, that's a lot of ammo.
- Blimey?
- Huh?
Oh, I meant wow.
All right, boys,
orders are shoot to kill.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Shouldn't we discuss what kind
of creature we're dealing with here?
We can't just go in guns a-blazing.
What if whatever's causing
this is just a little misguided?
It's a magical fugitive.
We kill those.
You two head out.
Stay on the comms.
I killed the man I loved,
and for what?
To buy New Orleans
a little more time?
Neron needs souls...
Okay, right, I think,
I think that something should be
landing right here any second now.
I work alone.
Got it.
All right, Gideon,
what are we looking at?
I've located multiple targets
on the ground
each one with a substantial
magical signature.
Do we have a visual yet?
Coming up now.
Wait, that's John Constantine,
and there's more than one of him.
Looks like our shape-shifter
has a shape-shifter friend.
Wait a second, how do you know that
that's not really Constantine
out there?
Because it's John Constantine.
He doesn't time travel.
Believe me. I tried to recruit him.
Okay, so why don't we capture
all three of them
so we can find out
if any of them are the real John?
What is wrong with you?
You feeling okay?
I'm fine.
I'm just a firm believer
in taking precautions.
Precautions. Good one.
Ray, Rory, what's your status?
All right, we're in position,
with our sights on the shape-shifter.
When do we get to shoot?
All right, on my mark, open fire.
Sara, don't.
Damn it, Ava, why not?
'Cause I'm the shape-shifter.
Guys, stand down,
we have a code blue on the ship.
What the hell's a code blue?
Just don't shoot yet.
There's something going on
in your life.
Just be honest with me.
Yeah, do you know what?
This thing between us?
It isn't real. It never was.
It doesn't exist.
You should go.
Yeah, you're right. I should.
But this, this was real, Johnny.
Hey, you, you dropped this.
My phone.
How did you get down here?
You were just upstairs.
Yeah, never mind
about that right now.
I have something
really important to tell you.
You know what? I think you've said
quite enough today already...
No, no, Dez, please.
Give me a minute, all right?
So, you're the shape-shifter.
Why do you look like Amaya?
It is complicated,
but this is how you know me.
What's happened to the Legends
to make you like this?
What do you mean?
You guys are so intent
on killing magical creatures.
Can't you see that this is wrong?
Not really.
Look, now I know this sounds crazy,
but the me that you were just
speaking to upstairs
is my past.
So, you break up
with me out of the blue,
act like a total ass, and suddenly
that's in the past, just like that?
Listen, literally,
that is me from ages ago,
but the person who's standing
in front of you right now
is a little bit older
and he's a little bit wiser.
Sure. Still playing games, clearly.
Look.
I thought this was real.
Yeah, it is real, Dez, and that's why
I moved heaven and earth
so that I could save you
from a lifetime
and eternity of anguish,
anguish that I caused.
Look...
I guess what I'm trying to say
is I'm sorry you ever even met me.
Don't be sorry.
Only a fool would fall in love
with John Constantine
and not expect it to be rocky.
I knew the risks...
and I took them anyway for you.
I'm still pissed at you.
Why can't we just go back
to the ways things were?
That's exactly what I was thinking.
- What is that?
- Know one thing, Desmond.
I'm not quitting on you.
Sara, crazy-looking Constantine
just memory-flashed a civilian.
- Can we shoot him yet?
- Wait for my signal.
I'm dealing with a situation
on the ship.
Constantine might be...
Sara?
- Sara?
- Hold on a second, Ray.
Where did you get that?
Look, I don't know who you are,
or why you are on my ship,
but you're never leaving.
Oh, hello, handsome.
What are you doing standing
in the middle of the street?
I was...
You... you went to the market.
I did.
Next thing I know
I was standing in the street.
I don't, I don't know.
Wait, Sara, please.
Just tell me why you're so intent
on killing magical creatures.
Because that's how we stay alive.
Stop doing that!
- Don't you remember London?
- No.
When you and I first met
and I helped you see the truth
about magical creatures.
And how did you do that?
By being me?
By showing you that I'm not here
to hurt humans.
That not all monsters need
to be put down.
That's cute, but never happened.
What...
How can you not remember?
Bollocks.
Because of Constantine,
you and I never met
and you never changed.
I'm the missing ingredient
in every one of these
botched timelines.
I'm sorry, but all I see is a threat
that needs to be taken out.
Ray, fire when ready.
- So you got eggs?
- I got the eggs.
I got the bread.
Got everything we need.
Souffle?
Souffle, but first things first, eh.
You need to be a part of the team.
Your shape-shifting days
are over, sweetheart.
- No!
- I know who's coming for you.
But choosing a life of magic,
it never leads to a happy ending.
That's the thing about time travel,
there's always a way.
I'm sorry, Dez.
John, you okay?
Yeah, well...
my mind is no longer split in two,
but can't say the same
about my heart though.
You?
Well, lost my powers.
Back to being mortal.
Sorry, guys. It had to be done.
Well, let's go on
and find the Legends, shall we?
Yeah, see if all this was worth it.
Yeah.
Well, everything seems
pretty normal so far.
This isn't over, you dingalings.
You better watch your knees,
Sara Lance.
Oh, no, is everyone a puppet again?
What?
- What are you talking about?
- I'll kill you all!
I got an anti-magic isolation chamber
with your name on it, Mike the Spike.
The usual insanity that passes
for normal around here.
What is this?
Why are you being so weird?
Well, I...
I do have a little bit of a tale
to tell, to be honest.
You fancy a drink?
One of those stories.
Let's go.
Hey, Zari,
I wanted to say that I'm sorry.
For what? For stuffing me into a bag
or almost destroying all of history?
Well, yeah, that too,
but what I'm really sorry about
is that we got off on the wrong foot.
You're a shape-shifter.
Your whole deal is tricking people.
Yeah, but now
I'm being honest with you.
You know, I could have been anyone
when I got my powers back.
Do you know why I kept coming
back to this form?
Because Amaya is very hot?
It's because this is the form I was
when I joined the Legends.
Now, I have been a part
of many crews, and you guys,
well, you're not rubbish.
Listen, destroying history
for personal gain,
it's happened to almost
everyone here.
Rite of passage.
So you think I'm hot then?
I made snicker doodles
with your recipe.
Not bad.
I'm reading your novel.
I'm on the last chapter.
Your females characters
are shallow, libidinous,
and so much fun to read.
- Thanks.
- Yeah, good job, Rebecca Silver?
Nom de plume.
Got it.
So let me get this straight.
They're making love
on the surface of the sun?
It's a metaphor.
Got it.
And the worst part?
It didn't even make
a bloody difference.
I was a fool thinking
I could outrun this fight
flying around with you lot.
Yeah, we tend to fly directly
into fights.
But we do it together,
and we have your back.
Well, as long as you know
what you're getting yourself into
because a demon like Neron,
he doesn't just want to win.
He wants to win
in the cruelest possible way.
Yeah?
The Kaupe escaped?
Here's what I want you to do.
Track him down
and recapture him, or else.
There's been a setback,
but we'll make it right.
Oh, you'd better.