- In 2166, an immortal tyrant
named vandal savage
Conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
And stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan
is opposed by the body
I'd sworn my allegiance to,
the time masters.
In the future, my friends
may not be heroes,
But if we succeed,
They will be remembered
as legends.
Female narrator: Previously
on "legends of tomorrow"...
- I was her.
- Tragedy or heartbreak.
That's how it always ends
if the man's not carter.
[energy surges]
- time master druce?
- You and your band
of rogues have run rampant
Throughout history.
This is why we work alone, rip.
A team is a liability.
- The time masters have issued
omega protocols on all of us.
They've sent the pilgrim.
- Who's the pilgrim?
- The pilgrim is the time
masters' most deadly assassin.
- She's hunting
our younger selves.
- Kaylex druzan,
you have been found guilty
Of time piracy
in the first degree
And sentenced to death
via omega protocol.
The pilgrim has made contact
with your younger self.
- [gasping]
- This will all be over quickly.
- [gasps]
[dramatic music]
♪
- Well done.
Here's your next assignment.
These individuals
have manipulated the timeline
Without authorization
on multiple occasions.
You are hereby ordered to hunt
Down these individuals'
younger selves
And eliminate them.
♪
[sirens wailing]
- This isn't my element.
- [groans]
it's mine.
- Just keep a weather eye open
for the pilgrim.
Gideon calculates a 97% chance
That she will attack
your younger self
In this exact time and place.
- Roll it.
♪
- Young rory's not in there.
- But we found his parents.
They're dead.
- Then where the hell
is he?
♪
[laser fires]
- Come with me
if you want to live.
I always wanted to say that.
[exciting music]
♪
[engine roaring]
- That's younger you?
- What'd you tell him?
- That we work for a secret
agency called a.R.G.U.S.
I think he bought it.
- Course he did.
He's an idiot.
- Hey, no offense,
But do you really think
it's a good idea
To leave him unsupervised?
- You're right.
Have fun.
- You seem calm.
- What, you mean considering
a temporal bounty hunter
Is trying to murder
our younger selves?
- I was gonna put it a little
more delicately
Than that, but yeah.
- I think at some point,
You just learn to live
with a sword over your head.
[dramatic music]
[metal clanking]
Either you're getting better
or I'm getting lazy.
So it seems like you decided
to ignore the advice
From old west you
about not being with ray.
- Ignoring her advice about ray
was your advice, remember?
- Don't listen to my advice.
So did you tell him
what she said?
- Oh, sure.
"hey, ray, by the way,
"the woman I met in 1871 was me.
"and she told me our love
was doomed to fail
Because you're not carter."
- so that was a no?
- Look, ray and I
are happy together.
We should be able to enjoy that
before I have to drop the whole
Doomed-love-affair thing
on his head.
- Yeah, I mean,
Who wants a relationship
based on honesty
And communication?
Ugh.
- Believe me.
A relationship based
on an ancient egyptian curse
Doesn't work much better.
♪
- Mr. Rory.
How are you feeling?
I mean, your younger self.
- Jax is watching him.
- That young man, you,
just lost his family.
You might want
a shoulder to cry on.
- I don't cry, professor.
Oh, and, haircut,
thanks for saving me.
- You're welcome.
You know what I don't get
is why doesn't the pilgrim just
Go back a week earlier
and kill younger rory then?
- 'cause the omega
protocol calls for precision.
Multiple attempts
from the pilgrim
Could do irreparable
temporal damage.
- Which means
she's only got one shot
At killing each
and every one of us.
- And we only have one shot
to extract your younger selves
From the timeline
before she pulls the trigger.
- Sir, based
on the temporal wake generated
By the pilgrim's time ship,
I calculate a 96% likelihood
That she is heading
to starling city circa 2007.
- Pilgrim is targeting
miss lance.
♪
[indistinct police radio]
- Name?
- Lance.
Sara lance.
This is ridiculous.
- Come on.
I thought it was take
your daughter to work day.
- Yeah,
if I was in grade school.
- "daddy, I'm doing a paper
on the criminal justice system.
I want to see what it looks
like on the inside".
- Well, I didn't mean
inside a jail cell.
- Too bad, 'cause
that's the next stop
On our little tour.
- I think you're enjoying
this a little too much.
- Honey, it's the dream
of every father
To keep their daughters
locked up until they're 30.
Maybe even 40.
- [screaming]
- What the--
[overlapping shouts]
♪
[gunfire]
[officers grunting]
- [grunts]
[gunfire, shouting]
♪
- Daddy!
[gunfire, shouting]
- [grunts]
♪
- Get out of here.
Get out of here!
Go, go, go!
♪
[glass shattering]
[shouting]
♪
- [yells]
[blows landing]
♪
[grunting, blows landing]
- God, she's--
- quite the badass.
♪
[pilgrim groans]
- I put her in the cargo bay
with mini-you,
Told them both to stay put.
The less they know
what's going on, the better.
- You sure you want
to leave daddy's little girl
With that punk?
- Even before the league
of assassins,
I knew how to handle
guys like you.
- Has gideon figured out
the pilgrim's next target yet?
- That's peculiar.
- Peculiar or bad?
- Gideon, run another scan
For the whereabouts
of the pilgrim.
- I'm sorry, sir.
The timeline shows
no temporal distortions.
I seem to be unable
to track the pilgrim.
- That doesn't sound good.
- No, it's quite the opposite.
Without a way to track
the whereabouts of the pilgrim,
She could target
any one of you
At any point in time.
♪
- Gideon was tracking
the pilgrim's temporal wake.
I didn't think it was possible
To conceal one's movements
through time.
- Well, it is if the time
masters are on your side.
- How does this all work?
If she can travel
to any place at any time,
She could be killing
any of us right now.
- And if we die in the past--
- we die in the present.
- Wow. So interesting.
How long does it take for
what happens in the past
To affect the present?
Could I be dead right now
and not know it?
Maybe I am dead right now.
Hello? Can anybody hear me?
- No.
- Look, the important
thing is not to panic.
- Somebody's playing
russian roulette
With our younger selves.
Why would we panic?
- Well, there are
a few exceptions.
Kendra's ability to reincarnate
Means that it would
do the pilgrim
No good to target her.
And as a former time master,
To remove me from history
Would be quite dangerous
to the timeline.
- Well, that's convenient.
- And what's that supposed
to mean?
- Nothing.
It just occurs to me
You've never told us
about your past, rip.
And I don't trust
a man with secrets.
- Look, the less information
you have to offer on me,
The less valuable
You are to our now
numerous enemies.
- Like I said, convenient.
- Are they fighting?
- This is not a fight.
It's merely
an exchange of ideas.
- No, not you. Them.
♪
- Ah-ha!
- She slapped me.
- The little weirdo said
That he liked the way
that I smelled.
- I'm usually a lot smoother,
But I'm sort of
freaking out right now.
- You, hands to yourself.
The next time, hit
with a flat palm.
And you...You're not her type.
Now, do I need
to separate you two?
♪
- No.
- Hey, when do I get to go home?
- You're safer here.
Trust me.
- Well, where is here?
And why do you look like me?
Please, will you just tell me
what the hell's going on?
- Look, it's safer
for you if I don't.
And we look alike, because--
Because we're like family.
And I need you to trust me.
- Look, my dad,
he's got to be freaking out.
If he ever lost me--
- He won't lose you.
Ever.
I promise.
♪
- Hey.
Did you know that rip
has a secret stash
Of vintage cereals?
Fruit brute was always
my favorite.
- Are you okay?
- I'm a little on edge.
- You know, we've been
through a lot together,
And you've never quite resorted
to eating sugary cereals.
- Look, I've spent a lot
of my life
Thinking about the future.
And now, I have to think
about the past,
Which is sometimes the present.
And...
The point is, do you know
Where I go to
when things get crazy?
- Which for us is always.
- [chuckles]
I go to those two years
in hub city,
When it was just you and me,
And it felt like we had forever.
- Yeah.
- That's what kept me grounded.
In fact...
Seconds before rip
and the team came back,
I was about--
[screams]
- Ray!
- [groaning]
- What's wrong?
♪
Oh, my god.
Gideon, we need help!
♪
[devices beeping]
What's happening to him?
- He is suffering
from severe internal injuries.
- [groaning]
♪
- Who's doing this?
- A deep scan
of mr. Palmer's timeline
Reveals a temporal anomaly
On December 19, 2014,
In the vicinity
of palmer technologies.
- The pilgrim.
Gideon, get us
to that location now!
♪
[crashing]
- [groaning]
♪
Who are you?
- I'm no one.
We have that in common.
♪
[laser fires]
- We need to get you to cover.
♪
- What is that thing?
Who is she?
Who are you?
♪
- No time to explain.
[laser fires]
- [groaning]
♪
No.
- Rip and the team
are saving you in the past,
And I'm here now.
However long we have, I want
to spend it with you.
♪
- My suit.
[laser fires]
♪
- It works.
- Mr. Palmer's
vitals are stabilizing.
- They did it.
- Actually, I think you get most
of the credit.
I couldn't miss spending
the rest of our lives together.
♪
- I meant it, ray.
I love you.
- I guess you found the ring.
- The ring?
[instrumental music]
♪
- Kind of a strange way
to get engaged, but...
♪
I'll take it.
- What the pilgrim did, the way
She turned our attacks
back on us,
It was as if she was
reversing time.
- It's called
temporal micro-manipulation.
The ability to control time
in one's immediate vicinity.
We are lucky to have
saved dr. Palmer.
- So basically we have no idea
who she's going after next.
- We know it's not rip,
because he doesn't have a past
To go back to.
- Gideon, prepare
for multiple time jumps.
Plot points here, here and here.
[beeping]
- My birthday?
Why are we--
- The only way to ensure
you're not harmed in your past--
- Is to abduct ourselves
as newborns,
Thus removing ourselves
from our future timelines.
It's brilliant.
- It's morally questionable.
- It's suicidal.
If we take too long
in getting them home--
- Then history is altered.
There won't be a home
to go back to.
You'll disappear from the minds
Of everyone
who's ever known you.
- You mean,
my own mom won't even know me?
- My wife.
- Yeah, and my--
Oh, yeah.
I don't have anyone.
♪
- Sure as hell beats dying.
- Hey.
- How's ray?
- Fine.
Um, his younger self
is in the hospital,
So our ray is healing
rather quickly.
- You know, you don't seem
too happy about it.
- I'm not unhappy.
I'm...
I'm engaged.
- What?
- Yeah.
Ray proposed to me
while he was--
You know what,
it's a long story.
- But you said yes.
- At the time.
♪
I...I never thought
about marriage.
I didn't think I was
able to think about marriage.
♪
I don't know what to do.
- That's hard.
♪
Do you like babies?
- Yeah, but that sounds
like doubling down to me.
- I need your help.
And then I'll help
you figure out
What you should say to ray.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
[dramatic music]
♪
- All right, this is just
like any other mission.
The mark may be a newborn,
But it might as well
be a diamond or a microchip.
- You know what?
You're starting
to sound like snart.
Ugh.
[babies crying]
- Okay, which one is snart?
- Look for the one with horns.
- Found him.
- Great, grab him.
Let's go.
- Well, hello, baby snart.
Look at you.
- Kendra, come on.
We don't have time for this.
[babies crying]
Oh, look at those little cheeks.
You are the cutest little baby
In the world.
[babies crying]
- Poor kid.
He's gonna have a rough life
Ahead of him.
- Good thing
we're kidnapping him.
♪
- What are you doing?
- I'm getting us out of here.
- We don't even
know where here is.
[palm scanner beeps]
- Identity confirmed.
Sara lance.
- Let's go.
- Where do you think
you're going?
Give me that.
Inside.
- Is that a baby?
- Yes, and you guys
are in charge of him.
- Wait, I--
- You made five grand
last summer babysitting.
You'll be fine.
- No, I don't do babies.
- You do now.
Think of it as a thank
you for saving your life.
- You better not drop my future
criminal partner.
Otherwise you're
in trouble, comprende?
Hmm.
[baby crying]
- We've got mr. Snart's
younger self.
Next stop is you, professor,
and you, mr. Jackson.
- How strange to imagine,
holding one's infant self.
- Actually, none of you
should participate
In your own abductions.
Let's call it
paradox prevention.
- It's almost worth the risk.
To experience
how our own fathers
Must have felt
the day we were born.
- Yeah, well, not my dad.
He shipped out before my mom
went into labor.
Yeah, he died
two weeks later
In somalia, so...
- I'm so sorry.
- Yeah.
♪
- [groaning]
[steam hissing]
- I think I see the head.
- Oh!
[baby crying]
- Look at that.
What do you think
of jeremy as a name?
- Oh, I think he looks
more like a martin.
- You guys asked
for a doctor, right?
- Yeah, how would we?
- He means that we were
on our way to the hospital
And we saw your automobile.
- Yeah, and this little munchkin
needs a checkup.
Prenatal care,
it's very important.
- He means post-natal.
We'll take him
straight to the hospital.
We'll meet you there.
- What about my wife?
♪
- It's somewhat disconcerting
that my father
Would give me up so willingly
to two complete strangers.
- Well, the 1950s was a much
more trusting time.
Trust me, I lived then.
- He's not in somalia.
- Huh?
- We need to hold off
on taking baby jefferson.
I need to find grown jefferson.
- But rip said that we--
- I doubt very much
that giving the boy
A moment with his
soon-to-be-dead father
Will do the universe any harm.
♪
- What are you doing, gray?
- Trust me, jefferson,
there's someone here
I really think you should meet.
♪
Go talk to him.
- And say what?
- Speak from your heart.
♪
Go.
- You were supposed
to be shipping out.
- How do you know that?
Oh, right.
My transport got delayed.
I told my co
my wife's giving birth.
He got me a pass and a jeep.
And I made it.
I saw him.
My boy.
Which one's yours?
- Oh, oh, no, I'm--I'm--
I'm not a dad.
I just...
I'm here for my family.
♪
- Well, I hope you get
to experience this
For yourself one day.
Imagining all the things my
boy's gonna be when he grows up.
- How do you know?
- 'cause he's my son.
Jefferson jackson,
remember that name.
He's destined for great things.
♪
I've got to go.
Will you give the nurse
a message for my wife?
- You're leaving already?
- Be awol if I don't.
I just want her to know
that I saw my son,
And that I couldn't be
more proud and happy.
And tell her I'll be home
as soon as I can.
Can you do that?
♪
- Wait.
I got to tell you something.
♪
Congratulations.
- Thanks.
Appreciate that.
♪
[babies crying]
[foreboding music]
♪
[babies crying]
[engine roaring]
[dramatic music]
♪
- We're here.
- Where is here?
- Come, I'll show you.
♪
- Again, where is here?
- We need a safe harbor
to keep your younger selves.
♪
- I've been waiting.
It's good to see you.
♪
- It is good
to see you too, mother.
♪
[dramatic music]
- Don't forget to take
your boots off
Before you come back in.
[door slams]
♪
Oi!
Off you go.
- So, this is where rip plans
on keeping our baby selves.
- If all goes
according to plan,
We'll only be here
for a few minutes,
Then presumably never remember.
- When's the last thing
anything went according to plan?
- I don't think
there was a last time.
- I really would sit up
if I were you.
She'll kill you
if she catches you slouching.
Don't be fooled
by appearances.
That woman is as tough as nails.
- Funny how you never
mentioned having a mother.
- Adoptive mother.
Now, can I interest any of you
in some more tea?
- Thank you.
- So, michael--
- Michael?
- That's me.
My birth name.
- The time masters
insist on the adoption
Of new identities
for their protection.
- How do you know so much
about the time masters?
- I work for them.
Oh, don't worry.
My true loyalty
is to my children.
- Thank you.
The time masters
fill their ranks
With children, orphans
Pulled from throughout
the course of history.
- When michael
arrived at the refuge,
He had nothing
but the clothes on his back.
There's a reason
it's called the refuge,
And a reason that it exists
in a secret location in history.
The time masters will never
think to look for you here.
- Thank you for your assistance.
- Look, I know I make a gorgeous
baby, but I should warn you.
You've got your hands
full with me.
- I assure you,
you're not the first tough case
To arrive at my door.
♪
- Where'd you find the match?
- You can always find them.
- Beautiful, isn't it?
Not as beautiful
as a whole house
Going up in flames, though.
- It was an accident.
- Sure it was.
- You don't know me.
You think I wanted
to kill my family?
- I think you fell in love
with your dad's lighter fluid.
I think you fell in love
with the flames dancing around.
But then you realized
you couldn't control them,
And you ran without
waking your family.
The only thing
You were concerned about
was your own skin.
♪
Now, while I'm gone,
There better not be
any accidents.
If there is, I'm gonna
come looking for you.
I'm gonna kill you.
- You sound just like my dad.
♪
[children laughing]
- I couldn't quite bring myself
to leave this place just yet.
- I've made you something
for your travels.
Some mince pies
for your friends.
- My friends.
They're the people
whose relationships
With their friends and family
I've put at risk
to save my family.
- You think you've been selfish?
- I do, yes.
- What a load of old codswallop.
I've always known
That you were brought to me
for a reason, michael.
That you were ready
for great things,
But you won't accomplish
anything by wallowing.
So for goodness' sake,
pull yourself out of it
And get the job done.
- And what about you?
I have put you
in terrible danger.
- You don't honestly
think I'd let
You go away
with my best serving dish
If I didn't think
I'd see you again, do you?
I can manage quite happily
With a house full
of 10-year-old time masters,
So I think I can perfectly deal
with the adult version.
Go on!
- Yes, yes.
Thank you.
[engine roaring]
♪
- Jefferson?
- Hey.
What's up, man, we good?
- Oh, please.
We share a psychic connection.
I know how you're feeling,
and I'm sorry.
I thought affording you time
with your father
Would lift your spirits.
- Yeah.
I--I thought so too.
I just...
I should have said something.
I should've told him about what
happens to him in mogadishu.
I could've saved him.
- You don't know that.
It's highly unlikely
You could've said anything
that would've changed his fate.
- My whole life,
Everything good I ever did,
Every report card,
Every touchdown,
in the back of my mind,
I always wondered, what would
my dad think about this?
♪
- Hey.
I was just on my way
to the bridge.
- No, wait.
Wait, please.
I didn't mean to be a lurker,
But I heard you
and sara talking.
And I get it.
You thought I was dying.
You told me
what I needed to hear.
And it worked.
So if you need a reason,
A way to let me down easy--
- Ray, no.
I want to be with you.
It's just that I know
that we can't last.
- Says who?
- Me.
The woman I met in 1871...
Was me.
And she warned me
That it would end
in heartbreak
If I ever tried
to be with someone--
- Other than carter.
- God, this is just too
complicated.
- No, it isn't, really.
I mean, if I make you happy,
If being with me
makes you happy,
Then you can be happy.
Or you can choose to listen
to some former version
Of yourself
who believes in curses.
When you decide,
let me know.
♪
- Everyone please report
to the main deck immediately.
♪
- What's going on?
- Gideon has intercepted
a trans-chronal beacon.
Gideon, show them.
- This message
is for rip hunter.
I'm going to make this
very quick and very simple.
♪
If I can't find you,
I can find those you love.
♪
- Anna?
- Dad!
- All of them will suffer
And die because of you.
Your family, friends, anyone
you've ever cared about.
Unless you surrender
your younger selves to me.
- So she can erase you
all from history.
- If it's of any comfort,
you won't feel a thing.
As for your loved ones,
I cannot promise
the same thing.
♪
[pounds fist on table]
[engine roaring]
- Gideon, I take it
That the pilgrim's transmission
included a carrier frequency
Through which
she can be contacted?
- Yes, captain.
- Hail her, please.
- What are you planning to do?
- Captain hunter.
- Look, I'm gonna
make this easy.
- I already have.
The lives
of your team's nearest
And dearest
for their younger selves.
- And I'm gonna counter
that demand
With an offer of my own.
I will surrender myself
If you spare the lives
of my crew and their loved ones.
- A noble gesture.
But worthless.
My directive is to eliminate
your entire team, not just you.
- Yes, well,
I'm not talking about me now.
I'm offering you me in the past.
[dramatic music]
Rip hunter before he became
a time master.
Eliminate him, and this team
will never have been.
♪
- If this is some kind
of trick--
- It's no trick.
Enough people have died
at my expense.
Gideon will send you
the location.
And, mr. Snart, your wish
is about to come true.
You're going to meet
my younger self.
♪
- What is this place?
- Neutral ground.
It's a defunct
time masters outpost.
- I thought we were supposed to
be picking up your younger self.
- He's being brought
to us, actually.
♪
- That little boy
was at the refuge.
He's you.
- You got my message?
- I don't approve
of what you're planning.
Not that it ever
stopped you before.
Your younger selves
are all still safe and sound.
- Thank you.
- You're a naughty one.
- That's right.
♪
- I think it's probably
about time that you left.
- Give her hell.
- Where's my dad?
- On board my ship,
along with the rest.
All in perfect condition...
As long as your captain
honors his end of our bargain.
- You'd murder a child?
- I'd murder as many children
As is necessary
to accomplish my mission.
- Do you know what this will do
to the timeline,
Killing a time master?
- In case you've forgotten,
I am sanctioned
by the time masters
To do what my former colleague
chronos here failed to do.
- Enough of that.
♪
Let's get down to business.
- Where's the rest
of your group?
- They're around.
♪
- I'll be taking the boy.
- Before you do that,
We don't believe
for a second
Their loved ones
are on your ship.
- A show of good faith, then.
A prisoner exchange.
Send the boy,
and I'll send the father.
Once I have the future
captain hunter in my possession,
Then I'll release the rest.
♪
- What the hell's going on?
- You don't need to understand.
Only walk.
♪
- You are gonna
be absolutely fine.
I promise.
♪
- As soon
as my dad's in the clear,
Let's light this up.
- Remember,
we wait for ray's cue.
♪
- I'm in position.
- You wanted to see me?
Have I done
something wrong, miss?
- Not yet.
- Now!
♪
- Fool me once.
[laser fires]
[weapons firing]
♪
[explosion]
- [grunts]
♪
- Now, kendra!
- I was willing to proceed
in good faith.
Now you'll watch
those closest to you die.
[gasping]
- Thought you could
snuff me out?
You don't know me at all, miss.
- [screams]
[weapons firing]
♪
- Hey, are you okay?
- Not really.
- Yeah, let me explain.
- You poor boy.
I'll take you.
Are you all right?
- That's you.
- Yeah.
I was a cutpurse
from the age of five.
Starved more than I ate.
I knew what I'd do
if she tried to harm me.
- Lucky for us,
you didn't forget your roots.
- Believe me, mr. Snart,
I've tried.
♪
- There you are.
- The pilgrim
may have been dealt with,
But the omega protocol
is still in effect.
- I'll look after your friends,
don't worry.
- Oh, I know you will, mum.
You did the same for me.
- It must be strange
For you to see yourself
as you were.
- Hmm.
- Do you remember the first day
you were here?
- Yes, I think
I tried to steal your purse.
God, I was a mean
little bastard.
- You were tough.
- I was selfish.
- Well, you were surviving.
- I was home.
- Which is why I know
you'll be back.
♪
- Here to give me
Another "don't burn down
the house" speech?
- You think by hurting yourself,
it's gonna
Make you feel better
about the fire?
- You don't know anything
about me, man.
- Guess again, kid.
I'm you.
- What?
- That's right.
You're too young to understand.
But understand this.
It wasn't your fault.
♪
- I let that flame
get out of control,
Like you said.
I ran out without
waking anybody, like you said.
I was just so afraid.
- You were just a kid.
I spent my whole life
blaming you,
Hating you for something
you didn't mean to do.
♪
- Why are you telling me this?
- You can't change the things
you did.
But you can change
what you become.
♪
Don't be like me.
Be better.
♪
- Clarissa, it's me, martin.
- I'm sorry,
you look so familiar,
But I just can't place you.
- Spaceship?
What next, martians?
- No, actually, amnesia pill.
- Oh, yeah.
- This will just
wipe your short-term memory.
Of course, it's up to you,
but we don't want
To mess with time too much.
- Mmm.
I always knew
that you'd end up
Caring for people,
Protecting people.
- Well,
I learned it from my dad.
♪
- Proud of you, honey.
- Is everything all right?
- My wife
doesn't seem to remember me.
- Because until we return
your younger selves
To the timeline, you--
None of you will
have ever existed.
But we will return you.
- When we left 2016,
I just assumed I would return
to the exact moment I left,
That clarissa wouldn't even know
I was gone.
So I didn't say good-bye.
And now I fear I will never
have that chance.
- You will.
Look, I've told you before
That I am not going
to risk your marriage
In order to save my wife.
I promise you that.
- Thank you.
- Not even gonna pretend
to understand any of this.
- It's pretty crazy, huh?
- That was you in the hospital,
On the day you were born.
And earlier, on fire.
Amazing.
Where'd you learn those moves?
- From my dad.
♪
- You know, the day
you were born in the hospital,
I'd never been so scared.
I mean, even in combat.
But now, I know
for you to be the man
I see standing here,
I must do something right.
I can't wait to be there
to watch it happen.
♪
- Dad, listen.
On September 26th,
You're gonna be deployed
along the k4 circle.
Keep your head
on a swivel for an ied.
- You know this beca--
You're from the future.
- Please.
Promise me you'll be careful.
♪
- I'll be back soon, okay?
Hey.
- Hey.
- Hope you don't mind,
my fiancée...
My other fiancée
is in our quarters, resting.
- Yeah, no, that's...
That's fine.
- Hey, I'm sorry.
- No, really, it's fine.
- No, I-I mean,
Being at death's door
Is not the right time
to pop the question.
- Look, when you proposed,
I was so afraid of losing you.
And then facing the pilgrim,
I realized there is never
going to be
A right time for this.
So we should stop waiting
for the right time.
- I don't understand.
♪
- I want to marry you, ray.
I mean it.
♪
- How's your sister?
- She's a tough kid.
How's your dad?
- Sleeping off that amnesia pill
from rip.
♪
- Hey.
I might have just stopped my dad
From getting killed
in mogadishu.
I just thought I should tell you
In case there's
a time paradox or whatever.
- Well, as I've been saying, mr.
Jackson, time wants to happen.
- Yeah, I know.
But I had to try.
- And perhaps
what time wants
Is to see you
and your father back together.
♪
- Ugh.
Just pulled younger me's head
from out of his ass.
- I'm not sure it stuck.
- Me either.
Then I saw younger rip change,
And I thought,
why not give it a shot?
- Surprised you didn't advise
your teenage self
To not get on a certain boat.
- Yeah, me too.
- Yak, yak, yak.
I thought we were
on a clock here.
- Indeed we are.
Time, the history
From which your younger selves
were removed,
Is beginning to set...
As is evidenced by the change
In clarissa's memory.
- Okay.
So how long do we have till
these changes stick?
- No one knows.
- Which is why we need
to move swiftly
To locate vandal savage
If any of your lives
are to be restored to normal.
- So how long
will it take to determine
A new location for savage?
- Longer than we have.
Fortunately, there is
one place in time
That we know savage to be.
- You said he conquered
the world in 2166.
- You also said
it was too dangerous
To strike at savage while he was
at the height of his powers.
- That it is.
But with your younger selves
removed from history,
We have quite literally
run out of time.
♪
- Greg, move your head!