Previously,
on Legends Of Tomorrow...
Good job out there.
Are you sticking around?
Wally, ready to leave?
I'm actually gonna stay.
The hunt for the six totems
has begun.
- No.
- We'll fix this.
We'll get your totem back.
Nora was possessed by Mallus.
He seemed scared of my totem.
You're one of the six.
The good news
is we already have the air,
earth and fire.
And Kuasa has the water totem.
Which leaves us with the final totem,
which is still a complete mystery.
Good point. Way to go, Ray.
Memphis 1950
Hello, sir.
I, I've been saving up
for a while now
and I think it's time.
I'm here to buy a guitar.
Now, I know it ain't much.
But what do you think
I can get for what I got?
Well, I'm sure we could
find you something.
You know, a boy picking
his first guitar is a sacred moment.
In fact,
some say the instrument chooses you.
Don't waste your
hard earned money any more.
Used Guitars Buy & Sell
I'll take that one.
You don't want that guitar.
What happened to the instrument
choosing me, sir?
I was just building a moment.
Besides, you can't afford it.
Well, I'll get the money.
I'll come back.
Look, I gotta tell you the truth.
Before that guitar found
its way here,
it belonged to a one Robert Johnson.
You mean, the Robert Johnson?
Legend said he sold his soul
to the devil to play
as good as he did.
Legend also says that guitar
is cursed because of it.
I ain't afraid of no guitar, sir.
You gotta let me try it, at least.
They must be messing
with the power lines outside.
Sound like that,
how could it be cursed?
You know what?
The guitar's yours.
You just take it away from here.
Thank you, sir. Much, much obliged.
An instrument as good as this,
I promise, one day, you'll hear
my name on that radio.
Hey.
What is your name, son?
Presley, sir.
Elvis Presley.
Which brings us to the kitchen.
We divvy up cleaning duties
by Ray's chore wheel,
which uses a complex system
I pretend to not understand
until he eventually
does my chores for me.
Wipe down food fabricator.
Bet you thought time travel would
be seeing Woodstock,
saving Shakespeare
and having ethical debates
while standing over baby Hitler.
Trust me,
it takes time to get used to life...
Cool, so what's next?
It's gonna get time for me to get
used to life with a speedster.
This is my room.
Guess you and me are bunkmates
while we help move you
into Stein's quarters.
You just moved yourself in,
didn't you?
I figured, why bother anyone else?
You know, I was gonna invite you
to be my player two,
but you're officially not
my problem anymore.
Wait, who beat all my high scores?
Well, you see, the thing
with Ms. PacMan
is you gotta just ignore the fruit.
All the points come
from taking down the ghosts.
Yeah, I know that,
but nobody could beat
these scores without...
Without lightning fast fingers.
You better not have messed
with Guitar Hero.
Trombone Hero
What's Trombone Hero?
Hold on, Axl. Sammy's coming.
Just gotta find the damn mayo.
Come on, Mick.
What did I say about having him
in the kitchen?
- Not to.
- Yes.
Would you toss me the walnuts,
please?
Thank you.
I'm gonna need some brain food
if I'm gonna fix the fire totem.
You know,
Nora thought using cold fusion
to reboot it was a crazy idea,
- but...
- Don't care.
Where's the mayo!
The new kid.
I saw him speed moving in
to Marty's old quarters.
Too much change on this damn ship.
That's what I love about old Axl.
Doesn't change.
Josh Groban
Josh Groban?
Who the hell is Josh Groban?
And who the hell changed
the name of my rat?
All right, kids,
it's anachronism o'clock.
- What you got?
- How about this one?
It's a category two during
the Belle Epoque in Paris.
Sounds romantic.
Or this category three,
which is the launch
of the Spirit of St. Louis.
I always wanted to join
the mile high club.
It's when two people on a plane...
Hey, really cute that you guys
are crazy in love,
but date night
is going to have to wait.
If these anachronisms
are loosening Mallus' cage,
we need to double down.
What happened to your hair?
What are you talking about?
What?
- What? What is it?
- I...
What happened
to my trademark volume and sheen?
Who changed my rat's name?
Yo, who switched my game?
Gideon?
A scan of the timeline
reveals a change in Memphis,
Tennessee, 1954.
Says here Memphis
became a ghost town
after a mysterious
bout of mass hysteria in July, 1954.
That's what caused the changes.
Memphis is the birthplace
of rock and roll.
If rock never makes it out
of Memphis,
then none of these things exist.
Your pet rat's name-sake,
electric guitar.
- Your hair gel.
- It's not hair gel, Wally.
It's Royal Crown pomade.
- It's the same product used by...
- Elvis Presley.
See, she knows
what I'm talking about.
No, dodo. Look.
While the population fled
in hysterics,
one person was left standing
in the aftermath,
a local teen named Elvis Presley.
Don't tell me they messed
with the King.
Whatever he saw drove him crazy.
He was taken to
the Bolivar State Hospital.
- Treated for insanity.
- If Memphis is abandoned in '54,
then rock doesn't hit the mainstream,
which means there's no Howling Ray,
no Little Richard.
The Elvis sandwich,
peanut butter and banana
fried in greasy bacon fat.
The man was a visionary.
But if it didn't show up
on the anachronism map,
- then...
- Darhks.
The only people evil enough
to wanna kill rock and roll.
Oh, and I bet you
that sick bastard likes ska.
All right, let's go check this out.
We need to find Elvis
before panic sets in.
Elvis Presley's uncle preached
at the Church of Zion every Sunday.
The boy never missed a service.
You heard the lady.
What?
Why are you staring at me?
I dunno, waiting for you
- to the thing you do.
- What thing?
You know,
you usually send us into the field
with a little more pizzazz.
All right, Legends,
put on your Sunday best,
because we are going to church.
That was pretty good.
Amen.
Jesus loves me
He will stay
Close beside me all the way
Thou hast bled and died for me
- I will henceforth live for Thee
- Well, this is uncomfortable
and I'm not just talking
about my dress.
Yeah, I guess these people
didn't get the whole
"love thy neighbor" talk.
Shush yourself, lady.
Have you heard your singing voice?
Just keep Mick away
from the collection tray.
And the communion wafers.
That's not bread.
There's a sickness
coming over this town.
I see it in the school yard
as I pass in the morning.
And to my horror,
I see it in this very church
on Sundays.
It infects the mind.
It drives people crazy.
Maybe the righteous reverend
is on to something.
They call it rock and roll.
I call it the devil's music.
Nevermind, he has no idea
what he's talking about.
Now.
I would like to invite my nephew,
Elvis,
to play for us and encourage you all
to attend our first annual
Heavenly Night of Hymns.
Elvis?
Remember what we talked about, son.
Keep it godly.
Yes, ma'am.
Can you believe this?
The first show we see together
is Elvis live.
You're not the only one
who's excited.
This one's called...
Onward, Christian Soldiers.
Okay.
Onward Christian soldiers
Marching as to war
So, this is rock and roll?
With the cross
I mean, it's no Benny Goodman, but...
No, we did not come all this way
to listen to Elvis
play grandma songs.
Christ the royal master
That's it, Elvis.
Put a little sauce on it.
- Yeah, swivel.
- Leads against the foe
He's so cute.
Forward into battle
Satan's got ahold of her.
What the hell is going on?
My totem. It's reacting to something.
Be gone, Satan.
Well, I think she's talking to us.
- Come on.
- Behold
what you have seen
with your very eyes.
Witnessed...
in this house of God.
That is the act of Satan.
Yes, it is.
The Elvis sandwich.
I guess Elvis
is the king of rock and roll.
One hip shake and Z loses it.
Yeah, tell me about it, sister.
I didn't lose control
because of Elvis hips.
Yeah, me, either.
My totem was glowing
and so was Elvis' guitar.
- But that means that Elvis is...
- Yep.
Elvis is a totem bearer.
So Elvis is the bearer
of the long lost sixth totem.
Consider me all shook up.
So, he has to join the team, right?
- No.
- I mean, we can't defeat Mallus
unless we have a full set.
I mean,
we could get Gideon to fabricate him
a spangly jumpsuit
and he'll fit right in.
What totem would choose
a guitar-toting choir boy
- as its bearer?
- Isn't it obvious?
It's Elvis we're talking about.
- It's gotta be...
- A sandwich totem.
I was gonna say music.
Just imagine what the music totem
would do for my upper register.
I could finally give
local theater a shot.
That is,
after we use it to destroy Mallus.
So we're gonna vanquish a time demon
with our killer harmonies.
- It's gonna go great.
- Every totem is growing stronger
in response to Mallus' threat.
What if the preacher was right
and Elvis' music literally
drives Memphis insane?
Then we have to get it
before that happens.
I got it. Elvis' guitar totem.
So, I'm not the only one
who finds that annoying, right?
- So annoying.
- Yeah.
Okay, come on.
We're good to go, right?
Are we? Because Elvis hasn't
recorded his first single yet.
And without that guitar,
he may never record it.
Which means rock
and roll history is...
Josh Groban.
What if we have Gideon
fabricate a ringer guitar
and drop it off to the future King?
Great idea. I call A-mission.
Amaya, come with me.
I will teach you
what rock and roll is all about.
Until then, everyone, shake,
rattle and roll.
Beale Street was the heart
of the music scene in Memphis
in the 1950s.
Brothels, churches, juke joints,
all next to each other,
all black owned.
This, this was the spirit
of rock and roll.
There he is.
It was right here.
Hey, kid.
I don't think you wanna keep
this lying around.
Something tells me it's special.
- You have no idea.
- Yeah.
There's no way I'd ever be able
to thank you for this.
Well, if you wanna
write a song about me,
there are several words
that rhyme with Nate.
Just knock them dead.
I can't wait for you
to see Elvis live.
It's going to change your life.
You really believe that my life
can be changed by one song?
Of course. Music is so much more
than just songs.
Music is about identity.
It's, it's hearing a track
for the first time
and you think to yourself,
"Wow, this is who I am."
I don't care how long it takes,
we're gonna find your music,
whether it be rock and roll or
God forbid, ska.
Debuting tonight, y'all,
give it up for Elvis Presley.
I guess it's time
to have my life changed.
Yeah.
How you folks doing tonight?
If it's all right with you all,
I'm gonna play a little song
for my mama.
Sometime tonight.
Now, you...
Wait, don't go.
Why, you all wanna make fun
of my playing like everybody else?
No, actually. We're...
We're music managers.
And we think you're very talented.
So, what happened up there?
It's this doggone guitar.
It ain't working
how it's supposed to.
Y'all gonna think I'm crazy,
but my guitar,
it's more than just a guitar.
Now it ain't working right, I just...
You don't feel like yourself anymore.
Yes, ma'am.
And I'll tell you why, usually,
when I play...
I got my twin brother, Jesse,
up there to back me up.
You have a twin brother?
Well, he ain't with us no more.
Passed when he was a baby.
But this guitar of mine used
to connect me to him.
I told you y'all would think
I'm crazy.
No, not at all.
I've always believed
that objects can connect us
to our ancestors.
Yeah, I guess we call it a spirit,
like.
On stage,
on stage just now for the first time,
Jesse wasn't with me.
I mean, he's gone.
All of a sudden,
I just don't know where he is.
Whoa. That was weird.
Yeah.
You feel that?
Yeah, it's freezing.
I am detecting an EMF reading
of six milligaus
that is disturbing
the ship's electrical servers.
- EM what?
- Electromagnetic field.
It's a scientific term
that's been wrapped up
in a bunch of paranormal nonsense.
Paranormal, as in...
Ghosts.
Whoever you are,
just put the guitar down.
Doesn't look like
he's taking requests.
Maybe the preacher was right
about rock and roll.
You know, what never hurt anyone?
A nice show tune.
I got it.
Okay, Axl.
Time to break the seal.
- Axl, come back.
- What the hell is going on?
Guitar hit me in the head.
Oh, that explains nothing.
- I got you.
- The guitar.
- It's haunted.
- We know.
But by who?
That's what's so strange
about my brother.
I ain't never met Jesse,
but somehow I missed him all my life.
Until you bought your first guitar.
Yeah, the store said it was cursed.
He was only half right.
It was also a blessing, too.
Well, if my brother's out there
somewhere without me,
I can't imagine he's too happy.
Excuse me.
Guys, Elvis guitar's haunted.
- We know.
Yeah and I'm guessing it's gonna do
whatever it takes
to get back to Elvis.
Good guess.
- Where's Axl?
- About that ghost.
It's Elvis' dead twin, Jesse.
Jesse, stop! We know your brother.
Now, I know this all sounds
like hogwash.
Magical guitars,
the ghosts of gone family members,
but I, I can't play without him.
I got a session to record
at Sun Studios tomorrow.
I saved up to buy it.
It's your first recording session.
You're gonna keep that appointment.
And we're gonna get you Jesse back.
You will?
We will?
All right, so,
I talked to Constantine
about our totem.
He compared it with his notes
and this is what he found.
Death Totem? Pass.
Yeah, whoever wields it
has domain over the dead.
Which is why we need
to keep this totem with us
and safe at all times.
Elvis needs his totem back.
You have no idea
what we are dealing with.
The Death Totem?
The most volatile of all
of the totems lost
for eons along
with the sixth tribe of Zambezi.
Maybe they suffered the same fate
that's about to befall Memphis.
- You don't understand.
- No, you don't understand.
We are talking about a Death Totem
and it could turn this whole place
into a ghost town.
Elvis has a session at Sun Studios.
That's where he cuts his first demo.
That's how he gets discovered, okay?
We do not have the time
for Elvis to get his groove back.
Jesse has to be there.
Nathaniel, I understand
how important this is to you,
but we can't give Elvis
a totem just to save his music.
It's not about the music, okay?
Rock has inspired
many historic milestones.
Protests, revolutions,
me losing my virginity.
Elvis doesn't need a totem forever.
Just one song that changes the world.
Please.
Fine.
You take it to him,
you let him record with it
and you stay with it at all times.
At all times.
Recording
All right, son. Are you ready to lay
this down on wax, or what?
Oh, I've been waiting all my life,
sir.
You said that you loved me
It was a long, long time ago
And now the way that you've
been acting, babe
I know that it's not so
So I'm gone
Now, that's rock and roll.
What do you think?
I'm gone, gone mama
It's okay.
I just don't see
how it's worth risking
the most volatile of totems for.
I thought that was gonna be
our music moment.
Our music moment?
One of those times
where the right song comes on
and ties everything together
so perfectly that it becomes...
It becomes a story.
We already have plenty of stories.
We saved the world together.
- Yeah.
- We saw dinosaurs.
There was that time
that I discovered Netflix
and we watched every episode
of Friends in one week.
All stunning accomplishments, yes.
But a music moment's different.
You'll see.
Oh, babe
So long, baby
Baby, bye-bye
How was that?
Boy, now that's a record.
We gotta get this straight down
to WHBQ.
You're gonna be on the radio.
- Oh, boy.
- Yeah.
Uncle Lucious,
what are you doing here?
Well, well, well.
You missed choir practice.
Then I hear because you're down
at Sun Studios.
Well, no kin of mine
is gonna record the devil's music.
Not after what we saw in church.
Look, I got, I got talent.
My manager says so.
You got my nephew into this?
Yeah.
Hey, that ain't yours to take, now.
Give me that back.
I knew you'd put up a fight.
Sheriff.
Get him out of here.
Let's see if a night in the jailhouse
rocks some sense into you.
That record's gotta make it on
- the radio tonight.
- Get him outta here, too.
You're making a huge mistake.
Get behind me, Satan.
White Stripes. Great album.
At least, it was.
Your mama's
been too easy on you, boy.
Look at the sort
you got mixed up with.
These are the types
that go on down to Beale Street
and dance the hoochiekoo
like heathens.
You keep on preaching hate.
I'm only trying
to bring folks together.
As the Lord destroyed the wicked,
I must do the same with this record.
I'll make an example of you
at the Heavenly Nights of Hymns.
That ought to teach them
young folks a lesson.
Reverend, you don't know
what you're messing with.
The music your nephew makes...
Has turned Memphis
into Sodom and Gomorrah.
I will not allow it
to be the ruination
of that boy's soul, too.
Don't worry.
We'll get you out of here.
All I ever wanted to do
was make my mama proud.
Now, she ain't never gonna hear
my song on the radio.
At least I still got you, Jesse.
Guys, we have a bit of a setback.
- We're listening. What's up?
- Long story, funny ending.
Amaya, Elvis,
and I were thrown in the slammer.
So just steel up and break out.
Yeah, I know, I can, but I'm afraid
my work here isn't done.
- What do you need?
- I need you
to go back to the church,
get the record from the reverend
and bring it to WHBQ
and make sure it debuts tonight.
On it.
Despite everything you've seen,
I really think my powers
could come in handy right now
because I could just go grab
that record and then I...
Okay, if this were
a Central City bank robbery, sure.
You could just speed in,
save the day,
the mayor would give you
a key to the city.
That actually happened, you know.
See, Barry and I, we saw this...
History is different.
You can't be a chainsaw.
You need to be a scalpel.
You, you need to get in there,
talk to people,
find out what they really need.
Now, let's go talk to the preacher
like human beings.
Okay, Axl.
I know how to draw you out.
With a nice little snack.
Mick? Mick, don't panic.
You just forgot to chew again.
Axl.
Is this one of your
stupid science experiments?
- Looks like Josh Groban...
- Axl.
Found something even more lethal
than your Elvis sandwich.
I'm sorry, buddy.
Look, the life expectancy of a rat
is one and a half to two
and a half years.
So, you know,
the little guy really beat the odds.
And you know what?
We can pick you up another one
in the next time period we stop in.
Because what's one more
change on this ship?
Jailhouse blues
Jailhouse party
You're getting warmer.
There's gotta be a song
in here somewhere, Jesse.
Okay, songwriting time out.
Listen...
There's no easy way to say this,
but when we get out of here,
you're gonna have
to give us that guitar.
It has power and it can be dangerous.
No. I, I mean,
I can't play without Jesse.
I mean, before he came along,
sure, there was songs, but,
there wasn't ever any music.
Look, even after he's gone,
you're gonna have the music.
I mean, that's why you play, right?
The real reason music matters
is because it keeps things alive
long after they're gone.
Any idea why Ray needs us?
No clue.
Whatever this is, I don't like it.
Wait, what is that?
We're gathered here in remembrance
of our dear friend Axl.
Right. I'm outta here.
- I'm with him.
- Wait, you need this.
We... we all need this.
Fine, but when I mourn, I drink.
Fair enough.
Charles Dickens once wrote,
"Life is made of ever
so many partings,
welded together."
Axl is one such parting.
And while we may lose some,
they are never really gone.
And they certainly can't be replaced.
They'll live on in the memories
we shared with them
and the lessons they taught us.
And it is because of that,
that we can embrace the change.
I still remember
the first time I met Axl.
It was in the vents.
I was tiny Atom. He was a big rat.
And he tried to eat me.
I knew we'd laugh about it
one day together.
Sara, I believe it's customary
for the captain to share a few words.
Oh, no, you you're doing a great job.
Thank you.
Well, then, please join me in a
chorus of Sweet Child of Mine.
All right, I'll say something.
Axl was a friend.
Our friend.
Some might say he was the best of us.
A Heavenly Night Of Hymns
Can we have a word?
And not the good word.
We just wanna talk.
What could you possibly
wanna talk about?
We need to talk to you
about your nephew and his record.
You can't destroy it.
People need to hear it.
That includes you.
How would you all know
what I need to hear?
- Actually...
- I... I might
actually know
what you're going through.
You see, my dad,
he came into my life pretty late.
We couldn't always
figure each other out.
We didn't always know how to fit
into each other's lives
until I knew that I just had to go
and set out on my own.
Truly sorry to hear that, son.
I think that you might be afraid
that you're losing your nephew.
But if you both could just try
to understand each other,
you might actually find something
new between you two, you might,
you might even find something
really special.
Now, I know someone
that would love to play that record,
if you're ready to give it a chance.
And a lot of young souls
would be moved
by your nephew's voice.
Mysterious ways, indeed.
Okay, so, we walked real far
and it took a long time
- and then we got thrown around...
- History's at stake.
You better run fast.
Hoowee, Daddy-O-Dewey here
with a new record
literally burning my fingers
by a young local boy,
name of Elvis Presley.
Remember where you heard it first.
How on Earth...
My nephew is on the radio.
It was a long long time ago
- Well, I'll be.
- And now the way
- that you've been acting
- Kid kept his promise.
Babe, I know that it's not so
So, so, I'm gone
Yeah, I'm gone
I'm gone, gone mama
It would seem that Ms. Tomaz
and Mr. West have succeeded.
To Axl.
I'm gonna get me a big pink Cadillac
Been ages since I've seen
so much life in this place.
Maybe you ain't
so ungodly as I thought.
You know, you and I might
have different names for God,
but I'm guessing
we have a lot in common, too.
Yeah I'm gone
- What took you so long?
- Seriously?
I'm gone gone mama
Hey, what does dancing look like
in the future?
Oh, pretty much the same.
Oh, no...
Great, well, we'd love
to stick around for Hymn Night,
but we should head back to the...
On second thought,
how about those hymns?
That music, it summoned the dead.
This time he actually might be right.
Don't tell me you're converting.
No, Elvis recorded that song
with the Death Totem.
It must have given his music
the power to literally raise spirits.
- You're kidding.
- This must have been
what drives everyone out of Memphis.
Right,
ghosts can go through anything.
It's kind of their thing.
Okay, Mick.
Time to send him off.
What?
Axl lives.
You just had to throw
a rodent funeral, didn't you?
Wh... where's he going?
Remember, the real points come
from taking out the ghosts.
Let's make Ms. PacMan proud.
How's that for a high score?
Impressive. But I think it's gonna
be game over soon.
I'm gonna get me a big straw hat
Well, at least you got to hear
yourself on the radio.
Don't go quoting this
to my uncle now,
but I sound pretty damn good,
don't I?
Hey, what's going on out there?
The whole town's been
overrun by ghosts.
- Well, let us out.
- Let me in.
- Death Totem.
Well, I'll be.
It worked.
You can command spirits.
Well, if you can raise them,
maybe you can also lead them away.
Lead them where?
How about back
where they came from?
The cemetery outside
your uncle's church.
You were right.
His music really does have power.
Could have stood
to be wrong on this one.
Well, we need
to get past them somehow.
Don't be scared.
Dead don't want nothing
but to be acknowledged.
I mean,
is there anything this guy can't do?
I knew I should have
smashed that record
when I had a chance.
Now, your song has gone
and let the devil into my church.
This ain't the devil's doing.
You were right. Music has a power.
Brings life to the lifeless,
soothes the souls of the restless.
But it ain't just rock and roll,
either.
I would like to prove it.
Put an end to all this,
while I'm at it.
All right.
Get on up there, boy.
Now, I know you all can hear me.
Come on in.
All are welcome here.
Amazing grace
How sweet the sound
That saved a wretch
Like me
Should we take them out?
No, it's okay.
I think I understand what they need.
I once was lost
But now I'm found
Was blind but now
I see
'Twas grace that taught
My heart to feel
And grace
I actually know this one.
My fears relieved
- Care to dance?
- How precious did
That grace appear
The hour I first
Believed
Axl.
I'm sorry, your corpse,
it started to stink. I.
I didn't think you'd mind.
I...
Saved you a sammy.
Axl, what's... what's wrong?
Yea when this flesh
And heart shall fail
And mortal life
Shall cease
I think it's time, brother.
I've got a feeling this goodbye
ain't gonna be forever.
Thank you, Jesse.
Thank you very much.
Within the veil
A life of joy
And peace
When we've been there
Ten thousand years
Bright shining as
The sun
I think we just found our moment.
Less days
To sing God's praise
Than when we'd first
Begun
Well, better make yourself
comfortable.
Something tells me you'll be
spending a lot more time in here,
especially after that show
you just put on.
Yeah, something came over me,
I guess.
I was up there looking
at those ghosts,
I realized one day this is
all gonna be over for all of us.
Might as well get the most
out of life that we can.
You know what?
I think you just discovered
the spirit of rock and roll.
I think that this...
Is probably gonna be safer with you.
That was fun and all, but.
I don't soon wanna be raising
the dead again.
Promise me you'll keep playing,
even without your brother.
Jesse ain't really gone.
The things he taught me,
the love that we had...
it's gonna live on in my music.
Now, can I ask you a question?
You ain't really a music manager,
are you?
Busted.
But something tells me
you're gonna be just fine.
Even without this.
Thanks to you.
Think I'm just about ready.
Go get them.
All right, gentlemen.
How you all doing?
I say we start it off with something
a little bit fast tempo.
Okay, fellas, get your fingers going.
You rang, Captain?
Hello, gorgeous.
- Look at that volume.
- Don't touch it.
- How do you...
- I'm serious, don't touch it.
Well, well, well.
- Look who got his swagger back.
- Me?
Just because I saved rock and roll
and reinstated the King
to his proper throne doesn't...
Doesn't give you an excuse
to hog our one bathroom.
- Some of us need to...
- Celebrate the fact
that we beat the
Darhks to the Death Totem.
Although I don't imagine
our acquisition will stay off
the radar for long.
Well, think of it like this.
We're four totems up
in the fourth quarter.
Time's running out for those idiots.
Yep, even though
they still have mine.
Well, they'll be Time Stoning back
two whatever hell
they came from once
we get your totem back.
Yeah, and in the meantime,
we need to make sure
we keep that Death Totem on lock.
Box.
Lock boxes. I... I got it covered.
I made encrypted lock boxes
for each one of the totems.
Well, good.
The Death Totem's powers
are not to be taken lightly.
Perhaps you need some
assistance, Ms. Jiwe.
Just give me a moment,
Gideon, please.
I've sabotaged access tanks.
I am sure I can figure out
a stupid playlist.
Hey.
Gideon said you wanted to see me.
I wanted to say thank you.
Oh, you don't...
Check you out.
You got a playlist going?
As soon as I'm done uploading all
the Smiths music,
we'll do a deep dive
into the Morrissey solo stuff that...
Actually, I thought it was time
for me to teach you about my music.
Okay.
Like some big band stuff?
I think I'm at a point where I can
appreciate a trumpet solo.
No, this is the music of Zambesi.
Gideon helped me locate some
supposedly lost tracks.
You like it?
Yeah, it's, I like, I love it.
So good.
Now, you know how
I feel about rock and roll.
What's that?
I said you're almost
at the good part.
You mean this isn't the good part?
I love you, Nathaniel.
What?
I said there's a lot more
where that came from.
It's a good thing we got time.
In loving memory of Axl 2015 - 2018