Time travel is real,
and all of history is vulnerable
to the attack
of rogue time travelers.
But one group travels throughout time
to stop the spread of these
so-called Time Aberrations
and erase their damage to history.
A group of outcasts and misfits.
These individuals aren't heroes.
They're something else.
They're Legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Heywood, Dr. Nate Heywood.
I'm a historian.
I specialize in deductive
historical reconstruction.
In layman's terms,
I'm a time detective.
Ingestible translator.
You'll be able to speak
and understand
any language spoken to you.
You know how fragile
we historians can be.
I know my cuts and bruises.
You're a hemophiliac.
You can bleed to death.
So your superpower
is wearing the suit.
Without that fancy suit,
you're nothing
but a self-righteous rich guy.
Mr. Heywood's vitals are dropping.
I think I can save him.
I did a little tinkering
to the formula.
Hello, Rex.
- Rex! Rex!
- Time traveler.
- So how's our patient?
- Still stable.
Gideon has him under sedation.
Any side effects
from the Nazi super-serum
you injected him with?
No, but that may have
a little something to do
with the work
I did altering the serum
to remove the Nazi parts.
Yes, it would be a tad inconvenient
to have a monster roaming the ship.
Gideon,
can you pilot for a little bit?
I need a break.
Where are all the knives?
Oh, there's one.
Look, if this is about me
taking all the mayonnaise,
you might be slightly overreacting.
You killed him!
Killed him?
I've killed lots of people.
You're gonna have to be
a bit more specific.
What the hell happened to you?
I really don't know.
You injected me with Nazi serum?
Which I'd redesigned
to quintuple my own strength
and transform my skin into an alloy
a hundred times stronger than steel.
Steel, that's a cool name.
Yeah, especially since my grandfather
was called Commander Steel.
But what does that make me?
Corporal Steel? Mr. Steel?
Citizen Steel?
Who cares?
You got superpowers now, dude.
Except,I don't know
how I turned to steel
in the first place.
Ray will teach you.
- He will?
- You said it yourself.
You redesigned the serum.
Which I did beautifully,
but it's not like I have
some sort of instruction manual.
Guess you'll have to wing it.
Now, I'm gonna go have a chat
with our stowaway.
This is gonna be so much fun!
You stowed away
before we time-jumped from 1942.
I'm gonna get out of here
and I'm gonna finish what I started.
You mean, killing Mick?
Not that I haven't
thought of it myself, but why?
He killed Rex.
What?
Rex Tyler?
As in Hourman?
His killer stole the Askaran Amulet.
Look, I'm sorry. I am.
But Mick didn't do it.
He is a thief and a murderer.
He's also a Legend...
and Mick hasn't been off the ship
since we dropped
your team off at the JSA.
With his last words,
he told me his killer
was a time traveler.
You know,
we've been tracking someone
who's been trying to alter history.
We think it's the same person
that gave Krieger the super-serum.
This might be your time traveler.
Look, if I let you out of here,
you promise not to hurt Mick
unless he really deserves it?
Sorry for knocking you out.
Sorry for locking you up.
Call it even?
When I was a kid, I used to play
JSA versus Nazis with my dolls.
Well, they were action figures,
really.
But it doesn't matter
'cause I got superpowers now
and it's awesome.
Your powers manifested
as a result of
a heightened adrenal response.
Basically, Amaya threatened
you and you reacted.
So now...
what we need to do
is duplicate the conditions
which caused you to,
you know, steel on?
Wait, so you want to threaten me?
Not exactly.
Wait, let's discuss this.
I thought this was a time machine?
You saved the Justice Society.
Why can't you save Rex?
Because we're dealing
with another time traveler.
If we go back and save Rex,
the time traveler will just
go back before then
and kill Rex again.
So instead of chasing our own tails,
we need to identify
who we're up against.
I don't understand any of this.
Look, I just need you to trust us.
We're gonna find who do this.
I promise you.
In the meantime,
Gideon will fly you home.
I'm not going back until Rex's killer
is brought to justice.
We don't know
how long that will take.
Don't worry, we're professionals.
We know what we're doing.
Yeah, come on!
If Grandpa Heywood
could see me now.
Professional?
Ish.
I know you not gonna take that, Ray.
Go crush this Tin Man.
- Nice try.
- Come on.
Hold on, I'll close it!
Nate!
Ray, get inside!
We have to close the door.
No, I got to go after him.
Gideon, shut the cargo door.
What's happening to the ship?
Jax, what's our status?
I've rerouted power
from the secondary manifolds.
Where are Dr. Palmer
and Dr. Heywood?
- Did you check out the window?
- What?
How is it you people haven't
managed to kill yourselves yet?
The day is still young.
- Jax?
- Yeah, I'm working on it.
Gideon, I need you
to track down Ray and Nate
and take us to their position.
The explosive decompression
caused us
to lose corrective altitude,
which put too much strain on
the station-keeping thrusters.
For God's sake, say it how it is.
We're screwed.
Edo Period.
Mid-17th century Japan.
That's cool.
Well...
I'm still alive.
So far, so good.
Whoa, Samurais.
Oh, right, almost forgot.
Can you understand me now?
I'm looking for a friend of mine.
Okay, he fell from the sky.
He's about yeah tall.
Made out of metal.
No?
You're alive.
Hi. How did I get here?
I found you lying
at the bottom of a crater
like you had been dropped
from the sky.
Dropped from the sky?
That's the craziest thing
I've ever heard.
Yeah, I sailed here.
You know, across the ocean...
with some friends.
Who hopefully are gonna find me.
By the looks of it, I'm gonna say
we're on the island of...
Honshu, in the vicinity of Kyoto?
Yes.
How did you learn
to speak my language?
I studied it for many years.
You know, so I could trade
with your countrymen.
Yep, feudal Japan is my jam.
Masako, what are you doing
talking to this gaijin?
He was hurt, Father.
I brought him home
so you could care for him.
And who would care for us
when the Shogun finds out
we're aiding a foreigner?
Please, Father.
You know what they would do to him.
Very well.
Get him inside quickly.
My name is Nate, by the way.
- My name is Masako.
- Masako.
That's a pretty name.
The Shogun asked you a question.
Where did you find your armor?
I made it.
Your armor is mine now.
You don't understand.
I designed the suit specifically
for my body.
Take the armor away.
You're making a big mistake.
It could kill you!
Too hot?
Are you, sure your old man's cool
with you giving me a bath?
My father is not home.
I'm only giving you a bath
because you are dirty and injured.
About that. I'm...
I'm more durable than it looks.
You still have not told me
where you are from.
The United States...
which you've never heard of
because it doesn't exist
for another 200 years.
You are a strange man.
You have no idea.
Enough about me.
I overheard your father
talk about the Shogun.
Is that Tokugawa Iemitsu,
by any chance?
Historians view him as
a particularly brutal warlord
and...
Did I say something?
Tomorrow, I'm to be married
to Tokugawa Iemitsu.
Then my life is over.
How can you bring a thug
on a rescue mission?
I've known men like you.
Men who take and prey on the weak.
Listen, girly.
I'm risking my neck for two morons
who fell out of a ship. Why?
'Cause they'd do the same for me.
Why are you on the ship?
'Cause I'm a member of
the Justice Society of America.
- It's my job to protect everyone.
- Except for me.
You snuck up behind me
and sliced my throat like a ninja.
There's no such thing as ninjas,
you idiot.
- Tell that to Chuck Norris.
- Who's that?
- And I'm the idiot.
- And by the way,
- I'm not your girly.
- All right.
If you two don't quit
your squabbling,
I am going to maroon you
in a time period of my choosing.
Together.
Not to brag, but...
Between the docking stabilizers
and the blast doors...
I think this might be
my best patchwork ever.
Well, charming as your confidence is,
I think we better consult the expert.
Gideon, would you be so kind
as to run a diagnostic report?
Mr. Jackson's
work has done the trick.
A scan has revealed that
all 36 compartments of the ship
are in optimal condition.
That's weird.
Actually, I think
it's astonishing given
the considerable abuse
we've been under...
No, no. Not, not that.
Gideon, did you say
36 compartments?
Correct. The entirety of the ship.
Before Rip, you know, disappeared,
he made me learn
every inch of the Waverider.
And of those inches,
35 compartments.
So either I miscalculated or...
Captain Hunter
had a secret compartment
he failed to tell you about.
Gideon, please pull up
the schematics of the ship.
No, we still have
to fix the time drive.
And we will.
After.
Please, don't tell me
you're not intrigued.
Masako-san, a word please.
What's wrong?
The Shogun's men are here.
Please come outside.
Konnichiwa. How can I help you?
We found a gaijinin the forest.
The Shogun wants to make sure
there are not
any other foreigners around
to bother you.
Oh, that is very kind of him.
but you are the only visitor
we've had today.
Good.
The last thing the Shogun wants
before his wedding is surprises.
Too late!
What are you doing?
Relax, I got this.
- Who are you?
- I'm the guy telling you
that your Shogun's wedding
has been canceled
on account that he's an asshat.
But seriously.
Why don't you boys mosey on back
to your big bad boss
and tell him the news?
Or what?
Or it's gonna get ugly.
I am wearing a Samurai's armor.
You are not.
I wear my armor on the inside.
Nate, stop insulting him.
I beg of you.
Relax, I got this.
He caught me off guard.
Come at me now.
It's not turning on.
Stop! Stop! Please!
You're going to kill him.
That is entirely up to him.
Stay down, gaijin.
She doesn't want to marry him.
We will return tomorrow
to take you to the castle.
I trust there will be no more...
surprises.
The sword did not
cut any vital organs
but the blood loss...
Tell me about it.
What were you thinking?
I didn't mean to cause
you any more trouble.
I was just trying to help.
No one can help me.
We have that in common.
Nate? Nate!
The signal from Ray's ATOM
suit is getting stronger.
Doesn't exactly look inviting,
does it?
It's like
"Ninja III: The Domination."
Never took you for a cinephile.
All I know is ninjas
like to hide in trees.
- I don't see anything.
- Exactly.
You don't find them, they find you.
Just because you saw ninjas
in a movie...
that doesn't make them real.
I have to side with Mick on this one.
They're real.
You think there's
a secret brotherhood of men
trained in the art of assassination?
I hate to break it to you, Amaya,
but I'm basically a ninja.
I miss the JSA.
Compartment 36
should be right about here.
What are you doing, Grey?
I'm looking for any hidden doors.
We don't have time for this.
Nate and Ray
are lost in Feudal Japan.
Let's just fix the ship and go.
Did you hear that, Jefferson?
Move.
- Oh, my God.
- Secret hatch.
With a sequencing lock.
Clearly, Captain Hunter
didn't want anyone getting in.
Or maybe he was trying to
keep something from getting out.
If I've learned one thing
from "Lost",
it's you don't go
opening secret hatches.
Ray's close.
Look sharp.
Haircut, let's get out of here.
We're saving your ass, again.
It is you who need rescuing.
Fellas, getting a little cold
in here without my suit.
You are already defeated
before you have even begun.
I have been trained in the art
of war by Shimura himself.
League of Assassins, class of '09.
Don't take it easy on me.
We got to go.
Oh. Hey, guys!
Wrong way, Haircut.
What about my suit?
We can get it later.
My friend's serum...
it's cured my hemophilia.
Oh, long story.
Short version...
my blood didn't clot
like normal people.
So if I were to cut myself shaving
or get a paper cut, I could die.
So every day,
you were afraid to live?
Pretty much.
In the Samurai tradition...
a warrior is always prepared
for death.
A woman celebrates when
her husband dies with honor.
That's hardcore.
A Samurai who fights without armor...
that is hardcore.
Nate, you're alive.
Oh, hey, guys!
- You found me.
- Bad timing?
Nope. Nope.
Masako, these are...
my friends I was telling you about.
Hajimemashite.
Can I get you something to drink?
Sake, lots of it.
What he meant to say
is thanks for your hospitality
but we must be going.
- No, I didn't.
- Amaya's right.
- Nate, let's go.
- I can't.
We can't leave.
Masako's supposed to marry
the Shogun Tokugawa Iemitsu.
Yeah, met him. Not a fan.
Well, the reason he sticks out
in the history books is
because he likes
to murder his wives.
And I can't leave Masako
to his mercy.
Especially since
he stole my ATOM suit.
Exactly. Wait, what?
You let the Shogun steal
a 21st century super-suit?
After I crash-landed
trying to rescue you.
How does the Shogun even know
how to operate your ATOM suit?
I designed it
so an idiot could use it.
An idiot does.
Guys, bottom line is,
if the Shogun has the ATOM suit,
it's not just Masako and
the village we have to protect.
He can use it to conquer
the whole region.
You said the Shogun's coming
for your new girlfriend.
Easier to defend a village
- than to attack a castle.
- But anyone who tries
to fight the Shogun will be cut down.
Except, if that person
is made of steel.
About that.
I'm having a little problem
accessing my powers.
Sounds like you're having
performance issues
and it looks like you're not
done training him yet.
Now the rest of us need to figure out
how we can defend a village.
Not me.
Wake me up when the action starts.
What is this place?
It appears to be some sort of armory.
There's a reason why
Rip didn't want us in here.
Some things you can't un-see.
But why the big secret?
Rip didn't trust us to know that
there were heavy-duty
weapons on board?
Well, would you?
- What the...
- Look, Jefferson.
Our old friend
has hailed the Waverider.
Let's play it.
Sorry to contact you like this,
Captain Hunter.
But I can't risk putting
any more lives in danger.
Thought this was from Barry Allen?
It is. Only from 40 years
in the future.
- And neither can this.
- Fascinating.
Which is why you'll keep what
I'm about to tell you a secret.
Even from the rest of your team.
The ATOM suit is made of
and powered by dwarf star alloy.
It's strong enough to withstand
bullets, arrows, and explosives.
- So it's impenetrable?
- Not quite.
Underneath the left thruster
is the alpha-stabilizer.
- Alpha-stabilizer, got it.
- If you destroy it,
the photons that stream
from suit's weapons systems
will overheat.
Theoretically,
causing somatic overload.
that's... that's comforting.
You have to get close to the Shogun.
And in order to do that,
you have to be able to harden.
Well, when you're putting it
in those terms, it isn't helping.
Neither is that.
It worked the last time.
Come on.
My serum is flawless.
Your lack of focus is the problem.
You think I'm not focusing?
Like... enough!
- I can't do it.
- Yes, you can.
You don't think
I don't want to save the girl,
spare the village, and be a hero
for once in my damn life?
I spent half of my childhood
in the hospital
where it didn't even occur to me
to dream about having superpowers.
But guess what?
I got them, I lost them.
Now I really, really need them,
and I can't get them back.
This isn't all about you.
I worked for years,
spent billions of dollars
to develop the ATOM suit.
I nearly died learning to shrink.
And now, I have to teach you
to destroy the very thing,
the only thing, that makes me a hero.
Wait?
"Somatic overload"
means destroy the suit?
Yeah, Nate.
We can't beat the Shogun
while he's wearing the suit.
So we have to blow the suit up.
Your powers are within you.
After today...
I'll have nothing left.
Ray...
You should all be safe here.
They've never seen foreigners before.
I was once just like them.
My village was also
small and isolated.
Some would say that my people
were superstitious.
But... in truth,
we were protected.
Protected by that?
Legend has it that
this totem was one of five
created by the gods
and given to the five
great tribes of Zambesi.
This totem harnesses the ashe,
or the... the life force
of the animal kingdom.
It was passed down to me
from my mother
and from hers before that.
And why did you leave?
I was recruited by the JSA...
and I realized that
the world was much larger
than just my village...
and that there were people
beyond its borders
who also needed protection.
Sometimes, I can't help but worry
that with me gone...
there's no one left to guard my home.
From people like Mr. Rory.
At the end of the day,
Mick does the right thing.
Usually.
You remind me of my son.
Why?
Was he a terrible teacher, too?
He was a great Samurai.
I built him the strongest
and most formidable armor
in all of Japan.
Forged him a sword
fit for an Emperor.
What happened to him?
My son was popular
with the men who served under him
and the Shogun resented him for it.
So he ordered Oda
to commit seppuku.
We will make sure
that the Shogun pays
for what he's done to your family.
Maybe.
Maybe not.
But I ask you...
Would I rather hold my son again
or his armor?
Your son, obviously.
An armor is nothing but iron,
leather, and silk.
It can be replaced.
But, the man...
who wears the armor is...
I get it.
You're saying I don't need
a suit of armor
to defeat the Shogun.
Don't be ridiculous.
He'll kill you in seconds.
Follow me.
I'm gonna die.
Yeah, probably.
That was actually your cue
to cheer me up.
Oh, if you accept death
you have nothing to fear.
I'm more afraid of what's
gonna happen to you if I die.
I know I have these powers inside me.
I just can't figure out
how to use them.
Does a child learn to laugh?
Does he sit and practice laughing?
No. He just laughs.
"Do or do not, there is no try."
Exactly.
Where did you learn that?
From a great sensei
from where I'm from.
Yoda.
Oh, this Master Yoda is very wise.
The Shogun approaches.
Get to the temple.
Where is my bride?
She's not leaving.
Not with you.
I'm just gonna need a second.
Find the villagers. Kill them.
Your form is all wrong.
I ordered Ichiro
to destroy that blade
after the death of his son.
Very well.
I will destroy it myself.
Konnichiwa,scumbag.
Go get him.
I will kill you
with your own armor.
Check the temple.
Rematch?
Who is your master?
I have no master.
A ronin.
You're not worthy of the effort.
You have fought with honor.
Now you will die with it.
About that.
This village is under our protection.
Leave now and we'll spare your lives.
A sword is only as deadly
as the man who wields it.
And armor is only as strong
as the man who wears it.
I don't want to shoot you guys.
I love ninjas.
That was the armature relay.
It enhances the limbs' reaction time.
Where the hell is Mick?
Probably ransacking
the village himself.
Told you ninjas were real.
That's the cooling system.
Trust me, it gets hot in there.
I know.
You think you are clever.
You dishonor my family
and torture my village.
I will enjoy killing you.
Your family will be
extinguished from history.
We haven't been introduced.
Name's Steel.
Remember, you got to hit...
I remember!
Do it!
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
- You did it.
- I did it.
Yeah...
you blew up the ATOM suit.
I am so sorry.
It's okay.
You steeled on.
Kind of proud of you.
Master Yoda taught you well.
Right, Yoda. Well, thank you.
I was thinking now that
your wedding is canceled...
You come from the sky.
Something tells me
you have to return.
I...
I'm glad the katana sword
found a worthy owner.
Me too.
You.
Don't think I didn't see
how you stood up to the Shogun.
Even though he's gone,
your village still needs a protector.
That sword,
what did you say
your family name was?
Yamashiro.
Thank you for loaning me
your son's armor.
I'm sorry it got
a bit dinged up in the battle.
Then it served its purpose.
Haircut.
Steel.
Sara says we got to clear out.
- Good-bye, Masako.
- Good-bye, Nate.
What an amazing time period.
Definitely my favorite,
besides the Old West.
Why are you two
goofy bastards so happy?
You lost your damn suit,
the food sucks
and I've got no proof ninjas exist.
What are you staring at?
I've figured you out.
Congratulations.
You act like this selfish meathead...
but secretly, you're not so bad.
You know, you might even
have the makings of a hero.
Well, that proves one thing.
You don't know me.
Perhaps not.
Trying to kill me again?
Trying to give you a present.
In case you ever need proof
you met an actual ninja.
All right. What's your secret?
What on earth do you mean?
Well, you two must be magicians
considering how badly damaged
the Waverider was
- before we left.
- Oh, that.
Well, Jefferson and I went over
the ship top to bottom.
And safe to say there are no
surprises left on the Waverider.
Great. I'll go prep for takeoff.
So are we gonna say something
about future-Barry's message or not?
Barry was very clear
about the team not knowing
what he told Captain Hunter.
- Except now we know.
- Indeed.
You were right, Jefferson.
Some things you just can't un- see.
I think it's time we said sayonara
to Feudal Japan.
Now, where to next?
I could always open the hatch,
jump out, and see where I land.
I say we just sit back and see
where the timestream takes us.
Aren't you forgetting that
Rex's killer is still at- large?
Not my problem.
I mean, we should find
the bastard and kill him.
Perhaps we can enjoy
a little takeoff music.
Oh, nice one, Gideon.
Captain Hunter always
enjoyed this song.
Time...
Speaking of problems.
Don't worry. We're gonna find Rip
and Hourman's killer.
In the meantime,
everyone just shut up
and let me do the flying.
Yes, it is