Not even the six can stop me, now!
Beebo want cuddles.
Guys? Guys!
- Dad.
- I'm sorry, Nora.
He died a good man.
He died a demon, Ray.
Oh, I've been cleaning up some Beebo
Just to scrub the time anomalies away
Hey, can't you see
The blue fluff blowing
Hello?
Who's there?
I'm just gonna use my hand
to block out the sun's glare
so I can see you...
You.
No!
No! It can't be you!
The Loom of Fate.
An ancient artifact
that has the power
to change any person's life story
without wrecking the timeline.
Anyone's, like...
Astra's.
And we give her a life
where her mum never died
and where she never goes to Hell.
If you think I'm helping you,
you're daft as a brush.
I destroyed that thing
for a bloody good reason, John-o.
Come on, Sara.
You know this can solve
all of our problems.
It can erase all of the Encores.
Yeah, and make
all of our dreams come true.
John, I'm sorry,
but I'm with Charlie on this one.
That kind of cosmic power
doesn't belong
in the hands of anyone.
Astra has made her choices, John.
It's not up to you to undo them.
Now, this...
will be the solution
to our Encore problem.
Captain Lance,
there is a new Encore detected
in Salvation, 1874.
I love my Prognosticator.
All right, Legends!
Grab your cowboy hats
and leather straps
because we are going to...
Where is everyone?
I, might have got
a bit sentimental on my deathbed
and encouraged Raymond
to carpe his diem.
Nice rock.
She'll love that.
And when she finds it...
I'll pop the question.
She's here. She's really here.
Oh, man.
It's really happening.
Our work here is done.
Our boy is all grown up.
Nora Darhk, welcome.
I will have the pleasure
of serving you this evening.
Thanks, Gare.
Wow, Ray.
You really went all out
for date night.
I thought we were just having pizza.
Oh. I got a little inspired, I guess.
Yeah. Yeah, well...
I see Pippa is still your charge.
Yes, until we figure out
her heart's deepest need.
Big talker, I see.
Defiling the library, I see.
Yeah, well, you know,
I've quit smoking.
So, I need a new habit.
- Doing some research?
- Yeah. Yeah.
I need to find the Loom of Fate
to save Astra.
But since, Charlie
isn't making it easy for me,
I am doing it the hard way.
Why not ask an historian?
All right then, Mr. Professor,
tell me, what do you know?
Well, when I was in grad school,
my professor showed me a diary
of an explorer named
Ernest Shackleton.
Now, Shackleton
was obsessed with the Loom
and he believed a piece of it
was buried under the South Pole.
So, if I'm to find the Loom,
I've got to search the South Pole.
Shackleton thought so.
Bloody hell.
Nice one, mate.
Don't worry, John.
We'll figure out another way
to help you and Astra.
That ought to cool his jets.
Hey, Mick.
Saddle up.
We're going to the Wild West.
Is everything okay in there?
He's been in there for days.
What are you still doing here?
Exfoliating.
Mick, get out here right now!
- What?
- What is going on?
Someone's trashing
Rebecca Silver online.
Oh, cute. You have a troll.
What's wrong with your face?
Zari, your mission is to help Mick.
Okay. I have so many makeover ideas.
With his troll problem.
Did I just fritz out of existence?
Help! A train coming! Help me!
Please! Help me. Untie me.
I'm too beautiful to die so young.
Train's coming!
Oh, my God! Oh, God! The train!
Oh, God!
Director Sharpe, you saved me.
Okay.
Wait, wait a second.
Did you just say "Director Sharpe"?
Yeah.
Gary, what year are you from?
The present. 2018.
Okay, listen.
I need you to tell us who did this,
and then immediately
courier back to the Bureau.
I can't.
He stole my Time Courier.
Who?
Hi, Nora-doll.
Daddy's home.
Dad.
Oh, Nora-doll, I missed you so much.
This is amazing.
How are you...
You are an Encore.
Look, all I know is,
I'm up here right now
as part of some
soul-harvesting pyramid scheme.
Honestly, I can't keep up
with these millennials
and all their newfangled
world-domination plans.
So, you're doing
the whole villain thing again.
Well, you, no, I mean...
Part of my parole agreement.
But after spending two years in Hell
worrying about my little girl,
I had to come and see you first.
But look at this place!
You must be a master sorceress
by now.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
This is just a place
where I hang my hat
and do my dark rituals.
"Dark rituals."
How did you find me? Blood magic?
Your Palmer Tech watch.
It still has location-sharing on.
Palmer Tech, right.
Ray!
Sorry for the delay.
Gary seems to have run off.
My dad's here.
- What?
- My dad's here!
Your dad's here?
Oh, man. Is he an Encore?
Oh, man.
And Sara just found herself
a Hell Sword.
- Which means...
- She'll kill him.
- What do we do? What do we do?
- You have to leave.
- What about Pippa? Pippa! Pippa!
- Pippa. Pippa.
You have to take her.
You have to keep her comfortable,
so that she doesn't summon me.
That's it. That's gonna work.
- Thanks, Ray.
- Okay.
"Rebecca Silver knows
as much about love
as a teenage boy's sock drawer."
Okay. Bad reviews,
they just come with celebrity.
You should have heard
what they said about my perfume
when it made people
bleed out their noses.
He's gonna get more
than a bloody nose.
No. Don't stoop to his level.
Inside every troll is the heart of
a fan just dying for some attention.
And some swag.
One signed book, and he'll be
a Rebecca Silver stan forever.
Ta-da!
What's that?
Oh, this is a TV show
I used to watch when I was a kid.
It really helped me dig deep
and communicate my feelings better.
It's called
Mister Parker's Cul De Sac.
And I think
you're really gonna like it.
Hi.
Welcome to my cul-de-sac, friend
That's a street that ends in a circle
The thing about circles
Is they never end
So our friendship will be universal
This is very dumb.
Hi, boys and girls.
Well, just give it a chance, okay?
Today, we're going to have
ourselves a wonderful...
And how about 20 bucks?
I'll be right back.
Could you ever imagine
what it'd be like to live underwater?
So? Bachelor party?
No.
Nora's dad literally came back
from the dead
and ruined the evening.
Damien Darhk?
Anyway, Nora said she can handle it,
and so, she's handling it.
But we can't let anyone interfere.
Especially not Sara.
I mean,
he is your future father-in-law.
You don't think
we could talk Sara down?
When I see Damien Darhk,
I'm gonna kill him
for good this time.
What about Nora?
Well, ideally, she never finds out.
- Gideon, any hits?
- Yes, Captain.
In fact,
I'm detecting new Encore activity
at Constantine's home in 2020.
All right, let's do this discreetly.
Just us, no boys.
You know how sentimental
they can get.
- Yep.
- You also received a call
from a Wild Dog while you were away.
Yep, got it. Thanks, Gideon.
What was that all about?
Oh, I'm sure it's nothing.
This is extremely pornographic.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Troll made a post.
Must have gotten his swag back.
Oh, look,
he's showing off your signature.
This is perfect.
What the...
That little punk.
Okay. Change of tactic.
What are you doing?
Scouring the metadata from his posts
to composite his location.
- You hack?
- No.
- It's a girl.
- It's okay. Just go.
Do you know who I am?
Yeah, what are you doing here, Becky?
"I am Rebecca Silver, and you will
listen to me, you pimple-faced..."
- But she doesn't have pimples.
- Just go. Keep going.
"I'm a celebrated author.
My latest novel was a triumph
and you know it.
What... what the hell
have you done with your life
and who are you to judge others?"
Mick?
Ali?
Mick, why... why are you here?
- Why are you here?
- I live here.
Why is she filming us?
This your kid?
Well, I guess, since you're here,
I might as well tell you.
She's your kid, too.
This is Lita, your daughter.
Twist!
Oh, he's fine.
Well, that was my wizard's tower.
I love it.
You can just smell
the dark forces at work in here.
- Safe neighborhood?
- Super safe.
People just mostly keep
to themselves.
Good.
You know what the worst
kind of neighbors are?
- Kids.
- Hate kids.
You know, all I've ever asked for
are neighbors I don't have to kill.
But for people like us...
sometimes, it's kill or be killed.
You know what?
Better safe than sorry.
Right, Dad?
Atta girl.
- Did she see us?
- I don't know.
- What was that?
- You know what?
I have a surprise
for you in the study.
Well, I love surprises.
Yes, I saw you!
Listen, I know you're here
to kill my dad.
And I know you have good reason.
But I'm asking you, as my friends...
just to give me this one night
to handle it my way.
And what exactly is your way?
This...
Dad, may I present my...
henchmen.
Women.
- People. Hench-people.
- Wait a minute.
Are you saying
the head of the Time Bureau
and the Captain of the Waverider
work for you now?
Well, I can be very convincing.
That is a heck of a find.
Eleventh century Mongolia,
if I'm not mistaken.
Oh, yeah!
That's just a little something
they picked up for me.
Thanks.
It's not for indoor use, though.
So, I'm just gonna...
Safety first, Nora-doll.
Thanks, you guys, for playing along.
Tick-tock, ladies.
I could really use that cocktail
about now.
Remind me again why
I shouldn't go in there right now
and stab him with Khan's sword.
He's my dad.
He's also one of the most powerful
dark warlocks on the planet, so...
Wait.
What if he was just a man?
- What?
- There's a potion
that can strip him of his powers.
It's complicated to make,
but there are ingredients here
in this house.
I know we can make it work.
We can put it in his dinner.
- I volunteer as tribute.
- Gary.
What the hell are you doing in there?
I was cowering, from the man
who almost killed me with the train.
Give me the recipe to your potion,
I will not fail you.
Bad idea.
- Do it for book club.
- What?
Are you seriously
invoking book club right now?
Yeah.
You get one of those.
You get one. Are you sure?
Ava, I am invoking book club
to ask you to give me
one night with my dad.
And if he is a harmless,
normal man by the end of it...
you let him live.
Where are you going, Captain Cold?
Antarctica, of course.
That place is the worst.
But I'm following up
on the lead that you...
Bloody shape-shifters.
What?
Charlie. She used your face
to send me on some dead-end trail.
Send me to Antarctica.
Freeze my bloody arse off!
No! I'm getting off
this gormless jam jar.
Since there's no one here
that can help me, I'll do it my way.
Alone.
All right. I think I got
these stupid crostinis right.
How's the salad?
It just needs to be dressed,
and then there's the soup.
How many courses
did Ray have planned?
By my count, five.
Six if you include cocktails.
Come on, Ray.
Nobody gets laid after six courses.
Gary, how's the potion coming along?
Don't rush me.
Everything has to be done precisely
- or it will not work.
- Okay. Are you talking entree...
It'll be done by dessert.
Then let's get this dinner started.
Hello, you've reached
the office of Sara Lance.
How can I help you?
Well, hello, Mr. Dog.
What is this in reference to?
Cheers.
Oh, more crostinis!
These are delicious.
Bloody hell. Gary!
Damien Darhk.
John Constantine.
You know, I don't think
we've actually ever met before,
seeing as you're still breathing.
But you have died before,
though, right?
So, what's about to happen
should feel a little familiar.
Remitte istud.
That was an heirloom, you...
Stop it! Both of you.
This vagrant is trespassing.
This is my house, you plonker.
Your house? Nora, I thought...
Well...
technically, it is his house.
His name is on the title.
But, in practice...
it's our house.
Right, babe?
Just go with it.
Right, love.
My love, that is
because we are indeed together.
Oh, Nora-doll.
Here, I thought you were all alone.
But now, I know
that you have a powerful
warlock in your life.
Johnny C, you bring it in here.
You rascal!
The thing about circles is
They never end
So our friendship will be universal
Why does he keep changing his shoes?
Changing his shoes
is a soothing ritual
which takes him
from one space to another.
Where's my fairy godmother?
She's busy with her father.
So, why are you here and not there?
She asked me to give them space,
and I am respecting her boundaries.
She's hiding you from her dad.
Mr. Parker says you can love
whoever you want to love
and to not be ashamed.
Well, you don't have to quote
Season eight, Episode 15 to me.
Okay?
But look, she's not trying to hide...
Fairy godmother!
Come here, right now!
Damn it, Ray! I said no summoning.
Do you have any idea how many plates
I'm spinning right now,
trying to keep my dad happy?
Many. But quick question.
Are you hiding me?
Of course I am.
I am telling him
a thousand lies right now
to make sure nobody gets killed.
Oh, well,
why not just tell him the truth?
"Why not just tell him the truth?"
Okay.
Why don't I just tell
my megalomaniac dad
that his little girl is a slave
to the whims of children
and is schtupping an Eagle Scout?
That sounds amazing.
The longer you lie
about who you really are
the harder it's gonna be
when the truth finally comes out.
Listen, can you just give me
this one night?
Okay? Just help me out.
And save the guilt trip? Please.
- Okay?
- Of course.
- Okay? Good? Everything good?
Okay. Great.
Good night, boys and girls.
Do you need to change your shoes?
I think I do.
I named her Lita, after...
Yeah. Lita Ford of The Runaways.
Sorry I never told you.
Actually, I looked you up
after I found out I was pregnant
but you were in jail.
Again.
So, it...
It must have been challenging,
raising a kid by yourself.
I made it work.
Sure, Lita would ask about her dad,
but whenever she did...
She would just say, you know,
"My standards were low
and his sperm count was high."
- Oh, God.
- But...
when I learned that Rebecca Silver
was actually him...
I guess I let it slip that we
had hooked up at our reunion.
Lita's a smart kid.
I guess she figured it out.
Yeah. My dad writes crappy novels.
- They're brilliant.
- Debatable.
Either way, I still hate you.
Lita, he... he didn't know.
But, I guess now that the pussycat's
out of the pouch...
guess you two can get
to know one another.
Sounds like fun.
No! What the hell are you doing?
We were never here.
True story, that.
I never knew that...
Wine!
Good to see you two getting along.
Oh, we're just telling stories,
aren't we?
You know, I shouldn't be shocked
that you'd be drawn
to a fellow after your pop's
old line of work.
Oh, well, you know me, Dad.
I can't help
but keep the family business going.
That's my girl.
Not that I could ever live up
to a great collector
of artifacts such as yourself.
Oh, but sadly, some things
could never be found.
You take for instance,
the Loom of Fate.
I never did find that one.
That's because it was scattered
across the multi-verse.
Well, it's all on one Earth now.
Ours.
Intriguing.
Still, you'd need a Fate to put it
all together and operate it.
Right. Sounds like there's no point
in even looking for it, right, John?
Yeah, especially with so many
exciting opportunities
to think about, right, babe?
Yep. Maybe not the time.
I'm sensing something juicy
bubbling with the help.
No, I don't...
Is there trouble in paradise?
You know what?
It's none of your damn business.
Oh, sit and spill.
Uncle Damien wants
to hear everything.
No, they don't have to...
You know what?
Someone forgot
to tell their girlfriend
about a job offer
they received to work in Star City.
- Babe.
- Permanently.
I was going to talk to you about it
before it became permanent.
- So, you're actually considering it?
- Yes.
I don't know... Okay, how is that
supposed to work with you there
and me, one of Nora's hench-people?
Sara, she's right.
You know, long-distance
relationships can be tough.
- Thank you.
- It wasn't going
to be a long-distance relationship.
I thought that we could go together.
This... this is why I always have
a no-fraternizing policy
with my staff.
Next course, please.
The potion is now purple,
and therefore...
ready to de-power the supervillain.
So, let me get this straight.
You stood up for yourself,
and she shut you down?
She just, doesn't think
that Damien would accept me.
But aren't you setting yourself up
for a lifetime of lies?
Will you have to lie
when Damien comes to visit?
Or when you guys have kids?
Because you know
those babies are going to have
that beautiful Palmer jawline.
The Palmer jawline
is a dominant gene.
Damn right.
- Am I rushing into this?
- Yes!
We couldn't say something
unless you said something. Ray...
It feels rushed.
She's embarrassed of you.
After you made the perfect dinner,
took a massage class
and hid an engagement ring
in the mousse?
The ring is in the mousse!
Well, I hope
you saved room for dessert.
Chocolate mousse.
Yeah, you should try it.
Don't eat the mousse.
- There's no chocolate in Hell.
- Perfection!
Mousse!
- What's that?
- Chocolate mousse.
This has always been your favorite,
right, Dad?
This just looks sinful.
Everybody, isn't this delicious?
Perfection!
A ring?
Well, that's unexpected.
I'm surmising that perhaps,
that cup was put in front
of the wrong person.
John, was there a question
that you wanted to ask?
"Question"?
Oh, right, yeah!
Question, of course.
Nora Darhk...
will you marry me?
Just when I thought this night
couldn't get any better,
my daughter has found
the love of her life.
Forget the mousse.
- More champagne!
- No.
What? What? I'm sorry, what was that?
- I thought you said no.
- No.
Okay, she said...
Did she say "no"?
No, I won't marry John...
because I can't lie
to you anymore, Dad.
Oh, thank God.
Johnny C, Johnny C,
Johnny C, don't, what are you doing?
Dad, Sara and Ava
aren't my henchwomen.
They're just my friends.
I'm not a powerful sorceress.
I'm a fairy godmother.
Dad, this isn't my house.
John isn't my boyfriend.
He is.
And I love him madly.
Hi, Damien, Mr. Darhk.
Since you're here, I was wondering
if I could get your blessing
to have your daughter's hand
in marriage?
You deceived me, Nora-doll.
Your own father.
You tried to poison me.
That's, that's not as bad
as it looks.
I've been gone
for less than two years, and you...
You're a completely different person.
And I know who's to blame.
No, no, no, no. Dad!
Stop! Stop!
Inferni.
Brexit!
- No!
- Let him go.
Stop, Dad!
Dad, I am not a child.
You can't just kill
my friends anymore!
Did you think you were gonna kill me
with that little toy, Lance?
Why don't you give me
a chance and find out?
That's no Mongolian relic.
That's a Hell Sword.
My, oh, my.
I am so going to enjoy
obliterating all of you.
It's after 5:00
And I could use a cold one
Is Mr. Parker getting tipsy?
The guy has done 4,000 hours
of children's television.
He's earned it.
Oi! How have you guys
not noticed the Encore alarm?
- It's at Constantine's house.
- Ray.
- Let's go.
- I wanna go.
No!
I wish it.
Now, that guy is marriage material.
Quit insulting Ray!
He made you poison your own father.
No, he didn't. That was my idea.
That's because he twisted you.
Look at you.
You're, you're a powerless fairy.
That's it! Pippa, make a wish.
Yes. You can stop this.
This is the only way you'll learn.
I wish you were all
on Mister Parker's Cul De Sac.
Welcome to my cul-de-sac, friend
That's a street that ends in a circle
The thing about circles
Is they never end
So a friendship would be universal
- Hello, boys and girls.
- Hi, Mr. Parker.
Hope you're having a wonderful day.
I sure am.
Come with me.
What the...
Boys and girls, please welcome
my friends Nora and Damien.
Now, why don't we discuss
our problems?
Damien, what seems to be
on your mind?
Well, you simpleton,
my child means everything to me
and you've completely
corrupted her into this!
See, this is why I had to lie.
I knew you couldn't handle it
because emotionally,
you're the child!
Well, I think this is gonna be
tougher than we thought, kids.
Why don't we travel
to the Land of Make 'Em Ups
with Gary,
the Unspeakable Train Abomination?
- Hi, Gary.
- Toot, toot, everybody, toot, toot!
Toot, toot, to you!
- Hello, John.
- Hello, Charlie.
- Hey, Ava.
- Yeah, Sara?
Are you bloody kidding me?
Puppets? Again?
I wanted to say that I feel bad
that I made you feel bad.
Oh, well, maybe we should
communicate.
I'm sorry I kept the job offer
in Puppet Star City a secret.
I was only considering it because I
thought you wanted to settle down.
Well, I used to want that.
But I've been having
a lot of fun on the ship.
Then I'll tell Puppet Wild Dog
to shove it!
- Yay!
Maybe you can work out
your problem with communication.
Yeah!
You were gonna send me
to the South Pole, Charlie.
You don't understand
how dangerous that Loom is, John-o.
It gave my sisters and me control
over everyone's lives.
I smashed that thing,
so we could be free.
People could be free to rebel,
free to be weird.
Oh, come on, Charlie.
If you sensed that the Loom was
in one universe again,
what's to say
your sisters didn't feel it, too?
What's to stop them going after it,
and for the wrong reasons?
Listen, I will use
the Loom to help Astra.
And then, I will help you destroy it,
forever this time.
Forever?
Deal?
Deal.
Yay for communication
and cooperation!
Yay.
I wonder who that is?
It's Bike Messenger Behrad.
I hope you're having a wonderful day.
Let's see what was delivered.
Open it! Open it!
It's the Safe Space Sombrero.
Please make it stop.
Make it just stop.
I am going to just...
Only the person wearing
the Safe Space Sombrero may speak.
You've ruined her life.
Her life is absolutely in shambles
because of you and the idiot brigade
she hangs out with.
I mean, look at her. She is trapped
in this horrible fairy godmother job.
Horrible job?
You know what, Dad?
My life now...
that's not Ray's choice, it's mine.
I know you think
all magic should be self-serving,
but I like helping kids
because being raised by a demon cult
instead of my own father?
That wasn't my choice.
That was yours.
So, maybe working with kids
helps me cope with that.
And you're right.
I am not the Nora-doll you remember.
I like who I am...
and I'm never going back.
I've been an ass.
I've had this vision of this life
that would make you happy.
Obviously, I was wrong.
I just want you to be proud of me.
Proud?
Nora-doll...
I am.
Really?
I really am.
Oh, kids, look, the sun is smiling.
I thought my family was messed up,
but these guys are truly deranged.
I want to be with my own family now.
Fairy Godmother, I release you.
It worked!
I've been cured.
I'm not afraid of trains anymore!
No hard feelings, Ray.
Yes.
- Yes?
- Yes.
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
I love you so much.
I'm so sorry I tried to hide you.
I can't wait to marry you.
So, let's... let's do it.
Let's do it, let's do it right now.
- Right now?
- Right now.
I'm off-duty. My dad's here.
His schedule's unpredictable.
So, let's... let's do it.
Right now. Tonight.
Yeah. Okay.
- Okay? Okay!
- Okay.
You're not married yet.
Champagne?
I wanna tell you how much
I appreciate everything you've done
for my daughter.
Thank you,
but, I haven't really done that much.
She's pretty incredible
all on her own.
Yeah, but you make her happy.
That's something
that I ultimately failed at
when I was the main man in her life.
Well, you know, I... I think
you're being too hard on yourself.
I don't need a pep talk.
But I do need you
to do something for me.
I need you to support her.
Of course. Always.
No, I don't think you understand
what I'm trying to say.
Nora's job is very important
to her...
and she can't do it
on that silly little ship of yours.
Nora belongs in the real world...
and you belong together.
I hope you understand
what I'm trying to say here.
Do the right thing, son,
or I'll come back and get you.
I'm only kidding.
Okay. That's what I thought.
But not really.
Eating your feelings, I see?
She's better off without me.
She reached out to you for a reason.
She's an idiot. I'm an idiot.
She's a pain in the ass.
I'm a pain in the ass.
The fact that she's not already
in juvie is a miracle,
and it proves one thing.
What?
I'm no good for her.
Are you sure about that?
You know what?
You've inspired me
to forego this evil thing.
Maybe this old dog
can learn some new tricks.
So you'll stick around for a bit?
Oh, I think it's time both of us
move on to the next chapter.
Promise you'll check in on me
once in a while?
Of course.
I'll never be far.
I love you, Nora-doll.
I love you, Dad.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Taking off already?
Oh, I hate prolonged goodbyes.
I'd rather slip out while everyone's
in there still having a good time.
So, where are you going?
I was given this Encore
under certain conditions.
I was ordered
to cause pain and misery
and damn more souls to Hell.
But instead, you decided
to check in on your Nora-doll.
I just wanted to make sure
that my little girl's okay.
And she is.
Thanks to the help of you idiots.
Plus, Astra's going to recall me soon
to an eternity of torture.
I didn't want to bum my daughter out
with all of that
on her wedding night.
I know you'll never forgive me.
To tell you the truth...
I won't, either.