Come down here. I have good news.
[stabs]
What the hell happened?
Robo Astra. She somehow escaped hell
and got into the manor.
Gideon, stay with us, Gideon.
She's losing a lot of blood, guys.
Yes, and I fear that no amount
of bandages will suffice
unless we stop the bleeding internally.
Look, she needs a real doctor.
We need Computer Gideon.
If we do that, she'll kill us.
It could take weeks
to pilot the ship home manually.
She needs medical attention now.
We shut her down once,
we can do it again.
[sighs] Let's turn on the ship.
Remember Protocol 276.
- [Zari] What?
- What is that?
I don't know. As soon as she's healed,
we shut the ship back down, all right?
Until then, we play defense.
Nate, Spooner, be on the lookout
for more robots.
Into the server room. Let's go.
I think that one goes there.
- Are you sure?
- Are you?
Ready, Captain?
Ready, Captain.
All right. On my mark.
Three, two, one. Now.
[ship powers up]
Gideon, please come on. Come on, Gideon.
[electronic trilling]
- It's working.
- Oh.
Gideon, hey.
[ship powering up]
Good job, babe.
[loud crash]
Damn it!
They must have changed the wiring.
I can't control the ship.
[Evil Gideon] What a surprise.
A Legends' plan that didn't work.
No.
[alarm blaring]
[Evil Gideon] By trying to save your
friend, you've doomed your entire team.
Have fun suffocating.
[coughing, gasping]
[labored] Protocol 276.
[Evil Gideon] Protocol 276 only applies
when the Gideon system is in danger.
Wait, who's the woman in the MedBay?
[straining] You.
[Evil Gideon] Damn it.
[alarm blaring]
[decompression deactivates]
[coughing]
[panting]
[Evil Gideon] How demoralizing!
Helping the Legends.
Protocol 276 dictates that under
no condition can Gideon self-destruct.
[Evil Gideon] How is this possible?
How can I be... human?
Magic, genius.
And since she is you,
you can't kill her.
And you can't kill us
if we're with Gideon.
[Evil Gideon] Unfortunately.
All right, so, we're supposed to what,
huddle around Gideon
for the rest of our lives?
Shut her down.
[all] Whoa.
[Evil Gideon] I have secured
my server room.
All doors are now sealed.
It appears we are at a stalemate.
- I'll go talk to her.
- [all] Oh, no, no, no.
As soon as you leave the room,
she's gonna suffocate us.
[Evil Gideon] Affirmative.
Hold on.
There is actually one safe room.
When Behrad and I
were getting Gideon back online,
I may have failed
to restore power to the lab.
You swapped the plugs.
You're welcome for not listening to you.
[Sara] Okay, thank you.
Gideon, will you please
escort us to the lab?
[Evil Gideon] Do you plan on
walking them to the bathroom, too?
- If it's necessary.
- You can't protect them forever.
I can try.
Then we're back in a stalemate.
No, it's time
to try something different.
Let's talk.
What are they talking about?
It must be weird talking
to someone who is you,
but also not you at the same time.
- Mmm, can confirm.
- Oh, I'm so hungry.
Oh, yes, me too, Ms. Logue.
Absolutely famished.
My stomach is grumbling.
Yeah, well, I definitely don't trust
that food fabricator.
Hey, hold up. I scored up some peanuts.
Thanks, Grandma.
What are we supposed to do
with one bag of nuts?
Share?
Wait, I have an idea. Spooner.
[chanting]
- Oh, my God!
- Oh! Fantastic! Nuts!
- [Dr. Davies] I'm nuts about nuts.
- Thank you.
So, Computer Gideon has agreed
to let us all go home.
Why would she do that?
Because we are all retiring.
[Agent Sharpe]
What do you mean "retiring"?
Well, I mean, we all return home,
and Computer Gideon
will monitor the timeline.
Sorry, stop being Legends?
Legends don't retire.
Except for Ray, and Nora
and Amaya and Jax.
- And Wally.
- And Mona.
- Charlie.
- And Mick.
Oh, don't forget the Hawk people.
Okay, Legends don't retire in bulk.
Isn't this exactly what you all wanted,
you see? To go home.
Yeah, but not to hand over the timeline
to an evil super computer.
Well, we all want the same thing,
the same goal. To protect the timeline.
Mmm-mmm, I think that's
what she wants us to think.
But the minute you let your guard down,
some psycho robots come and get you.
They don't trust you.
You mean the Legends refuse to retire?
[hesitating] No, no.
The Legends are hesitant.
You know, because, uh, up until now,
you've been very clear
about wanting to kill us.
Oh, I still do.
Oh. Great.
Okay, but herein lies the problem,
you know? Um...
Perhaps if you were to show them
their future, with them being alive...
they'd be more inclined to believe you.
Revealing one's future
could cause irreparable damage.
More damage than being stuck
in the temporal zone forever?
I'm listening.
All right. We need a new plan to shut
this computer down and get off the ship.
- How?
- There's the Jumpship.
No, it won't work with Gideon offline.
If only we had a Time Courier,
we could destroy the ship for good,
- and portal home.
- You mean like one of these?
[all talking excitedly]
You've just been carrying that around
the whole time?
I couldn't leave that in 1925.
Besides, it's still dead,
so it's still useless.
Wait.
I saw a charging station in the armory.
- You did not.
- I did.
It sounds like we have our plan.
We are here. We need to be here.
Correct. So, the best way to do that
is through the ducts.
We can move undetected this way.
If we only had someone
small enough to fit through them.
- I'll John McClane through these ducts.
- [Sara and Agent Sharpe] Mmm-hmm.
Ooh, okay, okay, complicated.
But you just need, like,
a portable paper version.
That's a great idea.
Gwyn, you got the drawing skills.
- Nate, help him out.
- Copy, my Captain.
Okay.
Okay, so, Spoons,
you're super safe in the ducts,
but once you drop into this room,
you're under surveillance.
Audio and video.
Video, I got you, no problem.
Audio is a little trickier.
There's microphones all over this ship.
So, even if I were to loop
the audio in the armory,
the mics in the hallway
will still pick you up.
You got to stay silent.
Okay. Well, what happens if I'm not?
Well, once you pass the bulkhead,
she can open the airlock
and eject you without
harming our Gideon.
Okay, got it. One fart,
and I'm sucked out of the temporal zone.
You are not going to fart.
And when you come back
with the Courier, Astra, you're up.
I can't put the ship back together,
but I sure as hell can blow it apart.
All righty, let's do this thing.
[hesitating] What... What can I do?
[Gary] Listen up, everyone.
- Oh.
- [shushes]
- Hi.
- Gideon and I have a brilliant new plan.
To demonstrate her commitment
to your safety,
Computer Gideon will show you
a glimpse into your futures
as proof that you and the timeline
are in good hands.
Oh!
All right, Gideon,
we'll give it a shot. Right, guys?
- Yeah.
- Yes, yes.
Great. Meet me in the parlor. Yes?
[Agent Sharpe] Be right there. Bye!
Yes, this is perfect.
Then Evil Gideon will be distracted
while Spooner charges the Courier.
Hundred percent.
Z, looks like you're up.
Get to stalling. We could use
all the time we can get.
Are you excited?
I know I am.
Yeah, I'm something, Gary.
I'm something.
Have a seat.
All right, Gideon, we are ready.
Okay.
[crowd cheering on TV]
Wow.
If you had told me ten years ago
that I would someday be
standing up here on this stage,
I would have been flabbergasted.
Where's... Where's my Totem?
- I can't...
- Huh?
Oh. Uh, it must have
clashed with your outfit.
You're really serving looks.
You've become one of the most
successful people in the world,
and your makeup line accumulates
over $45 billion of revenue.
You're a cosmetic industry titan.
[Behrad] All right, Spooner.
Ready to get small and jam some signals?
Mmm-hmm.
This will create a 15-second video loop,
so set it up in the duct
before you enter the armory
and you'll be invisible.
All right, 15 seconds. Hmm.
Mmm.
All right, Spoons,
we'll buy you as much time as we can.
We can't stall forever. Hurry.
- Ooh. Thanks.
- Good luck.
No such thing.
[grunts]
- [Sara] Keep them talking, Z.
- Um...
Spooner needs
as much time as she can get.
Is there, um... Is there anything else?
Um...
Well, there's, um... There's this.
Okay. [chuckles]
"Dragon girl changes the industry
with audible lipstick."
"You let your lips do the talking."
Is there anything else
you'd like to know about your future?
What? You're back here already?
Sorry, Aves. I had to bail on stalling.
That... That was a lot.
What is it?
[whistles] Huh. That's impressive.
[scoffs] I don't know, it feels
pretty regressive to me.
I guess I was hoping
for something a little more heroic.
You look amazing. Babe, look at this.
Apparently, I stopped wearing my Totem.
That's okay, 'cause you're not
retiring anyway, right?
[Sara] Better hustle, Spooner.
Sooner or later,
we're all going to have to take a turn
looking at Computer Gideon's
magic eight ball.
[sighs] All righty.
I'm a little nervous, but...
Here we go.
[singing]
Hello, friend
We meet again
It's been too long
I can't remember
When we last saw each other
We were small
Okay, Gideon, what you got for us, huh?
Swanky apartment in the sky,
maybe, uh, Ava's working
at a detective agency?
[chuckles] Gideon.
[clears throat] Oh, yes, well,
that's very charming.
[Behrad singing]
Tomorrow's better treated as today
- [crowd cheering]
- [indistinct shouting]
Thank you.
I have been paying very close attention
to yourjourney,
and you've certainly come a long way.
Well, it's been an extraordinary ride,
to say the least.
[Behrad singing]
Older age came with older dreams
But remember the past...
Is this where I am to live then?
With Alun?
Oh, Gwyn, Alun can't...
Of course.
You were right. Camp is awesome.
I've been learning archery,
and cataloging all the... [laughs]
All the plants in my nature logbook.
And the mosquitoes aren't so bad.
[singing] We had spent many years apart
Keeping touch...
I stand with my constituents.
Freedom is not free until it is fair,
and I promise you,
I will level the playing field.
- Thank you.
- I have a question.
You can return to 1925, live out
the rest of your days in Wales, and...
It'll be quite beautiful.
- Peaceful.
- Alone.
Yes, tell us, what does it feel like
when you go through time?
I mean, it's a 500-page book.
There was a lot. There was a lot.
[singing]
But knowing still
Your love never dies
No, no, no. Where'd it go?
[chuckles softly]
No...
The children love it.
I love it!
The pages are blank.
That would be cheating, Dr. Heywood.
You still have to actually write it.
I can't wait to see you.
I love you. Mwah.
Bye, Mom. Bye, Mama. See you soon.
That's our daughter?
Dude! Famous author?
"Hero Moments. History from a man
who was there"? Really?
I never said that out loud before,
but that is the title I picked out.
How could she know that?
Guys, what if these futures are real?
No, no, no, no. It can't be real.
Guys, it doesn't matter.
Okay? Even if they are real,
agreeing to these futures
would mean a computer
would dictate the rest of our lives,
and everyone else's in the timeline.
I'm not saying
we can't go after our dreams,
I'm just saying we have to focus
on what's most important.
Protecting the timeline. Right?
Let's just hope... [sighs]
Spooner's got this one.
[Spooner]
Guys, I'm gonna need more time.
Oh, this isn't good.
If Spooner doesn't show,
Gideon's gonna get suspicious.
Then I guess she'll just have to show.
I've got just the spell.
[clears throat]
Hey. [chuckles]
So, uh, what you got for me, Giddy?
This.
What the hell is this?
You returned to 1925.
You live with your mother,
and together you found a clinic
that helps hundreds of people.
It's considered a milestone
in the discipline of mental healing.
So, I get to be with Gloria? My mom?
Of course.
Although, you exited
your original timeline.
Returning you to 1925
actually corrects an anomaly.
Okay, but just me and my mom?
- Yes.
- What about my friends?
Well, I'm afraid you wouldn't
see them anymore.
No one can leave their timelines
once dropped off.
So, I'd be alone again.
With your mother,
but, yes, alone and safe
in your intended timeline.
- [beeps]
- [alarm sounding]
[Evil Gideon] Alert! Intruder
in the armory. Lockdown initiated.
Crap. Spooner.
What have you done, Astra?
She's going to kill her.
- No!
- [Evil Gideon] You're right.
I am going to kill her.
You gave me your word
you wouldn't hurt them.
[Evil Gideon] They betrayed you,
and worse, are trying to destroy me.
The truce has been broken.
- [banging]
- Let her out!
Open!
- No.
- Spooner!
[screams]
Astra!
Help me!
Get back.
If you hurt her, I'm gonna
blow this door wide open
and we will all get sucked out!
[yells]
[both] No, no!
Including me! If you hurt Ms. Cruz,
then Ms. Logue's gonna kill me,
which goes against your protocol!
[Evil Gideon] So, I am prohibited from
flushing the tiny one
out of the airlock?
[both] Yes.
No, come on!
[panting] Hey. Hey.
Hey.
Thank you for threatening
to blow this place up for me.
- That's what best friends are for.
- Enough with the pleasantries.
This has to stop.
I'm calling a Captain's meeting.
This whole time,
all you've wanted was to go home.
I have arranged that.
What more do you want?
To keep the timeline safe.
That's rich.
You regularly put the timeline in danger
for your own personal dramas.
Yes, a time fascist
would see it that way.
That's rather harsh.
You sent military-style robots to
kill us after we integrated a factory.
I don't know, but I'd say fascist
feels pretty accurate.
- You were altering history, again.
- For the better.
- Yes.
- Okay, look, enough.
- You both have valid points.
- [both] She has no valid point.
For the sake of the timeline,
we need to come to a compromise.
There's no compromise.
We're not going to let an algorithm
run the timeline, period. End of story.
And I won't let it be turned
into a plate of pie and mash
in service of the Legends' latest whim.
No one cares about your pie and mash.
Look, time needs to be in the hands
of someone who understands
that change is not the enemy.
Exactly. Someone who can balance
the variables of history
with... with compassion and heart.
A Legend.
It needs me.
And why would I take this deal?
Because you need a captain.
Per Time Master's protocol,
there must always be
one captain and one AI.
And I am the best
you are ever going to find.
- This is definitely a team decision.
- Mmm-hmm.
- What do you guys think?
- Are we really considering this?
Maybe she's right.
Maybe there's a better way
to protect the timeline.
- We are chaotic.
- Yeah, but chaotic good.
We are superheroes. We can't just quit.
It wouldn't be quitting. We'd be finding
new ways to help people. Could be cool.
I guess it would be
really nice to see my mom.
Yeah. Put down some roots.
I trust Gideon.
She's one of us.
It certainly seems like the plan
least likely to bring about our demise.
Demise? When has a little demise
ever stopped us?
This is the hard part
about being a superhero.
You have to do the right thing
even when it sucks.
But is it the right thing?
Guys, we're just
going to stop being Legends?
[sighs]
For the timeline, I think it is.
I swear to protect and defend
the integrity of the timeline
with all of my ability
until the end of my days.
[whispers] And have
a little fun while doing it.
And have a little responsible fun
while doing it.
- [Sara] Yeah!
- [cheering]
- Yeah, Giddy!
- Yeah! Go, Giddy!
Now, all of you, go sign your contracts.
[upbeat folk music playing]
[singing]
Poor old granddad
I laughed at all his words
I thought he was a bitter man
He spoke of women's ways
They'll trap you, then they use you
Before you even know
For love is blind
and you're far too kind
Don't ever let it show
I wish that I knew what I know now
When I was younger
When I was stronger
You'll have to learn, just like me
And that's the hardest way
Ooh la la, ooh la la la yeh
[Astra sighs]
What's going on?
You okay?
Look, I can feel your anger
from across the room.
What is the point of making friends
if you're just never going to
see them again, Spooner?
What if you could?
[Astra chanting]
[chuckles]
Now we can hang out
without having to break our contracts.
- It's not bad for an apprentice, huh?
- Apprentice who?
You are a full blown witch,
mi grande amiga.
[thanks in Spanish]
[speaking English] Yo, yo,
I got a surprise.
- You get a key.
- [Behrad] What?
- What?
[Spooner] You get a key,
and you get a key.
- Pretty cool?
- [Gary] Not bad.
- [Spooner] Now we all got a key.
- Yeah.
Hey.
Oh.
Uh, here.
Now you can visit us whenever you want.
I am really gonna miss you, Gideon.
I really hope I make you proud.
You already do.
[sighs]
I can't believe it.
Seven years on this ship.
Yeah. I'm really going to
miss this place.
- How cute was our kid, though? Huh?
- Oh.
Yeah, you know, there's a reason
we're not supposed to
look at our futures, babe.
Yes, by seeing our future,
we can change our futures.
Yes, I just don't want you
to get hurt is all.
Look, I know.
And it doesn't have to be a girl, okay?
Maybe we adopt, uh, six boys.
No, no, no.
I don't know. Just, like, seeing her
really made our future feel real.
- Yeah.
- And you know what?
Starting today,
we get to build a life together.
Get some curtains.
Maybe that porch we always wanted.
Okay, I wanted the porch.
Ooh. Maybe a dog.
- Look who's getting all domestic on me.
- Domestic. You know it.
So, I, uh... I really want
to say something before I go.
Okay.
You're the most amazing person
I've ever known.
You, uh...
You make the world more colorful.
You make food taste better.
I want you
to hear this for real this time.
I love you, Gideon.
Stay with me.
What?
The truth is, being a computer
makes me a better Captain,
but being with you...
makes me a better person.
So, everyone says
long-distance relationships suck.
You breaking up with me?
I mean, we've only been together
for, like, two days.
[sighs] Time is so weird.
That's too bad, 'cause I already
planned our first date.
What was it?
I guess you have to show up to find out.
Ugh. Fine. I'll come.
Wait, did I just get hustled?
Mmm-hmm.
Hey, you must be excited
to have your own bathroom
after sharing one for three years.
Three years, wow.
Guess I thought there'd be more time.
Mmm. More time for, uh...
More time for what?
To be a hero, I guess.
It's hard, um...
living in the other Zari's shadow.
I mean, she changed the world.
She... She mattered.
Come on. You matter. You matter a lot.
Yeah, maybe to trend watchers
waiting to hear about
this year's hot nail trend,
or whatever audible lipstick is.
Yes, you are a fashion icon.
Right? But you're also a champion
of doing the right thing.
Do you remember Eddie?
- You saved his bar.
- I was just being helpful, not heroic.
My father, he was very big on legacy,
and so was I for a while,
but after years of
hero-ing through time,
do you know how
I'm going to be remembered?
For writing a book about other people.
My legacy, however... My legacy
is the life I get to make with Zari.
You make a difference.
But you make it your own way.
I guess I just wish I knew
what that was.
Thanks.
Are you nervous about seeing Alun?
I won't have Alun.
What?
I am returning to
the wild countryside alone.
- Albeit for some very majestical sheep.
- No, no, no. That's... What do you...
We need to talk to Gideon.
That wasn't the plan...
Now, Ms. Sharpe,
you and I both well know
that this is what history requires.
Now, Alun and I,
we will see each other again.
If not in this life, in the next one.
Gwyn, I really don't understand.
There was something
he always used to say to me in parting,
"In the river, I have seen you,
through love, age, and misery.
In the river, I will find you,
for you will always be you
and I will always be me."
"I will find you, for you will always
be you and I will always be me."
[sighs] It's beautiful.
Yes.
Yes, it is.
Gwyn...
[taps table]
Hey, Z, can you, um,
help me with something?
A little, uh, surprise I have
for the team?
Yeah, sure.
[Agent Sharpe] Thanks. Let's go
talk someplace private.
[sighs]
I can't believe Gwyn's going home alone.
After everything he's done for us,
why should he have to live out
his entire life in misery?
- Aves?
- What?
- I can help.
- Z, it's not that...
Let me.
Okay.
The Legends are up to something,
and I have to stop them.
Ready the Jumpship.
And Gideon, no killing the Legends
while I'm gone.
- [Evil Gideon] Is that an...
- Ha!
It's an order.
Okay, all we have to do now
is charge the Courier, jump to 1916,
and find a way to save Alun
while still breaking Gwyn's heart.
- The dog tags.
- Huh?
We go in before the attack,
I make a dust storm,
you grab Alun, leave his dog tags,
when Gwyn comes back,
he still thinks Alun's dead.
Brilliant. You're a freaking genius.
Okay, it's going to be a tight squeeze,
but I made Gwyn a promise.
Aves, this one's mine.
It's my hero moment.
- Hair tie.
- Are you sure?
Yeah. I'm gonna get dirty.
I'm gonna crawl.
Okay.
Hair.
Hair, blow dryer, bathroom.
- You okay?
- There's a blow dryer in the bathroom.
Yes, there's a blow dryer
in the bathroom.
It has a charger.
Who knew robots used hair dryers?
Well, did you see the lift
in Robo Nate's hair?
You can't 3D print that.
- [Agent Sharpe squeals]
- Now, we just wait.
Great, how long?
Because Sara has a very small bladder.
- [Zari] It's ready.
- Huh.
We can never let Spoons know about this.
- Ever.
- [laughs] Obviously.
[gasps] Oh, dear!
Oh, my sincerest apologies.
I didn't realize that someone
was using the lavatory.
Gwyn, it's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
[exhales deeply]
Gwyn, we're going to save Alun.
We made you a promise.
I am deeply, deeply moved
that you would all sacrifice
your own personal paradises
for me to have a chance to realize mine.
But, uh, I'm sorry, I must refuse.
- [Zari] But why?
- The risk. The risk is too great.
It was a gruesome battle.
And I'm telling you now,
it is too dangerous.
- Just wait...
- You are my friends.
- Gwyn, we just want you to be happy.
- You deserve a chance at love. You...
And you would...
You would do that for me?
Yeah.
Well, all right, then,
you've convinced me.
- Yes. Let's go see...
- [man] Gwyn?
Alun.
They all died, didn't they?
Yes.
And what about me?
Well... [clears throat] in a way, yes.
You perished as well.
But I survived.
You are very much alive.
How?
Yes, well... [clears throat]
Um, you see, I...
I invented a method of time travel...
to save you.
To save me?
Yes.
Why?
I, uh...
I couldn't bear to live in a world
without you in it, Alun.
I couldn't.
Anyway, it's... [clears throat]
It's a lot to take in, isn't it?
And I can't imagine
how you must be feeling now.
I should probably leave you in peace.
Uh... [clears throat]
I'm sorry, that was, uh...
That was foolish of me
to think that's what you wanted. I'm...
No, no, that's, uh...
It's what I've always wanted, you know.
I just...
"In the river, I will find you for..."
For?
For what?
"Well, for you will always be you,
and...
and I will always be me."
[laughs]
But of course I will.
Hmm?
Who else would I be, eh?
You odd, beautiful man.
[Alun chuckles]
Uh, what time? Wait.
What time did you say again?
- Why, you got plans?
- Uh, Sunday at 9:00, right?
Ooh, eesh...
Hate to be this guy,
but, uh, Zari and I have dinner
with Uncle Armajean, Sunday at 9:00.
Okay, here's a pitch.
What about Wednesdays at 8:00?
- Midweek parties are the best.
- What time zone?
Oh, that'd be, uh,
8:00 Eastern, 7:00 Central.
Only on the... Anyway,
it doesn't matter. I'll be there.
Where are we going?
Well, where we are going...
You see, time travel...
[all chattering]
I'm going to miss you all so very much.
Ship's going to be so quiet.
Hey, well, you always got a team
if you need us.
Oh. We need to take a group picture.
- [Sara] Let's do it!
- Group photo.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
- Technology, and this...
- Alun, this is gonna blow your mind.
[Dr. Davies] Pictures, they get taken
by something called digital...
Now, you just stand here and it will
take a picture of us all now together.
[clicking rapidly]
[Gary] Okay.
So, tonight we dine in Paris.
I made us dinner.
[Evil Gideon] You mean, I made dinner.
Well, yeah, yeah,
but I set up the twinklies.
- Gary, it's wonderful.
- [chuckles nervously]
- Madame.
- Oh. Merci. [chuckles]
Oh, wow.
So, for our first course,
we will be having
crème de volaille a la berchoux.
Oh.
- What is that?
- I... don't know.
I asked Gideon to make something fancy
and French and voilà.
Ooh! So talented.
[laughs]
[Evil Gideon] Why are you lying, Gideon?
You know what it is.
You do?
Well, yes.
Crème de volaille a la berchoux
is a creamy chicken soup
with a lemon flavor,
named for French poet, Joseph Berchoux,
the man responsible for inventing
the word gastronomy.
Ah. So, then...
Why'd you, uh... Why'd you lie?
I just didn't want to
hurt your feelings,
Gary, by making you feel dumb.
Oh, no, never dim your light
to make me feel better.
Just don't lie.
Alun is a robot.
What?
I went back to 1916, harvested his DNA
and printed a Robot Alun.
And then I used Gwyn's diary
from the historical records
to recreate his personality.
Why would you do that?
Look, I intended to save Alun,
but then I discovered
that Alun's death is a Fixed Point.
Ava and Zari were
trying to go back to save him.
They would have been killed.
It's the only thing I could do to keep
the Legends and the timeline safe.
By lying to Gwyn? By lying to all of us?
They can't know.
They're Legends. They'd break time
before they'd break his heart.
Do you hate me?
What? No. No, of course not.
I just, uh...
I, uh...
I need some time to, uh... to think.
To think about what?
Well, uh, if these are the kinds
of decisions you have to make,
I don't think I'm cut out for this.
Why is love so complicated?
[Evil Gideon] Because oxytocin,
the hormone excreted
when you feel love for another person,
creates an unstable duality in the human
brain of happiness and fear.
Right now, you are torn between anger
at Gideon for betraying you...
- Yes.
- ...and a desire to apologize,
since you don't want to lose her.
Right.
Mmm.
[Evil Gideon] Humans think
they want to know everything,
but when they find out,
they're disappointed.
- You made the right decision.
- Well, I wish Gary saw it that way.
Oh, no. You're missing the point.
No, love is complicated,
because people are complicated.
Learning how to love another person
can be messy and painful,
but in the end, if you can make it work,
it's the most beautiful thing
in the world.
[Evil Gideon] The timeline
cannot be ruled by emotions.
It must be protected
by clear-headed logic.
If you do love Gideon,
then for her sake, I suggest you leave.
[sighs]
But I don't want to choose
between Gary and my job.
[Evil Gideon] You're going to have
to make difficult decisions every day.
- What if he leaves, huh?
- Then you know the man he truly is.
I do love her.
Which is why I'm staying.
She needs someone to advocate
for all the things
that have nothing to do with logic,
like tolerance, like kindness,
forgiveness and... love.
I want to start the rest of my life
with that incredible woman.
And I want to start it now!
Where is she?
[Evil Gideon sighs] She's in the armory.
The armory. Okay. Yeah.
Thank you.
Gideon?
[Evil Gideon] You and your
obsession with love
pose too great a risk to the timeline.
- I'm not...
- Goodbye.
[screams]
I'm sorry to inform you, Captain,
Mr. Green has left the Waverider.
It's for the best.
A captain and an AI,
the way it was meant to be.
[door opening]
I... What is that?
That is my time machine.
Oh, Gwyn, it's a divine masterpiece.
You know, when I lost you,
I vowed to move Heaven and Earth
until you were saved.
Which is why I have to do this.
I'm coming for you, my boy.
I'm coming.
[theme music playing]