[Zari] Previously on
Legends Of Tomorrow...
Is this your new girlfriend?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
You and I dating would be totally weird.
Totally weird.
Wow, that's beautiful.
- [gunshot]
- [groans]
Step away from the creature, miss.
You murdered him!
[grunting]
[roars]
Hank is running some secret project.
He's not just taking the fugitives,
he's testing on them.
I don't need you anymore.
I don't need you anymore, either.
[groans]
- What did you do?
- I'm sorry.
[all grunting]
[sighs]
Maybe I shouldn't intrude.
Nate needs all of our support right now.
[Ray] What am I supposed to say to him?
"Sorry the woman I've been
exchanging love letters with in prison
killed your dad."
[scoffs] They ought to put that
on a condolence card.
Look, we are going inside
and we are going to strive, with grace,
to help our friend cope with his loss.
[Nate] Damn it.
[Zari] Here, let me help.
Hey, uh...
Thanks for sticking around
this past week.
What are pretend girlfriends for?
My mom is going to be so crushed
when I tell her we broke up.
Then don't.
I mean, she's going through a lot.
We can pretend break up anytime we want.
We should...
We should probably get out there.
You ready for this?
- [indistinct conversations]
- [Nate exhales deeply]
Oh, Nathaniel.
I need you to make a toast later.
Tell everyone what an amazing man
your father was.
Mom, I don't think that's a great idea.
What? Of course it is.
And, Zari, I am so glad that you're here
for Nathaniel to lean on right now.
Yeah, you know me. I'm... I'm his rock.
I can't... I can't face him.
Ray, wait.
[sighs]
[Constantine]
I hope you're not stress-eating, squire.
I don't know what else to do.
I can't believe this is happening.
[breathes deeply]
You feel the energy in this room.
It's like sitting on a keg of dynamite.
You see, wakes are notorious soft spots
where the supernatural
meets the living world.
You see Nate's aunt?
That particular prayer
is to ward off evil spirits.
They've covered the mirrors
so the bad lads can't get in.
- That's creepy.
- Yeah, well.
Creepy is my business.
[electricity crackling]
And it looks like business is good.
- [Nate] Oh!
- [Ray gasps]
Nate! Nate, Nate, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
No, it's okay, Ray.
No. No, no, it's not.
I keep giving Nora second chances
and she goes and does this.
Look, you thought Nora could change...
I never thought my dad would be
torturing magical creatures,
so I guess...
I guess we were both wrong.
[sighs]
I can't believe
you're the one comforting me.
Come on, I love you, bro.
That's never going to change.
I love you, too.
[crackling]
Oh, no, don't... No, no, no, don't...
Don't... Don't do it, Ray.
You're gonna do it.
[gasps]
Nora?
How... How are you doing this?
[scoffs] It's a reflection spell.
I can't hold it much longer.
Well, good. Because there's nothing
you could possibly say
that would make any difference.
This time, there will be
no more second chances.
Ray, I didn't kill Nate's dad.
Oh, thank God, you're innocent.
Tell me where you are.
I need to talk to you in person.
Now, who wants a nice, juicy steak?
Charlie, you know that I'm a vegetarian.
No, no, no, you used to be a vegetarian
when you were a normal, boring human.
- But now, you are...
- A monster?
Exactly.
I mean, how cool is that?
Wait, are you trying to get me
to shift into Wolfie?
Of course I am.
You've been moping about the ship
thinking about your lost love.
I think that he would really want you to
just embrace your wild side.
[chuckles]
Konane liked me as Mona.
Whoa!
The birds on your shirt?
These are the names of my favorite
Jane Austen characters.
[Gideon] It appears that
you are experiencing
the impact of a magical fugitive.
[both] Oh!
This better be good, Mona.
A fugitive got to Jane Austen.
She never wrote Sense and Sensibility.
And Pride and Prejudice disappeared,
too.
Whatever it is, it's gonna have to wait.
Did someone say history is in trouble?
Legends assemble.
Okay, yeah, I really need
to get out of here, too.
Hey, what's up?
Nothing. There's a fugitive alert,
but it can wait.
No, you should go.
It's hard enough I have to play pretend,
you guys shouldn't.
Okay.
Bye, Nate.
Bye, Zari.
Gideon traced the new fugitive
to a wedding
Jane Austen attended in Bath,
England, 1802.
I already had Gideon chart a course.
Can I come on the mission?
Please?
Sure.
Yeah, and as much as I love
a good wedding sneak,
I'm gonna QB from... From my bedroom.
Is he acting weirder than normal?
- [all] Yeah.
- [Zari clears throat]
- [Mona sniffing]
- Speaking of weird.
I think my sense of smell
has improved because of Wolfie
and you smell exactly like... Nate.
No, I don't.
It's definitely Nate.
Nate and something else.
[sniffs]
- Arousal?
- [laughing]
No, I don't... I don't like Nate.
That would be wrong and...
Nate likes you.
He confessed it
when he swallowed the truth bug.
We are so not passing
the Bechdel test right now.
It's okay to talk about guys sometimes.
Come on, I bet it's been months
since you got laid.
Now, why don't you just go smash Nate?
Or better yet, you should go
smash somebody else,
because if you're
still thinking about Nate,
then you know you're really into him.
Why don't you talk to Nate?
Tell him how you feel.
[scoffs] Boo.
That is a terrible idea.
Okay, I'm going. Bye.
This is like a Jane Austen novel
come to life.
- [wind blows]
- [gasps] My bonnet!
[man] Look out!
- [neighing]
- [man] Whoa, whoa, whoa!
[all gasp]
[grunts]
[man] Forgive me, miss.
Are you hurt?
Only my pride.
Injured pride is a small thing...
if it allowed us to meet.
[man 2] What's the holdup there?
Come, come, I say.
Duty calls.
[clears throat]
[man] Apologies, Lord Remington.
We'll be on our way shortly.
- [both laughing]
- Here.
[clears throat] Not a word.
Was that a curtsy?
- [all laughing]
- "Only my pride."
Okay, let's go. Shut up!
- [all laughing]
- A damsel.
- [hymn playing on church organ]
- [indistinct chattering]
[Zari clears throat]
If you don't jump that
buff coachman's bones, I will.
We're at this wedding
to catch a magical creature.
[smacks lips] If that's the groom,
then I'm glad I'm not the bride.
A man's charms are equal to his fortunes
and Mr. Dockerty's fortunes
are prodigious.
[shushes] Jane, don't be rude.
That's Jane Austen.
[wedding music playing]
I cannot marry you, Mr. Dockerty.
[all gasp]
- My heart yearns for another.
- [all gasp]
Our family scullery maid.
Ellen, are you here?
I'm here!
I love you, too.
- [exclaims]
- [woman] The scandal!
[all gasping]
Wow.
[Mr. Dockerty]
I give not one fig, Miss Sinclair.
For my heart, and my lower extremities,
yearn for your mother.
[all gasp]
Get over here, gorgeous.
[all murmuring]
[Mr. Dockerty] Come to me, my love.
Now, this is what I call a wedding.
[buzzing]
The coast is clear.
I really don't want you to get
in trouble with your friends.
Oh, it's no trouble.
It looks like everyone else
is still on mission.
Okay.
So, who did kill Hank?
- [sighs] The demon.
- Okay, good.
Obviously...
I mean, obviously, it's bad.
If it's a demon, that means
that John will be able to find proof
and you just need to lay low
until he comes back.
You really don't mind me staying here?
Yeah, no,
it'd be nice if you stayed here.
- Oi, Rayge? Where are you?
- [gasps]
- [Charlie continues indistinctly]
- [Nora groans]
Rayge?
- It's a long story. Go.
- What's a long...
[Charlie] What...
What are you hiding in there?
Hmm? What? Nothing.
Oh, buffing the old bishop, was we?
[chuckles]
It's all right, mate.
No judgement here, all right?
- Come on.
- Yeah.
So the bride and
the scullery maid, that was...
- Insane.
- Romantic.
I was gonna say hot.
Regardless, that definitely
did not happen in actual history.
[Sara] Ray, Charlie, what you got?
This wedding was the second of
a series of "lust outbreaks" in 1802.
Yeah, the sexual revolution
came a couple hundred years too early.
Why would it make
Jane Austen stop writing?
We need more info.
Jane Austen was known for
being a keen social observer.
So if anyone would have noticed
a new magical arrival in town,
it would be her.
Okay, let's go interview Jane.
[Charlie] Oh, wait, hang on a tick.
People with the real dirt,
always the servants.
Like a handsome coachman, perhaps.
Hmm?
Fine, I'll go ask him some questions.
- But that's it.
- You go get it, girl.
Okay.
[door opens]
Sister dear,
this is Miss Lance and Miss Wu.
They're new in town.
Try not to scare them away.
I shall do my best, Cassandra.
We are so sorry to interrupt
your writing, Miss Austen.
This? Just a letter.
Shall we take a turn around the room
while we converse?
We'd be delighted to.
It's a Regency thing, go with it.
So, the bride, Miss Sinclair,
her behavior must have been
quite a shock.
Ever since Lord Remington
arrived a week ago,
the entire town has been acting
most imprudently.
But Miss Sinclair's situation
is truly horrendous.
I think you of all people would
celebrate the triumph of romance.
What's to celebrate?
Miss Sinclair will be cut off
from her fortune
and the two women
will have nothing to live on.
But it's because of you, I mean...
I have come to believe that love will
find a way to overcome any obstacle.
Then you're either lying
or you're a fool.
Tell me, has love worked out
so well for you?
- No.
- Then you are a fool.
For you shouldn't have to
learn a lesson twice.
[Mona growling]
[grunts softy]
Let's go find Lord Remington.
We should be going.
[Zari] Hello?
[sighs] This is stupid.
[coachman clears throat]
What a pleasure to see you again.
Hey, man.
What's up, Pretty?
This whole toast thing is
eating me up on the inside.
My... My dad was such a dick.
He lied about everything and now
he's turning me into a liar, too.
[sighs] Listen,
your old man's gone, whatever you say
out there, that's for you.
You know what, Mick?
I think you're onto something.
- [exhales]
- [crackling]
[whispering voices]
[inhales sharply]
[Hank echoing] Nathaniel!
Hey, where is Nate?
We need to find him
because Hank's spirit is still here.
[door closes]
Hey, cheer up.
What does Jane Austen know?
How to be witty and wise
and mix satire with romance.
[women giggling]
I bet you these girls know
where Lord Remington is.
[Mona] They do look like fan girls.
Okay, you know the era,
you take the lead.
He's simply the handsomest man
I've ever laid eyes on.
[Mona giggling]
I know what you mean.
Lord Remington is such a fine specimen.
I can't say I share your sentiment.
[snoring]
His coachman though,
what he lacks in means,
he makes up for in magnetism.
[woman] I concur.
His arrival has sent
many hearts aflutter.
[Mona giggles nervously]
Coachman.
As in, the guy we pushed Zari
to hook up with.
Zari is gonna smash the fugitive.
Come on!
[panting] Sorry.
This is moving really fast.
- I agree.
- You do?
What's your name?
[scoffs] Uh...
My name is Zari. What's your name?
You know what? Don't answer that.
You don't kiss like any man
I've ever known.
What are you?
I am Kamadeva.
The Hindu god of love.
Awesome.
- [Kamadeva and Zari moaning]
- We're too late.
Zari?
- We think you might be dealing with...
- The fugitive?
Yeah, I know.
This is Kamadeva.
As in, the namesake of
Kama-sutra, Kamadeva?
That I did not know.
Look, I'm not going to sleep with
a magical fugitive.
You are incredible.
A woman has never before
resisted my charms.
All right, you're coming with us.
I would follow Miss Zari
to the world's end.
Well, your days of ruining Regency-era
marriages are over, Kamadeva.
I only sought to grant people the
courage to follow their heart's desire.
Oh, think he likes you.
Gideon, get us out of here.
I'm not so sure we can go yet.
[Gideon] Miss Wu is correct.
The historical records still indicate
that Jane Austen's career is
in jeopardy.
We caught the fugitive.
What's the problem?
Well, it's too late
to knock on Jane Austen's door tonight.
We'll talk to her tomorrow.
So, I'm to spend the night...
Alone.
[sighs] What a waste.
All right, everybody out.
- Come on.
- Hi.
Surely, I could have a bed?
[door opens]
Well, I had Gideon fabricate
some jimjams.
Because it's a slumber party.
Oh, thanks.
Obviously, since you are my guest,
you will get the bed.
Well, it's big enough
for the both of us. We can just share.
Oh, okay.
You can turn around now.
[Ray scoffs softly]
It really covers everything.
The thing is, I pride myself
on being a gentleman,
and the gentlemanly thing to do
would be to sleep in the chair, so...
[Ray clears throat]
[stammering] But you can't...
There's no way...
Oh...
That's not...
[snoring]
Okay.
[Nora sighing]
- [Constantine] Hey, mate.
- [knocking on door]
How is the old toast going?
Is there one or two "N"s in "conniving"?
Right then, may I suggest
a slight change of plan?
No, Mick is right.
It's time for me to tell the truth
about my dad.
How was I supposed to know
Hank's ghost was here?
Wait, what?
Yeah, that's about the gist of it,
Natey boy, you see.
Your old man's spirit is
working very hard
to stay attached to the mortal realm.
I can only surmise that he has something
he wants to say to you, so,
if you wouldn't mind leaving off
your roast for a bit,
join us for a brief séance
and I'll have him on his way in no time.
No.
There's nothing Hank can say now
to excuse him from embezzling money
and hurting creatures.
In fact, I'm glad he's still here.
'Cause it's his turn to listen to me.
- [powering up]
- [spooky voice moaning]
You don't scare me, Hank.
[record spinning rapidly]
Ray.
Do you want me in bed with you?
Yes, I did. I do.
I do.
[Nora moans]
Is this okay?
Yes.
[Nora gasping]
Ava...
[moaning]
[exhales]
Oh. Oh...
[growls]
[laughs]
[whooping]
Damn it, this is definitely a dream.
[Zari clears throat]
- The fugitive get to you, too?
- Yeah.
[Charlie] Well, personally,
I really enjoyed my night,
blowing David Bowie's mind.
[Sara chuckles]
Who'd you get a leg over, Z?
Wait, let me guess. Nate?
No, Kamadeva.
Both?
It was both! Blimey, Z,
I didn't know you had it in you.
What about you, Wolfie?
You dreamt about Konane.
Mona.
I'll get it.
- [sobbing]
- [Zari clears throat]
Hey. Hey, hey. It's okay.
He had the sweetest eyes.
And when he would look at me,
the whole world would disappear.
And now, he's dead.
Mona, I know it's hard, but,
try to have some perspective.
You didn't know him for very long.
So, you think I'm a fool too?
No, I just don't think anyone
should give their heart away
without thinking about the consequences.
But romance is taking
a chance on someone
without knowing how it's gonna end up.
Romance is something used
to sell novels. It's not real.
Well, it'll never be real for you.
Not if you never try.
Not if you never take a risk.
You know, it's hard
to take advice from someone
whose boyfriend turned her
into a werewolf.
- [growling]
- Hey, guys, let's just take a breath.
You're right.
I might be stupid for being a romantic,
but it's not Konane's fault.
[Mona grunting]
[Charlie] Bloody hell.
[snarling]
Finally, you look wicked, mate!
[groans]
[roars]
Mona, wait.
[roaring]
Jane Austen.
It's time for you to pay.
Stay back, beast!
If I'm a beast, it's because of you!
Your books made me
an incurable romantic.
You're the reason
I risked everything for love.
And now Konane is dead.
- [growls]
- [yelping]
And look at me.
[Jane gasps]
You don't believe in romance!
Your writing is all lies!
[howling]
Are you the girl from earlier?
Mona is weak.
Wolfie is strong.
Well, Wolfie,
I believe from the depths of my soul
that one should only marry for love.
You do?
So much so that I rejected the only man
who has ever asked for my hand.
He was a smug simpleton
who only read sermons!
[sighs]
How remarkable.
You shouldn't mess with people's dreams.
[chuckles]
My powers don't create passion
out of thin air.
Whomever you dreamt about,
you truly desire.
That doesn't mean I have to act on it.
It's called impulse control.
You sound like a woman who has never
let herself fall in love.
Where I'm from, love is a liability.
And yet, a life without love
is no life at all.
Tell me, what does a god know
about the human heart?
My real name is Sunjay.
I was born thousands of years ago.
When the actual Kamadeva
was immolated by Shiva,
I gathered his ashes in this vial.
They bestowed powers
I could have scarcely imagined.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I like you.
And I think you secretly yearn
to be impulsive and free.
Unless you lack the courage.
Okay. Give me a hit.
- Might I suggest...
- No, if I'm gonna do this,
I want to experience love, lust,
the whole shebang.
That is, unless you lack the courage.
One, two, three.
Wow.
Most of you here knew Hank well.
Or thought you did.
I'm gonna talk about a different Hank.
A Hank I got to know this year.
- [electricity crackling]
- [people gasp]
[mouthing] What are you doing?
[clears throat]
Hank was a workaholic
who never took a day off.
Well, Hank,
you can finally rest in peace.
[sighs]
Um...
Hank never knew his own father.
That's why he wanted to be there
for Nathaniel growing up.
But work often got in the way.
So, one year,
we planned to use Hank's leave
to stay for a week in Disney World.
Nathaniel was over the moon.
But the morning that
we were to fly to Orlando,
we ended up having to take Nathaniel
to the hospital instead.
When Hank saw the look of disappointment
in his son's eyes,
he went out and rented
a Mickey Mouse costume.
Put it on and went to the hospital.
He convinced everyone there that
Mickey Mouse had come to see them.
Hank Heywood was not a perfect man.
But when he was at his best,
that is who he was.
A man who could make you
believe in magic.
To Hank.
[all] To Hank.
Why did you tell me that
by following their hearts
those women would only
fall into despair?
[sighs]
Because my decision
was the result of my pride.
When my father dies, my sister and I
will be reduced to penury.
- But your writing...
- Has been rejected by every publisher.
[scoffs]
It's no wonder.
I satirize the manners of a society that
seems to have lost all sense of decorum.
Therefore,
I have decided to stop writing.
But you will publish.
You can't give up now,
because your books
are timeless.
- How can you be so sure?
- Because...
You're my favorite author.
May I offer you a bit of advice?
My books advocate a partnership
based on love and mutual respect,
not on losing control.
[both laughing]
[Sunjay sighs]
What shall we do next?
I have an idea.
Let's get married.
[music playing]
Do you hear that?
No, hear what?
There is definitely music playing.
Kamadeva loved music.
- Perhaps you should sing.
- [scoffs] I don't sing.
[singing] Every day I find a way
To shove my past and anger down
Go on, my love.
That was beautiful.
My humor's dry
I never cry
If I start, I'd surely drown
When I'm on my own
I can't help wanting something more
Today, instead of closing off
I'm opening a door
[both] So now I'm tossing sense aside
And I surrender
To the fantasy and pleasure
I surrender
To my happy ever after
I won't fight it, won't deny it
Do you have a ring? I'll try it
I surrender
In the morning, we should go ask
the parson to marry us.
A Christian wedding?
For a Muslim woman and a Hindu man?
Let's not think with our heads,
but feel with our hearts.
Gideon, where's that music coming from?
[Gideon] I took the liberty
of broadcasting Miss Tomaz's comms.
Ha! It's rather infectious.
Ray, this music, I think it's magical.
You're right. I want to express
my feelings to you in verse.
Is that really necessary?
[singing] I had a dirty dream of you
I'll bet mine was dirtier
Why didn't you go and make a move?
I would have if you'd been flirtier
[Nora gasps]
[singing] Look, this is complicated
- If Nate knew, he'd be enraged
- I know
And I'm sorry
but my desire's been uncaged
Don't let this moment pass us by
It could be our only chance
You're right, I need you now
Sorry, Nate and Captain Lance
[Nora gasps]
[singing] I fixed the timeline as a cat
Saved a cowboy, kept his hat
I took Salem's breath away
Got stuck reliving the same day
Through it all, I kept my cool
Never thought I'd play the fool
Now I've surrendered to you
It's time for me to say, "I do"
I do? What are you talking about?
We need to find Mona.
Wait a sec, is this
a Bollywood musical number?
You bet your ass it is. [blowing]
- [Bollywood music playing]
- [crowd cheering rhythmically]
[all singing]
Now we're tossing sense aside
And we surrender
To the fantasy and pleasure
We surrender
To our happy ever afters
We won't fight it, won't deny it
Losing all control? We'll try it
We surrender
I want you badly as my bride
Please make my wish come true
These feelings can't be denied
So, yes, I say I...
Stop!
You're making a mistake.
[singing] Zari
[in normal voice]
Whoa! Why did I just sing that?
Okay, I guess I'm just gonna
roll with the whole singing thing.
[Zari sighs]
[singing] Every day we find a way
To hold grief in, not let them see
We feel so wrong, we often long
Get swept away in fantasy
You've been so brave, wise and strong
By opening your door
Please, Zari, have courage now
To wait for something more
Don't listen to her, my love.
No, Mona's right, Z.
You don't even know this guy.
He's been using the powers
of a love god for years,
guarantee you he's got a wife.
- Is that true?
- Not exactly.
I have a thousand wives.
But lucky number 1,001
is the most important!
Seriously?
So, you still want to marry me?
No, I definitely do not.
[singing] Now I've got my senses back
But I'll surrender
Life's not done, I'll love again
I'll surrender
With my friends now by my side
I won't hide it, won't deny it
Real love comes my way, I'll try it
I'll surrender
[Constantine grunting]
Voi-bloody-là.
Now, only the particular spirit
we're after
will be able to enter the vessel.
What vessel?
The vessel is you.
I'm gonna kill you, weasel.
[Constantine chanting]
Hank Heywood.
I summon you.
[continues chanting spell]
Hank?
[in Hank's voice] Who else would it be?
Where's Nathaniel?
Nate gave you the big middle finger,
so I'm afraid you're stuck with me.
Still angry, is he?
Us Heywoods, we hold a good grudge.
Now, what's so important
that you had to stick around?
[groans]
It pains me to admit it,
but I made a terrible mistake.
A man approached me about a deal.
Unlimited funding.
And all I had to do was give him access
to all the magical creatures
within the Time Bureau,
but this man was
no ordinary beltway bandit.
He was a demon.
[door unlocks]
Only after he murdered me
did I realize the truth.
What was the demon's name?
- Promise me you'll keep Nathaniel safe.
- Yes, yes, yes. I promise.
Now, come on, Hank,
you can't delay the inevitable forever.
What was the demon's name?
His name was Neron.
[beeps]
Hey, world! I'm Hank Heywood.
And I'm here to tell you
about an exciting opportunity.
When I learned about the existence
of magical creatures...
Yes, magical creatures exist.
I ran right home
and pulled out a drawing,
made by my son Nathaniel
when he was only nine years old.
My son envisioned a theme park
where everyone could gaze in wonder
at dragons and unicorns,
werewolves and Minotaurs.
This is insane.
Now, you may be thinking,
this is insane.
But what great man hasn't been thought
of as insane at one point in his life?
I believe this park
can bring our country together.
And with your help,
I'm gonna turn my son's dream
into a reality.
I call it Heyworld.
[pauses video]
[gasps]
Oh, Hank.
Why?
I have so many questions.
You weren't torturing magical creatures,
you were training them
to be in a theme park.
That is nuts.
But I gotta respect you
for dreaming big.
It was your moon shot,
your way of risking it all
to make the world a better place.
I was so wrong about you.
At the end of the day,
you were just as wacky
and well-intentioned as any Legend.
[crying] And I wish I'd had the chance
to get to know that side of you.
[sniffles]
I'm gonna miss you.
I love you, Hank.
[sniffles]
I love you, Dad.
[whooshing]
[male voice] Look at you.
Take a look at yourself,
you miserable git.
That's right.
Soak it in.
Your big sacrifice, it was for nothing.
But instead of rolling up your sleeves
and taking it to that demon bastard,
you're getting rat-arse drunk in a shed.
I can't fight him.
He's too strong.
Well, this isn't about Neron.
You failed Desmond, you failed Astra.
And you'll fail Nate.
And do you know why?
Because deep down,
you want them all to go to hell.
You want the company.
You liar!
[laughing]
[groans]
[Desmond] Hey, Johnny.
Miss me?
Des?
I'm surprised
you haven't figured it out yet.
[mirror cracking]
Neron.
[roaring]
[theme music playing]