In 2166, an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately,
my plan is opposed by the body
I'd sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered as Legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Boys, ship's all yours.
Mick!
What are you gonna do, Snart?
My husband and I get along
just fine on our own.
We're still waiting on Sara
and the two lovebirds to get back.
Seems they've taken
quite a shine to 1958.
Sara swore her allegiance
to the League of Assassins.
It's time for her to return home.
My friend Thea calls it a bloodlust.
Sara, stop!
I'm a monster.
Not this guy again.
Captain, Chronos has breached
the starboard hatch.
How is that possible?
Clearly received some new toys
from his Time Master friend
since our last encounter.
1958's swell and all,
but I miss the Internet...
and cell phones.
Gideon!
Seal the bulkheads from here...
- Grey, come on!
- Let's do this!
If we merge on the Waverider,
it could destroy the entire ship!
Are you not paying attention
to what Chronos is doing?
Fall back!
Get to the Jumpship!
Hey, come on!
You sure it was a good idea leaving
the Terminator on the bridge?
Gideon has lockdown
protocols which...
Have been overridden, Captain.
Chronos is utilizing superior
Time Master technology.
I cannot countermand his orders.
Uh... what are they doing?
- Hey!
Where did they go?
Better question:
Why did they leave us?
He's time jumping the ship.
The ladies will be left in 1958.
- What about Ray?
- Like I said.
Let's go! We have to stop him!
Oh!
Gideon,
open the doors on my mark.
Get to the Jumpship and escape.
We are not abandoning you.
No, you are obeying a direct order
from your captain.
Now, Gideon.
No.
I don't know if the Jumpship will
even fly from the Temporal Zone.
- I don't know...
- No.
Aah.
Oh.
It doesn't matter.
We're not leaving our team.
What happened to:
We could destroy the whole ship?
A preferable alternative
to losing our friends.
Don't you agree?
Oh.
Yeah.
We could've just opened the door,
Jefferson.
Sorry, I got a little carried...
away.
Oh, hey, hey, hey.
Oh, God.
Where's Chronos?
He absconded with Mr. Snart
on the Jumpship.
I'm sorry, Captain.
Why would Chronos take Snart?
Gideon, can you track them?
We have a more pressing matter.
Strap yourselves in.
What's going on?
Chronos has sabotaged
the navigation system.
Unless we can find a way
to alter the course,
we'll be trapped in the Temporal Zone
for all time.
Gideon.
I cannot override Chronos' commands.
What did you do?
I rebooted Gideon.
Until she's fully operational,
we're free-falling through time.
We just have to stay calm.
Wherever they time jumped...
Whenever they'll come back
to this exact same moment.
They're not coming back.
Let's go.
Look, as a former Eagle Scout
with over 100 merit badges...
no big deal.
The first rule of getting lost
is stay the same place.
That way, you can be found.
And as a former member
of the League of Assassins,
the first rule when you've been
attacked is to keep moving.
I sort of think League wisdom
trumps the Eagle Scouts here.
Plus, Savage is still out there.
Guys, the rest of the team
would not leave us marooned in 1958.
Except for,
that's exactly what they did.
You said it yourself,
you have a time machine,
and you're never late.
They're not coming back.
One good thing about 1958.
No car alarms.
I didn't think they had cars
in Nanda Parbat.
Dated a lot of delinquents
as a teenager.
And now we're the delinquents.
If we leave Harmony Falls,
how's the rest of the team
gonna find us?
We don't know
if they're looking for us.
But we know Savage is.
We can't take him.
That means we can't stay here.
Let's go.
Oh, what did you do
to our apartment?
I'm creating a time beacon...
a transponder which matches
the Waverider's quantum signature,
basically creating
a radio wave firewall
that only our team can see.
It's cute that you think either of us
understood a word of that.
But I hope it works.
In the meantime, maybe we should
invest in some real beds.
How you make me scream because
You are no longer my queen
Congratulations. You are a doctor.
You know, I thought about
going to medical school once.
Here you go. $10,000 salary.
That's it? I made more as a barista.
Well, it's 1958.
You're lucky to make
that as a woman.
Touché.Your turn.
I miss Netflix.
Aha!
The time beacon radio
is officially complete.
- Well, great.
- Okay, here we go.
Come on.
Here we go.
Hope there's a spot on that game
that says Return to the Waverider,
because that's what's about
to happen.
Here we go.
Ooh.
Oh.
I just have to fix a few
of the kinks.
The next version will be
much less explosive.
Next version?
I thought you said you were
gonna say something to him.
- Say what?
- That your beacon.
It's a waste of time.
They're not coming back, Ray.
And it's not because the Waverider
is broken or they're lost,
or they can't find us, or whatever.
It's because they're dead.
And the sooner that you accept that,
the sooner you can move on...
the sooner we can all move on.
So, what?
We're just supposed to give up?
On being rescued, yeah.
Sara, what are you doing?
I can't stay here.
I need to find somewhere I belong.
Sara, wait. You can't go.
Savage is still out there.
Don't draw undue attention
on yourselves.
Sara.
Look, you two have each other.
Most people, in any time period,
aren't that lucky.
Take care.
Which gives us mesoscopic polymer
and biomolecular simulations.
Yes, Mr. Gates?
If that's true,
and you can soften matter,
then doesn't that mean you could
theoretically miniaturize an atom?
In theory, yes.
But trust me, you don't want
to try it at home.
And definitely not for at least
another 40 years.
Aren't you supposed to be at home?
I thought you said your son was sick.
Yes, William.
My in-laws are at my house,
so if you don't mind,
I'd rather be in here.
Your son is Bill Gates?
Bill?
That has a nice ring to it.
Midterms are next week.
Go ahead and pick up an exam book
on your way out.
Class dismissed.
- Happy second anniversary.
- Happy anniversary.
I thought we said no gifts.
I know. Just open it.
Your time beacon?
I thought we could
destroy it together.
You don't have to do that.
I want to.
You know, I never thought
that I could build a life...
with anybody but, Anna.
But...
That's exactly what we've done,
in the most unlikely time
and place imaginable.
And I know it may sound strange,
but I'm glad that we were
stranded here.
Me too.
I have one more surprise for you.
Ray.
The beacon.
It's picking up a signal!
Oh.
Shiby-washo... Sara, so... so...
You are suffering
from linguistic disorientation.
It's a side effect of such
a severe time jump.
I can't hear anything.
- It'll pass.
- What?
Gideon, status update?
I am detecting a time beacon
signaling the Waverider.
- But then again, this is 1960.
- 1960?
The temporal navigation system
was compromised
and did its best to return us
as close as possible to 1958.
Sorry we're late.
Two years.
You left us stranded in 1958.
That was never my intention.
Can't we rev the ship back up,
go back to 1958, and pick that us up?
You know very well that we can't.
Travel back to events we participated
in without time folding in on itself.
Raymond.
- Good to see you.
- Good to see you. Glad you're back.
Martin.
It's just...
I have 50 midterms
to grade next week by hand,
and I've just come to terms with
living in technological dark ages.
I have students who count on me.
Kendra and I have friends
and a life...
Ray.
This is what we've been waiting for.
Remember the mission.
We can finally be ourselves again.
Look, I'm sorry. This is all...
very intense.
It's been two years for us.
We thought you guys were dead.
That very well might have been
the case.
Chronos attacked us.
He sabotaged the ship and took Snart.
We need to recover Miss Lance,
as well.
Where is she?
Uh, no idea.
People go their separate ways,
lose track of each other.
Gideon, search the timeline
for any reference of a Sara Lance,
or a blonde vigilante, circa 1960.
Right away, Captain.
Why did Chronos take Snart?
Couldn't he have taken you all in?
You sound dubious.
If Chronos was gonna settle
for taking one person,
you'd think it would be you.
He took Snart for a reason.
Uh, hello?
A UFO sighting in Hub City in 1960
has created a time anomaly.
It looks like your friends survived.
And what would they be doing in 1960?
That is out of the question,
Mr. Palmer.
What are we talking about?
You changed.
Yeah, I couldn't wait
to get back in jeans.
So, what's going on?
I have to go back to our apartment.
Why?
Because when we were unexpectedly
picked up by a time ship,
I was not carrying the ATOM suit.
And not for nothing, but we spent
the last two years together
in that apartment.
Is there anything you want me
to pick up for you?
Your favorite coffee mug?
Our lucky water vase?
Lucky water vase?
Yeah, it... it's a long
but endearing story.
Nothing? Don't you care about
anything that we left behind?
Yes, but I don't think that I need
to go back to the apartment
to get any of our old junk.
Old junk?
We lived there this morning.
We certainly can't leave
Raymond's exo-suit back in 1960.
I'll accompany you back
to your apartment.
We'll recover the future tech
and any lucky ceramics.
- Ray.
- I'll get those blouses you like.
Well, I hope that Sara takes
to being back on the team
better than Ray seems
to be taking it.
Depends, I suppose, on where
exactly she ended up.
Ta-er al-Sahfer.
I can see that the herbs
and meditation are working.
Your thirst to kill no longer clouds
your judgment.
Proceed.
Stand up.
I've enjoyed watching you train.
I have never seen a pupil advance
so quickly.
I've had time to learn who I am,
and what it is I'm meant to do.
We will watch this one closely,
Talia.
There is much you can learn from her.
So, uh...
what's so special about me?
I mean, aside from
my sparkling personality.
Back on the Waverider,
you could've taken your boy, Rip.
But you took me instead.
Why?
Hey, if you're gonna kill me,
you could at least tell me
what's going on?
You should have figured it out
by now.
After all...
I am supposed to be the dumb one.
How?
I think I deserve to know
what the hell is going on here!
You deserve nothing.
Says the man who sold us out
to the pirates.
When I dropped you off
in that forest,
I meant to kill you.
That was the plan.
You should've stuck with the plan
and done me a favor.
I wish there were
some other way, Mick.
You haven't got the guts.
You want to kill me, kill me.
Only one of us is walking
out of here alive.
You're right.
I knew you lacked the guts.
I am sorry, Mick.
I may not have trusted you
on the ship with the team,
but I always, always
was coming back for you.
Seems like one of us
lost track of time.
- Well, how long did you...
- By the time they found me,
I'd nearly lost my mind.
I was so weak,
I was strangling rats to survive.
When who found you?
The Time Masters.
They took me to a place
called the Vanishing Point.
Time doesn't exist there
the way it does on Earth.
I've spent lifetimes
being restored by them,
training by them, fighting by them...
being reborn.
And, when exactly did your
new friends give you the lobotomy?
You think I was hunting
you and your friends
because the Time Masters
made me?
They barely had to ask.
Hey, can we talk for a sec?
Just with everything that's going on,
I don't know that
this is the best time.
You say that like there's gonna be
a better time.
Okay.
Look, we spent every night
the last two years together,
playing board games, eating,
deciding who was gonna cook
and who was going to wash dishes,
falling asleep to
The Ed Sullivan Show.
But the second,
you saw the Waverider,
it was like those two years
never happened.
Look, we were both trying to adapt
to an impossible situation.
But you are not a college professor,
and I'm definitely not a librarian.
So, honestly, I'm just excited
to be able to be myself again.
I mean, aren't you even a little bit
happy to be back on the ship?
I was happy with the life
we built together,
what I thought would be our future.
And this just all feels like
moving backwards.
Moving backwards.
What if Sara didn't move
forwards with her life,
she moved backwards?
She said she wanted to go to a place
where she belonged.
What's the one place in 1958
she already called home?
The League of Assassins.
There is one source that we could
check to test your theory.
Gideon, bring up the Shadow Record.
Shadow Record?
The list of every member
of the League of Assassins
since the invention of writing
in 3200 B.C.
Fascinating, except these sheets
of papyrus are entirely blank.
No, no, no.
The League uses invisible ink.
I did my graduate thesis
at the Academy on their history.
Gideon.
Sara said that Ra's al Ghul had lived
nearly a century before she met him.
Thanks to the Lazarus Pit.
It's basically a life-extending
Jacuzzi,
located in a place that's
the opposite of life-extending.
You should count yourself lucky,
Dr. Palmer.
Only a handful of outsiders have been
inside the League's fortress
and lived to tell the tale.
You are correct, Captain.
There is a mention
of a Ta-er al-Sahfer.
That's Sara's League
of Assassins name.
According to the Shadow Record,
she joined the League in 1958.
Incredible, Sara became a member
of the secret organization
that trained her to be an assassin
50 years prior to when
she initially joined.
Sara needs our help.
By all accounts,
Ra's al Ghul is a very controlling,
very homicidal fanatic.
Gideon, chart a course
for Nanda Parbat.
Look, if you're gonna kill me,
just do it already.
I'm not gonna kill you.
I'm gonna to take a trip
back to Central City
and visit your baby sister.
The beautiful thing about time travel
is I get to kill her more than once.
I can kill Lisa in front of you,
go back in time,
kill her in front of you again
and again, and again.
Sir, several anomalies
in the timeline suggest
the Waverider has touched down
in Nanda Parbat.
Chart a course.
I used to think the most beautiful
thing on Earth was fire.
Now I know it's vengeance.
Perhaps, Jefferson and I should...
Extricating Sara from the likes
of the League requires stealth.
So, no firestorm for the two of you.
And you're out of practice,
so no ATOM suit
unless absolutely necessary.
Look out!
Thanks.
Well done, Jefferson.
You guard the exit while I find Sara.
We will be in and out of here faster
than you can say Ra's al Ghul.
Sara.
It's me.
Rip?
I'm here to bring you back.
I'm so sorry
that it's taken me so long.
- Who else is here?
- The entire team.
Well, except for Mr. Snart.
I'll explain everything
back on the...
Something's wrong.
They should have been back by now.
Well, I think this counts
as absolutely necessary.
I've got my exo-suit shrunk down,
and I can miniaturize
and do some tiny sneaking.
It's been two years
since you've used that suit.
And that's after you scavenged it
for parts for your time beacon.
You don't even know if it works.
Is now really the time
for your little marital spat?
We're not married.
Can we just keep it down, please?
Sara?
Found her.
Oh, hey.
Hey.
Sara, what the hell?
You shouldn't have come here.
Yeah, I'm starting to get that.
We came here to rescue you.
I don't need to be rescued.
I've found peace here.
Peace with the League of Assassins?
That must be the first time that
sentence has ever been uttered.
Oh, I can't believe I'm back here.
If this is retribution of some kind
for stranding you in 1958...
It is the will of Ra's al Ghul.
Trespassers are to be executed.
We just need a little more time
to get through to her.
Do Time Masters have a different
understanding of the word "executed"?
No, no, no. It's called Time Drift.
When one spends too long
in an alien timeline,
one loses ties with one's
former self... former identity.
Oh, my God.
What?
I didn't understand it before, but...
my powers... they went dormant.
- What are you talking about?
- My wings.
You must have noticed
that I haven't been able to...
hawk out in almost two years.
I just thought
that you didn't want to.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because it was so hard
for you to give up hope
that the team would return.
When you finally did, you started
to be happy again,
and I couldn't bear telling you
that I wasn't.
- That ain't good.
- I had no idea.
Look, Ray,
I loved being with you.
I wasn't just losing my powers.
I was losing my memories
of my past lives.
I was starting to lose myself.
I'm sorry. I...
But, look,
you didn't have to protect me.
I could have handled the truth.
It couldn't have been so easy
for Raymond,
either having to give up being
the ATOM.
I'm sorry.
Can we have a private moment?
I think we all wish you would've had
this moment in private.
Don't you think that we were meant
for something greater
than being stuck in 1960,
eating fondue with the neighbors?
Yeah, we were meant to be tortured
and executed in Nanda
I can't believe I'm back here,
Parbat.
If we die...
at least it would be in pursuit
of a greater purpose.
- That's it.
- What's it?
Ra's al Ghul's purpose
in life is to see
that the League continues with all
of its ancient traditions intact...
Including murdering intruders?
I will appeal to Ra's al Ghul's
respect for the League's traditions,
invoking one of them right now.
Well, what kind of traditions, man?
Guards!
Would you mind loosening these up
a little bit before you leave?
Just out of curiosity,
what do you think your new
masters are gonna do with you
once you've delivered
the team up to them?
I don't expect there's a pension plan
for old bounty hunters.
Once they get what
they want from you,
they're gonna toss you aside.
Like you tossed me aside?
You and I both made choices
that led us to this moment.
What matters, Mick,
is your next move.
And I'm willing to bet
that some little piece of the old you
is in that armor somewhere.
No. You're wrong.
Mr. Hunter.
Captain, as point of fact.
Right.
Well, I do hope your request
for an audience
is not an attempt
to justify your trespass here.
Most certainly not.
But it would be remiss of me
if I didn't use this opportunity
to reiterate that Sara...
is very important to me...
to all of us.
And as she is to me.
And as you can all see,
she has chosen to remain here.
Yes, well, if that is her wish,
we will indeed honor it.
Well, thank you.
But your deaths will make
that concession irrelevant.
Well, according to my understanding
of League Law,
the whole death thing can be avoided,
should we prevail at trial.
Yeah, I don't think these guys
are the People's Court type.
I demand a trial by combat.
And how is a man such as you
so well-versed on our traditions?
Do we have an accord?
May victory be yours.
I... I was under the impression
that I would be fighting you.
Then it would seem your understanding
of our laws requires some refinement.
You see,
I may choose any champion I wish...
as may you.
I'll do it.
You haven't had very much experience
in swordsmanship, Mr. Palmer.
I nominate Miss Saunders.
What? No.
Didn't you hear?
She can't even hawk...
I accept.
- Kendra, you can't...
- I've got this.
You have to put a stop to this.
Sara taught Kendra to control
her warrior side.
I believe that Kendra can remind Sara
of her humanity.
Before or after Sara kills her?
Sara.
Ta-er al-Sahfer.
Whatever your name is now.
I know you don't want to kill me.
Want is irrelevant.
I serve Ra's al Ghul.
Remember that move?
You taught it to me.
Your teacher was excellent.
Sara, no!
Sara.
You're not a murderer
or an assassin.
No!
You're the White Canary.
I know that sound.
Chronos.
You can't face him.
You can't defeat him.
You brought him here.
It's only right you kill him.
It's a long story, pal.
Ray!
You son of a bitch.
Don't do it.
Don't kill him.
Snart?
Sorry, don't kill Chronos?
He's not Chronos.
Show them.
My God.
There is no God.
I imagine you have some questions
about what you witnessed.
When the lady you call Sara Lance
first arrived here,
her skills were unmatched.
It was as if she had completed
the training before.
I suppose that's because
you're both from the future.
When I came to your doorstep,
for the second time in my life,
I thought that I could find
a home here,
that this is where I really belong.
But your soul is divided...
by your ability to kill
and your desire to show mercy.
And there is no place for one
so conflicted within the League.
Ta-er al-Sahfer,
I release you.
You can reclaim your previous name...
and your past life.
Thank you.
In October 2008,
please see that your daughter
is off the coast of an island
in the North China Sea.
Lian Yu.
Why would I send Talia
on such a journey?
Not Talia.
Your daughter yet to be born.
I'm pretty sure
you'll call her Nyssa.
You think this is all over?
I will kill every single one of you.
I will watch you all burn!
You.
You should have killed me
when you had the...
You owe us an explanation.
Yes, it's quite remarkable,
Mr. Rory is working
for the Time Masters,
considering you killed him.
If you think back,
I never actually said I killed him.
No, you just let us think
that you did.
I didn't have to try too hard, did I?
Well, maybe I should have.
And at least he wouldn't have would
up a chew toy for the Time Masters.
But if you did,
we wouldn't have this opportunity.
An opportunity? To do what?
To reform Mr. Rory.
He killed Aldus.
Under the influence
of the Time Masters.
Chronos killed Aldus.
Mr. Rory was fighting
on our side that day.
I know what it's like to be trained
by an organization
for one purpose to kill,
and the kind of loyalty
that it can inspire.
I need to know that
we can reach Rory.
For my own sake.
The Time Masters took one of our own
and turned him against us.
I say we undo their handiwork.
Rory saved my life back in the gulag.
He's more than just a criminal
and an arsonist.
He's a member of our team.
He's a lost cause.
Oh, I wouldn't be so sure about that.
You will see that miracles abound
on this old time ship.
Gideon,
start the regeneration process.
What you mean regeneration?
I took genetic samples
from each of you
at the start of our voyage
for this exact eventuality.
Why am I only hearing about this now?
Because none of you had lost
a limb yet.
Ow.
So were you gonna tell me?
Sorry, tell you what?
That you were moving
into your room without me?
Oh, I just assumed that
you wanted some space.
You made it pretty clear
that you were over our old life.
Look...
just because I wasn't satisfied
with the circumstances
doesn't mean I didn't fall
in love with you.
It's just, I... I...
I don't want to lose you.
And I don't want to lose you.
For the first time,
in probably centuries,
I actually got to decide
who I want to fall in love with,
instead of having it decided for me.
So it doesn't matter where
or when we are.
You're the person I want to be with.
Wow.
That was... was that like, rehearsed?
Because that was really good.
So...
what do you want?
I believe we're ready to leave 1960.
And go where? I mean, when?
2147.
Mere decades before Vandal Savage
conquered the world.
I thought you had no idea
where he was.
You said Savage had been lost
to history.
Not world-changing history.
Records of the period are scarce,
but I've always known that
Vandal Savage can be located in 2147.
So, why haven't you told us
this sooner?
Because that period of history
is fraught with more peril
than I was willing to risk.
We have no choice
but to stop Vandal Savage in 2147...
or to die trying.
Well, I've died before.
So have I.
Gideon.
Plot a course
for Kasnia Conglomerate...
The year 2147.