In 2166,
an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan
is opposed by the body
I had sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered
as legends.
Previously, on
Legends of Tomorrow...
Hold on to something!
I wanna marry you, Ray.
Tragedy or heartbreak,
that's how it always ends
if the man's not Carter.
It's Carter.
He doesn't even remember
who he was.
Kendra, what are you
waiting for?
If I kill Savage,
his mind will be lost.
I'm so sorry, Rip.
Who are you, Gareeb?
Ramesses' men inform me
that you still refuse to speak.
To reveal your name
or why you tried to kill me.
Who are you?
The man who's trying
to save the world from you.
And how are
your efforts proceeding?
You can't even stand
for lack of food and water.
I will always rise up
against you.
I will never give up.
Soon, the sky rocks
will lay waste to this kingdom
and you along with it.
This cell will be your tomb.
What do you know of the future
that I don't, Gareeb?
Mission almost accomplished.
That bottle of Scotch
was given to me
by Rob Roy MacGregor in 1689.
It's not half-bad.
We should be toasting
to Savage's death.
Apart from celebrating murder,
Savage still has
Carter brainwashed.
I don't know if you've been
paying attention, Professor,
but murdering Savage
was always the plan.
Besides, Carter reincarnates,
which is more
than I can say about us.
As long as he is on board
and breathing,
Savage is a threat
to everyone on this ship.
So, what, we just kill Savage
and leave Carter
a brainless drone?
Yes.
Sorry we're late,
but we found something.
We've been running diagnostics
on Ray's suit
after his battle with Savage's
Rock'em Sock'em Robot.
The telemetry data
included a comprehensive scan
of the robot's tech.
Amazing.
This neuromorphic profile
is astonishingly futuristic.
Yeah, it's from 2166.
Well, that's the thing.
It's not.
This technology
is light years more advanced
than anything from 2166.
Who cares?
The Time Masters.
They refuse to take action
against Savage
because he didn't pose
a threat to the timeline.
But if he comes into possession
of future technology...
It means he's been engaging
in exactly the same
manipulation of time
that the Time Council
were designed to prevent.
So now they'll finally
sign off on undoing
all the damage Savage
has done to the world.
Last time I checked,
the Time Council
was at the edge of the timeline.
And this bucket of bolts
can barely
hold it together as it is.
Gideon, what's the status
of the Time Drive?
Stable, Captain.
Plot a course
for the Vanishing Point.
Tonight, Vandal Savage faces
justice for his crimes.
Quite the reversal of fortune.
Isn't it, Gareeb?
Four thousand years ago,
it was you who was the prisoner.
Ever since I met you again,
I've always wondered
how you managed to escape.
Another time, perhaps.
For the moment,
I'm more interested in this.
The brains
to your robot super-weapon.
At least a century
more advanced than
anything to be found in 2166.
Do you have something to ask me?
How did you obtain the ability
to travel through time?
From you.
When I saw you again in 1975,
I realized that time travel
was the only explanation.
You showed a caveman fire.
And I had almost 200 years
to figure out
how to strike a flame.
All this time,
I've been wondering
why it was so difficult
to locate you
throughout history.
Because you've been
moving through history.
Well, you'll come to learn
that this is just
one of many things
we have in common, Gareeb.
We are both doing what we must
to save the world.
Subjugating the world
to your rule is not saving it.
You would create a wasteland
and call it peace.
Do not misquote Tacitus to me.
I knew him well.
I have lived long enough
to watch civilizations
rise and fall.
You weep for your son...
I have held dozens
of my children
as they perish from old age.
You might be a Time Master,
but I am a master of time.
And I play a far deeper game
that you could ever hope
to comprehend.
Gideon, go to maximum
on the Time Drive.
Inadvisable, Captain.
When Dr. Palmer siphoned power
from the auxiliary Time Drive,
- he reduced the...
- Gideon!
Take us to maximum.
We need to get
to the Vanishing Point
as fast as possible.
Where am I?
Somewhere safe.
Safe as long
as those cuffs hold.
Do you know who you are?
I'm Cythian Torgo.
Adjunct to Lord Savage.
And you will release me, or
I will kill you where you stand.
Your name is Carter Hall.
You used to be Prince Khufu
of the Middle Kingdom.
- And I am...
- Kendra Saunders.
Oh, you seem surprised.
You didn't think Lord Savage
would warn me of my enemies?
Let me go and I promise you
I will show mercy.
I will kill you
without making you suffer first.
Not to sound like a 6-year-old,
but are we there yet?
No, the Waverider
was severely damaged
in Savage's last attack.
Yeah, I can tell
by the way she's flying.
You sure you're not pushing her
too hard?
The longer Savage
is on board this ship,
the greater
the danger to all of us.
To us or your family?
I checked with Gideon.
Bringing Savage on board
didn't change the timeline.
And your family still dies.
The timeline is always in flux.
Once we get
to the Vanishing Point,
all will be well.
Is that why you're pushing
the ship beyond its limits?
This has been my ship
for the last 13 years.
No one knows its limits better
than I do. Not even Gideon.
The Waverider
will hold together,
I promise you.
Bollocks. Gideon!
Time Drive failure, Captain.
The mains are offline.
- What happened?
- It appears the Time Drive
is in need of some repair.
Uh, Ms. Lance, if you wouldn't mind
going and checking
on our guests.
On it.
Mr. Jackson. I'm going to need
your assistance
in fixing the Time Drive.
What if Jefferson can't get
the ship moving again?
Oh, thanks for
the vote of confidence.
No, what I mean is,
if the ship can't be repaired,
we're marooned
in the Time Stream.
There really
is no need to worry.
The Jumpship is equipped
with an auxiliary Time Drive
capable of a one-time jump
back to 2016.
Which will not be necessary,
considering you
are gonna fix the Waverider.
- I'll do my best.
- That's the spirit.
You look concerned, Martin.
I'm remembering
what Mr. Snart said
about Savage's
presence on this ship
being a danger to us all.
Have you spoken with
your sister, Laurel, lately?
How do you know
so much about us?
Oh, I've only had 191 years
to research my enemies.
Well, then you'd know
I don't scare that easily.
You should be scared.
Of Captain Hunter.
His obsession to save his family
will be the death of you all.
Thanks for the tip.
Enjoy being incarcerated.
Captain Hunter
lied to you so often,
and still you persist
in believing him.
You do know
why he selected all of you
for this endeavor, don't you?
Great bone structure?
He chose people
he could manipulate.
People that would
believe his lies.
Well, the lies
I don't believe are yours.
Do you blame him for putting
his family's lives first?
I'd tell you to go to hell,
but you'd probably
just feel at home there.
Okay, I've got eyes
on the Time Drive.
There seems to be
a large crack in it.
Well, if the housing's intact,
we should be all right.
I am going
to need you to reroute
the power
from the secondary manifold.
Okay, I'm on it.
Gideon, what is the level
of contamination
in the engine room?
Levels at 3%
above maximum, Captain.
We have to get him out of there.
Don't worry.
He should be able to finish
before the radiation
has any adverse effect.
Jefferson?
Mom? What are you doing here?
Good question.
I'm supposed to be meeting
- my son at Jitters.
- Oh...
But clearly, he misses his old
job more than his mother.
I am so sorry,
I must've lost track of time.
Well, this should help.
I know it's not much,
but it belonged to your father.
At least, it was going to.
I bought it for him
as a birthday present
before he passed.
It's awesome. Thanks.
Maybe you could use it tonight.
Dinner at your Grandma Louise's?
Yes, I will be there.
And I won't be late.
I just got to stop by
the university first.
The university?
I gotta say goodbye
to a friend who's leaving town.
- But I will be there.
- 6:00.
- Okay. And I love you.
- I love you, too, baby.
Jefferson! Jefferson!
I did it. I got it working.
You said he wouldn't be harmed.
Must've been a surge
when he brought the Time Drive
back online.
Gideon?
Mr. Jackson has suffered
an extreme amount
of temporal radiation exposure.
- That sounds ominous.
- Oh, it is,
and there is nothing I can
do to reverse the side effects.
What side effects?
Mr. Jackson's internal organs
are aging
at an accelerated rate.
The rest of his body
will soon follow.
Why are all the snacks
in the future sugar-free?
So much for progress.
You remember Alexa?
Yeah. The security deposit job.
What about it?
I just had a feeling
about that one.
A sixth sense
things would end badly.
And they would have if you
hadn't pulled us out of there.
So what?
I'm getting
the same feeling now.
Gideon, how effective
were Mr. Jackson's attempts
to bring
the Time Drive back online?
The Drive's functions
have been restored,
but the entire system
will require a master reboot
before we can continue on
to the Vanishing Point.
Yes, please begin.
And in the meantime,
could you check the timeline
for any variation
in my family's future?
I believe Ms. Lance already
told you the results.
Please.
The timeline remains unchanged.
Were you expecting
something different?
Hope springs eternal, Ms. Lance.
If it didn't,
I would have surrendered
to despair a long time ago.
I assume Mr. Savage
is still secure in his cell?
He wasn't exactly short
on opinions on you, though.
I'd imagine not.
Among them being
that you would sell us out
to save your family.
He's not wrong.
Mr. Jackson
is currently in the MedBay,
facing death due to temporal
radiation exposure.
Wait, what?
I sent him to fix
the Time Drive.
I could have gone myself.
And I'm left to wonder if,
in some way,
I didn't because of the risk.
So you sent Jax
on a suicide mission
so that you could stay alive
to save your family?
I don't know, Sara.
That's what vexes me.
You know what vexes me?
Thinking that we've thrown in
with a captain
who cares more about himself
than he does his crew.
Kendra, are you sure about this?
Do you remember him?
He was our son,
Aldus.
You really expect me
to believe that?
I expect you
to remember your feelings.
We were together.
And we were happy.
We were a family.
Stay back!
Oops.
You okay?
- I should have known better.
- But are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Stay away from him.
I'll be right back.
- Where are you going?
- To end this.
Dr. Palmer, to what do I owe
the pleasure of this visit?
You're going to tell me
how to free Carter's mind.
Well, all you had to do was ask.
Are you sure you want me to?
Of course I'm sure.
Because the moment
I release him,
you will lose her forever.
You don't know Kendra.
I know Chay-Ara.
And I know the man who stands
between you and your love
has stood between me
and mine for millennia.
We're actually quite alike,
you and I.
We're nothing alike.
You're insane.
But yet Chay-Ara once loved me
as she professes to love you.
Oh, you didn't know that, did you?
I don't even think
Chay-Ara remembers.
But 4,000 years ago,
I discovered that my Chay-Ara
had been reborn.
But with no memory
of what had happened.
Like you murdering
her and Carter.
True.
She had no recollection
of my crime of passion.
And she fell in love with me.
Very deeply.
And I with her.
That is perverse.
No, that is fact.
That is history.
We were happy, Dr. Palmer.
Very happy.
None of us blinded
by our cursed past.
Until he came.
He took her away from me.
He poisoned her against me.
He stole the happiness
that we shared, Dr. Palmer.
No.
No, Carter is a good man.
And you are my only enemy.
Am I?
Or am I just a man
experiencing the same things
as you are right now?
We have the same enemy.
If Carter is freed,
you lose her.
But then, she would hardly be
the first woman you've lost,
now, would she?
I am really gonna have to beef
up our security around here.
It was pretty easy
to bypass the system,
considering I designed it.
You like my ride?
Those are some
pretty hot wheels.
Yeah.
Maybe that's your new name.
- How you feeling?
- I'm okay.
- What are you doing here?
- I came to drop off a note.
Let me guess. It says,
"Hey, Felicity,
I hope you're well."
"I'm off to travel through time
and fight an immortal bad guy."
- Was that me?
- Yeah.
- That was pretty good.
- Thank you.
So, obviously, Oliver told you.
Don't let his broodiness
fool you.
He can be
quite chatty sometimes.
He also happened to mention
that you're going
on this suicide mission
because you think
there's nothing for you here.
You think
it's a suicide mission?
I don't think going after
Vandal Savage is a vacation.
But don't change the subject.
You have a life here, Ray.
Actually, everybody thinks
I'm dead.
Nothing puts things
in perspective more
than seeing yourself
become a ghost.
You're not a ghost.
You just need to come back
to the world.
And I will.
After we take out Savage.
Look, I became the Atom
to make the world
a better place.
And I'm pretty sure
that saving it counts.
- I'm pretty sure it does, too.
- Hmm.
See you soon.
You know,
I would've stayed for you.
I do.
But who knows? Maybe the future
Mrs. Palmer is out there
somewhere in the past
or the future.
- In some parallel universe.
- Oh, yeah.
I'm off to save the world,
not fall in love.
"And though my soul
departs the Earth,"
"I count the days
till my rebirth"
"I will wait across eternity
For my love to come back to me."
Please.
Come back.
Ray.
Ray. Ray, stop!
Please. Just give me a chance
to explain.
What you saw back there, it...
What? It wasn't
what it looked like?
You reciting a love poem
to your
brainwashed ex-boyfriend.
I am just trying to help Carter
remember who he really is.
Your soul mate.
Yeah, that's the part
in the conversation
where you're supposed to say,
"No, Ray, you're my soul mate."
Ray, you know that I love you.
Yeah, I know.
Just not enough.
I can't believe I'm saying it,
but Savage was right.
Loving you is like a curse.
Oh, Ray.
You have to know,
whatever he said,
he's just trying
to get inside your head.
I know that. But he's right.
Kendra, I don't think
I can do this anymore.
What are you saying?
What, you want to end things?
Unless you can tell me
that I'll ever be anything more
than just Carter's placeholder.
Ray.
Are you certain
these results are accurate?
Jefferson's blood chemistry
is akin to that of a...
A 63-year-old man.
Actually, I don't feel
a day over 60.
This isn't funny.
No, and it's all Rip's fault.
I'm afraid he's also suffering
from early stage osteoarthritis.
Your exposure
to the temporal radiation
has led to an accelerated rate
of intracellular degeneration.
This is what happens
when Rip goes with "Plan B."
And "Plan A" being taking
Savage's head in with that mace.
We're endeavoring to resolve
this without bloodshed.
And how's that working out
for you, Gandhi?
Look, there's nothing
we can do about it now.
We can talk to Hunter.
Even if Kendra
was to kill Savage,
my situation's still the same.
We're talking about
our situation, Pops.
We're not waiting around
for the other shoe to drop.
You deserve better.
Alexa.
You bet your ass.
- We need to talk.
- We saw what you did to Jax.
And we're worried
it's just the beginning.
- The beginning of what?
- It's like I said, Rip,
as long as Savage is alive
and on this ship,
he is dangerous.
The Time Drive is rebooting.
We will soon be on our way.
I'm asking for
a little faith, gentlemen.
Sorry. Fresh out.
I take it you and Mr. Snart
are of the same mind?
Yes.
And what of you, Ms. Lance?
You're the one who said
you'd sell us out
for your family.
Well, if that's how
you all feel,
none of you is obliged to
continue on this voyage with me.
As I told Martin,
the Jumpship can make a one-time
voyage back to 2016.
You saying it's ours?
I'm saying that this mission
has always been
a voluntary enterprise.
And the mission
was to kill Savage.
Which doesn't seem
to be on the table anymore.
Very well.
Leave if that's what...
It's been a blast, Rip.
Good luck getting
to the Vanishing Point.
Tell your pals Chronos says,
"Kiss my ass."
What about you, Sara?
Never been one
to run from a fight.
Hi.
Impossible.
When I saw you last...
I know.
A miracle.
When I'd thought there were
none left to be had.
I needed to see you.
Look, I don't know how,
but I'm gonna get you
out of here.
This isn't your fight anymore,
Ta-er al-Sahfer.
Look, I'm not gonna
let you rot here.
Not when you're in here
because of me.
I am in here
because of my choices, beloved.
I made them. I'm ready
to accept my punishment.
I won't leave you in here.
If you love me, you will.
If you love me, you will
leave this place far behind,
and live a life unburdened
by your past.
It's easier said than done.
Anything worth doing always is.
Oh, finally, an intellect
approximate to my own.
My imprisonment was starting
to get dreary, Professor.
I'm not here
to play mind games with you.
I'm here to ask you
if you remember a night
in October 1975,
a place called
the Greyhill Building.
That night,
you and your acolytes...
Were celebrating
the acquisition of your friend
Carter Hall's body.
Yes.
It's my understanding
this ritual
involved you sharing your
immortality with your followers.
And you wish for me
to do the same for someone else?
Someone dear to you.
Your nuclear
counterpart, perhaps?
Yes.
And as impertinent as this
may sound, I need your help.
Well, clearly, your friends
didn't give you
the full account of the ritual.
You see, it was Carter's blood
that worked the magic.
Perhaps you should talk to him.
Or better yet, Dr. Palmer.
I'm sure that he would be
more than happy
to help you spill some.
And I'm certain
you would enjoy that.
Pitting me and Raymond
against Carter. Against Kendra.
Having us all
at each other's throats
while being stranded
in the Time Stream.
But we're not stranded.
Not entirely.
Thank you, Mr. Savage.
As I'd hoped, you've provided me
with a solution to my problem.
I don't get it, Grey.
What's in here
that's gonna fix me?
Well, nothing inside
the Jumpship, Jefferson.
But rather the craft itself.
You see, this ship is
preprogrammed to return to 2016.
I've made some
additional adjustments
according to the theory
of Quantum Retro-Causality.
And if my math is correct,
the trip through the Time Stream
should reverse your condition.
No. No.
I'm not leaving you or the team.
Which is why
I'm not giving you a choice.
What did you do?
I administered a mild sedative.
You roofied me again?
When I tricked you
onto this ship the first time,
I was only thinking of myself.
Now, I'm thinking of you.
You can't do this!
If we're separated, you'll die.
I've already lived
my life, Jefferson.
Now, you must live yours.
Give my love to Clarissa.
Tell her I'm sorry.
She deserved a proper goodbye.
Grey! Grey, no! No!
- Knock, knock.
- Oh, hello.
I hope you don't mind,
but I thought I'd see if I could
interest you in a lunch date.
Oh, my darling, I'm right in
the middle of some research
that simply cannot wait.
What's the topic?
As a matter of fact,
time itself.
The irony. Oh!
Again. I completely forgot,
I promised I'd meet
with some fellow academics
to help resolve
an experiment of theirs.
Does this experiment
have anything
to do with time travel?
Almost certainly.
But it won't take long.
In fact, I'll be home
before you even know it.
Clarissa, you know
that I love you.
There's nothing I do that isn't
driven by that very thought.
Now let's get
the hell out of here.
What did you do, Poindexter?
- What do you mean?
- The Jumpship. Where is it?
Well, it's really more a question
of when, but...
Oh, yes. You both wanted
to return to 2016.
Got it in one.
I did what I had to do
to save Jefferson's life.
Now, we must do
whatever is necessary
to repair the Waverider
and deliver Savage
to the Vanishing Point.
Back so soon? With a stench
of defeat written all over you.
Can't say I didn't warn you.
Trying to get under my skin,
is that it?
I've got your
little game figured out.
And for all your intelligence,
you still didn't manage
to make Chay-Ara yours.
I wouldn't expect a psychopath
like you to understand.
Kendra is free to do
what she wants.
You know what I see
when I look at you?
I see weakness
masquerading as goodness.
I'm not the one trapped
in a cage.
Well, if it weren't
for this cage,
you wouldn't have
that arrogant look on your face.
You think I'm afraid of you?
No, I know you are.
At least Carter had the courage
to face me like a man.
No wonder she didn't choose you.
Oh.
You feel better now, Dr. Palmer?
Not even close.
And I thought
you were nothing like me.
I'll leave you
to contemplate on that.
Time Drive re-initialization
complete, Captain.
The primary systems
are back online and stable.
Begin ignition sequence
and resume our route
to the Vanishing Point.
You're a fool, Professor.
I'm trying
to save Jefferson's life.
Savage has escaped.
- What?
- I'm sorry.
Pull up all the surveillance
monitors now!
I'm afraid Vandal Savage
has already freed Carter Hall,
and is preparing to disengage...
That can't be good.
Gideon's entire operational
matrix is offline,
and without her help...
We'll have to make our
approach the old-fashioned way.
Shouldn't we be more worried
about Savage
and his brainwashed crony?
Yes. Which is why I need you
and Dr. Palmer
to go and recapture him.
In the meantime, if the rest
of us can't figure out
how to pilot the ship
without Gideon,
we're never going to be able
to leave the Time Stream.
If we live through this,
you bumbling idiot,
I might just kill you.
Exactly how old-fashioned
are you talking?
So, if the Time Stream
is like this vast river,
these maps plot the safest
course along that river's path.
Exactly. I keep these here,
just in case of emergency.
This certainly qualifies.
What's Jurgens Ridge?
Pray you need never find out.
Martin, you're gonna be
our engineer.
I need you to adjust
our energy output
to avoid overtaxing
the Waverider.
And you, Ms. Lance, you're going
to be our navigator.
I was in the League
of Assassins, not NASA.
I need someone
who can make tough calls
under extreme pressure.
No one fits that description
better than you.
Come to join the party?
You should have
left me back in 2166.
Yeah, yeah,
we know that, mullethead.
Who are you
to stand up against me,
Vandal Savage,
destroyer of empires?
Leonard Snart, robber of ATMs.
We need more power
to the Time Drive, Martin.
How much farther can we push it?
25%, and only for a brief burst,
but it might be all we need.
It's still two against four.
Come on!
What's our trajectory
looking like, Ms. Lance?
Just give me a second here.
Oddly enough,
as the Vanishing Point
is at the very end of time...
Yeah, and we're never
going to make it there
if you don't lower the ship
negative 12 degrees, on my mark.
Three, two, one, now!
Did it work?
Well, we're not dead.
I got this. Handle Savage.
Haircut,
move your fat head
so I can get a clean shot!
They seem to be getting closer.
- I'll go help them.
- No!
I'm not going to place
another one of you in jeopardy.
I'll go.
But who's gonna pilot the ship?
Gareeb. I was wondering
where you were hiding.
Bring her to me.
Chay-Ara. My love.
I'm sorry that it has to end
like this again.
Carter.
I will wait...
For eternity.
Come back to me.
Kendra.
He's alive.
You saved him.
You saved us all.
Is that...
Welcome to the Vanishing Point.
I can't believe we made it.
And what did you do
to your shoulder?
Hmm? Oh, I might have jumped
in front of a laser blast
intended for Ms. Saunders.
What?
I couldn't have my team
thinking I cared
more about myself than them,
now, could I?
Really?
Uh, I think I just lost control
of the ship.
Yeah, that might have something
to do with us
being the most wanted time
criminals in all of history.
Timeship Waverider,
we've taken control
of your guidance systems.
Disable your weapons
and prepare to be boarded.
Oh, it's good to be home.
Captain Hunter.
This is unexpected.
Well, I have a reputation
to maintain, don't I?
And I hereby request
an immediate assembly
of the Time Council
in accordance with
General Order 52.
So you've returned
to answer for your crimes?
No, I'm here to justify them.
If this truly is goodbye,
would you mind answering
just one final question?
It seems only sporting.
How did you manage to escape
my prison, all those years ago?
There were no signs of damage,
no clues to your tricks.
It left me puzzled
for centuries.
The best magic tricks
have the simplest solutions.
I bribed your guard
with a novelty pen.
It had a picture
of a woman on it,
turn it upside down,
her top comes off.
I won it from a drunk G.I.
in a Philippines bar in 1944.
It's a tacky souvenir,
but in this case, a lifesaver.
Now, unfortunate for you,
the guards
in the Vanishing Point
won't be quite so easily swayed.
- Hey.
Uh...
I was making sure he was okay.
I think most guys
would be more inclined
to smother him with a pillow.
Just because he stole my girl and tried
to take over the ship?
But seriously.
Carter saved your life.
He's a part of this team.
Always has been.
I wish things
could be different.
Yeah. Me too.
I need you to know
that what we had was real.
In a way,
a broken heart is just
what the doctor ordered.
It is?
Yeah.
When I lost Anna, I thought that...
I could never find anybody
who I could spend
the rest of my life with.
And you proved me wrong.
Thank you for showing me
that it's possible.
Rip Hunter.
On behalf of the Time Council,
you are hereby ordered...
Yeah, before you do that,
there's someone
I'd like you to meet.
You remember Mr. Savage?
Of course.
And we remember
how you pled for us
to remove him from the timeline
once before.
Well, as the first Time Master
was so fond of saying,
"That was then. This is now."
Incontrovertible proof
that Vandal Savage
has been engaged
in the manipulation of time.
Including a confession.
When I saw you again in 1975,
I realized that time travel
was the only explanation.
You showed a caveman fire.
And I had almost 200 years
to figure out
how to strike a flame.
Impressive, Captain Hunter.
You and your team
have accomplished
what none of us here in the
Time Council believed you would.
If the prisoner
would step forward.
Vandal Savage,
by the power of this chamber,
it is my duty
to return you
to Earth immediately.
What?
This man you've brought before
us is needed back in 2166.
You're in league with him?
I wouldn't expect you
to understand our reasons.
For all your wisdom,
you were never able to
take the long view of history.
Take him away.
Search their ship
for the others.
Did you hear that?
Don't try to distract me.
We need to find
somewhere to hide.
Why do we need to find
somewhere to hide?
Alexa.
Damn.
Ah.
If you're here for Savage,
you're too late.
- Mick, what's going on?
- You're under arrest.
Oh.
If I had a nickel
for every time I heard that.
Druce's men
have taken your ship.
Your friends are under arrest,
and you are
once again my prisoner.
This time,
I don't plan to lose you.
Oh, and yes, I do remember
the guard very well.
He died.
Now, if you would excuse me,
I better be
getting back to 2166.
I've been waiting so very long
to meet your family.
Wouldn't miss it for the world.
English - SDH