Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
You and I dating would be
totally weird.
Totally weird.
Hank is running some secret project.
A man came to me, Neron.
He offered me a deal.
Don't tell me you're having
second thoughts.
I have a new partner now. My son.
I don't need you anymore.
I don't need you anymore, either.
Dad?
I'm sorry.
I didn't kill Nate's dad.
Sara, you're asking me
to risk everything
for some conspiracy theory?
For a bunch of monsters?
- Ava, don't do this.
- I'm done.
Even I didn't just get into
an argument she asked me to leave.
Come on, Ava, open up.
Look, I...
I miss you.
I'm sorry things went down the way
they did, but...
Please just open the door.
Well, technically this is still
our apartment.
Ava.
Nora, what are you doing here?
- I can explain.
I didn't kill Hank, it was a demon.
Yeah, I know.
His name is Neron
and he's wearing Desmond
as a bleeding suit.
Ray!
Sara! Great news.
Hank was killed by a demon.
"Great" was not the word
he was looking for.
- Poor Nate.
- Look, Ava is missing.
- Missing?
- I should have checked
- on her sooner...
- It's Neron.
He has his sights set
on the Time Bureau
and the creatures,
and if he got to Hank,
then dingdongs to donuts,
Ava was next.
Hey, she is not dead.
Listen, when Neron was out
the Bureau,
he and I shared a connection.
If you can take me to Ava's place,
I might be able to know
where he took her.
Demons communicate,
he'll know your past,
how susceptible you are.
You're a liability.
She's not a liability.
She's a survivor.
Unlike you, she's turned her
dark experiences
into a source of strength,
not an excuse for alcoholism
or chain smoking.
She also saved your life.
Sorry.
Would you like to add anything?
No, that about covers it.
I don't care if she's a liability.
If Neron has Ava,
then I need all the magical firepower
that we've got.
You two with me.
Woman the ship.
This is from two weeks ago.
She's been gone a tick.
That's not good.
Yeah, thanks.
There.
What? What do you see?
He had her.
Here.
Ava.
That doesn't mean she's dead.
It doesn't mean she's alive, either.
I know where she is.
Conspiracies, embezzling,
paper trails...
I feel like Julia Roberts
in Erin Brockovich.
We're more Pacific Gas
and Electric, Gary.
Wait, we're the bad guys?
I don't know who we are,
Gary, all right?
We're the guys trying to keep
my dad's cracked out idea
of Jur-magic Park from tanking
the Time Bureau.
All right? So anything that has to do
with Heyworld, get rid of it!
How am I gonna explain
all this to Director Sharpe?
Actually, Ava's missing.
I knew it.
I knew it, you know, I had a dream
about her
where she was driving
and I was in a car seat in the back.
- We were headed to Schul.
- Gary.
She needs me.
I got... I got...
Sara, Constantine, and Nora are...
looking for her.
- Nora?
- Look, she didn't kill Hank.
- Come on, man.
- Just listen, okay?
Your dad made a deal
with a demon named Neron.
I guess something went wrong
and the demon killed him.
I'm sorry, buddy.
My dad made a deal with a demon
to open a theme park?
Oh, Ray,
I don't know how much more
of this I can take, man.
- Is that you?
- No.
If this is my dad's mistress,
I'm gonna jump out a window.
- Hello?
- Yo, Mr. H. It's Mikey T.
Listen, got a question for you
about the dragon lair.
Could sure use your eyes down here.
Do...down where?
What? Here, at the site.
Buckwood Downs?
Yeah, where else?
Talk to you later.
Who was it?
I don't know,
he sounded like a Soprano,
but apparently my dad started
building this theme park.
The guys who were working with him,
maybe they know something
about this Neron
and why he killed my dad.
Come on!
I'm Steel, you're The Atom.
There is nothing we cannot handle!
This one.
Ava?
Hey.
Ava.
She's alive.
- What did he do to her?
- He's preparing her.
Neron must be looking
for a new vessel.
It only makes sense going after Ava,
especially if he wants control
over the Time Bureau.
But when a demon possesses someone,
the body has to be willing,
and if it's not,
the demon has to force his way in
by sending the soul to purgatory.
That's where the real fight begins.
How do we save her?
Some souls go up and some go down.
But if she's been there
as long as she has,
then she's not coming back, Sara.
I'm not giving up on her, John.
You're going to send me
to purgatory to get her.
If I send you down there with her,
there's nothing that I can do
to protect you.
I'll take my chances.
This isn't something you can
just fight your way through, love.
John, please!
Fine.
Lay down.
Our purgatory is designed to drive
the soul to breaking point.
It's tailored to drive
the captive mad.
Now where you're going,
that's Ava's personal nightmare.
I've died, lost my soul,
and escaped a demon realm.
I'm pretty sure I can handle
Ava's purgatory.
Well, prepare for the worst,
Sara Lance.
Welcome.
Do you need a bag?
I got to get out of here.
I can't do this anymore.
I just gotta get out of here.
Ava!
Hey. Hey.
Oh, thank God.
Oh, my God.
Sara, is that really you?
It's me. I got you.
What the hell happened? Am I dead?
You were kidnapped by a demon
and he's trying to take over
your body
so he trapped your soul here
in your own personal purgatory.
But Ava, if you check out, you die.
Well, that's kind of on the nose,
isn't it?
Wait, does that mean
that he got you too?
No.
I'm taking you home.
I got it! Natari!
I'm gonna regret asking this,
but what's that?
It's your couple's name.
Nat for Nate and of course Ari
is for you.
You know I'm a superhero, right?
With a flick of my wrist I could
blast you with my wind powers.
Being honest, wind powers,
just not that scary.
Yeah, you're like
a magical hair dryer.
What is this? "Legends Eye
for the Straight Guy"?
You're straight?
Where's Sara?
She's with Constantine
and Nora, trying to find Ava.
Actually, they've just returned,
and Mr. Constantine
has called a team meeting in the lab.
- He can do that?
- No.
Let's go, dummies.
- Ava's in hell?
- She's not in hell.
Her soul is trapped in limbo.
And I am right there with her.
- Oh, Gary.
- Emotionally, poor Director Sharpe.
I've sent Sara down there
to try and pull her out.
I thought that they broke up.
She still loves her.
- What can we do?
- Sara chose to go in after her
so unless praying is your thing,
then the best thing
you can do is wait.
You don't have to worry.
- Oh, he's all right.
- I'll take good care of her.
Them.
All right, Charlie, you're with me.
This should be interesting.
Let's go find out what
this demon wants, shall we?
You up for it?
All right then,
let's raise some hell.
Oh, how you doing?
Can I help you guys?
Yeah, we're looking for Mister...
Mr. T.
Who's asking?
Because no one's allowed
on this site unle...
Hey, I know you.
I'd recognize that Heywood
jawline anywhere.
You must be "And Son."
You kidding me?
Hank is always going on about you.
Where, where is he?
Hank passed.
What?
Jeez, I... sorry to hear that.
You mind if we take a look around?
Hey,
it's all yours now, kid.
Question, did my dad ever mention
a man by the name of Neron?
Neron?
What is that, Greek?
No, it's Demonic... Danish, actually.
No, never heard of the guy.
Actually, to be honest with you,
Hank didn't really tell me a lot.
All he gave me was... was this.
We're building that right now.
A unicorn rodeo.
Can you imagine?
Two unicorns jousting?
I'd rather not.
Hey, come here, come here.
This. This is what I was
calling you guys about.
About the...
Dragon lair.
Yeah, I know.
I drew it.
- I drew all of this.
- Great, tell me something.
Look at this. See this here?
What is this?
Is this supposed to be real flame,
or were you thinking, like, plexi?
Because I got a guy that can do fire.
Like forget about it.
I can't believe he did it.
I know you and your dad struggled
and even if you got
your wires crossed,
you never stopped trying to connect.
I just hope my dad knew I loved him.
Oh, he knew.
Look at this place.
You know, I just wish
he would have found
a better way to, you know,
tell me he loved me.
One that didn't involve teaming up
with a demon
and embezzling money
from the government.
It's a bit much.
Mikey T!
Change of plans.
Tear it down.
The dragon lair?
The whole thing.
Waiting sucks.
Sexting Nate?
Boundaries, Mona.
I need vicarious feels.
There are more important things
to focus on right now
and Nate's got a lot going on.
It's not the right time.
What are you typing?
Hey, what's up?
Okay, I don't even know
why I'm talking to you two about it.
You don't even date humans.
Love's love.
Whatever you need, I'm here.
Why is Gary in your subconscious?
I may have some Gary issues
that need working out.
Okay, we just, we need to find
the door that you came in.
Does any of this look familiar?
No, it all looks exactly the same.
Why don't we just try to follow
the arrows back?
Maybe they'll take us
to the entrance.
Reminder, shoppers, the store
will be closing in one hour.
Constantine didn't say anything
about that.
What does it mean?
It means we take shortcuts.
Come on.
Hello, again, ladies.
Damn it.
- Okay, this way.
- No!
Or we could just ask Gary.
How do we get to the entrance?
We're not really allowed to give
that kind of advice.
- Come on. -
But,
the Ergrik wardrobe might be
just the thing you're looking for.
Looks like the wardrobe section.
Now what?
I think we're supposed
to put it together.
No sweat.
Here.
Wait, wait, wait.
Step one, insert the dowel.
- Here, babe.
- I got this.
- Shut up, man!
- No, you shut up!
You kidding me?
Why, you brain-damaged?
Papa's home.
Miss me?
I missed you.
We'll be together soon, my pet.
Not bloody likely.
Oh, Nora.
There's nowhere for you to run now,
you bile bladder.
Me, run?
You're the one who ran.
All I had to do was say,
"I'm coming for you, Johnny."
And you left 2018 to me.
It's delicious how easily humans
are corrupted,
especially here in D.C.
So that's your game?
You inflict fear and anger
on humanity?
I merely fan the flames.
People are primed to give in
to what they fear most.
You know what, mate?
I am going to send your ass
straight back to hell.
John, this isn't the plan.
Nora, we finally get to talk.
Hope you've enjoyed your little
dalliances inside my mind.
But it's not a one way street.
Is it, Nora?
I knew you were a liability.
We should be off with him.
You're playing right into his hands,
John.
You're the one who can't handle this.
Oh, yes, says Miss Lock Herself Up
because she can't handle
her own demons.
Well, this is me handling mine,
all right?
Out!
- He's getting to you.
- Oh, he's getting to me?
- Yeah.
- He's inside your head.
What, you don't think
I haven't seen you struggling?
Humanity hasn't exactly been
kind to you, has it, Nora?
You're addicted to this kind
of power,
and believe me, it doesn't go away.
No it doesn't and it hasn't
been easy, but if I can trust myself,
I don't think it's too much
to ask for you to try too.
Oh, it's killing you to look
at his face.
I know how hard it is to watch
someone you love become a demon.
Yeah, well too bad there
aren't any Beebos around
to hug it to death.
We can't just...
keep him locked up in there,
driving us all mad.
Yeah, well, I think
between the two of us,
we can figure something out.
Ta-dah!
- Damn it.
- What a surprise.
You followed none of the instructions
and it didn't work.
I'm sensing that this isn't
about the dresser.
No, this is what you always do.
- Just bulldoze your way though.
- I do not always do this.
Like lying to me about the Kaupe?
You were defending
torturing creatures.
Defen... I wasn't defending it.
I was defending myself.
Of course, I don't believe that
we should be intentionally hurting
anything or anyone but when we fight,
Sara, I get really scared,
and I just go to my corner.
Look, it's just fight or flight.
It couldn't be any more human.
I just really need to know
that you're on my team.
I am always on your team,
even when we disagree.
Now,
should we give it another go?
Thank you.
See?
Following instructions
is not that bad.
Oh, don't gloat.
Let's get out of here.
Something's wrong.
Did we miss a screw or something?
No.
We missed this.
- It's...
- How the hell did we
possibly miss this?
- Damn it.
- Hey, look.
It's not perfect, but it's ours.
Can you live with that?
Hey?
Don't go in your corner.
Yeah,
I can live with it.
Hell yeah. Let's go to Narnia.
Are we out?
We're out of the closet
but not the store.
- Touché.
- Welcome to our mattress showroom.
If you'll follow me?
The mattress you choose
will be the most important
decision of your life.
Wait, you're showing them
the mattresses?
We need everyone out
before Tabitha gets here.
Who the hell is Tabitha?
You don't want to know Tabitha.
Best of luck in your mattress choice.
- Wait, we need to...
- Gary, wait...
This is starting to feel like
that escape room we did.
Okay, so, subconscious Gary said
this would be the most important
choice of our life.
What do you think that means?
That even subconscious Gary needs
to get a life?
No, it's a puzzle.
Do you... what does it mean?
Do you think we need to...
It means we need to pick a mattress.
How about this one?
What?
Whoa, 600 bucks?
- That is ridiculously...
- Three year warranty?
Expensive, right?
I was thinking, like, 250.
Wha... Are you kidding?
It would be saggy in like a year.
So you just flip it over.
You just flip it over?
Is that what you do when things
get saggy, you just flip them over
so you don't have to look
at their saggy faces?
Okay.
How about this one?
Fifteen years.
Oh, that's better.
Oh, when did you start going grey?
This place has been really stressful.
Yeah.
I think it's the mattress.
Apparently your purgatory is...
your anxieties.
One of which must be getting old.
I'm not worried
about getting old, Sara.
I'm worried about
getting old with you.
So, were...
talking about marriage.
You look...
still really hot, but...
You too.
Oh, well, 50 years is a long time.
Sleeping on one mattress.
Sure is.
Look, I know it's a lot.
Fifty years with just one person.
Well, it's... its not
the one person thing.
I just...
I've never really thought that much
pass tomorrow.
Even with my past.
Planning anything for the future
it's just...
fees like tempting fate.
And I convince myself that I like it
that way.
Until you came along.
You just freaking came to purgatory
for me.
How's that forgiving middle finger
the fate?
Look, you're allowed to want things
sometimes, Sara.
But what if I can't be?
The person that you need.
Let's be honest neither of us
needs anybody.
Right?
But you...
are who I want.
I bet you there's some good liquor
in Ava's office.
I mean,
my dad's old office.
Oh, man. Things are bleak.
Hey, Ray,
thanks for sticking around here.
Yeah, buddy, of course.
That's what friends are for.
I just wish I wasn't such an idiot
at my dad's funeral.
I had a chance to talk to him,
but I blew it.
Now I'll never know what happened.
Well, maybe Constantine can get you
some answers.
Looks like they caught Neron.
Son of a bitch.
Is that the demon who killed my dad?
Whoa, there, Squire.
You take it easy, all right?
Nate, you don't want to go in there.
- Just walk away.
- No.
- Wait!
- Not a chance.
Wait!
Hello, Nathaniel.
I've heard so much about you.
So predictable.
The son, who, in life, could never
connect with the father.
Here now, seeking the truth.
Well, here it is.
Hank was an unfortunate snag
in my plans so I...
You evil bastard.
Yeah.
Demon.
Nate's already angry,
makes him prime pickings for Neron.
No, he'll be all right.
As long as he doesn't cross
that bloody barrier.
Why?
He built your theme park
just like you wanted.
You think I wanted a theme park?
I gave Hank power and in return,
he was to supply me
with fear mongering magical creatures
to terrorize people into giving up
their souls.
Instead, he went behind my back
and built some deranged zoo.
He betrayed me
because of you.
- No.
- If you'd had just
stayed out of our way,
maybe your old man
would still be alive.
Nate, no wait!
Ray, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, man.
It's okay, buddy,
I know it wasn't you.
It's locked.
There's nothing to build.
No furniture to choose.
Dishes.
Piece of cake.
Go, go, go.
Yeah, this seems more like
one of your fantasies
than your fears,
watching me do dishes.
Please, if it were up to you,
we would only have paper plates.
Here.
You on that?
Got it.
I'm on it.
It never ends.
- Did you send it?
- Honestly, mate,
whatever happened to just
talking to someone?
Emoji's are way more fun
and if he's not that into it,
you can pretend like you were
talking about something else.
Right. Nate's gonna think I was dying
to tell him about a dancing lady
carrying a burning eggplant.
Here, use words.
It's erotic but vulnerable.
Okay, let me see it.
I'm not saying "bulge."
Sula the Wolf Witch talked
about smothering a demon.
Does that make sense to you?
When Mallus was a part of me
I could feel his fear.
He was vulnerable here on Earth.
It made him nervous.
So if we can separate the demon
from his earthly vessel,
it will suffocate him.
Just like a fish out of water.
Why are you even working
with that arrogant dick?
He'll never value your true power.
Not like I will.
You all right there, love?
Yeah.
I just need some coffee.
I'm fine.
And I'm sober.
Hey.
Are you okay?
I'm all right.
Thanks.
You best let her alone, Squire.
This is all your mail!
You deal with it.
It's not like you have an address
to even get mail, so...
We both talked about it and agreed
that now wasn't the right time for me
to move in with you.
- But we're making it work.
- Are we?
Because, how I see it we're living
completely separate lives, so...
Ava, I want this
just when the time is right.
Timing doesn't just happen, Sara.
Okay, you have to make a choice.
So what?
What? This... this is what you want?
No, of course nobody just wants
dirty dishes but, yes.
Ava, we are time traveling
superheroes.
Okay, fine. But I'm not just my job.
I want some hobbies.
I want... I want a life with you
And sometimes life is... is...
just this, okay?
It's boring.
What then?
You hop to the next adventure?
No, but I can't just aside
every single moment of forever
right this instant.
So, please just...
Tell me what you want me to say
and I'll say it when we get out
of here.
I can't tell you what to say Sara
because that wouldn't mean anything.
Okay, well...
Let's just... let's go
to the suburbs
and we'll just recycle until we die.
Can we go now?
Oh, no.
It's just me.
Let's talk.
I've admired your...
power for a long time, Nora.
I don't take compliments from people
who frame me for murder.
All in the interest
of self-preservation.
You understand.
Do they even know
what you're capable of?
They have no idea.
Then why waste your time
with that arrogant bastard
and his pathetic delusion
that the world needs him to save it?
When I met John, I was just a kid.
He was kind.
Mallus wanted me, but I wasn't ready.
But I'll tell you this.
John did everything he could
to save me.
But when he failed, he abandoned me.
John knew what the Order were doing
to me and he just let them.
And he's the one who decides
who to send to hell.
Cocky cowboy wearing his hangover
like a 10 gal hat.
He might have won that last battle,
but the war is mine.
My Tabitha will be free soon...
and when she is, we're gonna
put John away for good.
Tabitha?
That's why you needed Ava
as a vessel.
There's a model for everyone.
Are you looking for one to clean?
One to keep you safe?
One to please you?
No, you creep.
I'm looking for Ava.
They're all Ava.
No, they're not.
Just remember, pick quickly.
Tabitha will be here soon
and once she's here...
Oh, no.
Once she's here, what?
Attention, the store will be closing
in five minutes.
I can't believe I got my dad killed.
No, it was Hank's choice
to make a deal with a demon.
That is not your fault.
You spending time with him
inspired him.
Made him happy.
I don't think you doomed him.
I think you saved him.
Here's to the man you helped
your dad become.
You know what, Ray?
You're right. I shouldn't be
embarrassed, I should be proud.
Yeah, my dad was a little wacky,
but most of the good ones are.
He was a Legend and he should be
remembered that way.
Mikey T!
I got to stop him.
Sara will never let you take Ava.
If not her, I'll find someone else.
You know,
I can bring back other people.
Damien misses you so much.
- You can bring my father...
- Of course.
Now be a lamb and let me out,
Nora, doll.
You know, you can't just walk out
of here.
Constantine will never let you
do that.
Maybe as Desmond.
But if you let me in,
you, with my power?
Nobody could stop us.
The monitors were wonky.
Are you all right?
Of course.
You shut them down.
I should have never trusted you.
Shut up, John.
Attention, the store will be closing
in two minutes.
Where is she?
None of these are Ava.
I'm not leaving without her!
Ava.
But you could have chosen
any one of those other women.
I don't want other women.
But I'm...
Hey.
You did it.
No.
We did it.
Let's do this.
Nora.
Now!
Vessel, what a pretty word
for victim.
Oh, I don't need your power, Neron.
I have my own.
We've got him.
Oh, just a few minutes more.
Nora!
Ray, no!
Guys, guys, guys.
Hey, hey, hey.
It's okay. It's okay, mate.
It's all right.
Where am I?
You're safe.
Nora?
Eggplant's a little obvious.
I say you go with mushroom.
Mushroom...
Ava! You're back from the dead.
- I knew you'd do it, Captain.
- Gently.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Oh, nice job, boss.
Okay, serious,
- which emoji's like...
- All right, enough with the emoji.
- Hey!
- Just... just leave while you can.
You should just...
-Okay.
-Maybe...
You know, we should probably talk
about whether or not we want kids.
Let's wait until the other eight
are old enough to handle the news.
I don't even know
what this text means anymore.
"You up? Hot dog, donut, thumbs up."
Well, you wanna snog him, yeah?
Or do you want him to get diabetes?
Okay, this doesn't sound
like me at all.
You like him and he likes you,
just tell him that.
Okay.
"Want to go out sometime...
On a date"?
Oh, yes. See? That wasn't so bad.
Now, it's all on Nate.
Oh, God.
Oh, God, what did I do?
Mikey, pick up. Mikey, pick up.
Yeah, you can just drop that down.
You're not gonna need it.
No. Mikey, no!
Mikey!
Mikey, stop!
Zari?
Is that you, And Son?
I changed my mind.
What are you doing?
You should have just called.
Jeez.
I knew I should have synced
to the stupid cloud.
Nate.
- Hey.
- Hi.
So about...
About that text.
Oh, yeah.
My phone had an unfortunate run in
with a wrecking ball, so...
Oh, my God.
That sucks.
What'd you wanna talk about?
I just wanted to let you know that
Sara and Ava, they're good.
- That's great!
- Yeah.
Anything else you wanna talk about?
No, no, not that I can think of.
Okay. Cool, cool, cool.
- Glah... yeah, bye.
- Bye.
Zari.
Bye.
Hello?
Is there anyone here who can call me
a cab?
Anything you need, mate.
I can get you a flight
to New Orleans,
anywhere in the world, you name it.
No.
I don't want anything from you.
I'm not asking for forgiveness, Des.
Good.
Just wait, wait, Des.
You saved me, Johnny.
I'm grateful for that.
But it doesn't change anything.
I know.
You know I can make it
all go away, Des.
This will make you forget.
No.
You sent me to hell.
That's something we're both
gonna have to live with.
How's she holding up, old son?
She's stable, but unresponsive.
Well, that's better
than the alternative.
I couldn't let her get hurt again.
Oh, yeah, well, you just rolled
straight in there
like a knight in shining armor
and nearly got her killed.
I didn't mean to.
Yeah, I know.
She's a brave lass,
nearly cost her her life.
But she killed that bloody demon.
She's amazing.
We'll get you out of this one, Nora.
I'm not gonna abandon you again.
It's okay, boy.
Dogs usually love me.