[Mona] Previously on
Legends Of Tomorrow...
[Sara] Hello, John.
You opened a door, love. And Mallus
wasn't the only thing that got out.
Now, there's magic.
The damage that these supernatural
fugitives can cause is unfathomable.
- How much money do you need?
- $4.2 billion a year.
Done.
[Hank] I'm gonna green light
additional funding
to fast track the completion
of your containment facility.
Hi. I'm your magical caretaker.
Your creature handler, she's great.
- Mona.
- Konane.
[Mona] Did someone hurt you?
[Hank] These creatures are controllable.
Project Hades is go.
Stop! Where are you taking him?
[alarm blaring]
Oh, thank God you're back.
What is going on?
Long story. Lots of twists and turns.
- Some dramatic irony.
- Cliff notes, Gary.
- The Kaupe is out.
- [Hank] Director Sharpe.
Gary, take him down to lockup.
Aw!
What an adorable little puppet.
Eat my fuzzy dung, you dick!
Well, well, well.
Look who finally decided
to show up for work.
Nice of you to grace us
with your presence, Director Sharpe.
One of your employees
let a creature loose,
and then not surprisingly
got attacked by it.
Wait. Mona let him out?
Why would she...
I want that wolfman back in his cell,
or you're done.
And fire that girl.
Of all the days this could happen.
[Agent Sharpe] All right, everyone.
Screen all calls
to animal control and 911.
Pull CCTV from every corner
in a ten-mile radius.
- Let's go.
- [man] Yes, ma'am.
- Don't listen to him.
- Sara, he's right.
I never should've left Mona
in charge of those fugitives.
I should've been here, and instead,
I was off gallivanting like a...
Like a Legend?
Look, we're on this.
That Kaupe doesn't stand a chance.
I'll fix this.
- Our potty mouth puppet is locked up.
- Wonderful.
Because I've got
another job for you, Gary.
But you're not gonna like it.
[groans]
[gasps]
Ow!
[Mona] Mom? Dad?
What's going on?
You were in a cycling accident.
[speaking Mandarin]
[in English] I wasn't on a bike.
I was scratched by...
Konane, let go!
[groans]
[stammers]
Oh, no. He's out there alone.
Who?
I can't talk about it.
It's work-related. Top secret.
[speaking Mandarin]
[in English] We have failed as parents.
It's all your fault.
[Mona speaking Mandarin]
[in English] Gary.
Oh, my God. I'm happy to see you.
My parents won't believe
what I really do for work.
Oh, you mean betraying the people
that gave you a chance?
Ava believed in you
and you let her down.
You let us all down.
Gary, what are you talking about?
You released a dangerous beast,
and now, he's out there running free.
Wait. You think I let the Kaupe out?
It was the men in black.
- Didn't you see the bodies?
- No.
There was only footage of you
letting the hairy hunk man out.
Now, there's me telling you...
You're fired.
You can't fire me.
I swear there were two men who came
for Konane, but he killed them.
Sorry, Mona.
I really liked you, you know,
and I know it hurts now,
but in a few seconds
you won't remember a thing.
Don't you dare. I need my mind!
You do not have clearance
to handle this device.
You can't take my memories!
What was I doing here?
You're here to give me your jacket.
[scoffs]
Right, right, right.
And also, you were gonna
give me your time courier.
Oh, yeah.
Now, take my place,
it's almost lunchtime.
Oh...
Ooh!
Jell-O.
[rustling]
I know you're there.
Stop following me,
or I'll turn your brain into pudding!
Konane?
You're alive.
I was so worried they'd find you.
Don't worry about that.
I know you didn't mean to hurt me.
- [tires screeching]
- [growls]
It's them! Run!
I won't let them get you.
I'll close this behind you,
so, they won't be able to follow.
- Mona.
- I have to keep you safe. Go!
- [grunts]
- Mona! Mona.
You're safe. We're the good guys.
Oh, yeah? Who sent you?
Was it the Bureau,
or the men in black?
Where is the wolfman?
He's gone. It's too late.
You'll never find him because
I don't even know where he went.
So, grill me all you want. You...
[gasps]
[thuds]
What kind of gun is this?
Did you just try to
"shoot her" shoot her?
Any hits?
I tried to isolate the portal
from today's courier activity
- but so far, no dice.
- [sighs]
It would help
if I had the actual courier.
Sure. Here you go.
Okay, never mind.
So, we have a vicious monster
on the loose,
and no idea
where it might have disappeared to.
He's not a vicious monster.
People just assume that
because of the way he looks.
- He's a demigod. He used to be a king.
- [cocks gun]
Hey, what are you doing?
Seeing if this thing
works on her mouth.
Or how about we just give our guest
the dignity of hearing her story first.
[grunts]
I'm telling you.
The men in black are behind all of this.
They're framing me, so, they can
keep hurting the magical creatures.
Hurting them how?
I don't know, but Konane was
terrified when they came for him.
I was just trying to help him.
Mona, we saw
the security footage and...
There were no men in black, just you.
Well, they must have altered
the footage to hide the truth.
I'm like Mulder,
and those guys are the shadow
government covering their tracks.
It's a conspiracy.
The truth is out there!
Okay, Fox, okay, Fox! Take a breath!
We believe you.
Right, Sara?
Yes. We do.
And we're gonna
get to the bottom of this,
but first, we need to find the Kaupe
before he hurts himself.
Can you help us do that?
So, I'll head to the Bureau
and do some digging?
What? No.
I need you on the hunt
for that monster.
- But you said...
- Exactly what I needed to say.
That girl is clearly bonkers,
but the Kaupe trusts her
and we need her as bait.
What if she's not crazy?
What if there really is
a cover-up at the Bureau?
Then Ava would know about it
and she wouldn't allow it.
[Gideon] Captain, I have found
a lead on our missing Kaupe.
In Mexico City, 1961,
an unidentified drug cartel
member was found dead,
apparently, the work of a wild animal
non-indigenous to the region.
That must be him.
All right, fine.
Do some digging through the footage,
but keep your head down.
- We don't wanna raise any red flags.
- Got it.
Gideon, rally the troops.
We are going to Mexico.
I'm picking up
a magical signature this way.
As far as hiding places go, smack
bang in the center of a major city
would not be my top choice.
What is this place?
[crowd cheering]
It sounds like a real party.
As long as there's beer.
The detector must be wrong.
There's no way Konane
could hide in a place like this.
Are you sure about that?
"El Lobo." The Kaupe isn't hiding.
He is the main event.
[crowd cheering]
Ooh!
[Charlie on comms] Blimey.
How'd our hairy friend end up
with that lot?
It doesn't surprise me in the slightest.
Lucha libre wrestling is all about
character and charisma.
The modern day morality play.
Good versus evil.
The people versus the man.
Well, according to
the altered historical record,
El Lobo arrived on the scene
six months ago
and quickly rose to the top.
The mystery surrounding
his true identity
inspired novels, movies and TV shows.
Oh, bollocks. This is the one
that I get sidelined for?
All right, let's split up.
Ray and Charlie stay on the comms,
John and I will cover the arena.
You guys watch from the stands.
[announcer speaking Spanish]
[in English] Tonight, you will witness
a spectacular match,
one that you will tell your
grandchildren of in vivid detail.
- [all cheering]
- [bell dings]
[Constantine speaking Spanish]
[Sara in English] Hey, we're working.
We can't afford any screw-ups
on this one.
We gotta bag this guy quick.
Gotta stay sharp, you mean.
[announcer speaking Spanish]
- [yelling]
- [bell dinging]
[crowd booing]
[in English] Oh, chillax, love.
El Lobo ain't going nowhere.
It's true.
He's impossible to get rid of.
I tried over and over. He won't go away.
Hold the bloody phone.
Are you El Cura?
[Sara] You know this guy?
Anyone who knows anything
about Mexican culture knows El Cura
the legendary luchador
and movie star.
No.
You know, I loved
your monster movies, mate.
Whoever wrote those gems
had a better handle on magic
than any of those tosspots
up in Hollywood.
I haven't been in any movies,
mi amigo.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, what's all this?
You're the warrior of piety
and goodness.
You don't drink,
not that I'm one to judge.
I didn't.
Until this hairy tonto showed up
and stole everything from me.
And finally, the man... No,
the legend you have
all come here to see...
You mean the thief.
...the undefeated champion.
The hero of the people!
El Lobo!
- [howling]
- [entrance music playing]
[crowd cheering]
[announcer speaking Spanish]
[crowd whistling]
[growling]
[in English] We don't have eyes
on the Kaupe. He's lying low.
I need this wrapped up
before tonight, Nathaniel.
I can't have it hanging
over my head during the benefit.
It's going to be fine.
You guys have been
throwing this fundraiser
since the first Bush administration.
Oh, is that Nathaniel?
Yes, dear. But this is a work matter.
- Yes, I need...
- I...
Please. Thank you. Thank you.
Hello, sweetie.
So, don't forget the benefit is tonight.
Mom, I don't know
if I'm gonna make it this year.
I have a work emergency.
- Work can wait. Right, Hank?
- No.
Yeah, your father is nodding.
Okay, darling. See you here at 7:00.
[kisses] Bye.
I... No...
- [exhales]
- The lilies go on the stage...
- [bell dings]
- [both grunting]
[bell dings]
Damn, he's good.
He's too good.
In lucha libre,
every match tells a story.
Sometimes you win, sometimes you lose,
so you can rise again.
But there are rules. There is a plan.
With this guy, there's no rules,
there's no plan.
He just wins every time.
So, that's why you're here, eh,
drowning your sorrows,
rather than being up there
where you belong.
Listen, mate. I've had my fair share
of defeats these past days,
but lying on your ass,
it's no way to get your mojo back.
[crowd counting in Spanish]
- [bell dings]
- [howling]
[crowd cheering]
Look at him.
This is what he's always wanted.
To be worshipped and admired
like the demigod he is.
Not feared and shunned
like some monster.
He better make the most of it.
The second he gets backstage,
it's lights out
and back to the Time Bureau.
That wasn't the plan.
He can't go back to the Time Bureau.
- It's not safe.
- Not my call. Don't care.
[gasps]
[sighs] Oh, good, it's just you.
What are you doing here?
I was digging.
Mona claims the footage
you saw earlier was doctored.
That there's a cover-up
around the creature's escape.
And you believe this tiny cuckoo?
Maybe you should, too.
According to these deleted access logs,
security footage
was removed and replaced
earlier this morning
from a wireless device.
Now all I have to do is figure out
who that phone number belongs to.
You don't have to. I know the number.
It belongs to my dad.
[wrestling bell dings]
- [crowd cheering]
- El Lobo triumphs again!
[Sara] Okay, Mona.
Make sure he sees you as he leaves
the ring, then bring him backstage,
and we'll meet you there.
Konane!
El Lobo! You thief!
- You cheat!
- [growling]
You have disgraced this ring.
You have stolen victories
from too many of us.
And I'm going to put a stop to it.
I challenge you
to a lucha de apuestas!
[all murmuring]
The loser will take off his mask
and forfeit and never set foot
in the ring ever again.
[growling]
You heard it here,
ladies and gentleman.
The gauntlet has been thrown.
Do you accept this match
and its conditions, señor?
[all cheering]
Then the fight is on!
Tomorrow night. Same time, same place.
This will be one for the history books.
Get your tickets now!
So, he's back on track,
historically-speaking.
Now, how's that
for a bang-up job, Lancey?
- Excuse me. Coming through.
- Hey, get back here.
What is going on?
Out of my way, fanboys. Get out!
[groans]
Damn it!
Mona's gonna get herself trampled.
[snarling]
You can say what you will,
but that Kaupe,
he's a real gent in my book.
So, this is where you've been living.
Wow! [chuckles]
I like what you've done with the place.
It's, um... It's homey.
It's like you're back on the island.
You miss Hawaii, don't you?
Home.
You miss home?
Mona home.
Do I miss home?
Eh, you know.
Guilt-tripping parents, lack of a job.
No one who understands me.
Wow, that's beautiful.
[both laughing]
Mona.
There has to be a logical reason
why Hank replaced the footage.
So, let's think about it.
Look, I get that you
and your dad are in a good place
for the first time in a while,
but we just can't ignore
that this is happening.
But can we please reserve judgement
until we see the footage?
Sure, uh, the original footage
can only be restored
from the device used to delete it.
- You mean my dad's phone?
- Yeah.
We gotta go for it tonight.
He's gonna be distracted.
He's gonna be boozing and schmoozing
at the benefit gala.
[snaps fingers]
I have a plus one. Are you in?
Yeah. Okay.
Uh... As long as
we don't have to do that thing
where we act like we're dating.
You and I dating would be totally weird.
Totally weird. Yeah.
Um...
Text me the details
and I will meet you there.
Yeah.
Bye.
I must be really hungry because
that actually looks kind of good.
[sniffing]
[Mona] What is it?
[growling]
Where is he, Mona?
He's gone. You scared him off.
We just want to make sure
he doesn't hurt anyone, love.
He isn't like that.
He's sweet and gentle.
He won't hurt any...
[grunts]
[grunting]
Eat this, you furball.
[Mona] Konane, stop!
[growling]
- [gunshot]
- [gasps]
You got one messed-up
definition of sweet.
[door opens]
[Sara] Hey, Gideon said you...
Wow.
- You got a date?
- No. It's not a date.
I am dressed like this
because the footage
you saw at the Bureau earlier,
was definitely altered. By Hank.
Okay, before I do the math on this,
are you sure?
Yeah, Mona was telling the truth.
There is a cover-up at the Bureau.
What are the chances
that Ava's wrapped up in this?
Honestly, I don't know yet,
but if she's not a part of it then...
She's probably in a lot of danger.
[elevator bell dings]
Gary!
Close that hospital gown,
or I will report you to HR.
Where the hell have you been all day?
I don't know who I am.
I don't know why anything is things.
I don't know where my nipple went.
Where is my nipple?
- Where is my nipple?
- Gary.
[growling]
He was so scared.
I had to do something to stop them.
- Where were they taking him?
- Somewhere terrible.
That's why he can't
go back to the Bureau.
The men in black are gonna
hurt him again or worse.
Well, he can't stay in Mexico.
So, take him back home.
Back to ancient Hawaii,
to his old kingdom.
You saw him in the arena.
He's meant to be a king.
- Mona, it is not that simple.
- Why?
[Gideon] Captain, you're being
hailed by Director Sharpe.
That is why.
Gideon, I'll take it on the bridge.
[Gideon] I'm afraid she's overridden
my security protocols.
Ava! Wow, look at you.
- You look great.
- Yeah, thanks.
But listen, Sara, the situation
with the Kaupe has gotten much worse.
He now has an accomplice, Mona Wu.
Now, she may not look it,
but she is extremely dangerous.
She completely wiped Gary's mind.
- [chair creaks]
- [Sara] Um...
[chuckles]
Wait, you've had Mona in custody
this whole time and you didn't...
It's a long story, but I need
to explain to you in person.
This line might not be secure.
The line isn't secure, Sara,
what are you...
[growls]
You have the Kaupe, too?
Look, I can't explain right now.
Okay, then I'm sending
an extraction team.
Gideon, mask our location.
Sara, you need to bring in
that fugitive now.
I'm sorry.
Don't you dare hang up on...
[sighs]
Whoa!
Did you just hang up
on your girlfriend?
Mona, you better not be wrong
about this.
I need to go to that benefit,
so, I can talk to Ava face-to-face.
Before you leave, I have a petition
to become interim captain
of the Waverider in your absence.
I have a John Hancock from every
Legend except you.
It looks like you crossed out
part of Rory's signature.
Really?
The team is to keep a low profile.
Radio silence and absolutely
no time travel.
Captain Palmer has got it covered.
Interim captain.
[door opens]
[Ray] After your recent, unfortunate
misadventures in time travel,
I created a team-building card game
to help you learn the dos and don'ts
of our prior missions.
I'm calling it...
Fun way to learn
from your mistakes, right?
Oh, you got to be joking.
"Vandal Savage."
That's a real name.
And here's me thinking that
Damien Darhk's moniker
was a touch on the nose.
[Gideon] Sorry to interrupt,
but I'm detecting
a disturbance in the timeline.
- Yes!
- Oh, thank God. [sighs]
[Gideon] In the wake of
El Lobo's sudden disappearance
from the lucha libre scene,
rumors spread of government censorship.
Country-wide protests erupted
and dozens were killed
in the ensuing riots.
I'm sure we can figure
something out once Sara gets back.
In the meantime, it's game time.
- [both] Oh!
- Come off it.
I mean, weren't you just nattering on
about team-building experiences?
Well, let's go out there
and actually fix something.
[scoffs] Well, yeah,
but Sara said to stay put.
Oh, come on, Raymundo.
This isn't just important
for some dusty old history book.
This is important
for the people of Mexico.
All we need to do is make sure
that the luchas de apuesta
fight goes on.
And make sure that El Cura
comes out on top.
- Grand finale.
- Yeah.
- Oh, come on, Rage.
- Come on, Rage.
Let's give the people what they want.
Let's give 'em what they need.
[yells]
Let's prepare ourselves to wrestle!
Or we could just go.
- [classical music playing]
- [guests chattering]
Why throw such a big fancy party
if you're only going to have
tiny, little treats?
Nathaniel, darling.
Hello. Yes.
Is this your new girlfriend?
- Um, yeah. This is Zari.
- Mmm-hmm.
Zari. What a beautiful name
for a beautiful woman
- with excellent child-bearing hips.
- [coughs]
Not to put a clock on it or anything,
but grandchildren would be so lovely.
Anyhoo, I'd better go make sure
everything is good
with your father's speech.
Oh, my God. That went well.
Are you...
Are you blushing right now?
No, shut up. Take my toothpick.
Stay on task.
We are here to get your dad's phone.
That's it.
[tango music playing]
You better have a damn good reason
for hanging up on me.
Where is the Kaupe
and why isn't he in Bureau custody?
- What are you doing?
- Making sure we're not overheard.
By who?
Sara, my ass is already on the line.
Feeling me up in front of my boss
is not a good idea right now.
- He didn't plant anything on you.
- What?
That's good.
Please tell me that nutcase Mona
hasn't gotten to you.
Just dance.
I think Mona was onto something
about secret agents trying
to infiltrate the Bureau.
That is insane.
- Sara...
- Just listen to me.
The security footage was altered
and I think Mona was framed.
Even if that was true, which I doubt,
you are still harboring a fugitive.
- Ava...
- Hand him over now.
We can deal with the rest of this later.
You know
I can't do that.
Then this conversation is over.
[groans]
Hey, could you help me out, amigo?
I think I might be stuck.
It's time to whip you back
into fighting shape, eh, mate?
Okay, you need to shake off
that ring rust
by tomorrow night, so, that you can win.
What the hell is he doing here?
- [growls]
- Whoa! Be nice. Be nice.
Look, just as you're here
to practice winning,
he's here to practice losing, all right?
I don't trust him.
He's never done choreography.
For the people to accept me
as their hero again,
my victory must be absolute.
Well, you'd better get to work then,
hadn't you?
[upbeat Mexican music playing]
Gentle, El Lobo, gentle.
[groans]
- [both cheering]
- That's what I'm talking about, El Cura.
You think he could still pull off
his finishing move?
Sure, muscle memory will kick in.
[El Cura groans]
Konane!
[howling]
[El Cura groaning]
You can't train the mutt.
[Mona] Konane.
I know you don't like losing,
but it doesn't make you
any less of a king.
In fact, it makes you a hero.
Like Buck,
in my favorite Rebecca Silver book.
Wait, wait, wait.
Where Buck crash lands
on Garima's home planet
and then is forced into mortal combat.
That one?
Yeah, you've read it?
Heard of it.
Konane... [speaking native language]
[growling]
Buck loved Garima,
and he didn't wanna hurt her sister.
So, he threw the contest
and the two star-crossed lovers
escaped into the night.
If you lose tomorrow,
me and you can escape, too.
I'll take you back to Hawaii.
We can make a life together
just like Buck and Garima.
[grunts]
Let's clear out.
Ava.
Where are you going?
Mexico City, 1961.
What, you didn't think I'd find out?
The Bureau is running just fine, Sara,
and we will catch that damn Kaupe.
[sighs]
On behalf of
the American Hemophilia Foundation,
I am honored to introduce
tonight's recipient
of the Altruistic Angel Award,
- Henry Heywood.
- [guests applauding]
Hey, Pops, Pops, Pops.
How about a quick pic?
You know, for Facebooks or whatever
you old people overshare on.
- Come on, Mom.
- Yep.
- Okay, say "grandbabies."
- [camera clicking]
Damn it, Ray. What happened
to keeping a low profile?
It's a long story,
but this fight must happen
in order to protect history,
so, just trust us, okay?
All right, so entering through
the north and south wings
is the best chance of catching
the Legends off guard.
- If you...
- Oh...
Uh... Should I transfer
to your private line in case it's,
- you know... Bom chica wow-wow...
- Gary, move.
Ava, I know you're mad,
but can we please just talk
about this like adults
before doing something rash.
I will put a stop to that fight.
Sara, now is not the time
for one of your crazy
fly-by-the-seat-of-your-pants plans.
Hand over the fugitive
before someone gets hurt.
I know this sounds crazy,
but there is no way around it.
Letting the Kaupe wrestle
is important to Mexico's history.
No, allowing
an escaped fugitive to fight
is endangering all of history.
Extraction team, move out.
[announcer] Introducing the fallen hero.
Once beloved, now disgraced,
a man clawing for a comeback,
El Cura!
- [entrance music playing]
- [crowd booing]
El Cura! El Cura!
They're fairweather fans, mate.
Don't worry, you'll prove them wrong.
[announcer] And now,
the man you are all here to see,
the undefeated champion of the people,
El Lobo!
- [entrance music playing]
- [crowd cheering]
[growling]
Bring it in, gentlemen.
Now, I want a good, clean fight.
No biting, no scratching.
Nothing below the belt.
All right, to your corners.
[Hank]
The strongest of us will never know
what it's like to live
with this disorder.
- And that's why I called my work...
- [beeps]
Okay, moment of truth.
[Hank] Because victory is possible.
In fact, it's inevitable.
I don't accept this
Altruistic Angel Award for myself
as some pat on the back.
I receive it as a call to arms.
Let's all come together
and end this fight.
- [groans]
- Oh!
All right, take it easy, remember?
Come on, shake it off, mate,
shake it off.
Look, I know you feel like throwing
in the towel right now, but trust me,
there's nothing people like more
than a good comeback. Now go.
[growling]
[all cheering]
You're losing so good. Keep it up.
Play dead, furball.
[El Cura yells]
[all cheering]
[bell dings]
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is an emergency evacuation.
Please exit the building
in an orderly fashion.
We have some
uninvited guests here, Sara.
Give them hell. That's an order.
No outside interference.
Finally, a real fight!
[Mexican music playing]
[all cheering]
These fools are trying to censor us.
But we ain't gonna stand
for that, are we?
On your left, mate.
Nice one, Raymundo.
Now, El Cura and his mates
they fight for the people.
The people!
Now, this is what I call
a bloody good show.
[Charlie] He didn't abandon you!
Have a towel, mate.
So, don't you dare abandon him!
- [groans]
- Whoa!
Come on!
[El Cura yelling]
Yeah!
- [all cheering]
- [bell dings]
Yeah! Yeah!
[all chanting]
Cura!
[crowd chanting] Cura! Cura! Cura!
I reckon we should team-build
like this more often, Legends.
[sighs]
Well, looks like you've saved
history again.
Congratulations, Sara.
- Ava, just let me explain...
- No need.
It's all very clear to me.
Ava, please don't hang up...
On me.
Some night, huh?
We just raised over $500,000.
Roaring success.
I saw the footage, Hank.
The real footage.
Nathaniel, it was you who convinced
me to fund the Bureau.
Don't...
Please don't remind me.
I went out on a limb for you.
I need you to trust me on this.
There's a purpose to what you saw.
Of course, I trust you.
I just need you to bring me in
on these sort of things.
- In due time, son.
- [cell phone ringing]
I got to take this.
Yeah.
You cloned all the data
off that phone, right?
Uh-huh.
Good.
Keep digging.
I wanna know everything.
What do you mean
you couldn't capture the asset?
[agent] Blame it on your son's
time-traveling pals, sir.
How would you like us to proceed?
[both laughing]
Kid, come here.
[Mick exhales deeply]
There's something about Buck
and Garima you should know.
They didn't live happily ever after.
They came from two different worlds.
Worlds that needed them.
They didn't belong together,
but they loved one another...
A lot.
How do you know?
The next book in the series
hasn't even been published yet.
I just do!
Here.
Don't do anything stupid.
I'm gonna take a leak.
I brought snickerdoodles.
I'll just, um, put them here.
[sighs]
Ava, look, I'm sorry.
I didn't come here to fight.
I know things got ugly between us today,
but I just wanna put it behind us.
I needed one thing
from you today, Sara.
For you to be in my corner.
That's all I asked.
Well, I'm here now.
Well, that's great.
Just in time for my meeting with Hank,
where I'll probably be fired,
thanks to you.
Ava, Hank is the real problem here.
I mean, he's been
torturing prisoners off-site...
Who cares?
A few weeks ago, the Legends
were sending them to hell.
I mean, since when
is protecting magical creatures,
things that shouldn't even be
in our world in the first place,
more important than protecting me?
And when have you become so callous
about the prisoners in your care?
My priority is to protect history, Sara.
Human history.
If Hank has to experiment
on a few creatures
to try to find a better way
to fight them, then so be it.
Ava, you do not believe that.
Come on, I know you.
You're not like Hank.
Look, this is your Bureau
and he's doing
something twisted with it.
You don't understand
how any of this works.
No, Hank is the reason
that this Bureau is here.
If we piss him off, it all goes away.
Think of how many people,
how many human people
- would get hurt if that happened.
- Well, he can't shut us down.
Oh, my God!
Sara, everything is not about you.
Do you understand you're asking me
to risk everything?
For what? For some conspiracy theory?
For a bunch of monsters? I'd...
For me.
Well, I've already given you
everything I have to give. So...
Today, I asked you for one thing.
Ava, don't do this.
Just go.
I'm done.
[door closes]
[crying]
Well, Konane,
it's time for our new adventure.
Konane, I, uh...
I can't.
I wanna live in your world.
I mean, look at it.
It's beautiful.
But I don't belong there.
[grunting]
If I went, I'd just be
running away from my world,
and that's not the right reason
to leave everything behind.
- [gunshot]
- [groans]
- You murdered him.
- Step away from the creature, miss.
No.
- I said step away.
- [crying]
You murdered him!
[growling]
[growling continues]
[agent screaming]
What the...
You were right.
There's no such thing
as happily ever after.
[theme music playing]