So, there are aliens
scattered throughout history.
Oh...
And on our windshield.
No, no, no!
- Rory, that was a lead.
- Yikes!
That alien could have told us something
about Sara's whereabouts.
No, girl, that alien is dead.
We don't know that.
We actually don't know
anything about these creatures.
Hey, some species could survive
head-on collisions.
With a spaceship?
- Going thousands of miles an hour?
- Stop.
Spooner, are you getting any readings?
It's dead.
But the face-sucking squid beasts
in those other pods
just got dumped into the river of time.
- Fantastic.
- Sounds like more unpaid labor to me.
Okay, so every single one of those
aliens was on the ship with Sara,
which means
we just have to find one of them,
and it should lead us back to my girl.
- Right?
- Your fiancée.
Right.
- Gidget, please find us some aliens.
- Please.
Actually, Ms. Tarazi,
it appears we already have a bite,
so to speak.
Where?
Okay, Gideon. What have we got?
October 10, 1955,
San Bernardino, California.
A town known as
the birthplace of fast food.
And ergo the death
of the great American eatery.
Before fast food,
mom-and-pop burger joints
were the beating heart of every town.
Funny you should mention it,
Mr. Tarazi.
The anomaly seems to have started
at Big Bang Burger,
owned by local businessman Bert Beeman.
And within 24 hours, San Bernardino went
from bustling suburban enclave to...
- Oh.
- Whoa.
The entire population was
killed overnight, leaving no survivors.
Historians dubbed it
the "Massacre on Main Street."
No, I would've gone with
"Suburban Slaughter."
Save it for the podcast.
This is good news.
Y'all are dark.
We go back, stop the alien
and it can tell us how to find Sara.
- Okay, so...
- And what exactly is the plan here?
Oh, the...
Well, you're the plan.
So you're going to
help us find the alien
and then you're gonna get it
to tell us where Sara is.
No way.
I'm only staying on this ship till
you guys get this thing out of my head.
That was the deal.
Apologies, Ms. Cruz,
but that won't be possible.
What?
I was going to tell you before
the whole, you know... alien pods thing.
Gideon didn't find anything to remove.
I'm sorry.
So first you kidnapped me,
then you lied.
Take me home, now.
Look, I'm really sorry,
but I can't do that.
I need you to talk to the alien.
This thing's not going
to give us directions
to find your girlfriend,
it's gonna kill us.
You're amongst
board-certified superheroes.
You don't have to worry
about getting killed.
They took your captain.
If you guys are so super,
then why didn't you just stop them...
Listen to me. I need you
to help us find Sara, okay?
After you do that, I will take you
wherever the hell you want to go.
Oh, look at those perfect patties.
Get 'em out while they're hot!
And don't forget...
Service with a smile.
We've got another one at the window.
Let's go! Let's go! Keep it moving.
We got a lot of mouths to feed.
Welcome to Big Bang Burger.
Try our new cosmic mushroom burger.
What, you think aliens are funny?
It's a paycheck.
The goal is to blend.
You picking up any alien signals?
Mmm-mmm.
Guys. Hey, split up, mingle.
Find out if anyone's seen anything
that could lead us to the alien.
And Sara...
Sara.
Are you okay?
We just crash-landed
on an alien spaceship.
No, Gary, I'm not okay.
Oh, boy, that's not good.
What did Alien Gideon say?
Uh... It's a little hard to translate
exactly since in my language,
there over 70 ways
to say, "explode from the inside."
The general idea is
we lost all our fuel when we crashed.
Whoa.
Where are we?
We were on course to land on Pliny X19.
But Kayla didn't give me
any other details.
Well, I thought she's
supposed to be your fiancée.
Ex-fiancée...
and communication
wasn't our strong suit.
But I do know that we were hired
by some power hungry space lord
to gather the universe's
most dangerous creatures.
And now, we're on his planet.
It could be Hunger Games out there
or the air could be poisonous gas...
Okay, we need to find something
that could fuel this ship,
so we can get back home.
Or what if we send out a distress signal
and then wait
for the Legends to come find us?
And good news...
I've got my deck
of strong American women playing cards.
Ruth Bader Ginsburg, Dolores Huerta,
Representative Shirley Chisholm.
Of all the people to be stuck with...
What is that?
Dog?
A really cute dog.
Three moons, three moons.
Yeah, I could get behind that.
But a dog? That's weird.
But if the dog can breathe,
that means we can breathe.
And it's wearing a scarf.
Okay, Gary, resist the cuteness.
You've been fooled by dogs before.
Where you going?
I'm gonna follow that dog.
Pretty busy here today.
Anything special going on?
Oh, it's always busy.
The burgers are out of this world.
- What is that?
- Dragon ash.
It's my line
of herbal nootropic supplements
designed to enhance brain power,
sex appeal, sleep cycle, spirit...
Sounds like more fries for me.
Takes me back to my days
at Burger Herder.
Satisfying ache in my forearm
from a day flipping patties.
Of course, those patties
were organic and free-range.
The meat they used in 1955
often contained ingredients
which precluded it
from being called "beef."
Ew.
You know, I've been thinking, bro...
It is time for us to start
sharing the family heirloom.
So you can dry your hair faster?
Ha-ha. I helped defeat a god
or whatever that scary blonde lady was.
I'm officially a Legend.
Now all I need is my superpower.
Here. I made a schedule.
- Hey, hey...
- Whoa, whoa.
No one is more stoked than me
to discover your powers.
But the totem chose me.
No, you literally stole it.
Uh, debatable.
Guys, guys. Shut up.
I'm working here.
- I have an idea. Just go with it.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Pardon me, Officers. Hi.
We're just here on vacation,
and we were wondering
how safe is San Bernardino?
Safe as houses.
So no...
arson or robbery?
Or any
gruesome eviscerations?
There's a 459A
at Sal's Deli. Repeat, 459A.
Pass me a napkin?
A 459A?
- That sounds mighty serious.
- Yes.
Ma'am?
If you wanna stick your nose
in someone's business,
I suggest you start with your friend.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I need another burger.
Hey, you all right?
Did you hear something?
I can feel it.
- It's hungry.
- Focus.
Now where's it coming from, love?
Maybe... that way.
The feeling's getting stronger.
What about the waitress?
She has glasses like Gary.
You mean the alien
in a waitress flesh suit?
- Spooner, wait.
- Hey!
All right. What are you really?
Her disguise is good.
No, no, wait! Just...
I am so sorry,
my friend thought you were an...
Someone else.
I'm sorry.
What happened?
What's wrong with your powers?
Nothing.
I felt it.
That thing is nearby, believe me.
- I found the alien.
- Rory?
You stole a cop car?
Okay, where is it?
That 459A at the deli was followed up
by a 415 at the butcher's
and a 240 at the meat aisle
of the local grocery.
Alarm at the deli,
assault at the groceries
and disturbance at the butcher's.
This thing loves meat.
It must be how the massacres start.
Well, let's find it before it gets
the taste for another kind of flesh.
Hey, guys, we have a lead on the alien.
I need you to guard the burger joint.
Turns out we have a very hungry alien
with a taste for meat.
Already on it, Captain.
Guess who just got summer jobs!
Nice.
So glad you lot applied for the jobs.
Business is booming.
I never thought I'd get the chance
to man the grill again professionally.
I'm excited to see the master at work.
Burger buddies!
Size nine, right?
Seven and a half,
and I am not wearing those.
You're right.
We could use...
A handsome man out there.
It's you.
- Me? No...
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Let's get you on wheels.
Looks like it's time to teach you
the ways of the burger.
Let's go meet the meats.
How did I get here?
Don't you have any alien superpowers
that can find a dog?
Super smell or echolocation?
I'm not that kind of alien.
I'm not that different from you, really.
- Carbon-based. A few more... tentacles.
- And you eat people.
I come from a savage planet.
They killed for sport, ate their own.
The concept of oral hygiene
was completely unknown.
And I wasn't so much engaged to Kayla,
as traded to her, and then I was
sent to Earth to find you.
I never imagined
a place like that could exist.
Birthday parties, rose water...
Friends.
Friends?
I've known you for three years, and I'm
only now learning you're an alien.
I took some creative license
with the details.
You know, so I could fit in
just like Charlie.
Why me?
Well, I guess whoever's behind all this
has a thing for powerful women, too.
Lucky me.
Do we want to know where that came from?
Yeah, it's here.
Here, like before or...
Look, I spent my whole life
trying not to let aliens into my head.
And now to try to save your girlfriend,
I've got them all in there,
which is no freaking picnic.
I don't know how the hell that works,
but I know it does.
So back off.
We got something.
It's close.
Is that the Big Bang Burger mascot?
That's just a bloke
in an alien's costume.
Alien disguised as a human
disguised as an alien.
Wow, these things are good.
Kid, he's not an alien.
Would you stop pointing your gun at him?
Look?
You sure?
Because I never saw a man
so mad for meat.
And I grew up
along our nation's storied Buffet Belt.
All right, let's get him back to the
MedBay and see what we can find out.
- Hey!
- This...
stays with me
until after we talk to the alien.
Careful, careful.
On my planet, there are plants
that can literally liquefy you.
Also, ones that can sing. Which I guess
is besides the point, but...
Gary, what did I say about talking?
Well, I believe
your precise word was "don't," but...
I sensed nuance in your tone.
Huh.
I guess I'm not the only
intelligent life form on this planet.
Wait, wait.
We don't know what's in there.
It could be a priblintz,
which is kind of like a half-jaguar,
half-snake thing or an apteroc,
which is also half-jaguar,
half-snake, but...
Gary! It's not like I haven't
faced aliens before.
Oh.
Who the blazes are you?
Right back at you.
Wait.
Are you... human?
Not just any human.
It's the queen of diamonds.
Amelia Earhart.
Big fan.
Take in that smoke and hold it.
Relaxing those muscles,
releasing any tension...
Can you please stop talking to yourself?
I'm not talking to myself.
I'm talking to my burger.
Releasing any tension
and turning it into flavor.
Oh!
All right,
no sign of trouble out there.
However, I think my shorts
may be a little too short.
None of my customers are leaving.
Any heat in the kitchen?
Well, if we're looking
for people obsessed with meat,
we should probably lock up
the burger whisperer here.
With this spatula
comes a duty to transfer
our positive energy into this burger
and out to that town.
If these are the vibes you put into
your food, they're going to taste it.
And if these are the vibes
you bring to the mission,
the totem's gonna feel it.
Oh, I get it.
You're just looking for another excuse
to keep the totem to yourself.
I don't think it cares
about my meaningless burger job.
Meaningless?
The Burger Herder was where I started
to find real meaning in life.
The first place
where people cared about me.
Not 'cause I was
"Dragon Girl's brother,"
but because I was Behrad.
Okay, got it.
So, you're going to just keep
hogging the totem as payback
because you were jealous of me.
Super mature.
I wasn't jealous.
Are you even listening?
Just felt good
to have something of myself, okay?
Fine. Keep the totem.
You know what, keep the spatula, too.
I wouldn't want to ruin
anything else with my negative energy.
That's not what I...
It's me. Need that table six order.
Come on.
One dry,
naked single coming right up.
- Whip!
- Go, go.
Wait. Nate, don't serve that.
They'll taste my bad vibes.
The scan confirms
the subject's biology is 100% human.
Look, his biology
might be human,
but I'm still feeling
strong alien vibes.
Well, if there is something in there,
the Divination of Hor
should do the trick.
It extracts all unwanted influences,
giving you facetime
with whatever's in him.
So you just...
rattle off this hooey
and magic stuff happens?
Yeah, that's right.
Don't finish that sentence.
Not unless you want
to summon a trickster prawn.
Yeah, I'd like to see a prawn
get one past me.
Let's get this over with.
All right.
Oh!
- That's some high-grade hooey.
- Wait a second.
I think I've seen this stuff before.
Is that Big Bang Burger's secret sauce?
Don't touch that.
- And definitely don't eat it.
- Why would I eat it?
That's the alien.
That's the alien?
You mean they're charging
25 cents extra to eat an alien?
That's kind of a bargain, really.
That's why I was
hearing it all over town.
Because everyone's got it in them.
Like an extra-terrestrial parasite.
Driving this town to eat itself alive.
Okay, so if that parasitic condiment
is the alien, fine,
then that means you can talk to it.
That's not how it works.
Will you just try?
Sara's one day closer to dead,
and your plan is to hunt mayo?
Thank you so much
for the constructive feedback, Mick.
It's very helpful.
Let me tell you honey
Why I love you so
Kiss me, baby, ooh!
Kiss me baby
Set my soul on fire
Kiss me, baby, ooh!
You're doing it! You're in the zone!
The people are loving your burgers, man!
I feel like I'm flying.
- Fly, B, fly!
- Spirit ash, do your work.
Guys, listen to me.
Can I take your order?
I need you to stop
serving those burgers,
bottle up all that secret sauce
and bring it back to the ship.
The sauce is the alien.
It's like a parasite.
It infects people
and makes them crave more meat.
And here I thought my short shorts
were selling burgers.
It's like that old movie, The Stuff,
except with aioli instead of ice cream.
Sorry, are you saying
that anyone who ate a burger
is gonna go super crazy now?
Copy that, Ava. We'll 86
the hockey pucks on the fly.
I think he means we're gonna
stop serving people alien goo.
Ew.
All right. Health code violation.
Come on, boys. You gotta go.
We don't have the permit
to serve food on roller skates.
Get! Get outta here!
So, you get the totem.
I get to take out the trash.
What is going on out here?
Where are my customers?
Why, you little...
You're stealing my secret sauce!
Bert, it's not what it looks like.
Who're you spying for?
It's those two brothers. The Mc...
Whatevers. I knew a chef as good as you
was too good to be true.
- Wow.
- It's an honor to hear that, boss.
But seriously, this sauce
is making people crazy.
Once they eat it,
they can't stop craving meat.
Son, that's called quality.
If you keep feeding people this,
they're going to die, Bert.
Well, people don't eat burgers
and fries to live longer.
Uh, you might want to...
Ugh.
More!
You believe us now, Bert?
This is the last of it?
Where do you even get this stuff?
- Answer him.
- Listen, I don't know.
My wife makes it.
It's her secret recipe.
She won't even tell me.
Ava, we got a problem.
We got all the sauce out of here,
but turns out,
there's a lot more of this stuff.
Bert says his wife
makes the sauce at their house.
Okay, well, if we find it all,
then Spooner should be able
to talk to it.
I'll head there now.
I still don't understand.
How did you end up here?
Well, Earhart's' interest in flying
began with a visit
to the Canadian National Exhibition.
Sorry. It's a fun fact.
I wish I had an answer for you.
Last thing I remember,
I was soaring over the Pacific.
Me and my navigator, Fred, almost done
our flight around the globe.
It was mission accomplished.
Then the left engine started sputtering,
the Canary bucked,
and I hit my head hard and blacked out.
When I woke up, Fred was gone,
and I was here.
And where is "here"?
I thought it was heaven or something,
but to tell you the truth,
I still don't know where we are exactly.
On the bright side, the food's good.
Hey, listen, I'm trying
to repair my aircraft.
Maybe you can take a look at it.
- It needs a fuel source...
- An aircraft?
But that means
that you can take me home.
Oh... Well, yeah.
I mean, I guess why not?
Let's do it. Let's go.
First, let me serve you.
Why let this meal go to waste?
It's been so long
since I've had any guests.
Uh...
Yeah, sure. Okay.
Hot dog!
I've been frightfully lonesome
since I've been here.
Yeah.
You two are lucky to have each other.
Oh, yeah.
This is the spot.
Let's go interrogate this thing.
I keep trying to tell you
that's not how it works.
I don't speak alien.
It's more like I can sense them,
know what they're feeling.
Know what they're feeling?
How is that supposed to get Sara back?
You're the one
that brought me here, jefa.
Why do you people listen to her?
She's gonna get you all killed.
Don't, mate...
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
It means you don't cross an alien
without losing something.
It means the longer you pretend
she's still out there,
that these things
will help you get her back,
the more you're gonna lose.
- Stop.
- She's gone.
And if you can get that in your head,
at least you can save yourself.
Shut up, Spooner.
Watch her, John.
Yeah.
- So you're with the police?
- Mmm-hmm.
Which officer are you married to?
Hmm? Oh...
Well, you probably haven't met him yet,
seeing as we just moved here and all.
But that's why I wanted
to introduce myself to you.
My, my, my.
What a lovely home you have here.
Is that an electric mixer?
It sure is.
I have heard about these.
Wow.
It's like I'm in the future.
It does everything...
Cakes, cookies.
You know, I just whipped up a batch.
You have to try them.
Oh... Oh!
No, I couldn't, I am stuffed.
I just had lunch at Big Bang Burger.
Talk about a welcome
to the neighborhood.
Well, isn't that something,
that's my husband's restaurant.
You don't say.
You know what makes
those burgers really special?
It's that secret sauce.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
And he was bragging to everyone
about how it's his wife's recipe.
It's true.
My little contribution
to the family business.
You have to tell me
how you came up with it.
What's your secret ingredient?
But I couldn't.
Oh, come on.
Just between us girls.
All right,
but what I'm about to say
cannot leave these walls.
To be honest, it's a little weird,
and I'm not too sure people
are ready for the truth.
I am all ears, no lips.
My secret ingredient?
It's rice vinegar.
From the East.
Wow!
- I know, exotic.
- Yes.
Well, I really should be
getting dinner started.
These eggs aren't gonna
devil themselves.
No, no.
Um...
I'll just see myself out.
Toodle-loo.
This better be the last of the alien
sauce or we will call the FDA.
All right. I've got Sandra set up
in the back office
with enough burgers to last her
through the night.
Meat!
Oh, no. Not the nice couple
from table six!
Get back!
Look alive, team.
The dinner rush is here.
What does that look like to you?
I don't know,
Mr. Beeman's midlife crisis?
No, not the car.
That weird bumpy box.
Anybody up here?
The alien's pod.
Wait...
I can read that.
Well, what does it say, squire?
"Giant air feeder."
And what the hell is that?
I don't know, but it sure
don't look like a sauce monster.
Yeah.
Good work.
Ava?
Just give me
a second, John.
Damn it!
Oh, my God.
I told you it does everything.
I won't let her take you from me.
I won't let her.
I knew you were
up to something.
Is your husband even a policeman?
Well, you see, my wife.
Well, she's my fiancée.
Technically, she hasn't asked me yet,
but I did say yes,
so I guess that makes us...
Never mind.
Sara, my friend.
She was abducted by aliens.
And that's exactly what that thing is.
It's an alien.
I have no idea which part of that
sentence makes the least sense.
I don't care what she is.
She's mine.
My little miracle.
She's the only thing
keeping our business alive.
Wait a minute.
You've been knowingly
serving your customers that slime?
At first I didn't know
where the stuff came from.
Last Wednesday,
I served Bert his favorite,
Salisbury steak,
when something from the ceiling
dripped onto his plate.
I tried to stop him,
but he tasted it and loved it.
He thought it was my recipe.
Bert's business had been failing,
and it was taking our marriage with it.
He was sure if we added
my secret sauce to the menu,
we could turn things around.
So I had to find out
where this sauce came from.
While Bert was asleep,
I came up here and discovered it.
This beautiful creature.
She'd found her way into our attic.
She was small back then.
And I knew the universe gave her to me
to save our marriage
and our family business.
Rhonda, I need you
to let me take it from here.
We're running out of time.
Look at it. It's growing.
It could take over the whole town.
Wait, you're right.
If she's growing, that means...
we could franchise.
Finally, the Beemans will get
the success they deserve.
We'll take over more than this town.
We'll put those brothers
out of business.
Big Bang Burger will be
a household name.
We'll be in every city, every state...
Oh!
Hate to see a small business
go down like that.
Spooner!
I am so glad
that you don't follow orders.
Well, looks like doomsday's
finally here,
and it's ordered the burger.
We need to calm these people down.
Wait, I have an idea.
Sleepytime dragon ash.
Even a small dose will calm
the most restless spirit.
Yeah, but how do we get them to eat it?
By giving the customer what they want.
I'll lace the burgers with dragon ash,
feed 'em to the horde.
Yes!
But I'll have to serve quick.
Behrad, wait. Let me help.
Zari, are you sure?
I learned from the best.
Today, you're not Dragon Girl's brother.
I'm Burger Boy's sister.
You're gonna need this.
So you're saying
this lady found a cocoon
oozing alien pus and thought,
"Let's put this on the menu"?
Yeah, you might not wanna look
at what's in fast food these days.
So if that's the alien,
then why is the sauce
driving everyone into a feeding frenzy?
When this thing pops,
she's gonna be hungry.
She's been fattening up the town
for her first meal.
The massacre.
I won't let you take this from me!
She's mine, all mine!
I won't let you destroy
our American dream!
We need to contain it.
I bet I know where it's going.
Four patties coming in hot!
Give 'em the works.
That would be four cows
buried in snow, RIP.
Pick up.
It worked.
They're falling asleep.
Burger buddies!
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, we found the alien.
Tell 'em we found the alien.
Yeah, it turns out the goo
isn't the alien.
It's a huge flying bug.
Like Mothra. Cool.
It has a taste
for human flesh,
and it is headed your way.
Well, that's less cool.
Guys...
I liked the alien better
when it was goo.
Damn it!
How are we supposed to get it down?
We need bait.
Oh, jeez.
Oh, shoo!
Shoo, you!
- Just what I need.
- Hey, get inside, you silly git!
Whoa!
You wanna take it back to the ship,
see if maybe I can talk to it?
Uh... Yeah. Light it up.
Whew!
I'm not gonna lie,
that was very satisfying.
Double-fisting?
I like your style.
Oh, I poured it for Sara.
It's just habit.
Hmm.
Hey, shouldn't let it go to waste.
I'm sorry I couldn't help you
find your lady.
Mmm. No.
Ava Sharpe does not give up that easily.
Listen, I owe you an apology.
I was so desperate for this alien
to be the answer to all my prayers
that I didn't even think about
how you'd be feeling about any of it.
No, I get it.
Sara's a lucky woman.
Thanks.
You know,
I know what it's like
to have people mess with you,
and it doesn't make you crazy.
Just makes you vigilant.
So what happened to you
when you were a kid?
Look, I don't really talk about...
My mom.
I don't know...
I don't know where they took us
or what they did to us.
But, you know, when I woke up,
she was gone.
- Maybe she's still...
- I had to stop thinking that way.
No hoping like that for that long.
That can drive you crazy.
And instead, I gave up everything,
preparing for the moment I'd get to blow
one of those things away.
You know, but now that I've done it,
I thought I'd feel something more.
Instead, I just got nothing left.
I mean, you've got us.
- You mean...
- If...
- If you'll stay.
- You want me to stay?
I almost killed a furry in the freezer.
We need to adjust
some of your tactics a little, but...
This thing in my head,
I don't know how to control it.
Well, we can help you learn.
This isn't the end
for either of us, so...
Yeah.
You're right. It isn't over.
There are still more aliens out there.
Exactly.
You can still find your girlfriend.
I know we will.
And that I just didn't shoot
enough of 'em.
Uh...
Wait, that's not...
All right.
I'm in.
We're gonna keep killing aliens until
you find Sara and I get some closure.
Yeah, that's not what...
Actually, that sounds
like a perfect plan.
Okay.
Well, thanks.
I loved being back behind the grill,
but my pores did not.
Time to cleanse.
In the wake
of what has been called
the deadliest butterfly attack
on record,
we have a little bit of good news.
After the death of the owner
of Big Bang Burger,
head waitress Sandy Sledge has decided
to re-open the beloved diner
under a new name.
Yes, girl boss.
I hope she turned it into a juice place.
It's belly, belly good!
She did not.
Hey, Z, about before,
you were right.
I've been selfish
about this whole totem thing.
And a little patriarchal.
It would be my privilege
to share it with you.
No, I need to respect your boundaries.
The totem is your thing. I get that.
It's a Tarazi family heirloom.
It only makes sense that we both use it.
There is no shortage of ways
for me to be super.
I don't need to take away your power
to harness my own.
Listen, you've given me
a new life, new friends.
I can't take this away from you.
It's already yours, Z.
The totem chose both of us.
Then I chose
to give it back to you, B.
But think of all the ways
you could use your wind powers
to help the team.
You know, I've been thinking
of talking to Ava.
I could see myself in a more
managerial capacity on the ship.
I can't take this anymore.
Whoa!
It's split in two.
We're, like, really good at sharing.
Fearless flyer, fashion icon
and a great hostess.
I mean, is there anything she can't do?
- Yeah, and the stew was good.
- Yes.
Hope you like your coffee straight.
Yep.
You've really made a home
for yourself here.
And how did you get through
those first few nights?
Wish I had an answer for you.
The last thing I remember,
I was soaring over the Pacific.
Me and my navigator, Fred,
were almost done with our flight
around the globe.
It was mission accomplished.
What? Are you feeling okay?
Wish I had an answer for you.
Last thing I remember,
I was soaring over the Pacific.
Me and my navigator, Fred,
almost done with our flight
around the globe.
It was mission accomplished.
Then the left engine
started stuttering...
I have a bad feeling about this
and we need to go now.
Come on.
Where you going?
We were just heading back to the ship
because it's getting dark.
No!
You can't leave me here.
I need to go with you.
What?
I need to go home!
Sara, we need to go.
God!
I'm sorry. This is all my fault.
I swear I will do everything
in my power to get you home.
Ideally in time for a spring wedding,
although with your matching
Nordic complexions,
a winter wedding would be spectacular.
Gary.
You're not planning my wedding.
Ouch.
Okay.
A winter wedding would be beautiful.
Yeah.
What is that?
A firefly to guide us to safety.
I hope.