In 2166, an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan
is opposed by the body
I'd sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future, my friends
may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered as legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Sorry we're late.
Aren't you even a little bit happy
to be back on the ship?
I was happy with that life
we built together.
You think I was hunting you
and your friends
because the Time Masters made me?
They barely had to ask.
Since I failed to bring you in,
the Time Masters want to bring me in.
They're called the Hunters,
and they'll stop at nothing
till every single one of us is erased
from the face of history.
- Do you have any suggestions?
- Run.
It's been quite a while
since I time-jumped
far enough to experience
side effects.
Fond memories.
- I can't feel my face.
- Fine feel I.
Linguistic dysplasia,
that should pass shortly.
Better it now.
Am I the only one
who can't feel their face?
I can't feel my...
I better not say.
Mr. Rory appears unaffected.
What's going on?
- We time-jump?
- Yeah, we time-jumped.
But "where to?"
is the better question.
The town of Salvation,
the Dakota territory, 1871.
I can't believe it, the Old West.
- This isn't going to work.
- It'll buy us time.
We can hide out here
while the Hunters search
the other Fragmentations.
What if they decide
to check this place first?
You know, feel free to loop us
in whenever it's convenient.
As you've seen, time doesn't
operate as is generally thought.
It wants to happen.
It takes time to harden.
The... the timeline is unclear
on occasion, constantly in flux.
Hence the difficulty
in locating Savage
- throughout history.
- Indeed.
And one of the other
interesting notions
of time travel is the existence
of Fragmentations.
Temporal blind spots,
specific places and times
the Time Masters can't see.
The town of Salvation
and its surrounding environs
are located within one
of these Fragmentations.
So, basically,
we're hiding out in the Old West
and hoping your boogeymen
don't find us here.
The Hunters are not boogeymen.
And you better hope
they don't find us.
Well, at least not until
I get a chance
to "punch a few doggies"
or "bust a bronco" or two.
Not that I condone animal cruelty.
It's just that I watched a lot
of Westerns as a kid.
Alas, you'll have to enjoy
the Old West from in here,
- I'm afraid.
- Oh, come on.
What's the harm
in us just taking a look around?
With this group?
Clearly, you haven't been
paying attention.
If I'm in the Old West
and I don't get to look around,
I'm going to kick myself.
I could help with that.
I'll keep an eye on them.
Don't worry.
I'll be a good boy.
I look just like Wyatt Earp.
Now, the fabricator
can make clothing,
but you're also going to need
era-appropriate protection.
This era can get a little rough.
- Oh, six shooters?
- Actually, most guns
of that time period
had hammer blocks,
thus reducing the number
of shots to five.
Now, this should go without saying,
but considering this group,
I am going to say it.
Only use these weapons
in the case of extreme emergencies.
You make it sound
like you're not coming with.
From your duster and revolver,
I'd imagined you
as much an Old West aficionado
as Dr. Palmer.
Indeed I am.
But my time is best spent back here
on the ship, plotting our next
move against Vandal Savage.
Besides, as Mr. Rory says,
it's only a matter of time
before the Hunters find us here.
Don't worry.
We're not going to put down roots.
Yeah, we'll stay out of trouble.
How I hope and pray that to be true.
Remember, we're just here
to get the lay of the land.
- No trouble.
- Sure, that'll happen.
I need a drink.
Wow. It's a real old-timey saloon.
Oh, I beg your pardon.
Not at all, ma'am.
That tastes like gasoline.
Pretty much. Hit me again.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
It's no bother.
Time doesn't pass normally
in the Vanishing Point.
It's been years since I've seen
the bottom of a glass.
Years?
How long were you...
Chronos?
Never counted. Doesn't matter.
Turns out it was
just another gig anyway.
Doesn't seem like it.
You're different now.
Better or worse?
Don't know yet.
You can handle your liquor.
I like that.
I've been on more than a few dates
with guys who thought
we'd get wasted and they'd get lucky.
But somehow, they always ended up
the ones under the table.
You haven't drunk with me.
Is that a challenge, Mick?
Line them up.
Didn't know you played cards.
Like you, Mr. Snart, I am an enigma.
Raise.
Thank you, gentlemen.
I'm impressed.
My father was what some might call
a degenerate gambler,
others would say criminal.
When I was old enough, he'd pull
me in on some of his schemes.
I picked up a thing or two at a few
of the card tables he frequented.
Then I took a different path.
Like father, like son
isn't always inevitable, Mr. Snart.
- I had a full boat.
- As did I.
Full of kings,
which beats your pair of queens.
Don't I look busy to you?
I'm sorry. I...
If you spill another drop of that
whiskey, and you will be...
Just because you're losing
doesn't mean you have
to pick on the waitstaff.
Mind your own business, grandpa.
Unhand the lady.
Now, now, boys.
Let's just take it easy.
Oh, when my friend here
is being reasonable,
we know we have a problem.
I'm not the one with the problem.
You are.
You killed him.
You're welcome.
Clearly, the deceased
was a friend of yours.
- But my friend here...
- Your friend drew first,
got put down.
It was a clean shot.
Do we look like we care about clean?
He has a point.
All right!
Playtime's over.
Anybody's got a problem with that,
they answer to me.
Thank you, Mister...
Hex.
Jonah Hex.
You're not from around here,
are you?
No.
My friends and I are...
from out of town.
Way out of town.
All right.
Why don't you folks tell me
where you're really from?
I'm not sure that's
any of your business, sir.
Let me rephrase that.
Tell me when y'all from.
You seven stick out
like a dog in a manger.
Like he said,
we're not from around here.
You think you're
the first time travelers
I've ever come across?
Yes.
Where is he?
I got some words that need saying.
Where is who?
Rip Hunter.
What is it about you people
that whenever we go
to a new timeline,
you feel the need to pick up...
strays?
Nice.
I didn't get to see it
last time around.
Last time?
A long story
which we will not be telling.
My coat suits you good.
What are you doing here, Jonah?
Collecting on a bounty,
wetting my whistle,
when your friends here
got in a lot of trouble.
We might've gotten into
a barroom brawl back in town.
Well, that was entirely predictable.
One of them poured lead into
a member of the Stillwater gang.
- Mr. Rory.
- Snart, actually.
Oh, that was gonna be my next guess.
This guy tried to kill Grey.
Snart saved him.
And brought this town a whole
lot of hell in the bargain.
Those boys you were trading
hands with in the saloon.
They're all members
of the Stillwater gang.
Why can't a gang ever be
a bunch of good guys?
Jeb Stillwater and his friends
were raiding this town
for the past three months.
Stealing, robbing, killing.
Well, he'll have to go through us.
No, he won't.
No doubt your, your little ruckus
has already placed
the timeline at risk,
to say nothing of potentially
alerting the Hunters
to our presence here.
Sounds like someone's planning
on busting out of town again.
- Leaving already?
- No. No.
Look, this town is being terrorized
by the Stillwater gang.
And I aim to do something about it.
You "aim to"?
You getting all native on us,
Haircut?
Look, we signed on to this mission...
- To stop Vandal Savage.
- To be heroes.
And saving a town
from a marauding gang of criminals...
that is what heroes do.
Quite a posse of saints
you're riding along with nowadays.
Hey. Bridge is... that way.
Yeah, I'm not going to the bridge.
I'm...
Where am I going, Gideon?
The valley you described
is consistent with Albano Gulch.
Yeah, there.
Okay, wait. Why?
Back at the saloon,
I ran into a woman
and she caused me to have
more memory flashes, so...
I think I might have known her
in one of my past lives.
And if so, she might be able
to help me find Carter.
Wait. So you're just gonna run
out there and try and find her?
Actually, I was planning on flying.
You want a partner in crime?
Okay, fine.
But you're definitely
not carrying me.
How do you propose we get there?
Howdy. I'm Ray...
John Wayne.
What do you want, Mr. Wayne?
Well, I... I reckon you could use
another hand
with the Stillwater gang.
You boys have any experience
with law enforcement?
Well, I have a fair bit
of experience fighting crime.
Congratulations, then.
You're making me your deputy?
Nope.
Just made you the new sheriff.
- Excuse me. What?
- Stillwater gang
has been shooting up this town
for months now.
It's only by the grace
of the good Lord
that I'm not
pushing up daisies myself.
And I am done with pushing my luck.
But you're the...
sheriff.
Congratulations.
By the way,
you might find a warrant
or two out for me
around these parts.
You know, we have stuff
back on the ship
that can fix your, you know.
Fix what?
Yep. Nothing. Never mind.
- What can I get you?
- Information.
Some friends of mine
are looking for Jeb Stillwater.
If they're the same friends
that shot Billy Conlon
and beat on the Stillwater posse,
I can guarantee you he'll find you.
That being said, we'd very
much like to find him first.
You got any more of them greenbacks?
Let me go find a map.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I just want to be alone.
I understand.
I'm new to these parts.
I didn't think it was customary
for a lady to drink alone.
Tonic water.
It's for my son.
I just needed a moment to myself.
Is everything all right?
I should be getting back to my boy.
If there's something wrong with him,
perhaps I can be of assistance.
I happen to be a scientist.
That's kind.
But I'm afraid
there's nothing you can do.
My boy is going to die.
What's wrong with him?
He has the consumption, they say.
Tuberculosis.
He's been like this on and off
for about a year now.
He always wanted to see
the American West.
Our doctor thought a constitutional
might do him some good.
It hasn't, clearly.
You know,
there are medicines that...
The doctor here says he has a day...
maybe two, if he's lucky.
Does he look lucky to you, Mister...
I don't know your name.
It's Martin.
Hello, young man.
We call him Bertie.
Bertie.
Your mother tells me
you wanted to come out west.
Can't imagine
you've seen much of it yet.
I want to ride a stagecoach.
Well, in that case...
I encourage you to get better.
My mum... she's not sure I will.
Well, then you must prove
your mother wrong...
so you can ride that stagecoach.
One of mine is dead.
And this here town's gonna pay.
Now, who the hell
are you supposed to be?
John Wayne.
Salvation's new sheriff.
And this here town
is under my protection.
Well, you being new and all,
you don't know
about the arrangement that we got.
See, me and my boys,
we ride into town,
we take whatever we want.
In exchange for what?
Not killing nobody.
Well, that sounds reasonable and all,
but arrangement's over.
Arrangement's over, boys.
They teach you numbers
where it is you're from?
'Cause the way I see it,
there's only one of you
and a whole mess of us.
You get out of town,
and you don't come back,
or the next bullet goes in your eye.
I got sharpshooters all around.
You really want to test me?
Let's ride, boys.
Hyah!
Nice, Haircut.
Dude, that was badass.
Let's not oversell it.
Running a bad guy out of town's
always been on my bucket list.
Bucket list?
A list of things one hopes
to accomplish before they die.
Well, you better hope
it's a real short list, String Bean.
We can handle the Stillwater gang.
Well, you're all just tearing up
the 1870s, aren't you?
Stillwater and his gang's
like a hornets' nest,
and your friends here
keep poking at it.
They saved the town
from being raided, man.
Today, but what about tomorrow?
Or the day after that?
For a bunch of time travelers,
you don't seem to understand
the future much.
The day will come
when you'll all leave...
and Salvation
will end up like Calvert.
- What's a Calvert?
- A closed matter.
A word, Mr. Hex?
I believe you've all done enough
for one day.
Well, now I definitely want
to know what a Calvert is.
Then it's a good thing we have access
to a supercomputer.
Gideon?
Calvert was a town
in Oklahoma circa 1868.
Was?
You know, there's something
weird going on with your face.
- What?
- You're smiling.
I didn't know you could do that.
Well, don't tell anyone my secret.
It's just all of this...
it's so pure, so simple.
I'd say I miss simple,
but I guess you have
to experience something first
to miss it.
I know what you mean.
I've been having more and more
memory flashes lately,
and I'm not entirely sure why.
Well, if this woman was a friend
of yours in a past life,
hopefully she'll have
another piece for your puzzle.
I feel like I'm being drawn
to this place.
- Which way?
- There.
You know, stealing's against the law.
I'm the sheriff of these here parts.
How did you know
I was appropriating this medicine?
That was my fault, Professor.
Et tu, Gideon?
I suppose this is going to earn me
a lecture
on the perils
of upsetting the timeline
by introducing futuristic
medicine to the 19th century.
Well, it seems you've already
given it to yourself.
Except this isn't
futuristic medicine.
I've had Gideon fabricate
simple streptomycin for me.
Excuse me.
Which won't be used in medical
treatments for another 70 years.
This is about a boy in town
who's dying
of an easily curable disease.
Just as you couldn't turn
your back on Jeb Stillwater
and his gang, I can't turn mine
on this boy and his mother.
Except Dr. Palmer is using
19th century technology
to deal with Stillwater,
whereas you...
Just spare me the lecture,
Captain Hunter.
You, of all people...
This isn't about the mission, Martin!
Do you not recall what happened
when Dr. Palmer
left a bit of his suit back in 1975
and nearly destroyed Central City?
That was an accident.
I'm not talking about our mission
or Dr. Palmer's technological gaffe.
Calvert...
that town clearly holds some
emotional resonance for you,
judging from the looks
you've been exchanging with Mr. Hex.
How do you know it's a town?
Gideon?
Calvert, Oklahoma.
What happened to you there, Rip?
And why is it so important to you?
Because the past is prologue.
It's not uncommon for criminal posses
such as Mr. Stillwater's to sack
and pillage towns
which they find uncooperative.
So Stillwater's done this before?
In the case of Calvert,
it was Quentin Turnbull's doing.
But it was my fault.
I'd come to Calvert on a mission
from the Time Masters.
This was years
before my son Jonas was born.
Jonas...
Did you name your son after Hex?
After my mission was completed,
I felt unable to leave.
I'd grown so attached to this era...
a victim of the same
time drift you experienced in 1958.
But obviously you left at some point.
Left? I had to tear myself away
from the time period
for fear that I would never see
my then-future wife, Miranda,
ever again.
Turnbull attacked Calvert
the very next day.
So...
you can understand why I must act.
No, Martin, I don't.
As I said before,
this is advanced medicine
unsuitable to the period,
to say nothing
of what this boy's survival
might do to the timeline.
Be that as it may,
I refuse to live with the regret
I see on your face right now.
The information Mr. Stein got
from the barkeep paid out.
I know where
the Stillwater gang's holed up.
All right. Let's ride.
Up high.
You coming, Rip?
That's what I thought.
I wonder why she lives alone
all the way out here.
Because...
I value my privacy!
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't you remember me...
from the saloon back in Salvation?
I remembered you,
you wigged-out little girl.
If I'd wanted to talk to you then,
I would have talked to you then.
I ain't fixing to talk to you now.
Now, get off of my land!
Listen, we're not trying
to start any trouble.
Do you want that pretty little
mouth of yours filled with lead?
Your friend has a colorful
personality.
I ain't got friends.
I keep to myself.
She's right.
She wasn't my friend.
I was her.
We sat for that picture
at the county fair, 1830.
He looked like such a gentleman.
- What was his name?
- Hannibal.
Hannibal Hawkes.
And what happened?
Was it Savage?
What is this?
It looks familiar.
That was ours in our first life.
I remember.
We crossed with Savage
in Jefferson City.
He had it with him.
We escaped with it and our lives.
Do you still have it?
We lost it to bandits
about a year later.
We heard that the Pinkertons
were after the same bandits,
but we just...
Hey.
What is it?
Objects present
at the moment of my...
our first death
can be used to kill Savage.
So, if I can get my hands
on that bracelet, then...
You're going to try
to kill Savage with a bracelet?
You need to stop.
- Stop what?
- Fighting our destiny.
Ain't destiny what brought you here?
What part of destiny is she fighting?
All of it.
We get reborn. We find Hannibal...
Carter, then Savage finds us,
and then we die.
That's... that's the way it is.
It's the way it's always gonna be.
I don't believe that.
Well, I have a few more years on you.
You can't break the cycle.
That's why I live out here, alone.
For the rest of your life?
Well, I guess I had to figure
that out the hard way.
I was still a young woman
when Savage left me a widow.
Instead of waiting for him
to find me and kill me
so that I could love my Hannibal
in the next life,
I tried to find love in this one.
Talk about a curse.
What happened?
He was a good man,
but he wasn't a soul mate.
It was like fate was trying
to break us apart.
Eventually,
fate broke both our hearts.
So I made a promise to myself
that I wasn't gonna do that
to a person again.
I'm... I'm sorry to hear that.
No, I'm who's sorry...
to have to be the one to let you know
that you're never going to be
able to love anyone else, ever.
How much do you know
about our previous lives?
I reckon not a lot
because you didn't recognize me.
So let me tell you
that we did love other men,
loved them real and pure,
but it never ended well, not ever.
Tragedy or heartbreak...
that's how it always ends
if the man's not Carter.
We could've used Sara
on this roundup.
A lady? You crazy?
Just remember,
we're here to arrest Stillwater,
not kill him.
He always this much
of a stick in the mud?
Yes.
How?
It's a miracle.
Oh, it's, it's not a miracle,
I can assure you.
- Mrs. Neal...
- Sarah.
Sarah...
when the illness is gone,
I need you to promise me
that you'll take what's left
of the medicine and burn it,
vials and all.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
Yes, I shall do it.
Sarah...
I wish you well.
Thank you.
I really must be going.
Oh, damn.
These boys got some stones.
Jeb Stillwater, you are under arrest.
You have the right to remain silent.
You have the right to an attorney.
There won't be Miranda rights
for another 100 years.
Fall back! Fall back!
Jax!
- We got to go!
- Not without Jax!
Well, we got Stillwater.
It means we got leverage.
Live to fight another day
or die tonight.
Your choice. Hyah!
Where is Stillwater?
He's knocked out cold
in the med bay.
Well, this is a simple matter.
We trade Stillwater for Jefferson
as Mr. Hex suggested.
It's not that simple.
If we release Stillwater,
we're back to square one
and the town is still in danger.
So is the kid.
And we'll figure out a way
to get him back
without releasing Stillwater.
I got a notion.
Set up a quick draw.
You win,
get your guy back.
You lose,
you set Stillwater free.
And, by "lose," you mean...
Get shot and killed.
Oh, great. Pistols at high noon.
Finally, someone's talking sense.
There has to be another way,
a better way.
Sure.
Go after Stillwater with all
your gear from the future.
I don't know how that'll sit
with your captain, though.
Let's assume it's a bad idea.
So who's standing
in the middle of Main Street?
I'll do it.
Raymond, now is not the time
to indulge your cowboy fantasies.
No one else is stepping forward.
Plus, I'm a decent shot...
at least I was with an air rifle.
I can't believe
you're encouraging this.
You know it's the only way.
Dr. Palmer's going to get
himself killed.
I think you forfeited
your right to an opinion
when you refused to leave the ship
since we've been here.
I had good reason.
Because of Calvert.
Yes, but not in the way you think.
Leaving Calvert, leaving this... era
is one of the hardest things
I've ever had to do.
And why is that, Captain?
A Time Master is trained to do
his work without interference,
which means not helping people
or being a hero.
But as you've seen, Dr. Palmer,
this era offers
many opportunities for heroism.
I found it...
enticing.
And you still managed to leave.
Something's been bugging me
all these years.
If you'd have known what
Turnbull was going to do to Calvert,
would you have left?
That's the thing, Jonah.
I did know.
- I deserve that.
- You deserve a lot worse.
You knew, and you still left?
Of course, I knew.
I was a Time Master.
And therein lay the problem.
Like Raymond, like Martin,
I felt the pull of heroism,
of this era's penchant
for being rife with opportunities
to make a difference.
That's one of the things
that called to me,
and that is why I had to leave.
Because had I stayed...
I could no longer
have remained a Time Master.
But I'm no longer a Time Master...
which is why I'll face Stillwater.
Wait. I said that I would do it.
And get yourself shot and killed?
It's appreciated,
but I'd rather you stayed alive.
Send word to Stillwater's posse.
I believe high noon is
in less than three hours.
You want to talk about it?
Not really.
You don't have to listen to her,
you know?
Is this you not talking about it?
No. This is me ignoring you
saying you don't want
to talk about it.
Look, I get it.
Things may have gone
very wrong for Old West you
and whoever she loved
who wasn't Carter.
But?
But Old West you
didn't know Ray Palmer.
She didn't love Ray Palmer.
You do.
And you have to live your life.
She already lived hers.
- You think Hunter can pull this off?
- Reasonably.
If not, I got dibs on that
newfangled revolver of his.
You sure about this?
Well, if anything, it feels
good to be out here again,
in this era.
Well, don't get too attached.
That is what I keep telling myself.
I'll be drawing for Sheriff Palmer.
How do me and my boys know
you're going to keep your word?
Sheriff Palmer's a straight shooter.
Then he should be
the one in the street.
- Jefferson, are you all right?
- Yeah.
Did you just shoot somebody for me?
Yeah. You're welcome.
I don't think we're done here yet.
Oh, no.
They found us.
Friends! Welcome.
I think you'll find this
slightly more effective
than your current sidearm.
Yes, I will be wanting
that back, by the way.
And you'll be needing this.
What about revealing
our future tech to the locals?
It doesn't seem to bother them.
Shall we?
What about our guns?
Sorry. Grabbed what I could.
That's what's up!
Y'all better stay the hell
away from us!
Calm down, Jefferson.
- Traitor!
- Not possible.
I was never on your side.
I was on my side.
- You'll never win!
- Wake up, pal. We already did.
Fool. The Time Masters
have initiated Omega Protocol.
The Pilgrim's coming for you,
Chronos.
Your deaths are
just a matter of time.
Yeah, yeah.
Well, that was easy.
- You're not staying.
- Are you?
Me? You know I can't.
But this town still needs a sheriff.
Well, I'm not
the law-and-order type...
nor the staying-in-one-place
type either.
Well, we have that much
in common at least.
At least.
Be well, Jonah.
Nice thing about my world
for you, it ain't going anywhere.
Perhaps we will see each other again,
my friend.
Yeah.
I reckon that'd be okay.
- Interesting fella.
- Indeed.
This town's seen
a lot of interesting.
Suppose you got
one of those doohickies
that erases people's memories
or something?
No. But...
skepticism and disbelief
are a far more effective tool.
So, if anybody here talks,
no one will believe them.
Would you, Mr. Snart?
I'm not going to pretend
to understand what I saw.
I'd prefer that you didn't
tell anyone about it either.
That goes for you too,
young Master Neal.
- My last name's Wells.
- Excuse me?
His father's surname.
Herbert George Wells.
You're H.G. Wells.
H.G. I like that.
Astonishing.
God, it feels so good to be
in normal clothes again.
The people here need to invent
fabric softener asap.
Is that all?
It's just that
you've seemed a little off
ever since you came back
from your walkabout.
Ray, I told you...
Something, but I don't
think it's the whole truth.
I thought that we decided to be
honest with each other.
And I am.
I am being honest with you, Ray.
Look, I met a woman,
and I learned some things.
I told you about killing Savage.
And the rest...
The rest is what she thought.
Not what I think.
I don't have to listen to her.
I love you.
I love you too.
I think they're waiting for us
on the bridge.
We should go.
So how are you feeling,
given your concerns
about becoming addicted
to this era once again?
The last time I left, Martin,
I did it to be
with those closest to me.
I'm doing the same again.
So where to now?
Or, more specifically, when?
Is there another Fragmentation
we can hide out in?
Unfortunately, matters are
not quite so simple.
How'd I know you were gonna
say something like that?
- Rip's buddies.
- And yours.
The Time Masters have issued
Omega Protocols on all of us.
That sounds pretty terrible.
The worst kind of order
they can issue...
they've sent the Pilgrim after us.
- Who's the Pilgrim?
- The Pilgrim is
the Time Masters'
most deadly assassin,
and she will stop at nothing
until each
and every one of you are dead.
Ooh, scary.
Pretty sure we can handle ourselves.
Indeed...
which is why
she won't be going after
the present-day versions of you.
She's hunting our younger selves.
And she won't stop until each
and every one of us
has been erased from the timeline.