[Agent Sharpe] Previously on
Legends Of Tomorrow...
Mallus wasn't the only prisoner
to escape.
Now, there's magic.
[whinnying]
An unknown number of
dangerous magical beings
got spat out across the timeline
and now, must be sent to hell.
[Ray] She's a shapeshifter.
[casting magic spell]
[Charlie] What did you do to me?
A lobotomy of sorts.
Your shapeshifting days are over,
sweetheart.
- No!
- She definitely isn't Amaya.
[twig snaps]
- Did you just hear that?
- Judy, relax.
There's nothing out here.
Tonight, it's just you and me. Okay?
- [roaring]
- [screaming]
- [TV chimes]
- [Sara] Wait a second.
Don't tell me that
the fearless Ms. Lance is scared
of a little horror film?
No, I love horror movies
and I watched them obsessively
as a kid.
So how could I have missed this gem?
- [Agent Sharpe chuckles]
- [TV chimes]
"Swamp Thaaaang." Never heard of it.
And what's with all the "A's"?
Okay, let me look.
Okay, Swamp Thaaaang.
Apparently, there are
four "A's" in the name
because it's the fourth film
in the franchise.
The AV Club gave it a D-plus,
saying, "The production design
"is as lazy as the action staging."
- Harsh.
- Yeah.
"Based on real life, tragic events
that occurred at Camp Ogawa, Maine,
"in the summer of 1995"?
Gideon.
We're in my room, babe.
- Right.
- [cell phone ringing]
[Sara] Speak of the devil.
[Gideon] Sorry to interrupt, Captain,
but I've detected
new magical events in the timeline.
It seems that a number of children
went missing from a summer camp.
Let me guess, Camp Ogawa, Maine.
Precisely.
Looks like the handiwork
of one of our fugitives.
Shall I plot a course to 1995, then?
While you're at it,
fabricate a mess of bug spray.
I'm on my way.
Well, how about that.
We almost got to spend two whole
uninterrupted hours together.
How about you come with me?
Summer camp? As in bug bites,
bunk beds and mean girls?
No. Summer camp as in campfires,
sing-alongs,
and friendship bracelets.
Camp's the best. You'll love it.
Pinky swear.
What are you doing?
[chuckles] It's something you do when
you're a kid. It's like a promise.
What? [chuckles]
Come on. No, pinky.
- Yes.
- You're weird. [chuckles]
This will be a great way for us
to spend some more time together
and plus, we get to make sure
that doesn't happen in real life.
[Agent Sharpe] I talked to Nate, and
he's got things covered at the Bureau.
He and Gary have their hands full
with all the magical creatures
popping up.
Nate and Gary are in charge.
Well, anyways,
I'm glad that he's there
because we've got something
I really don't want him to see.
What's that?
[chuckles] Amaya.
It just looks like her.
- Did you say "it"?
- She's a shapeshifter.
We found her in London, 1977.
Hmm. Hello.
Not much of a talker, I see.
Oh, she talks.
Go to hell!
Just her way of saying "hello."
Oh, let me out of here, you bastards!
She's still adjusting
to her new home.
[grunts]
[screaming]
Maybe it's the food.
But Constantine
sent the other fugitives
you encountered to hell, so...
She's not exactly
a bloodthirsty unicorn.
Or an evil fairy godmother.
But you decided to keep
the shapeshifter because...
Oh...
To exploit her for information
about the interdimensional prison
that she's been trapped in
to help us track down
other fugitives.
That is exactly what we are doing.
One hundred percent.
Isn't that right, Zari?
Yeah. Um, I'm gathering that intel
- as we speak.
- Mmm.
I love the initiative, team.
Yeah.
- Gentlemen.
- [Constantine] Oh, Director Sharpe.
Joining us, are we?
- Is that a problem?
- Not for me, love.
Good. Because we are headed
back to the '90s
to infiltrate a place called
Camp Ogawa.
Whoa, sneaking into a military facility,
are we?
Actually,
it's a summer camp for kids.
Oh, I love summer camp. Everyone used
to call me Kid Counselor.
Bet you took that as a compliment,
too, didn't you, mate?
Well, because of my
leadership skills obviously. [chuckles]
[Ray laughs]
- Right? That's why...
- Mmm-hmm. Yeah.
So, uh, any idea what kind of foul beast
we're up against, then?
- Well, based on... Research.
- [mouthing]
Sara and I have been doing,
we could be looking for
a swampy monster thing.
[Sara] According to the timeline,
before the end of summer,
several kids went missing,
never to be seen again.
Well, I happen to know a Swamp Thing.
But then again, Maine is
way too far north for that muppet.
Well, we used to use the buddy system
to make sure everyone was safe.
And this is where Nate would say,
"I'm your buddy,"
and we'd do a fist bump
or a silly jig or...
Well, we are shorthanded, so...
I need you to partner up with John.
Oh, don't worry, dreamboat. I've had
stranger bedfellows than you.
But just so you know, I'm not one
to get all gussied up
for a gig, all right?
[indistinct chatter]
Huh, you may take my coat,
but you will never take...
Nope. And lose the tie.
Oh, you have got to be kidding me.
Fine. One time.
But it's only for the kids.
Yeah. That's the camp spirit.
[Agent Sharpe]
Are these outfits really necessary?
[Sara] Girl!
Come on. Gideon made us official
Camp Ogawa counselor uniforms
using archival photos
so that we could fit in.
What are you guys doing
just standing around?
Hi. We are the new camp counselors.
Sorry to show up unannounced.
Well, freckles,
the name's Paula Cooper.
I'm the director here.
Welcome to Camp Ogawa.
My right-hand man, Chad Stevens,
will show you around. Chad.
Get over here.
[Chad exhales]
- S'up!
- Chad, you marbled cut of prime beef,
give these new counselors the tour.
Cool. All right.
Hey, let's bounce over this way.
I'll give you the 411
on this place, huh?
Yeah.
What we need are snipers
on that ridge line,
spotters on the ground
and an exfil site
for when we bag the creature.
Not a bad plan, Sharpie.
I'll put a protection spell
around the perimeter
to keep out the nasties.
Best offense is a strong defense.
- [Constantine] Mmm.
- Hmm.
So, as you can see,
Camp Ogawa is a miserable place,
and Paula runs it like a POW camp.
Not! [chuckles]
- [laughs]
- Oh, God, another '90's "not" joke.
Oh, it's like comic comfort food.
I'm sorry. I couldn't help
but admire your lanyard.
Did you make that yourself?
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
Yeah, along with
the 21 required merit badges,
I also went on to get certification
in Nuclear Science and Dentistry.
Oh, snap!
I've got some serious competition
for "Coolest Counselor"
this summer, huh? [chuckles]
Ah.
What about you?
You got any special skills?
Martial arts.
[yells]
[chuckles] Sorry. That's so fresh.
Jackie Chan, you know.
[Chad sighs]
I prefer knives and swords.
Right, yeah. Point taken.
- Point taken.
- [laughing] Good one, bro.
Anyway, let's head over here.
All right,
I'm gonna assign you your cabins.
It's gonna be a heck of a summer.
He'll grow on you.
Greetings, members of Newton Cabin.
I am Counselor Ray
and the mysterious gentlemen
behind you is Counselor John.
Cheers, lads.
Well, today's subject
is wilderness survival,
which includes
Tracking and Orienteering.
Who's excited?
Well, you will be, okay?
Two words to remember when tracking.
Displacement and direction.
Now, Counselor John will demonstrate
the kind of inadvertent markers
people leave behind
while walking in the woods.
And Counselor John
is missing already.
See how easy it is
to get lost in the woods, gentlemen?
- What's up, Franklin Cabin?
- [girls cheer]
We are in the house,
I am Sara and this is Ava.
We are your camp counselors.
Now, I was thinking
we need a secret handshake.
[girls] Yeah.
Something really cool
that only we know.
- Yeah.
- So cool.
- What are you doing?
- Bonding.
How's that supposed to keep them safe
from what's in the woods?
It allows us to form
a meaningful connection
and them to feel like
they're part of a team.
They're not gonna be a part
of anything if they're dead.
- Ava...
- We can go back to the fun and games
once we catch the creature. Yes?
[clearing throat]
All right, ladies. Change in plan.
Today, we're gonna celebrate
your first day of camp
by using safety and discipline.
Got it? Now,
when I blow this whistle,
you are to run, not walk,
to your respective beds. [blowing]
But it's still daytime.
It will feel like nighttime
when your eyes are closed. Now, move.
Very nice.
[exhales]
What are you doing?
I'm creating a protective barrier
to catch monsters.
- Monsters?
- Yeah.
You know, the kind that slice
your stomach open
and then eat your intestines
for supper.
Getting those kids to bed was
a lot easier than I expected.
You know, I'm really glad I came.
I just feel bad.
We're ruining camp for these kids.
It's such an important time.
Well, didn't realize you were so
gung ho about this whole camp thing.
I was even Color Captain one year.
Mmm?
Summer after eighth grade.
I really stuck it to Suzy Smith
and the Green Team that year.
That sounds magical.
It was.
Unfortunately, we're here
to stop magic, my love.
Well, with us guarding their cabin
and Constantine's perimeter,
at least no swampy monster
is getting into this camp tonight.
[twig snaps]
Who's there?
[chuckles]
Relax, Lenise. It's just me.
Zack.
So, what do you want to do?
Have you ever kissed anyone before?
Zack?
- [roaring]
- [screaming]
[sighs] Beautiful morning.
Yeah, sorry to burst your
summer-loving bubble, mate,
but we're missing one
of our young charges.
His name is Zack or something.
Well, are you sure you counted right?
Because based on
your whiskey cologne,
I think you're still drunk.
No, he's right.
Yeah. A girl's missing
from our cabin, too.
Even after I put
the fear of God in them.
Obviously, there's something wrong
with Constantine's booby trap.
Yeah, are you off your trolley, mate?
My spell was designed to keep
the monsters from getting in,
not children getting out.
They must have snuck out
in the middle of the night.
Snuck out? Why would they sneak out?
To make out, duh.
Well, I suppose we should notify
the camp director.
Okay, guys, so...
Oh, don't worry about those kids,
they're gonna be just fine.
- Uh, shouldn't we mount a search party...
- They couldn't have gotten too far.
Look, freckles,
this happens every year.
Kids under the influence
of their hormones
go off into the woods at night.
Just watch.
They'll eventually get hungry
and tired, and they'll come back.
Now, go out there
and do some counseling.
Well, someone gives
precisely zero craps
about the safety of her campers.
I guarantee you one of these kids
knows where the other two went.
How can you be so sure?
Because when I was in camp,
we used to hide stuff from
the counselors all the time.
We just need to figure out
how to get them to talk.
[exhaling]
The Circle of Trust creates
a safe space
for us to share our secrets
without judgement.
- [sighs]
- Now, take each other's hands.
- Now, I want you to...
- Uh...
Sorry to butt in, lads,
but can I have
a word with you for a second?
[sighs]
I want you to meditate on the word
"openness" and I'll be right back.
You're interrupt... [clears throat]
You're interrupting the flow.
Yeah, well, apologies
to you and your flow
but all of your psychobabble,
it ain't gonna cut the mustard
with the young ones, mate.
Let me show you how it's done.
Right then,
which one of you whippersnappers
wants to be hypnotized?
- [boys] Me, me, me.
- Pick me!
- Me first.
- [all talking at once]
Alexis, you and Lenise
are besties, right?
We were partners
in last year's talent show.
She didn't show up at roll call
this morning. I'm worried.
Do you know
where she might have gone?
All right, ladies! On your feet.
Report to the front of your beds,
arms by your sides, now!
What is with the police lineup?
This is summer camp,
not boot camp, remember?
You are too soft on these kids.
Children crave authority.
Besides, my way will be quicker.
[watch ticking]
[Constantine] That's it.
Look at my watch.
Now, where did your mate Zack
run off to last night?
He didn't say.
But I hope he didn't go
near the outdoor showers.
Why?
What's by the outdoor showers?
That's where I hid
my Victoria's Secret catalog.
Huh.
Your friend Lenise snuck out
of the cabin last night.
And no one's going anywhere
until I find out where she went.
But the ice cream social
is in, like, five minutes.
Well, then you better, like,
start talking, Kiana,
or you're gonna have to scrape
the bottom of the carton
for what's left.
[watch ticking]
Last night, Zack said something about
meeting someone in the woods.
Where in the woods exactly?
A baseball field, only there's
no baseball field out there.
Oh, that's all right. Keep digging.
He kept talking about
making it to first base with a girl.
But who plays baseball in the dark?
She probably went to the same place
your style went.
You could use a makeover.
Like, head to toe.
[screaming]
[Gideon] Ms. Tomaz,
the prisoner is growing quite unruly.
Tell her to knock herself out.
[groans]
I take that back.
[sighs]
Damn it. Not on my watch.
[beeping]
[grunting]
[laughs]
[whooping]
Okay. I feel like we got off
on the wrong foot.
It's just that you're wearing
my friend's face
and that's a little unsettling,
given your general demeanor.
Look, I didn't love it at first
when I got here,
but I found my place.
You can, too.
Take a look
in the mirror, sweetheart.
It's not my face
that should be unsettling.
You're the one putting things
in cages. [clicks tongue]
[sighs]
So, how many girls has
the missus made cry so far
- or have you lost count?
- [sighs]
Ava's interrogation techniques
aren't gonna work on them.
They'd rather take their secrets
to the grave than squeal.
Anything with the boys?
Oh, those boys aren't hiding a thing.
They're open books,
if those books were written
by hapless fools, that is.
If I could just become one of them,
another 12-year-old camper, I could
get these girls to talk like that.
I do believe that you've just sparked
an idea there, Ms. Lance.
[Mick] End of the road, kid.
[gun powering up]
In your cage.
[gun powers down]
Bloke like you doesn't strike me
as a jailer.
I believe we're more alike
than you think.
You look like
you've been on the inside.
That's right.
Then how do you sleep at night
hanging out with
these jailer mates of yours?
Alcohol.
Oh, I've made an additional list
of suspects I want questioned.
- Ava...
- Look,
I know that you just want them
to have fun, all right?
But the fact of the matter is
there is a monster out there
hunting down these kids
and these girls are stonewalling us.
Okay?
[girl] Counselor Ava?
Yes?
I'm ready to tell you
what's really going on.
Go on, honey. Spill the beans.
It won't stop
unless you do something.
What won't stop?
The monster
that lives under the dock.
The Lake Beast.
Who's the Lake Beast?
Years ago, at this very camp,
some mean kids played a prank
on a boy
and he drowned in the lake.
And now, every year he returns
to get his revenge.
And so you think
the Lake Beast took your friends?
[shudders]
They say the only way
to make him appear
is to go to the dock alone
and call his name three times.
Sweetie, you are so brave.
And I promise you,
the Lake Beast won't be
getting anyone tonight, okay?
[Ray] Guys!
Guys, I think I see
a Northern Saw-whet owl.
Ray! Focus.
[sighs] Fine. I'll save it
for my bird-watching journal.
Okay, you're in the clear, Ava.
- [bird screeches]
- [gasps]
Stupid bird.
Okay, let's get this over with.
Lake Beast. Lake Beast. Lake Beast.
[scoffs]
Guys, this feels like a bust to me.
[water splashing]
[gasps]
[laughing]
Oh, it was just a bloody prank.
- Let's go!
- Go, go, go!
You okay?
Nice night for a swim though,
eh, Sharpie.
[panting]
Those girls are monsters!
After we left the lake last night,
another one of our campers
went missing.
Another one of ours is missing, too.
That makes four in total.
They must have snuck out
to meet up with each other
and never made it back.
Yeah, well, I don't know
about you lot,
but I'm not just sitting around here
and waiting for the monster
to go and get another kid.
[Agent Sharpe] We better split up.
All right. You two check the woods
for the missing kids.
Ava and I will stay and watch here.
Hey, wait. Buddy system.
I heard about last night.
It's majorly uncool.
Who knew kids could be so mean?
They've been calling me "Lake Beast"
behind my back all day.
Excuse me, Lake Beast. [giggling]
And to my face.
[Chad] Okay. Hey.
That is enough, ladies.
The joke is over.
It's time for you to behave
or else your cabin will be banned
from the July Jamboree.
The only way we are gonna get
any information from these girls
is to infiltrate their clique.
How are we supposed to do that?
We're not kids.
Funny you should say that.
Constantine gave me a potion
that would turn us into kids
only temporarily.
You're kidding, right?
Wh...
Even if it worked, Sara, I wouldn't
have any idea how to act like a kid
because I've never been one.
All my childhood memories
are fake, remember?
How are we gonna find the kids
with that dangly thing?
You know,
this ritual usually works best
when someone isn't yammering
in my earlobe.
Well, if you want to find the kids,
we got to do it
the old-fashioned way.
Study their tracks.
It's a good thing I came prepared,
because one step
in the wrong direction here
and you'll be traveling for miles
in the wrong direction.
Damn it, you namby-pamby,
I said I need silence.
Oh, you meant right now.
I'm sorry, I thought you meant...
- [stutters]
- [grunts]
Why are you being such a jerk?
Because you shouldn't even be
out here chasing a magical creature.
All right?
It's too dangerous.
Too dangerous? [scoffs]
You're lucky you're out here with me,
because I can keep us alive
on bugs and berries alone.
You know, this has nothing to do
with survival in the wild,
and everything to do with surviving
magical creatures
and those who dabble
in the dark arts.
I'll have you know I am no stranger
to the world of magic.
Yeah. Oh, don't think I haven't heard
how Nora Darhk had you eating out of
the palm of her wicked little hand.
Oh, I bet she didn't even have to ask
for the time stone, did she?
No, you just gave it away
like biscuits at tea time.
Nora and I have
a mutual respect for each other.
It's not like I was tripping
over myself...
What is that?
Huh.
No doubt left behind
by the magical beast.
Who sheds its skin
after it eats the kids?
What are we looking for?
Some sort of snake monster?
No, the answer is in this book.
Is that a magical Audubon guide?
Neato.
Mmm.
It's good. What is it?
Hooch. I spent a little time
in a Siberian gulag.
Got a taste for it.
[chuckles] Where I was,
it felt like 500 years.
Time worked differently
in that realm.
Oh, I've been in a lot of cages,
but not a magical one.
What was it like?
The inside of my cage
was a constant battle
between creatures
from your worst nightmare.
I got to know some of them better
than I wanted to.
It was a dismal and a dark dimension
like nothing here on Earth.
And I'll be damned
if I'm ever going back.
Well, cheers to that.
[sighs]
Friendship bracelet?
No, it's an "I'm sorry" bracelet.
I shouldn't have run off like that.
It's just that,
you know I'm not normal
and I think you hit a nerve
or something.
No, I'm sorry.
I never even thought about the fact
that you've never been a kid.
- Yeah.
- But this is really good.
I confiscated it from Alexis.
See? I'm weird.
Do you know that those two actors
who are my parents,
I keep a picture of them
on my desk in my office
just so I can try to feel
a little bit normal.
Yeah. That is anything but normal.
- Yeah.
- [Ray] Guys.
I think we've ID'd our monster.
Constantine and I found a skin suit
shed by something called a shtriga.
- Come again?
- [Constantine] A shtriga.
It's a vampiric witch that feeds off
the life force of children.
Bloody brilliant setting up shop
at summer camp.
There's some good news, sort of.
It says here the shtriga feeds slowly
off its prey,
draining its life energy
over a course of days.
Which means the missing kids
could still be alive.
Then it's on you guys to find them.
Aye.
Look, and it's on us
to protect these girls.
Now, I know you think I'm crazy,
but what if the best way
to protect them
is by becoming one of them?
We'll lure the creature out.
We'll be the bait.
What if Constantine's potion
doesn't work on me?
There is only one way to find out.
And if does, I'll be with you
every step of the way.
I'll show you the ropes,
teach you how to be a kid.
Pinky swear?
Pinky swear.
[sighs]
[Chad] All right, lights out, everyone.
[children laughing]
[Chad] And that means you, too,
Hopper Cabin.
Don't make me come in there.
[Sara] You feel anything yet?
- Um...
- [sighs]
No. Maybe it doesn't work.
The pretty lights tell me otherwise.
[door opens]
Hey, what are you two doing in here?
[gasps] Oh, snap!
Where'd you guys come from
out of the blue?
Got kicked out of Clarke Cabin
for putting a frog
- under Christi Donovan's pillow.
- [laughter]
You should've heard her scream.
[laughter]
Cool. And you?
I was kicked out because I was
caught reading after lights out.
Reading? Lame.
Uh, her counselors only thought
she was reading,
but really she was writing a letter
to her boyfriend.
He lives in France.
This year's counselors are the worst.
Especially Lake Beast.
- Yeah, I heard she smells bad.
- [laughter]
Hey!
Um, yeah, I heard she looked really
funny when she fell into the water.
[chuckles] But you're lucky
she didn't catch pneumonia.
That's a very serious illness.
Uh, sure.
You must have had balls
to survive that hellhole.
Did what I had to.
Shapeshifted into whatever monster
would keep the others off my back.
But you know exactly what it's like.
Pretending to be something
worse than you are to survive.
Well, there's that.
And there's finding
someone you trust.
I did time in supermax
with my old partner.
It's hard to plot against a team.
I spent all my time
shapeshifting and running.
I never stuck around
in one place long enough
to find anyone that I could trust.
Well, you gotta start somewhere.
[Mick groans]
[into comms] Hey, it's me, Sara.
- You guys still out there?
- [Constantine] Sara.
The potion actually worked.
You didn't know if it was gonna work
before you gave us the potion?
Of course I didn't. I've never
tested it on humans, have I?
Damn it, John.
Well, just see it like this.
You two have now turned yourselves
into irresistible shtriga bait.
So, any suggestions on
how a couple of kids can take on
a magical, child-eating hag?
Mmm...
Well, if you're in a pinch,
you can always try
capsicum annuum, more commonly
known as cayenne pepper.
Witches hate the stuff,
- but you'll be fine. Cheers, love.
- [comms beeps]
[sighs]
Great. But where are we
gonna get cayenne pepper?
Follow my lead.
[Constantine] The shtriga's lair
can't be far now.
[Ray] Look. A camper must have tried
to hide from the shtriga here.
- What are you doing?
- [grunts]
- Oh, a spell?
- Yup.
[inhales deeply]
[chanting in other language]
A will-of-the-wisp.
Little bugger will lead us
to whoever owns that shirt.
Oh, go on, then. Light the way.
[chuckles] Look at us,
a pair of magical detectives.
Oh, and I was beginning to think
you were all right,
and you went and said that.
You know, there are other dabblers
of the dark arts out there
who think that I'm all right.
Referring to Nora Darhk, are we?
You best stay away
from that witch, mate.
Not even your big heart
can keep you safe
from someone who's wrestled
with literal demons.
[scoffs] What about you?
You're one of us now.
You even dressed up
for a little while.
You've wrestled with demons
and you're good...
Listen to me, all right.
You know, I had a friend like you.
Someone good, someone who trusted me.
Be smarter than him, all right?
Save yourself, Ray Palmer.
Because people like
me and Nora Darhk,
we're bloody hell
for people like you.
[sighs]
Truth or dare?
Truth.
I think you meant dare?
Dare?
[chuckles] Dare, I mean dare.
I dare you to sneak out of the cabin
and break into the mess hall.
But to prove
that you didn't chicken out,
you have to bring us something
back from the kitchen.
[girls] Ooh...
This must be the place.
Alexis, who would you rather
have babies with?
Jonathan Taylor Thomas
or Mario Lopez?
[door opens]
I ran into some trouble.
I knew it, she chickened out.
I tried to carry more, but I could
only sneak out with two of these.
I know you missed
the ice cream social, so...
Ice cream social is coming to you.
Rocky road and mint chocolate chip,
you are the best ever.
[girls chattering indistinctly]
And I have something just for us.
That's my girl.
[door creaking]
[Ray] Oh, I've seen enough
horror movie trailers
to know this won't end well.
Oh, those films are nothing compared
to the horrors you might see
in real life.
[Constantine grunts]
[gasps]
Are... Are we too late?
I'll need an incantation,
a crystal and a conduit
to draw the pilfered life force
from the shtriga
and back into their bodies.
Now just follow my lead
and do everything I say.
We really needed this.
Camp's been kind of rough this year.
What do you mean?
It's okay, you can talk to us.
We're super worried about
Lenise and Meredith.
We didn't want to say anything
for the longest time.
We thought we'd get in trouble
and ruin everything.
Ruin what?
The midnight meetup.
It's a tradition.
Every summer, girls take turns
choosing guys they like
to meet up with in the woods.
There's a string
that starts near the flag pole
and it leads out
into the meeting spot.
It changes every year.
So, they meet up
and what's supposed to happen next?
Well, you're supposed to have
your first kiss and come back.
But Lenise and Meredith
never came back.
We got to be getting close, right?
[rustling]
What was that?
[swishing]
It's way past lights out.
What punishment should I cook up
for you?
Come here, you two.
Get off me, you crusty old witch!
[screams] My eyes!
[grunts]
Is she dead?
All right, our team's dealing with
something called a shtriga.
Do you know anything
that could help them fight it?
Oh, a shtriga?
Very intelligent and very deadly.
If you want my help,
it's gonna cost you.
Great. Will that come
in the form of another haiku,
or can we expect something
a little more detailed?
What's that? What's that eye thing?
According to legend,
shtrigas are nasty old women.
But the one that I met in prison,
the one that you're looking for,
is beautiful. And he's a bloke.
- Hmm.
- [beeping]
What the hell are you doing?
Hey, you don't have
another bathroom break for...
Oh, that's right, never,
since you tried to break my face.
It is now or never.
Fine. Whatever.
[sighing] Guys, this shtriga thing
is not an old woman.
What's going on out here?
[Zari over comms] You are looking for
a young, handsome dude.
[Constantine] All right,
you ready, big man?
On with the show, then.
[groaning]
What did you guys do to her?
We didn't do anything.
Look, it's not safe
for you guys out here.
Okay? You're coming with me.
We can take care of ourselves.
You're coming with me
whether you like it or not.
[gasps]
[grunting]
[in demonic voice]
You think you're so tough?
I don't think it... I know it!
[grunting]
[whimpering]
[growling]
[chanting in other language]
[grunting]
[Ray continues chanting]
[growls]
[Ray] It's working.
- [chuckles]
- [panting]
[laughs] It worked.
[Constantine groans]
- Ooh, that was worse than a hangover.
- [laughs]
[growling]
[Sara grunts]
[shtriga yelling]
[panting]
[both chuckle]
Oh, no.
No, no, no. Come on, lad, wake up.
Wake up, lad! Wake up, come on, son!
Damn it.
Bollocks!
I'm not losing another kid.
[chanting in other language]
What are you doing?
[exhales]
John!
John.
John, John. John.
[groans]
Damn it.
Hey.
Any of you got a light?
What happened?
You saved him. You saved Randall.
Well, that's good.
I'll get you back to the ship.
I'm not sure how I'm gonna get
the rest of you out.
Found you guys! We got worried
when you didn't show up for dinner.
Those kids look famished. Get them
water and electrolytes, stat.
And that gurney we just made out of
rope and wood, bring it in.
Had a hunch it would come in handy.
How did you find us?
Displacement and direction.
Just like you taught us.
[laughs] Good job, Tobey.
[chuckles]
John's potion will
be wearing off soon.
And it's back to our normal lives
where we are only responsible
for babysitting Rory and Gary.
I'd like to thank you for giving me
real childhood memories.
To be honest, these memories
have been kind of awful,
mostly awkward, but totally awesome.
I mean, it wouldn't be childhood
without all the above. [chuckles]
I'm happy it was with you.
And considering all the trouble
those kids went through for a kiss,
I'm guessing no childhood
would be complete without one.
Couldn't help but notice
our magical friend
is not where she's supposed to be.
[Zari] Oh, she's not?
Rory, do you know
anything about that?
[clears throat] You don't pay me enough
to be a stinking prison guard.
I don't pay you anything.
Well, I let the fake Amaya go.
- Why would you do that?
- [Sara sighs]
Oh, in order to...
Have an extreme makeover.
Thanks for the shtriga tip.
Well, if you had
your hands full with a shtriga,
I figured you'd need my help
with whatever you plebs face next.
Sounds like
a mutually-beneficial partnership.
One condition, though.
I never set foot in that cage
ever again.
Got it?
[Gideon] Mr. Constantine's body
is rejecting my treatments.
His odds of survival are bleak.
John, what you did out there
was pretty selfless.
I told you you were good.
That's not good for you.
Get some rest, John.
Gideon, give him the good stuff.
- [injection hissing]
- [groaning] Oh, Gideon.
That was nice, love,
we should party more...
[Ray] He's getting worse.
The magic he used to save
that camper was pretty powerful.
Well, if magic has him
on death's door,
then maybe magic can save him.
I think I know someone who can help.
But I have no idea how to find her.
[bubbling]
Just one final ingredient.
I trust you'll find
that my potion is magical.
Ugh! [spits]
You call that soup?
[gags and coughs]
Oh, I... I can start over.
The Ren fair opens in an hour.
You know what? Forget it.
It's not like folks come to this tent
for the food anyways.
I'm sorry?
They come for the lusty wenches.
[chuckles] I'm...
I'm a witch.
Okay. Well, as long as
it's a lusty witch, okay?
[theme music playing]