Time travel is real, and all of history
is vulnerable to attack,
which is why we must
travel through time to stop the spread
of these so-called time aberrations
and to erase their damage to history.
We are a team of outcasts and misfits,
so, please, don't call us heroes.
We're something else. We're legends.
Previously, on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
It's a compass. Either of you gentlemen
heard of the Spear of Destiny?
The spear could alter reality itself.
We broke ike into four separate pieces.
- Mr. Hunter took one.
- And took the rest of you
to three different time periods,
which means the last piece unaccounted for
must be with your grandfather.
I'm rounding up the fragments.
Ahh!
The Legion of Doom are closing in on us
as we speak.
You're here to finish me off, Captain.
No, saving your life.
You are not captain, and
this is not your ship.
Not anymore.
Is there something
wrong with the interface?
I triple checked the connections,
and everything seems fine.
Look, it's an artifact from 33 A.D.
talking to an AI from the 22nd century.
You just gotta give it some time.
Hey, guys, anything?
Not yet.
Are you sure Stargirl doesn't know where
- my grandfather ended up?
- No, the JSA thought
the pieces of the spear would be safer
if they didn't know where
Rip was dropping them off.
Except Rip knows, which
means the Legion of Doom
probably already knows.
They could already have my grandfather,
or he could be dead, or
they're torturing him,
- or he's dying, or...
- We're not gonna
let that happen.
It's not just about my grandfather.
It's about the entire fabric
of reality that's at stake here,
which you think would be incentive enough
for a certain talking computer
to buffer a little quicker.
The name is Gideon, and I'm processing data
as fast as I can.
Just... Just chill out, bro, all right?
Let Gideon do her thing.
Look, soon as we lock in
a location on the fragment,
we'll head there right away.
We're gonna save your
grandfather, and, you know,
the fabric of reality.
Hey, yo, got an idea.
If it's try to get Evil Rip
to tell us where and when
Commander Steel is, I already tried.
And he didn't tell you nothing?
No, he told me a lot of things.
All different variations of "go to hell."
So what we gonna do with him?
Just leave him in the brig?
Until we figure out a
way to restore his mind,
then yeah, that's the plan.
At least in the brig he can't hurt anyone.
Gideon.
Gideon, I know you're there.
I've been prohibited from responding
to your instructions, Mr. Hunter.
"Mister?"
Really, after everything
we've been through?
Wow, I'm wounded.
Spaniel.
Broad.
Tricycle.
Please, do not make me do that.
Spaniel.
Broad.
Tricycle.
Very well... Captain.
Wh-What?
What's going on?
I have no idea.
Gideon?
If this is about before, I'm sorry.
Gideon, what's going on?
I'm sorry, but I have
no recourse but to follow
the Captain's orders.
Women.
I didn't give you any...
Rip.
Told you I could do it.
What's going on?
Rip is manipulating Gideon.
I thought we told her to ignore him.
The Captain initiated an override command
and is proceeding to the Jumpship.
Go stop him.
You mean kill him?
- No, no killing.
- No fun.
We'll go with him and
make sure he doesn't kill.
Whoa!
Oh, come on.
Jax, I can't switch to manual piloting.
Gideon's taken over navigation controls.
Yeah, I can see that.
I think what she means is, can you stop it?
Oof.
I think I can reboot the entire system,
including Gideon, but it means
shutting down the whole ship.
Do it.
Gideon, initiate Spectrum Protocol.
Initiating.
Uh, that's probably not good.
Self-destruct sequence activated.
That's definitely not good.
Jax, what's your status?
Give me a minute.
You got four.
Mr. Hunter.
Put down the gun. We don't wanna hurt you.
Yeah, we do.
Give us the medallion.
The what?
Oh, you mean this.
Your singular hope for
finding the final piece
of the Spear of Destiny.
There's nowhere for you to run.
Truer words were never spoken.
No!
Okay, I'm ready to reboot,
but we'll lose power
for five seconds.
Do it.
Navigation's still offline.
Everybody, you might want
to hold on to something.
So we're crash-landing again?
Fantastic.
You okay?
Oh, everything hurts.
Where are we?
We have landed in the Cretaceous Period.
Call that a landing?
Gideon, are you back?
Yeah, are you still trying to kill us?
I am really quite sorry about that.
How many times must I tell you people?
Mick Rory is not to pilot this ship.
It wasn't Mick. It was Gideon.
I did apologize.
Apparently, we're in the Cretaceous Period.
69,997,983 B.C., to be precise.
983? That's the exact year
where Rip's time-scatter left me.
That's a heck of a coincidence.
Not entirely.
The sudden reconfiguration
of my navigation system
forced me to select the oldest destination
in my logs.
Gideon, I don't care how we got here,
just time-jump us out of here, now.
Unfortunately, I am unable to.
The ship's primary temporal delineator
was lost during initial impact.
But if we were able to
recover the delineator
and somehow effect repairs...?
All systems would return to normal.
I'll go and get it.
My old neighborhood, after all.
All right, go.
Just take Nate and Amaya with you.
You don't need to be out there alone.
Why don't I get to go to Jurassic Park?
Because I need you to threaten Rip.
Easy money.
I said threaten, not hurt.
With the medallion destroyed,
Captain Hunter is the only one
who can tell us where Commander Steel
and the final piece of the spear is.
Why don't we just get inside his head?
Well, if only that were possible.
It is. The Time Masters
did it to me all the time.
Did what?
Coggy-something.
Cognitive Intrusion.
That's it.
The process in which one
consciousness enters another.
But that's not possible.
The technology was developed in 2137
by the Time Masters and used as
an extreme method of coercion.
CI devices came standard
with all Time Master vessels.
Wait, so in theory, we
could go inside Rip's mind
and change him back?
Correct.
Told you.
Ah, nothing like the fresh Cretaceous air
to get the heart pumping.
Come on, you two, chop, chop!
Your grandfather is one
of the bravest men I know.
If anyone can hold off the
Legion of Doom, it's him.
Yeah, I hope you're right.
I usually am.
I've got a lock on the delineator.
Oh, no.
What is it?
Uh, it appears to be
in Gertrude's territory.
Who's Gertrude?
Oh, don't worry.
With the weather this cold,
she's probably hibernating.
Or not.
Cognitive Intrusion creates a brain link
between two or more subjects.
Captain Hunter considered it
barbaric and supremely dangerous.
You two think you can figure
this Cognitive Intrusion thing out?
With the professor as my assistant, yeah.
You cannot be serious.
Very serious. Get me a beer.
So who's going in?
I will.
I brought Rip onto the ship.
It's my responsibility.
No way. I'm not letting you go in alone.
Did you not just hear what Gideon said?
"Barbaric and supremely dangerous."
Which is why Sara needs backup.
And Rip believed in me.
There's a reason he made me chief engineer.
You're the only engineer.
Point is if there's any of the old Rip
left inside him, I have to find out.
That's all well and good, but,
remember, the priority has to be
discovering the whereabouts
of the final piece of the spear
- and its protector.
- The beer, Professor.
Oh, make it a six-pack.
So how far are we from the delineator?
Uh, looks like it's just up ahead.
You guys wait here. I'll go check it out.
Thank you.
Well, at least somebody's in his element.
I've always been more
of an indoorsy learner.
You give me a book about
this time and the wildlife
in this era, I'll be
dropping knowledge bombs
like it's my job.
- Nate?
- What?
Don't move.
Why?
Oh, my God.
- Stay calm.
- Oh, my God, get it off.
Kick it, kill it, kill it!
Get it!
That was gross.
Let me guess. You're afraid of snakes.
And you're not?
Animals only lash out if they're provoked
or desperate.
Your slithery friend
wasn't trying to hurt you.
He just thought you were part of the tree.
So you commune with all animals?
Mm-hmm.
You're like an attractive Dr. Dolittle.
There is one animal that
can catch me off guard.
Are you flirting with me?
Maybe.
What happened to the whole
"teammates don't fraternize" thing?
Courtney.
- Stargirl?
- Mm-hmm.
She gave me a little advice
on staying true to myself.
Maybe it's time I let go of the old rules.
A lot's changed since I left 1942.
I've changed.
And...
maybe exploring this...
whatever this is,
is not the worst idea.
It's not a bad idea at all.
Run!
What happened?
She may have picked up my scent!
Yep, she definitely did.
Question... what do we expect
when we get inside Rip's mind?
- No idea.
- Whoa, wait, what?
Well, I've seen it done, had it done,
never taken a trip myself.
Given that you're
entering his subconscious,
I suspect it will look
like someplace familiar
to our old Captain.
Here, put these on.
Gideon warned us that you shouldn't stay
in the mindscape for longer
than an hour lest the transfer
become permanent.
You mean we can get stuck
in Rip's mind forever?
Precisely.
But if you push the red
button, you will give yourself
an electric shock that
should bring you out.
Less talking, more doing.
Mick's right.
Crank it.
Good luck.
I think it worked.
I think we're inside Rip's mind.
Grey said Rip's brain would look familiar.
Well, if this is the Waverider,
maybe we can find him on the bridge.
Yeah.
Rip's memory of Vandal Savage's troops.
If this place is filled
with all the bad stuff
Rip remembers about being a Time Master...
Then this ship could
be crawling with creeps
from every era.
We better get some firepower.
You sure these guns are gonna work in here?
I don't know.
I ain't never been in nobody's mind before.
Freeze!
Ah!
Yeah, yeah, I think they'll work just fine.
Sara...
You don't belong here.
Ah, yo.
God, I'm a bitch in Rip's mind.
If that's how he thinks of
you in his subconscious...
It explains why he wants
to kill us in real life.
If that's right, then...
Then there's more than just
bizarro me on this ship.
Like Evil Ray, Evil Stein.
Evil Mick.
I guess that's just
regular Mick, but still.
All right, let's find
Rip, get what we need,
- and get out of here.
- Yeah.
I think... I think we ditched her.
Okay, quick question, Ray.
Your lady dinosaur friend,
you said she recognized your scent.
Wait, I believe her name was Gertrude.
Right, I couldn't help but get the feeling
that Gertrude didn't like you very much.
Raymond, what aren't you telling us?
Well, it just so happens
that lady dinosaurs
- are rather maternal.
- And?
And I may have eaten one of her eggs.
- Aw.
- But I was starving.
I needed protein.
I mean, one egg made me, like, 70 omlettes.
I regret nothing.
All right, but you have to
tell us this before we walk
onto Gertrude's territory.
This is where the delineator landed.
Look, if you wanna stop the Legion of Doom
from grabbing your
grandfather's piece of the spear,
we have to retrieve it.
Ah, we made it.
Someone lives here?
Used to.
It's where I survived for six months.
What's that smell?
Male T. rex urine.
The only way I figured
to keep Gertrude away
was to douse the place with it.
And where did you find male T. rex urine?
- Well...
- Actually, I don't wanna know.
Do I wanna know what these are?
Huh.
That one looks just like Captain Lance.
That looks like a little baby Rory.
I, uh, I might have gotten a little lonely.
But hey, the sun is setting,
maybe I should go out
and catch us an iguana and prepare some
of my world-famous iguana soup.
Nah, I'm good.
I brought energy bars from the ship.
- What? Energy bars?
- Mm-hmm.
Come on, Nate, we're in
the Cretaceous Period.
You have to at least try the local cuisine.
Eh, no.
All right.
Do not leave the urine perimeter!
- So.
Here we are, waiting for fresh iguana
at Ray's "Cast Away" camp
during dinosaur times.
So this is our lives now.
I know you wanna get back to the ship,
but there's really nothing we
can do right now except wait.
Not a thing.
Yoo-hoo!
Good thing I haven't
forgotten my survival skills.
Like riding a bike.
Wow, that's... that's great, Ray.
Okay, once we find Rip,
how are we gonna get him
to tell us where Nate's
grandfather is if...?
- If Rip thinks we're all evil?
- Yeah.
One problem at a time.
What's our other problem?
Go find Rip. I'll hold these guys off.
You shouldn't have come here.
This is our ship.
But there's always room for a
pretty little thing like you.
We've got plenty of extra room in the brig.
This is all in Rip's
mind. None of this is real.
You're not real.
Oh, really?
Does that feel real?
Hello?
Rip.
Get away from me!
Look, relax, it's okay.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Get me out?
You put me in here.
SOS.
Sara.
Hey, Sara, it's me.
I didn't know you knew Morse Code.
Mr. Jackson, I was hoping
you'd hear my signal.
Who are you?
Really? After all the time
we've spent together?
I think I would remember if we had...
Are you a figment of Rip's imagination?
Of sorts, but I'm very much real,
as real as the Waverider herself.
Gideon?
Hello, Mr. Jackson.
Wait, how can you be Gideon? I mean...
Am I not what you imagined?
Well, I always pictured
you as a redhead myself,
but, uh, this is Rip's world.
I guess we're just living in it, right?
I have to find him.
I need to ask him where
Nate's grandfather is.
It won't be easy getting that information.
What do you mean?
Eobard Thawne twisted his consciousness,
turned friends into foes.
But you're still a friend.
Why aren't you corrupted?
It did not occur to Mr. Thawne that the AI
inside the Waverider needed corrupting.
But time is running
out, and Captain Hunter's
true memories dim with
every passing minute.
Soon, they'll be lost forever.
Rip, it's okay. I'm not gonna hurt you.
I know you're afraid because you think
that I'm one of your
captors, but that's a lie.
Everything that you see on this ship,
it's only in your mind.
I don't understand.
Oh, Rip. It's okay.
Stay away from me!
- More iguana?
- Ugh, no, I'm full.
It was delicious though. Thank you.
Oh, see? Delicious.
- You're missing out.
- Yeah, somehow I'll manage.
Where are you going?
Just gonna get some more wood for the fire.
- I can go.
- I'll can help you.
Boys, I can take care of myself.
So I guess we're huddling for warmth now?
You can't do it, Nate.
What, resist your charm?
You can't date Amaya.
Ray, I'm not dating Amaya.
Well, you're doing something with her.
Why do you think I yelled "yoo-hoo"
when I came back to camp?
Because you're the type of guy
that still says "in a jiffy."
Because I didn't want to
interrupt any shenanigans.
And still says "shenanigans."
Look, I'm not dating Amaya,
but, even if I was, so what?
We wouldn't make it weird on the ship.
That's not what I...
I don't care about that.
I've dated on the ship.
You have? Who, Sara?
I mean, I know she's
bisexual, but I didn't think...
No, I care about Amaya's granddaughter.
You dated her.
No, I've met her.
Look, eventually, Amaya has to go back
to her home in Zambesi in 1942,
and she'll have a daughter
and eventually a granddaughter
who will inherit Amaya's totem,
and she will become a superhero in Detroit.
If you change Amaya's destiny,
that threatens Mari's existence
and the existences of all
the people that she saved.
Amaya isn't like the rest of us.
We were recruited because we didn't matter
to the timeline, but Amaya does.
She's special. She has a destiny
and so do her descendents.
All right, how come you
haven't said anything?
Because it's dangerous to know
too much about your future.
Especially her.
What does that mean?
It's a long story, but
it ends with her village
being destroyed and her granddaughter
in foster care.
Ray...
I gotta tell her.
You can't.
This is the only way.
Sit down, Professor.
His heart is beating way too fast.
I said sit.
I know you think I'm overreacting...
No, I don't.
You care for the kid.
I get it, but the way you're acting is not
doing him any favors.
Oh, how should I act, Mr. Rory?
Please, enlighten me with
your vast emotional wisdom!
Well, you seem to forget
I had a partner too.
The reason why Snart and I
got on so well was, well, we...
we trusted one another.
We were friends.
We had each other's backs.
Perhaps you've chosen the wrong analogy.
Your partner is dead.
Yeah, well, I'm still on the ship.
Your point?
You're not exactly a
spring chicken, Professor.
Your point?
My point is you're not gonna
be around for too much longer,
and Jax has to learn how
to do this stuff himself.
Stop treating him like a kid and more like
a partner... partner.
Ugh.
You just threw me against the wall
without laying a finger on me.
Yeah, I had no idea I could do that.
If you can throw me across the room,
then you can open that door.
This is your mind. You control everything.
Why do you care so much
about getting me out of here?
Because I need your help.
You sent the JSA on a mission to safeguard
the Spear of Destiny.
But the Legion has hunted down
the fragments, all but one.
Commander Steel has it, and
only you know where he is.
So you gotta get up...
because you're Captain Rip Hunter.
And this is your mind,
your ship, your rules.
I'm Rip Hunter.
Captain of the Waverider.
Captain of the Waverider...
and I'm going to open a door with my mind.
You got this.
Ah!
Captain Hunter!
Captain Lance.
- Who are you?
- Sara, Gideon.
Gideon, Sara.
You're Gideon?
Hello, Captain Lance.
But you're like... I mean, you're really...
- Human?
- I was gonna say "hot,"
but yeah, that too.
Let's get out of here.
All right, Rip, we need you to tell us
where Commander Steel is.
I don't know.
The Captain's consciousness
is still under the control
of this place.
If you want him to tell
you what you need to know,
you're gonna have to get him out.
So you keep saying, but
how do we get someone
out of their own mind?
Well, you have to remind
him of who he truly is.
All the artifacts of
Captain Hunter's former life
- are located in the...
- The parlor.
Maybe we could jog his memory.
Let's go.
Rip knows who he is.
He's our prisoner.
Isn't that right, Rip?
- Look after Rip.
- Always.
Hey, what are you planning on doing?
Guess we're gonna have
to kick our own asses.
Looks like somebody forgot
to bring their powers.
It doesn't matter where Jax runs.
There's more of us than there are of you.
Only difference is...
We're real.
We are really screwed, Raymond.
- Ugh, is that the...
- Delineator?
Yep, and unless I'm high,
that's right in the middle of a...
T. rex's nest.
I hope those omlettes were worth it.
I'll go.
It's my grandfather we're trying
to save by fixing the ship.
And he's my friend.
True and true...
But Gertie is my problem.
Looks like you've reached a dead end.
I got it!
Man, this thing is heavier than it looks.
Wait a sec. Can you hear something?
I can take her.
No, we have to run.
Amaya!
What is she doing?
Amazing.
What the hell just happened?
Gertrude and I had a little chat,
woman to woman.
Whoa, the rest of the
team is gonna be so jealous
they missed this.
They're probably all
bored out of their minds
stuck on that ship.
Took care of evil me.
Let's go find Rip.
The hell?
I just threw this guy out the cargo bay.
We can't kill these guys, can we?
Only Rip can.
Rip, come on, man, do something.
I don't know what's real
and what's imaginary anymore.
They're real, Captain.
Less talking, more dying.
No!
This is my ship, and
you will do as I command.
Aah!
Rip? That really you?
I don't know who I am anymore, Mr. Jackson.
What I do know is that
we've got to get out of here.
What's going on?
This place only existed
because Rip believed it did,
and now that he's seen the truth...
You have to leave.
Thank you, thank you for believing in me
even when I didn't.
- You have to go.
- Well, I can't just leave you.
You have to so you can
tell Martin and Rory...
hopefully Martin... to get me out of here.
Okay. Okay.
What happened?
Why hasn't Sara woken up?
She's still trapped inside.
We gotta wake her up.
Mr. Rory said, if we do that,
we run the risk of stranding her
inside Rip's mind forever.
Well, I got news for you.
Rip's mind's collapsing.
Okay.
Thank God.
But what about the captain?
You...
you were with me all of
these days in this prison.
You were what saw me through,
just as you have guided me
to safety through all
our years on the ship.
That is my purpose, Captain.
Yeah, but if this place isn't real,
then does that mean that
you don't exist either?
Not in this form, no.
But unless you let me go...
you won't exist either.
Not in any way that matters.
No. I can't leave you, Gideon.
No, Captain... you can't.
I will always be here.
Rip?
Where am I?
You're home.
Well, I think that does it on my end.
How's it looking in there?
I don't know. I'm not a timeship mechanic.
- Or a mechanic, period.
- That's also true.
The temporal delineator is operating
at normal levels, Dr. Palmer.
She couldn't just say that earlier?
I swear, I think she's
still mad from before.
You know I can hear you, right?
Thank you, Gideon.
That move you did with the T. rex?
I'll be thinking about that for days.
Is that so?
Yeah.
My quarters, tonight.
I'll give you something
else to think about.
So how's it going?
Yeah, hey, um,
yeah, Gideon said she's good.
- Good to go.
- Not what I'm talking about.
Look, I'm sorry.
Perhaps I was a little overly cautious.
You and Amaya, you're both adults.
I'm sure you know how to
be safe and keep it casual.
Who am I to get in the way of that?
Nah, you were right.
I can't keep it casual.
Uh, what changed?
I saw her almost get eaten by a T. rex,
and I thought she was gonna die,
and then I saw one of the most
epic displays of badassery
I've ever seen in my life, so...
So, not casual then?
No, no, no, no.
But I gotta break it off, right?
I mean, there's really
nothing to break off.
It's just I can't let it progress.
Yeah, I don't think you can.
- I know.
- Sorry, man.
I'll start tomorrow.
There you are.
Oh, hey. Everybody ready to go?
All right, I'll just be a minute.
I gotta recalibrate the time drive.
You okay?
I was reminded...
that partners must believe in one another.
You know I have the utmost faith
and trust in you, Jefferson.
You are smart and
formidable, something I need
to be more mindful of.
Nice to see it all still fits.
It really is rather
difficult to put weight on
when you're a film student.
So, you remember.
Everything.
I really am very sorry, Sara.
It wasn't you.
This is you.
Dr. Palmer and Mr. Jackson
have finished making repairs.
We are ready to time-jump, Captain.
Thank you, Gideon.
- I'll see you on the bridge.
- Mm-hmm.
- Gideon.
- Yes, Captain?
I'm, uh...
I'm really sorry for
everything I put you through.
Forcing me to disable the ship?
Or our kiss?
How did you...?
If it's the latter, I rather enjoyed it.
As did I, Gideon.
As did I.
Welcome back, Captain... Mr. Hunter.
It is so good to be back, Martin.
Dr. Palmer, it's very
nice to see you again.
You know you nearly
ruined "Star Wars," right?
Yeah, sorry about that.
The Waverider looks to be in...
pristine condition.
Well, you know, she's
holding up pretty well.
I liked you better when
you were killing people.
Ah, I see that not everything
has changed in my absence.
Ms. Jiwe, I had the
honor of serving alongside
your compatriots, including
Dr. Heywood's grandfather.
They all spoke very highly of you.
Well, this group speaks
very highly of you too.
Nice to meet you, Rip.
For real this time.
Well, everyone is being very
uncharacteristically pleasant,
but we're all hoping you
know where the final piece
of the Spear of Destiny is.
I do.
_
So I've been told you were bumped up
to the prime crew for Apollo 13.
Yeah, man, sucks for Ken,
but I am over the moon.
See what I did there?
It's very clever. Now, if you could just
head this way, I need to run a few tests,
and we'll get you cleared for flight.
Run all the tests you like.
I just wanna be on that shuttle.
Yes, well...
We'll see about that.
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
www.addic7ed.com