Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Only a weapon from hell
can eliminate a hell-spawned Encore.
We could use those.
Yeah, let's just get them
and get out of here.
The Loom of Fate
is one of the most powerful tools
in existence.
It gave my sisters and me control
over everyone's lives.
None of this is how it should be.
Screw the Fates,
stop being so obedient.
They're free.
Then I can't help them anymore.
- Stop it.
- We will rule.
But even I like the Blue Mush.
Bollocks.
The Fates are always watching.
The world is perfect.
What kept you, sister?
Oh, you know,
running a TV empire is not as easy
as snipping threads, sister.
I was skeptical when you pitched
the idea of the Legends on TV, but,
they've helped pacify the masses.
Well, should we get started then?
We don't want to
keep our worshippers waiting.
Any luck finding the Loom?
Yeah, I think we found it, all right.
Yeah, well,
our ride is still very much MIA.
So don't destroy the Loom
until we find the ship.
She has a weird voice, right?
You okay?
Acid reflux.
Too much Green Mush.
Ava better find that ship
because if we succeed,
then we're gonna have
three very angry Fates on our hands.
- Hey.
- God.
- You're all from the TV, right?
- Yes.
Can we get your autographs?
That depends.
How attached are you to your clothes?
Oh, my Fates.
It's the Legends.
Gary, Mona, you're okay.
It worked. You're out of the TV.
Okay, I've been dying to ask,
was I a Legend?
Or a lovable rogue,
or a Manic Pixie Dream Boy?
Time Dweeb.
Where is the Waverider?
Is that like the U.S.S. Faterider
on Star Trip?
Yeah, sure. Have you seen it?
No, but I bet
it's in the Forbidden Dump.
Well, that sounds ominous.
It's where we send
all the contraband items.
I know, because I work for the
Historical Sanitation Department.
Okay, great.
So, how would we infiltrate
this Forbidden Dump?
The Waverider better be here.
If we stay, we'll raise suspicion.
Good luck, teammates.
I don't get it, fuzzy dice,
waffle maker, massage chairs.
This is all like the good stuff.
Yeah, if you make life bleak enough,
people become so focused on survival
they forget they can revolt.
Start clicking, Mickey.
You're not allowed back here.
Yeah, for good reason. Now.
Oh, nice one, love.
Hope they have benefits.
Here.
- What do you need me in there for?
- You'll see.
All right, keep your eyes out
for any more guards
and let's get rid of these two.
Okay, okay take that one,
I'll take this one.
I hope I have benefits.
What is your request?
More Blue Mush, please.
We shall weave it
into the fabric of time
this afternoon.
Thank you.
Speak, child.
Can you put my shows back on TV?
Well, they'll be back in a tick.
The actors just need a bit of rest,
that's all.
Why?
Are they tired from the crossover?
What is a crossover?
The Legends are here.
Clotho, I have let you play
your childish game long enough.
It is time to grow up
and face the music.
The Legends are my friends.
Are they?
Time and again,
they have sown chaos into this world.
Well, sometimes they screw things up
for the better.
I mean, think about it, Encores,
that wasn't their fault.
And they've been mopping
that up all year.
That's true.
The Encores
are not the Legends' fault.
They're yours.
Ambitious villains are the product
of the chaos you birthed.
Look at these people now.
Do you see a future Joseph Stalin
amongst these lambs?
Of the three of us,
you always loved
these mortal creatures best.
What do you think they would want?
More choices...
or a lifetime of peace?
Peace.
Wise choice, sister.
I really wish
you could see this, love.
Well, I can feel it.
Well, it's beautiful.
Now, destroy it, once and for all.
All right. We found the Loom.
John's working on it as we speak.
I'm standing guard,
any luck finding the ship?
Yeah, we still haven't found it.
Mick, how do you know the batteries
in that thing even work?
For all we know, the Waverider,
could be anywhere in this mess.
Shut the front door.
- No.
- Do you hear that?
I helped you find the ship.
Now, I'm gonna find my kid.
Okay, Mick will be fine on his own.
A spell to destroy something
as powerful as this,
it requires
a considerable well of magic.
I played hooky at Hogwarts.
I learned magic the hard way, John,
in hell.
It's dangerous.
You're Natalie Logue's daughter,
aren't you?
Your mother,
she was a natural conduit for magic.
Her blood flows through your veins,
meaning that you're conduit as well.
Close your eyes and go with me,
all right?
Gideon, bring all systems online.
G, you there?
Guys, we have a problem.
There is no Gideon.
- Which means no flying.
- Damn it, Fates. Well played.
What would it take to get the ship
off the ground manually?
I mean, we need a superconductor
to transfer a huge surge of energy
to the time core.
We could look in the junkyard.
Or...
I have an idea.
You sure this is gonna work?
Honestly, I'm 60-40.
But I believe in you.
Sixty-forty?
And we haven't really caught up.
I don't know what you've been up to.
You spent a year in a Totem.
- I mean.
- Guys, can we just focus?
- I don't wanna do this.
- I know.
Steel up, now.
All's quiet on our end.
What do you guys see?
Sara, I've got eyes on Charlie Fate
and Hippie Mom Fate.
No sign of Psycho Fate.
Found her.
You bear the scars
from our last encounter.
My scars only make me stronger.
I need you to connect to your mother.
Think back
to the last time you saw her.
Feel your mother's power.
Let it flow through you.
(Foreign language)
Oh, that's good.
Now, harness your connection.
Are you going to Scarborough Fair
Parsley, sage, rosemary, and thyme
Remember me
To one who lives there
Mom.
It's working.
Natalie's helping us drain
its energy.
For once she was a true love of mine
I love you, Mommy.
My sweet girl, your mother is gone.
- No, no.
- No, no, no.
Forget her or you will never be
the powerful woman I know you can be.
No, no.
Your power comes from me.
I alone am its master.
My power comes from my team.
John, open the door.
Behrad, now.
If my power comes from you,
then maybe I can do this.
Ava, where you at?
Pulling up now.
Clotho, what have you done?
Go, go. Let's move.
I don't think
we can hold this altitude.
Jump the ship.
Do it.
Wait, when are we?
I don't know.
It's hard to see
through all this trash.
It's not trash.
They're some of history's
most iconic mementos.
I don't care what it is.
All I care
is that I can see this face.
Oh, I think my powers are gone.
Yeah, well,
your powers were bestowed by a God.
Once that God kicked the bucket,
then bye-bye powers.
Everything's back to normal?
There's only one way to find out.
Gideon is down,
gotta do it the old fashioned way.
- All right.
- Sounds good.
- All right, let's go check it out.
- All right.
Okay, this feels like an improvement.
All right, this says we jumped
a few months, okay.
Well, gives the world some time
to get back on track.
Hey, Fate,
what's the best way to work today?
The subway.
Hey, Fate,
what should I have for lunch today?
Two soups and a smoothie.
Hey, Fate,
should I ask Renee to marry me?
Hey, Fate, what do I buy my brother
for his birthday?
What are the chances
that everyone's watches
got a weird update
over the last four months?
I'd say one in a monkey's ass, love.
- Absolutely.
- Great.
So, not only do Charlie
and her sister
have the Loom back, but,
now it's wearable.
Don't let choices
get in the way of your destiny.
Trust in Fate.
With Fatewatch,
your link to the Loom.
Always connected.
I get the Fates rebuilt the Loom.
But how'd they put it in a watch?
Well, that's why we're breaking
into the bloody temple.
Get some answers.
- What the hell? It's a...
- History museum.
Can't be all that bad.
Well, certainly an improvement
on the Loom Temple.
"Welcome to The History Museum.
Here you will learn the truth
about free will
and the atrocities
it has brought upon humankind."
Atrocities?
"Join us as we examine
the tragedies of choice
and the horrors of our past,
that we shall,
with benevolence and Fate,
never suffer again."
So they went from trashing history
to weaponizing it.
But why?
Well, if we want to know
what happened in the past,
we certainly came to the right place.
All right, first up,
the Hall of Bad Ideas.
Ray has that suit.
What the hell is a shake weight?
You don't want to know, babe.
Cigarettes? Oh, come on.
Bloody cheek of them.
John, you died of lung cancer.
- Come on, you know they're right.
- Yeah.
- Nice.
- Okay.
What's "The Thong Song"?
- Seriously?
- "She had dumps like a truck,
truck, truck.
Baby, move your butt, butt, butt."
I think I'll sing it again.
Man, screw the Fates.
That is a spring break classic.
As a matter of fact,
I'll play it for you.
I don't give a damn.
- I just...
- No, you won't, come on,
we have to go
to the Hall of Villains.
Later, Sisqó.
Okay, other Z.
I just rerouted the nav system.
Anything popping up yet?
No, nothing yet.
Hey, try patching
into the secondary hard drive.
Maybe we can pull something up
from the backup.
Backup, backup.
Zari, come on, run.
Behrad.
Hey, you okay?
I don't know it's...
There were these guys,
A.R.G.U.S. agents.
They had guns.
Huge guns.
I thought they were gonna shoot you.
I must have smoked something way off.
I thought you were Zari.
I, I am.
No, I mean, totally, I know.
It's just...
- It's weird.
- Yeah, I, I know.
Tell me about it.
I'm hanging out with myself.
A myself that has hots
for John Constantine.
- You caught that, too?
- Yeah.
It wasn't something you smoked.
It happened, you told me to run,
and I did.
You didn't.
And then I died.
Every day since then,
everything I've done
has been to save you.
Whoa, this is like, really uncanny.
Wait a second, are,
are these villains ranked?
I don't know,
who do you have over there?
I got Vlad the Impaler,
but he's number 14.
Hey, if he's number 14,
who's number one?
Hey, Mick. You're okay.
What did you expect?
- You left me, us behind.
- Okay, calm down, please.
We were waiting for four months,
what took you so long?
Yeah, that's a question
for the other Zari.
Oh, book club lady.
What are you guys doing here?
Well, when you guys broke the Loom,
people panicked.
Suddenly, all these memories
came flooding back.
No one knew what was real.
Or what to do.
They were so used
to the Fates telling them.
So, Gary and Mona found me and Dad,
and we went into hiding.
- Hiding? Why?
- Because we're Legends.
- Yeah.
- And if you were listening
to what the Fates had to say,
we were...
"God Killers"?
I've been called worse.
Is it weird that I'm offended
that we're only number two?
Well, then who's number one?
Charlie.
No.
No, how, how did you...
You can't be here,
you have to leave right now.
What are you talking about, Charlie?
It's over. You have to come with us.
No, Fate says to stay.
Fate, Fate says...
She's gonna kill you
if she finds you.
You have to get out while you can.
Charlie, I'm sorry,
but you'll thank us later. John?
- (Foreign language)
- No.
Charlie.
Hey, it's okay.
You're home, Charlie.
No.
No, no, no, I have to go back.
She's gonna know.
Where's my watch? I need it.
That's how the Loom
tells me what to do.
Why the hell do you listen
to that thing, Charlie?
Because I never should have destroyed
the Loom to begin with.
I mean, greed and war.
Human suffering?
All those Encores we were up against,
that's all on me.
I'm the Loom breaker.
- I'm the creator of chaos.
- Charlie.
That used to be
a badge of honor for you.
What happened?
We left. That's what happened.
You know, Charlie,
you were left all alone.
It's no wonder
Lachesis got into your head.
Lachesis, she's my family.
And family sticks together.
Hey, we are your family,
and we're here now, all right?
Charlie, what happened?
Lachesis rebuilt the Loom.
She saved everyone.
She restored the peace.
I replaced my own mother, John.
Well, summoning a ghost
can be difficult,
even under the best of circumstances.
No, I mean in hell.
I was terrified, helpless.
Lachesis found me, she took me in.
But the price for her protection
was my humanity.
She trained me to let go of anything
that made me feel.
And so I had to forget the person
I had loved the most.
You were just a kid.
Trying to survive is all.
But I wanted to forget.
I saw what happened
to good people down there,
and I swore that would never be me.
Listen to me, all right?
You are still her daughter.
Whose?
Natalie?
Or Lachesis?
Okay, I know you think free will
is a bad, scary thing.
So, we did a little dumpster diving
to give you some counterpoints.
Two words. The Beatles.
All right,
they taught an entire generation
that even during war and tragedy,
we can still make beauty.
Whilst also inspiring
Charles Manson to commit
some of the most brutal murders
in history.
Also, they let Ringo sing a song
about an octopus.
- Damn it, okay.
- Okay.
Just get out of the way.
Mamma Mia 2,
a celebration of free love,
reckless abandon
and following your bliss.
Even if that bliss means creating
a two-hour ABBA-palooza
where Cher plays Meryl Streep's mom.
Weren't the Legends almost murdered
by Napoleon because of ABBA?
Two words.
"Octopus's Garden."
Gary, no.
Would this have happened in a world
without free will?
I mean, seriously, Charlie, look,
I'm a clone,
- for God's sake.
- She's a clone.
You don't think it, anyway,
think about all the people
on this ship.
Think about how they came
to be together.
Yeah, Nate's crazy conspiracy theory.
Mick's turn
as a futuristic bounty hunter.
Zari and B's dystopian future.
You in that disco outfit.
Hey, come on, Charlie.
We were all in our own worlds,
but a twist in our stories
brought us together
and made us a family.
But humanity,
they've made so many mistakes.
Sometimes a mistake
is really just destiny.
What, you learn that being a Paragon?
No, I learned that being a person.
So, what do you think?
Can we track the Loom signal
with that thing?
Yeah, I just need
an external computer,
something with GPS and Wi-Fi.
Well, that's perfect.
Hey.
We all make sacrifices
for the greater good.
Oh, really? How much THC is running
through your system right now?
I'm self-medicating
for my Loom anxiety.
You know,
the brain processes phone screens
and drugs the same way.
That's why they're both so addicting.
All right, the Loom's signal's coming
from somewhere inside the building.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
John, other me.
We're gonna have to go
floor by floor.
Well, it's a dodgy spot
for the Loom of Fate.
You know, I've hosted many
an exclusive party
in a place like this.
The antithetical
keeps the riffraff out.
Hiding in plain sight.
Bloody brilliant.
Also, you can do whatever you want
and no one needs to know.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
Oh, God, this is weird.
All right, no windows, thick walls...
That's where I'd stash my artisanal,
- world altering apparatus.
- All right.
Guys, I think we found it.
I'm the worst.
Timing is impeccable.
Sara, we got to the Loom,
but there is no Loom.
Blimey.
Gideon.
Gidget.
Currently running Fate protocol.
I cannot be interrupted.
She's controlling everyone
with Gideon.
The watches,
they're just running a program
telling everyone what to do.
Wait. So there, there is no Loom?
We actually destroyed it.
Yeah, all we have to do
is shut down the network.
What, and inspire panic
when Fate abandons everyone
all at once?
You know,
my sister was right about you lot.
You shoot first
and play doctor later.
It won't matter anyway.
Lachesis will find another way
to keep her hooks in
- because that is what she does best.
- Okay, fine.
So we just expose her
for what she really is.
She's a fraud,
we take her down a notch,
show everybody
that she can't control them anymore.
Yeah.
Charlie, she's your sister.
You're the only person
that can stand up to her.
I'm sorry.
I can't help you.
The museum is now open.
For centuries after my sister broke
the Loom of Fate,
the world was filled with pain.
Boo.
Horror.
Outrageous hubris and brutality.
Chaos.
But I could not let people suffer
any longer.
Alone, I rebuilt the Loom
and imprisoned my sister,
so that now and forever,
you may live in peace.
Here she is.
Loom breaker.
Creator of calamity.
Do you accept your fate?
No.
What did you say?
I said no.
Your story is a load of crap.
Astra.
Where is Clotho?
That was always the question,
wasn't it?
Did you ever love me,
or were you just looking
to replace your sister?
You wanted a mother.
I had a mother.
A woman who understood
that to love someone
you have to set them free.
Shut your mouth, dear,
before you say something you regret.
Make me.
Come on, all powerful Fate, smite me.
Strike me down.
Yeah.
That's what I thought.
Why should these good people
listen to you?
Because she's telling the truth.
Take forever.
How's it looking, Zaris?
I need to get into her mainframe
to shut her down.
This might take a minute.
You tricked everyone
into giving up their freedom
by making them afraid of the past.
That's rich.
Coming from some of history's
most notorious criminals and killers.
Shame, shame, shame.
- Shame.
- All right.
Yes, you're right.
We've made mistakes,
but sometimes things get messed up
for the better.
Take Marie Antoinette, for instance.
Her indifference
caused a revolution in France.
It gave them democracy.
Look, if you listen to her,
your stories are over.
They're right, don't listen to me.
Listen to the Loom.
Come on, Zari.
Okay, I made it past
the first firewall.
Wait, is that...
Very well.
If it's chaos that you want,
chaos you shall have.
That's more like it.
(Foreign language)
That's our move.
They stole our move.
Enjoy your free will, Legends.
Stalin? Caligula?
If they get out,
they'll destroy the city.
Okay, you got any ideas, Cap?
Just a lot of bad ones.
Let's go save the world.
This thing right here
Is letting all the ladies know
What guys talk about
You know
The finer things in life
Check it out
Ooh, dat dress so scandalous
And ya know another
Couldn't handle it
See ya shaking that thang
Like who's da ish
With a look in ya eye so devilish
Ya like to dance
At all the hip-hop spots
And ya cruise to the crews
Like connect da dots
Not just urban, she likes the pop
Because she was living la vida loca
She had dumps like a truck
Truck, truck
Thighs like what, what, what
Baby, move your butt, butt, butt
I think I'll sing it again
She had dumps like a truck
Truck, truck
Thighs like what, what, what
All night long
Let me see that thong
Baby
That thong th-thong thong thong
- You again?
- I see your manners
have not improved,
you smelly peasant.
Thief.
Listen, that girl so scandalous
And I know another couldn't handle it
And she shakin' that thang
Like who's da ish
I liked you better
when you were a coin.
Ya like to dance
At all the hip hop spots
And she cruise to the crews
Like connect da dots
Not just urban, she like the pop
- Not again.
- Because she was living la vida loca
She had dumps like a truck
Truck, truck
Thighs like what, what, what
Baby, move your butt, butt, butt
- I think I'll sing it again
- (Foreign language)
Thighs like what, what, what
- All night long
- These brats just won't stay dead.
Let me see that thong
- Because they're not hell weapons.
- Baby
Show it to us
That thong th-thong thong thong
- Oh, thank God.
- Come on.
You gotta get over yourself.
So, 49 percent of life is crappy.
Fine, 51 percent isn't.
And that's the two percent
that's worth fighting for.
And how can you be so sure?
Because I am that two percent.
I'm the product of complete
and utter chaos.
My dad time-traveled
to his high school reunion,
and then slept with his ex
in a broom closet.
I don't think it gets
much more chaotic than that.
And then, he tried to erase you
from existence.
But out of all of that insanity,
I got a dad,
and I love him.
And life is messy,
but that's what makes it beautiful.
You want to go make a real mess?
- We can't let them out.
- Can't keep them in.
Then why not destroy them?
Now, grab a hell weapon,
and let's drop the curtain
on these bloody Encores.
Hey, need a hand?
Should have been here with you.
You're wild and unpredictable,
just how we like you.
Guess it's time for me to stand up
to my sister once and for all.
Well, then you're gonna need this.
Good luck, Captain.
Gideon, reboot Fate protocol.
Gideon?
It's over, Lachesis.
Our whole lives, you humiliated me.
You made me feel so small.
I tried to run away
and you hunted me down.
What do you want?
And all that time...
I thought that I needed
your forgiveness.
But it turns out,
it's you who needs forgiveness.
I forgive you.
You who have left me with nothing.
I gave you back your power.
I gave you back your immortality.
When you destroyed our Loom,
we all lost that gift.
I was a God.
Now, I'm...
I'm nothing.
You're not nothing.
You're a human.
And that means
that you only have one life to live.
Now, don't go wasting that
trying to keep everything
under your control.
All right, that should do 'er.
(Foreign language)
- What's she doing?
- English detected. Hello.
What is your name, Captain?
Captain? I like that.
Working on Gidi without me?
We tried comming you this morning,
but you didn't answer.
Broken eye contact, flushed cheeks.
I mean, that's not fair.
I can't keep a secret from myself.
What are we keeping a secret?
Well, bro, when a man and a woman
love each other very much...
Are you talking about sex with Nate?
That's not a secret.
Now, you and John, that's a secret.
- Behrad?
- Behrad, nice.
Hey, what's...
- What's happening?
- It's fine, I'm...
You're not fine, you're bleeding.
It's me.
By being here,
I'm causing a temporal disturbance,
and it's killing you.
What does that mean?
It means
there's two timelines fighting
for control of Behrad's life,
and in mine, you're dead.
I have to go back in the Totem.
- No way.
- Behrad-jan...
It's my turn to save you.
Can I text you in a Totem?
Oh, no,
there's no technology allowed.
Not even like a pager.
I'm gonna miss you,
so much.
Me too.
You know I have to do this, right?
Yeah.
I just wish...
I wish I was leaving you with some...
something.
You, you are, and you have, I mean...
I lost everything at Heyworld.
All of our memories.
But you brought those back to me.
And now I get to remember
the woman I love forever.
No regrets.
Hey.
It's not fair.
- I will just call you back.
- Yeah.
There has to be something
that we can do.
You already did.
You found me and brought me home.
- Wait, there are two of them?
- Mick.
So, how are you gonna get back?
Totem Master, remember?
Bye, guys.
I need so many drinks.
Yeah.
I know the perfect place.
We're The Smell.
Now, welcome to the best show
of your lives,
you wankers.
Welcome to my cul-de-sac, friends
That's a street that ends in a circle
The thing about circles
Is they never end
So our friendship will be universal
It's Mr. Parker's cul-de-sac
- Mr. Parker's cul-de-sac
- Weren't they dead?
- I mean, who hasn't died?
Hey, finally some time travel.
I can't believe Charlie
is the lead singer of The Smell,
that's insane, they're my favorite.
Them and The Runaways.
We can go see them next.
It's a school night,
how about the weekend?
- Mr. Parker's cul-de-sac
- Yeah.
Mr. Parker's cul-de-sac
- Excuse me, boss.
- Mr. Parker's cul-de-sac
So, what's next for you, love?
I guess I'll give life above ground
a fair shot.
New York? Paris? Tokyo?
I was thinking about
this haunted house out in the sticks.
- Were you, now?
- So let's run this thing together
I got my rent covered.
I'm Mr. Parker's cul-de-sac
- Finally.
- Mr. Parker's cul-de-sac
- All right, then. Cheers.
So, what, you're looking for
A friend that's new?
I've always wanted a friend like you
Welcome to my cul-de-sac, friends
It's a street that goes on forever
A friendship is family without end
So let's run this thing together
I'm Mr. Parker's cul-de-sac
Mr. Parker's cul-de-sac
That's my girl.
Guys, guys, guys,
I could taste the moon.
And that's enough for the evening.
All right, all right.
We came, we partied, we conquered.
And now, it's time to go,
it's time to go home.
Home.
Actually, guys...
I think this is the end of the line
for me.
- Well.
- Wait, what?
For reals?
Yeah, it's time for me
to just stay put for once.
And set down some roots.
All right. Well...
if you ever need anything,
and I mean anything,
you know where to find us.
Thanks, Captain.
Once a Legend...
Always a Legend.
Thank you.
Well, come on, all of you.
Get in here.
I love you.
I'm really gonna miss you guys.
Miss you.
All right, go on. Get out there.
Go and enjoy your vacations.
You've earned it.
Vacation.
- Vacation.
It's vacation.
- I'm gonna go to a spa.
- I like...
I think I'm gonna text Dion,
- or is that too desperado.
- This is why I don't have a phone.