Previously on
Legends Of Tomorrow...
Sara can never find out the truth
about Ava.
- I'm a...
- You're a clone.
I'm a future clone thing?
The first Totem bearers
imprisoned a great evil.
And time is his cage.
If you cannot
defeat me in this vessel,
how will you stop me once
I've assumed my true form?
Our family's destruction
looms in 1992.
You promised you'd save us.
Kuasa.
Gideon, set a course.
I have to save my family.
Code 131, all hands on the bridge.
What's going on?
Yeah, I gotta get
back to Lord of the Rings.
You read?
Code 131.
Come on, guys, I wrote a whole memo.
Yeah, nobody read it.
- I did.
- Thank you, Ray.
Pancakes for breakfast.
No, 131 is not...
- Is it?
- Yeah, does that mean no pancakes?
Anyway, I wrote a song to help us
remember all the codes.
It goes like this, from the top.
If the code is 111
Mallus escaped the time dungeon
If the code is 112...
All right, Nate, just tell us.
Someone stole the Jumpship.
Where's Amaya?
Uh, according to
the Jumpship logs,
Zambesi, 1992.
Right before the warlords
destroy her village.
And she dies.
The old her, that is.
Whoa, the temporal zone
is getting real choppy.
Yeah, the timeline was crumbling
even before Amaya
decided to change history.
If that happens, the Darhks
will be able to free their demon.
Oh, well, I better get back to my movie.
And we better stop Amaya
before she does something reckless.
Gideon, plot a course for...
Pardon me, Captain Lance,
but we are receiving
an urgent call from Mr. Hunter.
- You good?
- Gideon, put him on.
The Bureau needs back-up.
Grodd's going after Barry.
Well, that explains
the time turbulence.
Flash is always in trouble.
It's kind of his thing.
Not that particular Barry.
Barack Obama,
it will almost be
an honor to kill you.
All right, people, we're dealing
with two anachronisms now,
Zambesi and young Obama.
Wally, Nate, I want you guys
to go talk some sense into Amaya.
You mean, convince her to stand down
while her village and family
is torn apart?
What if I use my temporal
simulator to find some loophole
that Amaya can use
to help save Zambesi?
All right, do it.
The rest of us, we're on Obama care.
You will not escape.
Grodd will complete his mission.
Time to make America Grodd again.
Clearly you have some grievances.
But perhaps we can look for
a common ground.
Whoa!
Or not.
Finally, the cage is breaking.
I can feel his arrival.
Oh, goody.
Yes. Resist.
You will only prolong your suffering.
Should've wasted
your hairy ass in 'Nam.
Run, Barry, run.
A hairless ape
who fights with fire.
How primitive.
No!
Nora. Nora, honey.
Are you okay?
We were so close.
My master was escaping his bonds.
What happened?
Grodd's mission must have failed.
I mean, that could be a good thing.
It gives you and me time to figure
what the big guy's
arrival really means.
It means the end of history,
a chance for us
to live as gods.
As gods?
You know,
that sounds fantastic and all,
but what I just saw,
it seems like there won't be a you
anymore. It'll just be him.
That's what we always wanted.
Isn't it?
Totally.
100%.
You know, I'm just gonna
check on our grumpy gorilla
and see how he screwed this thing up.
I'll see you later.
No, you won't.
Of course.
'Cause once I complete
Grodd's mission, you will be gone.
What I meant to say was
I'll see Mallus later.
Goodbye, Nora doll.
Grodd will destroy you.
You're dead!
Nice work.
Let's get him back to the ship.
Yeah. Come on, teeny tiny Grodd.
I think we still have some chew toys
leftover from the saber tooth tiger.
Nice to meet you.
I'm a PhD student
doing history research.
- Andy Watkins.
- No one cares about the cover story.
Shut up, Darren Applebottom, talent
scout for the New York Knicks.
What are you doing here?
Preventing the genocide
of my people tomorrow.
We know, we're here to stop you.
Peacefully.
Look, Amaya.
I know you're upset about
what happened to Kuasa,
and all I can say is I am...
I'm truly sorry.
I don't blame you for
my granddaughter's death, Nathaniel.
I blame the warlords
who draw closer by the minute.
And I intend to stop them.
So stay out of my way.
I must say, it has been
such an honor, Barack.
Oh, I go by Barry.
I really like Barack.
Well, Barack is what
it says on my birth certificate.
Yeah, you might wanna
hold on to that.
So, what's the back-up plan?
Well, according to Ray's song,
this is a code 222.
What's that?
It means we're screwed
no matter what we do.
All right, crisis averted.
And a new one's just begun.
You're not getting Obama.
I'm not here for him.
I'm here for my daughter.
And I need your help.
I assure you this is
completely unnecessary.
I come, as they say, in peace.
And I, they say,
think you're full of crap.
I'm a changed man, Sara.
The only change I wanna see you
go through is from alive to dead.
Ray, how are we doing
with Constantine's spell?
Just need one more
splash of bat spleen.
Sorry, bat. And that should do it.
Maybe I missed an ingredient.
Your ankh symbol, it's upside down.
Uh...
- No, it's not.
- Yes, it is.
No, it's not.
Ooh, I knew it'd be difficult
to get you guys to trust me.
Mmm, try impossible.
Which is why I brought
this gesture of good faith.
The Water Totem?
I borrowed it from my daughter after
she ripped it from Kuasa's chest.
Sorry about that, by the way.
Do you guys mind if
I give you a hand with this?
You seem to be struggling a bit.
Yeah? Okay, great.
Cool.
Uh, now, try to choke me.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- You can't.
- Satisfied?
Yeah.
That Water Totem's
gotta be worth something.
With all six, you guys might actually
have a chance against Mallus.
You mean the same demon you've been
creating anachronisms to release?
That was before I realized
what our partnership would cost me.
- Nora...
- Dies the moment the demon escapes.
Now I know this might
rankle you a bit, Sara,
but our interests are aligned.
We can save Nora and
stop Mallus from being freed
together.
- No.
- Excuse me?
Rory, kill him.
No, no... Wait, wait, wait.
Okay, look.
I know Damien has done
terrible things in his past,
which cannot be forgiven, but
I know that he loves his daughter.
We can't just kill him.
He was already dead. Killing him
would be repairing an anachronism.
So would incarcerating him
in the Bureau.
I agree with Rip.
We need to think through
this situation rationally.
Boss?
Stand down.
Glad to see you came to your senses.
Think this makes us
straight, you're wrong.
What are we even doing here, man?
We need to stop Amaya,
not party with the village.
There she is.
Okay. Great, let's get her out of here.
Not our Amaya.
That Amaya.
What's wrong?
Nothing, it just means
my Amaya comes back to Zambesi.
And we don't grow old together.
For thousands of years,
the Anansi Totem
has been in my family,
and tonight, it is my great joy
to pass this Totem
down to my own daughter.
Make way
for the new protector of Zambesi.
Esi.
Kuasa,
where is Esi, child?
I'm sorry, Nana Baa,
but Mother isn't coming.
My daughter
has chosen to reject
her destiny and her duty.
I am sorry.
We have come here for nothing.
Come on.
Amaya.
What just happened?
My daughter rejected the Totem.
You sound more excited
than I thought you'd be.
Esi never bonded with the Totem.
This is why the warlords were
able to destroy my village.
You think you can convince Esi
to be a Totem bearer.
She'll protect the village tomorrow.
She'll protect Kuasa.
Everything will change.
That's the problem.
I saw what happened with Barry Allen
when he went back and
stopped his mother's murderer.
A little thing called Flashpoint.
We can't change history. I'm sorry.
Tell her, Nate.
Nate?
I can't believe I'm gonna say this,
but screw history for once.
Okay, so you go
talk to your daughter,
and I'll go talk to you.
The older you.
You always had a way with her.
Come on.
Wait, we're doing what?
So, listen.
Are you okay?
The hardest thing I ever had to do
in my life was to let Darhk live.
And now he's back.
And it is taking every
ounce of self-control
not to kill him.
And I keep asking myself
why?
For the good of the mission.
"For the good of the mission."
Listen to yourself,
you sound like some
- government...
- Clone?
I was gonna say stiff.
You know, Rip thought I could
talk some sense into you, but maybe...
Wait.
You're here because of Rip?
Why would you do
anything for that man?
Ava, he lied to you.
He implanted
false memories into your head,
he hired actors
to pretend to be your parents.
I mean, what more is it gonna
take to get you to confront him?
I am prioritizing the mission
over my own personal baggage.
You and your team
should try it sometime.
No.
That's not what you're doing.
You're covering,
because you're afraid of
what you might find out.
What else is there to find out, Sara?
I'm one of thousands.
I was grown in a lab.
There has to be
more to the story, Ava,
and you deserve to know.
Look, you need...
You need to
talk to Rip now.
Ah!
I could do with a wee nip myself.
Everything good, Director Sharpe?
Peachy.
Are we good to transport Mr. Darhk
back to the Bureau?
No, Rip, we're not.
Where are you going?
To go talk to someone
who can think straight
when the whole world has gone crazy.
So what you're saying is
you won't aid
the man that killed your sister
even if it'll prevent
Mollusk from escaping...
Mallus.
...from escaping his
interdimensional prison,
and wreaking havoc across time?
Yeah, when you put it that way,
it does sound kind of petty.
Not at all. It sounds...
It sounds human.
Okay.
But then what, I'm just
supposed to hand Darhk over
to Ava and let
the Time Bureau deal with him?
Your ex is clinging to
rules and regulations
in the face of the startling
revelation that she is...
I'm sorry, a clone, was it?
But here's the thing.
I'm not convinced
the Bureau is
best equipped to stop a demon.
No, it sounds like
that calls for a much more
unorthodox approach.
I really miss you.
Oh, hi, guys.
I do hope you're not feeling
all killy, killy, stabby, stabby.
I want you to listen to me carefully.
I don't believe for
a second that you have changed.
You're still the same
cowardly son of a bitch
that put an arrow in my sister.
But I will work with you
to defeat Mallus under one condition.
After this is over,
I'm putting you back
in the ground where you belong.
Deal.
Huh.
So, do any of these flashing
screens actually do anything?
Focus, Damien,
how do we capture
your demon daughter?
If we coordinate a strike between
the Legends and the Time Bureau,
we might be able to take it out.
How did that work
for you in Victorian London?
Besides, my little angel's
only gotten more powerful since.
What if we just ask Nora nicely?
I did have a bit of
a connection with her in Berlin.
Not that kind.
All right, maybe she'll
listen to her dear old dad.
Not anymore.
Nora only listens to Mallus now.
He's always in her ear.
That's it. What if I got inside Nora?
Not like that.
What if I shrunk down,
flew into her ear,
and pretended to be Mallus?
Okay, new guy on the team here,
is that a joke plan or a real plan?
We are so screwed.
No, this could work.
We just have to
convince her that it's actually him.
This is how you
would serve your city?
You would risk its utter ruin?
That's it.
I did what I judged
to be right.
What you judged to be right.
You sent the ring
of power into Mordor
in the hands of a witless halfling.
Well, the vocal similarity
to Mallus is uncanny.
Quiet!
Gideon? Who is that actor?
And how can we get him
without dealing with his agent?
Mr. Noble, uh, we have
some, uh, last minute rewrites.
Tell Peter Jackson no more chickens.
Huh?
I had four this morning. Hmm.
So what's up, mate?
Yeah, so the rewrites
are from Peter, and he'd like me to, uh,
run the lines with you.
You're kidding.
Okay.
Uh, let's see.
"Nora, you must heed my command."
Okay, that's good.
- Who's Nora?
- Nora?
Nora, she's a new character that, um...
They wanted to beef up
the female presence in the film.
You can't do that, mate.
It's Tolkien. Lord of the Rings.
Right, right, but it's a studio note.
Oh, studio note. Very good, now I care.
Yeah, from the top.
Mmm.
"Nora, you must heed my command."
Uh, "What is it, Master?"
"Go to the Waverider, Nora."
"I cannot go to the Waverider."
"The Totems are ripe
for the picking."
This is crap, isn't it, eh?
- Oh, well...
- I mean, who wrote this?
- I mean somebody...
- Don't worry about it.
Don't worry about it.
"The Totems are ripe
for the picking."
"Your father will lead you to them."
"My father?"
Esi.
Who are you?
I am a distant cousin.
I came for the ceremony.
Sorry to disappoint you.
I love it here.
When I was a child, I'd come here
and lose myself in the stars,
think about where my life would lead.
For as long as I can remember,
the Anansi Totem
has been my destiny.
But now, I'm not sure I want it.
You wouldn't understand.
Try me.
My mother
is the great Amaya Jiwe.
She's protected
our village her entire life.
She never doubted,
never wavered.
That's not true.
Every Totem bearer
starts their journey with doubt.
Even your mother.
I will never live up to her legacy.
You have her strength
and the strength of
all others who've come before her.
But there is danger coming.
And your people need you
to stand up for them.
All right, you ff-thoom
into Amaya's hut,
grab the Totem,
and we'll give it to her daughter.
Nate, now that you have
some space from her,
I need you to come to your senses.
Amaya can't see that.
She's too close,
but she's going to cause
more harm than good
if this releases Mallus.
- We don't know that.
- We do.
You do.
I can't not help her, Wally.
I love you, man, but I will stop you
if you take this too far.
Like stealing candy
from a very old baby.
Oh.
Ah!
Amaya, wait, it's me.
You know, I didn't think
this would do it for me,
but actually it kinda does.
Who are you?
It's me, Nate.
Who?
Nate.
I know it's been a while, but we
used to travel through time together,
you know, do other things.
If this is some kind of a joke...
It's not a joke. I have pictures
of us on my phone.
Ow!
This is me.
Of course.
You really don't remember, do you?
How is this possible?
You were part of a bitchin' team that
traveled through time together.
I mean, the 1942 you.
Why are you here, time traveler?
To keep my promise to you.
By making sure your daughter, Esi,
gets the Spirit Totem tonight.
She didn't even show up
to her own ceremony.
Her head is always somewhere else.
She doesn't know what she wants.
Yeah, you had a hard time
figuring that out too
when you were her age.
But look, if Esi believed
you were truly in her corner,
she wouldn't doubt herself.
She would accept
the Totem and be unstoppable.
Just like you.
Uh, hey there, Nora doll.
Why am I still here?
Why is the master still in prison?
You failed me!
I know, it's terrible.
The Legends captured Grodd,
and this whole Obama thing
is just not working, so perhaps,
Mallus can advise us
as to what to do next.
Mallus
only speaks when he desires.
I can't just summon him.
Well, maybe we'll just
wait here until he gets the itch.
Nora, you must heed my command.
It's him. He's speaking to me
very loudly.
Really? Mallus is speaking to you?
Shh, I need to concentrate.
Go to the Waverider, Nora.
The Waverider? Why?
The Totems are ripe for the picking.
Your father will lead you to them.
My father?
What? Mallus has plans for me?
I wonder what those are.
The Legends' ship.
The master wants you to take me there.
Oh, I would in a heartbeat,
but we are hopelessly
outnumbered, honey.
There's just no...
He must take you there now, Nora.
Do it! Dad, do it! Don't be a fool.
No problemo. Let's go.
Those Totems should be
around here somewhere.
You.
What is this?
I'm sorry, sweetheart,
but it's for your own good.
No.
No!
I get it.
You think that I failed you
because I joined with the Legends
and trapped you here.
Well, you're right. I did fail you.
But that's not how.
I was a terrible father.
I was obsessed with world domination.
Because of that,
I died.
Leaving you all alone as a child,
trapped with my name
and my foolish dreams.
Oh, I turned you into
a demon long before Mallus did.
That's why I'm begging you,
do not let him take you away from me.
Your daughter is long gone.
No!
I know you can hear me. Fight him!
Oh, there was no fight.
Her soul,
her flesh
were freely given.
You sick son of a bitch.
One more alteration to the timeline,
and my cage crumbles.
I can't believe that worked.
I can.
Sara knows what she's doing.
I may have my flaws,
but I do know how to pick
the best people for the job.
So why did you pick me?
What? Come on.
Brilliant mind, calm demeanor,
incredible strength,
and unlike the Legends,
you actually follow rules.
It almost sounds like
I was made for the job.
What are you getting at?
I know I'm a clone, Rip.
I see.
So why me, hmm?
Of all the clones in 2213,
why did you pick me?
You're special.
So why'd you erase my memory?
I thought it would be easier.
Easier?
Easier for you, or easier for me?
Don't lose focus, Ava,
you are too critical to this mission.
Well, the good news is, if I die,
you can just skip off to 2213
and get yourself another clone.
Oh, my God.
I wasn't even the first one, was I?
We both know how hard it is
to find agents as talented as you.
And to find one
who's also replaceable is invaluable.
How many?
You're the 12th.
The 12th?
So I wasn't even your first choice.
- Or your second, or...
- You don't understand.
- You are exceptional.
- Don't, Rip.
Just don't.
Nora's gone.
It's just Mallus now.
You must be enjoying this.
Seeing your nemesis with a broken heart.
I didn't know you
had a heart to break.
Where was it the night
you murdered my sister?
Look, what I did was unforgivable.
But back then
I hadn't loved anyone enough
to understand the pain that I caused.
Not that it's any comfort,
but if I could take it all back,
I would.
We all have regrets.
But we can't undo
the things that we've done.
True.
But even the worst of us
can be made whole again.
You, for example.
League to Legend, killer to Captain.
That's not a bad makeover, is it?
It's not good enough.
Why?
Because you put on the Death Totem
and almost killed your entire team?
- Yes.
- But you didn't.
Did you. And you know why?
The same reason I'm spilling my guts
to a woman who's imagined
my death 1,000 times over.
More like 10,000.
Love,
Sara.
'Cause without it, people like us,
we're left alone with the darkness.
That's not good for anyone, is it?
I'm so proud of you, my child.
Esi's embraced her destiny.
Tomorrow when
the marauders come, she'll be ready.
And if she's not, we'll be
right there to fight alongside her.
You don't have to stay, Nathaniel.
I know that what I did was selfish.
You couldn't be selfish if you tried.
Now, you see that
booming granny over there?
She doesn't remember me.
Or the Legends.
You know why that is?
I must have erased my memory.
And why would you do that?
Because if I chose to come back here
after everything
we've been through, then
erasing you would be the only way
that I could be
the protector my people deserve.
Otherwise, I'd always
be split in two.
And part of me would be
in love with you.
I tried to reason with them,
but they won't listen.
Amaya is dead set
on saving her village.
And Nate, he's just...
- Whipped.
- I was gonna say in love.
But yeah, same thing.
Zari, please tell me
that you found a loophole
that allows Amaya
to save her village.
There is no loophole.
I tried billions of variations
but this event has
too many ripple effects.
The village has to be destroyed.
Or Mallus is freed.
And we're all doomed.
What if we're not?
Hmm?
We have the six Totems,
the only thing that
Mallus is afraid of.
But you can't fight
what you can't see.
What if the only way to kill Mallus
is to let him out?
Are you really suggesting
that we allow Mallus to escape,
because you have
a collection of magical stones?
We have two choices.
We fight Amaya, or we fight Mallus.
And I know it sounds
crazy to let a time demon out,
but it's a hell of lot
easier to stomach
than turning on a friend.
Okay, yes, but didn't
the original Totem bearers try
and face Mallus and blow it?
Constantine said that the only
reason they couldn't kill Mallus
was because the
Death Totem betrayed them.
And that's not gonna
happen this time.
How can you be so sure?
I needn't remind you what happened
the last time you tried to wield it.
She won't have to wield it.
I will.
The Death Totem was
attracted to Captain Lance
because of a unique quality
we both share.
We were both brought
back from the dead.
Plus, I have a personal stake
in wanting to send
Mallus straight to hell.
He took my little girl.
True as that may be,
there is no chance
that Captain Lance will trust you
with such a dangerous weapon.
Death Totem's all yours.
Sara, you can't be serious.
Ava, we don't have a choice.
Our only choice is to stop Amaya
and stop the anachronisms.
- This is insanity.
- Insane is what we do best, Ava.
I will not
condone this behavior
and the Bureau certainly
does not stand behind you.
Rip, let's go, we have work to do.
Remember when I told you
that we would need
the Legends before this was through?
Perhaps it is time that
we set aside the scalpel,
and let them be the chainsaw.
I will consider that
your resignation.
Ava.
Ava, wait.
This plan can work and you know it.
You just need to trust your gut.
My gut?
You mean the one that was
manufactured to factory settings?
The same gut that 11 other Avas used
and got killed?
Ava, please.
- Just trust me.
- You don't understand.
This plan breaks
every rule in every book,
and all I have right now
are the rules, okay?
You have me.
What are you doing?
I'm admitting something
that could save us both.
I love you.
There is no me to love.
She looks good out there. Ready.
Like mother, like daughter.
The warlords are early.
Hey. Don't. Don't. Puma pounces.
Really, Wally, you're gonna do this?
It's not like that, Nate.
- I know why you're here.
- No, no, you really don't.
Short version, Nora's on the ship,
tripping on Mallus juice.
Damien Darhk gave us the Water Totem
after they saved Barack Obama,
and, uh, we are here to
help you create the anachronism
so we can release Mallus
and then we can kill him.
Oh, and I met John Noble.
So you're working with Damien Darhk.
Please don't rub it in.
And you're letting him
wield the Death Totem.
In order to do justice
for someone I love.
Sure you can understand that.
Thankfully, that is
our only similarity.
- Hmm.
- So, who gets Earth, who gets Water?
Well, as a man of steel,
which is an element, I always felt
a strong connection to the Earth.
Actually, steel is
an alloy of iron and carbon.
Also, I've watched every
single episode of Planet Earth
on Blu-ray and I was
only stoned all of the time.
Can I just please have
the damn Totem? Thank you.
All yours. And Water, anyone?
Actually water is really powerful.
It's crucial to life on Earth.
Did you know that
we are made up of 60% water?
All right, I think we get it.
Take a Totem.
Oh, I wasn't making a pitch for one.
Just take the Totem.
Okay, cool.
All right, so is there like
an instruction manual,
a YouTube video...
You better figure it out.
Warlords are coming, and that means
Mallus is about to make his debut.
Dad.
Nora...
You're here, but
how? The Totem means you're dead.
No.
Not yet.
Mallus is trying to take me
but I'm still fighting him.
For now.
But Dad...
I made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
I don't want him to take me.
Please don't let him
take me. I'm scared.
You ready?
Yeah, let's do this
before it's too late.
This place has been sacred
to my people since dawn of time.
The Totems will be strongest here.
Oh, they'd better be.
Because mine's not turning on.
It's time.
As soon as Esi defeats the warlords,
our fight against Mallus begins.
Should we help your daughter?
Esi's got this.
No, no! No, no, don't kill me!
Looks like it's time
to meet our monster.
Or our maker.
I'm not dying today.
Here's Mallus.
Why isn't she transforming?
Rip, what gives?
Historical record is showing
that Zambesi is still destroyed.
It doesn't make any sense.
The battle is over.
The good guys won.
Rip, what's going on?
Oh, my God.
The warlords don't
destroy the village.
The village is destroyed by
an angry gorilla.
I had to. She's my daughter.
You released Grodd.
I need history to run its course.
Your time must end.
This way. Quick.
You should go too, Mame.
I can handle this beast.
I believe in you, obaba.
Esi. No.
Amaya!
Amaya. Hey, hey.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Nate, my family. Ah!
I won't let them die.
I promise.
Damien, Mallus is coming.
This won't save Nora.
If there's a chance in hell,
I'm gonna take it.
I'll handle this.
Always incapacitate
your Speedster first.
That's day one stuff.
Let him go.
I'm warning you.
Don't stand in my way.
I was powerful
before I had this trinket
but now I'm unstoppable.
Yeah, we've heard that one before.
I don't wanna kill you.
I wanna kill them
to save my daughter.
Why can't you understand that?
I can't move.
What is happening?
Foolish human, you are
now mine to control.
You will not harm my village.
Mame.
Get away from him!
It worked!
Amaya.
Nathaniel.
I didn't take you for a Totem bearer.
That makes two of us.
Nora.
I'll find you, I promise.
Go.
Go!
Hey!
Performance anxiety, Raymond?
You're only proving my point that
this plan was never gonna work.
Oh, come on. Don't make me do this.
It's too bad, really.
I was just beginning
to like you after Berlin.
You literally stabbed me in the back.
It only seemed fitting.
You're lucky I wasn't
aiming for your heart.
I'm not gonna let
Nora be taken by him.
Nora's gone, Damien.
Finally,
I am free.
No.
- Nora.
- You can't help her, Ray.
Oh, my God.
I am so much more than a god.