Last season
on Legends of Tomorrow...
I am no longer the captain.
You are.
Permission to depart, Captain Lance.
I know that I am supposed to
go back to 1942.
I have to believe that time
is stronger than that.
It's a time quake.
The result of us
interacting with ourselves.
And whose bright idea was it to do
the one thing that could jeopardize
all of time?
Yours.
Guys,
I think we broke time.
I guess this means
we're not going to Aruba.
You said you broke time.
No, I said we broke time.
Yeah, but it was your idea.
No, my idea was to save reality
and save Amaya.
By violating
the first rule of time travel:
never visit the same time
and place twice,
thereby breaking time.
Perhaps we should
continue this argument
somewhere there aren't dinosaurs.
Whoa! Big Ben.
So what?
- Guys?
- I've always wanted to visit it.
Guys!
Amaya, talk to it.
- She can talk dinosaur?
- Like you wouldn't believe.
Please speed up that conversation.
Y'all just saw that, right?
And that.
Well, you really have buggered
everything up this time.
Her idea.
No matter. As you can see,
my agents are already hard at work,
dealing with these anachronisms.
Anachronisms?
People, places and things
displaced from
their native time periods.
I told you, I was leaving to create
an organization
to replace the Time Masters.
Fifteen minutes ago.
For you.
Forming the Time Bureau
has been the work of
the last five years of my life.
I've gotten quiet good at it,
I have to say.
Meaning, you have Time Agents at work
in the Cretaceous Period as we speak?
Indeed. And throughout Los Angeles,
making sure no one retains any memory
of this unfortunate incident.
Which is why your services
are no longer required.
Whoa! What?
Seems only fitting,
since I was the one
who brought this team together,
that I should be the one
to disband it.
So,
on behalf of the Time Bureau,
I hereby relieve the Legends
from duty.
This isn't auditions for
American Ninja Warrior, you know.
And how many times have I told you
not to play with the merchandise?
Oh, I know that look.
It's the look of someone who thinks
they could've gotten a better job.
Well, let me
tell you something, freckles,
you're lucky I even hired someone
who'd been reported dead. Twice.
Especially in this economy.
What? No thank you?
Thank you.
That's better.
Now, get over to Health & Beauty.
Somebody just spilled a whole
mess of conditioner.
Alan...
Alan, um, I've had a breakthrough.
I've told you not to interrupt me
when I'm plugged in.
Yes, I know this is very important
to you, but, um...
Alan, I've been working
on a side project.
Not only have I managed to
shrink organic matter,
but I've also streamlined
the technology, so that you can wear...
I'm not interested, brah.
Look, I get it, once upon a time
you were Ray Palmer, tech mogul.
But when you give your company to
a woman who runs it into the ground,
you lose all side project privileges.
Great news for you, though,
what we're doing here at Upswipz,
is trying to change the world.
Upswipz is a dating app
just like Tinder, except
you swipe up, down,
instead of left, right.
Which is far more intuitive.
And Upswipz isn't a dating app.
It's a holistic social...
Networking platform.
But, Alan,
my miniaturization technology has
the potential
to actually
make the world a better place.
If that were true, it'd be an app.
If it doesn't live on a phone,
it's not the future, Ray.
I've actually been to the future.
Like, three times.
Damn it, Wally, what did I say?
Ah. I was supposed to save
some of the bad guys for you.
Just a few.
You know what, I'll make it up to you.
First round is on me.
No. Thanks, man, we're good.
Actually, I have a girl waiting for me.
Next time.
Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
It was kind of a work thing.
- It's okay.
- Um...
I know a really great coffee place...
Alana?
- Hey, girl.
- Hi.
Hey, idiot.
Either refill my margarita,
or get outta my light.
This is a private beach.
Listen, pal, what I...
Who the hell are you supposed to be?
I am Gaius Julius Caesar of Rome.
Oh.
Thought I recognized you.
Knocked off one of your casinos
in Vegas.
I am here to conquer all
the known world.
Right. Wait a sec.
How did you get here?
I imagine through the mischief
of the goddess Ate?
But it matters not the land
I find myself in.
It's but a matter of time
before my banner flies over it.
Is that a fact?
Yeah.
Boss.
- Rory?
- I got a situation.
I think I bumped into
one of those mechanisms.
- Mechanism?
- A nagging-ism...
- Anachronism?
- Yes.
Julius Caesar is in Aruba.
Seriously?
Seriously. I got him tied up
in my casita.
What do you want me to do?
Just sit tight, and keep him safe.
If you screw up history, the Bureau
will be on your ass
before you can say...
Son of a bitch.
Are you taking a personal call
during peak consumer traffic?
No...
Because I quit.
All right. What's so important to make
you catch a train to Central City?
Where's Amaya?
We kind of broke up.
What?
It's not a big deal.
So, what's going on?
Rory found an anachronism.
Apparently, Julius Caesar
just wound up in Aruba.
Mick's got him all tied up.
This is our chance to get
the Time Bureau to deal us back in.
If we pull this off, Rip might
give us our old ship back.
Wow. I had no idea you were so
unhappy with your new life.
Are you kidding me? I'm loving it.
I'm doing really good work.
Says you work at Sink Shower & Stuff.
Yeah. Well, even vigilantes
have to pay their bills.
Mmm.
What are you guys so content with, huh?
What are you doing?
I'm doing pretty good,
thanks for asking. I am, uh...
The second-most
popular superhero in Central City.
So, that's pretty good.
Well, I'm the first-most popular
in Silicon Valley
when I'm not changing the world
with a holistic
social networking platform.
- Let's go.
- Thank God.
You sure this is where they're at?
I bumped into one of Rip's
Time Agents a while back.
He may have left his badge
at my place.
He left it at your place?
All right, maybe I lifted it off him
in the morning.
Freeze!
- Hands in the air.
- Eyes on! Eyes on!
Hey! Don't move!
- Ugh.
- Stay right there!
Hello, everyone, welcome.
On the floor.
Hands behind your heads.
Uh, sorry, there must be some
kind of mistake. We're the Legends...
Oh, we know exactly who you losers are.
Wow. This floor is, like, super clean.
Lady, why are you so mean?
Maybe it's that poly-blend pantsuit
that's got her so grumpy.
I didn't know Men's Wearhouse
gave group discounts.
What's wrong with you people?
Do you want to get shot?
Totally rather get shot than look
like a Sears model.
Hold your fire! Stand down, all of you.
Excuse me. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Hello. It's so good to see you all.
Next time, just call ahead.
You son of a bitch.
Eyes on! Eyes on!
There's been a slight
misunderstanding, Dr. Heywood.
Nate, what are you doing?
I want to hear Rip say it.
You told Amaya to go back to 1942.
Amaya went back to 1942?
It was her idea.
She wanted to go back home
to Zambesi.
What did you just say?
It was Amaya's idea
to go back to Zambesi.
I heard him, Ray.
I was just being rhetorical.
All right, this is just awkward.
So, what brings the rest of you
to the Time Bureau?
We found an anachronism.
I wasn't aware any of you were
searching for anachronisms.
We weren't.
Rory was on a bender
when Julius Caesar showed up.
Agent Sharpe,
have we seen any activity
that would match such a massive
historical displacement?
Absolutely not, sir.
Well, I guess you must have
missed one, then.
I find that very hard to believe...
Ready a go-team,
and we'll meet you at the Op-Center.
Sir.
In the meantime,
who fancies a tour?
Guess they're, uh,
not used to seeing famous people.
Yeah. Kind of like we're the
Founding Fathers of the Time Bureau.
In a way,
I suppose if you lot hadn't created
the greatest time-paradox
the world had ever known,
all these people would have
nothing to do.
Unhand me, you knave!
Is that...
Oh, yes. King Arthur.
His displacement
into the Spanish Civil War
caused quite the anachronism.
Evil sorcerer! I might have known
you were responsible for all of this.
Now, when he is returned
to his original time,
he'll have no memory
of his displacement.
All humility aside, we are the most
important security organization
that no one's ever heard of.
Who somehow missed the fact that
Julius Caesar is down in Aruba,
working on his tan.
I'm sure our detection system would
have picked up on his displacement.
Yeah, and we get that.
But all we are saying is if you want
to give us the old Waverider back,
we would be happy to go down there
and take care of it for you.
Yeah, you know, for old time's sake?
I'm sorry, but our old ship has
been put to new use.
You turned our ship into a simulator?
The Command Module is heading
towards a meteoroid belt.
The Apollo 13 astronauts will die
unless we do something.
Ah, that's cool, man. They're teaching
one of our old missions.
I've got an idea, why don't we swing
around and use our ship as a shield?
Kidding.
I'm not a total idiot.
Target the command module's oxygen
tank with our photons and fire.
Yes.
The ruptured tank propelled their
capsule out of harm's way, Captain!
Well done, class. See you all tomorrow.
We'll see how you do trying to stop
an atomic torpedo
from blowing up New York City.
What are they doing here?
We are here to help you.
That's very gracious of you,
but whatever it is,
we have professionals
who can handle the matter.
Along with whatever damage
Mr. Rory causes.
Your salad sucks.
You should know this is not the
first time I've been taken captive.
Oh, great, a story.
Once, when I was a young man,
I was kidnapped by pirates.
They ransomed me for 50 talents
of silver, a fortune.
My family paid the money, of course.
But I told my captors
they would be better off killing me.
Because if they did let me go,
I promised to come back one day,
and not only to take my silver,
but to crucify the pirates,
one by one.
And that's exactly what I did.
You're saying I should kill you?
You should believe me
when I make a promise.
The gold in this satchel is yours.
Gold?
But I swear by my household gods,
it will cost you your life.
Oh.
Do we have a location on Mr. Rory?
We followed a trail
of petty larceny reports.
He's been holed up on the beach,
running up a room service tab
and a serious collection of STDs.
- That's our Mick.
- He's been busy.
Locking in on coordinates now.
Is the go-team ready?
Locked and loaded, sir!
Opening a portal.
You broke my nose!
Out of my way.
Our team is under attack!
Definitely Rory.
Alpha Team,
do you have eyes on Caesar?
He's got the target.
What do you want us to do, Command?
Get the hell out of there before
Mr. Rory causes any more mayhem!
Roger that. Initiating extraction.
Get off me, you damn missionaries!
Get the hell off me, dude.
This is Julius Caesar?
Dude, my dad's a lawyer.
Gonna totally sue all your asses.
What is this place?
An institution you will never
step foot in again, Mr. Rory.
Get them out of here!
Rip.
Look, I'm sorry, I thought...
That the Legends would change?
Since when do we need to change?
When you left our team, you said
you had nothing left to teach me.
Yes, well, unfortunately,
all of history suddenly came unglued
moments after I uttered those words.
Look. I miss the good old days,
too, Sara.
But times have changed.
Yeah, and you don't think
you need us anymore.
Look, Rip, this is our mess.
You have to let us fix it.
Using your team to fix anything
is like doing brain surgery
with a chainsaw.
Whoa. You can't leave yet!
Not without parking validation.
Son of a bitch stole my money!
Whoa.
This is a genuine Roman aureus.
This is first century B.C.
That means Rory really saw
Julius Caesar.
Duh.
We've got to tell Rip
that he's got the wrong guy.
Yeah. Like he'd listen to us.
He's right. We got to grab
Caesar ourselves.
And prove to Rip
that we've got the right stuff.
Sara, exit's this way.
Our ship's this way.
We're gonna steal the Waverider?
We're gonna fix our mistakes.
Oh, damn it! I mean, darn it.
There's a class in session.
Ah.
Listen up, punks. Class dismissed.
Get outta here.
This must be a part of
the training exercise.
Our ship has been boarded
by a Time Pirate.
On behalf of the Time Bureau,
and in accordance to Article 15.6,
Section B, concerning the unlawful
seizure of Time Ships...
Anyone else?
Gideon's been in sleep-mode
for five years.
But if I can divert her power
back to the core...
Hello, Legends! What did I miss?
Well, we're about to steal the ship,
go grab Julius Caesar in Aruba,
all before
history completely collapses!
So, it's business as usual, then.
Exactly.
Gideon, engines to power.
Turbines to speed.
Right away, Captain.
Sounds like this old boat
needs a lube job.
What in the hell
do they think they're doing?
The hangar's sealed.
There's no way out of here.
Well, I'm afraid
the Legends have never permitted
something like logic to stop them.
I hope you know what
you're doing, Ms. Lance.
Gideon, time-jump us out of here.
Uh, are you sure we can time-jump
inside the building?
We're about to find out.
Gideon, when are we?
I was only able to time-jump us
three minutes into the future.
We are still in Star City.
If you haven't noticed, the ship is
in desperate need of maintenance.
Yeah, there's no way we're
gonna make it to Aruba.
Can we make it to Central City?
I know a good mechanic there.
Jefferson. What a nice surprise.
Lily also dropped by with some
rather exciting news.
Oh, well, if it's a bad time,
I can always...
Wait, what is it?
Something's wrong. I can feel it.
We may only see each other once
a week for our bonding sessions,
but we still share a psychic connection.
I dropped out of school.
Why would you do that? You could
have your master's in two years.
I know, it's just,
learning about engineering
is not half as fun as actually being
an engineer on a Time Ship.
Oh, hey, Jax!
Whoa. Whoa, Lily. You're...
What? I'm what?
You look healthy.
I'm kidding! I'm pregnant.
Oh, my God. Congratulations!
Thank you.
I was on sabbatical in Rome
with my boyfriend...
She means her future husband.
And we decided
we wanted to come home,
and break the big news in person.
Oh, I got to put the osso buco
in the oven,
but you should totally stay
for dinner. Right, Daddy?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Dude, what?
My heart still melts when
she says that word. It's crazy.
Oh, my God.
Is that what I think it is?
Come on, Grey, a chance to meet
Julius Caesar and fix history.
Look, we have a Time Ship. We can get
you home in time for dessert.
That's what I told Clarissa
the last time I left.
And when you came home,
you had a surprise daughter.
Mmm-hmm.
Your point?
The point is sometimes, we screw
things up for the better.
That's a good motto.
We should use that.
Fine. Whatever. I'll come.
Great. Now, all we need is Amaya,
and we can get the band back together.
That's not happening.
- Whoa. Did I miss something?
- Mmm-mmm.
Amaya dumped him,
went back to 1942.
She didn't dump me.
Amaya went back to Zambesi
because Rip told her
she has some sort of destiny
to fulfill back in 1942. That's it.
Unlike the rest of us, who don't have
crap waiting for us in the real world.
Speak for yourself, numbnuts.
I don't know about you all,
but I was destined for greater things
than folding towels.
And Rip thinks he doesn't need us
because he's got the Time Bureau.
Ray's right.
We're the ones who broke history,
we should be the ones who fix it.
But instead of operating
on history with a chainsaw, this time,
we are going to be the scalpel.
This your idea of subtle?
Just try to blend in, okay?
No problem.
Great Caesar's ghost...
That's him.
So, what I have to say to you is this,
are you willing to fight with me?
- Yeah!
And claim this savage land for Rome?
What, did you teach Caesar English?
No. He just showed up speaking fancy.
Temporal linguistic dysplasia.
What?
A side effect of historical
displacement. Astonishing!
You know, cowards die many times
before their deaths.
The valiant never taste death
but once!
Yeah, and Delta Nu Phi sucks!
Delta Nu Phi sucks!
- Alpha Psi Gamma sucks!
- Delta Nu Phi sucks!
Can we not agree they all suck?
All right, let's shut
this toga party down
before things really get out of hand.
No powers... It could
make the anachronism worse.
Right, be the scalpel.
I've got an idea.
Come on, man.
You're really trying to hook-up now?
No, I'm creating a dating profile
on our new Upswipz app.
Gideon, I need you to hit every phone
on the beach with a match.
"Exotic beauty looking for casual sex
with young frat stud?"
It might work.
Now, all I need is a profile picture.
I believe I've got that covered.
Ooh. Not bad.
- For Mars.
- Yeah!
- For Rome.
Death or glory!
All right, J.C. Party's over.
You're coming with us.
I'd rather fall on my sword
than surrender it to a woman.
Well, then, today is your lucky day.
Uh... Shouldn't we help her?
It's him I'm worried about.
Yep, I'd say our work here is done.
And to quote the great conqueror
himself, "We came, we saw..."
We kicked Caesar's ass.
- Suckers.
- Nice work.
I'd have done it faster.
Oh. I'm sorry. Did that hurt?
Easy, Mick.
He broke my nose, my best feature.
Still. We have to get him back to
his time in one piece.
Or he doesn't go on to
conquer the world and help
create the greatest empire
history has ever known.
We need to get moving.
It's not going to take Rip long
to track down a stolen Time Ship.
Quiet so, Ms. Lance.
It appears that you've captured
the real Julius Caesar.
Well done.
Now, if you'll just return him to us,
we'll be happy to handle
his reinsertion back into history.
You don't think we can handle it?
It's not that. Maybe it is that.
But the fact remains that
you've hijacked our property.
If you return it to us, along
with our anachronistic guest,
all will be forgiven.
I trust you'll use your best judgment.
Does he not know this team?
Shouldn't we entrust Caesar's return
to the people who do
that sort of thing professionally?
I thought that this was our chance to
prove that we're professional-ish.
Your call, Captain.
Gideon, plot a course
for the Time Bureau.
I'm afraid that won't be
possible without additional repairs.
Of course.
Et tu, Sara?
I'm using my best judgment.
You know, I've taken these engines
apart so many times,
feels like this ship is a part of me.
It is a part of you that you can take on
whatever adventure life
offers you next.
What adventure could be better
than this one?
I mean, I got to be a superhero
who traveled through time,
changing history.
Yes, I know.
Look, I know you wanna do the whole
granddad thing.
Smoke a pipe by the fire, but
I've got a whole lot of life left,
and I have no idea how to fill it.
Jefferson, you are
hands down the most gifted, capable,
driven young man I've ever known.
You can do anything you want to do.
Well, that's all well and good,
but what I want to do is to be half
of a nuclear-powered superhero.
And I can't do that
if you don't want to.
Have you come to gloat?
Or to grant me the mercy
of taking my own life?
Getting beaten by a woman
bothers you that much?
Yes.
If your intention is neither boasting
nor mercy,
to what do I owe the honor
of this visit?
You doubt
your present course of action
and seem to believe that Caesar
holds the key to resolving it.
There's nothing to resolve.
My course of action isn't up to me.
So, you believe your future lies in
the hands of the Three Fates?
No, it lies in the hands of a group
called the Time Bureau.
And if I go against them now,
they'll take my ship.
And if I screw this up,
then I lose everything.
And that's all you're willing to
wager for greatness?
Pompey said he would have my head
for going against the Senate.
But when I lead my army
across the Rubicon,
Rome will welcome me as a god.
Well, I wish
I shared your confidence.
It cost me eight years and countless
centurions to conquer Gaul.
But with an Amazonian queen like you
by my side,
I could make short work
of the rest of the world.
Conquering the world does sound nice.
But I don't need you to do it.
Ship's fixed, Captain.
Fixed enough to get us back to the
Time Bureau?
Mmm-hmm.
How about Ancient Rome?
Only one way to find out.
According to Gideon,
Caesar disappeared
the night before his
famous march on Rome.
No crossing the Rubicon means
no civil war, no civil war means
no Ides of March, no Ides of March
means no Roman Empire.
- What happens on the Ides of March?
- Mmm.
Well, that's when your friends,
who really aren't your friends,
stab you in the back
to stop your rise to power.
Not that you'll remember any of this.
Check it out.
History is back to normal.
And now, a little something
for the Heywood scrapbook.
Oh, man. That's a keeper.
Enjoy conquering the world.
Perhaps my eyes deceive me,
but that does not look
like the Time Bureau to me.
It says here we landed in 49 BC.
Relax. Because we just dropped off
J.C. back where he belonged.
So, history has been restored,
and we can go a-home.
I'm afraid that's not possible.
Why? Something wrong with the ship?
No, but your home
no longer exists.
Here is a map of
what was formerly known
as the United States, circa 2017.
I thought you said that
history had been restored.
Does that look restored to you?
What does Magna Hesperia mean?
Means Caesar went on to conquer
the known world,
and then the unknown world.
One of you fools must have
entrusted him with future knowledge,
something that allowed him to alter
the course of history.
No. No. I mean, Sara hit him with
Rip's flashy-thing.
Flashy-thing.
Oh, my God.
What?
My book.
What book?
Change of plans.
We're not marching on Rome, sir?
We're still marching.
But when we get there, we're going
to visit a few old friends.
Starting with Brutus and Cassius.
I can't believe you let Caesar steal
the answers to the test!
Why are you all looking at me?
It's not my fault.
How did mop head even know
there'd be a test?
It's a figure of speech.
Caesar knew
how to alter history because
he already knew how it would unfold.
Okay, so all we got to do is get back
out there and refold history.
Or contact Mr. Hunter and let
the Time Bureau handle it.
No, we do not let
those time turds have
the satisfaction of knowing that we...
That you lost the book?
Stop blaming me, okay? Caesar must've
swiped it when I wasn't looking.
- Nate's right.
- Thank you.
Not about it not being your fault.
About the Time Bureau.
They're 2,000 years away.
We can fix this before they even...
Too late.
- Ms. Lance, a word?
- Yeah.
Look, I know what you're gonna say,
but we are gonna fix this.
You shall do nothing of the sort.
My agents will clear up this mess
in no time.
And what if something goes sideways?
None of these guys are field agents.
Admit it, Rip. You need us.
No, Sara. You need this.
But just because you all found life
outside this ship boring,
doesn't mean you get
your old jobs back.
Because the Time Bureau is capable of
getting the job done without the mess.
Status?
We've got eyes on the target,
go-team is hot.
Yes, you are.
Watch and learn, Ms. Lance.
Execute.
Asset acquired.
Proceed to target and commence
memory erasure protocol.
I've seen this play before.
Leave the merchandise unattended,
draw the target out...
League of Assassins strategy?
No. It's Sink Shower & Stuff. We use
it to catch shoplift... It's a trap!
You've got to pull your team
out of there.
Agent Sharpe, initiate extraction.
Extract.
Uh... Agent Sharpe has been apprehended.
We were caught unprepared,
but we'll go back in and...
Screw things up worse
than you already have?
Boss is right. We need to go
and rescue Agent Hotcakes.
Please. This entire situation is
happening because of you idiots...
Idiots?
Idiots with special abilities.
We know how to handle ourselves.
Not against Julius Caesar, who has
an entire legion at his command.
We're pretty good
at taking down legions.
Damn straight.
I'm assuming the answer is no, but
do any of you happen to have a plan?
We're about to rejoin my army.
Be grateful.
Not only am I letting you live,
I am permitting you to witness
the rise of the Roman Empire.
The Time Bureau will never permit
you to alter history.
Caesar does not alter history.
He makes it.
Surrender your prisoner in the name
of Ares, the God of War!
Mars is the Roman
God of War, Jefferson.
Yeah, whatever.
- What are you doing?
- Rescuing you.
I can take care of myself.
Howdy.
What'd you say to him?
Uh... Sleep tight, buddy,
I guess. Maybe.
- I think this deserves a bro-hug.
- Bring it.
Damn, Ray.
You ruined my vacation.
And my nose.
Now, we're even.
See? Problem solved.
I gotta say, Ms. Lance,
now that I've seen your team
in action with my own eyes,
you're even worse than I imagined.
You're welcome.
Well, like Nate said, sometimes we
screw things up for the better.
I fail to see
how that's true in this case.
It's our new motto.
New motto? Right.
Does that mean
you all plan to continue
swashbuckling your way
through history?
With the Time Bureau's permission,
of course.
And if I deny you permission?
- We'll do it anyways.
- Yeah.
Sir, the go-team has erased the
memories of Caesar and his forces.
Good. We best take our leave, then.
Sara. Mr. Rory. Do your best
to stay out of trouble.
What's that?
It's a, uh, portal thingy.
Communications thing.
And a... Ah, yes, the memory thing.
So, I guess that means
you're staying.
Well, I kind of have to.
You'd be dead without me.
Cheers.
They're irresponsible, undependable,
unpredictable, dangerous...
And yet effective. At least on occasion.
Is that the reason
they're not warming a cell
back at headquarters as we speak?
They're not warming a cell,
Agent Sharpe, because
they might just be our best hope
of defeating what's coming.
They're the reason Mallus is a threat.
Indeed. But there might just come a day
when we need the Legends
to do what they do best.
Which is what, exactly?
Be the chainsaw.
Would you open a portal
back to headquarters?
I seem to have misplaced
my Time Courier.
How is she running?
Lousy. Rip's monkeys
really screwed up the works.
It's gonna take Ray months
to figure this out.
Why Raymond?
I told Sara to take us back home.
Oh, that's unfortunate considering
I've decided to stay aboard.
Whoa. Wait. What?
I Shanghaied you into our first voyage.
I forced this life upon you.
I can hardly ask you to give it up now.
But your life... Your family...
I'll make it home for the birth
of my first grandchild.
As for my family...
They're on this ship as well.
- Yeah.
Ah.
You doing okay?
Yeah, nothing says doing okay like
pining over files of your ex.
Yeah, I was just thinking.
About her?
Yeah, about her and...
This place. I miss being on the ship.
Yeah, of course you do.
This is your home.
And she's back home, too.
She's happy, I'm happy.
She's happy, right?
Yeah. Totally.
This is the village.
Get out of our way, woman.
Actually, that's what I was gonna
tell you.
We have business here.
If you call
poaching and raping business.
Zambesi is under my protection.
No! No, please, no!