PROFESSOR STEIN:
Time travel is real,
and all of history
is vulnerable to attack,
which is why we must travel
through time to stop the spread of
these so-called time Aberrations
and to erase their damage to history.
We are a team of outcasts and misfits,
so please don't call us heroes.
We're legends.
AMAYA: Previously, on
Legends of Tomorrow...
I think I can save him.
RAY: It's a bio-molecular enhancer.
JAX: You've got superpowers now, dude.
- (GROANS)
- Name's Steel.
I'm not going back
until Rex's killer is brought to justice.
You let the Shogun steal
a 21 st century super-suit?
I have to teach you to destroy
the only thing that makes me a hero.
Do it!
(YELLING)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
I am so sorry.
It's okay.
MAN: Dontaar.
(COUGHING)
Dontaar, are you reading this?
- (THUDDING)
- (GRUNTING)
They're dead. They're all dead.
The heist went off easy.
We got the TX-90
out of 2235 as contracted, but...
But Alec got infected.
And then he...
God, you wouldn't imagine
what he did to everyone...
(COUGHING)
I don't know when I am...
I'm activating the temporal beacon.
You get in the Dauntless
and you get out here and rescue my ass.
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
MAN 1: Don't move.
MAN 2: What the hell is this thing?
(GRUNTING)
(GROWLING)
FUTURE BARRY: I can't risk
putting any more lives in danger.
And neither can you.
Which is why you'll keep
what I'm about to tell you a secret.
Even from the rest of your team.
A war is coming, Captain Hunter.
How many times are we gonna listen
to this message from future Barry?
Until it makes sense.
So, "Forever" is
basically what you're saying.
You haven't spoken
to anyone else about this?
No. We agreed that we wouldn't.
And yet I find myself asking.
SARA: (OVER COMMS) Martin?
Um, Sara! What can I do for you?
You never call me "Sara."
Everything with you is "Ms. Lance".
I'm turning over a new leaf.
Well, turn it over in the library.
We've got something.
I don't know when I am...
I'm activating the temporal beacon.
You get in the Dauntless
and you get out here and rescue my ass.
A bit vulgar for a Time Master...
Time pirate, we're thinking.
He activated a beacon.
We have to go after him.
He's a time pirate.
Why would we rescue him?
Because if he ends up
somewhere he shouldn't...
And does something he shouldn't...
It's Aberration-palooza.
So where do we think he's going to end up?
Looks like Mississippi, 1863.
Height of the American Civil War.
RAY: It's also the bloodiest year
in American history.
We got to watch each other's backs
out there.
Yes, which is why you'll be watching ours
from right here.
Huh?
If you don't mind.
Someone has to stay behind as backup.
JAX: Can't believe Ray got pined.
No suit, no powers, no tech.
I mean, I guess Sara had no choice
but to bench him.
Well, I'm sure
she was just trying to keep him safe.
This time period
is replete with various perils.
Perhaps, it might be easier
if you were to remain behind
and keep Dr. Palmer company.
Perhaps you should remain behind.
No? Because you're not black?
Because you think that
me going back to 1863,
I can't handle it?
That doesn't mean there's a need for you
to subject yourself
to the horrors that await you in that era.
Okay.
Now I get, it might be
difficult for you to understand this.
But I've been black my entire life, Grey.
And honestly, I can't think of a
time period we could go to
where I wouldn't face some sort of racism.
So don't worry, okay?
Along with comms devices,
I've also packed sack lunches.
I figure the food in 1863 is pretty lousy.
All right. The operation is simple.
We isolate the target,
we eliminate the time ship
and we get out of there.
And all while wearing this dress...
RAY: Come back safe.
RAY: (OVER COMMS)
It's Mississippi, 1863.
The weather is a temperate 58 degrees.
Ooh! A little trivia.
You guys are in Hinds County,
- which was named after General Thomas...
{TURNS COMMS OFF)
Did you just...
Shut off his comms? Yup.
Guys. Guys.
I can't believe it.
It looks to be some kind of escape pod.
No doubt,
it fell out of the temporal zone.
No sign of anyone.
Power core looks exposed.
AMAYA: Does that mean
what I think it means?
Only one way to find out.
- Ah. Thought you'd never ask.
- Back up, everyone.
What's next?
Don't you think that's enough
incineration for one day, Mr. Rory?
No, I do not, Professor.
(CHUCKLES) This has turned out to be
one of our easiest missions yet.
HENRY SCOTT: Help me! Somebody, please!
You had to say that, didn't you?
It's over there.
Help me! Help!
Whoa, wait. We're not supposed
to interfere with historical events.
Try and stop me.
Women.
She certainly has a fiery spirit.
Which is either gonna get her killed
or completely screw up history.
Just end it fast.
Help! Help!
(PANTING)
Let's get those Confederates off his back.
(GRUNTING)
Whoa, whoa. Relax.
All right, you're safe now.
What in tarnation was that?
What did I just see?
What was what? I, uh...
I didn't see anything.
Who are you guys?
What's goin' on here?
Look, we're just passing through.
Okay, guys, let's get the hell outta here.
We can't just leave him here.
Unfortunately, we have to.
If we rescue one man,
we could alter history in the wrong way.
You're a dispatch, aren't you?
AMAYA: Wait. What's a dispatch?
A former slave providing
information to the Union Army.
My name is Henry Scott.
I'm a free man from Trenton, New Jersey.
Well, you're a long way from home.
And we need to be getting out of here.
Uh, guys.
(GROWLING)
Oh, my God.
Those Confederates look a lot like...
Don't say it!
Just merge!
(GRUNTS)
(ZOMBIE GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROWLING)
(HEAD SPLATTERS)
Is everybody okay?
(PANTING)
What the hell was that?
- You ask me, they looked like...
- Don't... Don't say it.
I know they're essentially a myth,
but I have this irrational fear of...
Zombies?
- Please don't say it.
- Oh, god.
- (HENRY SCOTT GROANING)
Hey, hey, hey.
- Hang on.
- Satch...
What?
My satchel.
Are you... Union?
Kind of.
(GASPING) My orders. Collins Plantation.
Confederate troop movements.
Without them...
(CHOKING)
Hey. Hey.
RAY: Nice job blowing up
the time pirates' escape pod!
Put in another win
in the "mission" column!
Did you not see what happened next?
No, I took a break,
had to go to the bathroom.
You okay?
We were attacked by zombies.
And somebody put sprouts on my sandwich.
The Time Pirate's distress call referenced
something called a "TX-90."
It's a futuristic bioweapon.
The infected's condition
represents strongly those things...
The... I can't say...
And if that infected time pirate
is out there spreading this virus,
then our work is not done here.
No kidding. Having
zombies or whatever they are
running around the Civil War
is not a good thing.
(THUDS)
Speaking of not good...
Get him to the MedBay.
What's goin' on?
Apparently, you were wounded during
our encounter with the infected.
Impossible.
Those creepy bastards
didn't lay a finger on me.
But they might've gotten in a tooth.
Or 30.
(RAY GASPS)
Oh, my God, he's already starting to turn.
Ray, you gotta fix me.
I don't want to be turned into a...
Fricking zombie.
SARA: Oh, my God.
DR. HEYWOOD: Yeah.
It's pretty disastrous.
I'm guessing thanks to the zombies,
the Confederacy won its
independence from the Union.
It wasn't just them.
That guy. The dispatch?
These are his mission orders.
From General Ulysses S. Grant.
My God.
He was supposed to
infiltrate the Collins Plantation
and steal
Confederate troop movement orders.
SARA: They named a high school after him?
DR. HEYWOOD: That's because,
in the original version of history,
the plans Scott stole helped Grant win
the Battle of Champion Hill.
And I'm guessing none of that happened
because Scott was bayonetted
by a Confederate turned into
a zombie by a future virus.
Okay, so...
How do we fix it?
We don't. I do.
Jax.
There's a reason
black people were used as spies.
Because we were invisible.
That's why I'm going in there.
Don't worry. If anything happens,
it's on me.
No, Jax, it's on me.
Look, Mick's already hurt.
And I don't like the idea
of putting anyone else in harm's way.
And I don't like the idea of
having a flag that has 20 stars on it.
(SIGHS)
I'm definitely not letting you
go in there alone.
Fine. I'll take Amaya.
All right.
Nate and I will go warn the Union Army
about the infected soldiers.
Okay.
When we get to wherever we're going,
maybe I should be the one that
breaks the zombie news to General Grant.
I'm someone he'll listen to.
Because you're a man.
We're a couple hundred years
away from gender equality.
Only a couple hundred?
Look, all I'm saying is, maybe,
just maybe,
when we get to the Union Army,
you let me do the talking.
Stay where you are!
Right there.
Okay, you do the talking.
So what's our plan?
Well, if things go easy,
we sneak in while everybody's asleep,
find the Confederate plans and grab 'em.
(EXHALES) Are things ever easy
with your group?
Good point.
WOMAN: (CRYING) Please don't!
I'm sorry! I didn't mean
to burn the table cloth.
It was an accident, I swear.
An accident?
You just let yourself get distracted,
that's all.
While you should've been
thinking about the ironing,
you were probably daydreaming
about Ulysses S. Grant marching
down here to free all the slaves.
No, sir. I wasn't...
Which is why I need
to focus your attention.
- No, no, wait.
- He's going to hurt her.
I know. And it's awful.
But if we blow our cover now,
we won't be able to fix the Aberration,
and we might lose the Civil War.
(CRYING)
No matter how much you cry,
I'm still gonna hurt you.
- (GRUNTS)
- (WOMAN SCREAMS)
- (WHIP CRACKING)
- (WOMAN SCREAMING)
Raymond, please hurry.
I don't like the way this is going.
You don't like the way this is going?
How close are you to
formulating a workable vaccine?
Very. I think.
Raymond.
I'm counting on you.
Don't worry, Mick. I got you.
Here we go.
(YELLS)
- What's happening?
- (EKG BEEPING RAPIDLY)
His heart rate's spiking!
Gideon, administer a sedative now!
(GRUNTING)
Zombie! Zombie!
- Zombie!
- The screaming isn't helping!
Gideon, put the ship on lockdown!
GIDEON: Lockdown mode activated.
This is incredible.
I did my sophomore thesis
on the Civil War.
I smell a history lesson coming.
DR. HEYWOOD: Fun fact.
Did you know that out of the three million
people who fought on both sides,
300 were women in drag?
How is that not a fun fact for you?
General.
We caught these two
outside the northeast perimeter.
This here's a war zone.
So either you two are Confederate spies
or you...
Are very lost.
Actually, we're neither, General Grant.
How do you know my name?
I'm a fan. Actually,
I'm, like, a really big fan.
And you are surprisingly taller
than I thought in real life.
Ahem. Um...
I'm a colonel in the Union Army.
Colonel Sanders. I'm Colonel Sanders
with the 31st Pennsylvania Infantry.
Then why are you
not in proper uniform, son?
My uniform is in the wash, sir.
Or you're a Confederate spy.
- Okay.
- Look, we're not Confederates.
And truth be told, we're not
a part of the Union either.
But we are here to tell you
that your company is in danger.
In danger?
Of what?
Well, believe it or not,
a horde of zombies is headed your way.
What is a zombie?
They're not familiar with that word
for another 70 years.
I've had enough nonsense.
SARA: Look, it's not nonsense.
It's just really hard to explain.
And it'd be a lot easier
if I just showed you.
And if I'm not back for any reason,
feel free to shoot him.
Just don't listen to her.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING INSIDE)
(PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
They're having some kind of party.
"Cotillion," actually.
According to Scott's mission papers.
He was going to get in disguised
as the help.
You mean, "Slave."
We could've helped her.
We should have.
Look, I've been doing this time travel
thing for a little while now.
And if I've learned one thing,
it's you never know what's gonna change
history and have massive consequences.
Do you think
this doesn't make me angry as well?
But we have a job to do.
And if we don't do it,
we can make things a lot worse.
Just stay on comms, okay?
- (GASPING) He was... He was...
- Calm down. Calm down.
We're going to die.
You just need to calm down.
I will not "calm down."
He was threatening enough before
he was one of the walking dead!
Why didn't your vaccine work?
I... I don't know.
It could be that subcutaneous delivery
needs more than one dose.
Oh, and that didn't occur to you
while formulating your serum?
At least I'm not the one with
an irrational fear of zombies.
There's nothing irrational about
my fear of zombies.
He's a zombie!
- Look. I'm pretty sure that I stunned him.
- Oh, you're pretty sure?
And if he's knocked out cold
in the MedBay,
all we have to do is
go back in there and inject him again.
And if he's not,
I'm "pretty sure" he'll kill us.
So me and my "irrational fear"
are staying right here.
Listen to me, Marty.
- Can I call you "Marty"?
- No.
You have to help me.
If you don't and I get bitten, then
you will have two zombies to deal with.
My God.
(WOMEN LAUGHING)
(PEOPLE TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Amaya, it's Jax.
Study is a bust. I'm gonna check out
the rest of the plantation house.
Oh!
I'm so sorry, ma'am.
Boy.
What did you just do?
I, uh... I'm sorry.
You took that woman's hand
and addressed her directly.
No, sir, I did not.
Are you calling me a liar, boy?
I'm not calling you anything, sir.
Who the hell are you?
I'm with the additional staff.
- For tonight's festivities.
- Oh.
So you're ignorant about the house rules.
You see, my staff know better
than to talk back to me.
I'm very sorry.
It won't happen again, sir.
Hey!
(CHATTER CEASES)
Don't you turn your back on me, boy.
There a problem, Mr. Collins?
Just a house boy
who don't know his place.
And needs to be taught some manners.
These zombies.
They're going to kill all of you.
And I keep asking.
What in perdition's flames is a "zombie"?
This.
- I found him and 50 others just like him
- (SNARLING)
less than a mile outside your camp.
And, yeah, I said less than a mile.
Which means we don't have a lot of time.
Okay. You ready?
Mmm-mmm.
Just relax. He's unconscious, remember?
- Raymond...
- Yeah?
If he's unconscious,
wouldn't he be here?
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
(GUNS FIRING)
This isn't working.
We need more sharpshooters.
Can't spare the men.
Did you see what's out there?
We have to think
about the battle that lies ahead.
If we don't take Vicksburg,
we won't control the Mississippi.
And we need command of the river
to win the war.
At this rate, I'm afraid we will be
out of ammunition before dawn.
We need some backup.
Damn, it's dark.
Even if Mr. Rory
wasn't in a zombified state,
I doubt he possesses the intelligence
to operate a light switch.
He probably destroyed a conduit
or something.
That's hardly comforting, Raymond.
(RORY GROWLING)
(PROFESSOR STEIN SHRIEKS)
Martin, come on.
He's got me! He's got my foot. Oh, my God.
- Run, run!
- Come on.
PROFESSOR STEIN: This is a nightmare.
If Mr. Rory's intention
is to eat our brains,
can you imagine the feast we'll provide
him given our combined intellect?
Wait, wait. (GRUNTING)
You get comfortable now.
- (JAX GRUNTS)
- (CHAIN RATTLING)
You got a long night ahead of you.
(BREATHING HEAVILY) Wait.
(GRUNTS, COUGHS)
(GROANS)
(LAUGHS)
Hey.
Damn it.
(GROANS)
- What is it?
- It's...
It's Jefferson.
- What's happening to him?
- I'm not sure.
I've never felt him
so frightened or angry before.
I know I should've gone with him.
Sara and Nate are still out there.
Maybe they can get to him.
Ray? Martin?
I've lost contact with Jax and Amaya.
I really could use some help out here.
I suppose there's your answer.
Here's the thing, Sara.
We'd love to come help,
but my vaccine didn't work and
Mick got turned into one of those things.
And he's confined us to the galley.
(BANGING)
Until we can cure him,
you guys are on your own.
Yeah. Looks like we all are.
Yeah.
Who are you?
My name is Jackson.
(GROANING)
Jefferson Jackson.
Those're some pretty famous slave
owners you're named for, Jefferson.
Look at his hands.
Have you ever worked a day in your life?
It's a long story.
What are you doing here?
Also a long story.
Actually... (GRUNTS)
Maybe... Maybe you could help me.
I'm here for General Grant.
The Union general?
He sent me here to steal details
of Confederate troop movements.
MAN: Even if you got your hands on 'em,
there ain't no way off this plantation,
Mr. Jackson.
There's always a way.
WOMAN: No.
Master Collins got guard dogs.
Cuban bloodhounds.
MAN: Yeah, we had some friends,
they got caught less than a mile out.
But they didn't kill 'em.
No, they didn't want to lose the labor.
So they cut off their manhood
and then they hobbled them
so they could never think
of trying to run again.
How do you endure this?
- How does it not...
- Drive us all mad?
Because that's what they want it to do.
They think they can break us.
(MAN SINGING)
When the sun comes up
(ALL SINGING)
♪ And the first quail calls ♪
♪ Follow the drinking gourd ♪
♪ For the old man is a waiting ♪
♪ For to carry you to freedom ♪
♪ Follow the drinking gourd ♪
Jax, are you there?
Damn.
(SIGHS)
Well, well, well.
Who invited you to the party?
Actually, my invitation
must have gotten lost in the mail.
You sure have a smart mouth on you.
Hmm.
A pretty one, though.
We'll have to teach you a lesson
on how to talk to your betters.
We told Mick that we would save him.
Plus, I still have the vaccine.
We just have to figure out a way
to get it to work.
- (BANGING)
- (RORY GROWLING)
Vaccine wasn't effective
when we injected Mick.
But if we can aerosolize the serum,
and deploy it using something
like a fire extinguisher
we can deliver the cure as a spray.
"We" are not doing anything.
But you, on the other hand...
Look, Martin, I know that you're scared.
I've been nothing but scared
since my suit was destroyed.
I've been terrified that
I have nothing to offer the team.
But you have to get over your fears
if we're gonna survive this.
(BANGING CONTINUES)
We've only seen these things
downwind from here.
We can pick them off in this valley
until they're all gone.
I got my best men
on the ridge to the west
but reports are
they are running out of ammunition.
What? Helps me think.
DR. HEYWOOD: Well,
without ammo, we can't take all these
zombies out even with perfect shots.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Yeah.
Mr. Collins is going to love spending
the midnight hour with you, girlie.
I'm looking forward to it.
I hope he enjoys
getting punched in the face.
(GRUNTING)
And thank you ever so much
for showing me where to find my friend.
(GRUNTS)
What the hell was that?
Don't you know a breakout
when you see one?
Okay.
Good. Now let's free them.
I thought you said if we didn't do our job
we could end up doing more harm than good.
Yeah, that's still a risk.
So what's changed?
The way these people are being treated,
that's the real Aberration.
I can see that now.
This is the history
that needs to be fixed.
Nah, nah. I'm obliged, ma'am. But I told
you what happens if they catch us...
Don't worry, we're gonna protect you.
I know you're scared. I get it.
Don't ask me how I know this, but...
It gets better.
Not perfect. Nowhere near close, but...
Better than this.
But it starts right now
with us not giving up.
Zambesi. Your amulet.
You are a warrior of the Zambesi.
You're familiar with it?
That's where my mother was born.
We must follow her.
I believe in her.
I believe in them.
Then I do, too.
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
What is it?
We've got company.
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
We've got to get out of here.
Not without the Confederate plans.
I think I know where they are.
Okay. You get everyone to safety.
- Come on.
- Wait, Jax.
Good luck.
You ready?
(GROWLING)
Come on.
This way.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Mr. Jackson.
What are you doing, man?
For when things to get better,
like you said.
- (ZOMBIE SNARLS)
- Okay, come on.
(GUN FIRES)
What in Sam Hill are these things?
They're infected with something.
We've got to work together or
we'll never make it out of here alive.
What are you saying?
I'm saying, "Give us weapons."
Without us, you'll never
be able to fight them off.
You think I'm dumb enough
to arm my own slaves?
(SCREAMS)
- Help!
- Come on.
Help!
For God sakes, help me!
Come on, move!
(GUNS FIRING)
We're down to our last rounds with no hope
of stopping those abominations.
Whatever you have up your sleeve, I
suggest you play that card now, Ms. Lance.
We're working on it.
- Good?
- Am I good?
Well, considering my survival hinges
on me accessing the superpower
I'm not familiar with,
I'm a little, ugh...
- (SIGHS)
- Run fast. Run hard.
Don't die.
I can promise you two of those things.
- I'm in the MedBay.
- PROFESSOR STEIN: Be careful, Raymond.
It won't take long for Mr. Rory
to figure out where you are.
- Tell me something I don't know.
- (GROWLING)
(RORY GROWLING)
(GROWLING CONTINUES)
Party's over.
(SCREAMING)
- (GRUNTING)
- (GUNS FIRING)
Those things are
right outside the perimeter.
Kill the lights and hold your fire!
(FIRE HISSES)
(ZOMBIES GROWLING)
(BLOWS LANDING)
Hey! Over here!
Come and get it, you ugly freaks!
Follow me, you big dummies!
Come on! Follow the light!
Raymond?
Raymond, where are you?
What happened?
Oh, no. Don't be dead, Raymond.
On the other hand,
if you are dead, please stay dead.
Oh.
Just unconscious. Well done.
Now.
Where is that fire extinguisher?
Okay, Martin.
Just do what they did
in those zombie movies.
That you never had the courage to watch.
Come on!
That gentleman is either
the bravest man I've ever had
in my ranks...
Or the dumbest.
(GROWLING)
(EXPLOSION)
(GROWLING SOFTLY)
(STAMMERING)
If you... If you just cooperate,
things will go much easier for us.
(PROFESSOR STEIN GRUNTS)
You may be stronger
but I assure you
you will not eat me today!
(GRUNTING)
Professor, what's going on?
Was I just trying to kiss you?
I can only hope, Mr. Rory.
I can only hope.
- Everybody good?
- Yeah.
Jax, we got to go.
This fire is gonna attract
a lot of unwanted attention.
I know.
But I want to enjoy this for a moment.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
Okay.
Do you see your man anywhere?
Wait, hold your fire!
(DR. HEYWOOD GROANS)
Nate?
I'm covered in zombie guts!
But you're alive.
I think I'm gonna be sick.
This is a godsend.
We know how the rebels
are planning to take Champion Hill.
And when they do,
we'll be there to give 'em hell.
Set our cannon battery
up on the western ridge.
Yes, sir.
We'll light 'em up like the Fourth of July
when they roll over that hill.
- What's your name, son?
- Uh, it's...
Henry Scott.
Mr. Scott, thank you
for your incredible bravery
and your service to the United States.
You may have just won this war for us.
And are these men and women
from the Collins Plantation?
Yes, they are, sir.
We will care for anyone seeking refuge
in our camp from the Confederate states.
We have plenty of food and water
for everyone.
Thank you.
We've spread the vaccine
our friends worked up.
The only Confederates
you'll have to worry about now
are the living ones.
I'm obliged.
Your man, Colonel Sanders,
he, uh, tells me you're his captain?
In any case, he mentioned
something about you having regrets
about putting men in harm's way.
I don't think that's something
I can ever get used to.
You know,
by the time
I had taken over this division,
there had already been
three other generals in place before me.
They'd all stepped down and given up.
But I believe in my men.
And I believe
in the good that we're doing.
Do you?
Do you believe in your mission,
Captain Lance?
I do.
Then don't regret
making those tough decisions.
Ma'am.
- Hey.
Just checking up on you.
I don't feel like eating anyone's brains,
so...
Thank you.
Well, maybe you feel like eating a burger.
No sprouts.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Well, there's a little something.
- I had to ask, didn't I?
- It's just...
I don't think it's any secret
that without my suit,
I've been wondering
what my place on the team is.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
If I even have a place, you know?
Being an outsider is a good thing.
It's a great thing.
I've been an outsider my whole life.
You get to tell people to go shove it.
(SIGHING)
(GUN POWERING UP)
What are you doing?
Something I hope I don't regret.
This belonged to the greatest outsider
I ever knew.
I'm looking for a partner.
(GUN POWERING UP)
Cool.
What on earth are you doing?
Oh, uh...
Scrimshaw. It was my mom's thing.
She taught me a little.
Makes me think of her.
Oh.
I had no idea.
Are you homesick?
You checking up on me, Grey?
Given what you've witnessed,
what you've endured...
Would that really be so bad?
No.
You've just witnessed
the very worst of humanity.
We share a psychic connection
but I still can't even begin to fathom
what you must be feeling.
It must be like your heart is broken.
Yeah.
It is.
But I saw something
in those people's eyes...
I didn't expect to see.
I saw hope.
I saw dignity.
These men and women...
They were treated worse than animals.
But they never let anybody
stop them from being people.
You know?
I suppose there will always be
those who seek to dehumanize us,
but I believe there are more
that cling to hope despite the darkness.
Yeah, that's exactly how they were.
I was actually thinking of you, Jefferson.