Time travel is real,
and all of history is vulnerable
to attack,
which is why we must
travel through time
to stop the spread of these
so-called time Aberrations
and to erase their damage to history.
We are a team of outcasts
and misfits,
so please don't call us heroes.
We're Legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Thank you, Mister...
Hex. Jonah Hex.
Temporal Aberrations cause
these things called timequakes.
If there was a way of locating
their epicenters,
maybe we'll be able to fix
the Aberrations before they happen.
Whoa, there, wanderer.
Don't see many folks around here.
Been a while since this old mine
turned up anything worth taking.
Then I guess I'll be on my way.
And let you be on yours.
Oh, ain't you heard?
I'm the one that does
the letting around here.
Or do you need a reminder?
Wait. I know things
about these mines.
Things I can't tell you if I'm shot.
Oh, you'll tell me.
Or I'll shoot you, otherwise.
Now lower that iron
and start talking.
The ore in there? It's rare.
And powerful.
More powerful than gold.
And how would you
be the one to know that?
I can show you.
With your permission.
Found it using this.
There's enough in that mine
for the both of us.
We're the only ones who know.
We can be like partners.
Give it here.
Nice doing business with you,
partner.
What's with bad guys
and ancient amulets?
Any idea why Darhk wants this?
All I know is,
it's never a good idea
when your nemesis
starts accessorizing.
And he's teamed up with a Speedster.
- What's a Speedster?
- Someone with super speed.
That's how Darhk escaped.
The energy of the Speed Force
grants the Speedster
Chronokinesis, temporal manipulation.
English, Professor.
It means that his running real fast,
lets him time travel.
I'll be in my room.
Martin, I need you to gather
everything you can on Speedsters.
And, Nate's right,
this amulet looks a lot like the one
we recovered off the Nazis.
There's got to be a connection.
Let me guess. I'm on library duty.
We're dealing with a Speedster here.
How long we gonna keep this secret
from them, Grey?
Come on, future Barry's message.
Yes, I know what you're talking
about, Jefferson.
And we have been through this.
Barry implored us not
to share any info...
You okay?
I'm fine,
it's just... just a headache.
You would tell me
if something was up, right?
Because if we start keeping things
from each other...
I just need to rest.
Saving history can be extremely
wearing on the body.
I'm thinking this amulet dates back
to Late Antiquity
and is Judeo-Christian in origin.
Great.
Is... is that great?
Well, I can't find a reference of it
anywhere.
Like, none.
Historically speaking,
this doesn't exist.
Well, this is right in front of us,
so I'd say it does exist.
And we know that Damien Darhk
and the Speedster
are willing to kill for it.
Sounds like you got
some more homework to do.
What?
I... I just thought, becoming
a superhero,
I would spend less time in
the library than my old job.
That's all.
Well, research skills
are a kind of superpower.
And you can turn to steel.
So you got two.
Saved by the Aberration.
Oh, what's the Trouble Alert say?
Look, I told you, don't call it that.
The timequake's epicenter is
Liberty, Colorado, 1874.
Hah! Back to the Wild West.
You guys were in the Old West?
- Yeah, town made me a Sheriff.
- That's cool.
All right. Well, I will go tell
Jax and Stein.
Who wants to tell Rory?
- Not it.
What?
Okay. I'll do it.
I don't know how to use them,
but I'm wearing spurs.
I remember my first time
in the Wild West.
I drove a real-life desperado
out of town.
- That's cool.
- And that was my hat.
Thanks.
- That's cool.
- What's this?
Oh, that's nothing.
Don't open that.
You don't have to open...
You opened it.
Did you draw your own
superhero costume?
No.
Absolutely not. Yeah, I did.
And I only did,
because when I steel up,
my clothes stretch out
and they fit all weird.
And besides, don't I deserve a suit?
I mean, am I just
the research guy here?
Look, I... I know what it's like
to be a rookie.
Just follow my lead,
and you'll be fine out there.
Oh, I know a few things
about the Old West.
Like, for instance, nobody says,
"howdy."
- Uh-huh.
- And, uh...
you know how to ride a horse, right?
Yeah, I can figure it out.
This loaded?
Yes. It is?
Oh.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Guys, I think my horse is broken!
Where's the Professor?
Uh, he's feeling a little off.
More whiskey for me.
- Yee-haw!
- Whoo-whoo-whoo!
Sounds like a commotion
of some kind.
Hold back, let's get a better look.
Yee-ha!
Look at him up there, boy!
Ah, it's a hanging.
Is that Hex?
You know that man?
We got to help him.
Well, we got to take
his crew out first.
- They look armed.
- Don't worry, guys.
I got this!
What?
Well, well, well,
you look a lot less mean
with that noose around your neck,
don't you, Hex?
You think this is finished?
Looking pretty finished to me.
Don't you think, boys?
You son of a bitch!
You might want to slow down there.
Because these here parts
ain't big enough for the...
five of us.
And who the hell are you?
What he said.
On second thought,
I don't give a damn!
Hold still, Hex.
Nice shot.
Now you get on that horse
and you ride till you feel like
you can't ride any further, then...
you ride some more.
- Now go on, get! Go on!
- Yeah.
Whoo!
Hyah! Whoo!
Hyah!
Woo-ah!
Face.
What?
Nothing.
Oh, hell.
They're back.
Saved by a filly.
Ain't that the damnedest?
A simple "thank you" would suffice.
How'd you know I needed saving?
Because we got an alert
that history was being changed,
and the coordinates led us
to your hanging.
Well, I guess it's nice to know
that I matter.
Leaving already?
I didn't get to shoot anyone.
I need a drink.
Where's Rip?
He's MIA.
Damn.
How the hell did you
miscreants manage
to not get yourselves killed
without him?
Miss Lance has been
serving as Captain.
But she's a lady.
You are a lady, right?
You know I could take your life
just as easily as I saved it.
Oh, fiery.
Whoever breaks her's
in for a wild ride.
Too bad this filly's
into other fillies.
You don't say.
So how did you end up
in the noose?
Well, I was collecting the bounty
on a pissant
by the name of Quentin Turnbull.
- As in Turnbull Country?
- Never heard of it.
That's because it's not supposed
to exist.
This book has changed
since the last time I saw it.
- Check this out, Gideon.
- Right away.
That's a map of the United States
from 1876.
All right, who is Turnbull?
Two-bit, yellow-bellied
cattle rustler.
Who controls all of the land
west of the Rocky Mountains.
Looks like we found our Aberration.
Am I supposed to have the faintest
idea what the hell this means?
It means that we need to stop
Turnbull from taking over the West.
Looks like you got yourself
a posse, partner.
Where is everybody?
Ever since Turnbull set up shop
about six months ago,
everyone's been run out of town
or made to work in the mine.
Mine? What kind of mine?
- Gold?
- Hell if I know.
Nobody's been mining for gold through
these parts for half a century.
Listen to me. These parts...
I sound like I'm a cowboy.
Well, he's pulling something out of
the ground that's making him rich.
Turnbull also owns the saloon.
The hotel, the laundry...
and the whorehouse.
The answer's no, Mick.
Turnbull's got an office
above the saloon.
It's also got about a dozen men
making sure nobody gets close to him.
I think I know how we can.
Mick.
Why don't you mosey on in there?
Have yourself a good time.
If you insist.
I'm not sure I understand your plan.
You just set a match to a powder keg.
And if Turnbull doesn't want
his saloon to burn down,
then he's gonna have to come out
of his office and deal with it.
Better yet, get your boy to get
in a fight with Turnbull,
and bring him out here on the street.
Amaya, your job is to make sure Rory
keeps his pistol in his pants
until he's outside the saloon.
Clearly, I drew the short straw.
So what you want us to do?
Reckon I can post up nearby
with a long gun.
- Are you chewing tobacco?
- Tootsie Roll.
Get rid of your hats and your guns.
What? I thought we were supposed
to be some badass cowboys?
You guys want to know how Turnbull
went from being a cattle rustler
to running his own country?
I'm gonna need you to infiltrate
his base of operations.
As what?
You all are tax collectors?
We're here to go over your books
and make sure everything's in order.
And we're in a bit of a hurry, so...
Yes, we're on the next train
back to Washington D.C.
Well, there ain't no train
to Washington.
Pass won't be open till spring.
He means mule train.
This guy.
How do I go from desperado
to accountant?
At least, Mick's having fun.
Stuck here doing research
while everyone else is out drinking.
It's like high school all over again.
A shot.
Make it two.
You're with him?
Unfortunately.
Guys, I think I found something.
According to this ledger,
Turnbull's stockpiling some kind
of ore in a nearby mining camp.
And you are?
I work for Mr. Turnbull.
Who are you?
My friends and I are with
the Internal Revenue Service...
Ah, Mr. Turnbull don't like
no taxmen.
Well, nobody likes paying taxes,
but they are an essential part
of the Federal Government...
Mr. Turnbull don't like
the Federal Government, neither.
Is that why he's trying to start
his own country?
Oh, now I see why'd you have to go
and say something like that.
Now I got to pump some lead into you
so you don't go blabbing
to the wrong person.
Hey, hey, would you shoot
an unarmed man?
I think that's a yes.
So what's your history with Turnbull?
Come again?
Well, you said that you had dealings
over the years.
I can tell a vendetta when I see one.
I'm kind of an expert
when it comes to revenge.
This is what it's like working
with a woman?
You just sit around
and talk about your feelings?
Well, if your feelings
are what almost got you hung,
then, yeah.
I'd say they're worth talking about.
Not in my century.
Now that we've got outlaw outfits,
it's time to find out what Turnbull's
stockpiling at his mining camp.
Or we could do the responsible thing
and head back to the ship
with the rest of the team.
You're joking, right?
Time to cowboy up.
Oh!
- Another blackjack.
- Must be my lucky day.
- You're cheating.
- I'm winning.
Sweetheart, that's for you.
I'll see you around.
Piano man. Play something else.
I've had more fun at a funeral.
Bartender!
And who might you be?
Name's Turnbull.
Never heard of him.
That's my name on the sign
in front of the saloon.
Or can't you read?
So it's your money I'm winning?
Well, that's interesting.
I'd say your luck has run out,
partner.
You just gonna stand there
and make threats?
Or you gonna back it up?
Amaya, what's going on in there?
You wanted Rory to start a fight.
I'd say your plan's working.
Man, these clothes smell like ass.
People didn't wash
in the Wild, Wild West?
Well, we're criminals, remember?
It's important to smell the part.
Game faces, boys.
We got company.
I don't recognize you three.
That's probably because
of our new bandanas.
This one off his rocker?
You could blow his brains out,
only he doesn't got any.
Nice work.
Gideon, let's run the neural imaging
scan again.
There... there must be something
you missed.
The odds that I misdiagnosed your
condition are infinitesimally thin.
The algorithm programmed
into my medical diagnostic systems...
Please just do it.
As you wish, Professor.
Biometric scan reveals
all brain functions
are within normal parameters.
Physiologically,
there's nothing wrong with you.
Are... are you implying that my
symptoms are psychosomatic?
Because...
Please...
I need you to run the test again.
Oh, my God.
What is it?
It's dwarf star.
One of the rarest minerals
in the universe.
How does this help Turnbull
take over the West?
I used dwarf star to power
the ATOM suit.
The piece I had was the size
of your little finger.
There's enough potential energy here
to power the entire Wild West.
Or blow it up.
Question is, how does Turnbull
even know what it is?
Bet you this has something
to do with it.
It's some sort of tracker,
definitely not from the 1800s.
Probably stole it
from the time pirate.
- We got to get this out of here.
- Yeah.
Oh, I should've mentioned,
it's also the densest material
in the universe.
Let's get the rest of the team.
Amaya, it's been forever.
What the hell is going on in there?
Your plan's caught something
of a snag.
Explain.
Well, it's hard to...
But Mr. Rory and Mr. Turnbull...
like each other.
What?
What happened to Rory
starting a fight?
I think it's more likely that him
and Turnbull get matching tattoos.
Then they told me to put my hands up
and my pants fell down.
Because of all the loot
I was carrying!
You see, that's what them damn fools
in government back in Washington
don't understand,
that men like you and me,
we wasn't meant to live in cages.
Hell, that's why our forebearers
busted away from England
to begin with, so we could be free!
And that's what
Turnbull Country is all about.
It's about keeping
the Wild West wild.
I'll drink to that.
Will you have some of that?
Are you gonna sit around
while those two bend elbows?
What are you doing?
I'm gonna collect my bounty,
whether you like it or not.
Stick to the plan, Jonah.
Your guy on the inside
ain't sticking to no plan,
why the hell should I?
Sara? What do you want me to do?
Brace yourself.
Turnbull!
Well, if it ain't
the great Jonah Hex himself.
Whoo, you got quite a pair to walk
into my establishment like this.
You're like a cockroach.
Hard to kill.
I'm taking you in.
Alive or dead.
Your choice.
I choose...
dead!
Actually, Jonah...
I'm glad you decided to pay me
this little visit.
You see I've been working
on a little something.
It seems that ore
that I discovered...
Well, it's got special qualities.
Let's party!
Come on!
Why do you guys
get to have all the fun?
We just got back
from Turnbull's mine.
The reason for the Aberration?
He's digging up dwarf star.
Get back to the ship.
That's right, run,
you yellow-bellied cowards!
Finally! Some excitement.
Mick, no!
And here I thought you and me
was gonna be friends!
I don't have friends.
Nate?
- Nate? Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I'm the Man of Steel, remember?
Oh, my gosh.
Gideon, prepare to run diagnostics.
What's to run? I've been shot!
The bullet has lodged itself
between several
of Dr. Haywood's internal organs.
How's that possible?
He's made of steel.
Because it wasn't a normal bullet.
It was dwarf star.
I estimate his chance
of survival at 51 percent.
Would it kill you to say
better than average, Gideon?
We had a plan.
You went off book.
Now you're gonna cut the crap,
and tell me what the hell is going on
between you and Turnbull.
I don't answer to you, Miss Lance.
It's Captain Lance.
And if you did answer to me,
Nate wouldn't have gotten shot.
Now, I know you don't like
taking orders from a woman...
but you're gonna like getting your
ass kicked by one even less.
I've been after Turnbull
for eight years now.
I almost got him twice.
He wants to see me
pushing up daisies
just as bad as I want to see him
do the same.
Because why?
Little town in Oklahoma.
Goes by the name of Calvert.
Turnbull and his men
were harassing it.
And they hired me to fight back.
Calvert, that's the town
that Rip left in the lurch.
My little rebellion...
made other towns think they didn't
need to pay protection money
to Turnbull and his gang.
So one night...
Turnbull gathered every man, woman,
and child in Calvert.
Locked us in the church.
Set it on fire.
Somehow, I escaped.
The good Lord saw fit to leave me
with a souvenir.
Oh, what the hell am I telling
a woman this for?
You'd never understand.
Wrong.
Like I said,
vendetta's kind of my thing.
I've got a Turnbull.
And he's still out there.
Well, here you are with a timeship.
Been there, tried that.
Killing Darhk would create ripples
in history that I can't control.
But there are things
that I can control.
I can help you capture Turnbull.
Even though I screwed up?
Been there too.
I'm starting to think
that screwing up is...
just an essential part of surviving.
So how's your headache?
Oh, it's fine.
Nothing a little aspirin
couldn't help.
Funny, that's not what
Gideon told me.
What's going on?
And don't lie, because you know
I can always tell.
All right,. While you were away, I...
I had a vision.
A vision? Like a hallucination?
It's possible it could merely be a...
a side effect from multiple
time jumps.
Whoa, Grey! Grey!
Grey?
That is not a reaction
to time travel.
What did you just see?
A... a woman.
Someone I've never met,
but her face, it keeps...
flashing in my mind.
It's like...
I'm having memories of a stranger,
but she's... she's not...
not really a stranger.
But I...
I haven't the slightest notion, why?
Trying to work out your frustration?
Something like that.
What happened out there today?
You lost control.
Says you.
That man back in town, the drinker,
the gambler, the animal...
that wants to watch the whole
world burn...
that's the real me.
I happen to know a thing
or two about animals.
They're not vicious by nature.
Unless they're attacked.
If you're trying to tell me to...
to tell you some sob story about
how horrible and painful my life is,
forget it.
I'm no victim.
Sara's told me all the things
that you've done for this team.
And you don't sound like an animal
who just wants to watch
the world burn.
They like to pretend
I'm part of the team,
that they have me on a leash.
No.
Now...
if you'll excuse me.
Some superhero.
Maybe I am better suited
for the library.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
You had no idea that Turnbull
laced the bullets with dwarf star,
or that you were even
vulnerable to it.
When I was a kid...
there was this bully, Shane Blocklin.
And one day, I decided,
"I'm gonna stand up to old Shane."
Long story short,
he breaks my nose in two places.
But from that point on, I was, uh...
I was different.
I was afraid.
And then I meet you guys,
and I get these superpowers.
And I said to myself,
"Nate, you don't have
to feel afraid again."
Well, maybe now you know how I felt
after you destroyed my ATOM suit.
When we were out fighting
with the Shogun,
without my suit, I was afraid.
Well, you hid it well.
That's because I realized that...
weakness, or not being invulnerable,
is what makes me a hero.
There's no bravery without fear.
That was a really good
inspirational speech.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well, I have a few other aphorisms
in my back pocket.
Like, courage is the mastery of fear,
not the absence of fear.
Strength is...
You know what, buddy?
You nailed it.
Sorry, got a little carried away
with my train of...
That's it.
I think I know how Turnbull's
gonna make his own country.
When I saw how much dwarf star
ore he had in that mine,
I started to wonder. How could
he transport such a heavy shipment?
He'd have to use...
- The railroad.
Okay, get to the part where we care,
Ray.
I think he's gonna use the railroad
and the dwarf star to...
wait for it.
I don't want to wait for it.
Close Summit Pass.
- Oh, my God, Ray's right.
- Thank you.
Summit Pass connects
East-West via railroad.
Not if Turnbull uses this...
- the magic.
- Dwarf star?
Yeah, to blow the thing up.
Well, if he destroys the pass,
there's no way of transporting
soldiers and supplies
from the East coast.
The U.S. Army is effectively
locked out of the West.
So it's simple. We just stop
Turnbull from blowing up the pass.
Yeah, simple.
You don't have a suit.
You just had invasive surgery.
Stein's out of commission.
We'll think of something.
"Courage is the mastery of fear,
not the absence of it."
Yeah, what about Turnbull?
If that train goes boom...
he's not gonna be on it.
I overheard one of his people saying,
Turnbull just called for a meeting
at his mine.
You, Jax, and Ray, stop the train.
The rest of us,
we'll deal with Turnbull.
You sure about this?
Of course.
This isn't my first rodeo.
I wanted to say that.
There's our train.
Loaded with enough dwarf star
to punch a hole in a mountain
and cut off the pass to the East.
How do we stop a moving locomotive?
We don't.
I do.
I think.
Yeah!
- So what do you think?
- I think I liked him.
That's three of them
for every one of us.
Hex and I will draw their attention.
While you two go make sure
Turnbull can't pull
anymore dwarf star out of the ground.
We'll need about five minutes
to plant enough dynamite
to seal the mine.
It's about time we got
to light something up.
Just light the fuse and run.
Don't stick around for the fireworks.
Yeah, yeah.
All right, I've got a plan
to get us close to Turnbull.
Are you ready to follow
my orders this time?
Aye, aye, Captain.
Good. Now, put these on.
Quentin Turnbull!
Who's asking?
I heard you're looking for someone.
Jonah Hex!
Well, hell, looks like I'm gonna
have to kill you for the third time.
I'm impressed, boy.
Jonah, Jonah, Jonah.
Back in the belly of the whale.
A lily-livered whale who killed women
and children.
Whoa, no, that was before.
I've changed.
I got purpose now.
Matter of fact, why don't I show you
what I'm working on
so you know why you died?
You come along too, boy.
Anyone who can bring in Hex,
always got a place on my crew.
Nate, what are you doing, man?
Hold on!
Keep your distance!
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna cut them off at the pass.
I've always wanted to say that.
You can't get in front
of a moving train!
You said it yourself,
there is no bravery without fear!
Which is good, because
I am scared as hell right now.
Yeah!
Colt Single Action Army.
The gun that won the West.
Some folks like to call it,
The Peacemaker.
Only I don't much care for peace.
Yeah, thanks to what
I pulled out of this mine,
I got my own weapon now.
Something that's gonna tip
the scales.
Win the West back for the folks
it belongs to.
The outlaws!
Hyah!
- Okay. I'm in position.
- And out of your mind!
You couldn't even stop
a bullet made with that stuff.
That train is loaded
with dwarf star, man!
You guys aren't helping.
You got a whole minute
to get out of here.
You mean we have a minute.
That's what I meant.
Should we tell them about the minute?
No.
Good.
I was hoping you were gonna say that.
Who's next?
Mick, we got to go!
Mick, now!
Put the animal away.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
Those bullets ain't nothing.
Wait till you see what I got now.
Now, get on in there!
You ain't no man!
You burned down Calvert!
You murdered all those people!
For what?
For power?
Oh, get it over with!
Alive or dead?
Alive!
You lucky son of a bitch.
I got this. I got this.
I got this.
I got this, I got this,
I got this, I got this.
Did you see that? Did you see that?
Tell me you saw that.
Yo, that was badass, dude.
Totally badass.
- You all right?
- No.
But I stopped a train.
I think he's good.
Whoo!
I stopped a train!
That's a mighty fine job
you did back there.
Captain.
I'll drink to that.
So now that you have your man,
what are you gonna do with him?
Turnbull?
If I had my way, he'd be in
for a long, painful demise.
I'd let him bleed out from the gut.
But I'm gonna turn him over
to the authorities.
So you don't have to worry about your
Aberration.
Only territory Turnbull's gonna be
claiming is a cold, dark prison cell.
Then our work here is done.
You do a mighty fine job bearing
a burden few men could deal with.
Good thing I'm a woman then.
Yes, ma'am.
I best get Turnbull.
Collect my bounty.
Now, you try to stay out of trouble.
Not likely.
Wouldn't imagine so.
It really is beautiful.
It's no wonder that human beings
have worshiped fire for millennia.
Fire gives us life...
but also has the power to destroy
everything in its path.
Your point?
Or are you gonna keep talking
in metaphors?
Yeah, I know what a metaphor is.
But don't tell them.
You were right.
The animal who wants
to watch the world burn...
that is who you are.
But it's not all that you are.
Your point?
Don't deny the animal.
But don't let it control you either.
I can help you.
Believe me, I know a thing or two
about controlling wild beasts.
Oh, there you are.
So I've been thinking about
your memory flashes.
Manopause moments, or whatever
it is you want to call them.
I got a theory.
What if when you interacted with
your younger self in 1987, you...
Inadvertently changed my past
so... so that my memories
from my new life
are supplanting the memories
from my old life,
thus creating temporal dissonance.
Yeah, that's exactly
what I was thinking.
Oh, it's a brilliant theory,
which I... I happen to share with you
but it... it doesn't explain...
Who the mystery lady is.
Or...
that I'm fairly certain I love her.
Man, Clarissa is gonna
kill you when you get home.
Assuming there even is
a Clarissa to go home to.
Hey, heard you were looking for me.
Oh, yeah, I just wanted to thank you
for saving all that dwarf star ore.
I have enough to power
20 ATOM suits now.
That's cool, man, so we all get one?
Actually, there's something
I've been working on
before I start building
a new exo-suit.
It's not exactly what was
in your drawing.
I made a few improvements.
Shut the front door.
Yeah. I figure you earned it.
Steel.
Cool name.
Hey, are you guys done bro-ing out?
I mean, well, not really but...
- We can.
- Good.
Because our friends back in 2016,
they need our help.