Time travel is real, and all of history
is vulnerable to attack which is why
we must travel through
time to stop the spread
of these so-called time aberrations
and to erase their damage to history.
We are a team of outcasts and misfits,
so please don't call us heroes.
We're something else, we're legends.
Previously, on “Legends of Tomorrow”...
I'd forgotten how handsome I was.
- Hi, I'm Marty.
- Have a wonderful life, Martin.
This belonged to the
greatest outsider I ever knew.
I'm looking for a partner.
- Hello, Rex.
- [screams]
With his last words,
he told me his killer
was a time traveler.
Damien Darhk murdered my sister.
If I take him out here...
You save her. We gotta let him go.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
So it's all here, then?
Every sweet-smelling speck of it.
♪ ♪
As for my compensation?
Strange form of payment.
[dramatic music]
Why this and not cash?
Everyone has a hobby.
Some men collect stamps.
I collect relics.
This "thing" is called a fasces,
a ceremonial axe
carried by the bodyguard of Emperor Nero
from which a term "fascism" derived.
No? A form of rule,
which, in my opinion,
is getting a bit of a bad rap lately.
DEA! Get your hands in the air, now!
[electric crackling]
[grunts]
You know, I had this under control.
My way's faster.
Speed isn't everything, Mr. Thawne.
You should've learned that lesson by now.
What's it been... 45 years since
you hired me to nuke New York?
Well, 45 years for you,
maybe, but for me?
Huh.
Good seeing you again, old friend.
Old? That's fair. Friend?
Now that's something
that has to be earned.
Lovely piece. What is this?
First century AD, if I'm not mistaken?
What is it that you want?
A partner.
Pass... I prefer to work alone.
Oh, yeah, gathering
your hive of followers,
building your empire, designing your ark.
Yeah, I know what you're planning.
And how it works out.
You want to reshape the world?
Try reshaping history.
Try rewriting destiny...
Try putting our partnership
into concrete terms,
as in, what's in it for me?
Well, perhaps content
collecting symbols of power,
but... I can give you actual power.
EDIT BY
||Abdullah Elalmany||
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
We have the tools to make a difference.
We can make history better.
Even if we act with
the best of intentions,
these changes can
ripple throughout time...
A temporal domino effect
with disastrous consequences.
So we start small.
Make changes we can control.
What you're talking about can't be done.
It's... it's like playing God,
and it goes against everything
we're trying to do.
I thought we were trying to help people.
We're helping by fixing aberrations,
not creating them. You're not thinking
fourth dimensionally.
Did you really just use Doc Brown on me?
Who the hell is that?
Sarah, come on, you can't
be Switzerland on this one.
In my heart, I agree with you...
but that's not what Rip
entrusted us to do.
Our job is to protect history.
You mean clean it up after somebody else
makes a mess of it. Time janitors...
That's all we are.
[sighs]
[electric crackling]
Easy, point and shoot.
You're up.
All right, point and shoot.
[electronic whirring]
[glass shattering]
[grunts]
- [sighs]
- You killed my beers.
Come on, the trigger's really sensitive,
and these goggles make
everything look blue.
[sighs] You know, it'd be really easy
for me to improve this
whole setup by just
iterating the power source.
There's nothing wrong with the gun.
You've just gotta be cool. Like Snart.
Yeah, I can be cool.
[sighs]
- What are you doing?
- Trying to be cool.
Maybe this was a bad idea.
[scoffs] You know, this may shock you,
but I was considered
extremely cool when I left
my cushy six-figure Silicon Valley job
and started my own tech company.
Ladies were lining up.
Listen, Haircut, if you want to fit
into Snart's shoes, you gotta
find the pain, the darkness,
the anger. You got it in you?
Call me Haircut again and I'll ice you.
Not bad.
Hey, what are you doing?
A little side project
I've been working on
with Ray and the professor.
Hmm. It said that
temporal aberrations cause
these things called timequakes.
So I started thinking, if there was a way
of locating their epicenters,
maybe we'll be able to fix
the aberrations before they happen.
- Like a time seismograph.
- That's an awesome name,
and I'm totally gonna steal that.
If the JSA could get
even a glimpse of all this,
- they would...
- They'd what?
Never mind.
Hey, wait. We've barely had
half a conversation since
you came on board,
and you were friends with my grandfather.
Talk to me. What was he like as a person?
Your grandfather was a great man.
That's it? He's a great man?
Is it because your
missions were classified,
or is it because you
really didn't know him
- well as a person?
- It's because the JSA
didn't encourage its
members to fraternize.
Something you and your
team should consider.
[whirring]
It worked?
Oh, it worked all right.
Where's it coming from?
Washington D.C., December 7, 1987.
1600 Pennsylvania Avenue.
- So?
- Dude, that's the White House.
So what?
December 7th was the day
before Reagan and Gorbachev
signed the INF Treaty,
reducing both countries'
nuclear arsenals and
paving the way for the end
- of the Cold War.
- How do you know all that?
Because I was in the
capital for that very summit.
The Reagan Administration
would call upon the top
nuclear physicists to act
as technical advisors.
You think someone might
have traveled back in time
to stop the treaty from being signed?
That, or worse. Think about it,
Reagan and Gorbachev under the same roof
at one of the most volatile
moments in history?
The JSA has a training academy in D.C.
I could reach out to
the current membership,
see if they have any intel
or resources we could use.
Good idea, but you shouldn't go alone.
1987 is a long way from 1942,
and it's dangerous to know
too much about the future.
- I can handle myself.
- I'll go with her.
Great, you two reach out to
the JSA while the rest of us
break into the most secure
residence in the country.
And how exactly do we do that?
Welcome to the White House.
This is Cross Hall,
a magnificent space that
connects the State Dining Room
with the East Room.
All right, fan out, stay on the coms,
and report if anything
seems out of place.
[dramatic music]
Women actually wore these
things in the '80s?
Shoulder pads? Yeah,
they were supposed to
make women more imposing,
more, I don't know...
- Manly?
- Yeah.
I'd hoped that by this decade,
women wouldn't need to use
clothing to compensate for their status.
Surely by now men and women
are considered equals.
Never lose that optimism.
This is it.
This is the JSA Academy?
Inside a crummy warehouse?
The JSA Academy is hidden
inside a crummy warehouse.
Prepare to see the most
elite training facility
in all of history.
[patriotic music]
♪ ♪
Maybe "elite" means
something different in 1987.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
When I was recruited,
this is where I was brought to train.
What happened to the JSA?
No clue...
but a lot can change in 45 years.
I thought you said you were a historian.
How can you not know?
Hey, every memo, every executive action
relating to the JSA is top secret.
I only pieced together their
World War II activities
from my father's bedtime stories,
witness testimonies,
and government leaks.
♪ ♪
I never should have left 1942.
Look, Amaya, whatever
happened to them, that's...
That's not your fault.
You don't know that.
Like you said, you don't know
what happened to them.
[sighs]
1987... the halcyon days
of Whitney Houston
and "Star Trek: The Next Generation."
I can remember this year
as if it were yesterday.
Well, it looks like there's
something you forgot about.
Mr. Stein, so nice to meet you.
Uh-oh...
That's me.
Go, go.
I thought you said you
were stuck in meetings
- on the Hill all day.
- I was.
I never stepped foot
inside the White House.
The aberration must've
caused infinitesimal ripples
that affected the movements
of my younger self.
The temporal domino effect...
This is why we should
never interfere with history.
Well, we'll agree to disagree.
But one thing's for sure,
we cannot let him see you.
Indeed, the last time he and I interacted
nearly erased our
marriage from existence.
[sighs]
Those are jelly beans.
I can see that.
President Reagan's jelly beans.
So what? Eat 'em.
What? I'm pretty sure
that's against the rules.
We don't follow rules, remember?
Oh, right.
[mysterious music]
♪ ♪
Hah.
Reagan wasn't even one of my
top three favorite presidents.
- Want some?
- Yeah.
Oh, it'll take some massaging,
but I believe we can get
the Soviets to agree to
eliminating all nuclear
ground-launched, ballistic,
and cruise missiles.
I'll even make them
believe it was their idea.
I don't know what we'd do
without you, Mr. Darhk.
Oh, you'd manage,
but winning is always better.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
I think we found our aberration.
Our next stop is the...
Damien Darhk is here.
Sara, don't do anything rash.
Sara? Sara, are you lis...
Here's another diplomatic cable from 1956
fromfrhe British ambassador
warning the JSA about
Soviet spies in their midst.
I thought fighting
Hitler would unite the U.S.
and the Soviet Union.
Oh, we have so much Cold War
history to catch you up on.
[metallic crashes]
Okay, what's this?
[intense music]
♪ ♪
[bird shrieks]
[hissing]
♪ ♪
Aah!
Todd?
Why? Why did you abandon us?
[grunts]
Who is that?
It's Obsidian.
From the JSA?
Ohh.
- Soviets to agree to...
- [inaudible speech]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Ma'am, I'm gonna need
you to drop the weapon.
Drop the knife and place
your hands behind your head.
We've got a situation in the East Wing.
[grunts]
I know you want vengeance for
Laura, but it's not that simple.
Get out of the way.
- Don't move!
- Stay where you are!
- Damn it.
- We gonna fight or leave?
Fight.
[lasers blasting]
All right, get out of here. I got this.
No, you go. I got this.
I said go!
[lasers blasting]
What did I say about crossing streams?
You said we don't follow the rules.
That's the one rule...
One rule we follow!
[grunts] Go!
[grunts]
[glass shattering]
[electric crackling]
[intense music]
♪ ♪
[upbeat music]
We interrupt this broadcast
with breaking news:
Chaos in the capital.
Just a day before
President Reagan is set to
welcome General Secretary
Gorbachev to the White House
to sign the INF Treaty,
a White House tour ends in
violence and what witnesses
describe as "a rocket man."
Was this an act of terrorism...
Please, turn it off, Gideon.
I can't bear it.
So your thirst for
vengeance nearly landed
the entire team in prison.
I guess it's only okay to change history
if it's with your personal vendetta.
Wasn't all Blondie's fault.
Haircut screwed up as well.
Wha... If you would just
let me tinker with the cold gun,
I told you I could figure out the whole
crossing the streams problem.
There's nothing wrong with the cold gun.
It's you, you goof.
The bigger question is:
Why did Damien Darhk become an advisor
to Reagan's White House on
the eve of a nuclear treaty
with the USSR?
If his involvement with the Nazis in 1942
is any indication, he's working with
our time traveling nemesis.
It's the same person who killed Hourman.
Amaya needs to hear about this.
So she can also lose focus,
risking everything in a
selfish pursuit of revenge?
Do you have something you'd
like to say to me, Martin?
Yes, that killing Damien
Darhk almost 30 years
before his actual death will
have countless unforeseeable
effects on the history that we
are charged with protecting.
Well, what about protecting my sister?
She brought me back from the dead.
She risked everything for me.
How could I not do the same for her?
Because you answer to
a higher calling, Sara.
I'm sorry, but we cannot stray
from our guiding principle.
Well, I'm sorry, too.
It sounds like you've never
really cared about anyone.
[whispering] Do you think I killed him?
I hope I didn't kill him.
He's gotta be in his late 70s at least!
Maybe he couldn't take the hit.
Oh, my God, I just killed a
member of the Justice Society.
Why are you whispering?
In case he's not dead,
he could probably use the nap.
- I'm not an invalid...
- [sighs]
Just old.
And you, you haven't aged a day.
It's one of the few
benefits of time travel.
So you left us to join
the loveable losers.
I was trying to find Rex's killer.
And you never thought to tell me?
I found Rex dying.
His last words were "time traveler."
I didn't think. I just acted.
What happened to them, Todd?
After the war, our friendship
with the Soviet Union ended,
and we continued fighting
as what was known as
the "Iron Curtain" descended
over central and eastern Europe.
Does "we" include my grandfather?
Right to the end.
In 1956, President Eisenhower
sent a team on a mission to Leipzig.
They never made it back.
Why didn't you go?
'56 was a charged time.
They were concerned that
I couldn't be trusted.
- Why not?
- Leave it be, Nathaniel.
Nate, Amaya, report
back to the Waverider.
I promise you, Todd, I will fix this.
What's done is done, Amaya.
Not when you have a time machine.
I'm sorry for leaving, Todd.
I truly am.
Rex's killer is here? In 1987?
Potentially, if Damien Darhk
is still working with him.
No way, Damien Darhk
joined the Reagan Administration
as an advisor at the Reykjavík Summit?
And after the collapse of the summit,
Darhk was credited with
reviving the disarmament talks?
Darhk prefers stockpiling nukes,
not getting rid of them.
The nuclear treaty must be a cover.
For what purpose?
That's what we need to find out.
Gideon, where is Damien Darhk now?
I'm accessing the
calendar on his secretary's
IBM personal computer.
Mr. Darhk has a meeting in
Georgetown Park at 8:00 p.m.
Late night meeting in the park,
that's not suspicious.
Ray, take Mick. Find out who Darhk
is meeting with and why.
Wait, just us?
[sighs] Look, it's not a good idea
for me to be anywhere near
Damien Darhk right now.
I... I agree.
Okay, we're a go on audio.
Cutting it close, haircut.
That's Snart's jacket.
I... thought it would help
me get into character.
- I'm Colonel Cold.
- The hell you are.
You're not gonna give yourself a promotion.
Fine.
What are you doing?
Well, we're on a stake-out.
Brought snacks.
Apple slice?
Guess you're still upset
about the White House.
Look, I can be more careful.
I can be more meticulous,
more like Snart.
I don't want you to be like Snart.
What?
You gave me his gun. You told me I had to
try to fill his shoes.
I was wrong.
You keep reminding me of my...
my dead friend.
It's bringing up... It's bringing up f...
- Feelings?
- Yes.
So just stop and be you.
Well, that's a little difficult,
considering I lost my suit,
my company, my powers.
Is this what an existential
crisis feels like?
Shut up. Just... shut up.
♪ Oh, I, I just died in
your arms tonight ♪
I hate the '80s! [smash]
Is there any sign of
who Darhk's meeting with?
Not yet!
Clandestine meeting in a D.C. park.
It feels like the beginning
of a John le Carré spy novel.
I'm more of an Ian Fleming guy.
Mm, more explosions, less clothing.
What if Darhk is
meeting with Rex's killer?
Then we don't let either of them leave.
We've got movement.
A man just entered the park.
Ray, we need audio.
Yep, way ahead of you, Cap.
Thankfully, there was
a Tech Village nearby.
You wouldn't believe what
you can hack together
with a few household items.
Dobriy Vecher, Mr. Darhk.
Sounds like he's meeting with a member of
the Soviet delegation, not Rex's killer.
The package is procured.
Excellent news, Boris.
That is your name, isn't it?
Boris? Or is it Igor?
I find it's always one or the
other with you KGB agents.
Anywho, once the treaty is signed,
during the State Dinner,
you'll deliver the package.
And you will uphold
your half of the bargain?
As agreed.
But first, a toast.
To peace between our two nations.
Darhk was never interested
in the nuclear treaty.
He's working a side deal with the KGB.
Uh-oh. Mayday!
My... My name is Martin Stein.
You must have heard of me.
You may have heard of me.
Marty, younger you just entered the park.
What? But that... that's impossible.
Today is December 7th,
Clarissa's birthday.
I distinctly remember we
had a dinner reservation
for this evening which
took me months to procure.
Well, you must have blown her off.
- This ought to be good.
- Should we stop him?
Stop what? What am I doing?
Mr. Darhk, uh, allow
me to introduce myself.
My name is Martin Stein.
You may have heard of me.
I'm on the negotiating team
and was recently nominated
for my sixth Carlin Award in physics.
Congratulations.
Thank you. [laughs]
Did you follow me here?
I did. [laughs]
You see, I'm... I'm working on a...
a transmutation project that
is vital to national security.
I was hoping you might pass the
proposal on to the President.
Excuse me, I can't help
but notice you're wearing
a Komandirskie watch, typically supplied to
the Soviet Ministry of Defense.
Meeting with a Soviet outside
of the official negotiation schedule?
That is highly irregular.
[speaking Russian]
Ray, Mick, get in there, now.
Okay. [laughs]
Clearly, uh, there's been some
kind of misunderstanding.
I'll just leave and pretend these last
five minutes didn't happen. [laughs]
Unfortunately, my imagination
isn't quite that vivid.
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
[groans]
- Gray!
- Martin!
[grunts]
[coughs]
Ahh. [whistling]
Ray, what happened?
Darhk just stabbed Marty's younger self.
Where's Darhk?
We lost him.
It's gonna be okay.
I'm gonna get you back.
- Where is he?
- He's on his way now.
Don't worry, you're gonna be fine.
[groaning] You again?
I mean, me again.
Guess you figured it out.
How did this happen?
I'm too young to die.
Too brilliant to die.
Will one of you please shut me up?
- Gladly.
- Gideon?
I'm cauterizing the
younger Martin's wound.
I'm afraid it will leave both patients
with a rather nasty scar.
You should've let me punch him.
This is about time travel, isn't it?
That's why Special Advisor
Darhk stabbed me.
He wouldn't have stabbed you
if you had been having dinner
with Clarissa at L'Auberge
as previously planned.
Good God, Clarissa.
She's waiting for me at the hotel.
How could you have left
her alone on her birthday?
She ordered room service.
You are a careless, self-centered idiot.
Gray, Gray, look, I'll go to the hotel,
and I'll tell Clarissa that
her husband's working late.
Okay? Just relax.
Oh, oh, Martin, what on
Earth were you thinking?
Hubba-hubba, who's that?
Professor Stein's wife.
Jax is at her hotel
explaining why she has to
spend her birthday alone.
Wait a minute, if he used everyone's
favorite talking computer to find her...
Gideon, do you have the
location on Damien Darhk?
Unfortunately, I have no intel
on his current whereabouts.
But we know where he's gonna be.
His little side deal with
the Soviets is going down
at the State Dinner tomorrow night.
Which is probably the
most heavily guarded
dinner in history.
I think we know someone
who may be able to help.
Is that so?
One of Amaya's old JSA buddies,
and, by old, I mean old.
He may still have some
government contacts
- we can exploit.
- Absolutely not.
Whatever Darhk is planning
to exchange with the Soviets,
it can't be good.
Well, I'll contact the FBI.
You don't have to worry about it.
Except we do. Darhk's working
with a time traveler. That's way out
of the Bureau's league.
I believe this time traveler killed Rex.
All the more reason to stay
clear of that State Dinner.
You can't remain professional.
Are you kidding me?
She's nothing but professional.
She's all about being professional.
The only reason I could ever see her
not being... Oh, my God, you
and Rex Tyler were together.
- No.
- They were together,
weren't they? This makes total sense.
We weren't together.
Like I said before, fraternization among
teammates is unprofessional.
Rex and I were going to
leave the JSA after the war,
try and start a new life with each other.
And then he was cut down.
That's why I left the team,
and that's why I wouldn't
talk to you about them.
It's too hard.
And this is why I'm
reluctant to help you.
Because your emotions are
clouding your judgment.
She won't be facing Darhk alone.
We need your help.
I know you feel like I abandoned you,
but, please, don't abandon me.
Hey, how you doing?
I'm all right.
You know, the truth is,
this young man is like a stranger to me.
Every time I encounter
him, I can't imagine
I was ever that person.
I think anyone would
feel that way about meeting
their younger self.
I don't recognize my current self.
Mick told me I need to be more like me.
And he's right, which is rare.
Hmm, indeed.
The problem is I don't know
what being me means right now.
I don't know if that makes any sense.
Of course it does.
I think everyone struggles
at least on occasion
with who they are and
then what their place is
in the world.
So what's the answer?
I have no idea.
But, I suppose it's just to live.
It's all any of us can really do.
And then, hopefully,
through the act of living
we discover who we truly are
and learn to grow from that.
Amaya got us invites to the State Dinner.
Are you feeling up to it?
Yes, I'm feeling much better.
You feeling up to it?
I think what he means is:
are you gonna create
a diplomatic crisis and
risk unknown damage
to history by killing Damien Darhk?
I know what he means, Ray.
Earlier, you accused me of
not ever caring for anyone,
but you know that's not true.
I care very much about you.
And I'm less concerned about history
than I am about your conscience.
You're no longer an assassin, Sara.
You're our Captain.
Well, let's hope I remember that
when the time comes.
Now let's do this.
[Kenny Loggins' “Danger Zone” playing]
♪ ♪
♪ Revvin' up your engine ♪
Thank you for helping us get in.
Feels good to be back in the game.
I don't see Damien Darhk anywhere.
He'll be here.
♪ ♪
Oh, my God, what is she doing here?
Probably looking for her
husband, no doubt.
She's... she's coming this way,
what... what should I do?
Just... Just talk to her.
Mr. Jackson, I expected
to meet my husband here.
Have you seen him yet?
I'm sorry, no. I haven't.
I'd be worried, but it's just like Martin
- to lose track of time.
- [all chuckle]
Well, I'm sure, wherever he is,
you are foremost in his mind.
Who are you?
I'm... I'm a colleague of his.
My name is also Martin.
He never mentioned you.
Well, I'm sure he has more
important things to talk about.
[jazzy piano music]
Oh, uh, would you...
Would you care to dance?
I never seem to take the time
to enjoy these State Dinners.
Sure.
You all right? You seem tense.
When you find Rex's killer,
what are you gonna do to him?
Arrest him. What else is there?
You could kill him.
I'm a member of the Justice Society,
or at least I was when it existed,
I'm not some vigilante.
♪ ♪
I'm sorry, I don't mean
to pry, but you don't
seem too happy to be here.
It's just... Martin invited
me on this trip for my birthday,
and I've spent the
better part of it alone.
Perhaps you should talk to him.
I've tried, but Martin's
love for nuclear science...
It's irrepressible.
Sometimes my husband has tunnel vision.
Well, Martin is a fool, but,
believe me, he loves you.
You're far more important to him than
any of his scientific achievements.
I have the strangest feeling,
like we've danced before.
[dramatic music]
Sara, Darhk's in the hallway.
♪ ♪
Mick, Ray, guard the exits.
And everybody else,
get ready to move.
Now that our governments
are waging peace upstairs,
what do you say we get
down to the real business?
You have brought us the codes?
It's called a CD-ROM, the latest
in Defense Department technology.
As for my half of the exchange?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[laughing]
Hand over the box.
And the kick-ass CD-ROM.
What is this?
[speaking Russian] _
He thinks we're working with Darhk.
Never.
No one has to get hurt.
That's not really my style.
Now, we can waste time chit-chatting,
or you can deal with the
explosive my people
have secreted inside
the State Dining Room.
See, in about six minutes,
Reagan, Gorbachev,
and every hope of peace goes kaboom.
- Ray?
- We're on it.
I am sorry... inconvenient,
I know, but try being me.
[all grunting]
[gasping] Todd?
We're on the move to find the bomb.
The bomb... We must save Clarissa.
♪ ♪
[all grunting]
I got this, Sara. Go stop Darhk.
Ooh!
[grunting]
[panting] That's cool, man.
Mary Todd's hope chest.
[smash]
Ooh, you have gone too far!
Everyone.
Get the hell out of here, right now.
[confused murmurs]
Now that we have your attention,
would you all please leave
the dining room immediately?
We believe there's a
bomb on the premises.
[screaming and yelling]
Oof!
[crashing]
[beeping]
- You okay?
- Who are you?
A friend of your husband's.
[beeping]
[suspenseful music]
[grunts]
Good news, I found the bomb.
Bad news, this type of
firing system is obsolete.
I have no idea how to
disarm such a crude weapon.
[gasping] Figure it out, Ray.
I'm a little busy.
[grunts]
[grunting]
Rah!
[choking]
There's nothing I can do.
Yes, there is.
I was wrong trying to
make you like Snart.
You're Ray Palmer...
You can science your way
out of anything.
I'm Ray Palmer. I'm Ray Palmer.
I can science my way out of anything.
I...
If I can send an electrical
pulse from an outside
power source, I might be able to overload
the bomb's incendiary trigger,
but I-I'd have to dismantle to cold gun.
Less talking, more doing.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- [gunshots]
- [grunts]
Huh.
[gunshot]
No!
[laughs]
Ahh!
- [grunts]
- Ray?
Tell me the bomb's disarmed.
[grunts] That would be a lie.
Well, ten seconds to live.
There are worse ways of dying.
[beeping]
[gasps]
[panting]
I did it.
Good.
Hold on, Todd. Okay?
Just hold on.
You and I have met before.
New York City, 1942.
You haven't aged a bit.
Lazarus Pit?
Oh, woman of mystery.
I know that look in your eye, though.
That's the look of someone that
I've taken everything from.
Not everything.
You haven't taken my soul,
which I've already lost,
and I'm not eager to do again.
And that's why I'm sparing your life.
How merciful of you.
I'm sparing you to
prolong your suffering.
'Cause I'm from the future,
Damien, and I know
how this all ends.
Your ark, your grand vision.
Just as you're about to accomplish
everything you desire,
your wife is murdered,
the love of your life.
And in total despair,
you even try to kill your own daughter.
An entire city rises up against you,
and then you die...
defeated and alone.
[electric crackling]
[gasps]
What happened? Where's Darhk?
He took him.
The time traveler working against us...
He's a speedster.
- Like the Flash?
- Faster.
So the speedster and Darhk,
they have whatever
the KGB gave Darhk?
Unless...
Unless?
I swiped it off Darhk.
- Shut up.
- [snorts]
Can I hug you? Do we hug?
- Okay, just this once.
- There's gonna be more.
Yeah!
You took a bullet for me.
For a fellow member of
the JSA, it was nothing.
Astonishing to be back here again.
A ship that can travel through
time and heal any wound.
- Think of the possibilities...
- Let me remind you,
it's imperative that you
carry on as if you never
so, me or anything else from the future.
That you would pass
up the chance to show me
even the barest glimpse of that future,
catapulting our transmutation
research into the 21st century,
I had no idea I could ever be so selfish.
Interesting, considering that's exactly
how you've been to Clarissa.
She nearly died last night
because of your blind
devotion to your work.
You of all people understand
the importance of our research.
I understand the importance
of one thing and one thing only:
After everything
I've accomplished, all...
- All of the awards I've won...
- Did we win the sixth Carlin?
The only thing that brings
meaning to my life is Clarissa.
Yes, Martin, our wife, who you spent
the last two days ignoring.
But I love Clarissa.
Then cherish her, Martin,
because I promise you,
she is the only thing you
will care to remember.
And I promise you...
I'll make sure she knows I love her.
I pray that you do.
[beeping]
[sighs]
Are you sure you won't come with us?
Rex's killer is still out there.
We could find him together.
I think last night proved
my fighting days are over.
You were amazing out there.
It felt like old times.
But there's something keeping
you here in 1987, isn't there?
After the JSA disbanded,
I spent a lot of lonely years
until I finally met someone, Amaya.
And he's waiting for me at home.
[laughs]
I have ameliorated Mr. Rice's injuries.
That's incredible. Wow.
A word of advice from an old
man who's lived long enough
to see the world change,
and mostly for the better:
If you are lucky enough
to find love again...
Embrace it.
Are you leaving already?
I was hoping we'd have a beer.
Oh, unlike you, my time is limited,
and I don't need the carbs.
Good-bye, Todd.
Well, I guess I just, uh...
He loved to sing.
Henry, your grandfather.
He had a... A beautiful voice.
During long convoys or stake-outs,
he would serenade the team.
He made it his personal mission
to get me to sing along,
but he never succeeded.
But when the chips were down
and all hope seemed lost,
we could always count on
Henry to lift our spirits.
That's the kind of man
your grandfather was.
[bottles clink]
Then take me back there now.
I will get your item back for you.
The Legends have left 1987.
The item is beyond your reach.
That blonde woman...
She's a time traveler like you.
She knows what happens
to me in the future.
- I'm sure she does.
- Then take me with you.
I need to change my destiny.
Tell you what, why don't we work together
to change both of our destinies?
Step inside.
Whoa.
[electric crackling]
[whirring]
EDIT BY
||Abdullah Elalmany||
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --