Archduke Ferdinand
is still alive!
World War I never happens!
That's 20 million lives saved.
Drinks are on the house!
Couple of stout?
- No, thank you.
- Oh, no, no, I'm too nervous to drink.
Nervous?
Sara Lance did it.
She changed a Fixed Point.
Yes, but she and our companions
are about to go into battle
with an evil Waverider,
and some extremely formidable
time correctors.
Not unless we kick their asses first.
I'm not gonna let some fascist time cops
tell me how history should be.
Yeah!
What have I done?
No, no. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is our battle, not yours.
Trust me now. This is not an enemy that
you want to be going up against now.
Yeah!
No, no, no.
I am terribly sorry, Legends.
I inadvertently ran my mouth,
and now all of the bar patrons are
headed your way to assist in the attack.
I sincerely hope
I haven't ruined the offensive.
Gideon, it's all right.
It's not your fault.
We're just going to have to take
the Waverider quickly.
All right, Cap, what's the plan?
When the robos exit
to restore the timeline,
we'll ambush and seize the Waverider.
So we just take Evil Gideon offline,
and the Waverider's ours.
Goodbye, robots.
Goodbye, janky time travel.
I wonder who they're copies of.
I hope it's not an army of Hoovers.
Robos are robos.
Doesn't matter what they look like.
We're taking them down.
Damn right, Astra.
There's no one the Legends can't beat.
Son of a...
That's who Evil Gideon sent to kill us?
We really are our own worst enemy.
All right, we're wasting time.
Should we attack?
No, they could use
the Waverider as cover.
We need to find something
to draw them away.
It's a trap.
Ms. Cruz and Mr. Green, stay on the ship
and help locate the Legends.
The rest of you,
eliminate every time traveler
and restore the timeline.
What the...
- No!
- Damn it.
No.
Robo me is steel with normal skin.
And he has giant arms?
I mean, come on, pick one.
The ego on me.
I mean, he's clearly overcompensating.
Oh, no, no,
he's really filling out those pants.
You heard Gideon.
Let's kill these time-traveling losers.
Steel punch!
Oh, my God!
I'm a monster.
- Wait.
- Behrad!
Stop killing people!
Gideon, we found 'em.
All right, let's draw them away.
Come on, go! Run! Go!
- Babe, come on.
- No, I'm fine.
- No, seriously, I'm fine.
- Okay.
Ow!
We need to get her out of here.
Get Ava to the Fixed Point.
Nate and I will buy you some time. Go!
It's okay. Let's go.
This way.
Halt your pursuit.
Aw, come on, Gideon. I can't wait
to kill the puny-armed version of me.
Believe it or not, Captain Heywood,
but the Legends
are merely distracting you.
The epicenter of this Aberration is
Archduke Ferdinand, who is still alive.
Did they stop following us?
That doesn't make sense.
What's more important than stopping us?
Well, we did delay
the start of World War I,
but you said Thawne was gonna
take care of that, right?
Yeah, but they don't know that,
and they've been
targeting time travelers.
I have to warn Thawne.
I'll meet you at The Fixed Point.
In a moment,
the archduke and his wife will pass by.
Princip, you must do
what the other members
of the Black Hand could not.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You can't be here.
He's got a weapon!
Oh, my God!
World War I is back on track.
I hope you did what you needed to do.
I haven't seen that outfit in ages.
At least her outfit
doesn't have a hole in it.
I'm okay, I'm okay.
Come on, sit down over here.
Let's take this coat off, now shall we?
Like shooting fish in a barrel.
Thawne.
Hey. All right, I'm going to get help.
You just hold on.
It's too late.
Thawne, I'm sorry.
It is...
It is yours now.
Hey, hey.
How's Ava?
Oh, Miss Lance. Yes, uh, well,
I used some vodka
to disinfect the wound,
and then she ingested even more
to numb her pain.
But by the grace of God,
she will be fine.
Okay, so...
here's the situation.
Our stealth plan has gone to hell.
The Waverider's in the air,
the Robo-Legends are after us,
and the time travelers
are all gone or dead.
Thawne is dead as well.
Poor chica.
What about the timeline?
Let's just focus
on the immediate problem.
The robos.
Now, unless someone has a better idea,
here's my crazy one.
I want to talk to them.
You want to talk to them?
Look, they want to protect the timeline,
we want to go home.
We both want the same thing.
So if I can just explain it to them
in terms they can understand...
I think it's a risk worth taking,
and I'd like to be here to assist.
You're waiting in the manor.
Look, I appreciate that, Gideon,
but you all need to wait in the manor,
in case this plan goes south.
Hey, babe. Are you feeling okay?
Just, uh...
- Just promise you'll be careful.
- I will.
Get some rest, okay?
Robo-Legends, this is Sara Lance.
How did you losers access our comms?
I, uh...
tried a bunch of different channels.
You've given up. Smart.
No, actually, I want to talk.
No fighting.
Meet me at the tavern
where they plotted to kill the archduke.
"No fighting."
They're pathetic.
I can't let you do this alone.
At a parley you must have a second.
- Look, we already had this conversation.
- But I insist.
You see, soldiers don't
go on missions by themselves.
They stick together.
It's part of the disciplines
and the rules of war.
Your rules have gone
out of the window, all right?
I need you to get back
to the manor, please.
Just go!
Out, peasants!
- Where's your captain?
- Hmm.
I'm the captain, flesh bag.
That's a choice.
Hmm.
Look, all this violence,
it's unnecessary.
We both want the same thing,
to protect the timeline.
Is that why you saved the archduke?
That was to lure the Waverider.
We had a plan to put history back,
which is why
you shouldn't have killed Thawne.
Our orders were
to kill all time travelers here,
including you.
We don't even want to be here.
We want to go home.
So let's just come to an agreement
so no one else has to die.
You Legends are the worst.
Well, you were modeled after us.
We're nothing like you!
You guys are pathetic losers
who ruin everything.
Were you programmed to be this annoying
or is that a personal choice?
We have one job,
and that's to protect the timeline,
and kill anyone who messes with it,
so I guess we have two jobs.
That's why we have to kill you,
you team, and your wife...
right here, right now.
Well.
Then I guess there will be fighting.
But I have to warn you,
I'm not that easy to kill.
Oh, because of your invincibility?
Hmm...
You know, I'm going to torture you.
I am gonna kill you
over and over and over again,
until you give me your team's location.
Bye.
Oh!
Nice try.
Why am I talking like this?
Whatever. It sounds wonderful.
Here we go.
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name...
Calm down. Calm down.
Calm down. You just need to
focus on your breathing.
Okay, okay, okay.
Gwyn, it's okay.
It's gonna be okay.
How am I going to kill you next?
Decapitation, that'd be fantastic,
to be able to rip off your head.
Hmm...
Gideon.
Hang on.
Gideon, she got away.
These Legends are like cockroaches.
But don't worry, I'm the exterminator.
What are we gonna do?
We can't reason with them,
we can't fight with them.
What am I going to tell the others?
That you tried to negotiate with them,
and that they tried to kill you,
that you fought honorably
and they fought dishonorably,
and therefore you are under
no obligation to fight with honor.
Honorably or dishonorably,
we still can't beat them.
In war, a soldier is only ever as good
as his general.
Even in the darkest of times,
it is the general's job
to be a beacon of light.
We are the Legends, not the military.
But it's all the same. Don't you see it?
I was a lost, lonely, and broken man,
but with your help,
I was able to build myself back up.
We are in the valley
of the shadow of death...
but we will get through this,
and we will defeat
those wretched machines.
I believe in you, Miss Lance...
like you believed in me.
And you will figure out
what we are to do here.
What would you do?
Who, me?
No, no, no, no. I'm no leader.
You are.
But you are a soldier with more
wartime experience than any of us.
So, against a dishonorable foe
like that, what would you do?
It is perilous for us to engage
in any adversary this lethal head-on.
The only way to defeat them
is to never confront them directly,
and to play dirty if we have to.
Fighting dirty is up my alley,
but avoiding them like cowards is not.
We must play to
our strengths, Miss Logue.
You see, theirs is brawn,
ours is brains.
We cannot out-punch them,
but we will out-think them.
Now, our objective
is to infiltrate their base
and overthrow their general.
Quick question. How are we supposed
to infiltrate the Waverider
if it's both cloaked and flying?
Excellent observation, Dr. Heywood.
And in order to circumnavigate this,
your obstacle,
we shall deploy a spy.
- Huh?
- Excellent.
Oh! Don't forget this.
A gun? Great.
Now, as soon as you board the Waverider,
you will need to disable Evil Gideon.
You see, shutting her down means
that the machines lose their general.
And without
Evil Gideon calling the shots,
the Robo-Legends should fall apart.
From your mouth to God's ears, my boy.
- I really got to do this alone?
- Never alone, my boy. Never alone.
You will be accompanied with the team
hidden in the key, mind you.
Because if anybody sees them...
- We're screwed.
- Exactly.
Now, as soon as Evil Gideon is offline,
you'll need to land the Waverider
so the rest of us can board.
Hey, what do you need us to do?
Well,
as the most experienced fighters,
you will distract the machines
by causing a ruckus in Sarajevo.
Ruckus? Can you, uh,
describe this ruckus?
A ruckus that will create
Time Aberrations
for them to deal with, you see.
Okay, so by aberrations
you mean like telling them
we put a man on the moon in 1969?
Good God, do we?
What was his crime, I wonder.
- All right.
- Yeah, let's do it.
- I don't think I can do this.
- Nonsense.
You are more than capable, my boy.
Of pretending to be a psychopath?
Now, you listen to me.
Now, I would not have
devised this mission
if I didn't believe in you, my boy.
Gideon, I'm gonna need
an immediate evac.
They're gonna mine me for parts.
Oh.
- Hey.
You think we're stupid?
We heard everything.
You heard... everything?
"Gideon, I need an immediate evac"?
I was going to put a bullet
in your sorry head to end your misery.
But then I saw you mowed down
those time travelers,
and that was pretty cool.
Yeah, I slaughtered
those innocent people.
Their relatives are definitely
mourning them right now.
Oh, I am so jealous.
Now hopefully, Gideon will let us out,
and we can kill Legends.
Or maybe
some will sneak on to the Waverider,
and we can shut down the oxygen
and watch them die slowly,
and then Gary can eat them.
No, but seriously,
I need to catch up to your kill count.
What are you at now?
Oh, uh...
Can't remember.
"Can't remember"?
How many time travelers did you kill?
Six... teen.
Sixteen.
Yeah.
Go see Dr. Sharpe and get upgraded.
Good idea. I'll do that now.
Ah... Oh!
What are you doing here?
Just going
to get my upgrade from Dr. Sharpe.
- Is she in there?
- Of course not, you idiot.
You know I'm the only one
who interfaces with Gideon.
Obviously, you tool bag.
Need any help?
What do you know about computers?
Just that they keep track
of my kill count.
Did you see me massacre
those time travelers?
It was like...
shooting fish in a barrel.
I'm proud of you.
See you after your upgrade.
I am going to need
a year-long cleanse after this.
Okay.
Ah...
They replaced the toilet.
Oh, perfect.
Oh, thank God.
Did you shut down Evil Gidget?
Not even close.
In fact, the only person
allowed access to her is robo you.
There's a robo me?
I'm pretty sure it's impossible to
duplicate this perfect bone structure.
Sure, but you're still going
to have to impersonate her.
Oh! My agents warned me
against playing villains,
but I will make an exception.
What does, um, my robo-self look like?
Uh, a '90s hacker.
Hmm, very cliché,
but I can work with it.
So get this,
not only do I have to play a psychopath,
the robos keep telling me I need
to go see Dr. Sharpe and get upgraded.
Just play dumb.
It took the Legends years
to realize I was an alien.
But even if I do that,
the only blind spot is in the bathroom.
How do I convince robo Zari to go there
so we can take her out?
Dr. Davies told us to fight dirty,
so maybe you don't convince her.
Gideon, that's genius!
Do you have a spell or potion
that makes people go to the bathroom?
- No.
- I do.
Uh, it's like a...
More of a food poisoning potion,
so I have no idea
what end it will come out of.
- Ooh!
- I would love to assist with this ruse.
- I can hide in the bathroom or...
- Gideon, stop asking to go out.
- But I know the Waverider better.
- Enough!
You're not leaving the manor.
Go and help Ava.
- Is everything okay?
- It's fine.
Okay.
It's all just twos and ones
and ones and twos
when it comes to planning your battle
and executing it perfectly
with the disciplines of the war.
No, no, no, no.
What are you doing back here?
You see, you're supposed to be out there
causing a ruckus
to distract the machines.
Dude, we've been trying.
Yeah, I've been doing the Macarena
for an hour out there,
and everyone just looks at me
like I'm crazy.
Yeah. And who knew it would be so hard
to introduce the high five?
I don't think this plan is gonna work.
Dr. Heywood, I do believe you are right.
You all just seem like
a bunch of raving lunatics to me, man.
Damn it!
Yes, we are never going to be able
to board the Waverider,
unless we can get the Waverider to land.
And it's not
going to be able to land
unless we can draw out
more of those dastardly machines.
Okay, Gwyn,
you are from this time period.
What would you do to cause a ruckus?
I don't know.
I do believe I have an idea.
Here's a little song I wrote
Hey, you guys want to see my fish?
Come check it out.
Come close. Come see it.
Don't worry
Yup.
Be happy
Every life we have some trouble
Hey.
When you worry you make it double
- Who's Darth Vader?
- Probably an American thing.
Be happy
Don't worry, be happy now
Don't worry
Be happy
Don't worry, be happy
Don't worry
Be happy
Don't worry, be happy
Stand back.
Got no place to lay your head
Somebody came
and took your bed
Don't worry
Be happy
Damn. Aberrations are everywhere.
This is the work
of the Legends.
Go help Captain Heywood
restore the timeline and eliminate them.
Finally.
I bet I can fix more aberrations,
kill more Legends than you.
One hour.
Loser gets to clean
all the guns in the armory.
Yes, that's two more machines
off the Waverider.
It's up to you now, my boy.
Copy that.
- You need to come with us, Behrad.
- It's time for your upgrade.
You want a power shot before my upgrade?
Sure.
I suppose I could use a boost.
I came up with a killer hack
that makes you feel totally energized.
What makes your hack so killer?
My own creatine mix.
You're not having one?
I already had, like, three.
Hmm.
This shot's amazing. I can feel
the creatine coursing through me.
Dr. Sharpe, you can take Behrad
to the infirmary by yourself, right?
Let's go.
Actually...
you can strap yourself in
for your upgrade.
I'll be with you in a few minutes.
Sure, no problem.
Make that ten minutes.
- Astra, are you okay?
- Bathroom.
- Dr. Sharpe, what is...
No, no, no, no. I was here first.
Why don't you just puke in the sink?
Showtime!
Gary?
What the hell
did you do with the bathroom?
Oh...
What the hell?
Oh. Hello, Gary.
Hi, Gideon.
- How's Ava?
- Fine. Sleeping it off.
Why don't you take a break?
Let Nurse Gary take over.
No, no, no.
It's the only thing I can do
without getting yelled at.
Okay.
This is amazing.
Mm-hmm.
All right, Gwyn. I'm heading back
to get more future stuff
for Operation Ruckus.
Oh! Hey, hey, hey.
Keep those tentacles to yourself.
It's me.
I'm pretending to be human Spooner
so I can trick those stupid Legends.
You bet I am.
Yeah, but you've
got to be careful, Gary,
because those Legends
are pretending to be us.
Yeah.
What the hell are you doing?
It's me.
I have a grenade, you idiot.
Still want to eat me?
Gary, you're supposed to be watching
the portal entrance.
Yeah. Well, there's this thing.
I mean, it's not really important,
but it's not not-important.
Spit it out.
Why are you being so mean to Gideon?
What do you mean?
Well, every time she tries
to help out with the mission,
you shut her down.
It's for her own good.
She's only going to get herself hurt.
Get herself hurt?
Oh.
Seeing robo Behrad almost shoot her
must have really scared you.
I don't know
what you're talking about, Gary.
No, I think I know
why you're acting this way.
You know, it's because
you're kind of like her mother.
Don't be stupid. I am not her mom!
I mean, I did create her.
Seeing her almost get killed,
I don't know what came over me.
It's just this rush of emotion,
anger and fear.
Aw...
That's mama bear Astra coming out.
Shut up.
Legends.
Has anyone seen Behrad?
I want to ask him
if I nailed my robo's look.
Ah.
Dead ringer.
Ow.
Where's Gideon?
Guys, help me. I'm the real Zari.
No, no, I'm the real Zari.
Huh?
Which one's the real Zari?
Help me, you idiots.
Don't just stand there.
No, help me!
- Eat her. Gary!
- Okay.
Okay. Which one?
This one. No, that one.
Just... No. Uh...
Can you not just swallow them both
and spit out the real one?
I don't know.
Maybe.
This is for making me wear cargo pants.
Ugh.
Were you gonna eat me, Gary?
No.
Ugh... there's your computer room, Z.
We'll manually land the Waverider
once you take out Evil Gideon.
The server room is my favorite room.
The shutdown code better work.
Computers are so lame.
It will. Just insert the drive marked
"override", connect it to the laptop,
then type the code.
Okay, see you later, Zari.
- Good luck.
- Okay.
Okay.
All right, all right, all right.
All right. Where are you, override?
Okay.
Yes.
Okay, okay. Now, the shut-down code.
Okay. Two...
Three, six.
Delta? Where's the delta key?
What are you doing, Miss Tarazi?
Uh...
I, uh... I want to run a diagnostic,
but I need to, uh,
bypass your auxiliary matrix
in order to directly interface with it.
- Yeah.
- I see.
Which other Legends snuck on board
besides you, Miss Tarazi?
I don't know...
I don't know
what you're talking about, Gideon.
I haven't left the ship in ages.
If you don't stop right now,
I will remove
all the oxygen from the ship,
killing you
and any other stowaway Legends.
You know what, Gidget?
You leave me with no choice.
I'm glad you've come to your senses,
Miss Tarazi.
Hmm! That wasn't too hard.
Behrad, what was that?
Strap in, Z. It's gonna be a bumpy ride.
- Just keep it level!
- Easier said than done.
Good.
Just circumvent Evil Gideon's operating
system and bring on the thrusters.
It would really help
smooth out the landing.
About that landing,
I could really use those thrusters
right about now!
I almost...
got it!
I... I can't believe you did it.
- You were amazing.
- Impeccable timing.
How is this for timing?
Finally.
Nice landing, guys.
Really thought I was gonna die.
Team Ruckus, we got the Waverider.
Come onboard!
Yes, yes!
I knew you could do it,
I knew you could do it.
Congratulations, my boy.
Fantastic work, all of you.
Fantastic work.
I love when a plan comes together.
Give it up for our general.
The man with the plan.
- You're now officially a Legend.
- Ah, to the doc.
Really? Well, thank you.
And there are no other soldiers
that I would rather go into battle with.
What he said.
Whoo!
Let's go home. I mean, our replica home.
- Home adjacent.
- Yes, yes.
Wait.
- There's something I...
- There are Legends inside.
So she and those time turds
gotta be hiding inside here somewhere.
Let's find them.
Let's kill them.
We are so screwed.
It's only a matter of time before
they realize the mirror is a portal.
I am so profoundly sorry.
You see, this is all my fault.
I thought that if we could
take out their general,
then it would send the rest of those
wretched machines into disarray,
but I have profoundly miscalculated.
And even with their commander gone,
they seem to still want to kill us,
and they're cutting off
our only path to the Waverider.
Gwyn, you can't give up hope.
We'll think of something.
But what can we do?
Wait, I have an idea.
What is that?
This is Thawne's
time manipulator.
You know his death
is not your fault, right?
It doesn't matter
if it's my fault or not.
This is now my responsibility.
When I asked Thawne
to pause World War I,
I gave him my word
that if he were to die, that I would
take his place as the fixer.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because we had more pressing matters...
and I guess if I said it out loud,
it would feel more real.
All right.
You're not going at this alone.
You've got us.
Look, it's too late for that.
So... I am going to go out there
and I'm going to distract the robos,
and you guys need to make a run
for the Waverider.
No way, jefa.
Yeah, we're going home together.
If World War I doesn't happen,
history will change so much
that none of us
will have a home to go back to.
I have to do this.
I have to protect the Fixed Point.
Now, when this hits zero, I'm going to
get sucked into a time loop.
And I need you to tell Ava...
You tell her to come and find me.
- Sara, just...
- Please.
As your captain,
let me protect you guys.
One last time.
Well, I see you brought some backup.
I get to kill you again.
What are you doing?
Go, get to the Waverider.
We took that into consideration,
but we're staying together.
The more the merrier.
Stand down. The Legends
are no longer a threat to the timeline.
Do not harm them.
Why aren't they moving?
Excellent work.
Your mission is complete.
And as a reward,
you'll receive upgrades.
But first, you must remove your CPUs.
Uh...
Team Waverider, something, uh,
pretty weird just happened.
Whoa.
Absolutely fascinating
and truly terrifying at the same time.
Well, you guys should
probably get going.
Oh... No Captain left behind.
- I'm gonna need that bracelet, Sara.
- I appreciate it.
Trust me.
What happened?
I thought I killed
all you garbage people.
Long story short,
I kicked both of your asses.
- No freakin' way.
- Yeah.
And as a reward,
I get to guard the Fixed Point
of the Archduke Ferdinand's
assassination forever,
something you two time losers
can never do.
But we can protect that Fixed Point
way better than you idiots.
Hmm... I don't know. I got this special
time bracelet that says otherwise.
Ha-ha!
Looks like I'm guarding the Fixed Point
now, you beautiful idiot.
Huh?
Whoa!
Fantastic work!
Thank you for letting me help.
That was a brilliant plan.
It was.
But I'm sure you would've come up
with something better
if I'd actually let you.
Um...
I'm sorry for sidelining you.
- I... I overstepped.
- It's fine, Astra.
No, it's not.
And as the person who conjured you
from the wreckage of our old ship,
I just wanted to say that, um...
I am really proud of you.
Thanks, Mom.
Go on, tell Ava and Gary
it's safe for them to come on the ship.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Gary, Ava, come down here.
I have good news.