- Previously,
on "Legends of Tomorrow..."
- Come with us.
The choice is yours.
- What's next for you, love?
- I guess I'll give life
above ground a fair shot.
- Aha.
Finally.
- I think this is the end
of the line for me.
- Ah, get in here.
- Aww.
- Whoo.
- Piss off, you bloody guv'nor!
Punks, can't handle
their liquor.
- Is that the ocean?
- No.
And you look like garbage.
- I feel like garbage.
Why don't you, huh?
Where the hell were you
last night?
- I dropped Lita off
at her mom's.
- Oh.
Well, aren't you just
a good dad, huh?
Ow.
Hey.
How come nobody tucked me
into bed, huh?
- You're asking me?
- Yeah.
Where's Sara?
- Don't know.
- Oh.
What do you--
Gideon, where's Sara?
- Sara Lance is not on board
the Waverider.
- Sara's missing?
Everyone's missing.
Gideon, who is on board?
- Ava Sharpe, Mick Rory,
and several punks.
- Uh, where could they be?
- Skyemont.
- Why do you say that?
- It's on your hand.
Mick, you're a genius.
Maybe it's from Sara.
Let's go.
Oh, God. Okay.
No, no, no, no, no.
- London, 1977.
The tangled knot of grime,
the stodgy monarchy.
This collision of punk rock
and aristocracy
slamming into each other
like two doomed worlds, this--
- This is a lot at 7:00 a.m.,
John.
I'm glad you're
in a good mood though.
- Well, why shouldn't I be?
You see, my soul
finally belongs to me.
Astra is redeemed,
and--
I get to wake up next to you,
you lovely creature.
- Mm.
- How are you feeling?
- I think a no-strings-attached
hookup every now and then
is good for the soul.
- Even if it's with a guy
whose only coat
smells like booze
and cigarettes.
- Ugh.
Oh, hel-lo.
- Oh.
Sorry, guys.
You, uh, missed the party.
- Wait, are you two--
- Yeah.
- Uh-oh.
Okay, sorry.
I'm not judging, I just--
it's none of my business.
I'm fine.
It's an involuntary reaction.
- We should burn the room.
- Hey, at least we know
how to use protection, Pops.
Do either of you know
where Sara is?
- Uh, we seem to have
lost track of her.
- Oh.
Someone did hand me this.
Is this anything?
- I call.
- Full house, fellas.
- That's three in a row.
She's a shady card sharp.
- Oh, no.
Just lucky.
What about now?
- Still lucky
and now also richer.
I just love toying
with these poor mortals.
- Oh, yeah, well you are one of
these poor mortals now, love.
Try remembering that
the next time
you come across one
with a gun, yeah?
- Astra, have you seen Sara?
- Uh, not recently.
Maybe ask Behrad.
- Yeah, where is my brother?
- I can't believe how much
we have in common.
It's like we're riding
the same cosmic vibe, you know?
We just click.
It's like we were destined
to connect in this moment.
- Hey, wrap it up Behrad.
- We gonna pick this up later.
Cheerio.
- Hey.
Have you seen Sara?
- No.
- Ugh!
- Maybe she's with Nate.
He was headed back to the club.
- Back?
Why?
- We met Starman
at the after-after.
Said he had to prep
for his show there tonight.
- What the hell's a Starman?
- Major T?
Ziggy Stardust?
- Bowie!
He's talking about David Bowie.
- See, my girlfriend's
from another time.
- Oh, like the future.
- No.
Well...
technically, yes,
but she's from the future
with a different
timeline entirely.
Now she lives in a Totem.
And I'm forced
to be at peace with it.
- What's her name?
- Zari.
Her name is Zari.
And I'm afraid I'm never
gonna see her again.
Hi, Zari.
Hey, guys.
This is David Bowie.
- Marvelous.
- Okay, Nate.
We're looking for Sara.
Is she here with you?
- Last time I saw her
was at the concert.
I figured she was with you.
- Did he just say
"disappeared"?
Sara disappeared.
Is he singing about Sara?
- Deh, deh, deh--do not
interrupt David's process.
He's trying to cheer me up
by singing a song about Zari.
1.0, not you.
- Obviously.
Still weird.
- Guys, blonde hair.
Does that not remind you
of Sara?
- Bowie!
Cut that crap out!
- Hey, listen, mate.
Is that song you're singing
about Nate's sad love life?
- No, mate.
- Are you singing
about Sara Lance?
- Is that her name?
Your friend who got sucked up
into a spaceship?
- W--sucked into a spaceship?
- Isn't it wild?
- So you saw this
with your own
beautiful, asymmetrical eyes?
- I was filming that night
on my Super 8.
See for yourself.
- Okay.
Film is developed.
Let's see what Bowie saw.
- You lads are out
of this world.
- David freaking Bowie?
You're a Smell fan?
- They're something else.
- Hey, wait, wait, wait.
I gotta--I gotta let you in
on a little secret, all right,
David freaking Bowie?
'Cause tonight--tonight,
I am going
to propose to my girlfriend!
Holy--
Wish me luck.
- Whoa.
She's a space girl.
- Ava--
- Okay.
Um, Sara's been abducted so,
uh, Sara's been abducted.
Uh...I'll be right back.
- So she's a mess.
- All right, so let's just
give her some space.
In the meantime,
what do we know about aliens?
- Literally nothing.
- They're green.
- Listen, you fools.
Sara's missing
because you guys
were partying last night.
We have to find her.
We're running out of time.
- Time to get organized.
- Ava, you're back.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh.
Whoa.
- Here you go.
- Girl, are you okay?
- What?
I'm fine.
Why?
- Well, we just thought that--
- You know,
with Sara being lost,
you may wanna sit this one out.
- Uh, she is not lost.
She is pre-found.
There's a solution to every
problem including this one.
- Wow, indexed.
Thorough.
- You are all
the best of the best.
If we handle this logically
and rationally,
we will get Sara back, okay?
- Right, well, uh,
this a waste of time.
I've got a better idea.
- Oh?
- Yeah, ever since
I rescued her from Purgatory,
Sara and I have
a psychic connection.
It'll allow me to locate her,
and everything I need
is at the mansion.
- Damn it, John.
That's insubordinate.
But I won't try to stop you.
- You know, he's actually
most effective
not left to his own devices.
I can just--
- Thank you, Z.
- We're gonna fix this.
- Mm-hmm.
Astra, would you mind keeping
them on mission please?
- Uh, I'm not really
on the team, so...
- We're accepting outside help.
Thank you.
- Okay. I think I need
to just calm down
and do some "research."
- Really?
Right now?
Dude, Sara needs us!
- I'm freaking out here, man.
- Aw, come on, B.
Ah, Mick.
Perfect timing.
I need you to check
on any leads you may have
in the underworld please.
- Not gonna work.
This whole thing's
not gonna work.
Nothing works without Sara.
- Okay, so what?
Are you just gonna drink?
That's real mature, Rory.
Real mature.
- Wow. You really got this team
figured out.
- Mm-hmm.
- So what do we do?
- Uh, we are gonna call
the experts, the D.E.O.
- Good idea. Eesh--
- What?
- Is it gonna get weird
between you and Alex Danvers
'cause she and Sara
had a fling?
- It's--swing a dead cat.
Sara never liked to be alone.
- Are you okay?
Whoa.
Who are you?
- I'm Spartacus,
the Undefeatable.
- Oh.
Yeah, that "undefeatable" part
didn't quite stick, but...
- Uh, wait.
Hey, get back here!
- Sorry.
Did you find Sara?
- No.
Care to wet your whistle?
- I'm confused.
What did you learn?
That Sara Lance is
far beyond my reach.
- You told Ava
you could reach her.
- Yeah, well, I overpromised.
- You can't just give up
on Sara.
There's got to be
something you can do.
- Come on. Anything?
- Look--
aliens took her, all right?
To space.
This is really not my area
of expertise.
Now if it was a ghost,
or a demon,
or even a handle of whiskey,
I could help you out
with that, but I'm sorry.
All right?
I'm an astrologer.
And you need an astronomer.
- What an ass.
- Yeah, he does have
that going for him.
- Look, he's right.
This is out of his league.
This is out of all our leagues.
- I disagree.
Astra, let's talk
about your "network."
- My network?
I've been on Earth
for, like, five minutes.
- Exactly.
- Gideon, why isn't
the D.E.O. answering?
- The Department
of Extranormal Operations
was destroyed in the infamous
year 2020 by Rama Khan.
- Nate, this is a huge setback.
We needed the D.E.O.
Aliens is their jurisdiction.
- Yeah.
- Captain Sharpe,
I believe we are dealing
with a temporal anomaly.
According to
the original timeline,
there was no alien spacecraft
over London in 1977.
- Meaning this is
our jurisdiction.
- Huh?
- We're the experts.
No.
We're--we're the experts?
- Damn right we are.
You, me, the Legends.
We're the only people
who are capable
of handling
time-traveling aliens.
- Nate, if I trusted the team,
I wouldn't have made an entire
binder to get rid of them.
Okay?
The D.E.O. was plan A.
Well, Ava, you are now
in charge of the Legends.
So welcome to plan B.
Now breathe it in.
Breathe with me.
- No.
- Come.
- Plan B smells like pot.
- I got something.
- You are a walking
contact high.
- You're welcome.
Gideon, put this up.
- That's a cute little kid.
- B, that's a tabloid.
- Yes, tabloids
help me not think
about how we live
on a technological terror
hurtling through
a swirling green nightmare.
- Damn.
- So this girl,
Esperanza Cruz,
says that she was abducted
by aliens,
and from then on, she could
communicate with them.
They implanted something
in her head.
- B!
I'm s--this is a tabloid, okay?
From how--what, 20 years ago?
It's probably
totally fabricated.
I need real leads.
- She's real, man.
Gideon located her.
- I mean...
little kid
with alien tech in her head.
Not a bad lead.
- Okay, sure.
Fine.
You know? Whatever.
It's all we've got.
I mean, Rory's probably
good and boozed up by now,
so why don't you take Micky
and go investigate
this Esperanza--
what is her last name?
- Uh, Cruz.
Are we really sure bringing
Mick to talk to a kid
is, like, best practices?
- No, n--
You're gonna go see her
present day.
Some of us are still trying
not to mess with the timeline.
- Right.
The timeline.
Aye-aye.
- You're excused.
Ugh!
- What is it?
- I was confined to one
of these glass prisons.
You were as well.
Which means there
are also others inside.
- You just figured
that out now?
- I did.
I also commanded an army
of 120,000 slaves,
gladiators, and peasants
against the Roman republic.
- Yeah, I've heard.
- Mm, excellent.
Then we'll liberate
our fellow prisoners
and we'll lead a rebellion
against our captors.
- Wait, no.
We don't know who's in there.
- Rise, compatriot.
I am your savior.
I am Spartacus!
- What, pray tell, are you?
A Saxon?
- Nope, that's definitely
an alien.
Hey, a little help here!
- The thrill of the battle.
Reminds me of being back
in the Colosseum.
- Yeah, you just stand there
in the Colosseum too?
- I was letting it
tire itself out.
If it had slain you,
I would've been well-rested
and easily avenged your death.
- Being an avenger is stupid.
The goal is to prevent death.
I am a Preventer.
You wanna join the Preventers,
Sparty?
- Yeah--yes?
- Good choice.
Now stop opening pods.
We're gonna go find
who's flying the ship,
and we're gonna prevent them
from breathing.
- I'm telling you.
Sara ain't here.
It's a waste of our time.
- We're gonna find Sara.
The fact that we found
this person is a sign.
And when the universe
shows you a sign,
you should believe it.
- Is that right?
The universe exists
for one reason.
To kill you.
Hello.
Miss Cruz?
Ma'am?
Hm.
Must not be home.
- Let's not tell Miss Cruz
we broke in.
- When they split up, we'll
take them out one by one.
- Nonsense.
We have the element
of surprise.
We attack both savages now,
and we slay them
in one fell swoop.
- We have no idea
what they're capable of.
Look, I was an assassin.
Rule number one:
isolate your targets.
- Do not fight
from the shadows.
I commanded an undefeated army
of 120,000 warriors.
- Well, I assure you
they are all dead now.
- Then I must avenge them.
- No, no avenging.
No avenging.
It's preventing!
- Prepare to die, savages!
- I am very, very sorry, David,
you're under pressure.
Look, maybe I can help you.
Ooh, whoa, whoa.
Why would you do that?
- Astra has a lead.
- Okay.
All right.
She has a lead.
- Go ahead.
- So I heard about this guy
who was once in hell.
Raved about aliens.
His name was Aleister Crowley.
Aleister bloody Crowley.
Come off it.
Crowley's a kook.
- That is
the conventional wisdom.
But he had this tome of secrets
called the "Book of the Law."
- In it, Crowley detailed
these alien encounters
and spells that
these aliens taught him.
But he disappeared from hell.
Maybe he used these
alien spells to escape.
- Yeah.
Crowley didn't escape.
All right?
I summoned him, and then
I trapped him on Earth.
- You trapped--sorry--
isn't that a felony?
- No.
But like most things I do,
it probably should be.
So, what'd
you do with the book, John?
- All right, okay.
Being as we don't have
any other ideas,
I kept it safe right over...
Gary!
What'd I tell you
about nicking my things, eh?
- Why did you kidnap me?
- Gary!
Gary!
Bloody hell Gary
would be reading Crowley,
I have no idea.
There it is.
- Find it?
- What the hell is that?
- Ew.
- You better help me
understand you,
or this is gonna end quick.
- Hey!
Hands where I can see them.
Gary?
- Please don't be mad.
- If she could talk
to aliens,
why would she live
in a redneck dump like this?
- Maybe you're right.
But isn't it worth making sure?
Besides,
Ava really needs a win.
- I don't need a win.
We all need a win.
This isn't about me.
Oh, my God.
Don't give me that look.
- What look?
- You know exactly what look.
- "You'll feel better
not bottling up
your emotions" look?
- I'm not bottling them up.
I just don't wanna talk
about them.
- Okay.
I'm just gonna say one thing.
- Nate.
- You have not mentioned
Sara's proposal once.
- I am setting aside
my feelings
to focus on the goal
of getting Sara back.
Okay?
You should too.
- I wonder what's in there.
- Let me guess.
More dumb redneck stuff.
Guess she's not such
a dumb redneck after all.
- Guess not.
- Behrad, Mick, answer me.
Great.
Two more abductions.
This is why we don't talk
about emotions
during the mission.
- Okay, Gideon's scanning
for heat signatures.
It's--it's gonna be okay.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
- Three Legends are missing.
Things are pretty far
from okay.
- Yeah, well they just
got further, love.
We found something
in Gary's room.
- A human-sized chrysalis.
- Guys, we don't understand.
- Gary is an alien.
- An alien?
Oh, my--
Okay.
I don't buy it.
- Well, we also found these.
- Gary's glasses?
- Oh, allow me to demonstrate.
And brace yourselves.
- No.
Gary abducted Sara.
- I was sent to Earth to kidnap
the quintessential human.
- Spartacus?
- Oh, no, no, no.
You!
Spartacus was just
my boss's lunch.
But don't worry.
I don't eat humans.
Anymore.
- Terrific.
- The point is, I couldn't go
through with your abduction
because I fell
in love with you,
with Ava, with all humans.
- Yeah, well that's funny
because I still feel
very abducted, Gary.
- Well, my boss, Kayla,
found us.
But I remained loyal.
That's why I saved you.
- You saved me?
- Yeah!
I rigged the pod to open
with your handprint.
- Okay--Gary,
where are we going?
- No clue.
Kayla doesn't trust me anymore.
I don't blame her.
- Yeah, well, you and I
are also not okay.
Do you have any idea
how wrecked
Ava must feel right now?
I mean, yeah, I'm sure she's
pretending to keep it together
for everyone else's sake,
but inside,
she must be dying.
- Stop, stop!
It's torture to even think
about what Ava's going through.
Do me in.
I deserve it.
I've destroyed the very thing
I most stan.
- Knock it off.
You're gonna help me get home.
Now tell me everything
that you know about this ship.
Well...
when you first met,
you butt heads.
But any fool could tell you two
were meant for each other.
- This spaceship, Gary.
- Oh.
What the--what the--hey!
- Ava?
Nate?
- Behrad, are you guys okay?
- Yeah, it is very far
from chill in here.
- 2100 hours.
Trespassers have
regained consciousness.
They were armed
with some fancy weapons.
Not sure why.
Only one way to find out.
- I told you the universe
was trying to kill us.
- What was that, old timer?
- I wasn't talking to you,
Miss Crazy.
- I don't like
being called that.
- He didn't mean that,
Miss Cruz.
- Spooner.
I go by Spooner now.
- Okay, Spooner, ma'am.
This is all just
a misunderstanding.
The alien communicator
in your head,
we need you to use it
to find our friend.
- So y'all's plan was not only
to break onto my property,
but to kidnap me?
- We were gonna ask.
In fact, we still are.
- What?
- Shh.
Will you come with us?
- Come with you?
Oh, but you ain't going.
- Please hurry.
She's getting real friendly
with her knife.
- Who you talking to?
- Uh, he's a schizophrenic.
He talks to himself.
- It's true.
It's a nervous tick actually.
Uh--could--could--hey.
Wait.
Hey, hey, hey--hey.
Wait, wait.
Hey, hey!
No!
- Behrad?
What's happening?
- Uh, the universe
ripped his comms out.
- Captain Sharpe, I've
pinpointed their location.
- Oh, thank God.
I'm not losing
any more Legends today.
Gideon, take the ship
to that location.
- A ship?
- Nate, you're with me.
Wait, hang on.
Why is my voice echoing?
- She hacked my comms.
She can hear everything
you're saying.
- That thing
against the Waverider?
- Whoa!
- Touché, Spooner.
- Please stop shooting my ship.
- Don't come any closer.
I ain't gon' let y'all
abduct me again.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on, hold on.
That's what you think this is?
You think we're aliens?
- The hell else could you be?
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're time travelers.
- Time travelers?
- Yes!
That's our time ship.
Which is also a spaceship,
but that's beside the point.
Look, I'm sorry
that we trespassed, okay?
It was wrong.
But--
We're desperate.
Listen.
The woman I love was abducted
by aliens last night.
And I just found that
she's gonna propose to me.
I will do anything
if you can find her.
Will you please help me?
- Exactly what an alien
would say.
- Just--
- Now can I burn
this place down?
- Can we go over the plan
one more time?
Because it still feels
slightly suicidal.
- Well, we don't have
enough fuel
to turn around and go home,
right?
- Uh-huh.
- So we commandeer the ship.
- From Kayla,
my vicious, violent,
and very vindictive boss.
- Then we open a wormhole back
to Earth's temporal zone.
- An unstable rip
in spacetime itself.
- And then we fly the ship
through it.
- On whatever fumes remain
after we burn everything
opening the wormhole.
- Well then,
we better get moving.
First things, you gotta go
get rid of your boss.
- Right.
Okay.
Here goes nothing.
- Gary, your glasses.
- Whoops.
All right.
Guess we'll do it this way.
- Okay.
Wormhole time.
- Morning, sunshine.
- Tables may have turned,
but I ain't going down
without a fight.
- Whoa.
We're not gonna hurt you.
- Look.
- Where the hell am I?
- Like Ava said before,
we're time travelers.
This is our time ship.
- Admit it.
You're only being nice so
I'll help you find your friend.
- 100%.
Yes.
- Even if I wanted
to help y'all, I can't.
- Why not?
- This thing in my head
is like an antenna.
If I send a signal
to your friend,
the aliens who put it there
could find me.
- Look, we have the technology
to remove whatever's
in your head
if--if you help us find Sara.
- How is my signal
gonna locate her?
- It doesn't have to.
Our friend will direct it
to the aliens that she's with.
Oh!
If you think we're weird,
wait till you meet John.
- So I send out my signal
and connect to this alien guy.
- His name is Gary.
- He's an alien named Gary?
- Gary Green.
- Ah, Green.
Yeah, now it makes sense.
- Once you make the connection,
I'll step into that Sigil
then Astral Project myself
to Gary's location.
And then I'll look for Sara.
- Right.
And how do I connect
to this Gary alien
who I've never met?
- You'll drink a potion
of sorts.
- One delish smoothie
coming at you.
Good luck.
- Crowley's spell requires you
to ingest something of Gary's.
The chrysalis
is all we've got.
- Seriously?
- No, she's not gonna--
- The sooner this is over,
the sooner
this thing's out of my head.
But I hope it works.
Salud.
- Oh, God.
- Oh.
- She did it.
- Eh.
Kinda tangy.
All right, um, ready?
Yeah, after my abduction,
I started wearing tinfoil hats.
It blocked any alien signals
I could pick up.
- Huh. Nifty.
Right.
On with the show.
- I can feel him.
I found the alien.
A lot dweebier than I thought.
- Bloody Crowley was right.
- I can sense him.
He's worried and wants
to come down to Earth.
It looks like he's trying
to help Sara.
- Oh, I just need
to step into the Sigil
and find her.
- John, are you okay?
Spooner's connection
is unstable.
I'm giving it everything
just to maintain it.
- I'll do it.
- No, whoa, whoa.
Are you crazy?
You'll kill yourself.
Look what's happening to John.
- It's plan B, Nate.
Embrace it.
- Sara?
- Ava.
Wait, how...
How are you...
Are you here?
- Hey, hey, hey.
Stay with me.
Look at me.
Yes.
- Yes, what?
- When you get home,
I'll marry you.
So you better get home, okay?
I love you.
- He's killing himself.
We have to stop him.
- John.
Look at me.
- Round two.
- Wormhole's open, Sara!
- Whoa!
- No, no!
Once again, I wake
to Zari Tarazi.
- Oh, you're up?
- I almost died.
But you saved me.
- Yeah, well I couldn't
let you die
right after getting
your soul back, so...
- Gidget said you
might be dehydrated,
so I made you a green smoothie
to help you recover.
Sans alien cocoon.
- Oh, cheers.
Mmm.
Yep.
It's very tasty.
- Hey, uh, let me know when
you have your strength back.
It's a fling.
- Uh-huh.
You know I can tell
when someone's bluffing, right?
It looks like Crowley wasn't.
- Yeah, well,
even if alien magic is real,
Crowley is a slippery fish.
He's not to be trusted.
- Hm.
Whatever you say, roomie.
- Hey, that was a short
residence on the Waverider, eh?
- Yeah, I can't keep getting
roped into Legends missions.
Let's just say
I'm not as enamored
of the timeline
as everyone else.
It's like you said,
I'm mortal now.
I wanna see what it's like
to be...normal.
Maybe I can love this world
like the rest of you do.
- You've come a long way,
you little Hellspawn.
- And come on, John.
Just a fling?
She's got you
on a juice cleanse.
- Sure you won't stick around?
You've got a pretty chill vibe
beneath your gun-toting
outcast vibe.
- Look, we contacted
your friend,
and I'm sorry
she's not back yet.
But I want this thing removed
so I can finally live
a normal life.
- I get that.
You wanna keep it zen
in the brain stem.
Dr. Gideon will fix you up.
What do you see, Gideon?
- Nothing out of the ordinary.
- Really?
Can you look closer?
- If I removed and thoroughly
dissected her brain,
we might something
the scan did not detect.
May I proceed?
- What's going on out there?
- No.
Don't kill her, Gideon.
- Yeah, I can hear it.
- I wasn't gonna let her--
- You can't hear it, can you?
They're all around us.
- I've never seen
anything like this
in a temporal zone.
- Aliens.
Lots of 'em.
- They're falling
into the timeline.
- Why are you smiling?
We gotta clean this mess up.
- I know.
It's just that the only person
who could create
this much mayhem is Sara
which means she's alive.
- Well, if the universe
shows you a sign,
you should believe it.
- Mm!
- Engaged?
I'm so happy I could cry.
- Gary, if we don't get
through that wormhole,
we are stuck here.
- I'm going as fast as I can.
[straining] I'm sorry.
I'm not as good a pilot
as my fiancé.
- Wait, you and that
other alien are engaged?
- Her name's Kayla, but yeah.
I assume the wedding's off now.
Did I not mention that?
- We can talk about this later.
Right now, just get us
through that wormhole.
- Yeah.
- We're gonna make it.
- We're not gonna make it.
We didn't make it.
- Greg, move your head!