Sales for the first generation
of Ava clones have been
through the roof as predicted.
My dream of an Ava in every home
and business has become a reality.
How wonderful. Congratulations, sir.
Sir...
I was going to wait until after
the investment meeting to mention this.
But I think it's time you told me
about this mystery project
you've been working on.
It's just that
you've diverted billions into it,
and I really feel like it's time I knew
what the project was all about.
Where do you think I'm taking you?
Ta-da!
It's called a Wa verider.
Wa verider?
Oh!
Because it's shaped like a boat?
Like it rides on the waves?
No, though it can go underwater.
But never mind that.
Wa verider is what it's called in the
futuristic blueprints I was given.
It's a Timeship.
Wa verider?
Are you married to that name,
or can we still pitch on it?
Welcome to the bridge.
The nerve center of the entire ship.
Not the most efficient use
of space, though.
Maybe it could double
as a conference room.
And now it's time for you
to see an old friend.
Gideon.
Time to wake up.
There you are.
[Gideon] My transfer to the ship's
mainframe appears to be a success.
You remember Gideon?
Oh, yes. Her.
Welcome to your new home, Gideon.
So much more space to roam
than that tiny hard drive you were in.
Take a couple laps around,
stretch your legs.
You have vantage points
all over the ship.
[Gideon] You followed
my exact specifications,
but I don't have
any visual access in Section A2.
Section A2 is the only bathroom
on the ship.
I can't have you spying on me in there.
A man needs his privacy.
[chuckles] Yes.
Sir, as impressive as this ship is,
how does it relate to
the Ava Corp mission
of improving people's lives
through clone technology exactly?
Well, I'm simply expanding our mission
by adding time travel to the mix.
But the true perk of this ship
is to finally get revenge
on those time travelers who abducted me,
used me for my genius
and then messed with my mind.
[Gideon] May I remind you that
a Time Master's number one duty is
to protect the timeline from any
and all threats to its integrity.
Yes. Yes, Gideon. That's a given,
considering the job title.
Time Master.
[Gideon] And before we start,
you must take the Time Masters' oath.
"I swear to protect and defend
the integrity of the timeline
with all my ability
until the end of my days."
[Gideon] Congratulations.
You are now Time Master
of this Wa verider.
Great.
Let's set sail on our maiden voyage
and protect the timeline
from those damn Legends.
[theme music playing]
[screams]
The machine is ruined,
wrecked, absolutely kaput.
- And all because of you lot!
- Okay, hold on.
How is it our fault
we didn't land in Tahiti?
Because it wasn't designed
to take all you people.
The excess weight. It threw it all off!
Okay, so I'm guessing we have
no idea what year we're in?
The chrono-gauge and the ignition coil
are both sequenced
to the directional compass,
which was damaged in the landing.
So no, I don't think so.
Well, that doesn't sound too good.
But, hey, who needs a chrono-gauge
when you have two ex-Time Bureau agents
with extensive historical knowledge?
Gary?
That's right, Ava.
And based on the local flora,
there's a chance
we're in the prehistoric era.
Give or take a few thousand years.
Maybe we'll see dinosaurs.
You better hope
we don't see a dinosaur, Gary.
Okay, so it looks like we're
making this prehistoric forest
home for a while.
- So let's get comfortable, gang.
- [all groan]
Guys, come on. This team
has been stranded more times
than I can count
and in way worse places than this.
She's right.
I know nothing has gone our way
since we left Odessa, but...
they're gonna get better.
- Yeah.
- Okay?
All right. So, you are the only one
that can fix this time machine.
If you can repair
that directional compass,
are we back in business?
It would be a difficult task,
even if we did have the proper tools.
- I can help.
- Me too.
You got two techies
at your disposal, my man.
Just some peace to be able
to get on with my work is all I ask.
You know, I will venture off
and maybe find some lodestone,
or some other magnetic material
which conducts electricity
and, well, then I can fix the compass.
Hey, maybe you and B
should go with Dr. Cranky.
We'll set up camp here.
Mmm-hmm. All over it.
Hey, look. I know
we didn't really get a chance
to talk about the whole moving in thing.
No, it's totally cool.
As usual, we have bigger fish to fry.
I know, but, you know,
moving into a spiritual realm
there's a lot to take in.
I just want to make sure
you're not... freaking out.
Freak out? Me? No. I'm super chill.
I am, however,
concerned about our captains.
Yeah, well. Good luck with that.
- Bye.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Miss you.
Bye.
Psst! Hey! You two.
Come here. Shut up.
Do either one of you
know how to read lips?
Who needs to read lips
when Spooner can read minds?
Mmm.
Phew!
I'm getting some major anxiety vibes
from Sara right now.
Yeah, and I don't need superpowers
to see that Ava is cracking.
They're just stressing
each other out at this point.
Okay, so let's separate them
so they each
don't have a complete
and total meltdown.
Okay?
Hey there, jefa. How about
we hunt down some dinner?
Yeah, let's go stab something.
Wanna go for a hike?
We could get some firewood.
Yeah, I would love a multi-task.
Great.
- So...
- Oh, Gary.
You and Zari. Saw you talking.
And?
She asked me to move in with her
in the Totem.
Oh, that's great!
That's not, not great?
Sorry, the more handsome the face,
the harder it is for me to get a read.
All right, just back up.
It's just... [sighs]
I haven't spent that much time
in the Totem.
She sprung it on me
before we time jumped here,
so I really haven't had
a chance to process it.
But, Nate, the Totem seems quite small.
How'd you get inside?
Are you and Zari gonna live
in a house together?
Will there be pie? Because I really like
strawberry rhubarb.
- I love strawberry rhubarb.
- We need to focus on today's problems.
Okay? How about you guys forage
for some food? Leaves, nuts, berries.
Anything we can eat, okay? Go.
- Okay.
- Go.
You sure you don't want me
to stick around? Be your sounding board?
- We can...
- Gary.
You will not be my sounding board today.
Okay? Thank you.
- Okay.
- Go on.
[exhales]
Well, at least these two ding dongs
can't screw anything up here
that will attract the evil Wa verider.
[whooshing]
Check out that view
of the temporal zone.
- Worth a million bucks. Huh?
- Mmm.
Considering this ship costs
many thousand times more,
I'm not sure how the board's gonna feel
about your investment, sir.
There's one thing you just can't put
a price on, assistant Ava.
- Hmm?
- Revenge.
Ah.
[Gideon] Captain, we're getting an alert
of several anachronisms
in 1925 Odessa, Texas.
Hmm.
"Captain." I like that.
Odessa. Wait a second. Texas.
That's where the Legends took me.
Gideon, you found them!
Engage weapons systems.
I'm gonna bomb
the living daylights out of them.
[Gideon] I am advising against
this course of action.
How else am I supposed to
wipe them off the face of the earth?
[Gideon] Eliminating the Legends
in this blunt manner
will cause excessive collateral damage.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Your warning is duly noted.
[all gasp]
Yes! [laughs]
Those bastards finally got
what they deserved!
It's a lot easier than I expected.
Can we please go home now, sir?
[Gideon] No, the captain's impulsive
and violent actions
guarantee ripple effects in the timeline
that we will have to clean up.
More precise measures must be taken when
dealing with threats moving forward.
Trust me, this was the only way
to deal with those Legends.
And if any ripples arise, we'll just use
our brand new Timeship
to smooth them out.
Hey, buddy.
Got your coat.
You okay?
[sighs] Listen. We don't really
have time for a rest stop.
We need to find the materials you need
to fix your time machine. Yeah?
You really don't understand, do you?
I just told you lot
what you wanted to hear.
In reality, there is no point
in fixing the wretched machine.
Sure, there was
a little problem with the dismount,
but your invention actually worked.
Yeah. So, why don't we
put our shoes back on
and we can help you find magnetite
or whatever mineral it is
you need to get your invention
back up and running.
To fix the machine,
we need to fix the compass,
and in order to do that,
we need magnetic material,
which conducts electricity.
And I doubt that you would even know
what to look for, and either way,
it's not about fixing the machine
or not fixing the machine, you see,
because no matter what I do,
I'm always meant...
to fail.
You see, my machine,
it was meant to explode.
Yeah, but it didn't explode.
We're alive and we're here.
Yes, yes, we're here.
We're here in the middle of nowhere!
[bird caws and flutters]
My divine mission,
derailed once again.
There is no fighting God's will, my boy.
Being here is proof of that.
You lot might as well get comfortable.
We're not going anywhere,
because nowhere is exactly
where I'm meant to be.
Astounding. You can't even tell
that Gideon fabricated this food.
Fabricated? From what?
[Gideon] We've received an alert
about a disturbance in the timeline.
Fun! Which thrilling time period
are we headed to next?
- [Gideon] 1925.
- Ooh!
Weren't we just in 1925?
That is quite a coincidence.
What's the disturbance, Gideon?
[Gideon] J. Edgar Hoover
has disappeared,
and unfortunately,
it is not a coincidence.
My calculations confirm your attack
on the Legends caused this aberration.
Well, if Hoover is the problem,
then Hoover is the solution.
We'll just use my clone technology...
And make a clone of Mr. Hoover.
So we can plop them right back
into the timeline
- and no one will even know.
- Mmm-hmm.
[Gideon] Clones are still human
and humans are fallible.
Remember, one of your Ava clones
eventually became a Legend
and helped kidnap you.
Okay, Gideon.
Absolutely no need to lump us all in
with that horrible traitor.
[Gideon] Mr. Hoover is integral
to many seminal moments in history.
We cannot risk a clone straying
from his historical to-do list.
Then we'll combine my clone tech
with your computer tech
and make a Hoover robot.
We can program him to carry out every
action that is critical to history.
It's actually quite brilliant.
I know. I came up with it. [chuckles]
I'll have to add "robot maker"
to my hyphenate.
It's alive!
A cure for crime
is not the electric chair,
but the high chair.
He's perfect.
Time to go forth
and save history, Mr. Hoover.
It's like no matter what we do,
we make everything worse.
And I try to keep it together, you know?
For Sara and the team,
but I don't always have all the answers.
And being co-captains in life and
on the ship, it's a delicate balance.
Sometimes I just wish
someone else was in charge.
But it's what I signed up for,
so it's fine.
- I mean, I'm fine.
- You're not fine.
- I'm fine.
- You're not, Ava.
[speaks in other language]
But you're on your way.
Cheers, to your well-earned promotion
to Time Mistress!
Mmm, Time Mistress Ava does have
a certain ring to it, doesn't it?
[Gideon] Captain, it appears
that the Hoover robot
initiated its self-destruct sequence
in the state of Arkansas
and has been destroyed.
Destroyed?
We just put him into the time...
I'm pulling up the robot's visual feed
to see what happened.
No, it can't be.
J. Edgar Hoo ver, a robot.
Are those the Legends?
[Gideon] It appears they're still alive.
Thank you. I can see that.
Well, I'll just build
another Hoover-Bot and...
add a special protocol
to hunt down and eliminate the Legends.
[Gideon] That protocol is not part
of J. Edgar Hoover's original timeline.
And once the Hoover-Bot's
done with the Legends,
it can resume
its historical to-do list, yes?
Exactly! She gets it!
[Gideon] I'd advise against
this course of action.
Let's vote.
We all have equal say, now that
we have a Time Mistress on board.
All those in favor
of the special protocol, say "aye."
- Aye.
[Gideon] Nay.
Looks like you've been outvoted, Gideon.
Come, Time Mistress Ava.
We have work to do.
What do you mean Hoover 2.0 blew up?
[Gideon] Its programming was hacked.
The incident also caused
another massive Aberration.
Thomas Edison suffered
a heart attack and died.
Really? We should have
just gone back to Ava Corp.
This situation with the Legends
is getting worse and worse.
It's because these androids are weak.
They need weapons to defend themselves
against the Legends,
something built in, like lasers
that shoot out of their eyes.
What if their hands were guns?
[Gideon] You're forgetting our
prime directive to protect the timeline.
[scoffs] You're such a computer, Gideon.
Start thinking outside of that
little computer box of yours.
I am digging this weapons idea.
Let's start fresh in the morning.
Once we make these adjustments,
those Legends won't stand a chance.
So let's talk, Nate.
[grunts] Should you move into
the Totem with Zari?
Pros... [grunts]
and cons.
Pro. I get to see Zari every day,
which is a really good thing.
Con. What if I don't like it
in the Totem?
Then what?
Pro. Zari is happy in the Totem
and she wants me to be with her.
- Maybe that's enough.
- Wait!
Were you just talking to yourself?
Did I miss your epiphany?
You better not have one without me.
Gary, I already told you. You are not
my sounding board today, okay?
So why don't you guys
just go back into the woods
and find some more food?
It's gonna be dark soon.
Enjoy the great outdoors.
I just need a little more time
to work on this stuff.
Fine, but no epiphanies without me.
Bye.
- Bye.
Now, where was I? Oh, con.
What if her ancestors hate me?
I totally get how you're feeling, Gwyn.
We all have our low points,
but you gotta hang in there.
[laughs sarcastically]
Hang in there. "Hang in there," he says.
See, there was this time
when I was enrolled in business school.
I did it to make
my parents happy, and it sucked.
In my gut, I knew I wasn't
where I was supposed to be.
And on a crazy whim, I just decided
to borrow my family's Wind Totem.
You mean steal, right?
And because of this Totem,
I hooked up with the Legends.
Sometimes that's exactly what you need
to get through the dark times. Friends.
- What's wrong?
- What's wrong? What's right?
There's nothing right, is there?
What's wrong
is that I am up to here
of listening to your inane prattling.
You're like some mollycoddled child-man.
Give me that.
- Okay, hang on.
- Let's not add more fuel to the fire.
Let's just take a deep breath. Hmm?
[inhales, exhales deeply]
Yeah, no, that's not working for me.
Hey!
[Gideon] Excuse me, Time Mistress Ava.
Bishop is asking for your presence
in the cargo bay.
Cargo bay?
[Gideon] He wants to show you
the prototype
for the Hoover 3.0 weapons system
he built to kill the Legends.
Mmm, sounds deadly.
Must've beat him here.
Gideon, open the door.
Bishop's not here yet.
Gideon.
Open this door and let me back in.
[Gideon] I'm sorry, Ava.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
What do you mean
you can't do that? Gideon!
Open this damn door right now.
[Gideon] This mission is too important
for me to allow you to jeopardize it.
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
[Gideon] Bishop needs
to concentrate on the mission
and you are a distraction.
It's time for you to go.
Goodbye, Ava.
Hey!
You can't talk to my brother like that.
That's my job.
You can't just run off either.
We're supposed be working together.
Just leave me alone, will you?
Hey! You're not even
looking for lodestone
or magnetite, or whatever it is,
are you?
Come on, let's go.
Don't touch me! Don't touch me!
Get away!
I'm sorry.
You're obviously
going through something.
I just need you to focus
so we can get out of dinosaur times
or whatever it is that we are.
You don't even have to come with us.
Just help us fix the time machine
so my friends can finally go home.
Trust me, you don't want my help, okay?
I definitely do.
You're the only one
who can get us out of here.
Well, then you're all done for.
The last people who depended
on me for help all died.
Listen, Gwyn.
I know a thing or two about tragedy...
You don't know the first thing about me
or what I've been through, all right?
Okay, I'm just saying
if you wanna talk...
Talk? [chuckles]
Talk. What do you
want to talk about, then?
What happened to you...
Oh, right, you're from the olden times.
Sometimes talking
to another person about a hard thing
can make it hurt a little less.
[animal chittering]
[exhales]
- Nice work.
- You too.
[Agent Sharpe sighs] This damn IOU list
just keeps getting longer and longer.
We're never going to be able
to fix it at this point.
I'm so sick and tired
of being sidetracked, you know?
And if I ever
see another one of those Hoover-Bots,
I swear I'm just gonna...
[screams]
That was a phenomenal scream.
Trust me, I know.
I've caused a lot of them.
Well, you know what?
I think I really needed that.
And we really needed some firewood.
Your knowledge
of the universe is so useful,
especially in the wilderness.
So glad you're here, Gideon.
I'm glad I'm here too, Gary!
If I hadn't pulled that nightshade
out of your mouth,
you'd be dead and your lifeless body
would be too heavy for me to carry.
Mmm. Try these gooseberries.
They're sweet and high in antioxidants.
- Mmm!
- Mmm?
Oh!
Eating. Favorite thing
about being human.
- Yeah?
- Mmm-hmm.
Mmm.
I don't think I could
choose my favorite thing.
You could see why I became so obsessed.
They have so many fun quirks.
Eyebrows, belly buttons.
Nipples.
You have nipples, too?
Little secret...
[whispers] I have three!
And when you put your glasses on,
your entire body turns human?
Oh, yeah. Mmm-hmm.
Head to toe.
You've been living
as a human for quite a while now,
so you must have
so many wonderful experiences.
Yeah.
But there's so many more things I'd do
if we weren't so busy saving the world.
Mmm-hmm? Like what else?
Would you swim in the ocean?
Oh, as soon as I get the chance.
- Would you skydive?
- No!
I'm afraid of heights.
Would you like to have
sexual intercourse with me?
Have you seen
Time Mistress Ava this morning?
She's supposed to show me
sketches of her gun-hands idea.
[Gideon] Unfortunately, she had to go.
Go? Go where?
The founding Time Masters
established a very specific protocol.
One captain, one AI.
There is no room for a Time Mistress,
which can lead
to distractions from the mission.
What did you do to her?
[Gideon] I predicted you would not react
favorably to this information,
so I gave you a sedative
to dampen your response.
How did you give me a sedative?
Oh.
It was 1916.
Two years into the war,
I was in the army, infantry unit.
All Welsh division, over in France.
We were trying to take
Mametz Wood from the Germans.
During the fighting,
me and another soldier, we were tasked
with delivering a message
to the general.
You see, we desperately
needed reinforcements, but...
You didn't make it in time?
We made it about halfway...
and the other soldier
that I was with was gunned down.
I just froze.
I was like a statue.
Darn legs wouldn't move.
I just stood there.
Just looking at him on the ground.
By the time I delivered
the message, it was too late.
There wasn't even a unit to go back to.
All of those boys...
I thought that God had spared me
so that I could go back in time
and save them, but I...
I keep failing at that task.
God must be punishing me for my sins,
punishing me for being a coward,
for not being able
to save them that night.
You are not a coward.
You lived through something most people
can't even begin to understand.
And by the way, talking to me about it,
it's pretty brave.
[man speaking other language]
[panicking]
[speaking English] Okay. Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, no.
Gideon, we're going to have
to discuss your behavior.
[Gideon] While you were resting,
I took the liberty of creating
another Hoover and an Edison robot.
Both are in the timeline fulfilling
their historically mandated duties.
Good for you,
making sure history stays on track.
Now, I think it's time
you take me back home.
[Gideon] Home?
You're a Time Master now.
This is your home.
[device calling]
[man on phone] Hello?
Who the hell is this?
Where's receptionist Ava?
[man] Who the hell is this?
It's me, Bishop.
Is this a prank?
Is that you, voice actor Ava?
Your impressions are uncanny.
No, listen. It's Bishop.
Okay? This is getting annoying.
How did you get this number?
Why do you sound exactly like me?
No, you sound exactly like me.
It's like someone...
No, no, no, no, no.
Gideon made a copy of me.
Of me?
How dare she?
There could only be one me.
[keyboard clacking]
Wait a second,
this can't be my actual to-do list.
I pay someone to kidnap a superhero
and take them
to a planet called Pliny X19?
What the hell's a Necrian?
The Fountain of Imperium?
I try to destroy the world?
And the Legends are the good guys?
They kidnapped me to give me a chance
to redeem myself, to save the world.
Oh, no.
I've been wrong about them
this whole time?
[Gideon] You should not be looking
at that information, Captain.
Tell me it's not true.
Tell me I don't become a bad guy.
[Gideon] Having information about your
own future can be extremely dangerous.
I started Ava Corporation
to make people's lives better.
I'm a good guy.
Somewhere along the way, I started
using my genius to do terrible things.
[Gideon] You no longer have
to do any of those things.
The Bishop robot will do them for you.
You're saying that robot I spoke to
on the phone will live my life?
[Gideon] That is correct.
Which means you are free
to fulfill your duty as a Time Master,
with me, forever.
[exhales heavily]
Yo, who's hungry?
It was a good day for hunting,
but a bad day for squirrels.
And we have enough firewood
to last all night.
Who knew Ava was part lumberjack?
Yeah, apparently,
when it comes to my anxiety and wood,
the wood's gonna lose every time.
That's my girl. Come here.
Man, I have missed you.
Mission accomplished.
It was really nice not to have
to think about the team for a second.
I missed you too,
but I really needed
to get some aggression out, you know?
Oh, yeah. Okay, I'll take that.
- I was really crazy.
- I know, I've seen that.
The captains look like happy campers,
and we got squirrel for dinner.
A real win-win.
Wait. Did you say "squirrel"?
Hey.
That human experience we had,
it was fun, wasn't it?
Oh, yes, it was great fun.
You know what I just realized?
My favorite thing about being human
is being with other humans.
Me too.
[man speaking Russian]
Hey, you can't just leave us in here.
Where?
- Hey, hey, hey.
- [mumbling frantically]
It's all right.
Sorry, it's my fault.
Whose fault?
A lad in my infantry unit.
He was my best friend from back home.
Okay, hey.
Tell me about him.
You do like to talk a lot, don't you?
I don't know.
Somehow he just managed
to light up a room with a smile.
He laughed at all of my terrible jokes.
Never wrote me any letters,
only the most...
the most delightful poetry.
Sounds like you really cared about him.
You loved him, didn't you?
Hey.
It's okay.
Yeah. Yeah.
I loved him.
God forgive me,
I loved Alun more than anything.
And it broke my heart
seeing how the war dimmed his light.
But he was a changed man,
even before my cowardice got him killed.
And seeing your brother,
see, it reminds me of how he used to be.
Hopeful.
Yes, I loved Alun.
And I failed him.
You know, actually, Behrad,
the original version, it's a long story.
He was a lot like you,
a soldier who was forced
to grow up too fast.
And I, um, I lost him because of that.
For years,
there wasn't a day that went by
when I didn't wish
that I had died instead of him.
But I was lucky.
I found these friends who had my back.
And eventually I was able
to save my brother and my parents,
and even make the world a better place
for a bunch of people I've never met.
So, you're telling me that
a ragtag group of eccentrics,
they helped you do all of that?
Yeah, believe it or not.
So, even though things
may feel hopeless right now,
you've got us.
[speaking Russian]
Okay.
Perfect.
Don't worry. I'm coming for you guys.
No.
[door unlocking]
There you are.
- Blessed saints.
- You found us.
Good news is I think I found the parts
we need to fix the machine.
Bravo, my boy, bravo!
The bad news is,
it's 1986, we're in Chernobyl,
and the meltdown is happening tonight.
I don't understand.
What is the significance
of this Chernobyl?
By the 1930s, scientists
had figured out nuclear fission,
which led to them creating
nuclear reactors to harness that energy.
Lord in heaven, nuclear fission,
they learnt how to split the atom.
Yeah, and by 1986,
there are a lot of nuclear reactors
like the one here in Chernobyl.
But tonight, a reactor explodes,
and civilians won't be evacuated
for almost two days.
People will die, and a lot more
will get radiation sickness.
Hang on a second now.
You said that the explosion
hasn't happened yet.
Yeah.
Whoa, whoa!
Maybe this is why I am here.
I might not have been able
to save Alun and the boys,
but my divine purpose,
maybe this is it, God's will for me,
to save people.
- No, no. Hold on, buddy.
- Come back!
Hey, hey.
Look, I'm all for hacking history,
but if we make that big
of a change to the timeline,
that killer Wa verider
will be right on top of us.
It would be worth it
if we can save some lives.
Yes, we must save lives.
Okay, fine. How do we alert people?
I think I know how. Come on.
Okay. [groans]
[sighs]
Now that there's a robot version
of me living my life,
I'm expendable.
I'm a nobody now.
[Gideon] The life of a Time Master
is one of anonymity,
and in some sense, expendability.
About as far back as I can remember,
I've always wanted
to help the world with my genius.
I was convinced the world needed me.
[Gideon] You are helping the world
as a Time Master,
and you'll start
by thoroughly eliminating the Legends.
Right.
The Legends.
The folks who gave me
a chance to redeem myself
after I tried to destroy the world.
Yeah, there it is.
Fantastic work again, my boy.
- I'll keep an eye out.
- Good you speak Russian.
Yes, well, I picked it up working in
a lab with some Russian scientists.
Lovely gentlemen, you know.
But I never thought
I'd be using it for this.
Okay, let's try this.
- Right, go ahead.
- Okay.
[clears throat]
[speaking Russian]
- Quickly, let's get out of here.
- Yes, let's get out of here.
[man speaking Russian]
[exclaims]
It worked! Look, everybody's leaving!
Yeah, but we won't have time
to run back and warn the gang
before that Wa verider shows up.
We will if we drive. Let's see
if I remember how to drive stick.
Wow! Wow!
Motorcars of the future
are truly fascinating.
Come on.
Now, will you look at that?
We took a little break
from leading the team,
and everything turned out fine.
Yeah. The kids are all grown up.
[chuckles]
Hey, what's up with those two?
I think they got into a fight
with a gooseberry bush and lost.
- You don't think that they...
- No.
[both laugh]
Any sign of them yet?
No, I hope they don't
run into any dinosaurs.
[Astra] Hey, guys, listen.
- [rustling]
- What's that weird noise?
According to my audio analysis,
it's a straight-four engine
with manual transmission.
And the squeaking noise suggests
there's a problem with the clutch.
Guess we're not gonna
see those dinosaurs.
[speaking indistinctly]
Please get the hell out of here.
We're in 1986,
just outside of Chernobyl.
- What?
The meltdown's gonna happen
in about 20 minutes.
We did make
a small change to the timeline.
Hold on. What did you guys do?
We broadcast a message
from a military base
informing everyone
that the meltdown was imminent,
that they should flee immediately.
I wasn't in good conscience gonna leave
without doing something, was I?
Okay. While I definitely
understand, you guys,
that's not a small change
to the timeline.
You've potentially affected
thousands of lives...
Yeah, and you just
put a huge target on our backs.
[Gideon] We have another disturbance
in the timeline, Captain.
Where to, Gideon?
[Gideon] 1986. The city of Chernobyl
in the Soviet Union.
Guess who's causing the disturbance?
I doubt that's necessary.
[Gideon] Because the Legends
wreak havoc wherever they go.
And you can finally end it,
once and for all,
by eliminating them for good.
Didn't you say rash actions
add more ripples to the timeline?
Fortunately, we're at
an opportune moment in history.
Any ripple effect you cause
will be negligible
due to its close proximity
to such a catastrophic event.
[sighs wearily]
Are you ready to save the timeline
from the Legends, Captain?
What's that noise?
- It's the Wa verider.
- Oh, man!
You guys need to go
fix that time machine. Now!
We need to put out this fire.
Be ready. We have no idea
who or what is on that ship.
Now, if we can wire
the magnetic components together...
We can bridge the electric current
from the compass to the ignition coil
and start the machine.
Absolutely fantastic work, young lady.
Fantastic! Very well.
Hey, Zari.
I've been doing a lot of thinking.
You... you wanna talk right now?
If I don't get this off my chest,
I won't be able
to think about anything else.
Go for it. I got it!
[exhales]
Yes, I want to live
in the Totem with you.
You do?
Are you sure? You haven't had
a lot of time to think about it.
You don't get it.
It doesn't matter where I go,
as long as I'm with you.
Uh, yes, we need more wire.
Mmm. I got it! This is very us.
- This is so us.
- Yeah.
Ah! Here it comes.
Not if I stop it first.
Come on. We've gotta go. Let's go!
[Gideon] We're right above
the Legends, Captain.
Only you can engage our weapons.
It's time to prove to me
that you're the man I know you are.
Oh, I'm sorry, Gideon,
I just can't do it!
I just can't kill the Legends.
Sure, they used me,
but they used me to do good.
[Gideon] Please return to your seat
and focus on the mission, Captain.
So one of these days, you're gonna
shoot me out the cargo bay,
like you did to Time Mistress Ava.
And I'd rather die
with a little more dignity.
[Gideon] There's nowhere to run!
You're wrong about that, Gideon!
[Gideon] No, do not go into Section A2.
That thing I just said
about dying with dignity...
[machine beeping]
I lied.
Dignity is overrated.
[screams]
Yes!
[screaming]
[continues screaming]
[Gary] What is that?
It's coming straight for us.
Is that someone on a toilet?
Who cares? Let's go!
[screaming]
Somebody press the red button.
Whoever it is,
they're gonna land right on top of us.
[screams]
[all] Oh, crap!
[theme music playing]