In 2166,
an immortal tyrant named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan is opposed
by the body I had sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered as legends.
Previously,
on Legends of Tomorrow...
You need to learn to embrace
your human side.
And what if that side of me is gone?
What if she doesn't exist anymore?
No, this is a dictatorship.
You get to call all the shots,
and I get to take all the shots.
The most powerful evil
the world has ever known
has just gone red
at the height of the Cold War.
Valentina Vostok.
She's trying to build a Soviet Firestorm.
Your comrade here tells me you know
quite a bit about this project of mine.
You're hanging us all out to dry, Rip.
I need backup.
Half the team is gone.
I'm gonna remember that, comrade.
You and Dr. Vostok
have much work to do in the morning.
Incredible. This is the exact formula
for the thermocore that's needed
to build a new Firestorm.
How did you manage to arrive at something
that took decades to produce?
But here's what I don't understand.
The Firestorm matrix is unstable.
The thermocore reacts exponentially
to the rate of fission in the host body.
Fortunately,
Dr. Wells developed a Quantum Splicer
to address that very problem.
I'm so happy to see that
you're taking an interest in my work.
What can I say, sir?
Nuclear physics is my passion.
"Sir?"
The Cisco I know
never dwelled on formality.
What's more, your hair is different,
your wardrobe neat,
your comportment gentlemanly.
Yeah, you like?
I just subscribed to GQ.
A snide attempt at humor.
Almost Cisco-like.
Almost.
What are you implying?
What I am stating, unequivocally, sir,
is that you are not Cisco.
Which means, I am not in S.T.A.R. Labs.
Furthermore, I will never,
never give you the formula.
Bravo, Professor Stein.
What cocktail of hallucinogens
have you given me, Doctor?
Don't worry.
I would never dream of damaging
that beautiful mind of yours.
I simply want to open it.
Finish the formula
and these little games of ours can stop.
You'll never trick me
into giving out my research.
And since you also cannot kill me
and destroy any hope
of creating a Soviet Firestorm,
I would like a hot shower
and a change of clothes.
And I thought I gave a good speech.
I'm sorry, have we met?
Eleven years ago, you bought
a nuclear warhead off me in Norway.
And then you and your time-traveling
friends tried to kill me.
Just like me, you haven't aged a day.
I have a good hairdresser.
In my long life, I have met some of
the most skilled interrogators in history.
But since we are in the Soviet Union,
let me tell you a story
about a friend of mine,
Joseph Stalin.
He became quite skilled at breaking a man.
Carefully aimed strikes to
the bridge of the nose,
along the shoulder blades
and right underneath the chin.
Stalin gave me this
as a gift.
So it's to be torture, then.
Get on with it.
No.
Nothing so prosaic for you, Professor.
There are infinite ways to break a man,
and I have an infinite amount of time.
Firestorm is my life's work.
I will never allow you to pervert it
in pursuit of global conquest.
This is going to be so much fun.
Jefferson. Jefferson.
Jax? What are you doing in here?
Hey, are you all right?
Yeah, I...
I haven't been able to sleep
the past two nights.
I prescribed Mr. Jackson
some mild medication.
Which don't seem to be doing a damn thing.
What's wrong?
It's Stein.
They've started in on him again.
He's scared to death. I can feel it.
- He's trying to be strong, but...
- We're gonna get him back.
Ray and Rory too.
I'm sure Captain Hunter has a plan.
It's my fault he got captured.
If he wasn't trying to protect me,
he would have never gone in there alone.
It's gonna be okay, Jax, I promise.
Well, you don't know what kind of place
they've got him locked up in.
Labor Camp Number 54,
formerly known as the Koshmar
or Nightmare Gulag.
Built in the 18th century...
Can we skip past the Wikipedia crap
and get to the good stuff,
like how to break in?
Perhaps you didn't register that
as a question, Gideon?
I understood.
But in its 200 years of operation,
no one has successfully escaped...
No offense, Gideon, but I never met
a building I couldn't break into.
Well, I hope you're right.
Savage knows that Stein created Firestorm,
but if he finds out that he is Firestorm...
It's always Savage with you, isn't it?
My partner's in prison, too.
- And Ray.
- Yeah, whatever.
The point is, you didn't lift a finger.
You know damn well it was never my
intention to get them thrown into a gulag.
But I had no other option.
Besides, I doubt that
it's Mr. Rory's first time in prison.
Or second or, I imagine, tenth.
All right, arguing is not gonna
bring the team back any faster.
And Rip's right.
Criminals usually do feel
more at home in prison.
And they know it better than anyone else.
So...
So, what if the key to breaking in
is asking someone who's been in and out
of Soviet prisons their whole life?
And who might that be?
Are you familiar with the Bratva?
Ooh, the Russian mob.
In 1986, they would have ruled
the criminal underground
inside every prison.
Your tattoo.
It stands for "Menia Ispravit Rasstrel, "
if I'm not mistaken.
In English, it translates to,
"Execution will reform me."
What brings you to the banya, little man?
The name's Rip.
I understand that you are familiar
with the Koshmar Gulag.
We need to break into that prison.
And can you make it fast?
I despise the heat.
A man by the name of Vandal Savage
runs his secret operation out of it.
A prison within a prison, if you will.
I have heard of this Savage.
He has no respect for my country's
rich criminal traditions.
So you'll help us?
You men have no tattoos.
And a man who has no life story
cannot be trusted.
Igor! Andrei!
Don't all volunteer at once.
Igor and Andrei
seem to be a bit preoccupied.
Now about that gulag...
No matter.
In this life, a man fights for himself.
Perhaps you'd like this one?
He's all yours.
So you like having Vandal Savage run
his evil empire from your country?
As much as a pig enjoys being
Christmas dinner.
Help us, and we will destroy
his entire operation.
I just took out six men.
You guys couldn't handle one?
- You killed my men?
- They're not dead, yet.
And neither are you, assuming you help us.
My organization runs
black market goods into Koshmar.
Three of our, well, comrades
are being held there by Savage.
Koshmar is not a hotel
for petty criminals.
If your friends are there,
they must be insane, ruthless animals.
Hey. Howdy.
- How you doing?
- What the hell are you doing?
Just being friendly.
This must be where they keep the VIPs.
This is prison, jackass.
There are no VIPs.
Some of these guys
have been here for a while.
Hey, maybe this guy
can tell us where Stein is.
The only thing you should be
worrying about, pretty,
is lasting the night.
- Stein needs help, he's in real trouble.
- News flash, so are we.
Think they'll bring us blankets later?
Now, according to Yuri,
this is where his men have access.
Got it?
- This isn't my first prison break.
- We've got it covered.
So, how can we help?
By staying on the ship.
We don't need any more casualties.
Besides, Mr. Snart and Sara
have got it covered...
Man...
Why does it feel like we're
on the JV team all of a sudden?
What you are, is one half of everything
Savage needs to change
the face of the Cold War.
And you are the only person
who can kill him.
- Yes, so you can't...
- I am not going to gift-wrap
the two people in the world
that Savage wants the most.
We should get going.
Ms. Lance, could I borrow you
for a moment?
I have something that might help you out
with the mission.
So, what did you really want
to talk to me about?
Gideon, will you please show Ms. Lance
the projection of 2016,
should our rescue mission fail.
I'd be happy to, Captain.
So this is what will happen to Russia
if we don't get Stein back?
Not Russia.
This is Star City.
The rest of the world
doesn't look much better.
That's impossible.
Not if Stein creates
a stable Firestorm for the Soviets.
Here in 1986, they are already
perilously close to creating a prototype.
Listen to me, Sara, everything,
everything we've tried to achieve
so far could be lost.
And not only will my family die
150 years from now,
but your family, your city,
your entire 21st century
world will suffer.
That's why we're going to get Stein back
before Vostok can break him.
Well, I hope so.
But we need a contingency plan.
What are you saying?
I'm saying that if at any point
throughout the operation,
it becomes clear that Martin is
beyond our reach...
You want me to kill Stein.
Impressive, how many weapons
you can fit in that outfit.
And how much stupidity
Raymond can squeeze into this one.
The plan is to save him, too.
Not just Stein and your partner.
I'm gonna save Raymond, all right.
So I can beat some sense into him.
And what about you?
What about me?
Clearly, I'm not the only one
with a side-mission.
What did Rip keep you after class
to talk about?
He just wanted to go over
a few details of the plan.
He wants you to take out the old man,
doesn't he?
It's the obvious play.
It's also heartless.
The plan is to save Stein.
And if, for whatever reason, we can't,
Rip showed me what will happen
to my home in 2016, to our families.
If Stein breaks,
the damage is irreversible.
I've been on a lot of heists.
And even when things got rough,
I never took out one of my own.
Well, this isn't a bank heist.
First, he left my partner
twisting in the wind,
now he's gonna have you
ice old silver-top?
We're all just pawns, Sara.
Come on, I'm the crook,
you're the assassin.
He's not just asking me to kill.
He's asking me to save the future,
and if for whatever reason
we can't save Stein,
then I'm gonna do what needs to be done.
It's just like scout camp.
Man, the food was terrible.
There was one time they gave us
Salisbury steak.
You ever stop talking?
What I wouldn't give
for a little Salisbury steak now.
Hey, Ray Palmer.
Put your hand down.
He might know
where Vostok is keeping the Professor.
Shut up and eat.
Do you know if there's any other place
where they keep prisoners here?
We're looking for a friend.
There is a place.
They send you there
and you never come back.
You can hear the screams all night.
This place, where is it?
Who said you could eat?
Hey.
He's not hurting anybody.
Who is this American
with the pretty teeth?
Must be a comedian.
I'm sure we can handle this like adults.
I brought you
something to eat, Professor.
If this is a bribe, I politely decline.
So stubborn, so proud, so American.
You've already built a thermocore,
so just build another one.
It'll only take you eight to 10 years.
You thought that, what?
Your friends stealing the thermocore
would save the West?
As if I would only build one.
We're so close, Professor.
All I need to learn now is
how to stabilize the thermocore
and my dream of creating a Nuclear Man
will be achieved.
To what end?
If you launch a Soviet Firestorm,
the United States
will have no choice but to retaliate.
Both countries will be annihilated.
And out of the ashes,
we will rise stronger.
Just as we did when the Nazis invaded.
But America is weak.
With your Big Mac, MTV,
movie star president.
Do you really think Vandal Savage
cares about the Cold War?
He's just using you, Doctor.
Do not think of insulting
Mr. Savage in front of me.
Hey, what's wrong?
Something's changed.
Grey thinks we've abandoned him.
He's starting to lose it in there.
I can't take this.
We've got to tell Rip.
The guy who benched us?
He'll just tell us to sit tight.
You know, I hate feeling so helpless.
This is exactly what it was like
when I blew out my knee.
I could barely walk,
the recruiters stopped calling,
my mom always crying.
I just wish there was something
I could do.
Wait.
Your connection with Stein,
it goes both ways, right?
- Yeah.
- So, maybe we can send him a signal.
Grey did tell me about this one time
he and Ronnie...
Get a knife. You need to cut me.
Tell me how to stabilize Firestorm.
If Einstein had the opportunity,
he would have traveled back in time
to prevent the creation
of the atomic bomb.
How can I, in good conscience,
lead the world to the invention
of something far more destructive?
You don't really have a choice.
This toxin, it's not lethal.
But it'll make you wish that it were.
Are you sure about this?
So, Professor,
would you like to talk
or would you prefer to scream?
Do your worst, Doctor.
Hey, Pyro, what was that there
back in the yard?
Just your typical prison alpha.
He didn't like you
threatening his reputation.
Not that, I mean, you sitting there
while I was getting my ass kicked.
None of my business.
None of your business?
None of your business? We're...
Supposed to be a team.
The only team I'm on is mine and Snart's.
Besides, you had that beat-down coming.
Oh, well, I can't sit back and watch
an old man get pushed around.
Then you're a bigger fool than I thought.
These are the ones I want.
Remember me?
Identification papers.
Yuri the Bear sent me.
Remember, we get Stein first.
And if the plan fails, you'll kill him.
- You want my advice?
- No.
Don't use your gun.
Do it with your hands, do it while
you're looking right into Stein's eyes.
You're talking about a member of our team.
I just don't want you to forget
who we're talking about.
Thank you.
Valentina has failed to make you talk.
Now, it's my turn.
Colonel,
let's begin.
So, are you still planning...
What did you threaten before,
"To go all Rocky IV on my ass"?
I've changed my mind.
Ivan Drago lives at the end of the movie.
Isn't he supposed to
ask us some questions?
They don't care what we got to say.
We're just part of the show.
Stein?
Professor, we're okay.
Don't tell these bastards anything.
If you think I have
a sentimental attachment to them,
you are as foolish as you are mad.
You held up longer than expected.
But if 4,000 years of life
has taught me one thing,
it is patience.
- When I get out of here...
- There is your mistake.
Thinking that you will get out of here.
Hey.
Can we get some water in here?
Something to drink? I'm a little thirsty.
A sandwich would be nice.
A little turkey and mayo?
They have mayo in Russia?
No?
At least in America you get a last meal.
Communism really sucks.
What are you doing, Boy Scout?
Yes, Boy Scout, what are you doing?
Nothing compared to what I did
to your mother last night.
You have quite a mouth on you.
So does she.
Enough. You're killing him.
That's it?
But the Colonel will think
that we're cheating him.
I'll tell you how to stabilize Firestorm.
Just let them live.
Please.
So, how does it feel to be dead again?
Take the next left.
You can't be down here, comrade.
I was ordered to take this corpse
to the incinerator.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
Dr. Vostok used him
for one of her smallpox weapons trials.
Highly contagious.
All right, this duct
should take us to solitary.
- We get to Stein...
- Yeah, I'm not going.
That's the plan.
That's Rip's plan. My priority is Mick.
Fine. Forget it.
So much for your code, crook.
Anytime, assassin.
Of all the dumb things
I've seen in my life,
you getting that guy to beat on you
takes the cake.
You're welcome.
You think you proved something back there?
- I proved I wasn't scared.
- You proved you'd make a great pinata.
He could have beaten you to death.
There are some things
that are more important than survival.
Like standing up for what you believe in.
Your principles.
Your team.
Must be something
you're willing to die for.
The perfect score.
The only difference between us is
how we define score.
I'm sorry to inform you, Captain.
The probability of the United States
losing the Cold War
has risen to 99%.
Star City, the seat of the resistance,
is predicted to fall in 2003.
Come on, Sara.
You mentioned the Quantum Splicer
earlier, Professor.
Your friends are counting on you
to make the right decision.
I have eyes on Stein.
The future is cementing.
You must extract Stein
before he enters the lab.
Move! Kill her!
What's happening, Miss Lance?
I couldn't rescue Stein.
Have they moved him into the lab?
Yeah, where Savage has every guard
in the gulag watching him.
Well, if that's the case...
I know what I have to do.
The formula for stabilizing
Firestorm, Professor.
This may surprise you,
but in my youth, I longed to visit Russia.
I was obsessed by your culture.
Rachmaninoff, Dostoyevsky, Tolstoy...
Stop stalling.
It's a shame I never got to see it
before the collapse.
What sort of nonsense
are you talking about?
In 1991, your economy fails
and your empire crumbles.
But the truth is, the world is better off.
In my time, crooks and thieves
rule your country,
desperate to hang on to power
and the riches they divide
amongst their cronies.
My country is by no means perfect,
but at least we are free to
criticize our government,
vote in fair elections,
and love whom we choose.
I, uh, hate to break this
to you, Dr. Vostok,
you are on the wrong side of history.
For now.
But you will help us change history.
Proceed.
Gideon, are you able to detect
the Professor's life functions remotely?
Yes, Captain.
His pulse is still strong.
Well, not for much longer.
Rip, Jax and I need to talk to you.
- Now is really not a good time.
- Yeah, this will only take a minute.
I know you think you can't risk losing us,
but that's assuming we'd fail.
And we won't.
I'm not afraid anymore.
I can do this.
And I don't got to be Firestorm
to be a part of this team.
Look, I am not prepared
to risk anyone else.
- Ever since...
- Carter?
- His death wasn't your fault.
- I know.
But Stein's will be.
All I got to do is touch him
and we can fly out of there.
Yeah, once you've scaled a 50-foot fence
topped with razor wire,
gotten past eight sharpshooters,
and entered a gulag full of the most
dangerous criminals in the USSR.
Okay, so...
You create a distraction and
I'll fly Jax in and no one will see us.
Listen, you're playing chess
without all your pieces on the board.
Maybe you're right.
So that's a yes?
You call that a flame?
- Ah, nice costume.
- Got one for you, too.
Ah.
Wakey, wakey. Time to shrink. Or not.
- Let's go.
- What about him?
We can't ditch him. He won't survive.
Two guards walking out of here,
not suspicious.
- Two guards carrying him out, suspicious.
- He took a beating for me.
Raymond would take a beating
for a total stranger.
Mick, if our time in the can
taught us anything,
it's we look after each other.
It's you and me, right?
So, if we enter here,
we can cut the circuit breaker.
Shutting off all the power.
Distracting the guards and giving us time
to save our team.
The probability of this plan
being successful...
There's a 15-second window
where the sharpshooters on the tower
aren't covering the breaker.
Which means that somebody would have
to run 120 yards in less than 12 seconds.
Given Mr. Jackson tore
his anterior cruciate ligament...
Have a little faith, Gideon.
You can do this. I know you can.
It's done.
You know, I've never seen a theorem
so simple, so poetic, before.
With this, I can decelerate
the subject's rate of fission
and decrease core body temperature.
Yet, something is missing.
I'm telling you, that is the equation.
Everything you need to build
a Quantum Splicer...
"We're coming?"
Explain.
- I cut myself.
- Impossible.
You have been monitored ever since
your arrival here, so unless...
So unless someone else was cut,
- yet it appears on your body.
- That's preposterous.
No, no, no. You're somehow connected
to the Burning Man.
That is how you were able to absorb
the nuclear energy at Luskavic.
You are mistaken.
No, you didn't only create Firestorm,
you are one half of Firestorm.
- That's ridiculous.
- Bring the core online.
And to think, all this time,
you were the missing link.
Listen to me, it is extremely rare
to find two people who are compatible.
And without the Splicer...
Have you ever merged
with a woman before, Professor?
I think you and I are going
to make a wonderful Firestorm.
What the hell are they doing?
What I should have done from the start,
helping rescue Stein.
- What about the timeline?
- I have a plan.
- Forget about the fail-safe.
- Isn't it a little late for plan C?
Not if Jax can reach
that circuit breaker.
Can't believe you're risking
your life for this idiot.
Okay. Okay. You got this.
Twelve seconds, open field.
Done it a million times.
Barry Allen, who?
Electromagnetic locks.
- We're dressed as guards.
- Run.
Everyone back in your cells!
Enjoy your new cell mate.
No!
That door leads to the loading bay.
From there, you can get to the Jumpship.
Hey, Mick. This is a strange kind of hug.
- Where are you going?
- I got something to do.
Mr. Savage,
I need to get you to the helicopter.
Make sure the Professor
enters the reactor.
His nuclear mate is waiting for him.
Take the core to full power.
There seems to be a riot going on.
You might want to reconsider your orders.
Vostok knows Stein's
the other half of Firestorm.
She's trying to merge with him.
Rip.
Once Stein is inside the reactor,
he will become Soviet Firestorm.
Do you copy?
I have the shot.
Sara, don't do it.
I don't have a choice.
It's the only way to save Star City.
The future.
That's how a killer thinks.
And that's not you anymore.
Our energy.
It yearns to be whole, Professor.
Not without the Splicer.
Without the Splicer, you'll never be able
to control our nuclear reaction.
You have to listen to me, Dr. Vostok.
Unless we un-fuse,
you'll end up killing us both.
Rip Hunter must be a fool
to send you into my arms.
Come with me, Chay-Ara,
and I will find a way
to prolong your life.
We will live together in eternity.
No.
"No?"
My answer will always be no.
Go.
You want to kill me
again?
Doesn't this game
ever get too old for you, Gareeb?
- It's Captain Hunter, if you don't mind.
- Oh.
I'm here to make sure
you never build a Firestorm.
And for my watch actually.
You stole it from me during
a pagan blood ritual back in 1975.
Ring any bells?
Uh-uh.
Slowly.
I have no desire to kill you.
I want you alive.
I want you to see the world burn.
I have looked so often at your wife
and son these last 11 years.
Miranda and Jonas.
Their faces etched into my mind.
And when I finally get to meet them,
I will let them know
that you and your friends
are responsible for their suffering.
Not if I see you first.
How's it going up there?
Sara? Sara, are you there?
Now you're on the comms?
We need to get out of here.
- No, don't shoot, Grey is in there.
- A lot of good it would do, anyhow.
- Man, screw this.
- What are you doing?
- I'm getting Stein back.
- We'll cover you.
I know you're in there, Grey.
And he's begging for you to save yourself.
I wasn't talking to you.
I was talking to Professor Stein.
Your mind is stronger than hers, Grey.
I get it.
I know why you've been so hard on me.
You're trying to protect me.
You don't want to lose me
like you lost Ronnie.
And that's why I know
you're not going to let her kill me.
'Cause I've had you inside of my head,
and I know what a tough
old son of a bitch you can be.
So, you got to fight her.
Because you and me, we're Firestorm, Grey.
You and me.
Jefferson. You okay?
- Yeah. You?
- Yeah.
Not for long.
I tried to warn her.
Without the Splicer, and myself,
her nuclear powers
are dangerously unstable.
It appears Dr. Vostok
is having a bit of a meltdown.
It's fascinating.
I think what he means to say is, "Run."
I'll have the Jumpship waiting
just beyond the main gate.
Courtesy of Yuri the Bear.
- How did you even have time to steal this?
- There's always time to steal.
Thank you.
And just so you know,
I know you're more than just a thief.
You took a beating for me.
We're even. End of story.
Well, thank you.
More drinking. Less feeling.
A toast. To the first time we haven't
completely ruined the timeline.
Please tell me that's true, Gideon.
The projections of the future
are back to normal.
- I'll drink to that.
- To Rip.
To things not going according to his plan.
- To the Captain.
- All right.
- Hold on.
- Jefferson, you're not quite 21.
- No.
In 1986, the drinking age
in Russia was 12, so...
Well, perhaps we could let it slide
this one time. After all, you
were the hero today. You saved my life.
Oh, that? That was no biggie.
Having merged
with an insane Russian scientist,
I now know how lucky I am
to have you as my partner.
Partners.
Stein doesn't know, does he?
- That I almost killed him?
- That I advised you to kill him.
It's funny.
When I was in the League of Assassins,
failure to follow through on a hit
was unforgivable,
a thousand times worse than death.
Maybe I'm losing my edge.
Or gaining a new one.
The fact that you didn't pull the trigger
speaks volumes.
The safe move was to kill Martin,
with the Cold War hanging in the balance.
I would like to think it was
your humanity that stayed your hand.
I'd like to think that, too.
But I had some help.
What was that?
We have been struck
with an explosive projectile.
- No kidding.
- Everyone get strapped in. Now!
We're in the Temporal Zone,
I don't understand.
No one should be able to...
You were saying?
A scan of the vessel suggests
that it is the bounty hunter Chronos.
Oh, man, this guy has impeccable timing.
He appears to be following us.
Firing counter-measures.
Counter-measures effective.
- Have we lost him?
- Yes, but not his missile.
Our aft shield is gravely compromised.
Initiating evasive maneuvers.
Vodka was a bad choice.
Impact in three, two, one...
Sir, we've just been
knocked out of the time stream.
- What does that mean?
- It means we're crash landing.
In place and time.
Gideon, camouflage the ship.
This doesn't look like the type of place
we want to linger out in the open.
That looks a lot
like a Palmer Tech building,
but why does it have a Smoak logo on it?
Wait, this is Star City.
I thought you said the timeline was safe.
Yes, Star City was intact in 2016.
This... This is 2046.
Don't move.
- Oh, Thank God.
- I said, don't move.
It's me. It's Sara.
Hey, Oliver, look.
I know it's been a long time,
but don't you remember that Rip Hunter
recruited us to become Legends?
I never heard of any Legends.
English - SDH