PROFESSOR STEIN: Time travel is real,
and all of history
is vulnerable to attack.
Which is why we must travel through time
to stop the spread
of these so-called Time Aberrations
and to erase their damage to history.
We are a team of outcasts and misfits,
so please don't call us heroes.
We're legends.
RORY:
Previously, on Legends of Tomorrow...
RIP: Mick has elected to stay.
SNART: Why?
Someone needs to be present
to destroy the Oculus.
SNART: Get him out of here!
RAY: He traded his life for ours.
He was a hero.
RORY: Leonard?
I must be losing my mind.
You're not right in the head, Mick.
That's why I'm here.
To set you straight.
SARA:
The amulet, why is it so important?
Hand over the box.
I swiped it off Darhk.
You have something we need.
I would like to broker a deal with you.
How did you manage to defeat him?
I gave him the amulet.
EOBARD: It's a compass.
DARHK: Compasses generally find things.
Have either of you gentlemen
heard of the Spear of Destiny?
It can be used to rewrite reality itself.
How do we find it?
EOBARD: You remember Captain Rip Hunter?
RIP: Cut!
Gideon, what's our status?
GIDEON: The Waverider is surprisingly
not destroyed, Captain.
Though, that condition
may not be permanent.
How long will it take to effect repairs?
GIDEON: Fifteen years.
Well, that won't do.
GIDEON: What is that, Captain?
There are some things, Gideon,
I can't even tell you.
Initiate repair procedures.
Auto repair engaged.
Shogun Ballistic.
Captain, that is the shutdown code
for my primary system...
Angels and Ministers of Grace,
defend us.
RORY: You're my best friend.
I love you, man.
What did you hear?
Nothing. Absolutely nothing.
Though, if I did, I suppose,
I might be flattered.
I wasn't talking to you.
Perhaps you've had enough to drink
for one night.
That's the point, I haven't had enough.
So, if you weren't talking to me, then...
- Snart.
- Snart, what?
I've been talking to Snart.
I've been seeing him lately.
You've been having hallucinations
of Leonard Snart...
If you tell anyone, I'll kill you.
I believe you.
- You can fix me.
- Me?
- You're a doctor.
- Of nuclear physics.
- Same thing.
- Mr. Rory, I can't...
You can fix me.
But you can't tell anybody about it.
- You got that?
- Yes.
Nate. Nate.
Nate.
Sorry, guys. It helps me concentrate.
- It's 3:00 in the morning.
- Amaya and I were trying to sleep.
Not together.
What are you doing up so late?
Just trying to figure out
what the Legion of Doom wants
with those two amulets.
"The Legion of Doom"?
Darhk, Merlyn and the Speedster.
It's from a Hanna-Barbera cartoon
I liked when I was a kid.
Sorry I woke you guys up.
We weren't together.
- He knows, Ray.
- Yeah.
Well, have you figured anything out?
Well, I carbon-dated the amulet
that Sara took from Darhk in 1987.
Before she gave it back
to the Legion of Doom, I'm guessing.
Yeah, and Gideon puts the amulet's date
of origin around 30 A.D.
High concentrations
of manganese, copper and zinc.
Which would make bronze.
Correct. Now, Roman centurions
put bronze in all their metalwork.
Circa 30 A.D.
I also sketched the two amulets
the best I could from memory,
but they don't match
any artifacts on record.
What if they are not two artifacts?
What if they're one?
Shut up.
The Longinus Medallion.
Hmm.
Longinus is the name generally
associated with the Roman centurion
who pierced the side of Christ
during the Crucifixion.
Yeah, he was blind
and got the blood of Jesus in his eyes
and then he could see again.
- DR. HEYWOOD: Look at you.
- What? I went to Sunday School.
Now, that blood
allegedly got on the Medallion,
and empowered it and the Spear
with magical powers.
Well, why does the Legion of Doom
want the Medallion?
"Legion of Doom"?
- Yeah.
- Don't ask.
Well, according to legend,
the Medallion calls for the Spear,
and basically takes you right to it.
The Spear is also known as
the Holy Lance or the Spear of Destiny.
Hold on, this all just sounds
like an Indiana Jones movie.
Raiders of the Lost Ark is the reason
I became a historian. You know that?
Okay, so the Legion wanted the Medallion
so they could get the Spear.
But what do they want with the Spear?
Well, the Spear allegedly
has the power to rewrite reality.
But how's that different from us
traveling through time,
making changes in history?
Changes to history cause timequakes
and Aberrations which we can undo.
Changes to reality, however,
those are permanent.
SARA: Great.
And I just handed them over the Medallion.
In exchange for Grey's life.
Any one of us would've made that call.
Would Rip?
So much for sunny California.
When we're done here, we need to go
to the 1600 block of Vine Street.
Why, pray tell?
It's where Frank Sinatra's star
is on the Walk of Fame.
I've always wanted to see it.
I am not sure if that's part of
our little trinket's itinerary.
I said, "When we're done."
As far as magical artifacts go,
this one is frustratingly unspecific.
Actually, like most magical artifacts,
its ways are nuanced.
That's just a fancy word for vague.
And I'm getting tired of walking.
True. We could use some transportation.
Wow.
Afternoon, fellas.
Not so fast, buddy.
Wallets.
Now.
Just give us your motorcycles.
Excuse me?
Give us the bikes and we'll let you live.
What are you?
Some sort of comedians or something?
Oh. Something.
That charming-looking fellow
is Cal DeVito.
Instead of being killed, he's supposed
to go on to invent a new carburetor
for Shovelhead motorcycles.
As far as Aberrations go,
don't you think that's a bit...
Puny? Yeah.
Well, Gideon was going over
autopsy reports,
and, well, I'll just let her tell you.
Gideon?
GIDEON: Both gentlemen
were killed in close quarters
with suzuki strikes to the
xiphoid processes of their sternums.
A League of Assassins technique.
Weren't Darhk and Merlyn former L.O.A.?
He must be getting closer
to the Holy Lance.
I'm leaning towards Spear of Destiny.
I prefer Holy Lance.
Can't imagine why.
Gideon, plot a course
for the point of origin of the Aberration.
GIDEON: I already have, Captain.
Hollywood, 1967.
AMAYA: Is the Professor all right?
Uh, depends on
what you mean by "all right."
He's helping Mick with something.
I don't know.
He's been kinda quiet about it.
I hope he figures it out soon,
'cause if the Legion of Doom is here...
Really like how that name's catching on.
We're gonna need Mick and Firestorm.
Let's figure out what's going on first.
Look, all I know is Gideon said,
the motorcycles Darhk
and Merlyn stole are here.
What? We're just supposed to walk around
until we see a sign that says, "This Way"?
Good idea.
Subjugating the world to your rule
isn't saving it.
You would create a wasteland,
and call it peace.
Do not misquote Tacitus to me.
I knew him well.
I lived long enough to watch
civilizations rise and fall...
Cut! Just stop.
- Cut, please.
- MAN: All right. Cut.
And everyone take five.
I just need to think.
George.
What do I do?
It wasn't that bad...
You saw him.
I just can't seem to get Peter
to bring any menace to the part.
I may need to recast.
No, no, no.
You don't have time to recast, okay?
Your thesis film is due
in less than a month.
I know, I know, but...
Look, a film is only as good
as its villain.
And I have an antagonist
who's as threatening as a...
Weiner dog.
Rip Hunter?
No, I'm the director,
Rip's being played by Adam Glassman.
He's probably at craft services.
Nice to see your reputation
for dry humor is well-earned.
You see, this is what I'm talking about.
You guys are good.
Yeah. These are great props.
Did you make these yourselves?
Hey, we're on something of a clock here.
SARA: Oh, my God. It's Rip.
Don't worry. We got you, Rip.
- Who the hell are you guys?
- We don't have time for this.
Get outta here. Save yourself!
- What about you?
- I can't leave my film in there!
Get out of here, man!
No film is worth losing your life.
Jesus!
Get Rip out of here.
- Hey, come on. We got to go.
- Get away from me.
What the hell, man?
- Fall back!
- RAY: Run!
OFFICER 1: Stay right there!
OFFICER 2: Hands! Hands!
Freeze! Don't Move!
- Where do you think you're going?
- My movie's inside.
- These lunatics just showed up...
- Do you know these people?
- No, no. I told you...
- Against the wall, long hair.
What? But my movie...
- Can wait. You're under arrest.
- What?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Well, that went apocalyptically awful.
I've got Nate and Amaya researching
where the police took Rip.
We'll spring him, and then...
We'll find out what the hell is
going on with him?
Dude tried to bludgeon me
with this non-lethal weapon.
Look, we don't know how long
he was in 1967.
He could be suffering from time drift,
which is why he doesn't remember us.
The question is, how?
Well, he could have time-scattered himself
like he did with us.
No. He sent us his final message
after scattering us.
He wouldn't have been able
to use it for a second time.
Well, he got here somehow,
and so did Darhk and Merlyn.
The Legion of Doom.
- I'm not calling them that.
- Okay.
If they came to 1967 looking for Rip,
that means...
The Medallion must have led them here.
Rip has the Spear of Destiny.
We gotta bust him out of jail
before they get to him first.
And ever since,
I've had a fear of giant toads.
Mr. Rory, while I appreciate
the thoroughness of your insights,
perhaps we could focus
on the issue at hand.
I thought shrinks liked mommy talk.
I'm not a...
You know, I think I've heard
enough on that subject.
Now, when did you
first encounter the apparition?
The ghost of Mr. Snart.
When did he first appear?
Back in Chicago.
Can you remember anything specific?
Something that might have
triggered the vision?
He said something about
setting me straight.
- Why do you think he'd say that?
- I don't know.
Maybe he's, um...
Captain! Hello.
What can we do for you?
It's Rip. He's here, in 1967.
That's astonishing. How?
We don't know. But Damien Darhk
and Malcolm Merlyn are after him,
which means you two
cannot sit this one out.
Of course. My apologies.
I was helping Mr. Rory with his migraine.
Yes. I have a very bad headache.
Well, you're going to have to suck it up,
'cause I need your help
breaking Rip out of jail.
What's he doing in prison
and how do you plan on breaking him out?
It involves you playing a shrink.
Do you think you can do it?
If I must.
Great.
Good day.
Can I help you?
Yes, I believe you have
one of my patients in custody.
Name?
His name...
Gideon, a little help.
GIDEON: According to his mug shot,
he was booked as Phil Gasmer.
Philip Gasmer.
It's imperative that he be released
into my custody immediately.
He suffers from delusions
of being pursued by futuristic spacemen.
Oh, yeah, that guy.
This way.
Astonishing.
It's really you.
Yeah. It's me.
Who are you?
I'm your doctor, Mr. Gasmer.
I'm here to take care of you.
I have never laid eyes on you before
in my life.
Memory problems are part of the delusion.
I'll have to admit him.
He can't be treated here.
What? No...
Look, don't leave.
This man is not my doctor.
I'm not crazy!
Hey, I know. I know. It's okay.
Look, my name is Sara Lance.
This is Mick Rory and Martin Stein.
We're your friends.
Two of them are.
You're one of them.
- Help! Help!
Hey, okay. Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Listen to me, all right? Calm down.
We're here to help you.
You got to trust me.
Your name is Rip Hunter.
Rip Hunter's a figment of my imagination!
Help!
Mick.
We've got Rip.
We're headed to the extraction point.
Oh, no.
DR. HEYWOOD: What is it?
Can I help you?
Hey.
DR. HEYWOOD:
Sara, you've got incoming.
Darhk and Merlyn
just entered the precinct.
SARA: Yeah. I see him.
- They're blocking our escape.
- There must be another way out.
Ray, how well can you fly the Waverider?
RAY: I thought you'd never ask.
- Wait, you know how to fly the ship?
- Sure do.
I just have to channel my inner Han Solo.
- Gideon does most of the work.
- She does?
GIDEON: I do.
Where to, Cap?
All right. We're here.
Get to the cargo bay.
Ray, do not crash my ship.
You break it, you buy it.
- Get away from me!
- Captain Hunter, you must listen to us.
Why do you keep calling me that?
- Look, Rip...
- Is this some kind of joke?
Rip, just calm down, okay?
We need you to remember.
Your name is Rip Hunter.
You are a Time Master.
You fly the Waverider. It's a time ship.
Rip! Rip, just wait.
This cannot be happening.
- Am I dreaming?
- Rip?
Oh, God! Did I drop some really bad acid?
Rip, be careful.
Why? I'm hallucinating.
There's no such thing as Rip Hunter,
and there's no such thing as a time ship.
There's a...
Get to the ship. Go!
- Let's go. Let's go!
- Guys, come on. Quick.
Come on!
SARA: Well, Gideon?
GIDEON: I'm afraid the news isn't good,
Captain.
A deep scan reveals that.
Captain Hunter's neural architecture
has been completely restructured.
His limbic system reprogrammed
with a new identity.
So it isn't time drift.
Rip didn't forget who he was. He...
- Changed.
- RAY: Reprogrammed?
The technology to alter the brain
at that level doesn't even exist.
Unless Rip's brain was somehow altered
by impulses from the...
- From the...
- From the ship's time drive?
Yeah.
You're talking temporal electrocution
as a method of time travel.
- It's practically suicidal.
- Does that track?
I'm not sure. Excuse me.
What's his problem?
I don't know.
GIDEON: Captain Hunter must have
shut down my systems because he knew
I would never permit him to
make physical contact with the time drive.
For good reason,
he could have ended up anywhere,
and in any period in time.
But before he deactivated me,
he recovered something from his parlor.
A piece of wood
approximately .6 meters long.
A piece of wood?
The Spear of Destiny?
Could be. I'm gonna go tell the others.
I got an idea.
So this would be
a new milestone for you then.
What's your idea?
Why don't we use that thing
to see what's up with my brain?
I doubt you'd find the results
you're hoping for.
These tests are meant to find
neurological changes,
while my theory is that
your visions are the result of emotion.
You're saying I'm crazy?
I'm saying you're feeling something.
And in the wake of your partner's demise,
that's perfectly normal.
I don't do feelings.
Run a test. Fix my brain.
Hey, what's up?
Sara asked us to find
any physical descriptions
of the Spear that might help us find it.
She thinks Rip had it with him
when he traveled to 1967.
And she also wanted you to work on
figuring out, um, a way
to reverse the effects on Rip
since he came in contact with the...
Time drive.
GIDEON: I've brought up the time drive
schematics for you, Dr. Palmer.
What? How do you expect me
to understand any of that?
Uh, maybe using one of your four PhDs?
I don't have four...
What's wrong?
It's like I should have memories
that aren't there,
and I should understand what this is,
but I don't.
Yeah, I feel it, too.
It's happening right now.
I'm reading this book
about Centurion Longinus
and it's just a bunch of words.
How long have the two of you
been feeling like this?
- Since, uh...
- RAY: Since, uh...
- Film set.
- DR. HEYWOOD: Film set.
Mr. Hunter's film.
Sara had Jax go and recover
what he could find.
"Glucas."
Wait. Isn't that what you pretend
you're allergic to, Ray?
What? First of all, my gluten allergy
is very real and challenging.
Secondly, it's G. Lucas,
as in George Lucas.
Wait. George Lucas.
How do I know that name?
Gideon, pull up George Lucas
on the historical record.
GIDEON: George Lucas, born in Modesto,
California, on May 14th, 1944.
Named Modesto Hartman's
"insurance Salesman of the Year"
in 1977, 1980, and 1983.
Three years. Hmm.
- That doesn't seem right.
- No.
Gideon, is there a version of history
where Mr. Lucas
did something else with his life?
Apparently, this Mr. Lucas
is an Aberration.
He's not the Aberration.
The Legion of Doom scaring him
is the Aberration.
An Aberration
that directly affects our lives!
Okay! Calm down. Take it back.
Gideon thinks that the Legion's attack
on Mr. Hunter's film set
caused this George Lucas guy
to quit moviemaking.
As a result, he never made some movie
about space battles,
or another one about an
improbably handsome archeologist.
And we care about this because?
GIDEON: In the unaltered timeline,
Dr. Palmer sees Star Wars as a child
and is inspired to become an inventor.
Likewise, Dr. Heywood
chooses to be a historian
after seeing Indiana Jones
instead of becoming a yoga instructor.
Aw, man!
Wait. So, you're telling me
that because some film geek
drops out of school,
my inventor and my historian
are now, essentially, useless?
- Yes.
- Hey.
- I'm just saying.
GIDEON:
If the Aberration is not corrected, yes.
We need to fix this now.
GIDEON:
I fear you may already be too late.
As of today, George Lucas
is no longer enrolled in film school.
DR. HEYWOOD: There he is.
George Lucas, the man who inspires
both of our careers.
- Supposedly.
- Well, let's go inspire him.
- Guys, maybe I should do the...
- Hey, George!
You remember us? I had metallic skin.
- No! No! No, no!
- Hey. George Lucas, wait.
Look, time takes time to harden.
Sooner or later,
we're going to lose our superpowers
the same way we're losing our memories.
If you don't make the movies
that you make,
I don't become a brilliant inventor.
And I don't become
an incredibly handsome historian.
I haven't made any movies yet, okay?
I'm still in film school.
- Or I was.
- RAY: That's the point.
If you don't go back to school,
you'll screw up both of our lives.
We don't live up to our full potential.
And I do not want to be a heart surgeon!
DR. HEYWOOD: And I don't want
to be a yoga instructor.
Okay, guys, like I said,
why don't I talk to our Time Aberration?
- Yeah, but...
- Shh.
Stay in school.
I'm sorry about my friends,
they're just...
Completely insane?
Yeah, but what they say is true.
Okay, what?
That you guys are from the future?
That you've somehow seen a bunch of movies
that I haven't even made yet?
Well, actually I'm from the past,
but that's beside the point.
Look, George, I don't care about movies,
but guys like them,
they do.
So, before you get in that oar
and drive back to Modesto,
just think about them, okay?
Them and all the millions of other people
that your stories will someday inspire.
The future of the entire world
is at stake.
And you're our only hope.
I've never actually seen
your quarters, Mr. Rory.
They're charming.
- Oh, my God.
- What is it?
PROFESSOR STEIN: Something unusual. Some sort of receiver.
Judging from its design,
one sensitive
to gravitation wave transmissions.
You're telling me
I have an antenna in my head.
- Well, the good news is you're not crazy.
- RORY: Oh, really?
So, seeing and talking to Snart is real.
Well, in a sense, yes.
Your former partner was killed
when the Oculus exploded
in a blast of temporal energy.
Now, if Mr. Snart
was able to bond with that blast,
the version of him you're now seeing
could be, um...
How will I put this?
Like a time-ghost?
Precisely!
But what I want to know is,
how did someone manage to put a device
inside your brain without you knowing it?
MAN: You're Chronos.
The Time Masters.
They did some sick things to me
when I was Chronos.
I'm sorry, I forgot.
So, what you're saying is,
Snart's stuck out there,
blasted into a billion pieces
floating around in time and space.
A rather simplistic way of looking at it,
but, yes.
You're an idiot.
- Excuse me?
- It didn't have to end like this.
Mr. Snart, is he here?
Why am I here? Why are you here?
You are dead.
What's he saying?
He's telling me I've gone soft
because I'm still on the ship.
Doc. Doc.
You gotta get this thing out of my head.
As I explained, I'm not a medical doctor.
But I'm sure Gideon and I
can figure something out.
- That can work?
- In theory, yes.
Huh.
Groovy office.
Used to be yours.
Come on. None of this is bringing back
any memories for you?
Listen, lady. I wish that I could be
the guy that you want me to be.
The "Rip." But I am not.
I take it you two were pretty tight?
- Yeah, he saved my life.
- Cool.
You.
You saved my life.
I was lost. You came, you recruited me.
You gave me purpose.
It sounds like Sandra.
She's the hero of my movie.
- That's weird...
- What? A female hero?
Get with the times, lady.
Yo, we're all in his movie.
I mean, it's different versions of us,
but this is definitely the team.
Like on page 89, my character, Max,
he saves...
Hold on.
You're telling me that this burnout
used repressed memories
to write a screenplay?
That's not all.
He's writing about the Spear of Destiny.
Which you had with you
when you time-jumped off the Waverider.
I don't know what you're talking about.
- Yes, you do.
- Come on, now.
What, I just made it all up.
The spear is the McGuffin.
- The what?
The thing in the movie
that everyone's trying to get.
Well, where is it?
In the movie, it's in pieces.
Rip just has a fragment of it.
What inspired you to write it that way?
I don't know.
I just had this old piece of wood.
I thought it'd be a cool movie prop.
- Where is it?
- Uh, I gave it to my prop master. George.
Oh.
Great.
George Lucas has the Spear of Destiny.
Glad you changed your mind, George Lucas.
Going back to film school,
definitely the right call.
We agree.
MALCOLM: Neat trinket.
One of the lost totems of Zambesi, right?
Ah, Mr. Lucas,
you have something that we have
traveled a very long way to find.
A piece of the Spear of Destiny.
Where is it?
Lady and gentlemen,
if you don't mind, hands up.
And if you do mind,
we'd be happy to kill you.
- I'll cover George Lucas.
- And I've got...
What?
It's not here. My suit's not here.
I can't steel up.
Maybe I didn't make myself clear.
Put 'em up.
- He was talking, I didn't...
- Hands up.
- Shut up.
- They're up.
Thank God. I don't think it's here.
All right, Specky Four-eyes,
I'm starting to lose my patience with you.
Where is the Spear?
What spear?
We had a little chat
with the members of your film crew.
And they all claimed the
"Spear of Destiny" was a prop,
and that you, Mr. Lucas, were its master.
Yeah, but the movie was done.
I tossed all the props
down the garbage chute.
- They were just trash.
- But, but, but, but... Shh!
I've one question for you, Mr. Lucas.
And your life depends on
answering me honestly.
Where is the city dump?
Gideon, set us down
as close to their location as you can get.
GIDEON: Yes, Captain Lance.
And while you're at it, find Mick and...
Grey?
SARA: What the hell are you doing?
Brain surgery. What does it look like?
DARHK: We down there somewhere.
Good, because you'll never find it.
You're right.
You're going to.
I could be in Modesto by now.
Shut up and dig, George Lucas.
What kind of superheroes
are you guys, anyway? Huh?
I mean, sure they have laser guns,
but aren't you guys
supposed to have superpowers?
Yeah, well, we had superpowers.
But because you don't make Star Wars,
I don't become a scientist,
I don't make the Atom suit.
Or the serum that turns me into steel.
I can't believe we're all going to die
because of a stupid movie.
Perhaps they need a little incentive.
DARHK: Oh.
Agreed.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- RAY: Oh, no.
What was that?
Don't just stand there,
try and brace it with something.
Oh, no.
- Guys, I found it.
- Don't show 'em.
What? We're in a trash compactor.
We're going to die.
No, Ray's right. If we give them what
they want, they're gonna kill us anyway.
Okay, well, then what do we do?
They're going too slow.
Shoot one of them to move things along.
- Which one?
- Dealer's choice.
What was that?
This rescue mission
is not going very well, is it?
GIDEON: I'm afraid not, Captain.
Would you stop calling me that, please?
I'm not a captain, I'm just a regular guy.
So was Captain Hunter.
He had no superpowers,
unless you count his courage,
intellect, and honor.
Well, what would he do, huh?
Your captain, if he were here?
You guys, we have to give it to them.
There's no other way.
There is. You have to become a filmmaker,
you have to make movies.
And you, George Lucas,
have to believe that.
- What?
- You have to make your movies,
so that we can become
who we're supposed to become.
So we can save you.
Your movies go on to change the world.
All you have to do is believe in yourself.
You have to believe
you are gonna make amazing movies.
You have to believe it,
like there's no tomorrow.
Say it, George, say it out loud.
George Lucas, what do you really want?
What I really want?
What I really want is to direct.
Ah!
Whoa!
- About time you showed.
- Where were you?
Always busy, gentlemen,
and yet never late.
So, who do we kill first?
That would be me.
EOBARD: Captain Rip Hunter.
It's been ages.
I was beginning to think you were dead.
On the contrary,
for the first time in recent memory,
I am finally, truly, alive.
Oh, crap.
Hey, does this thing work?
Screw it. Gideon, fire!
Fire everything!
Go!
- Hey, come on.
- Rip!
- Hey, Sara.
- We gotta go, he's gone.
- Gideon...
- Rip!
We couldn't have got him.
You know that, right?
Yeah.
Look, Sara,
you can't beat yourself up about this.
It's my responsibility, as captain,
to make sure that everyone
gets back on this ship.
Everyone.
And I failed.
You call getting a piece
of the Spear of Destiny
and the Medallion a failure?
The Legion have nothing.
They have Rip.
We lost him, Jax. Again.
But they won't have him for long.
If I know one thing about you,
it's that you don't give up.
When you really want something,
you are unstoppable,
and God help anybody
that tries to get in your way.
We are gonna find him
and we're gonna bring him home.
Is that a promise?
That's a prophecy.
How are you feeling? Have you seen
our mutual friend around lately?
No, that's because you took the chip out.
Well, actually...
- You did take the chip out?
- Yes, I did.
But after further inspection,
I discovered that the device
hasn't functioned in months.
It seems you've taken one too many
blows to the head.
So I am going crazy.
- I'm seeing a ghost.
- There is no ghost.
Leonard Snart truly is no more.
Then why do I keep hearing his voice?
That voice inside your head is your own.
If Leonard Snart is second-guessing
your moral obligation to this team...
But that's what I feel.
We all hear contradictory voices
inside our heads, Mr. Rory,
creating what is known in psychology
as cognitive dissonance.
My brain hurts.
Well, I'm sure it does.
The complexities of human emotion
can, at times, be mindboggling.
What's this?
I thought you got your smarts back.
It's movie night.
Gideon checked the timeline.
It seems all of George's movies
are now part of history again.
Huh. I've almost forgotten
how to perform a median sternotomy.
Well, I guess, I'll just go back to being
a billionaire inventor with four PhDs.
So, what are we gonna watch first?
I mean, after we watch Raiders,
clearly his best film.
Which he never would've made
if he hadn't made Star Wars first.
Oh, wait, this one sounds cute,
it's called Howard the Duck?
- No.
Okay.
Maybe movie night
wasn't such a good idea.
Maybe you're right.
After all, we did just lose Rip.
I know Nate and I
never really got to know Rip,
but we know how much
he means to the rest of you.
Yeah.
GIDEON: Might I offer my opinion?
RAY: Fire away.
I believe Captain Hunter would want you
to enjoy yourselves tonight.
All right then, dim the lights.
Gideon, pick the movie.
We'll watch Raiders after.
- Then, Empire.
- Then, Last Crusade.
Get comfy. It's gonna be a long night.
Uh...
Hello?
Is anybody there?
Hey, man.
Welcome, Captain Hunter.
You know I was bluffing, right?
I am not actually Rip Hunter.
My name is Phil.
I'm a full-time film student,
and part-time recreational drug user.
Seriously regretting the latter.
Oh, I know exactly who you are.
I know that you are one of the
protectors of the Spear of Destiny.
And I know that you know
where the other pieces are hidden.
I don't know anything! I swear.
I am not Rip Hunter!
I am nobody!
I can't believe this is happening to me.
You're gonna torture me, aren't you?
Oh, I'm not going to torture you,
Mr. Hunter.
No.
They are.
No, please, please. Please,
please, please, let me go.
Let me go!