Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
- I plan on asking Nora to marry me.
- Yes.
You don't understand
how dangerous that Loom is, John-o.
Come on, Charlie.
We use the Loom to help Astra,
and then I will help you
destroy it forever. Deal?
Someone's trashing
Rebecca Silver online.
Cute. You have a troll.
- This your kid?
- She's your kid, too.
Nora belongs in the real world...
I need you to support her.
And she can't do it
on that ship of yours.
Do the right thing, son.
Morning, babe.
Hey.
You okay?
Actually, I was thinking
about your dad.
That's romantic.
Thinking about something
he said to me.
When I committed my life to you,
I meant it.
So I've been thinking...
maybe our life together
isn't on this ship.
Maybe it's time for us
to move on, and move out.
Together.
Oh, hey.
Listen, I wanna build a life
with you wherever we are.
I know, but...
you can't really do your job
on a Timeship.
What about the Legends?
They've become my family.
But we can't begin our life together
when I literally have
one foot in the past.
So I think I'll do one last mission
with the team.
Say goodbye.
Are we doing this?
Yeah.
- Okay.
Okay.
Yeah, but maybe
after we brush our teeth?
Okay.
Come on! Is she still in there?
Zari, there's a line.
I'm doing my hair.
You can't stop
the glam routine mid-process.
Come on, we talked about this!
Let me guess. Zari?
Hey, what happened
to the sign-up sheet I made?
Oh, Mick burned it in frustration
after Zari's last Korean
Sheet Mask day.
Well, I guess now is as good a time
as any to tell you two that...
Nora and I have some big news.
We're talking big news?
Because, guys, I got a whopper.
I told John we'll help him
find the Loom of Fate.
Nuh-uh. You know the rules.
No MacGuffin talk until after
I've finished my coffee.
Yeah, and besides, you guys were
- about to make a big announcement?
- Yes.
Is it time for morning announcements?
'Cause I need you all to know,
I have to go so badly.
If my sister ever leaves
the bathroom!
- B!
- Come on.
Hey, bro, let's not pretend like
you don't take this long
with your hair.
Get in line.
Bathrooms are also for other things.
And in other announcements...
She still in there?
I would be too
if I had all that damn hair.
Okay, well, this is the perfect time,
now that we're all here,
to let you know that Nora and I...
You're moving out.
- How'd you know that?
- Well, you got married.
Next logical step in a relationship.
And by the way,
I heard you two going at it
like jackrabbits last night.
- At least someone's getting it.
- Oh, my God.
Look, after one final mission...
Nora and I will be leaving.
- I'm gonna miss you, man.
- Wait. For real?
- Seriously?
- Congrats.
I mean, we always knew
this day would come,
but I never thought it
would be so soon.
How are you gonna tell Nate?
- Tell Nate what?
- What?
The wait for the bathroom
is upwards of 30 minutes.
- Can you believe it?
- Hey, take it easy.
At least I get to wait in line
with the happy new couple.
Nora, welcome to your
new morning routine.
Uptown!
- Thank God.
- Good morning. Good morning.
Damn, she looks good.
Glam complete.
You guys could really
work on your hygiene.
It's 7:15.
Mick! There you are.
Mona.
Consent to hug you?
I'll take that as a no.
So what's new?
Any torrid affairs, flourishing
romances, lovers left behind?
Rebecca Silver could always
use fresh inspiration.
No.
Anyway, had to be here
for Nora's first book club
as a married woman.
And speaking of books,
I could use your advice.
Rebecca Silver has been
besieged by a troll.
Forget about her.
I mean "him." Whoever.
Well, I tried that,
and it didn't stop.
I was thinking of reaching out.
Don't. It's just gonna
make you feel worse.
Well, I think it's a cry for help.
Maybe someone just needs
to show them love.
It's got nothing to do with love!
Hey, I was packing up my stuff
in the lab,
and I noticed
that Marie Antoinette is gone,
and the jars of Rasputin are empty.
Astra must have recalled
their souls to hell.
Damien said something
about "eternal torture."
So, packing, huh?
You talk to Nate yet?
When I saw his face back there,
I just couldn't.
He was so excited
about us living together.
I just have to wait
for the perfect moment, you know?
Look, I say just get it over with.
And then you guys can enjoy
your last "hoorah" together.
Yeah. Saying goodbye to Nate,
it's my biggest mission yet.
I did go to the moon once,
so second biggest.
The Loom of Fate.
Eons ago, I tossed it
through space and time
because it was too dangerous.
But now, for all my sins,
we're gonna piece it
back together again.
And finally put an end
to our Encore problem.
By rewriting Astra's life
and setting her on the right path.
Yeah, speaking of life changes...
Must be a life-changing experience
for you, Charlie,
to know that the Loom
is back on our Earth.
- Charlie?
- Yeah, it is.
But there's only one piece
whose spot I'm sure of.
I gave it to a close mate
of mine for safekeeping.
All right, so we'll go back
to right after you dropped it off.
That's our move.
And speaking of moves...
Let's get a move on it.
Where are we headed, Charlie?
Well, the last place I left it
was in London, 1594.
Gideon, set a course.
Affirmative, Captain.
And speaking of setting
a new course...
Of course, she means...
Sara, please give us one of those
terrific period-specific send-offs.
Fine.
Enjoy the jolly old London,
you blokes!
That was, that was bad.
And, frankly, offensive.
Oh, it warms my cockles to know
that Londoners haven't changed a bit.
Let's find this bloody Loom piece,
shall we?
Well, I've disguised
the pieces as rings.
And this one,
I gave to a close mate of mine.
And if I know him, he'll be here.
Wasn't a day
he didn't stop by for a pint.
Why stop at one pint?
Well, found our guy.
Will the Quill.
You didn't tell me you were friends
with the real William Shakespeare.
I didn't wanna name-drop.
Pardon the intrusion, squire.
We have the knowledge
that you came into possession
of a particular ring
some several days past.
I know not of what you speak,
good constables.
And why should anyone hand me a ring?
Do I appear as a jeweler
to thine eyes?
It's a pity!
Because that ring
was stolen from the...
- Duke...
- And, and he wants it back!
And if it were to be discovered
that someone had lied
about its whereabouts...
let's just say, heads would roll.
Yes! Yes, the ring.
The ring, now, I remember it well.
Would that I could yield it for you,
but I just sold that very ring
of which you speak.
What? You sold it already,
you lousy git?
It was by necessity.
See, a stubborn case
of writer's block
is preventing me from finding
the ending to my new play,
Romeo and Juliet.
Sounds like an instant classic.
My producer, Philip Henslowe,
has threatened to remove me of hands
by way of sword if I can't finish.
Thus, I gave him the ring
in exchange for more time.
If I can't bring my story to a close,
my career is over.
So much for quick and easy.
Discussing Romeo and Juliet
in Elizabethan England.
Ava, you needed me?
Sorry, is this an intervention?
No, no, no, no, no.
So, since you're a member
of the team,
we wanted to invite you to book club!
That is very sweet, but I actually
have a lot on my plate right now,
so I don't really have time
to talk about books.
The thing about book club is,
we don't really talk about books.
Because book club is magic.
What she means is,
book club is a place
where you can hang out with your
friends and talk about your problems.
- And eat tiny crackers!
- And drink.
Well, according to the ironmonger
at the bar, for 20 shillings,
I can get a bottle
of wine and a strumpet.
Also, Henslowe and his goons
just arrived,
and they're right over there.
Yeah, I can see the ring on his hand.
I doubt he's gonna give it up
so easily.
That's simple.
You distract the goons,
and I'll punch the producer
in the face.
Anyone got 20 shillings?
This mission has to be epic. Okay?
By which I mean, extremely well
and elaborately coordinated.
Ray's right.
And I have the perfect plan.
We have the element
of surprise on our side,
so I say, aerial attack.
I'll rappel down
while he's totally distracted.
Love it.
And then I'll rappel next to Nate.
And then we'll high-five mid-air,
and it will be epic.
And then...
Wait. Ray, are you crying?
It's just that I love this plan.
No. Yeah, man, I get it.
I'm a little choked up.
It's a great plan.
And then we'll land behind
Henslowe to his total surprise.
You'll subdue him,
and I'll grab the ring.
Got it.
Then Behrad will air-blast Henslowe's
thugs with a killer gust of wind.
Dude, I don't dance like that.
And then Constantine will emerge
from the shadows, per uje.
Spout some nonsense and cast a spell
on any troublemakers
to make them think
that they're animals.
And then we go to Star City.
- We pick up Wild Dog and we...
- Oi.
Story time's over. I got it.
How the hell did you do that?
What, I just nicked it off his hand
while you lot were prattling on.
Does that mean the mission is over?
Which is why we should get moving,
find that next Loom piece, yeah?
And it's time for you to go, Haircut.
Ray, where are you going?
On, on my honeymoon.
Nora and I are going
to Bermuda, Bahamas.
Shut up!
You're doing
the whole "Kokomo" package?
Bro, you're gonna be gone for weeks.
I didn't even throw you
a proper bachelor party.
The mission isn't officially over
until we bring the ring back
to the ship, right?
Which is where
we should be going right now.
- Come on, let's go.
- Ray! You're not going anywhere.
Grab your doublet and your ruff,
because this bachelor party is gonna
be an Elizabethan extravaganza!
You know, the other thing
about book club is,
it can help you figure out what your
true path is supposed to be.
Oh, so this is a cult.
No, no, no.
We don't, we don't use certain
"C" words. "Cult," "clone."
I would know
because book club helped me
move forward after my time
in a real cult.
Look, I get your reservations.
The last "club" I joined programmed
me to be an assassin.
But book club,
it's helping me be a real person.
And I'd killed a federal agent.
I meant to lead with, I'm a Kaupe.
It's like a Hawaiian Werewolf.
Book club helped me cope with that.
That's also a lot to... okay.
So what do you think, Zari?
Can book club help you?
You know what? Enough about me.
This is Nora's last book club.
Shouldn't we be throwing her
a belated bachelorette bash?
- Yes!
- That's what I'm saying, right?
Captain, I have
an incoming transmission.
- The boys.
- Let's get a fireman.
What?
Hey, Sara. Sorry that the mission
is taking so long.
It's just that a dog took the ring,
and it turned out to be the...
You know, the Queen's dog.
But we got it covered. We're good.
Well, great then.
Keep us posted, and be safe.
Copy that.
Fill them up! She bought it.
All right, the boys
are gonna be a while.
So pop that champagne
and fill her up!
I noticed John Constantine
is walking topside.
Plans changed.
I needed leverage.
John is working for me now.
He promised me something.
What exactly is John Constantine
doing for you, Astra?
He said something
about some powerful artifact.
Whatever it is,
that can bring my mom back.
I'd have a family again.
So...
John makes this grand promise
to bring your family back,
and you quickly forget
that I'm the one who found you
roaming the streets as a child.
I'm the one who pulled you
from the gutter.
- I raised you...
- No! No, I haven't forgotten.
Then did it occur to you,
if John brings your mother back,
I will no longer be in your life.
You know I don't want that.
You are my family.
If there's a way to discover
what he's after,
maybe you could get it for yourself.
I know a way we can find out.
This is an exspiravit ritual.
It will allow you to see
the other side.
You'll be among those on Earth,
able to spy on John like a ghost.
You sure you're ready?
Fill it up.
Go on, Ray.
Say a few words.
- Speech! Speech!
I just wanna say thank you
for this bachelor party.
You're the best friend a guy
could have.
No, no.
- Because you are!
- You are!
Is there anything else
you'd like to say, Ray?
Anyone have any big life changes
that they wanna reveal?
I got a kid.
You what?
I've been trying to ignore her,
but I...
can't stop thinking about her.
It's a good thing, Mick.
It's called love.
Let's keep this share-fest going.
All right, who's next?
Hey, we're a regular old,
Fellowship of the Ring.
Here's to getting to the first piece
of the Loom of Destiny...
Yeah, the Spear of Fate.
Do you remember the totems?
The totems.
- I met Elvis.
- I mean, it's the "Loom of Fate."
Once we piece it all together,
we rewrite Astra's life
and I'm telling you,
all this is gonna be worth it.
Who's there?
Charge thee, speak!
Oi!
Watch it, you pigeon-livered worm!
Piss off.
You want some?
Hey! Leave him alone.
What the devil?
Yes, B! That was it!
Speak to me!
What plane of hell did you surface?
Well, whoever you are,
I'm afraid I must do my duty
and send you back.
Fuge.
Astra!
Astra?
Astra.
Oh, no.
Yeah, buddy.
Time for the Atometh
to saveth the dayeth.
Deactivate suit.
Deactivate suit!
Sorry.
Watch out!
Code X-94.
X-94!
Dr. Palmer voice authenticated.
Party's over.
Yeah, Jock-o's right about that one.
Zounds!
Yeah, we'd better mind-wipe
that dude.
I got it.
Wait, no!
It's pointing the wrong way.
I got it.
Well, another Legends' mission
perfect.
Let's head back to the ship.
Sorry.
Hey!
Turn off the music!
Look at this.
Take a look at that. What is that?
Did something go wrong
with the mission?
- Is that Mick?
- What's "Romeo v. Juliet"?
Shakespeare is writing
superhero plays?
Oh, that's gonna be a problem.
I cannot believe you guys!
I put you in charge of the mission,
and you lied to me.
You, you lied to me!
So, why? So why, you could just...
You could go party?
That's what we should have done.
We should have waited
for Ray and Nora to come back
from their honeymoon
and throw one big party.
- My bad, buddy.
- Yeah, and guess what?
We're well on our way
to assembling the Loom.
But you're right, Sara.
I really should have insisted
that we come back to the ship sooner.
- Yeah.
- "Tybalt draws his sword
on Mercutio,
but Mercutio turns to steel!"
- What?
- Well, thanks to you guys
and your stupid party,
this mission is not over.
"With another swing,
Tybalt stabs Mercutio."
I am hurt.
Why didn't he just steel up again?
Stupid Mercutio.
This is the least of our worries.
We need to get out there
and fix hissory.
- What's that?
- Histrory. History.
Time! We gotta fix time.
- What?
- Are you sloshed?
Follow-up question.
Why is there glitter on your face?
Looks like your tachyon scrubber
needs to be replaced.
Whatever that means.
Could someone just see this
fine gentleman out?
- Thank you.
- With pleasure.
Let's go, sexy firefighter.
Go on, get!
Ray, can I talk to you, please?
Yeah.
All right, Ray. What's up?
Why haven't you told Nate
that you're leaving?
Because he's my best friend.
And the moment I tell him,
then this all becomes real.
And I know it's my choice,
my decision.
But I don't, I don't know
if I'm really ready for it.
You remember
when we first moved on the ship?
We left our entire lives behind us.
We had no idea what to expect.
But because we embraced the change...
We made history.
Sure did.
Who would have thought
that we would still be here...
and that we'd be saying
goodbye already?
I'm gonna miss you, Captain Lance.
Don't make me cry.
I'm gonna miss you too, Ray.
A lot.
Come here.
Let's hope the actors
aren't off-book yet.
You have to talk Shakespeare
out of his superhero play.
And make sure you get those scripts.
Back, foul villain! Whoosh!
Take to the skies, brethren!
For tonight, there will be justice.
Behold! What worthy hero faces me?
My face is silver.
Fists like thunder strikes.
We must collect the gems
to save the world,
while learning how to work more
as a team.
- Yes.
- Come hither.
We have much to discuss.
Wow. And it's still
in iambic pentameter.
Okay, you guys take care of the cast
and get the scripts.
- I'll talk to Shakespeare.
- Copy.
Take to the skies, brethren.
I can't believe
we have to destroy these.
This show has potential.
Hear ye! Hear ye!
So there's been a change of plans.
You guys have been replaced
by Riverdale.
- William Shakespeare?
- Bother me not.
I'm making amendments to my script.
I must elucidate more clearly
what the Steel Man's takeaway lesson
is from the story.
Oh, well, I'm actually here to speak
to you about your new play.
I know you.
You're one of the constables
that asked for the ring,
and who caused such a glorious row
with Henslowe and his men.
Yes, and now I'm here to say
that you cannot put on the show.
But I finally struck inspiration.
Look, I have a plan.
Romeo and Juliet will form a team,
and I will henceforth
introduce the allies,
Hamlet, Viola, and Puck,
who will join forces
to face Richard III.
Now I understand why you've written
this new version of the play.
You don't want
Romeo and Juliet's story to end.
Exactly.
I love the characters,
so why say goodbye?
But if you truly love the characters,
don't they deserve a great ending?
I've always known
how to finish their story.
If I let them go,
I'm unsure what happens next.
I understand, but...
endings are necessary for growth.
No matter how painful they may be.
You speak quite wisely.
I'm speaking from experience.
I find myself in a similar situation.
When I'm done here, I am leaving
my team for a new adventure,
and ending our journey
has proven more heartbreaking...
than I can bear.
And while I can't imagine
saying goodbye,
I know that I must.
Very well.
I shall do what is needed
for my beloved characters,
give Romeo and Juliet an ending
no one will forget.
All righty.
If we did our job right,
this cover should change back
to Romeo and Juliet any second.
I know you're leaving, Ray.
Yeah, to my honeymoon.
Would you just knock it off?
I know you're leaving the team.
Nate, I'm, I'm sorry.
I was gonna tell you sooner.
I swear, but I just,
I didn't know how to do it.
Maybe if you had the balls
to say it sooner,
maybe I could have done something
like make us a last-mission playlist
or get us matching T-shirts.
That would have been amazing.
But I was waiting
for some perfect moment,
which doesn't exist,
because I didn't want to upset you.
Of course, I'm upset!
Today could have been awesome.
It could have been amazing,
but now it's just...
It's just over.
Eventually, everything has to change.
Yeah, I know everything
changes eventually.
I didn't think it'd be so soon,
and I didn't think
I'd be the last one to know.
Attention, Legends.
There is no record of the play
Romeo and Juliet
in the timeline, which means...
Shakespeare didn't put
on the play yet.
The final mission isn't completed.
We can still go back
and fix history together.
The team has it, Ray.
You should go. You're right.
Things change eventually,
so why not start now?
Nate.
Nate!
Willy Shakes, what's happening?
Spare me your whimsical turns
of phrase.
Barkeep, my draught has gone hollow.
I'll have another.
Will, what happened to the play?
Henslowe withdrew the moneys
and shut us down.
In his mind's eye, he thinks
I stole back his ring.
Now, I have no theater,
no actors, and so no career.
Tell us where Henslowe is.
We'll help you.
Just leave me be.
I've seen your help in action,
and it is anything but.
So you're just gonna give up?
It's like the tall one said.
All things must cease.
And this is the end
of William Shakespeare.
- He is so dramatic.
- Yeah.
- Packed already?
Figured why wait.
Well, there's no rush,
you know, we can stick around
until they get back.
I think we've stuck around
too long already.
What is going on?
Well, we ruined
the Western literary canon,
and Shakespeare hates us,
so here's to Legends of Tomorrow,
who single-handedly destroyed
storytelling as we know it.
Sorry, so that's it?
First, you pick a fight with Ray,
and now you admit defeat!
Are you just trying to prove
that everything is as miserable
as how you feel?
I don't wanna talk about Ray.
Look, Nate, I get it.
I'm afraid of losing Ray, too.
Honestly, I don't know
what we're gonna do
without his stupid optimism
and blind faith
and ridiculous plans
that somehow always work.
I know what we need to do.
Gideon, tell the team it's all hands
on deck here at the tavern,
and fabricate some codpieces.
The show must go on.
All right, it's almost showtime.
Remember, Gideon is going to be
feeding you your lines.
Yeah, no pressure.
It's not like we're rebooting
Shakespeare's career or anything.
It really is book club's
greatest mission yet.
I can't believe I let you guys
rope me into this one.
Look, if you want to find the Loom,
you gotta do things our way.
You think this is gonna work,
Captain?
Honestly, no.
But Ray would.
"My bounty is as boundless
as the sea."
- That's crap.
- Just say the words,
because you are on!
Listen up, you uncultured jerks.
Two households, both alike
in dignity, in fair Verona,
- where we lay our scene.
- What?
From ancient grudge breaks
to new mutiny.
- What?
- Where civil blood...
What? What? Stop.
Those are my words!
a pair of starstruck lovers
take their life.
Just enjoy the show, all right?
Whose misadventured piteous
overthrows...
- Looks like the audience is.
- done to their death.
Clubs, bills, and partisans.
Strike!
Beat them down.
Down with the Capulets.
Down with the Montagues!
What noise is this?
Give me my long sword, ho!
A sword? A crutch!
Why call you for a sword?
My sword, I say!
Old Montague has come,
and flourishes his blade
in spite of me.
Thou villain Capulet.
Hold me not! Let me go.
Thou shalt not stir one foot
to seek a foe.
Fight.
Exciting.
What shall I swear by?
If my heart's dear love...
Do not swear.
Although I take joy in thee,
I take no joy
in this contract tonight.
It is too rash,
too unadvised, too sudden.
Too rash, too unadvised, too sudden.
Too like the lightning,
which doth cease to be.
One can say, it lightens.
Sweet, good night.
Wilt thou leave me so unsatisfied?
What's wrong?
I mean, other than the fact this role
clearly should have gone to a woman.
I just need a second, okay?
Acting is hard.
I know it can be hard to face
that your time with someone
is coming to an end.
Sometimes, it's easier to just
send them away before it hits you.
Like Juliet's doing here.
She got all that?
She was meant for book club.
Change is hard,
but it can also be beautiful.
It can be both.
You know, it's not too late
to say goodbye to your friend.
- What about Juliet?
- I have it handled.
Among my many talents,
I'm a classically trained actor.
Gidget, I'm off-book.
This bud of love,
by summer's ripening breath,
may prove a beauteous flower
when next we meet.
Is that a man?
- Good night.
- Does it matter?
Good night.
As sweet repose
and rest come to thy heart
- as that within my breast.
- Excuse me. Excuse me.
Oh, wilt thou leave me
so unsatisfied?
All right, Gideon.
It's time for me to go.
Will I ever see you again?
I hope so.
Thank you for everything.
And take care of the Legends for me.
Safe travels, Dr. Palmer.
Ray, are you there?
Can you hear me?
Ray.
You again.
Get over here.
Help.
Ray!
What satisfaction canst thou
have tonight?
The exchange of thy love's
faithful vows for mine.
I gave thee mine
before thou didst request it,
and yet I would it
were to give again.
Wouldst thou withdraw it?
For what purpose, love?
But to be frank,
and give it thee again.
And yet I wish
but for the thing I have...
my bounty is as boundless as the sea.
My love as deep.
The more I give to thee,
the more I have,
for both are infinite.
I hear some noise within.
Dear love, adieu.
Ray! Ray! Ray!
I missed him.
He's gone.
Nate. Nate!
I'm still here, buddy.
Romeo. Romeo.
Ray, I am so sorry
I lashed out at you.
It was just a lot to process,
and I didn't know how to say it.
The thing is, I'm just really sad...
but I'm really happy for you guys.
I'm sorry that you found out
the way you did...
and that just, I wish
there was some way that everything
and nothing could change all at once.
This sucks.
But I love you.
This totally sucks.
But I love you, too.
Good night.
Parting is such sweet sorrow
that I shall say good night
till it be morrow.
Zari was pretty good at Juliet.
I mean, not as good as you, but...
You okay?
It's a weird thing with friendship.
It starts
because you need each other.
And then, if you do it right
and help each other grow,
you need each other less.
I guess change is the whole point.
Well, if you,
you ever need a bro hug...
I'm your gal.
Bring it in.
Sorry.
It's okay. Ray was terrible
at bro hugs at first too.
- Yeah.
- But you're really terrible.
You're such a dick.
Why are you so strong?
On a Shakespeare kick?
Didn't care much
for those Italian kids,
but this guy...
This guy is a hero.
You know King Lear is a tragic figure
whose stubbornness
and fear of the future
leads to his own misery?
Sounds like someone I can get behind.
You should talk to your daughter.
There's no secrets in book club.
I'm not hiding from her.
- I'm protecting her.
- From what?
Nurturing fathers
don't run in my family.
But I'm better off
because I had you in my life.
She will be, too.
It's good to see you.
Consent to hug you?
Gonna take that as a yes.
So this is part of the Loom of Fate?
Well, I had to disguise the bit
so that mere mortals like you
wouldn't burst into flames
when you looked at it.
Well, that is certainly
very thoughtful of you, Charlie.
Not so fast.
This is too powerful, John.
And, honestly,
you're too close to it.
You know, this is my mission, Sara.
And this is my ship.
- So what's the plan?
- This is just the beginning.
But with that,
we can find the other pieces.
I was so worried.
I wasn't sure when you'd wake up.
What did you see?
I, I was in a bar and people were...
laughing and...
And John was there with his friends.
Did he say what he was looking for?
He's looking for the Loom of Fate.
The Loom?
- So you've heard of it?
- Of course.
The Loom of Fate is one of the most
powerful tools in existence.
It could completely
rewrite your life.
Are you sure you want to trust
that power in someone else's hands?
Especially John Constantine's?
- Can't sleep either, huh?
- Yeah.
You know,
we all spend time off the ship,
but people usually don't feel this...
- Gone.
- gone.
How early does a guy have to get up
to get some alone time?
Ray's green juice.
You feeling sentimental too, huh,
Mick?
The juice was taking up
all the room in the fridge.
Now shut up, pretty.
Missing someone after they're gone
almost makes them more present.
Heard you get up, babe.
- I was awake anyway.
- Hi, babe.
I had a feeling other people
would be up.
Oh, gross! Is that Ray's green juice?
- Yep.
- Give me some.
To Ray...
who taught me
how to be a better friend
by being a better friend
than I deserved.
Who told me that if you're dumb
enough to expect good from the world,
well, it might just live up
to your expectations.
And who showed us
that there's never a problem so big
it can't be solved with a smile.
To the big guy.
- To Ray.
To Ray.
I'm really gonna miss him.
Tastes like death.
It's delicious.
You think Ray left
that bathroom sign-up sheet?
No, no, no!