Previously on
Legends Of Tomorrow...
That's my dad.
This must be one
of his secret government projects
he could never tell me about.
You know, my whole life,
I always believed my power was evil.
Nora Darhk, hands up.
It's time for me to pay
for my past.
I just...
I believe she can be a better person.
- Amaya.
- Itjust looks like her.
She's a shapeshifter.
She's still adjusting
to her new home.
I'm gonna green light
additional funding
to fast track the completion
of your containment facility.
Is that a Kaupe?
I can't believe you guys
have magical creatures here,
this is like the coolest place ever.
Hey, Ava, hope I'm not too early.
It's Director Sharpe.
You're not early, Mona, you're late.
Oh, no. Are you firing me?
Why does this always happen?
I'm not firing you, Mona.
Awesome, because I cannot wait
to decorate my cubicle.
There's Rose from Golden Girls.
She's like the OG of girl power.
Am I right?
No. Take that off
and anything else that's metal.
Leave the toys with these guys.
You do not want to bring anything
into the containment unit
that can be used
as a weapon against you.
But Rose couldn't hurt a fly.
Your job is to feed
our various magical detainees.
Keeping these creatures secure
is the Bureau's newest
and highest priority.
Aloha, Kaupe. Good to see you.
Each cell is encoded
with the captive's genetic signature.
Allowing you to pass them provisions...
all while keeping you safe
from the monsters.
Well, this place
definitely needs decorating.
Now for the Kaupe we're gonna need
a palm tree, some volcanic rock...
This is a prison, Mona, not a home.
Let's go.
And they are our prisoners,
not our friends.
Which is especially true of our most
recent acquisition.
Nora Darhk.
Of all the creatures here,
she's the most despicable.
Hi, I'm Mona.
I'm your magical caretaker.
So if you have
any dietary restrictions
or special requests,
be sure to let me know.
Um...
You should have this.
It just came out.
It's called Uncaged Desire.
Actually, there is something
you can get me, Mona.
Anything, just... You name it.
Some peace...
and quiet. Hmm?
I think you just learned
a very valuable lesson, Mona.
Don't fraternize with the prisoners.
I told you, no interrupt...
Well, you're not Gary.
Perceptive.
And those are not work shoes.
What are you doing here?
Don't play coy with me.
Happy birthday, Director Sharpe.
Oh, sweet God. Um...
Wow.
You know that I don't normally like
to celebrate my birthday, but...
Well, I am here to fix that,
so close your eyes.
What?
- I said close your eyes.
- Okay. Okay.
Now...
Are you ready
for your birthday present?
Yes.
Are we really doing this?
- Oh!
- Director Sharpe, we need to talk.
Of course, sir, I...
I was just, uh, meditating.
There's this great app that...
Meditate on this.
- Oh, my God!
- Exactly.
These are expenses generated
by the crew of the Waverider.
- The tip of the Time Bureau spear.
- Mmm-hmm.
Your Legends.
You said they were worth
the additional funding.
Let me refer you
to some of my favorite line items.
One hundred and thirty-five million
dollars for a new time core.
What was wrong with the old one?
Oh, well, uh, Rip blew it up
when he sacrificed his life
to save the world.
Sacrifice is right. One point seven
million for historical costumes.
Mmm-hmm. Well, admittedly,
their costumes are flamboyant.
A line item for, and I quote,
"assorted condiments." Assorted?
No one ever accused
the Legends of starving, sir.
If I didn't know any better, I'd say
you were in bed with the Legends.
Either that
or this Captain Sara Lance
is simply screwing you.
Screwing me... Sara Lance?
What are you...
Sir, that is, that is crazy.
Which is exactly what the Pentagon
is going to call me
unless we find a way
to justify these numbers.
Got it, sir.
I know that your team
is worth the money, but I...
I will talk to the team,
see if we can tighten our belts.
Thank you.
I increase their budget
so they can build
magical containment cells
to start capturing these creatures.
Meanwhile, they're running a
nine-figure deficit on a Timeship.
Take a deep breath, Hank.
Hey, if you knew what the Legends did
you'd realize they're, they're
worth every single penny.
Now, how about this?
I'll set up a ride along,
you can meet the gang
and see where I used to live.
I can see where my money is going.
- Sure.
- You're right.
Why don't we go now?
Now?
You know, um, we should
probably give them a chance,
you know, to clean up.
We can't warn them we're coming.
That would defeat the purpose.
Okay. Um, I mean,
I've got to hail the Waverider,
and that's gonna take forever.
Nathaniel, as your boss,
I demand you take me
to the Waverider.
Gonna play the boss card again.
Okay, Dad, sorry, Captain Heywood.
Let's go see what
the Legends are up to.
I can deal with Hank.
And we still have plenty of time to
get things on the ship back in order.
What are they...
- I should probably...
- Go, go, go.
Delivery for...
Damn it!
Sorry!
Wait, don't forget your, uh...
Birthday cake.
Red alert. Nate is on the ship.
And he brought his dad for what's
gotta be a surprise inspection.
We are so not ready
for guests.
Nate's here? I could really use a hug
and get his advice on Nora.
Did you forget
who else is on the ship?
Charlie! You can't let him see her
until we have time to explain
why there's
an Amaya lookalike on board.
Right.
Last time I saw her
she was in the lab.
Everyone keep Nate
away from the lab. I'm on my way.
Any tour of the ship
should start here.
This is where Legends
have team meetings
and hold lively symposiums
of ideas and solutions,
all led by Captain Sara Lance.
And where is this Captain Lance?
Um...
Um, it is a little quiet,
but I assure you Captain Lance is
securing the Legends'
next daring mission.
Next stop,
the parlour,
which we spell with a "U"
because our first captain
was British.
So, why does this ship...
formerly manned by a single person,
now need...
Need a crew of six?
- I can explain. Uh...
- Hey, Ray.
He means five. You mean five.
I mean five. I mean five.
I must have been thinking about
Gideon as a real person.
Are you trying to hurt
my feelings, Dr. Palmer?
Oh, wow, Gideon, hubba hubba.
Love the new look.
Ms. Tomaz gave me,
in her words, a face lift.
This is a talking computer?
Actually, I'm a quantum-enhanced
AI program
capable of operating
completely autonomously...
So, what you're saying is,
you don't need any people
on the ship?
Oh, no, no, no. We do.
Ray, why don't you show Hank
what you do in the...
Not the lab.
Hello, sir.
Uh, you should take him to the library,
it's very impressive
and there are books...
- And bookshelves.
- Bookshelves.
See, Hank, it takes a village.
Follow me.
God.
It was good. It was a good save.
Now, the library is my domain.
I have assembled
quite a collection of...
Nate. It's good to see you,
mate.
You haven't seen the laboratory yet,
have you?
No, why?
Because you should always
save the best for last.
Yeah, you should really put some
clothes on when we have guests.
So, this is your domain?
Why don't we move on. Huh?
Mr. Heywood, welcome aboard.
I see you've already had
the complete tour.
He hasn't seen the lab yet.
That's a great idea.
Wait till you see this.
Hey, so maybe your dad would like
to see the galley.
Or the cargo bay with the crates.
Or the bathroom
is a marvel of efficiency.
Look, you guys need
to pull it together.
Okay, look, I know my dad
sprung this on us,
but we have dealt
with crazier things than...
Amaya?
So this is the ex-girlfriend
you can't shut up about?
Look, I'm sorry,
I should have told you...
She came back.
I knew she'd come back.
You don't understand. It's not...
You look beautiful.
Get your stinking mitts
off of me, you knob!
We should just...
- We're gonna...
- Yeah, just go. Go.
You've changed.
What the hell is going on?
And what's with that accent?
I mean, I dig it, but...
What's going on?
Well, I'm not
your disco-loving ex, mate.
Meet the newest member
of our team.
Charlie.
Charlie here is a shapeshifter.
Except she can no longer shapeshift.
It's actually a pretty crazy...
Let me guess.
She turned into Amaya
and conned you into
not sending her to hell
and Constantine put a spell on her
and now she's stuck like this?
- That is weirdly accurate, yeah.
- Yeah.
I guess it's not such a crazy story.
It's insane, Ray!
I told my dad you guys
were good at your jobs.
And now you're adopting
some magical creature
who's pretending to be Amaya...
Hey, I'm not pretending to be anyone.
That said...
Hank's already looking for ways
to slash our funding,
so maybe it's not the worst idea
to fake it for one mission.
You want me to pretend
to be this wanker's ex?
Sounds like classic
Legends hijinks to me.
We can't let Hank know
that we're harboring a fugitive.
We just need to show him one mission
and send him on his way
before anything can go wrong.
Okay, then maybe
it wasn't the best idea
to leave him with those three.
- We should go.
- Yeah.
All right, team, showtime.
Drinking at work.
Who said anything about work?
Hey, Legends, you hear that?
We got a hit on the magic-ometer.
Oh, where in history are
we gonna end up next?
Where will it be? The wild west?
Medieval China? Or...
Paris in the Roaring Twenties!
- Ooh, la la.
- Gideon, plot a course.
Yes, Captain, right away.
Uh, explain to me how this
magic-ometer of yours works.
- Oh, well...
- Thingy goes beep and we kick ass.
Meaning we investigate
each time period.
- Oh, we find the creature.
- We bring it to the Bureau.
And hopefully learn some
life lessons along the way.
And it takes six of you to do that?
- Seven, if you count Amaya.
- Eight, if you count me.
Sounds a little inefficient.
Which is why we separate
into two very important teams.
Z, John, Ray and Amaya
will stay on the ship to quarterback
while the rest of us go in search of
whatever is wreaking havoc
on gay Paree.
I thought that was, uh,
impolitically correct.
Politically incorrect.
Hey, our first mission together.
Don't worry. Anything goes wrong
in the field, I got you covered.
Yeah, well...
I didn't get cold cocked by a girl.
Have you ever been
hit by a girl, Hank?
No, ma'am.
Mmm. We should head out.
Café du Dôme, 1927.
Home to the Lost Generation.
Writers, artists, expats.
- They all...
- All right, so where is this monster?
Yeah, who needs historical context
and wonderment?
I need a drink.
What he means is we need to blend in
with the locals.
This is a recon mission.
Oh, my God, it's him. Salvador Dalí.
What, the creep with the weird mustache?
Don't point.
That's the father of Surrealism.
Look, this is your plan
to catch this creature?
You ask a bunch of
artsy-fartsy fools...
Oh, my God, it's him.
It's Papa.
Papa? What? Your grandfather's here?
Thought he blew up in space.
You are so insensitive.
Not that Papa.
Ernest Hemingway,
he's like my dad's spirit animal.
I say, if we wanna get things done...
we ask the original man of action.
Your dad is totally geeking out
right now.
Mmm-hmm. My entire life my father would
go on and on about Hemingway
and how that was
his idea of a real man.
And that is when I was attacked
by the monstrous man
of the Catacombs.
Well, it's time to talk to
some artsy-fartsy fools.
Uh, you said you saw
a monstrous man? Can you explain?
Of course. Um...
There was a logarithmic curve
to his form...
The drama of his movement
expressing deep personal cosmogony.
Can you draw me a picture?
Okay, let's try one more time.
My name is Amaya Jiwe
of the, uh, Justice Society of...
Complete and utter bloody rubbish,
wasn't it?
Yep, it sucks.
Just remember, the Yanks,
they don't say rubbish.
They'd say,
"That was absolute garbage.
"I'm American. Soccer. Yardsticks.
"Ranch dressing. Weasel."
You know what? I quit. Yeah.
I'd rather get some fresh air
than pretend to be this twee old nag.
You can't quit. She can't quit.
Sara needs us to quarterback
the mission.
You don't really think
that's why she left us here, do you?
Uh, she just doesn't want us making
a scene in front of Nate's dad.
Efficiency is the new watchword,
gents.
And while Hank is around,
the three of us...
Four, if you count Charlie.
Five, if you count me.
Are extraneous.
You know, mate, you could just
walk straight off this ship and
no one would even bleeding notice.
Well,
maybe I'll test that theory.
Except I'm not walking.
I'm taking the Jumpship.
The answer is no, Ray.
What? You haven't heard my pitch yet.
You want access to a
secret containment facility
for magical creatures where,
I might add,
there are no conjugal visits.
Wait, what?
You think that I wanna visit Nora
so that we can... We...
I just wanna make sure
that she's okay.
Oh, that is so sweet.
I almost believe that story,
you big, lovable teddy bear, you.
But the answer is still no.
With Nate's dad watching
our each and every move,
there is just no time
for love at the Time Bureau.
There's always time for love.
- Were you eavesdropping?
- Maybe.
Or maybe I was meant
to hear your plight.
Uh, I'm sorry. Who are you again?
Name's Mona, and I know
where they've got Nora locked up.
- You do?
- Mmm-hmm.
And while I can't sneak you in,
I can help you sneak in
the next best thing...
a love letter.
The bull is not the enemy
of the bullfighter.
He is his partner. They are dancers
locked in a dance of death.
Whichever dies, man or bull,
the dance is a thing of beauty.
Hey, we gotta go.
I got a lead on that, uh, thing
we're hunting.
- You're hunters?
- Stay out of this, Hemingway.
Perhaps you'd like to settle
our differences like men.
Oh, I don't have time
for this macho crap, man.
Okay, you two with me.
Rory, keep him busy.
Fine specimen of male vitality.
Fellow pugilist, no doubt.
Author.
Ha! My kind of man. Join me.
Okay, Dalí saw the monster firsthand
when it attacked him
in the Catacombs,
and he drew me this.
- What the hell am I looking at?
- No, no, here.
Yeah, I still don't see it.
All right, ignore the melting clocks.
We got to get this back to the ship
and I have to find a match
to Dalí's drawing
somewhere in the library.
We're supposed to protect history
from the library, Nathaniel?
Okay, I see that
you're really into drinking
the Hemingway Kool-Aid,
and by Kool-Aid I mean scotch,
but we are here to catch a monster.
Of course, but I know we sure as hell
aren't gonna find out what it is
by studying some finger paintings.
We gotta go back to the ship
to figure out what we're doing.
- That's the way we do things, right?
- Yes.
When the mission isn't also
showing Hank a good time.
I'm sorry, but...
You know, I thought this would
be good for the both of us, but...
Hank is at his happiest
when he's telling me
- what I'm doing wrong, so...
- mission accomplished.
Aw, cheer up, bud. You are right,
so Rory and I,
we will keep an eye on Hank,
let him have a few laughs
with Hemingway
while you go figure out
what this thing is.
We bag the creature,
we keep our jobs.
Whoa, where are you all going?
Henry here told me of a creature
hiding in the Catacombs.
Oh, did you, Henry?
- Therefore, we hunt.
- Let's go get our monster.
Nate's right. We have no idea
what this thing is.
A man hunts not to learn
about his prey,
but to learn about himself.
We need to regroup with the team
and get some backup.
What better backup than Hemingway?
I'm finally starting to understand
what it is the Legends do.
Marcel, fetch me my rifles.
Right away, sir.
I need a Marcel.
Yeah, just a little drunk hunting
with Hemingway.
What could go wrong?
Have you ever held a gun before?
Once or twice.
Your friend is much woman.
Have my own.
Signature weapon, I like it.
The drunk painter was right.
The creature is hiding
in the Catacombs.
And it's getting closer.
We need a plan.
We have no idea what this thing is
and if it can even be stopped
with bullets.
I've found that in life the
shortest answer... is doing the thing.
Let's do this thing.
I knew you couldn't resist.
Did you get to the end
where the correctional officer
convinces the judge
to send her to prison,
so he can go free?
Uh, well, I have now.
Sorry, didn't mean to ruin it.
But I brought you an
even a better one.
What the hell is this?
It's a letter from your crush.
Ray left it behind for you.
Don't you see?
Yours is a love no bars can contain.
No, I... I don't want it.
But don't you wanna
at least open it?
Uh, no.
But what if you change your mind,
or your heart?
I'm not gonna change my...
Take the damn letter.
- Look what you made me do!
- Uh-oh.
I'm sorry.
Uh, I swear it's one of these buttons.
What the hell?
Are you okay?
Did she attack you?
It's fine, just...
just a misunderstanding.
What the hell is this?
Where'd you get this?
Did Mona deliver this to you?
Okay, since neither of you
have anything to say,
I'll let the letter speak for itself.
No!
Requesting emergency assistance.
I didn't... I didn't mean to...
We're stuck.
Well, at least
we're all here together, right?
Now I know why
you took my shoelaces.
Lost?
- No, I'm good.
- Uh...
'Cause you're heading
in the wrong direction.
- The Waverider's over there.
- I don't need directions from you.
Listen, sunshine.
I don't know what beef
you had with your ex,
but don't bring it on me.
Zelda, dear, I do believe they're
giving us a run for our money.
You're the Fitzgeralds.
And we pride ourselves the most
quarrelsome couple in Paris.
Don't worry, we're not a couple.
Well, the night is still young.
You should join us for a drink.
Besides, no one should be out
on the streets alone tonight.
There is a monster on the loose.
You heard about the monster?
Come with me.
What conversation isn't better
had over a gin rickey?
You hear that?
Dalí's the only one
who's seen the beast.
Take it for what it's worth.
Well, I spoke with him myself.
And according to Dalí,
this is what it looks like.
I can never make heads
or tails of Salvador's work.
That's a minotaur.
A beast, half man, half bull,
spent its whole life lost in a maze?
Oh, now, that's the common myth.
But I heard a different story.
The Minotaur, he's not lost.
He's hiding.
Rejected by his father,
he felt that he had
no place in the real world,
and so he chose to stay in the maze.
If Dalí thinks he's
seen one of these,
I want what he's drinking.
Where are you going?
I am going to figure out a
way to catch a minotaur
and show my father what
a real man of action looks like.
There it is, awaiting the fight.
I got this. Mine's longer.
Fall back!
Wait! I got the shot.
We have to go, now!
I'll never surrender.
But I will strategically retreat.
Get back!
Gideon, Hank's hurt.
Show him what you can do.
- Right away, Captain.
- Dad?
Are you okay?
Please don't blame the Legends,
I should have been there.
Because then you would have
seen me lock eyes with the beast.
And it was in that moment
that I felt a deep
and mutual respect.
- Well, someone's been bonding with Papa.
- Yeah.
Respect that gave way to resolve,
as the beast drew its blade.
The dance had begun.
- Okay. Gideon?
- Initiating scan.
So, CliffNotes.
Big axe, bigger monster.
Knows we're on it.
We need a plan B, quick.
Okay.
Dad, you heal up, we've got this.
No, like hell!
I owe it to him to finish this fight.
Sedative administered.
And you thought a minotaur
was bull-headed?
Ooh, mythology burn.
It's good to have you back.
There has to be a way outta here.
Well, it's a prison cell.
Or an incubator for our
burgeoning friendship.
Isn't breaking out of prison
your thing?
Only reason I escaped last time was
because Ray gave me a time stone.
Tell me everything, because I am
big time shipping you two.
No shipping the inmates.
That's the reason we're
stuck in here in the first place.
I know that getting your
boss locked in a prison
isn't the best way to start a job.
So, if it comes to it,
I'd like you to eat me first.
No one's eating anyone, Mona.
But, when we get out of here,
we do have to talk about your
continued employment at the Bureau.
Wait, no, no, no. You can't fire me.
Give me one good reason why.
Okay, okay.
I was gonna save
this for upstairs but...
Surprise!
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to...
This isn't making things better,
is it?
No, it's fantastic, keep going.
So that's it.
I finally find a job
where I can use my skills...
Debatable.
And I blow it in the first week.
Guess I'm stuck
doing my fallback plan.
Going back to law school.
At least Yale wants me.
Wait! Wait!
That's the "fallback plan"?
Law school?
What are you,
what are you even doing here?
This is my dream job.
It's my mom
who wants me to be a lawyer.
No, you can't give in
to what your parents want.
That's what I did
and look how that ended.
Okay, you're not going to
take life advice from Nora Darhk, right?
That's rich.
You should listen to your parents,
think about your future.
Oh, easy for you to say.
At least you had a future.
When I was a kid, my dad
convinced me to be a demon vessel.
You think it was easy for me?
At least you got to be a kid.
Try being a clone from 2213.
Okay, the only taste
of childhood I ever had
was almost being killed by
a Shtriga at summer camp.
Wow. Okay, I need to hear your entire
life stories right now.
- No!
We might as well get to know
each other if we're stuck here.
Or...
At least have a drink?
What?
We need to bag ourselves a minotaur
before your dad gets himself killed.
Oh, what is that smell?
Did you guys get
a team dog without me?
Because that was my idea.
I bet you guys are having
post-mission pizza parties now, too.
This is the artificial musk
of a female minotaur.
See, minotaurs have
a very sharp sense of smell
when it comes to tracking prey,
but with this little bad boy
I can lure it in by convincing it
that I'm a potential mate.
Then what? You two
gonna ride off together?
Get a nice little flat in Soho?
It's good, but we still need a way to
tame it and get it to the Bureau.
Taming the beast. Taming the beast.
I read about this, I read about this.
Um, let's see, the
Magical Treatise of Solomon.
Here we go.
"To ease the Minotaur's rage
"his mother would play him
a lullaby on a lute built by..."
- "Daedalus."
- That's it.
We'll lure it out
and lull it to sleep.
No one gets hurt,
not even the minotaur.
And then we'll have a pizza party.
And that's when I found out
I was from the future.
- Oh, the future?
- Yep.
It was all fake.
My parents, my memories.
Growing up in Fresno.
It's still better than
spending your childhood
with the Order of
the Shrouded Compass.
Is that like
The Sisterhood of Traveling Pants?
Even worse, death cult.
And before that, I just
moved around from one
mental institution to the next.
Point is, you're lucky.
I'm lucky?
I just wish my past was made up.
What, so you can
wake up one day and realize
that you don't have
any family, friends,
or life experiences to hold on to?
Doesn't sound that different
from waking up in a prison cell.
Touché.
Are you two kidding me right now?
Ava, you're a clone from the future.
And you run the Time Travel Bureau.
And you're a witch.
And you escaped a cult.
- And a real-life demon.
- I did.
You two are like the two
coolest women I have ever met.
And I once met Gillian Anderson
at an X-Files meet and greet.
Wow. Mona, you are a gem.
You know, we can't have a birthday
without birthday cake.
Yeah.
Back on your feet already, Hank?
Your gal patched me up good,
I'm just running
through our strategy.
Oh, wait, did you let him use our
D&D miniatures?
No, I didn't let him touch Sindra,
Lord of the Dark Elves.
You guys D&D without me too?
Son, why are
you holding a tiny guitar?
Or do I even wanna know?
- Uh, this, this is a lute.
- Someone say, "loot"?
This is what we're gonna use to
put the minotaur to sleep.
- I thought you said that was "loot."
- I don't understand.
Well, I suppose it is more of a lyre.
Everyone's a liar.
This is how we're going
to catch our creature, Dad.
- That's your plan?
- Yeah.
We're facing a literal monster.
You think you
can destroy it with a lute?
Well, in the hands of a master,
a lute is a formidable weapon.
Just look at Sting, mate.
Sorry to interrupt,
but there's a change in the timeline.
An attack at
Café du Dôme is imminent.
There will be no survivors.
The minotaur must be tracking
Hemingway's scent.
Let's move out.
Uh, Nathaniel, get out of my way.
I don't have to do
what you say anymore, Hank.
Really? Because as your superior,
I'm telling you to stand down.
There goes the "superior"
thing again, you know?
You don't wanna listen to me
or understand me, you just...
You just wanna be better than me.
Well, you're one to
talk about listening,
you've ignored every lesson
I've ever tried to teach you.
Because it's the same lesson
over and over again.
You want me to
be more like you, Hank.
But guess what? I'm not like you.
I don't like televised golf
or Tom Clancy books
or '70s folk rock.
I don't know if you happened to
notice but I'm a grown-ass superhero.
Who's just trying to
play the lute for a minotaur.
Fine.
Don't listen to your old man.
Maybe you'll listen to your captain.
I'm sorry, but I'm with Nate.
I know his idea sounds crazy,
but he's right.
And that's what makes him a Legend.
No matter where he is.
Look, you said you wanted
to see a Legends mission.
Well, you're about to.
And if it goes wrong, well...
You go ahead and fire all of us.
The beast advanced.
I turned on him,
gun raised.
Seeing we'd reached an agreement,
I fired!
So I don't think we'll be seeing
that creature anytime soon.
Yeah? Then what is that?
Back for another go, are you?
Oye, fuzzball, come on.
Have a nice little
whiff of this, will ya?
- All right, that's your cue.
- Okay.
I haven't had
much time to rehearse, but...
- Now, we end this.
- No!
I warn you, I will strike a woman.
That's for being on my
summer eighth grade reading list.
Uh, guys?
Nathaniel!
Always preferred Faulkner.
So, not a bad birthday, huh?
Considering my original plan was
a House Hunters marathon?
That actually sounds pretty great.
You know what?
You should have this.
You know you wanna read it.
Look.
I learned from being
locked up that the
only way to survive is to shut down.
If you don't have a future,
it's best not to look forward.
Not to meals, or birthdays...
or relationships.
Just because this is your present,
doesn't mean it
has to be your future.
Who knows, maybe some day you can
get outta here
without having to escape.
Yeah.
And aren't you glad
you didn't shut down today?
Well, this cake is pretty good.
Come on! Come on!
Who doesn't wanna see
a Ray Palmer love letter?
You have to open it,
there's probably glitter in it.
- I wanna know.
- Go on.
- Open it. Open it.
You know what?
- Come on.
- No...
Oh, hi there.
- Ray?
Yeah, hi. Uh, could I get some help?
Uh, I'm a little stuck.
- Get behind the bar.
- Good idea.
I meant for cover.
Well, I like your version.
See? He looks just as I drew it.
You leave that weirdo alone!
Your fight is with me.
Come on.
Now, the dance begins.
I needed to make sure she was okay.
I wanted to make sure you were okay.
Uh, actually, I just really
wanted to see her.
And then I thought I'd
deliver the message myself.
But then I got stuck in the glue.
That was sweet.
Stupid, but sweet.
No, it's unacceptable.
But in this case...
Clearly convenient.
So, since you are so
good at getting people out of prison...
let's get the hell outta here,
shall we?
Oh. Yeah. Yeah.
Let's just hope the team
wasn't missing the QB.
That's my boy!
Over here!
There is a young cowboy
that lives on the range
His horse and his cattle
are his only companions
He works in the saddle
and he sleeps in the canyons
Waiting for summer
His pastures to change
What is happening?
James Taylor, and it's good.
And as the moon rises
he sits by his fire
Thinking about women
and glasses of beer
And closing his eyes
as the dogies retire
He sings out a song
which is soft but it's clear
As if maybe someone could hear
You got this, Dad.
Goodnight, you moonlight ladies
Rockabye, sweet baby James
Deep greens and blues
are the colors I choose
Won't you let me go down in my dreams
And rockabye, sweet baby James
Now, that is how you finish
a Legends mission.
You did good, son.
Well, right back at you, Dad.
I learned it from you, Nathaniel.
Hola, Juni.
Privyet, Baba Yaga.
What's up, Nora?
I thought you were headed to Yale.
After last night, I marched home
and told my parents
I didn't wanna be a lawyer.
And also that I was craving nachos
and wanted to do karaoke.
The rosé had really
kicked in at that point.
Oh, and here, my mom's homemade congee.
Great hangover cure.
Hey, can you do me a favor?
I wrote...
I wrote Ray a letter. Uh...
Uh, yeah, it'd be an honor
to deliver it.
Yeah.
Anything for my
generation's Ross and Rachel.
Uh, morning, Director Sharpe.
A word, Mona.
What?
Wait, are you firing me this time?
No, Mona.
After yesterday, I realized...
There is some room for
a little humanity in this place.
Aloha, Kaupe.
Permission to scratch his tummy?
Permission granted.
And you should deliver that letter.
Well.
That was a chaotic, reckless,
wasteful mess.
I think I finally see
the value in the Legends.
Yeah. You could have
led with that last part.
We're glad to have you on board.
Well, this has been fun.
But it's time for me to get back.
Yeah, you know what? Um...
I'll meet you back there,
Dad.
He's right, this was fun.
It's good to be back.
Well, the door is always open.
You know, coming back here, I thought
it'd be like the old days.
But, I don't know
what's more surprising,
the fact that so much has changed,
or at some point
this became the old days.
You'd think we of all people would
understand that time makes no sense.
- Yeah.
- But...
I guess it's something
you never accept.
You know I love you guys, right?
But, uh...
I belong over there.
I get it.
I'm proud of you.
Now, go on. Go do your adult thing.
And we'll see you around.
Okay.
Though...
If you're not in a rush?
- It's a pizza party.
- Yeah.
Yeah. Here he is!
- Everybody!
- Hey, welcome back, ugly.
Yes, what other bright ideas
are you gonna leave us with
before you bugger off?
Softball team.
Oh, no, only electronic sports.
Piñata Fridays.
How many times
do I have to say no to that?
Unionizing.
Ooh! Don't let Hank hear you say that.
You know, it's still weird
not having you around.
Oh, man, I'll always
be right there, big guy,
- in that giant heart of yours.
- Aw.
And I'll be at the Bureau.
So you guys can literally
stop by whenever you want.
But you know,
before I go, I do wanna say one thing.
When I first stepped onto this ship,
I was, you know,
trying to get away from
all my baggage back home and,
I can't believe I'm gonna say this...
Hemingway once wrote,
"You can't get away from yourself
by moving from one place to another."
And thanks to you guys,
I don't have to run anymore.
Being here with you all
has turned me into
the man I need to be.
And, uh, this place is special.
And you never know
when it's gonna be over, so...
I say, Legends,
enjoy the ride while it lasts.
- Hear! Hear! Cheers.
- Cheers.
- Cheers. Cheers.
Uh, you'll find your place here.
I know I did.