- In 2166, an immortal madman
named vandal savage
Conquered the world and
murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
And stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately,
my plan is opposed
By the body
I'd sworn my allegiance to,
The time masters.
In the future,
they may not be heroes,
But if we succeed,
They will be remembered
as legends.
- Previously
on "legends of tomorrow"...
- I'm a time master,
Making discrete alterations
to the timeline is what I do.
- Half of what
you told us about the mission
Turned out to be lies.
- Lewis smart, convicted
of larceny, armed robbery.
You and your entire family
are criminals.
- Things are complicated
with family.
- The lazarus pit
brought me back,
But it left me with
this need to kill.
- You're princess chay-ara,
I'm prince khufu,
And we're lovers.
I know you're worth the wait.
- [grunts]
- Aah!
- Well, I say
we kick savage's ass
For carter.
All: For carter.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Ah!
[grunts]
- Who are you?
♪ ♪
- The man who's here
to kill you.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
- We've arrived
in leipzig, germany,
The most current location
for vandal savage.
And by the way, captain,
You are are urgently needed
in the medbay.
- I thought she'd stabilized.
- As did I.
[alarm blares]
- [whimpering]
Carter!
Where's carter?
- He's gone, kendra.
I'm so sorry.
- [wailing]
- Gideon,
turn that bloody noise off!
- Yes, captain.
- What happened?
- Saunders appears
to have had a complication.
- Ye--I know, what kind of
complication?
- How could you leave him?
- Is she--
- medbay gave her a sedative,
But obviously her condition
is worsening.
- Pieces of the dagger
have apparently broken off
And are, as we speak,
en route to her heart.
- Can't we just time jump
into the future
Where they got the stuff
that can fix her?
- This ship is from that very
same future and has, thus far,
Been unsuccessful in saving her.
- Kendra wouldn't survive
the time jump anyway.
I pay attention.
- To sum up,
carter hall is dead,
The girlfriend's
not too far behind,
Vandal savage
is sitting pretty in 1975,
Which we're all stuck in.
That how the plan
supposed to work, rip?
- Obviously not,
but the mission is simple.
We stop vandal savage
here in the past
And we save the future.
- Simple don't mean easy,
captain.
- Oh, I never said it was.
The benefit of being a
time master is that
The length and breadth
of history gives one...
Perspective.
I've seen darker days.
I've seen men of steel die
and dark knights fall,
And even then I accomplished
my mission no matter what.
Gideon, what is our status?
- When the waverider was
attacked by chronos,
The jumpship was damaged.
Unless you make repairs,
we will be unable to--
- Wait, jumpship?
- It's a small
expeditionary vessel
At the belly of the waverider--
You're a mechanic!
You have a look at it.
- Uh...Auto mechanic.
Uh...Spaceship.
Okay, if you've got a set
of wrenches,
I'll see what I can do.
- What about the rest of us?
Do we just sit?
- Capital idea, mr. Rory.
You're not nearly as thick
as most people say.
- Thick...
Does that mean stupid?
- Is that your son?
He looks like you.
Sorry.
Trained by league of assassins,
Sneaking up on people
is kind of our thing.
- I'd like to be alone
for a moment.
- You don't actually have
a plan, do you?
And that speech wasn't
about convincing us.
It was about convincing you.
Didn't work, did it?
- Not particularly, no.
Hence my desire to be alone.
- So we can't kill savage.
- Oh, I see you've grasped
the concept of immortality,
Well done.
- Maybe we could slow him down.
Now, ra's al ghul
taught me a thing or two
About fighting
powerful adversaries.
If you can't kill your enemy,
weaken him.
If you can't cut off his head,
Take his heart.
- Mr. Al ghul was quite
the poet.
- Back at the weapons auction,
Savage was trying
to sell his nuke.
- Money is power.
- Take away savage's fortune
and he's just a regular guy
With a really long lifespan.
- It certainly would set
his plan for world domination
Back a few decades.
- So where does vandal savage
keep his money in 1975?
- The broken knife fragments
Are moving through her
circulatory system,
And if you'll notice these,
They're closing
in towards her heart.
- So what do we do?
- The fragments are miniscule.
Even the ship's technology
Isn't capable
of neutralizing them.
- Fortunately, there's
a technology onboard that is.
The atom suit.
I can shrink down,
slip into her bloodstream,
And use the photon canons
to vaporize the knife fragments.
- You'll be pushing
the suit's limits.
We should run some tests,
Make sure this is
the best plan of action.
- This isn't the ivory tower,
professor.
We don't have time--
- listen to me, raymond.
- I'm not your student anymore.
- You were never my student!
- Just because you don't
remember me--
- If you had been my student,
I'd have taught you
the principles
Of using scientific analysis,
not this bravado.
- There isn't time.
I'm going in.
- [sighs]
- Gideon!
Where's his money now?
- Dr. Boardman theorized
that savage entrusted it
To the brüemberg group,
the oldest bank in the world.
- I'll go tell
the rest of the team.
- That won't be necessary.
I'm going alone.
I can't have any more blood
on my hands.
- Except for your own?
You can't go in there
without backup.
- Look, I brought you all
with me under false pretenses.
Carter would still be alive
If I hadn't have
convinced him to come.
- No one's on this ship
that doesn't want to be here.
- But I can't risk
the whole team.
- Fine. Just me.
And if it helps,
I'm not giving you a choice.
I'm going with you to that bank.
- Somebody say bank?
- Your services aren't required,
mr. Snart.
This is purely reconnaissance.
- We know how to case banks.
We're practically bankers.
- 'cept we take the money out.
- Yes, and when I need someone
to steal something,
You'll be the first to know,
I assure you.
- Listen, englishman.
I'm getting bored being stuck
on this tin can.
And when I get bored,
I make bad decisions.
- Now, now, now,
we're all on the same side here.
My hot-headed friend
and I just want to be helpful.
That's all.
- Duly noted.
♪ ♪
- You should have let me
punch him.
- Yeah, then we wouldn't have
gotten this.
- Hm.
- You ready?
- Yes.
[monitor beeps]
[whirring]
♪ ♪
- All right,
where am I headed?
- You're exiting
the tracheal artery.
You should see
the first fragment.
- No sign of it.
Did I miss it?
- It's the size of an iceberg.
It seems highly unlikely
that you could miss it.
- That's probably what they said
on the titanic.
- [groans]
- Think I found it.
Looks like all those years
of playing "asteroids"
Is about to pay off.
♪ ♪
[electricity whines, surges]
[monitor beeps]
- Her vitals are improving.
It seems to be working.
- [grunts]
[sighs]
- There's still 19 more
fragments.
Raymond?
Raymond, you're not done!
- I'm losing core containment.
Plot me a course out of here.
Now!
[the isley brother's
"fight the power" plays]
- ♪ ha! ♪
♪ oh! ♪
♪ hey ♪
♪ ha! ♪
♪ time is truly wasting ♪
♪ there's no guarantee ♪
♪ smile is in the making ♪
- Excuse me.
We'd like to deposit
some family heirlooms.
- I'm sorry,
we're a private bank.
We don't secure valuables
worth less than $10 million.
- Well,
I'm sure this will suffice.
Doubloons from the wreck
of the "esplinade".
They've been appraised
at $10 million dollars...
Apiece.
- ♪ fight the power ♪
♪ fight it ♪
- Such a pleasure.
You won't regret your decision.
The brüemberg group
is known for its discretion.
- I'm sure there'll be a fair
deal of paperwork to sign.
- Not too much.
We like to cut through
the red tape here.
Let me get this to one
of our safe deposit boxes,
And I'll get my secretary
to move in on this paperwork.
[suspicious music]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Interesting.
There are records here referring
To something called
the "vessel."
- We have a problem.
- Yes, I know, none of savage's
funds are in this bank.
I'm working
on locating this "vessel",
But I'm not sure I'll do so
before our new friend returns.
- To kill us.
The receptionist had a silenced
beretta under her desk.
The guards,
south african mercenaries.
You can tell by the initiation
burns on their neck.
And our new friend here has
calluses on his right hand
Consistent with being
kuroda-trained swordsmen.
- How do you know?
- Because I have
the same calluses.
Which means
they've probably figured out
That we are not rockefellers
Who just came
into their inheritance.
- Oh, don't be so alarmist.
Calluses are hardly definitive
proof of anything.
- Pretty sure they made us.
- Well, if this is how
you treat your customers,
We might just have to take
our business elsewhere.
- [grunts]
- [groans]
- I thought I specifically
said no weapons!
- You can thank me later.
[montrose's
"I got the fire" plays]
- ♪ if you're looking
for someone ♪
♪ that you can keep ♪
♪ well, baby ♪
- Exactly how many knives
do you have?
♪ ♪
- Seems you brought
a knife to a swordfight.
- ♪ and if you want something ♪
♪ that's 20 years deep ♪
[both grunting]
♪ baby don't even try ♪
[grunting]
♪ maybe lift you
a little bit higher ♪
♪ I got the fire! ♪
- [grunting]
- Sara.
- [grunts]
- Sara!
Sara, don't!
We didn't get anything
from the computer!
We need him alive!
- [breathing heavily]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- What the hell happened
back there?
- You know I'm a killer.
That's why you put me
in your little group.
- I didn't witness
just a killer at work, sara.
What I saw was an animal.
- You are the last person
on this ship to judge anyone!
- This is not judgment, sara.
It is concern.
- I thought you knew
how I was resurrected
And--and what it did to me.
- I know you were restored
By something called
the lazarus pit.
- Well,
apparently there's a downside
To being brought back to life.
My friend thea
calls it a blood lust,
And I think that's being too
generous,
And so is calling me an animal.
I'm a monster.
- Ha! Nice ride!
- Yeah, it can
hit a mach 3 in a walk.
Pretty cool.
- How'd you know
so much about it?
- Little thing called
an instruction manual.
- Did you read the part
about how to fly this thing?
- Maybe...
Why?
- We're gonna take a little
sojourn to central city.
There's a priceless jewel
That needs
to be freed from captivity.
- You want me to
help you steal something?
Nah, man.
I'll pass.
- Not exactly asking,
jax.
- Wow. Carter is dead,
Kendra is this close
to joining him,
And vandal savage is still alive
And out there
doing god knows what,
And all you can think
about is stealing some diamond?
- It's an emerald.
- Is there anything you think
about other than yourself?
- Yes. Money.
- Nah. I'm not helping
you guys steal anything.
So if you want to shoot me,
then shoot me.
- Can I shoot him?
- You got a pair on you, kid.
I respect that.
- So no shooting...
- Look, you don't actually have
to help us steal anything.
We just need to get
to central city.
We'll be there and back before
anyone knows we're even gone.
- Man, even if I wanted to help,
and I'm not saying that I do,
This thing's got
a security lockout.
We need an access key.
- You can't tell me you don't
wanna see what this baby can do.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I believe I've determined
a way to more efficiently
Track the fragments still
inside ms. Saunders body.
Next time you'll
be better prepared.
- There won't be a next time.
- Can't you fix the suit?
- It's not the suit.
- Raymond,
you--you mustn't be discouraged.
We're scientists.
We learn from failure,
and we keep going.
- Kendra isn't a lab experiment.
She's a person.
- I know.
You need to have confidence
this will work.
- Well, I don't.
I can't save her.
- Based on what evidence?
Are we not empirical thinkers,
dr. Palmer?
Exactly how many people
have you lost?
- One.
- Who did you lose?
Someone close to you?
Who was she, raymond?
- For someone who doesn't
remember me,
You sure have a lot of personal
observations to offer.
- Fine,
don't talk to me,
But fix the suit.
It's the only chance
that poor girl has.
♪ ♪
- I'm gonna make this very
simple for you, mr. Blake.
You tell me where vandal savage
is hiding his fortune
And we will let you
leave here unmolested.
- Vandal savage...
Is that the name
you know him by?
- Let's assume so, yes.
- And what is your name?
Gareeb?
- Will you give us a moment?
- Gareeb?
- It's a legend passed down
for 4,000 years.
When my master was first
Bestowed the gift
of eternal life,
An enemy tried to kill him.
Every myth has its monster,
its devil.
For those of our order,
it's him, the gareeb.
- I'd stop talking now
if I were you, mate.
- If I were you, I'd run.
Your friend has already failed
to kill my master once.
He won't be able to protect you.
In fact, I highly doubt
He's ever been able
to protect anyone.
- [grunts]
- What did he mean you already
tried to kill savage?
- Leave it be, sara.
- No, if you want us
to do this--
- Yes, okay!
Yes, I-I had the chance
to kill savage once before.
I had him dead to rights
and I hesitated.
[both grunting]
♪ ♪
- [yelling]
[speaking foreign language]
Get off me!
Aah!
- I asked you a question.
Who are you, gareeb?
- Killing is never easy,
Especially for a good man.
- But the man killed
my wife and son
And god knows how many other
wives and sons,
And yet I couldn't--
Your killing people doesn't make
you a monster, sara,
But having the chance
to avenge your family
And not taking it...
That does.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Let's try this again.
- Back for more.
- Where's savage's fortune?
Now, I'm particularly interested
In this thing called
the "vessel."
- The vessel is my master's
most treasured possession.
- Excellent,
and where can we find it?
- The greyhill building.
There's a gathering tonight
in celebration of it.
- And clearly you want us to go
so we can get ourselves killed.
- Clearly.
- What is the vessel?
- It's the remains
of prince khufu
Of the middle kingdom.
I believe you know him
as carter hall.
- What is savage going
to do with carter's body?
- Well, there's only one way
to find out, isn't there?
♪ ♪
- Gideon,
locate the greyhill building
And set a course.
- Wait. We have a plan.
Going after savage's fortune.
- Yeah, well, not anymore!
I won't let carter's remains
be desecrated by that monster.
I won't let him win again.
And when kendra wakes up--
and she will wake up,
She can give her soul mate
a proper farewell.
- Then let us at least go
in with the rest of the team.
- Hm.
Gideon!
- Sir, mr. Snart, mr. Rory,
and mr. Jackson
Are no longer aboard the ship.
- That's what I call
a clean heist.
- And thanks for not setting
the museum on fire, partner.
And you, thanks for being
our getaway driver.
- Speaking of, let's get
the hell back to the ship.
- Oh, one more stop.
- What're you
talking about, boss?
- 1629 handley avenue.
- What's on handley avenue?
- It's where we grew up.
That's why you wanted
to steal the maximilian emerald.
- Mick, enough.
- You wanted to give it
to your old man
So he wouldn't go to jail
Trying to steal it
for himself.
- Your father was a thief too?
- And unfortunately,
not a very good one.
- Didn't rip say something about
not messing with the timeline?
- You could accidently blink
yourself out of existence.
You're screwing
with history here, man.
- Yeah, well,
history screwed with me first.
[monitor beeps]
- I know how it feels.
- What?
- To have a crisis
of confidence.
As unlikely as that might seem,
I know.
It was 2002.
I was teaching
quantum mechanics
And I had one particularly
gifted student.
He was able to solve
the ehrenfest theorem
In less than an hour.
He was, quite frankly,
the only student
In all my years of teaching
Who ever made me
feel inferior.
That student...Was you.
You were exceptional.
- And suddenly, just like that,
You remember having me
in your class.
- I always remembered.
I just enjoyed taking
you down a peg or two.
- [chuckles]
and why tell me now?
- Because I cannot
for the life of me reconcile
That cocksure student
I remember with a man
Who believes he doesn't have
What it takes
to save ms. Saunders' life.
Who did you lose, raymond?
- My fiancée,
anna loring.
She was killed two years ago
in a starling city siege.
Right in front of me.
I couldn't have stopped them.
I couldn't do anything.
My leg had been broken.
I couldn't get to her.
I could only watch...
As they broke her neck.
I built this suit because
I promised myself that night
That I would never be powerless
to save anyone again.
So when a fragment
broke free and damaged my suit,
I...
Panicked.
Froze.
- Raymond,
you couldn't save anna,
But you can save kendra.
I believe it.
I believe in that student.
I just need him
to believe it too.
[triumphant music]
♪ ♪
- Let's do it.
- Ah, mr. Blake.
Welcome.
I take it mrs. Blake
is out of town?
- That's a very pointed
observation.
♪ ♪
- If you're going to find
the vessel, you'll need my help.
- No, I think we're
quite good without it.
Sara.
- [grunts]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I came down
for a glass of water.
I'm leo.
Are you friends
with my daddy?
- Kind of.
- I think
my daddy's sleeping.
- Can I tell you something,
leo?
It's important.
Don't ever let anyone hurt you.
Ever.
Not here...
And especially...
Not here.
No matter what, you always have
to look out for yourself.
Okay?
You understand?
- I think so.
[gun cocks]
- You get the hell away
from my boy, you son of a bitch.
- Why don't you
go on up to bed?
Go on.
♪ ♪
- Talk fast,
or you take a bullet.
What're you doing in my home?
- A favor for you.
- Watch it.
- Relax.
- How the hell did you get--
- Two days from now,
you try to steal this
And you get arrested,
and you spend five years
In iron heights.
- What are you talking about?
- Cut the crap.
We both know if I go down
to the basement right now,
I'll find floor plans
for the central city museum.
Let's just say I've saved
you the trouble...
And from being arrested.
- How do you know all this?
- The same way I'll know
if you even think
Of raising a hand
to your wife and son.
I know who you are.
I know the man you become
And it's all I can do to keep
From ending you right here,
right now,
But if I do,
That means
my sister's never born,
So you get a pass.
- Your sister?
- Looks like you didn't write
yourself out of the timeline.
- Looks like.
- But?
- I don't know,
I just thought maybe things
Would feel differently.
- The englishman says it
takes time for time to change.
- What were you trying
to change?
- My dad was never
father of the year,
But at least he never raised
a hand to any of us.
- Until he went to prison,
which now he won't.
- Let's get out of here.
[violin music playing]
- Maybe we should have
had blake show us around.
- Hm.
Perhaps there's
a less conspicuous way
For us to do reconnaissance.
May I?
- I'm not much of a dancer.
- I'll lead, then.
♪ ♪
Well, for a monster,
You dance quite gracefully,
ms. Lance.
- Don't make fun.
- I know, I'm not.
Nor do I consider you
a monster.
All I see is someone
who is tortured
By an appetite
that she cannot control.
- There's no magical cure
for what's wrong with me.
- Of course there is.
It's called being better.
When my family was killed,
I thought there
was no way I could go on,
But I did.
The truth of our existence
Is that we're
all blessed and cursed
With the drive to move forward.
Live the next day.
To get better.
And you will too, sara.
♪ ♪
- Well, maybe I can start by
managing not to kill these guys.
They're scarred up like our
friends at the bank.
- South african mercenaries.
Why didn't you say so?
Ladies first.
[both laughing]
- This area's restricted,
folks.
- [slurred] I'm just looking
for the ladies' room.
Oh!
[laughs]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Hope you have a plan
to get him out of here.
- Yup, there's a maintenance
elevator leads to a loading bay.
I'll have gideon
fly the waverider down.
- I just wish we knew
What savage was gonna do
with carter's body.
- Why not stay and find out?
Ah, the gareeb.
Mr. Blake has told us
so much about you.
♪ ♪
[monitors beeping]
- I've located three fragments.
- Okay, I see them.
Damn, they're big.
- Remember,
the initial blast will create
Smaller pieces.
You'll need to--
- How does jax put up
with having you in his head?
- I believe he finds
my presence rather comforting.
- I doubt that very much.
♪ ♪
Targeting system's overloaded.
- Focus, raymond.
Remember, you can do this.
It's not the suit,
It's you that kendra
needs right now.
♪ ♪
Well done,
just one more fragment to go.
- I see it.
It's the biggest one yet.
[electricity whining, whirring]
- You did it!
[exhales sharply]
♪ ♪
Well done.
I couldn't possibly
be more proud.
- Well,
maybe if you actually remembered
Me being your student.
Right around
the subclavian artery,
I remembered something.
How I figured the solve
to the ehrenfest theorem...
Two years after
I was in your class.
Why did you tell me you
remembered me when you didn't?
- Because you needed a push.
- So all that stuff
about me being exceptional?
- Was probably true.
The fact of the matter is,
I had many exceptional students
over the years,
I couldn't possibly
remember them all.
- I was pretty amazing.
- If that were true,
I suspect I'd have
given you a higher grade.
- I meant tonight.
- Oh, yes.
On that score,
I cannot disagree.
[triumphant music]
♪ ♪
- What're you planning
on doing with carter's body?
- Oh, you'll see.
Mr. Blake informs us
That you were hoping
to steal our master's fortune,
But while money has its uses,
It is not the source
of his power.
- Then what is?
- Let us show you.
- [all chanting]
hym nu setta, rash mun setta.
- Our numbers are legion.
All drawn to the man
who is immune to death.
Wealth is not power...
Belief is.
- [all chanting]
hym nu setta, rash mun setta.
[intense music]
♪ ♪
- Hello, gareeb.
How long as it been?
4,000 years?
You look well.
- When you and your friends
Attacked my estate
in st. Roch.
I was afraid I wouldn't get
The chance
to meet you once again.
Well, if there's something
that I've learned
In 4,000 years...
It's patience.
And this time I only had
to wait one short day.
You're probably wondering
What my plans
are with your friend's body.
I already have
his life's essence,
But his blood still
has its uses.
- [all chanting]
hym nu setta, rash mun setta.
- Jack the ripper
showed me
The virtues of severing
the carotid artery.
- [chanting]
hym nu setta.
- Ok, what's this now?
- Rash mun setta.
- [all chanting]
hym nu setta, rash mun setta.
Hym nu setta, rash mun setta.
- Centuries ago,
I discovered that although
Immortality is mine alone,
I can share a taste...
With my faithful.
Help them live
an extra hundred years or so.
- [all chanting]
hym nu setta, rash mun setta.
Hym nu setta, rash mun setta.
Hym nu setta--
- hum nu setta, rash mun--
[whimpers]
they're in trouble.
- She appears
to be hallucinating.
- Rip...Sara...
You have to save them!
Vandal! And carter!
The greyhill building!
Carter! Rip! Sara!
- Gideon,
search "greyhill building."
- I've already searched for it
on behalf of the captain,
Who's there now
with ms. Lance.
- What?
They left without us?
- It's a mansion
several miles away.
Apparently, there's some sort
of private event.
- How the hell could kendra
know that they're there?
- You have to save them!
- What's going on?
- I don't know!
- When we first met,
I asked you who you were.
Remember?
That was the wrong question.
I should have asked you "why?"
Why did you seek to kill me?
What could I have possibly done
to deserve that hatred
I see burning in your eyes.
Did I take something from you?
Someone?
[chuckles]
- Get your hands off that.
- Ah, your wife, I take it.
Oh, she is lovely.
The boy has your eyes.
I will be sure to keep
the picture close.
I don't remember killing them...
Yet.
It seems like I have a lot
to look forward to.
♪ ♪
- Gideon,
get me jefferson.
- Mr. Jackson is not aboard.
- Oh, don't tell me--
- He's with mr. Snart
and mr. Rory on the jumpship.
I'm patching you through.
- Jefferson?
Jefferson, where are you?
- Well, it's not a short story.
- There's no time!
Gideon will upload you
Coordinates
to the greyhill building.
Rip and sara are in danger.
- We're on our way,
professor.
- This is a perversion.
- No, this is the power
You have no hope of defeating.
Everyone here is sworn
to live and die at my command.
Why?
'cause to them, I am a god!
♪ ♪
I pity you.
You have no idea what
it's like to have people
Willing to follow you up
to the gates of hell!
[whirring]
- Actually,
I have a little bit of an idea.
- Let's get this party started!
- Here's our invitation!
[electricity whines]
- Aah!
[terrified chatter]
[electricity whines]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Well, this is different.
I didn't have him pegged
as the "eyes wide shut" type.
♪ ♪
Aah. Go!
Here!
♪ ♪
- You came!
- We're a team!
Next time, remember that.
- Enough!
[electricity buzzing]
- Get carter's body out of here.
Sara!
- I got this.
♪ ♪
[grunting]
- [yells]
♪ ♪
- Go! I'll deal with savage.
- Good luck with that.
- Ah!
♪ ♪
- [grunting]
[both grunting]
- This is for
miranda and jonas.
[grunts]
- Aah!
At least I know
their names now.
Miranda and jo--
[coughs]
Jonas.
- [grunting]
- I will heal...
And then I will rise...
And I'll simply wait.
I am looking forward
to meeting them.
♪ ♪
- Sara.
Sara.
Sara!
♪ ♪
- Gideon, I need a check
of the timeline.
Vandal savage.
- The timeline
is unchanged, captain.
You know better than anyone
that savage is immortal.
He cannot be killed through
conventional means.
- Which is why I need you
to work on finding out
Where history records
seeing him next.
How is she?
- Better.
Thank you for what
you did for carter.
- Believe me,
it was a team effort.
As was, apparently,
your recovery.
- Well, actually,
I did most of the physical work
And professor was there
for emotional support.
- You're welcome.
Now, if we could
just figure out a way
To wrest the amon dagger out
of savage's hand into yours.
- I don't think I'm exactly up
to taking him on right now.
- No, but you will be...
And we'll help you get ready.
♪ ♪
- Maybe you didn't
understand me,
I asked for the new timeline,
gideon.
- This is the new timeline.
Two days from now,
your father will be arrested
Trying to sell
the maximilian emerald
To an undercover police
officer.
- Stupid son of a bitch.
- He'll be sentenced
to five years in iron heights.
Despite your intervention,
his future remains unchanged.
- Hey,
you tried to save him.
That's got to count
for something.
- Turns out it doesn't.
- Come on.
- Where are we going now?
- To say good-bye.
- [sigh]
The other day, I tried to find
some words of inspiration.
Words that would restore hope
to us in the wake of our losses,
But it is all of you
who have inspired me.
Beginning with
professor boardman
And then with carter,
Their heroism is...
An inspiration to us all.
And a reminder
that one person acting alone
Can't save the world.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Come back to me.
[sniffles]
Thank you.
Both of you.
- We're sorry for your loss,
kendra.
- I believe
anna would be proud.
As am I.
- Gideon,
ready us for take off.
- Whoa, are we being chased
or something?
- No, but I imagine
that right about now,
The museum has realized that
their prized emerald is missing.
- You want me to say I'm sorry?
- Sorry, I don't do sorry.
- Which is fine, mr. Rory,
Because you are owed
the apology.
I should have told
you all before
That this wasn't
my first attempt
To vanquish vandal savage,
But the reason I failed before--
- Was because you
didn't have all of us.
- Obviously dr. Palmer
and I had our hands full
Tending to ms. Saunders,
But now that she's back
on her feet--
- We're back to full strength.
- Or as strong as
we can be without carter.
- Quite true,
But there is no point
in us continuing any further.
Unless we are all--
and myself included,
Committed to working in concert.
- You don't ditch us,
we won't ditch you.
Deal?
- Sir, I've completed
my review of the timeline.
I calculate a 98% likelihood
That savage reappears in 1986.
- Chart a course, gideon.
- Guess we're headed
to the '80s.
Better break out
your parachute pants.
- What the hell
are parachute pants?
♪ ♪