[Sara] Previously on
Legends Of Tomorrow...
I have to keep you safe. Go!
[Agent Sharpe] You've had Mona
in custody this whole time?
You have the Kaupe, too?
Sara, you need to bring in that fugitive
before someone gets hurt.
- [gunshot]
- [groans]
[agent] Step away
from the creature, miss.
You murdered him!
[growling]
Today, I asked you for one thing.
- Ava, don't do this.
- Just go.
[Zari] So, I'll head to the Bureau
and do some digging.
Hank is torturing prisoners off-site.
Keep digging.
I wanna know everything.
What do you mean
you couldn't capture the asset?
[agent] Blame it on your son's
time-traveling pals, sir.
Now, let me just say this.
And I wanna say this
for the television audience.
The people have a right to know,
whether or not
their President is a crook.
Well, I am a crook.
It actually felt good
to get that off my chest.
What other secrets
have I been holding back...
Oh, yes. Despite the constant
reassurances of my wife,
I know that I'm certainly
only an adequate lover.
- [reporter 1] Mr. President?
- [reporter 2] Mr. President?
The President won't be taking
any more questions at this time.
That is more about Tricky Dick
than I ever needed to know.
[Gideon] And it's more than
the public needed to know.
In the days following
the news conference,
Nixon found himself unable to
tell a lie, resulting in global chaos.
Nixon's blathering fouled up ongoing
peace talks and trade agreements...
Without the release of
All the President's Men,
Robert Redford's career floundered.
What? No Redford?
No Sundance. No indie film.
No artful nudity? We have to fix this!
The only thing nastier
than a politician lying,
is when he says how he really feels.
Now, there's no way he'd tell the truth
without a magical assist.
I hope the Watergate has vacancies,
because we need to make sure
that Nixon still cheats the press.
Captain's orders and all,
but you think it's really the best time
to be back on mission?
Yeah, I mean,
might do well to take a beat.
I appreciate your concern,
but I'll be fine.
Just because Ava and I
had a disagreement,
doesn't mean that I can't do my job.
I was actually talking about the fact
that we're on the outs
with the Time Bureau.
Yeah, and I was talking about Mona.
I mean, Hank's gonna be after us since
her boyfriend offed that agent, and...
Well, we can't
just stash her away forever.
Right.
Well, it has been eventful, but things
are gonna blow over with the Bureau.
We'll find a safe place for Mona,
and in the meantime,
I feel like we should be doing
what we do best.
- Am I right?
- Right.
Save Redford and independent film!
That's the spirit!
- Done it for worse reasons.
- Why not?
Director Sharpe, you look terrible.
What happened?
Joke acknowledged, Nathaniel,
but tighten up.
Director Sharpe is taking a leave of
absence to get her priorities straight.
I'll be acting as
Director of the Bureau.
[stammers] Wait, so, you're gonna be
in charge from now on?
- That's... It's great.
- Great.
Looking forward to working with you,
Director Heywood.
Glad to have you on board, Agent Tomaz.
Though my first job is a sensitive one.
I need to catch the Legends.
This is the last time
they will thumb their nose at authority,
and get away with it.
I know they are your friends.
So, you wanna sit this one out?
No, no, Dad. You know what?
We have your back.
Agreed. I stand by the Time Bureau,
and by my man.
Thank you, babe.
[Hank] Glad to hear it.
We'll pinpoint the location
of the Waverider, and pay it a visit.
We'll meet in the situation room, 0900.
Yes, sir, copy that.
We need to expose what Hank's up to
before he drops a hammer on the Legends.
Did you just call me "babe"?
Yeah, I was riffing,
I was trying to keep this thing afloat.
[clears throat] Anyway,
now that we are stuck with Hank,
we can't go through his phone ourselves.
With Ava gone,
there's no one here left to trust.
Well, there's one person we can trust.
Gary, we need to talk.
Is this about what happened
between Sara and Ava?
Wait. You're working at the Bureau?
Yes, and...
I need you to do something for me.
And you're my boss! Which is great.
You know, I'm happy for you.
- No one deserves it more.
- Damn it, Gary, focus.
Hank is causing total chaos here.
Did you notice him
using Director Sharpe's mug, too?
- I was gonna say something.
- It goes much deeper than that.
Mona was right.
Hank is running some secret project.
Now that he's in charge of the Bureau,
he's trying to shut down the Legends.
Nate and I cloned his phone.
We're going to keep him busy.
You need to go through his activity,
find out what he's been up to
so we can end his time with the Bureau.
Use this to stay in touch
without being monitored, okay?
I've always wanted
to untangle a conspiracy.
I'll need a bulletin board, index cards,
I already have yarn,
I've been getting into crochet.
- Yeah, me, too.
- We should start a club.
We'll talk.
Okay.
[sighs]
[Mona] Konane! No!
[growling]
[growls]
- [Mick] Kid, you okay in there?
- [gasps]
Sorry, I never used a future
tech toilet before. So many buttons.
Hmm.
Give it time.
You'll learn to live with it.
Oh, uh...
Don't touch the red button.
[Mona] Oh, Captain,
I wanted to talk to you.
Good. I need to talk to you, too.
So, as far as the Bureau is concerned,
you're a fugitive.
I need you to stay on the ship,
and not draw any attention.
It's not just that. Um...
- When we were in Mexico...
- When we were in Mexico,
a man got murdered by Konane
because you said we could trust him.
No, Konane didn't...
He didn't mean to.
Look, Mona, whatever it is,
it's in the past.
Now it's on to the next problem.
That's how this works.
Mick, Nixon's supposed to give his
"I'm not a crook" speech tomorrow.
We need him back
to his lying self by then.
You and John stay on the ship,
look after Mona,
and make sure
she doesn't get into any trouble.
And make sure
she doesn't touch that red button.
I'm telling you I'm not crazy.
In fact,
I've never felt better in my life.
And that's the truth!
Hear that? "The truth." Something
is very wrong with the President.
And he's supposed to be
at Disney's Contemporary Hotel
to address the entire
American press corps tomorrow.
We'll take care of it.
[agent] I'll update the VP.
All right, sir.
We'll start off with a little sedative.
[groans]
I don't know why you lot
are relying on my powers.
They're still all mucked up.
[Sara] It'll be fine.
We'll get him to the ship, fix what's
wrong, and we'll be right back.
[sigh] Now, let's see
your Nixon impression.
[sighs]
- [chuckles]
- Nice.
We got the cargo. We're on our way.
Let's figure out what loosed his tongue
and get the hell out of here, shall we?
Listen, you guys can't be here.
The Bureau's on to you.
Good, time for a pig roast.
No one's roasting anyone,
and it's not just the Bureau,
it's my dad, and he's got backup. Go!
No, not again.
Guys, we're working on
stopping Hank for good.
In the meantime, you need to find
the team and stay ahead of him.
On it.
What's going on?
Nate's old man commandeered the ship.
There they are!
Okay, take the stairs. Get Nixon.
[Ray] Come on.
[chanting]
[groans]
[agent] We have eyes on the Legends,
and they have the President.
They've gone too far again!
Siri, what... Alexa!
Gideon, fire up the engine!
The Legends must have bricked the ship.
Oh, they think of everything.
Nicely done.
I want our men watching every time jump,
listening to every comm.
How are we gonna make distance
with five of us, and a kidnapped Nixon?
There. There's our getaway.
That's a bit on the nose, no?
We left subtlety back in Mexico.
Gotta go.
[tires screeching]
[agent] The Legends
are in the wind, Director.
Damn it!
[agent] They must have stolen a vehicle
and hit the road.
You know what?
I've never needed a Waverider before,
and I don't need one now.
You give me a dragnet.
I want agents at every rest stop, diner,
store along the highway. Move!
And you, set up a police scanner.
If the Legends
so much as forget to signal,
we'll hear about it.
They'll slip up eventually.
That's probably accurate.
[Mick grunts]
Okay.
Captain, you should know that
me and tight spaces might not mix.
Do you think any of us
want to be stuck in this RV?
- Punch buggy! No punch backs.
- [Sara sighs]
Mona, the team's back
is up against the wall.
And right now,
you are a part of this team,
and if you want it to stay that way,
then you need to help,
- not create more problems.
- Okay.
Great.
[DJ 1]
Jim-Bob is struck with appendicitis
on an all-new The Waltons.
[DJ 2] For all you lonely hearts on the
road today, here's a tune just for you.
You know, I've never been
in a car that's a room before.
[sighs]
Patricia.
No, I'm not Patricia, Dick.
[Mona] Ooh!
Camera! [chuckles]
Not to bother you,
but we've lost the ship,
drugged the President,
and I'm stuck in the back with her.
Now, what are we gonna do?
We are going to Disney World.
[grunts]
Haven't we been tortured enough?
I mean, we are going to fix Nixon
in time to get him to Florida
to lie his ass off.
We are not gonna let anything stop us
from what we set out to do.
Mick, watch our tail.
John, see if you can figure out
what's wrong with Nixon,
and, Mona, find us something to wear.
Charlie...
- We forgot Charlie!
"We'll be right back," they said.
Yeah, bloody right!
[knocking on door]
[man] Mr. President?
No, no, no! Okay!
Quick, quick, quick, Charlie!
[man]
Mr. President, are you okay in there?
[gasps]
Just checking in, Mr. President.
You check in again, you'll be lucky
to be guarding a shopping mall.
Um...
- Okay, make your next left.
- Okay.
No, your next right.
Hey guys, looks like Nixon over here
is finally winning the war on drugs.
[Nixon groans]
Good God,
I've been kidnapped by hippies!
What is it you want?
Money, power? I'll do anything.
- Look, we're here to help you.
- Let's talk about money.
You know, right now, we're your best
shot at getting back to your right self.
Now, let's have a look.
Now, I have my suspicions
as to what's got at ya.
Yep! Okay.
[chanting]
What the hell are you babbling about?
[choking]
Ugh!
It's a roach.
I've been bugged!
This is an agent of Ma'at,
the goddess of truth
in the Egyptian pantheon.
You see, the creature,
it feeds off lies,
and whoever it eats at,
has nothing but truth left to tell.
No wonder it found its way to Nixon.
You must've been a feast.
No, no! [groans]
[Sara] Sorry.
Put him in the closet.
- Come on, Dickie!
- Yeah.
Let's put Dick in a box! [sighs]
Um...
Captain, can we talk?
A lot's been going on, and...
And the truth roach, well...
That's gonna be a wrinkle.
Look, Mona, I have
a really big responsibility for you.
I need you to watch the roach.
Me? But, um...
Your job was to take care
of creatures, right?
Who better than you?
[nervously]
Hey, little guy, bet you're hungry.
Hank Heywood.
Renewed his Bestflix subscription...
December 16th...
So, that means...
Oh, my God. How did this happen?
I am way out of my league.
What is it, Jerry?
[stammers] No, it's "Gary."
Hmm.
I notice you're reading
Body of Proof by Rebecca Silver.
Is that a conspiracy thriller?
Book club's at capacity.
Uh... No... No, that's not it. It's...
I need your help
uncovering a conspiracy.
And why would I help you?
Because you might be in trouble.
Hank has his agents taking fugitives
out of their cells at night.
And I don't want you to be next.
So, I thought,
if I release you for the night,
maybe you could help me.
Hey, you okay?
It's not easy being trapped somewhere
where no one will listen to you, huh?
Hey, can you hear me?
[gasps]
You probably need air.
[grunts] Oh!
No, no, no!
What's going on?
Oh, I just dropped it, but it's okay.
I got... [grunts]
What's wrong with the brakes?
[tires screeching]
Can't slow down, can't slow down!
[horn tooting]
[tires screeching]
[Sara] Move your...
Your foot, Ray!
[Ray sighs]
Got it.
- [siren blaring]
- Who called the cops?
Cops?
I've never been pulled over before.
What do I do?
You just pull over.
[Ray sighs and clears his throat]
All right, just be cool, you got this.
[grunts]
Good afternoon...
Good afternoon, Officer.
I watched you drivin'.
- You're havin' a fine afternoon.
- Yeah.
What is it? Drinkin'?
Drugs?
No, sir. No, sir, we're just, uh...
Just driving and having
a little steering-wheel problem.
Tell me some more about
this steering-wheel trouble.
Well, it's a real doozy.
So, I'm here with my family,
and we're on our way to North Carolina
to see the largest chest of drawers.
Ray!
So, the steering wheel was a little
loose, and so, I turned to my wife,
Claire, and I said...
[swallows]
My friends and I here
are time travelers.
We've kidnapped Nixon,
and we're headed to Disney World.
[sighs]
Like I thought.
You're high as a Goodyear blimp.
I'm calling this in.
[chuckles] Get this out of me!
[chanting]
How'd it even...
Mona!
[officer] I'm at Exit 244.
I got an RV full of hopheads
who claim they're from the future.
See?
[chuckles] Come on, son, let's go grab
our guys the old-fashioned way.
Mmm-hmm.
Wait, Nate. I tuned this to a frequency
Hank can't read.
And I think I know a way
to contact the team.
It's a little old-school,
but it should work.
I'll be in touch.
[sighs] I can't have a ticket
on my record.
I can't have a ticket on my record!
Nabbin' Nixon is gonna give you
more than a bloody ticket, mate.
Gun it! I'm bored.
He's right. Gun it.
- But then we'll become fugitives!
- We're already fugitives.
- Move.
- Hey!
You come back here!
Officer, we heard
your report from up high.
Where are the offenders?
[officer]
Uh... I was fixing to call it in.
You let them get away?
You're gonna have to find another
way home because that's my car now.
There's a new sheriff in town.
Let's ride.
[laughter]
Nice moves, Palmer.
[siren blaring]
They're gaining.
Yeah, I don't think
that's the cops on us, mate.
Whoa! Hank! This car has no airbags
or traction control.
[laughs] Exactly!
Nothin' but pure V8 power!
- [engine revving]
- Whoa! Okay.
We gotta lose Hank.
You got something for this, John?
I might. But I'll need you
to get us off the road quick, squire.
[chanting]
Where the hell did they go?
[radio static]
What is with the radio?
[Zari] The heat's heavy
on the highway tonight,
and that's no weather report.
But lucky for you, you're not alone,
because you've got DJ Z to guide you
past those bad vibes.
"DJ Z." That sounds like Zari.
Right now, the beat on the street
is to lay low.
But while you park it,
here's a hit to keep you safe.
All right, you heard her.
We should keep a low profile.
If we leave by night,
we should be able to make it.
In the meantime, no drawing attention,
and no altering the timeline.
Well, we best keep that bug
bottled then, eh?
The only way to keep it contained is
for everyone to stay completely honest.
What the hell is going on here?
Checkers!
Maybe it's best if
we all just don't talk.
Now, we just enter a command line
to a mirror site...
And we can get into his email.
His email's linked to a private server.
Must be where he's got his dirt.
We need a password.
Uh... Or we can reset it.
I forget my passwords all the time.
Those memory flashers
have a lot of side effects.
Password reset question.
We'll need some personal info from Hank.
[tablet beeps]
What's the word?
Sorry.
Gary, what's the word?
I'll need some scoop on Hank.
[Zari] Stand by, Gary.
[sighs]
Hey, Nate, we need to know the name
of your dad's childhood pet.
And whatever you do,
keep your dad off the FM.
I'm on it, Z.
[Hank groans]
That's a pretty cool trick.
You drink a lot of Cokes
when you were a kid?
Yeah.
Mom used to give me a quarter
for the corner store,
let me pick out whatever I wanted.
With her raising me on her own,
a quarter was more than I even knew.
You never really talked
about your childhood much.
Like, I'm not sure I know
where you were born.
Hackensack. In New Jersey.
Like the Billy Joel song.
We should turn on the radio.
1973, great year for music.
Actually, why don't we, uh, talk?
You know, get to know each other.
[chuckles]
- You're right, Nathaniel.
- You could call me "Nate."
You have a dog?
[scoffs] A lab.
You know, named him Silver.
- After the Lone Ranger...
- Lone Ranger's horse, yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
You used to show me old episodes.
Well, at least I taught you something.
Huh.
[Hank clears throat]
You know, my mom used to take me
on road trips, stop for ice cream...
Without Dad around,
she really had to play both roles.
She didn't know how to be a father,
but... She did her best.
Guess I could say the same for myself.
[clears throat] Well, it's nice we get
to make up for some lost time. Huh?
But we should get back to the ship.
See if Zari's back online.
Actually, um,
why don't we forget the Legends
for a minute and go get some ice cream?
Fine idea, Nathaniel.
Nate.
[engine starts]
[Zari]
Hey, Gary, the answer is "Silver."
- "Silver." I'm in!
- [beeps]
Hackers do say that in real life.
[Nora] What is this?
Property deed in Hank's name from 1912?
It's a shipment for dwarf-star alloy...
From 1837?
He's using time travel
for personal gain?
That is against Bureau creed.
I have a copy in my wallet.
- [footsteps approaching]
- [shushes]
Somebody's coming!
[eerie indistinct voices]
[eerie indistinct voices continue]
- [sighs]
- Who was that?
Are you okay?
You have to take this to Zari,
and stop digging.
I'll go back to my cell.
And, Gary...
Be careful.
[car honks]
[phone ringing]
I got an alert that someone recovered
your password from the Time Bureau,
and they're accessing your accounts.
But who would...
How would they even...
Thanks.
It won't happen again.
[music playing on stereo]
You know, I was just thinking that
even though we've had some setbacks,
that this road trip has really been
a great bonding experience.
I think you're an idiot.
[hissing]
[Ray drumming]
Well, look,
we've dealt with a lot lately,
and I think this is a very needed chance
for us to sit,
and really talk about how we feel.
Well, I'm glad you're happy.
No, wait, I mean... [gasps]
I don't give a damn if you're happy,
and I certainly don't trust you lot
in helping me face Neron, no matter
how many go-team prep talks you give.
Well, you can't keep me down.
[Ray] Actually, ever since I met you,
I sometimes lie awake at night,
staring into the dark thinking,
"I am it, and it is me."
Also, I don't think Han shot first.
I'm gonna go sit up front.
[Ray] Also, I used the strategy guide
to beat the Water Temple
in The Legend of Zelda.
I think it's a cool look, but the whole
loosened tie is a little try-hard...
Yeah, well, it's not like
I went and loosened it myself.
Yeah, well, at least
I don't go and make up
my own silly superhero names
like Atom and Heat Wave.
Like I care what you think.
[gasps]
I wanna grow my hair out
to look like Fabio.
Right, I think that'd be good.
So, honestly,
even as much as I trust Sara,
this has been
one disaster after another,
and I really think that this time,
we are totally screwed.
[Sara sighs]
Captain, we're okay, right?
I mean, we just
have to focus on the mission.
Yeah, Mona, we're gonna be fine.
[gasps]
[groans]
Of course we're not fine, Mona!
Nothing is fine,
and I am definitely not fine.
Ava and I didn't just
get into an argument.
She asked me to leave, and she
hasn't answered any of my calls since.
And she was my one chance,
my one chance, Mona, at something real.
And now, I don't have a ship,
I don't have a girlfriend,
and I am the captain of an RV,
and it is all your fault!
Well, I won't be your problem anymore.
- [door opens]
- [sighs]
Mona! Mona, wait!
Mona, come back!
Look, I meant everything I said,
but if you stay here in 1973,
you'll never survive!
John, get this thing out of me!
[chanting]
[spits]
All right, you guys
get Nixon to Florida.
If you leave now,
there'll be time to spare.
What about you?
Mona's out there alone,
and we don't leave our people behind,
no matter how much
they bug the crap out of us.
I'd say no pun intended,
but that would be a lie.
- Here you go, mate. Hold that, will you?
- What? Where are you going?
I just need to stretch my legs, squire.
You all right, Dad?
You didn't finish your ice cream.
- Put on your seat belt.
- What's the hurry?
The Legends' RVwas spotted
just outside Richmond.
My men are setting up a blockade.
They won't get away this time.
That's great. That's great!
[whooping]
This is what I dreamed about
when I joined the Bureau.
Stealing a cop car?
You and me working together.
Uh, yeah, well... Ooh.
You know what, Dad,
that ice cream is not agreeing with me.
Can you, uh... [clears throat]
Can you pull over?
[exhales heavily]
[Nate] Z? Z, can you hear me?
Nate, is that you?
Hey, listen, I need you
to warn the team.
Hank's got a blockade on the highway
north of Richmond.
They gotta find another route.
You got it?
Roger. Over and out.
There you go, hon.
- [agent 1] All right, what do you want?
- [agent 2] Whatever's fast and cheap.
[Mona] Oh, no, please, no.
Can I get six Daphne House burgers
and a round of sodas?
[waitress] Comin' up.
Sara, hold up. Hey!
How do you even know where she went?
Bike treads went this way,
we passed a diner a while back,
- she's probably headed there.
- Hmm.
Go ahead.
I know you've been dying to say,
"I told you so," so, just do it.
It was quite the opposite, actually.
I wanted to see how you're holdin' up.
[sighs] Honestly, I'm freaking out.
With the Kaupe dead and Mona in
the wind, and then there's Ava, and...
[sighs]
What happened?
I went to go talk to her and...
And I thought everything was
gonna be fine, 'cause it's always fine,
and... It was bad, John.
I don't know how to convince everybody
that everything's okay
when I'm not okay.
Well, you know, if we were
in each other's shoes right now,
then you'd be giving me
some rubbish speech
about how you don't have to
shoulder the burden myself,
when I have friends around me
to help me carry it.
Not that I believe you for a second,
but that doesn't mean it's not true.
Thanks.
Even if you're just lying
to make me feel better.
No, I definitely am.
Hope it worked, though.
- You all right there?
- Yeah. I'm great.
Let's grab some tunes.
- No, no, no.
- Hey!
[turns on radio]
[Zari] I just got a white-hot tip.
That voice sounds familiar.
I don't recognize her... Or him.
I don't hear gender.
[Zari] There's a smoky checkpoint
outside Richmond.
If you wanna make it
to your final destination,
do yourself a favor and take Route 301
all the way home, bandits.
Sounds like we're takin' a detour.
[tires screeching]
Dad, Dad, Dad!
[siren wailing]
Are you insane?
You could have got us killed.
Yeah, you're still here, ain't ya?
- Yeah, but we're going the wrong way!
- No. We're right on target.
All units,
Legends are headed down Route 301.
Reroute all units to converge
on their location, now!
Come on. I'm not gonna miss a chance
to get back at the Legends for Mexico.
They're gonna get what they deserve
for trying to protect that wolf bastard!
[Mona] His name was Konane.
[agent] What?
Wait. I remember you.
You're the one Director Heywood fired.
You're the reason that mutt got out
of the containment facility
in the first place.
I said, his name was Konane.
[grunting]
[roaring]
There's Mona's bike. Where is she?
Where is everybody?
Yeah. I know this kind of quiet,
and it never means anything good.
- Everybody out!
- [people screaming]
[growling]
Mona.
I'll do it. I'll shoot!
The Kaupe must have scratched her.
She tried to tell me...
And I didn't listen.
- Mona, put him down!
- Come on, love, this isn't you.
[roars]
- [agent 1] Stop the RV!
- [agent 2] Step out of the vehicle!
[Ray] What are we gonna do?
- We can't drive through 'em.
- Kill 'em.
- What?
- Kill 'em all.
- No!
- Yes.
- Yes!
- No! No...
[siren wiling]
Nate's here.
I'm sure we can talk this all out.
You wanna do the honors, son?
Damn right, Dad.
All right. Don't worry, buddy,
I'll get you out of this.
Hey, Mr. Heywood,
if we could just talk about this,
I'm sure we can explain and show you how
this is just one big misunderstanding...
How's that
for a misunderstanding, you pig!
By the power vested to me
by the United States government,
I hereby arrest both of you
on five charges of treason,
- two of conspiracy, and...
- [agent] Uh... Sir?
Mr. President, are you all right?
No!
These two men and their
co-conspirators kidnapped me.
They've besmirched my good name
and I've done nothing to deserve it.
Uh-oh!
[hissing]
[gulps]
Well, actually, there is nothing good
about my name.
If you were born with
the name "Dick Milhous,"
you'd grow up to be a bastard, too.
- [sighs]
- [chuckles]
What the hell?
Listen to me, Mona.
No one else needs to get hurt.
[chanting]
[grunts]
I'm sorry about that, love.
Bloody hell!
[Mona growling]
Mona, can you hear me?
Come on, I know you're in there!
Look, it's me! It's Sara.
I know it's you, Sara.
I remember everything.
You pretended to be a friend.
- I looked up to you!
- Mona...
It was all lies.
Mr. President, what is going on?
I don't know! I'm supposed
to be in Florida, lying to the press.
He ingested a truth bug.
See, these blunders are the exact reason
why we should lock up the Legends.
Nathaniel, are you all right?
No, I'm not.
I've been keeping secrets from you.
You think I don't know that?
But it's more than
your secret Pentagon side project.
It's always been like this, Dad.
The lying,
and the hiding of the feelings...
Now that I'm getting to be honest,
I just wanna tell you I love you,
but you just make it so damn hard.
Look, son, you don't understand.
And I like working with you
at the Time Bureau, side by side.
I've never felt closer to you.
But now, I'm having like a hard time
even looking in your face.
Just tell me why.
Why are you doing all this?
Why are you pretending
that we are on the same side?
I can't.
But everything I've done
has been for you.
And the fact that it's hurting you,
Nate, it's killing me.
But I wanna make this right.
Okay.
You let the Legends walk.
That, or you lock me up, too.
Because if you don't trust them,
then you and I are not on the same side.
Stand down!
The Legends are free to go.
From now on, we work together.
No more lies.
[roaring]
[Constantine grunting]
Watch yourself, love.
She's not in her right mind.
No, that's the problem.
She is.
Mona, look, please stop.
I should've never blamed you
for everything.
Look, Ava, the ship, Konane,
none of it was your fault.
And I am so sorry
that I told you to ignore your feelings.
It was because I thought...
Look, I thought that if I could
forget the way that I was feeling,
then maybe, it wouldn't hurt so bad.
Look, Mona, I was wrong. I was so wrong.
And you don't have to
bury your feelings.
You can let them out.
[sniffles]
[panting]
And if you ever need a shoulder
to lean on, I will be there.
You promise?
I promise.
[chuckles]
- Are you guys okay?
- Yes. No, I don't know.
First time in my adult life,
I told my dad I love him.
Years of therapy
couldn't even get me to do that.
Hey, speaking of, I love you so big,
I love you so big...
- I love you so big.
- Aw! [chuckles]
Look, I don't always
agree with you, but, uh...
If Nathaniel trusts you, then so do I.
You're free to fly if
you can get that ship of yours working.
[Gideon] Someone ask for a lift?
Ship was never broken, was it?
Nope, it was Zari the whole time.
Is she even your girlfriend?
Nope, but I'm open to it.
[laughing] Fat chance.
Come on, you poor bastard,
let's delouse you
and get that truth bug
contained for good, yeah?
[Ray] And Nixon here
has an important speech to deliver.
Let's get you back to Orlando.
You know,
the truth really does set you free.
After spending a few days
with all of you,
I know that I can be a better leader.
And even more so, a better man.
Ah... History needs you, crooked Dick!
Who are you?
I really think
I'm gonna miss this thing.
Yeah, if I had to be
stuck on a road trip,
at least it was with you guys.
You know, maybe that's what family is.
The people you don't mind
being annoyed by.
[Ray scoffs]
So, you don't mind being annoyed by me?
Are you saying I can stay?
We could always use
another shoulder to lean on.
Besides, you're not the first magical
creature that we've taken in.
[Ray gasps]
- We forgot Charlie!
Hey, Nate, hold up.
Gary, he surprisingly got
to the bottom of things.
It's not good.
Your dad's embezzling funds for some
black-site operation in Baltimore.
But he's not just taking the fugitives,
he's testing on them.
But why?
I don't know, but I've seen this
before with A.R.G.U.S.
This is what they were doing to metas
to turn them into supersoldiers.
[clears throat]
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Now, I know who my father really is.
Hank says he's doing this for me.
I want nothing to do with it, or him.
Hey, I'm sorry.
[sighs]
Yeah.
[beeps]
You called.
A little late for a meeting.
This better be good.
When you came to me,
I agreed to this plan
because I saw the potential
in your vision, and I still do.
Don't tell me
you're having second thoughts.
[eerie indistinct voices]
[gasping]
I mean no disrespect.
I value the work that we've done,
and I understand why it needs
to remain top-secret.
But I have a new partner now.
My son.
And I can't let anything
come between us.
What are you saying, Henry?
I'm saying that
I don't need you anymore.
If that's the case,
I don't need you anymore, either.
[gasps] No!
You're gonna have to let me
out of here.
You need to let me out of here! Gary!
Anybody!
[Hank] No! No!
[groaning]
[screaming]
[Hank] Please, no! No.
Somebody help me.
Help me!
[screaming]
[grunts]
No! No, no, no!
[Nate] Dad?
Nate!
- What did you do?
- I didn't...
What did you do?
[sighs]
Nate. Listen... Listen to me.
She's right there.
I'm sorry.
[groans]
[theme music playing]