Total mind-bender, right?
You have no idea
how many times
I've stumbled across
one of my dead bodies.
When I said I'm gonna save
all of humanity starting with you,
I wasn't lying.
But tragically, there is no antidote
for a Zaguron sting.
See, what I gave you was a primer...
The nanobots have
completed their scan.
...so I could make a new you.
Transition can be tough.
Sara 2.0, alive and well,
and that's just the beginning.
Hey, wait. Come here.
I gotta... I gotta let you in
on a little secret,
all right, David freaking Bowie?
'Cause tonight, tonight
I am going to propose
to my girlfriend!
Ah!
Hey. Hey, wait, wait, wait. Come here.
I gotta... I gotta let you in
on a little secret,
all right, David freaking Bowie?
'Cause tonight, tonight, I am...
I wanted to check on you.
Gideon said you haven't been eating.
I'm not hungry.
Ava, you gotta eat.
What's the point?
She's gone, Nate.
- I'm just... done, okay?
- Okay.
If you need anything,
I guess, you're gonna ask Gideon,
but I'm here for you, too.
We all are.
Thanks.
How's everybody else doing?
They're grieving in their own way.
How is she?
Worse. She still won't eat,
and Gideon made her favorite quiche.
What about that bloody video?
Still watching it on a loop.
We gotta do something.
We just need to give her some space.
When I lost Behrad,
that's what I needed.
Speaking of, where's B?
Oh, he won't leave the lab.
He's taking Sara's death
almost as hard as Ava.
All right, so we'll give Ava space,
but as your reluctant
default interim captain,
I'm ordering the rest of us
to stay together for moral support.
I'll go get B.
You know what, I'll come with.
You're more of a reluctant
default interim co-captain.
What about Rory?
If Sara's dead, then...
I think Rory's like a cockroach,
that bugger will survive anything.
Yeah.
That was great.
Whoa.
Except for the ear thing.
You want to go again?
Why don't you see if Bishop
put the barrier back up?
How can I tell if it's safe?
You just did.
Once you're done with that,
we rescue Sara.
Once I'm done, I'm off this planet.
- What? You owe me.
- For the sex?
I saved your life.
This for that,
such a human way of thinking.
You have until the third moon sets.
Deal.
Oh, finally! Do you mind?
Much better. Ooh!
I hate having broken bones.
They make these awful
crunching sounds.
Now, where was I?
Oh, yes, the plan. You're gonna love it.
Merging alien and human DNA.
I knew that was the answer,
but it turns out, that kind of merger
requires an awesome degree
of mental fortitude.
Hard to find mental fortitude,
but you know who's got it in spades?
I'll give you three guesses.
Never mind. I'll give you zero.
I got them off these
old romance novels by some lady,
Rebecca... Steel?
No, Gold... Mmm, Silver!
Anyway. Your story was so inspiring.
Resilience, it seems, is the key.
Otherwise, we get
an Amelia Earhart situation.
You're sick.
You wanna see something sick?
Check this out.
Hmm?
Photoshop Ava put
this concept art together.
See? That's you,
and that's you, and that's you,
but also not you.
A better you.
They're Alien-Sara Lance hybrids
and together we'll
colonize every planet in the galaxy
and begin the next chapter
of the human race.
You're gonna put millions
of alien mes
onto planets billions of miles away?
What are you? Six?
It's cloud printing
Uh-uh.
This... is a symbol
of your old life.
You need to engage
With your future
Why would I help you?
Because I died and you cloned me?
I die about once a year
and my girlfriend's a clone.
Now, I'm gonna get off this planet,
and I'm gonna propose to her
with that ring.
Now give it back to me. Son of a...
Bummer. Thought this version
of you would be cooler.
Take her to the incinerator.
I'll just keep tinkering until I get
a version that cooperates.
No version of me will ever help you!
I love that fighting spirit
Oh! And save the dress.
I'd hate to waste
such a fine piece of silk.
This is B Squad. Delta sector's clear.
I really hate clones.
We don't care for you either.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Give him some time,
Mick's, uh... an acquired taste.
Gary.
I believe the words you're
looking for are, uh, "Thank you."
B?
That's weird.
That's his thinking music.
Uh, Gidget, where's my brother?
Mr. Tarazi
is not on the Waverider.
Oh, no.
It's his thinking weed.
As your reluctant
default interim co-captain,
we need to work on our shorthand
because I don't understand you.
Oh, no.
Guys, we need backup.
I was born with spikes.
Where are we?
Last year's finale.
What's a finale?
You'll see. They're pretty fun.
I mean, except for the one
where I died.
Okay, shh, so,
has anyone seen our Behrad?
Hey, hey, hey.
There he is.
The Smell is up next.
I bloody love The Smell.
Hey, did you think
we wouldn't notice?
There are a million reasons
why I shouldn't do this,
but I'll stop Sara from being abducted
and dying and you can't stop me.
Stop you?
We're here to help you do it right.
Yeah.
Should we really be strategizing
across from The Hole?
None of us came here
that night, mate.
The only other building in the area
was a fireworks factory.
Hey, so, what's the plan, bro?
All right, we need to get Sara
onto the Waverider
before the aliens arrive.
I'm thinking, fire alarm.
No, The Hole
doesn't have fire alarms.
The place is a death trap.
I felt like I was back in hell.
- Why don't we ask Ava for a plan?
- No, no, no, no.
Ava would never allow
something like this. It's too risky.
It's up to us to save Sara
without interacting
with our former selves.
So, at any point during the night,
did anyone slip away
that would give us
a window to step in?
Honestly, mate,
that night was a blur.
Do you remember anything?
Well, I said goodbye forever
to the love of my life,
so, yeah, it went pretty hard. Blur.
Look, if we can pull this off,
we not only save Sara,
but we prevent aliens
from scattering across the timeline.
Wait, if there are never any aliens,
I never look for Spooner.
And I never join you.
I mean, y'all are great,
but there were perks to my old life.
You know, never getting attacked
by alien Amelia Earhart,
never getting turned into a fork.
That was one time.
Don't trust you.
All right. Smoke o'clock.
Wait. That's it.
I smoke every night at midnight
and tonight,
I went on the roof to smoke.
That means the other you
is not involved.
And I could get Sara
on the Waverider!
"Sara, the Fates are back."
Nah, too obvious.
"Sara, your sister and dad called."
Are they even alive in this timeline?
B?
Yes, it's me,
your current friend, Behrad.
Okay.
You're needed
on the Waverider immediately.
It's a Timequake wave-mergency.
That's the beauty
of having a time machine.
I can always
just go back in time and fix it.
But, Sara...
B, look, I'm not gonna go, all right?
I'm gonna tell you
a little secret.
Okay.
I just picked this up,
because I am going to propose
to Ava tonight.
Where'd you get this?
Versailles? The Romanovs?
My mom.
Go figure.
Sara Lance, old school romantic.
Yeah, you know me,
and tonight is the night
and nothing,
not even a timeline emergency,
is gonna get in my way.
There you are.
- Hey.
What are you two doing?
Just talking rings,
- fates, looms...
- Yeah.
- ...you know, recap stuff?
- Mmm.
Whoa. Wasn't that silver streak
in your hair
on the other side before?
Yeah, actually.
Oh.
Babe, Charlie's about to go on.
- Yes, let's go.
- Come on.
- I'll meet you inside.
You're not coming?
Smoke o'clock.
Oh.
Stop!
Avas are on our side.
They're helping us rescue you.
- Us?
- Yeah.
Mick, oh, my God. You're alive.
He flew here with Kayla.
Wait, why didn't she try to eat you?
- We gotta go.
- I can't until I stop Bishop.
He's got this crazy
intergalactic plan
to try to clone me.
A planet of cloned Avas and Saras?
Are we sure we want to stop that?
Um, I speak for all the Avas when I say
it would be an honor
to help thwart him.
Great. How do we do it?
Redundancy is Bishop's religion.
If we take down one generator,
the backup kicks in.
But I guess if we destroy them
all simultaneously,
his operation would go down.
You better make it fast.
When those moons set, Kayla's gone.
All right, let's split up.
We can cover more ground.
I'll get some explosives.
Thank you for finding me.
The ship sucked without you.
Come on.
Sara's not leaving
until she proposes to Ava.
Yeah, but Sara never
proposed that night.
Why not?
No clue.
But if we get Sara to propose,
she can get on the ship
before the aliens.
Unfortunately, we were all
with Sara the rest of the night.
Not all of us.
Do you two have something you want
to share with the rest of the class?
There is a 20-minute window
where we'll be
out of the picture.
More like a generous ten.
- Fifteen.
- Eight.
Just go get Sara to propose.
Where the bloody hell is Sara, eh?
Hey, girl!
Hi.
Have you seen Sara?
Yeah, she's in the bathroom. Why?
She borrowed my makeup,
and John needs it now.
You look great.
So good to see you.
Sara, are you all right?
Are you pissed?
No, I think
I just need to drink more,
and a mint.
She's nervous about proposing.
Wait, how did you...
Ugh!
Behrad!
Yeah, you listen to me, all right?
You are Sara freaking Lance.
Now, who's gonna turn you down, eh?
Now, go out there,
get on bended knee,
you put a ring on it
and you take that lady home
to celebrate, okay?
'Cause you deserve it.
What's it to you?
What?
I just love love.
"You just love love"?
Yeah.
Hey, Charlie, is that you?
Just stop messing with me,
all right?
I'm gonna do it my way, in my time.
God.
- Hey, what was that?
- What was what?
Willingness to go along
with a crazy plan,
corny lines about love.
This is somehow about you.
You don't have your magic,
do you?
And before?
- Astra covered for me.
- Yup.
Rehab's not working, all right?
I say the words,
but I can't... rekindle the flame.
Resetting the timeline,
it's my only chance
of getting my magic back.
Yeah, and you thought telling Sara
you love love would be your best bet?
- Too much?
- Yeah.
Right.
- Hey, John.
- Yeah?
No more lies.
- The words.
- No more lies.
Good. Okay.
Now we have to find the team
and come up with a plan C
to save Sara.
Yeah, and a plan D to save me.
Wow.
- She's nervous?
- How do we fix that?
Hey!
I knew it.
Oh! Hey, girl.
Uh, we were just...
Celebrating the finale.
By eating mushroom curry like we do!
You and those Shake Weights?
Sisqó, am I right?
Don't even.
I know you're not my Legends, okay?
And where am I, huh?
Nowhere. Which is how I know
that whatever you're all doing
is a terrible idea. Okay?
Am I dead? No, never mind.
Don't answer that, please.
Did you nod your head?
- Hmm?
- Okay, girl, you're right.
We are from the future.
But we have a really good reason.
No, no, stop.
I don't wanna hear any more words.
How many missions
is it gonna take
for you to realize
that you can't
change the past.
It always causes millions of ripples.
That's the danger
of what you're doing here.
It is chaos to the timeline.
- So, you're taking our drinks?
- No.
They're for me, because, now,
I have to get blackout drunk
to forget that this ever happened.
Damn it. Mmm!
All of you, back to your timelines.
- I'm not even kidding. That's an order.
- Oh!
Jeez. I don't think y'all
would be this upset about losing me.
This isn't about me, is it?
Come on! I'm walkin' here.
Arriving at the last
generator now, Mick.
Aah!
Oh, no.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine. It's just...
Wow.
Have you always been able to do that?
Regeneration.
Bishop. What did he do?
I swear I have no idea.
Finish up here.
Stand by on blowing up the generators.
There's someone I gotta see first.
It's got me swingin' to the beat
Whoa, yeah
You really got me going...
What have you done to me?
Shouldn't you be... Oh, the Avas.
That one's on me.
Should have seen it coming.
What did you do?
Show-and-tell time.
What the hell is that?
That... is you.
I merged you with this beauty,
making you the Eve
of alien human hybrids.
You're welcome.
This is getting a bit tiresome.
What's the big plan?
You're gonna kill me? Again?
Not this time.
No new Bishops.
You're stuck with this one.
Now tell me
how to make myself human again.
This is just your pain cycle
speaking, Sara.
Look past your rage, Sara,
and imagine the possibilities.
You with wings.
You with the ability to live
in sub-zero temperatures.
Fun!
You've fought so hard
to save the timeline, but for what?
Humanity has no future without me,
without us.
So what do you say?
Hard pass.
And if you won't fix me,
then I'll make
a clean clone of myself
and then,
I'm gonna blow up this place
and get the hell off this planet.
Good luck with that.
No generators means
no electrostatic barrier,
which means, yes, Zagurons.
If I were you,
I wouldn't book a venue
for your wedding just yet.
Goodbye, Bishop.
Behind y'all.
Mmm. Thank you.
Ew.
I mean,
honestly, leave it to Ava
to bring up some very valid concerns.
Very valid concernitunities.
Exactly. We need to get creative.
We need to find a way
to get Sara back
and make sure
everything stays the same.
So, our present doesn't change.
And I still join the Legends.
Shh. Okay, so, how?
I might have a way.
With a mannequin?
No!
With an exploding mannequin.
Ava.
- There you are.
- Can you make a clean version of me?
Me? No.
Bishop does all the cloning.
He's the brilliant scientist.
Yeah, but you were
the brilliant nurse who helped him.
Hmm?
I know that you can do this.
All right? I trust you.
Sara, the generators
are ready to blow.
Give me that.
We have to get to the ship now.
You go. I'll meet you there.
Did she just hang up on me?
How many bowls is that?
What's the point of time travel
if I can't enjoy the local cuisine?
B, I love you, and I co-sign your
creativity 100%, but this plan is...
- Is rubbish, mate.
- Yeah.
Those fireworks need to go off.
at just the right time,
in just the right place
with just the right amount of force.
I don't like those odds.
And that hair is trag.
The alien is definitely gonna know.
Gary is on the ship.
He'll pick up
what I'm laying down here.
I had Gideon run a reverse model
on the pods' disbursement.
And accounting for temporal drift,
in 12 hours and 14 minutes,
the ship will be
in the exact location it was
when Sara sent aliens
into the timeline.
The bomb goes boom,
scattering aliens
across the timeline.
We get our Sara back.
All I need now
is my woman on the inside.
All right, I'm here. Now what?
Keep your eyes peeled.
Let me know when the Legends
are on the move.
And whatever you do,
don't interact with Sara.
Look, I don't even know the lady.
What would I possibly say to her?
Hey. How's it going?
Rough night?
I've been having a weird one myself.
Cheers.
So, lay it on me.
Oh, come on. I could use a distraction.
What the hell.
Twenty years ago,
I was abducted by aliens.
But they did something to me,
and ever since, I, uh...
I feel things,
hear voices from aliens,
and it's freaking me out.
What if there's something
inside me that I can't control?
And the people I live with,
well, they're gonna think
I'm some kind of monster.
And now you think I'm crazy.
Crazy is the word people use
when they're afraid
of what you're capable of.
I'm not afraid. I am intrigued.
Man, you really are cool.
Look, it sounds like
you're on the beginning
of an amazing journey.
And if I could give you
one piece of advice from experience,
don't go at it alone.
What if I hurt them?
What if they help you?
What if I can't live up
to their expectations?
Hmm.
Yeah, I feel you on that one.
I was supposed to propose
to my girlfriend tonight,
and then I realized
that she's probably gonna say yes.
That's great, right?
I have been
so many different people in my life,
and I'm worried
that this version of me
might just be a phase.
And I would get a lifetime
of the woman I love,
but I can't promise
she'd get the same in return.
Look, I just met you,
and I certainly
don't know your girlfriend,
but, uh, my gut tells me
that she can handle change.
It might even be good for her.
And what if I hurt her?
What if you help her?
We're The Smell.
Welcome to the best show
of your lives, you wankers!
She's perfect just the way she is.
Maybe just a cup of coffee
before I propose.
Maybe two.
You lads are out of this world.
David freaking Bowie?
- You're a Smell fan?
- They're something else.
Wait. I gotta...
I gotta let you in on a little secret,
all right, David freaking Bowie?
Because tonight...
Tonight, I am going
to propose to my girlfriend. Ah!
Okay. Yes, yes, yes.
Okay. Well, girl, at least
you stand a fighting chance
of getting through the door now-ish.
Are bombs
supposed to make that sound?
That's not a bomb. That's not a bomb.
- Ew!
- Ooh!
Man of steel,
intestines of Play-Doh.
Bring this to the bathroom.
I'll need it in 90 seconds.
- No.
- Who are you?
I'm Nate from the timeline
you're currently creating
with that blonde bomb again.
Why are you wearing my coat?
Shh. Let it happen.
Because of your stupid plan,
this bomb drops the aliens
in New York during the Gilded Age.
They take over Wall Street.
John, you're poisoned
by a califax in the trading pit.
I got to go undercover as Constantine
and join a magic cult
to stop this invasion.
- What about Sara?
- What about her?
It's a mannequin, B.
Gary and his alien friends
just make a U-turn
and come back and grab her.
I'm sorry, she's gone.
- Hey.
B, Sara's
heading out to the parking lot.
I'm not gonna let her die.
B, no!
I could have used that a minute ago.
So, what did I miss?
I'm really gonna miss you guys.
- We'll miss you.
- All right, go on.
Get out of here.
Go and enjoy your vacations.
You've earnt it.
Whoo!
Vacation.
- Vaca...
- Vacacione!
Vacacione!
- Vacation.
- Sara!
Sara, listen to me.
When you...
No!
Ugh! Those idiots are trying to save me.
They'll destroy the timeline
if I don't get back there soon.
I'm almost done.
What will you do after we print?
Human me will go home,
and then this me will stay here.
You sure you want...
All right.
How long is this gonna take?
With these new specifications,
ten minutes.
Well, let's just hope Rory and Gary
don't get too antsy.
Sara.
Well, well,
look who I underestimated.
Where's Sara?
I can arrange for you
to see her most expeditiously.
Ah,
that's much better.
No, no, no. You ruined everything.
He's a psychopath.
Now, he's a dead psychopath.
He's not dead. He's everywhere.
Sara definitely picked the right Ava.
The rest of you are nuts.
Much obliged, Mr. Rory,
for giving my transformation
such poetry.
Damn it. It doesn't matter.
You won't have time to reprint
before I blow this place up.
You're thinking too small again, Sara.
Why be where you're not wanted
when the universe has offered
a standing invitation.
Oh, no. His consciousness is digital,
and he's uploading it to the cloud.
Once that upload's complete,
he can print himself
- from anywhere...
- Anywhere in the universe.
- Exactly.
- All right, so we stop it.
The only way to do that
is to detonate the generators.
How long until he's uploaded?
Three minutes.
What will you do, Sara,
save yourself or stop me?
What a sticky little wicket.
Can't this thing
print any faster?
Leaving your fate
in the hands of a printer?
I'm disappointed.
- Make a choice, Sara.
- Shut up.
What is that?
It's me.
What?
- I died.
- Again?
Yeah. But this time,
I didn't make it back.
- So, who am I talking to?
- A monster.
Which is why you need to make sure
that you take this version of me
home with you, all right?
This body, it's not me.
Uh, one minute until
Bishop's upload is complete.
- Then blow it.
- No, don't, don't.
I can't go back
to the team half-alien.
What if I hurt you guys,
what if I hurt Ava?
Listen, that creep can't get away.
That creep changed me, Rory.
Look, I don't even know
what I am anymore, all right?
You cannot see it, but I'm damaged.
Damaged?
No, I see someone
who has been through hell,
but never stopped being herself.
I see Captain Lance.
I see Sara, my oldest friend.
We need you.
Please.
Let's get out of here.
Hmm.
Come on.
Gary, let's blow this place.
No!
Whoo!
We did it! Viva la Avalucion!
Let's move.
Okay. So, once the barrier's gone,
it'll be cold
and you'll need masks to breathe.
You'll need these
to fend off the Zagurons.
They hate light. Okay. Good luck
You sure you won't come?
This is my home.
Are you gonna be okay?
We're a team of trained warriors,
medics, engineers and gourmet chefs.
We'll be fine.
The Zagurons
have broken past the barrier.
We gotta go.
Mick, you out there?
- The third moon has set.
- She'll wait.
How can you be so sure?
I just am.
Kayla wouldn't leave without me.
Where's the ship?
Don't take it personally, Mick.
Let's move.
Ah! Let's go, go, go, go!
She came back for me.
Well, I guess
you were right about Kayla.
Those dirt rats were starting
to scratch off the finish,
so I had to get
my ship off the ground.
You're Kayla?
And you're still the woman
who almost destroyed my ship.
If we're done standing around,
let's get off this stinking planet.
Whoa!
Kayla!
Help! Help!
Mick!
Yeah, Sara!
Kayla!
Mick.
Get Kayla's ship ready to go.
- On it.
- Mick, we gotta go.
- I'm not leaving without her.
- We'll wait inside the ship.
Guys, we've got incoming.
Gary, get this bird in the air.
Aye-aye, Captain.
Are you okay?
It's my fault. I got Sara abducted.
If I'd never tried to warn her,
she just would have kept walking.
Never would have been
sucked up into space.
I'm sure they would have
gotten her elsewhere,
but, all right, you convinced me.
It's all your fault.
You have
an unorthodox comforting style.
Yeah, we didn't really do a lot
of comforting where I grew up.
Look, if you hadn't
tried to save her,
you'd have spent
the rest of your life wondering,
"What if I had?"
I should know.
You still miss her, your mom?
Every day.
But losing her brought me here,
and that's not all bad.
I'd say it's pretty good.
Hey, you two.
- I'm sorry, Behrad-jaan.
- I learned the hard way, mate.
Some things can't be changed.
I'm still here.
I'm guessing the plan didn't work.
Well, there's one silver lining.
I just can't believe she's gone.
Legends never die.
I could use a drink.
I'll second that, love.
I gotta let you in
on a little secret,
all right, David freaking Bowie?
'Cause tonight, tonight,
I am going to propose
to my girlfriend. Ah!
to my girlfriend.
Gideon, what's happening?
My apologies, Captain Sharpe.
It appears
the file has been corrupted.
Come on. This can't be happening.
God.
Ava.
It's really you?
Yeah, babe, it's me.
I don't want to turn around,
because I'm afraid if I do,
you'll disappear.
I'm not going anywhere ever again,
I promise.
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
I am now.
I can't believe this.
- Ava will want to know I'm okay, too.
- No, she won't.
Do the rest of the Legends
know you're here?
Hmm.
Now that you've mentioned it,
it was eerily quiet.
Maybe they went to John's.
Oh.
Nope. I know exactly where they went.
Tonight, we talk the best
of Sara Lance.
Yep.
The tallest tales.
It's time to write the Legend.
Who wants to go first?
Hey, I will.
Yes!
I knew it in my bones.
Oh, my God. Is this really real?
Oh, my God. I missed your hair.
Oh, Mick, you salty, bloody bastard.
I can't believe you did it.
You saved her. Well done.
I'm so proud of you.
I never lost faith.
Oh, look who it is.
Alien Gary, who kidnapped Sara.
No, I can explain that. That's not...
He didn't kidnap me, he saved me.
Be honest.
Rory flew up to the planet,
but it was really me
that saved you, right?
Yeah, B.
Let's, uh, go with that one.
All right, you guys.
What do you think, huh?
Let's go home.
- Let's go home!
- Yes, please. Let's go. Come on.
Tonight got me thinking,
what if I don't get my magic back?
Okay.
But I've still got you.
You do.
But I know you're gonna try.
I'll turn hell upside down, love.
Well, it's gonna come in handy having
a superhero girlfriend then.
Yeah.
Those two sure got serious.
I have so much to tell you
when we get back to the ship.
- I cannot even...
- Time travel is so weird.
And here we are again.
It's like nothing has changed,
and yet everything's
changed at the same time.
Yes, but tonight,
I'm not leaving you behind.
And tonight,
I want to propose to my girlfriend.
No.
Oh!
Oh, my God. It's happening.
Ava...
Yes, I will.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm so excited. Please finish.
"When I was up there in space,
floating further and further away,
I realized something.
No matter where I go or when I am,
I will never be lost,
because I have you.
You are my North Star,
you are my guiding light.
And wherever you lead me,
that's my home."
Do I say yes now?
No, not yet.
Ava Sharpe...
will you marry me?
This is when you say it.
Yes, yes! Yes, baby.
You remembered to take the bomb
out of the mannequin, right?