Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow.
Astra, this place, it's twisted you.
It's made me more like you.
When you took on the wand's power,
you also took on its charge.
Oh, Fairy Godmother.
Go find John
and help him rescue Ray from hell.
Gary, you dick.
I have created a simple app.
You will be able to share
monster sightings.
"In exchange for this service,
the user agrees to forfeit
their eternal soul
to the demon Neron."
He may be planning a monster attack.
Get every single one
of those monsters
out of the Time Bureau.
It's a bloody jailbreak.
No.
What kind of egg is that?
It's a dragon egg.
My name is Zari.
Whoopsie. Hey.
You haven't happened to see
an ogre wandering around
about high, likes to grunt,
drink beer?
Ask Rory.
Ogre wins again.
Cheating bastard.
No one outdrinks Mick Rory.
Hey, fellas.
Sorry to break up all the fun,
but technically,
I wasn't supposed to allow
any magical creatures
out of the lab, so...
On second thought,
why don't you two finish up here?
And I'll go, track down the Minotaur.
You're not a horrible mother.
You just have a lot on your mind.
I left our dragon egg
in the care of 9-year-old me.
Has anybody seen Gary?
- Wait, what did you just say?
- I was distracted.
I just found out the Eyes app
is stealing peoples' souls,
and then baby me comes home,
and I...
You two need to grab that egg
before it hatches.
We can't risk Ne-ray getting
his hands on a baby dragon.
It's already bad enough
that he has Charlie.
- Okay.
- Fair.
Get up. Time's a wasting.
There are souls just waiting
to be sold.
You're off your rocker, you old nag.
This here shape-shifter
don't take requests.
Shape-shifter?
Is that all you think you are?
You may have
your human friends fooled, dearie,
but you and I both know
what you're truly capable of.
- You don't know me.
- Don't I?
The shape your wearing,
though lovely, is a costume.
It's not who you really are.
You aren't meant to hide, my pet.
You are meant to show humans
their greatest fears.
And lucky for you,
helping monsters
fulfill their potential...
is what I do.
Yes.
Damn it, Gary.
Oh, excuse me, hey. Hi.
Excuse me, sir.
Hi, pardon me,
I just, I don't belong here.
No? And I'm a...
I'm a Fairy Godmother sent
to find John Constantine.
Really?
What, are the King and Queen
of hell
making their grand debut?
Not our debut, dearie.
No, no, no. Stop.
What are you doing?
As much as I'd like to pontificate
about my grander plan...
I've taught him better than that.
- Who the hell are you?
- Really? The dress doesn't sell it?
You didn't tell me you had
a Fairy Godmother, John.
Not his, Gary's.
And I thought I was the one
being tortured.
Look, Princess,
we got rules here in hell.
All right? You can't just...
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Going to find Ray,
same way I found you.
The only difference
is Ray doesn't have a body.
So let's go find his soul.
His soul token,
that's the currency in hell.
While a soul is being tortured,
then its token is traded
around town like money.
As long as you have it,
then you'll always
have access to the soul.
But since Neron is still topside,
then his token's likely
locked in his vault.
Then let's go find it.
- Why isn't this working?
- I'm sorry, love.
You can't just go poofing yourself
into the vaults of hell.
We'll have to find someone
to help us break in.
And I think I know just the person.
I don't see her.
How do you know
what 9 year old me looks like?
I'm just looking for
the coolest kid in school.
Yeah, there's a lot
I haven't told you
about my childhood.
There, that's the spot
where kids used to gang up on me
and say, "Zari, Zari,
why your clothes so sorry?"
I would have said, "Zari, Zari,
you smell like calamari."
Bullying is bad.
All right, let's break this up
and find out where I stashed the egg.
- He's so cool.
- Oh, look how cute he is.
- I want a dragon.
- He's so adorable.
Come here.
I want to take him home with me.
Oh, my God, he hatched.
And I brought him to school.
Okay, so we got to get him
- before...
- Whoa, wait. Look.
Mithra, dance.
So cool.
- Awesome, Zari.
- Thank you.
Come on.
What's going on, children?
It's okay. He's my pet, Mithra.
- I named him after the...
- Run, children.
It's a monster.
Wait, Zari. Zari, wait. Wait.
Don't hurt him.
Oh, my God, I lost him again.
Captain, I've located Neron.
Now live to Capitol Hill,
where the Palmer X CEO is testifying
before the Senate subcommittee.
Look, I know Senator Wellington
doesn't believe that
it's up to the private sector
to intervene in such
a unprecedented crisis.
But I should mention,
not a single one
of my subscribers has been harmed
in a monster attack.
Senator, do you care to respond?
This bloke is just trying
to scare folks
into downloading his evil,
soul-sucking app.
There ain't no such thing
as monst...
This isn't me.
I'm not doing this.
Like I said, they could be
hiding anywhere...
and only you can stop them.
Wait, it might be Charlie.
Well, who am I supposed to shoot?
There.
Damn pigs.
I'm trying to help you out.
Stay there.
We got to go.
Come on.
Let her go.
She served her purpose.
Astra Logue. Name's Neron.
I hear good things about you.
Now that I'm taking over
for your former employers, I...
Give it a rest, John.
You think I can't see through
your cheap little parlor trick?
How'd you get out
of the torture pits anyway?
- Nice sparkles.
- Nice shoulder pads.
What do you want, John?
And please tell me
you're not here to make
some sad, sappy plea for me
to remember who I really am.
I know exactly who you are.
You're someone I can work with.
Now, the Triumvirate,
they were too short-sighted
to take my deal, and now they
are roasting rats for supper.
But you're smarter than that, Astra.
All I need is access
to one measly soul,
and in exchange, I'll go kill Neron,
and your boys will be back on top.
This soul you're after...
must be pretty special.
He is.
I was special to you, too, John once.
And yet, you left me down here
to rot all those years.
- Astra, you can't...
- I'm over it.
I made the best of a bad situation,
and guess what.
I flourished.
Down here, I had prospects
until Neron wiped his ass with them.
So...
do we have a deal?
Let's go rob the King.
Today's attack at the U.S. Capitol
has sparked worldwide panic
and paranoia
over the threat of magical creatures.
Enough, Gideon.
Where is Neron in all of this?
Why isn't he responding
to his magical-creature alerts?
What alerts? All the creatures
are here on the ship.
You know what?
It doesn't even matter.
Neron's shown the world
that anyone can be a monster.
People are turning on each other.
Everyone's terrified.
I thought Neron wanted
to collect souls.
How does hacking the app
only to let it fail
get him what he wants?
It's not about souls anymore.
It's something worse.
Well, they didn't share
their endgame,
but from what I could figure out,
they don't give a "fa"
about ruling hell.
It's actually fear
that they're after.
- Why?
- Fear is power. It's energy.
And thanks to me, they have
a wallop of it to muck about with.
That might explain the strange
meteorological event
forming over Washington, D.C.
Right above the Time Bureau.
Gideon, do you have a visual?
You're welcome, world.
The air is thick with human fear.
The hour of our coronation
draws near, my pet.
It's time to send your message
to your legions below.
The bank's right around the corner.
What's happening?
Denizens of hell,
for far too long, we have been forced
to live like insects
underneath the Earth.
Soon, a door will open.
Look to the sky and await my signal.
With me as your king,
we will make Earth hell again.
So that's been his play all along.
We best keep moving, loves,
before all hell literally
breaks loose.
Stay calm, they smell fear.
What if fear is my natural scent?
Good afternoon, everyone.
We have your favorites.
I know it's a bit crowded in here,
but we're making the best of it.
Anybody want a sammy whammy?
Put that in your whammy, you dick.
Okay.
Bon appétit.
- They are savages.
- Oh, calm down, Gary.
The longer we keep
the magical creatures locked up,
the more they're gonna act like
actual monsters.
They are monsters, you twit,
and so are you.
We all are.
How are we supposed
to defeat fear itself?
I mean, people afraid of Metas,
magical creatures afraid
of people, and...
Monsters hated by everyone.
Not everyone. Gideon, play the...
- The "dancing dragon sneeze" video.
- Yep, that.
Mithra, dance.
- What is this?
- Wicksty.
Yeah, this innocent moment
where kids aren't afraid,
it's resonating with people.
They don't see a monster,
- they see something amazing.
- So do I.
Me on that playground
surrounded by people
who want to be my friend...
Even if it was just for a day, that
little baby dragon changed my world.
You sound like my dad's pitch for...
HeyWorld.
Oh, my God, guys, that's it.
What? What's... what?
My dad had a dream
to build a theme park
that people would come to see
because of magic.
That's what the world needs
right now,
a place for people to come
and see the wonder
of these creatures in person.
What, so they can just shoot us all
in one place?
That's bloody brilliant, that.
No, so they can see creatures
the way that you helped us
see creatures, Charlie.
Not as monsters, but as misfits
just trying to find their place.
Look, if we can learn that lesson,
then so can the rest of the world.
We just need to bring people
and creatures together.
Think of it like
a magical version of Woodstock.
- "If we build it"...
- "They will come."
How long until we can get it up
and running?
If Mikey T and the boys
work weekends.
Quick math in my head.
Two, maybe three years.
He's not a coin.
- Observant.
- No flesh bags, just souls.
That's why they call it
the Soul Exchange.
Oh, right, then.
I'll be on me way, then.
This is John Constantine.
Oh, and me without
my autograph book.
No worries, love. Next time, yeah?
Look, if you would like to convert
his soul into cash, you need...
Maybe you don't get it.
Neron owns the marker on his soul,
and Neron wants to torture him
as soon as he gets here.
But, hey, if you want to tell
the new boss why
his prized victim isn't waiting
in his vault.
This way.
Not so rough.
FYI, there's no bathroom in here,
and I'm not feeding him.
I'm a bank teller, not a zoo...
Pretty cool for a grown woman
wearing taffeta and a tiara.
How does this work?
We find a coin? There are 1,000.
Some of history's worst.
Yeah, I'd wager he's keeping
it somewhere special.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- What?
Revolution's in the air,
I've got to look out for number one.
You were a golden opportunity
to bankroll my future.
I took it.
What about Bridget's diary?
If we put it in Nate's hands,
he could just dream us up
a theme park.
Z, you are a genius. The...
It's in the Time Bureau.
It's okay, so we just break in,
but it's not gonna be easy.
Even if it isn't demon central,
the vault that it's being held in
is practically impenetrable.
Oh, it's penetrable.
Oh, my God.
I love you, Rory.
Give it back when you're done.
Buck and Garima's sexual odyssey
is far from over.
All right, team.
Nate, you have a theme park
to dream up.
Gary, help Mona "Pretty Woman"
our creatures into something
a little more kid friendly.
And the rest of us,
it's time to come up
with a marketing plan
for the happiest place on the planet.
Ms. Tomaz, your simulation program
has detected a change
in your presently predicted future.
Good change or bad change?
In one potential 2042,
building HeyWorld
leads to an era of understanding
and tolerance.
The Anti-Meta-Human Act
of 2029 never passes,
your parents live out
their lives peacefully in Seattle.
The future as you know it
would be completely changed.
My parents.
They're...
That means a piece
of this crazy plan actually works.
This is great news, right?
God, I've been running
that stupid program for so long,
I'd given up hope of it
actually working.
If this works, my brother survives...
I never steal his totem back
from A.R.G.U.S.,
I never join the Legends.
Last two years
wouldn't have happened.
Who knows where I'll be
or who I'll be?
You'll be you.
Because while we're at HeyWorld,
you'll be here on the ship
in the temporal zone,
and you'll be safe.
Sara, I can't...
I can't sit this one out.
Look, I'm not gonna lose
another Legend.
And who said we're not
putting you to work?
Look, we need to make sure
what happens at HeyWorld
is seen globally.
I can use the Eyes app as a backdoor
into the phones that downloaded it.
Thank you.
I found it, I found it. Ray's coin.
- So long, then, John boy, for now.
- Whoa, hold on a minute.
Our deal was for his soul,
not a bleeding coin.
Fine, a promise is a promise.
What are they doing to him in there?
Prepare yourself, love.
What's behind this door,
it won't be pretty.
Down there, they twist a man's soul
until he's no longer human.
And what they've done to the big man,
he might not even be...
No!
Ray. Ray?
Nora, John, we're just about to start
another game of Giant Jenga.
You got to meet my old friend
well, technically, my new friend.
We used to be mortal enemies.
Oh, hi, guys.
Well, you're just in time
for the next round.
When the world needs heroes,
they answer the call.
We'll be at HeyWorld,
the new adventure capital
of eastern Maryland...
Where we will hit fun
in the bull's-eye.
And we'll give your children
a flash of excitement.
And cut.
- That was good, guys.
- That was a good take.
- It felt good.
- That was a great take.
Guys, I feel like that
would have worked
a little bit better
with the real Trinity.
Yeah, well, I asked,
and they said hard pass.
- We should have done a crossover.
- Yeah.
Well, who needs
the Trinity anyway, right?
I mean, the Legends are super enough.
But HeyWorld isn't a superhero park.
Promising them something
and giving them something else feels,
I don't know, wrong, doesn't it?
People aren't going to go to a park
filled with things
they're terrified of.
People need franchise
superheroes to feel safe,
so that's how we're gonna
get them in the door.
Okay, everyone,
let's just go around the room
one by one and say what talent
you can contribute
to the HeyWorld revue.
Oh, Minotaur, let's start with you.
I hear you like guitar.
Don't tell her nothing, bull face.
- Let us out of here.
- We can't do that, Mr. Ogre.
It's not safe out there.
Well, we ain't helping you,
what, with you moving us around
from one prison to another.
So why should we trust you?
Listen up, if you lot
don't want to go back
to a real prison,
then this is your chance.
This is your chance to change
the way that humans see you.
Show them that just because
you look scary.
Doesn't mean you are scary.
That's right, Wolfie.
Look, I know how infuriating
humans can be.
They have a hard time seeing past
their own noses, don't they?
But they can change
if you help them to look deeper.
And if they see the amount of good
that you lot are capable of,
then maybe,
maybe they'll believe in you
even when you doubt yourself.
Now, I know that there's more
to all of you than meets the eye.
Like you, Ogre.
My name is Frederic.
But what's the point?
Every time I try to show
a human who I really am,
they run away or try to kill me.
And that must really hurt
your feelings.
Yeah, it does.
All I ever wanted to do was sing.
Well, it looks like we found
ourselves a double act.
Now, who else has a hidden talent?
Brilliant. Beautiful.
I think we've got ourselves a show.
Wait, what are you doing here?
Are you dead?
Oh, please tell me you're not dead.
What are you doing in that dress?
Not that I don't like it, but.
Idiot. What were you thinking
selling your soul to a demon?
- You, Ray?
- I.
- You doomed the whole planet.
- Look, I didn't have a choice.
He was gonna kill Nate.
It was the only way I could make sure
my best friend would be safe.
So that was the deal you made...
his life for your body.
Oh, Raymondo, you sweet,
dumb son of a softie.
Yeah, right? What a guy.
I was sent here to torture him,
but then we got to talking.
- Oh, it got really deep, man.
- It really did.
What were we even fighting
about all those years ago?
Your compulsion for world domination
and inability to accept rejection.
Translation, it was about a girl.
A girl? What girl?
- It doesn't matter. We should go.
- Wait.
Something's happening.
I think I fulfilled Gary's wish.
Ray, take my hand. John.
Oh, all right. Ciao for now.
Say hi to the Legends for me,
will you?
Oh, I love those groovy guys.
Jenga time.
Oh, almost forgot,
extra hot sauce for the chupacabra.
What in the hell?
More like "out of it," mate.
It worked. It worked.
- You got Constantine.
- All right, okay.
- Be cool, just be cool.
- Okay.
- Simmer down, simmer down, sunshine.
- Where's Ray?
He was just here. He.
Yeah, that's the only way
he can travel
as long as Neron's
using his body.
Fairy Godmother,
I wish for Ray to get his body back.
All magic has its limitations
you know,
stroke of midnight and all that.
But don't worry...
I'm sure the Legends have
something up their sleeves.
This isn't playtime, you twits.
Neron is using fear
to open up the gates of hell.
Well, that's why we have
to fight fear
with something wonderful.
We have to show the world
that these magical creatures
are just that, they're magical.
And everyone else
is on board with this?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, pretty much.
- Bloody hell.
- All right, great.
Well, now that you're all on board,
we have work to do.
There is another way.
Whilst in hell, we learned that
Neron's possession of Ray's body
is contingent on Nate
not being killed.
Is that why Ner-Ray
didn't strangle me
- when he had the chance?
- Yeah.
A demon is only as good as his word.
If Neron breaks that deal,
he'll be ejected from Ray's body.
I could kill him.
And once I do, all the souls
he's nabbed will be released.
And all Neron has to do is...
Me?
No, absolutely not.
Look, there is no Plan B,
only Plan A, got it?
Yeah, got it.
Look, I meant what I said earlier.
I am not losing another Legend.
So forget what you heard back there,
because we are all-in on HeyWorld.
Now, I believe in you,
and if I'm not mistaken,
- someone has a theme park to build.
- Yeah.
I can't believe it all
comes down to this.
After years of anxiety
of whether or not
I could live up
to my dad's expectations,
I'm about to bring
his crazy dream to life...
knowing what it could cost me.
Nate, I'm not going anywhere.
You got this.
Okay.
Let's do this.
I'm standing in front of HeyWorld,
a new superhero inspired theme park
that seems to have sprung up
overnight like magic.
Welcome to HeyWorld,
the happiest place on the globe.
Hey, kid, welcome to HeyWorld.
Try the churros and not just
because the real money
is in the concessions,
they're also delicious.
Z, you and your mom are here.
I see them, I mean us.
All right, stream's up.
You look great, by the way.
Oh, thank you for noticing.
I showered.
How's the clickety-clackety-hackety
coming along?
Once Ava hits "record,"
this will stream out to about,
you know, 3 billion people or so.
No pressure.
Come one, come all
to our thrilling stage spectacular
"Superheroes versus Monsters."
Okay, you got
the choreography down?
Everyone, follow her lead.
Baba Yaga, remember,
those kids are audience members,
not appetizers.
Mike, watch your language
out there, right?
We don't want those gormyus wankers
from standards
and practices up our you-know-whats.
Everyone,
they're gonna love you guys.
All right, gang, it's showtime.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please don't call them heroes,
call them Legends.
Now, let's see what daring do
the Legends of Tomorrow get into...
today.
And that'll teach those bad guys
that crime doesn't pay.
Thanks for the assist, Green Arrow.
See you later, Supergirl.
Whoa. Do you see that?
That's the Flash,
and he wants to hang out.
Should we got hang out?
Break a leg, guys.
Wait a second.
I think that I hear something.
Monsters.
What do you think, White Canary?
Should we show them what we got?
Wait, hold on.
What if, instead of showing them
what we got,
we ask them what they have?
You mean get to know them?
What if, getting to know them,
we realize
that we have nothing to fear.
Minotaur, your passion is music.
Why don't you show us what you got?
They said this was a superhero show.
These brats don't respect art.
Hey, hey. I think we're losing them.
What was that?
Bloody hell, I know that sound.
Finally, a real-life dragon.
- Oh, no, is that.
- Wicksty?
Now, this is a show.
You really thought you could stop us?
These fools you brought here
will only serve our hellish end.
Everyone remain calm.
This is all just, a part of the show.
Damn it, Gary. Now I'm powerless.
Enough, filling your heads
with this silly,
little morality play.
Now all of you will bear witness
to the birth of a new era.
She wants these people scared.
They'll open up
the portal right here.
This way. Go, go.
We got to get that staff.
We got to get these kids
out of here, go.
Follow them.
Everybody, go back inside.
Back inside.
It's all right. It's all right.
Burn her. Burn them all.
Stop.
Burn the child. Do it now.
Kid, you got to run.
Mithra, dance.
No.
Tabitha.
Mithra, wait.
Rise, my demon brethren.
The door is open.
Rise.
Oh, it's gonna take more
than a musical number to stop this.
Neron.
This fight is between me and you,
so let's settle it once and for all.
Gladly.
I've already won.
Killing you is just a bonus.
You may take me, Neron,
but the Legends will always win.
- What's happening?
- Looks like the deal's off, mate.
No.
Nate? No.
Gideon, take us to HeyWorld.
I must advise against
that course of action.
The change to your future
is still in progress.
If you leave the temporal zone,
your current memories won't be safe.
You didn't.
I'm sorry, love. It was his choice.
- Finish it off, John.
- Gladly.
(Foreign language)
Come on, Ray.
Raymond Palmer,
I return your soul to your body.
What happened to me?
Where am I?
I'm in HeyWorld?
Everybody's here.
No, Nate. No.
- No.
- Ray, Ray.
- No, no, no.
- Ray, I'm so sorry.
- Nate, hey.
- But, but.
- You can't be here.
- Come on.
Hey. Nate, you can't be dead.
Come on. Hey, come on, come on.
Come on, you can't be.
Bring him back to life, weasel.
Oh, I wish I could, Rory,
but that requires magic
beyond my means, mate.
Not a bad show if you ask me.
- Dad.
- Hello, Nate.
I missed you so much, Dad.
I haven't been far.
Oh, I guess.
I guess it sucks.
Dying before you're ready, huh?
- Sure does.
- Yeah.
Believe me, I went through
all the emotions
I mean, anger, worry...
I had so many regrets,
I almost missed my ticket
to the happy place.
- What changed?
- I had faith.
- You're saying there's actually a...
- In you, Nate.
And I was right
to believe that my boy
and all his freaky buddies
would see this thing through.
But you know the only thing missing
from that big show of yours?
Music.
There is a young cowboy
Who lives on the range
His horse and his cattle
Are his only companions
Do I have something on my face?
Did you just sing?
James Taylor?
I don't sing.
I think someone from beyond
is trying to help us out.
You got to be kidding me.
He works in the saddle
And sleeps in the canyons
Waiting for summer
His pastures to change
And as the moon rises
He sits by his fire
Thinking about women
Look.
- Closing his eyes
- Keep singing.
As the dogies retire
- He sings out a song...
- Of course.
If fear can be energy,
it only stands to reason
that love can be energy, too.
Everyone, if you want to see
Nate up and kicking,
he needs to hear your voices
right now.
We need everyone to hold hands.
And we mean everyone.
- Are we really doing this?
- Couldn't hurt.
Didn't they do this last year?
We're part of the circle this time.
Dad, do you hear that?
It's for you, son.
Won't you let me go down
In my dreams?
- And rock-a-bye, sweet baby
- Oh, come on, people.
Do you want him to stay dead?
Come on, sing.
Good night, you moonlight ladies
- Rock-a-bye, sweet baby James
- It's working.
Deep greens and blues
Are the colors I choose
- I love you, Nate.
- Down in my dreams
And rock-a-bye, sweet baby James
Yes.
No, no, no.
You're not in the temporal zone.
We changed history.
We changed everything.
I couldn't let you die.
No.
Dude, you just came back to life.
Something's wrong.
There was more pelvis
in that hug than usual.
It's all good, Nate dog.
Love you, too, bro.
Yeah, my bad, bro.
It just feels like...
feels like something's missing.
Ray. Buddy.
I can't believe you went
all the to hell
to stop Neron from killing me.
You would have done the same thing.
- I kind of just did.
- Yeah, you did.
All right, Time Bros.
- Oh, and Time Ladies.
- And Time Monsters.
And Gary?
As I was saying, Legends...
our work here is done.
Gideon, fire up the ship.
It's time to hit it.
I'm here to make a withdrawal.
These are some truly serious sinners.
Cut down too soon, all of them.
It's a real shame
when someone doesn't get to...
fulfill their destiny.
Don't you think?
Everyone deserves a second act.