Where are we?
At the dawn of time.
Well, look who's finally...
- Awake.
- Alex?
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry!
No, no, no, it's okay. It's okay.
Are, are you okay?
Did you have a bad dream?
I don't know. I'm...
How did I get here?
Well, you fell asleep
in front of the TV
and you just looked so peaceful,
so I didn't have the heart
to move you to the bed.
The dawn of time.
Dawn of time.
Is that what you were watching
before you nodded off?
Wait.
What is...
This isn't right.
Okay, well, I mean, it's right.
But it's not right
because it's right.
The White Martian did a number
on you last night.
White Martian.
White Martian. White Martian.
Listen, I gotta run.
Kelly and I are trying out
a new indoor rowing class downtown.
So, are you...
- You sure you're okay?
- I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Okay.
- Alex?
- Yeah?
I love you.
I love you too.
- Nia!
- Kara?
It's good to hear your voice.
Well, it would be better
to see my face.
Where are you?
The ceremony is about to start.
Ceremony?
They're awarding
the Nobel Peace Prize any minute.
Don't worry.
I saved you a seat, but,
that lady from the Gazette
is giving me angry eyes.
If you miss this,
Andrea's gonna blow a gasket.
- Please take your seats.
- Good timing.
Hey, I had a really
weird dream last night.
Could you maybe help me interpret it?
What happened?
The world ended.
But, like, all the worlds.
All of them.
That's dramatic, even for us.
And now, I am proud to introduce
the winner of this year's
Nobel Peace Prize, Lex Luthor.
Nia?
- Nia, am I still dreaming?
- I know, right?
It is so great when this award goes
to someone who actually deserves it.
We live in dangerous times.
Earth is a dangerous place.
I suppose that's why people love
superheroes so much.
The power, the chutzpah...
Of someone who can fly
faster than a speeding bullet.
But that's what makes this
so special.
I don't have any powers.
I can't leap tall buildings
in a single bound.
But I have dedicated my life
to fighting on the side of humanity,
and to be recognized for that
is more than I can put into words.
So, I will just say...
I stand with mankind.
I'm gonna throw up.
Are you still feeling weird?
We should get you to the med bay.
You did not seem okay this morning.
No, no, I'm fine.
I'm just disoriented.
The world is...
What was Lex doing up there?
Well, they keep throwing
all these awards at him.
He doesn't usually accept them
in person,
but this one meant a lot to him.
People think he's a good guy?
Kara, we're talking about Lex Luthor.
He's the best guy.
No, he's not.
He's a psychopathic lunatic!
What? No, he...
He's the boss.
And he's your number-one supporter.
I mean, besides Lena.
And all the times
they defended you to the President...
What has gotten into you?
Hang on. Wait, wait,
did you just say "boss"?
No.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Alex, are we...
Supergirl.
- J'onn?
- I know you must be confused.
I was too.
But it happened.
It all happened.
Why are we the only two
that remember?
What are we that they are not?
Paragons.
We helped Oliver
restart the universe.
And this...
is the result.
I suspect there
will be more such changes
that are yet to reveal themselves.
There's something
happening downtown.
- I'll send a team.
- No, no, no. It's fine.
I need to punch something.
Hey!
Look who came to join the fun.
I'm sorry, who are you?
Weather Witch.
And you are no match for my wrath.
I'm having...
Not so great a day,
which is actually your bad luck.
Sorry, she's one of mine.
Well, what's she doing on my Earth?
What?
Wait, wait, what are you doing
on my Earth?
What, your Earth? This is my Earth.
- I thought...
Supergirl? Flash?
I just love it when you guys team up.
Would you sign this for me, please?
Okay. Oh. Sure...
Wait, you know both of us?
And it's normal to see us together?
Well, normally you'd also have
Green Arrow and a Legend or two.
Last year, even Batwoman joined in.
Make that out to Marv. M-A- R-V.
- "Marv. M-A-R-V."
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Marv, as far as you know,
how long have Supergirl
and I and all the rest of us
been working...
Together, on this Earth?
Since forever.
What the heck?
Call for help.
Now!
How did I get back here?
Ray, where are you?
Hey, Cap. Over here.
Ray!
Hey, hey.
Hey, are you okay?
Not that I'm ever one
to question a hug.
Ray, what was the last thing
that you remember?
Portaling to this location
on your orders.
You don't remember
coming here for trivia night,
and being teleported
to an alternate Waverider
to stop the multiverse
from being destroyed?
Wait, was there a crossover?
Were we invited? Did we win?
That's certainly how it looks.
Did you just hear...
It's good to see you both safe.
J'onn, that's a neat trick.
Wait, you know J'onn J'onzz
from Supergirl's Earth?
Of course I know J'onn.
Wait, go back.
Supergirl has her own Earth?
Not any more.
When we restarted the universe,
our worlds combined,
and only we Paragons
know it was ever any different.
Okay, sorry, guys.
I'm a little lost here.
Here, this will be faster.
There was a multiverse?
It all got destroyed,
there's an evil Batman,
and there's a me that's a super-me?
It'll take him some time
to assimilate to this new paradigm.
I have been going from city to city,
restoring the memories
of our compatriots as best I can.
And what about Oliver?
There's been no sign of him.
Hey, where you going?
To find my friend.
Oliver!
Sara.
No, I need to talk to you guys.
We already know.
Martian J'onn came by
and gave us a splitting headache.
It all happened, didn't it?
He died twice, Sara.
Yeah.
I wasn't there.
Both times.
Both times, I failed him.
- Digg...
- I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
I wasn't there.
He was my brother.
I know.
Listen to me.
Look, we all...
We all died.
The entire universe, the multiverse.
Now we're back.
That means Oliver,
he might be back too.
After the brain dump...
we had Felicity run a global search.
I mean, nobody's better
at finding people.
But they've got to be here
to be found.
You don't know, look...
When Oliver died,
he became something else.
He called it "the Spectre."
And maybe Felicity,
she just can't find him in that form.
Digg, she just can't find him
in this form.
Sara.
Sara, gone is gone.
He's gone.
J'onn.
What are you doing here?
Is something wrong?
Not any more.
No thanks to him.
Do you know why he's like this?
And now, so do you.
Oliver!
This is all his fault.
He's the one
who released the Anti-Monitor.
He paid dearly for his misjudgment,
but not as much as some others.
What happened?
Where am I? How did I get here?
You nearly damned us
all to hell, Nash Wells!
Well, that's an introduction.
Who the hell are you,
and what are you talking about?
You need to stay calm.
Your system's still recovering.
You, you need to calm down.
I'm not going to stay here
and get lectured
by some government suit...
God!
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
And so you should be.
This is all your fault.
It is my fault.
But you, you solved it.
You and the others,
you saved the universe.
You fixed my mistake.
Right?
Not entirely.
It's true.
We all live on the same Earth now.
Our Earths must have merged when
we helped Oliver reboot the universe.
I can't believe it.
- What are you guys doing here?
- I had to see if it was true.
The DEO, CatCo, all of National City
is on this Earth now.
Even Argo's up there.
We did it!
We saved everyone.
Not everyone.
Oliver...
He didn't make it.
Guess we just have to face facts.
No, that's not, that's...
Why did he give everyone else
a fresh start, but not himself?
Maybe this was the only way, Kara.
Maybe his sacrifice
made all of this possible.
Him for us.
- What is that?
- We're being attacked.
By who?
You wouldn't believe it
if I told you.
Beebo hungry.
How the hell did Beebo get here?
Isn't the more pressing question,
why is there a giant Beebo
walking down the street?
This wouldn't be the first time.
- It's a long story.
- That's right.
Wally told us about the time
you guys used those totems
to turn yourselves into a giant Beebo
to find a time demon.
I guess it's not a long story.
Could that be what's happening here?
Ava, Nate, you there?
I need a 20 on Behrad and his totem.
Sara, are you okay?
Ray called us to tell us
you were on some special mission.
But he was a little flimsy
with the deets,
so what's the happs, Caps?
Yeah, we've been busy
saving the multiverse.
You got shanghaied into another
crossover, didn't you?
Yeah, kind of.
Did they kidnap you?
This is a classic crossover move.
We tell them we're too busy,
they commit a felony.
Guys, Beebo is rampaging
through Star City.
- Does Behrad have his totem?
- Beebo?
That doesn't make any sense.
You would need all six totems
to make that happen,
and Behrad's
definitely still on the ship.
All right, I gotta go.
- Wait, do you need help?
- No, stay in DC.
I don't want any more of my people
getting roped into this mess.
Well, here's the thing...
One of us is kind of already there.
Who?
And who should I make this out to?
Doris. I'm such a huge fan,
Rebecca...
I mean, what should I call you?
"Rebecca" is fine.
"To Doris.
"Thanks for the passion, love..."
- What is that?
- Why are they running?
Furball.
Oh, my!
Oh, man, I can't believe
Nate's gonna miss seeing Beebo.
He's gonna be so jealous.
Here he comes.
What's the plan?
Smile, Beebo.
What are you...
I'm sorry, you guys
don't want to be in it?
Oh, bad timing.
Is this seriously happening
right now?
Maybe it's a good thing.
Guess we could all use a distraction.
Right, compartmentalize,
focus on the work. Good idea.
Guys, Beebo's still on the warpath.
Any suggestions on how
we take him down?
- What is that?
- It's a utility truck. Why?
You guys ready to do
a tag-team trip up?
Yeah, what do you have in mind?
All right, Supergirl, Atom,
keep him contained.
Flash, use those cables to your left.
- All right. Can do.
- Got it.
Beebo want cuddles.
Is this actually happening?
Is this what all the crossovers
are like?
Yes, and not exactly.
I'm never letting my child
watch that show again.
- Done.
- All right, now get him moving.
- Die, furball!
- Mick?
That blue bastard ruined
my book signing.
Okay, everybody get ready to pull.
Take it, take it.
All right.
The bigger they are...
The harder they fall.
Thanks, Supergirl.
What the heck?
Guys, something's off.
I'm not reading any known elements.
Nothing off the periodic table.
I don't think the rules apply
to a 50-foot talking plush toy.
Hey! Hey, Kate's here too. That's...
Sorry, what were you saying?
- It's unnatural.
- Alien?
- Hey!
- Or magic?
Sara, don't you and the Legends deal
with that kind of stuff all the time?
Or maybe it's just here
to keep us talking.
A diversion.
But for what?
I know what I'd do.
It is finally time
for Sargon the Sorcerer
to claim his reward...
Oh, and buy
that beautiful time-share in Bogota.
Come on, man. Beebo?
Is nothing sacred?
You know, it's a smart move.
Distracting all the fuzz
with giant fuzz,
but someone should have told you...
Beebo? He's off-limits.
Beebo.
Got him again.
Pugh.
So, how normal was that for everyone?
And don't say "very."
Oh, well, with this new Earth,
it just may be.
Dear God, I hope not.
What is that?
Alcohol.
Rory, huh?
We had a Rory once on our team.
We did.
What's this?
Was there a memo that went out
on how to infiltrate
our secret bunker?
Why are you here?
I'm here to warn you.
You see this?
This gauntlet is primed
to detect anti-matter,
of which there has been
a massive surge
here in the Star City area.
Okay, well,
you're about two hours too late.
- Already took care of it.
- Did you? Really?
My readings say different.
This thing ain't over.
As a matter of fact...
It's just beginning.
Something's not right.
Is that thing still working?
Yeah, it's working.
I built it myself. It's infallible.
Yeah, but you're still
detecting traces of anti-matter.
Then our fight isn't done, is it?
No. Or worse...
it's starting up all over again.
Hey.
How'd you find me?
You feel that gust of wind
a few seconds ago?
That was me. I did a quick search
of the whole city for you.
When you didn't come back
for the post-Beebo celebration,
I got a little worried.
Yeah.
You see that tree over there?
My sister and I used to race
to the top when we were little.
I'd win every time.
I used to think it was
'cause I was a better climber, but...
Now I think Laurel let me win.
She knew I was a sore loser.
A lot has changed since then.
I was an assassin.
I was dead.
Now I'm the captain
of a freaking Timeship.
One thing remains the same...
I'm still a sore loser.
I know it's...
It's hard,
not having Oliver here with us.
But look at what his sacrifice
made possible.
Our world is...
It's different.
But at least it's safe.
Yeah.
He was just the last tether...
To my old life, you know?
And he was the only person left
who knew me when I was just...
Me.
With him gone,
my connection to this world,
this place...
To that tree...
It's gone.
I know what it's like to lose family.
My mom, my dad.
Each death felt like...
There was no moving forward.
Like, life would never be the same.
Yeah.
And I was right.
It's not the same, but...
Somehow it's okay.
Family isn't just the people
that you grew up with,
it's the people you find, the...
the ones you love,
the ones who make you crazy...
Make you smile.
When did you get so wise?
The Legends, they are my family.
They have been for a while.
I guess I just...
I always thought
there would be at least someone
who remembered what I was like
before I got on that boat.
I thought we got rid
of all those things.
Barry, Sara,
the Shadow Demons are back.
I believe we are being hunted.
If they're hunting the Paragons,
that means...
Ryan.
Sara?
What the hell's going on?
You have to come with me. Now.
All right, Barry, John, Supergirl
and Batlady are gathering the troops.
Those attacks were probably
just the first wave.
Assassins sent to pick us off
in pairs.
How are the Shadow Demons
even still here?
Didn't Oliver destroy the guy
who controls them?
Well, not according to the surge
in anti-matter energy I'm reading.
The Anti-Monitor is alive?
But you said
Oliver sacrificed himself...
To create this new world.
Apparently, his sacrifice
didn't kill the Anti-Monitor.
Well, then how do we do that?
Well, let's just throw him
into the sun
and let the bastard burn.
Oh, yeah, let's throw him in the sun,
and cause an anti-matter explosion
that obliterates the solar system.
You know what? Let's not do that.
At least he's trying
to offer up a solution
instead of being
the cause of the problem.
That's the solution,
blow up the solar system?
Okay. Guys, guys,
we're all on the same team, okay?
No, Scrappy's right.
It's my fault we're in this mess.
We gotta fix it.
- Gotta fix it!
- It's just a little tricky.
The Anti-Monitor
is made of anti-matter,
and like its opposite, it can neither
be created nor destroyed.
- It can only...
- Change form
and move from place to place.
So what if we do just that?
What if we could set off
a chain reaction
that will destabilize his form,
compressing his molecules
so he's essentially
shrinking for eternity?
Is that kind of reaction
even possible?
Sure it is.
I did it a bunch of times by accident
when I was developing
my A.T.O.M. Exosuit.
So you think you can keep him
shrinking indefinitely?
Essentially we'd be sending him
to the "Atomverse."
I like to call it the "Microverse."
That's better.
Possible trademark issues,
but that's better.
He could get stuck there
for, like, ever.
In theory, it could totally work.
But developing a device in time...
Leave that to me, dear leaguers.
Gotta get to S.T.A.R. Labs.
Scrappy.
Look, if this goes down
anything like it did on Earth-38,
then things are gonna get messy.
Geek team, get on it.
Mick, go with them. Keep them safe.
The rest of us,
we'll need to hold back
this incoming army.
This can work, Sara.
I, I know it can.
That's what we thought
back at the Dawn of Time.
Here we are, back at square one.
This new Earth isn't square one.
It's what Oliver gave up his life
to create.
We have to protect it.
If we're gonna go down...
We go down fighting.
All right, listen up!
I got a ton of those Shadow things
descending on Gardener Pier.
Copy. We're en route.
This is new.
New world, new look.
Cut the chatter, they're here.
What the hell?
Was that it?
It's not over yet.
Paragons.
The universal safeguard
meant to thwart me.
It is time to meet your end.
We'll need a reinforced core
to contain the reaction.
- Titanium?
- No, that's too heavy.
What we need, what we need is...
Depleted promethium.
S.T.A.R. Labs, I've got Shadows
advancing on your position.
On it.
It's been a while, Frosty.
- You look good.
- Thanks.
I read your book, "Rebecca."
Which one? I'm very prolific.
Do you wanna take this guy
or should I?
Ladies first.
Age before beauty.
Who the hell are you?
The guy who just saved your ass.
We had that covered.
Sure you did.
Company's coming. You ready?
I stay ready.
I am destiny incarnate.
Inexorable and inescapable.
You are nothing.
Insects...
fated to be crushed beneath my heel
without a moment's thought.
Fighting is useless.
Surrender.
Not today.
Not ever.
Oliver died so that
we could continue to fight.
He sacrificed everything
for this new world,
and we will not fail him.
We will not fail this world.
For Oliver!
For Oliver.
- For Oliver!
The age of heroes ends now.
Guys, we're gonna need a bigger bomb.
Sky team, you're with me.
Ray, how's that shrink bomb coming?
Well, we could really use
some fast hands.
Could we ever.
Barry?
Supergirl, look out!
J'onn!
Where are you from, Sparkles?
Don't call me "Sparkles."
I'm from Freeland.
Martian came, got in my head,
told me y'all were caught up.
It's been a weird day.
That's an understatement.
- All right, what are we making?
- Hey.
- All right, so, plans...
- Yup.
Right? Now, this is
what we have to build.
Now, these pieces
are all very volatile.
We need to, yeah, you...
- How's this look?
- Okay, that's good.
I love when he does that.
It's perfect, actually.
Okay, so, now, all we have to do
is get it into direct contact
with the Anti-Monitor
once we've activated it.
Okay, to activate it,
I just press this...
- No, no, don't!
- You're crazy!
Okay, relax! Relax.
- Okay, Ray, you're coming with me.
- Oh, cool.
No!
Shadows are on the move again.
Perez Landing.
Yeah, we know. We're here.
Barry!
Bomb's ready.
Ray's running it to the sky team.
We're running out of time here, Ray.
- Hurry!
- Hurrying.
Hope I'm not too late.
- Ray?
- Hang on, Superman.
Throw it like a girl.
Always.
No!
We did it. We did it!
Wait, but, where is Kal?
I'm right here.
Sorry about that, Superman.
Here you go.
Thank you, Ollie.
My fellow Americans,
today, our way of life, our world...
Almost came to an end.
An entity known
as the Anti-Monitor attacked Earth,
intent on its destruction.
Thankfully, we were saved
by Earth's greatest heroes,
who came together...
Sara.
Hey, sweetie.
Baby, come over here,
your brother wants to play with you.
Their unity and strength
should be an example for us all.
I'm told this assembly
was led by Star City's Oliver Queen,
otherwise known as the Green Arrow.
We give thanks
to these brave women and men
who, with great tenacity, tireless
work and the utmost courage
put their lives on the line
for our country, our planet.
Hey, Lois.
Clark, I need you to get
to Metropolis now, it's the boys.
The boys?
Yeah, honey, your sons.
While in a hard-fought battle
loss is expected,
it never gets any easier.
So, it is with great sadness
that I must inform you
that Oliver Queen sacrificed his life
for our world's survival.
He is known to us
as the first of our heroes.
And while this is a devastating loss,
we can take solace in knowing
that he lived as he died...
with honor.
I ask all of you,
to join me in a moment of silence
to honor him now.
A grateful nation thanks you,
Mr. Queen.
May you finally find rest
in the hereafter.
God bless you...
and God bless
the United States of America.
Good night.
In the end, there was only one.
A single black infinitude.
Then the infinitude found release.
And finally, the darkness broke,
filling it with life...
With the multiverse.
Every existence,
multiplied by possibility...
and spread out before space
and time in infinite measure.
Civilizations rose and fell...
And rose again,
across reality's grasping expanse.
Life, a precious gift,
persevering in the face
of every obstacle.
Until, finally...
the age of heroes was born.
Thanks for saving us, Oliver.
The world has hope again.
I have hope again.
I'll never forget you.
Thanks for believing in me,
even when I didn't.
You had this way of...
bringing out the very best
in all of us.
I'm gonna miss you, man.
I've lost a lot of people
that I love,
and I never imagined my life
without you in it.
You were always there for me.
And now...
Ollie, you changed my fate...
for the better.
Thank you.
I never met Oliver, but...
he must have been a good dude.
But why'd you choose
a condemned building?
What?
No. This is not a condemned building.
No, listen, this is an old
S.T.A.R. Labs research facility
that nobody uses.
And what's even better,
no one knows it exists.
- Good for you.
- No, good for us.
I figure we could all use this
to gather if...
anything ever happens again.
- It's a great idea, Barry.
- Thanks, Superman.
It's a better option
than you all dropping by the DEO.
Why do we even need it?
I mean, how often does the world
almost come to an end?
Oh, it's like that?
Don't worry,
I was the new kid last year.
All right, listen, I haven't even
showed you guys the best part yet.
Ready?
Oh, nice!
- You should have led with that, bro.
- Yeah.
- Not bad.
- I love it!
It's perfect.
Sounds like
we need to call Pest Control.
What was that?