Nothing.
There's gotta be some spell,
some potion,
something to give us the power
so we can touch the Loom
without turning extra-crispy.
There's also the question
of who's gonna use it with me.
The Loom requires three weavers
who are as powerful as Gods.
Well, I'm not leaving my mom's life
in the hands of you idiots.
Wow. Okay, well, that's one person.
What do you think, Sara?
I'm already a blind time-traveling
Paragon who can see the future.
So, might as well just add
wannabe God to the list.
Speaking of which,
can you use your Sara-Vision
to tell me
if what I need is in this book?
Nothing there. You know,
you could just read the book.
You know I would do anything
to save Behrad, but this is faster.
These are all the spell books
in the manor you asked for.
Yes, you're a good man, Gary.
And these...
are for you.
Can you just give them to me?
Thank you.
- Shouldn't you be resting?
- Shouldn't you get out of my face?
- Yeah.
- No, he's right, love.
Getting some rest
wouldn't be a bad thing.
Not gonna happen.
Look, the sooner we find
this magical cure-all,
then the sooner we can use the Loom
and get my sight back.
Wait, wait, wait. This book says
that Merlin used
the Philosopher's Stone.
That thing's as real as Santa.
Gary's in the room.
- What?
- Wait, wait, wait.
The Chalice of Dionysus.
It says here that the Chalice was
gifted to an Olympian, Dionysus,
by his father, Zeus.
Whoever drinks from it becomes a God.
But only for a day.
Look, don't get your hopes up,
all right?
The Olympians fed off devotion,
so once they lost their followers,
they just died off,
and their enchanted objects.
Lost to time.
I've seen that.
I've seen that in college.
Okay, your degree
is finally paying off.
What class did you see it in?
That was not in a class.
Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug! Chug!
It's called the Chug Cup.
Chug! Chug! Chug!
Right, campus legend said
that whoever drank from it
became invincible for a day.
Oh, yeah.
Now, I went to a rival school,
so the only way I could get a taste
of it is if we, you know...
- Hey!
- Drink.
Who's that?
Hudson sucks, Brixton rules!
Yeah!
Stole it.
We really think
that Dionysus' Chalice
- is with bunch of frat boys?
- Yes.
A scan of social media
confirms that a Chalice
matching that of Dionysus
is currently in possession
of the Sigma Psi Phi fraternity
at Hudson University.
So, we get that,
I become immortal, use the Loom,
and I can forget
I ever knew you people.
Well, then, Legends,
you better get your togas dry-cleaned
because we are going Greek.
So, babe, all right.
Every year, the Chug Cup
is presented at the student fair.
And then, apparently,
fraternities and sororities
compete for the right to drink in it
in something
called the Chug Challenge.
Definitely our best place
to try to steal the Chalice.
Truth.
Okay, I can get around the ship,
but I'm not so sure
about navigating my way
through a bunch
of drunk college kids, so...
- You got this.
- Yeah.
Team loves you. Don't worry.
Okay, I'm not... I'm not really
worried about them accepting me.
The college kids,
on the other hand...
Hi, Aunt Ava, Sara.
Lita, honey, I am so, so glad
that you're still here.
I need you to help me with something.
What are the, like,
kids into these days?
Like, I need them to think I'm cool.
- Mission's at Hudson U.
- Yeah.
Oh, my guidance counselor
told me to apply there.
- Sweetie, that's amazing.
- I can't afford it.
You should do it.
If you want to do it,
I can make it happen.
Yeah, I mean,
it could be cool to take a tour.
We're here, right?
Yeah, yeah. The mission's all good.
Rory, you should definitely do that.
Okay. Thanks.
If you want kids to think
you're cool, I wouldn't wear that.
They're gonna think
you look like a narc.
I'm... What...
When Sisters.
9 12
Welcome to Hudson University.
You smell that?
That smells like the good ol' days.
I've had it. I can't breathe in here.
Maybe it was for the better.
What is that smell?
Okay, so the Sigmas hosted the games.
We find them, we find the cup.
Great. Let's fan out.
Zari, thank you.
Nate, take up the north end.
Thank you.
Astra, Charlie, you guys...
Let's just find this Chalice,
so we can get this over with.
I wasn't finished, but...
- I'll go after her.
- Thank you.
Pledge Theta. Find your girl gang.
Maybe you can tell me where
I can find the Chalice of Dionysus.
Sorry, we're just really excited
about the Chug Challenge.
Why are we even doing this?
We should just take it by force.
Listen to me.
In order to use the Loom,
the weavers have to be in sync.
Now, I'm not gonna let you use it
unless you can prove
that you can work as a team.
Let me?
I left Hell because I was done
working for a Fate.
And that was Quincy Hall,
our economics building.
Hudson has the top program
in the country.
- Did you hear that, Henry?
- Yeah.
He's majoring in finance.
I told him, you have to go to Hudson.
You know
that's not the only reason, Gene.
Guilty.
I want him to follow
in Dad's footsteps.
I'm an alumnus,
you probably noticed the scarf.
Yeah.
I'd like to wring your neck with it.
What was that?
I said...
I said it's a great building.
Good brick structure, fire-resistant.
Oh, you really know your
architecture.
- Where did you study?
- Iron Heights.
Haven't heard of it.
It's a super prestigious art school.
Yeah.
Just go with it.
I can't believe I'm back here.
They used to call me Shotgun Nate.
I think I know why, but why?
Is that true, Pops?
Show us what you got.
Pops?
Pops. Pops.
Pops.
And I also turn to steel.
Okay, come on, Grandpa.
- We gotta keep looking.
- Yeah.
Sigma Psi Phi! Sigma Psi Phi!
- What?
- Sigma Psi Phi!
Ava, I think we found the Sigmas.
Ava? Hello?
Bake
I'm on my way.
Sigma Psi Phi!
Sigma Psi Phi! Sigma Psi Phi!
That was just like my entrance
to the 2044 VMAs.
What's up, Hudson hedonists?
Welcome to the Chug Challenge's
pre-game!
- That's the Chalice.
- Wait, wait, wait.
That's Dion.
He was the head of the Sigmas
when I was in school.
The guy hasn't aged a day.
We have so much in common.
Dude, that's because your Dion
is Dionysus.
This is the Greek God of wine
and revelry.
God, the guy's a riot, honestly.
Now, as chug keeper,
I get the honor of announcing
our 2020 Challenges.
I will reveal the first round tonight
at the Sigma rager.
Now let the Challenge begin!
Look, just leave this to me,
all right?
Oi, Dion.
Or should I say, Dionysus.
- It's me, Clotho.
- Clotho?
- Yes.
- Damn, it's really you.
My God.
The Loombreaker is in the house!
Dude, back before people had
free will,
the Gods were always reining
in the party.
But look at me now.
You're in college.
Yeah, I know. I'm a lifer.
I found a place where the party
doesn't stop,
and I haven't left since.
Honestly, they worship me here,
and they don't even know
that I'm the party God.
- Hey, listen, man...
- Yeah.
I kind of wanted
to ask a little favor of you.
Yeah, anything
for the Loombreaker, and...
- Sick, is this your squad?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, they call me Shotgun Nate.
- I went to Brixton, but...
- All right, enough of this.
Hey.
So, that's why you're really here.
Wanted to give your gang
a little taste of immortality.
Is that what it is?
Well, here's the thing.
To pick this up, you gotta be Greek,
and I gotta deem you worthy.
Okay, how are we supposed to do that?
Good question.
You gotta either join a sorority,
a fraternity or a frorority,
and you gotta win the Chug Challenge.
This is ridiculous.
And that's what makes it fun.
See you, Clotho.
He's still so...
Just stop. I need to focus.
I need to think of something.
- I have an idea.
- No.
Something that does not involve
maiming.
OAP
Since the Chalice belongs to Dion,
we've gotta follow his rules.
You guys, we're gonna win that cup.
So, what you're saying
is in order to use the Loom of Fate,
we have to join a sorority?
Finally. A mission I can get behind.
Luckily for us, the Thetas
are hosting a pledge social today.
This cannot be your plan.
Look, as long as Dion's got the cup,
we've gotta play by his rules.
Counterpoint. You don't get anywhere
playing by the rules.
Oh, really? Because I think
I was about to win him over
before you tried to nab the cup.
Hey, okay.
So, who wants to rush
Theta Lambda Rho?
- No, no, no. Just stop.
- No.
Charlie, Astra, you'll pledge Theta.
Just try to remember
you're on the same side, yeah?
Yeah.
Yeah. Sure we are.
She's exhausting.
So, I'm doing track and debate,
plus my dad got me this internship.
What are your extracurriculars?
I was in band for a while, but I quit
because no one else wanted
to play The Replacements.
And I have a part-time job.
I heard that helps.
Actually, to get into a place
like this,
you'll really want to build out
your application.
And here we are at Neuman Hall.
The name might sound familiar
to some families on this tour.
Oh, Henry Neuman.
This is actually
my grandfather's building,
which should help my chances
of getting in here.
Hey, hope I didn't miss
too much of the tour.
Just to be super clear,
I'm not a prospective student.
Okay, my name is Dr. Nate Heywood.
I got my PhD from Brixton.
Go, Big Red.
- Oh, a doctor.
- Yeah.
And Lita's dad.
- What?
Just go with it.
Thank you for your enquiry.
I think it's really important...
- Hi, how's it going?
- Be yourself.
Hi.
I can't believe we are this close
to becoming Thetas.
I don't even know you,
but we could be sisters.
I'm only here as a performance.
Notice my empty teacup,
a commentary on the emptiness
of this charade.
Oh, my God.
We should start a group text.
What are your numbers?
Welcome to the Theta luncheon.
Everybody, look around you.
This could be your new family,
the ones you turn to for support,
sisterhood, guidance.
That is, as long as you make the cut.
So, bid Theta.
For real?
What are you doing?
Come on, we gotta try and convince
these people, no matter what.
Now, just try and fit in, please.
Fine. You want me to fit in?
Waiter, replace this drink.
If I wanted weak tea, I'd rush Omega.
This girl's fire. I like that.
We're gonna start with your table.
This here is the house paddle,
our most sacred object.
I'm going to ask a question,
and when you're holding the paddle,
it's your turn to answer.
Okay?
What did you do before college?
So, I grew up in Hell,
had minions do my bidding
and rose to power
until I practically ran the place.
Oh, and she's ambitious.
- Now you go.
- Okay.
Well, I traveled around the world
with a bunch of friends.
More like rejects.
But before that, I was actually
in this really cool punk band.
Yeah, Thetas don't really do punk.
Yeah, I know her type.
You pretend like you're
all about bucking the system,
and then you get pissed when people
don't fall in line behind you.
You think you're better
than the sisters you ran away from,
but the truth is...
you're all the same.
That's a little bit rich, isn't it?
Coming from my sister's lapdog.
No.
Theta, no.
You know what?
This whole table is exiled.
None of you are Theta material.
How'd the mission go?
You immortal sorority girls yet?
I need a drink.
The refreshing sound of failure.
We would be well on our way
to using the Loom right now
if someone hadn't blown it.
Our cover was blown because you
decided to go Hell mode on us.
Oh, you think that was Hell mode?
Honey...
Call me honey again.
Go on, I dare you.
Try me
and you'll wish you were immortal.
- Okay, okay.
- Okay, whoa, whoa, whoa, stop.
No one's killing anyone.
Astra was definitely gonna go for it.
Zari, hide that fork.
Charlie, just chill. Please sit down.
Just take a breath, yeah?
All right. You good?
Okay.
All right, we need to find
another way to get the Chalice.
You can't defy a God.
We have to win as a sorority.
And with no sorority...
- We're screwed.
- Yeah.
Ladies, we're gonna start our own.
I can't tell, is she serious?
I think so.
Becoming an official sorority
by tonight?
I mean, the paperwork alone would...
- Let's do it.
- Yes.
Why not?
I really should've killed you all
when I had the chance.
Go, sisters.
We'll get there.
B
- Do you think my dad's okay?
- Oh, yeah.
He comes and goes as he pleases.
It's really part of his charm.
Bright side is I get to show you
what college is all about.
This is Greek Row.
This is where the fraternities
and the sororities live.
They're the most influential people
on campus.
These are the guys
that have the Chalice?
Wish I could be more impressed.
Yeah.
Call the Bro Patrol.
- Looks like somebody wants to party.
- Is he talking to us?
- Act cool. Be cool. Shut up.
- I don't...
This is Agent Heywood to Bro Patrol.
Desire to party confirmed.
- How cool was that?
- Do you have a man-crush?
- No. It's unrequited.
- It's okay.
- You should tell him.
- Shut up.
Super-stoked that you're here.
Anyone who's a friend
of the Loombreaker is chill with me.
So snag some bags and some brews.
Oh, and fear not, we have energy
drinks for the little ones.
It's all peers,
no pressure at Casa de Sigma.
I want to say that's tight,
but, I got responsibilities.
Well, hey, come by anytime,
and we'll party like it's 1999.
Wait, hold on.
You said these are the guys
that have the Chalice, right?
So, why don't you go inside
and get requited,
and I can do some scouting
and find out where they keep it.
Only if your dad doesn't try to set
me on fire while I'm asleep.
- Deal?
- Yeah, deal.
All right, so what are we doing?
League rules?
All right, two points
for those overhangs!
Okay, I call to order the charter
meeting of Delta Chi Sigma,
Sisterhood of Legends.
Let's make a sorority.
First up, we need a house.
I say we steal the Thetas' place.
You disable
the carbon monoxide detector,
I'll go in, cut the power...
Or I have a more non-fatal idea.
There's a place that's been empty
since Pi Epsilon's last rager.
Something about a de-Jell-O-ing?
- Oh, that is really foul.
- Yeah.
But with a little trickery,
I'll just open up a portal,
instant remodel.
They'll never know the difference.
You know, I can't believe
I let you talk me into this.
It's not my fault you can't resist
my effortless charms.
Obviously,
we're gonna have to redecorate.
Well, you lot have fun.
I can't bear
to watch you desecrate this place.
Oh, and watch out for these bad boys.
They bite.
So do I.
Okay, so, in order
to be an official sorority,
we need three more sisters.
And if we wanna win that Chalice,
they gotta be good.
So, Gideon, what do you got?
Inez Martin was voted out of pep
squad for being too enthusiastic.
Hey. How's it going? What's up?
Hi. Hey, there.
- Oh, Inez, right?
- Yes.
This is weird, but I was just
wondering if you wanted to join...
Definitely.
- You don't even know what I...
- It doesn't matter.
Where can I meet you?
Lisa Lindhome. Aspiring influencer,
shunned after becoming the subject
of a viral video
entitled Girl Snarts at Party.
Wait.
What is a snart?
- It's when you sneeze and...
- And let's not.
Let's just ease Astra
back onto Earth, all right?
Fair.
Silvia Hines created
her own major in performance art.
You're the ones who tried
to kill each other at the tea party.
Yeah, about that.
We've actually started
our own sorority and...
What is the point of partying
with a bunch of brain-dead wasteoids?
I get it.
Seems impossible
to feel any kind of power in a cruel,
dying world, right?
But have you considered
that winning the masses
over with the illusion of fun
might be the perfect way to ply them
to do your bidding?
I'm in.
Unfortunately, Captain,
the pool of Theta rejects is slim.
- Beggars can't be choosers.
- I like 'em.
We chose you
because we know what it's like,
looking for a place to belong.
Because we, too,
were there at your age.
That's why we've created that place.
And as of today, you are Deltas.
Welcome to the sisterhood.
- Wait, are you blind?
- Yes.
I love it. Deltas are so inclusive.
But don't we need a motto?
We can't do anything without a motto.
Yeah. The sisters...
Are the glue.
Glue that greases the wheels of...
time.
That doesn't make any sense.
It's called avant-garde.
What about...
we might not have it all together,
but together we have it all?
Okay, I need that on a T-shirt,
like, now.
- Okay, go, sisters.
- Sisters.
Sisters.
I'm telling you, I can take it.
Dude, it's 2020.
We don't do that anymore.
- Just do it.
- Yeah.
It's like his ass is made of steel.
Because it is.
Keg's here, D.
Hey. So glad that you found us.
I knew that you had bro-tential
the second I saw you.
- That's nice of you.
- I wanted to mark the occasion.
It's my special stash.
I brew it out back.
I hope you like IPAs.
Bro, I am all about the IPAs.
- Yeah?
- You mind?
- My man.
- So good.
- Yeah, that brew right there,
- Yeah.
honestly, will just take you back
to the glory days.
Make you forget all about that stupid
and stressful world out there.
- Honestly, it's magic, bro.
- Yeah.
I, I just need to check up.
I feel awesome.
- I knew you would.
- Thank you.
- Hey, I wanted to ask you something.
- What?
Why did you and your friends
really end up here, of all places?
Oh, man, they're cool.
We just wanted to take your Chalice,
so we can use the Loom of Fate.
Are you saying that the Loombreaker
is a Loomfaker?
Bro, you're a looker and a cooker.
Right, but she puts
that Loom together...
I mean, there, there goes free will.
There goes the party.
God.
And that is very not tight.
Our name is Delta Chi Sigma.
We've assembled
an elite team of women...
to save this campus
from the cliques and cruelty
of the common Greek house.
And together,
we will display true sisterhood.
And win the Chug Challenge.
Ready and throw.
And then...
Party.
But please, don't call us heroes.
Call us Deltas.
And... post.
All right, we are officially a part
of the Chug Challenge.
- Yeah.
- This should scare the competition.
Yeah, and put us well on track
to using the Loom.
Okay, I think this calls
for a snack party.
Who wants nachos?
It's my brother's special recipe.
Hey, I just wanted to say thank you.
I've just always been so focused
on changing the world at all costs
that I just push people away.
So... thanks.
Oh, I mean,
they're really the ones who...
thank you.
Loom or no Loom,
at least some things are changing.
I can still put a stiletto
through your head.
But your plan does seem
to be working.
I still think it's the stupidest way
to get what we want, but...
'Sup, ladies?
Heard there was a new sorority
on the block.
Had to come and hit y'all
with that Big D welcome.
What?
You guys tricked out this place.
Gargoyles in sunglasses? Sick.
So sick.
- Nate, what the hell are you...
- No, it's Shotgun Nate.
You guys have got to come to Dion's.
I mean, it makes me wonder
why I ever left college.
Dionysus has the power to put people
in a constant state of ecstasy.
- Nate's under his spell.
- You mean Shotgun Nate.
Yeah, we're gonna go train
for your dumb challenge,
so go bother some other house.
Oh, right.
I'm not here
just to meet the new neighbors.
I also wanted to tell you...
that you're disqualified
from the Chug Challenges.
There's no way you're getting
that Chalice.
The hell are you on about?
Shotgun told me
why you're really here.
And the thing is, I just can't
have you using that Loom.
Thing's a total buzzkill.
We did everything you said,
played by every stupid rule.
You can't just change them on us now.
Well, yeah, I can.
I mean,
who says that you have to play fair?
I'm a God.
I just gotta keep it whimsical, bro.
Let's roll.
Whimsy! Whimsy!
Whimsy! Whimsy! Whimsy!
Who was at the door? What's wrong?
We're not getting the Chalice,
that's what.
Dion's refusing to let us participate
in the challenges.
He somehow got to Nate,
figured out what we're doing.
Of course he did.
It's okay, we will figure this out.
I am done trying to figure this out
with you people.
I should've done this my way
from the start,
so I'm taking that Chalice by force.
Look, even if you tried,
that won't work.
You can't defy a God.
And there is no way you're using
the Loom on your own.
Being a grown-up sounds weird.
If I can't get Dion's cup,
I can at least make him suffer.
Him and all his bros,
including your
hyp-bro-tized friend, Nate.
Hold on a minute. You can't do that.
We're a sisterhood, remember?
You can stop feeding me
that line right now.
You pretend we're sisters,
but all you do
is expect me to change.
I'm only your sister
if I become more like you.
- Astra, calm down, that's not...
- You never listen to my ideas,
and I see how you all look at me.
I might be new to this,
but that is not sisterhood,
and I am done trying to fit in.
- Hey, got your text.
- Hey.
Where were you?
Trying to get you into this place.
What do you think?
What? Dad, how'd you do this?
Went back in time. Donated.
You're as good as in.
Thank you,
but I didn't really need a building.
I just needed you here.
Well, I thought you were embarrassed
to be with me.
I don't belong with these people.
I didn't want to ruin your chances.
I'm sorry, it wasn't about you.
I was just ashamed of me.
What are you talking about?
Don't be stupid. You're great.
Yeah, but I don't belong
with them either.
I mean, the only reason
that I survived high school
was because I was imagining
that one day I would get out
and find my people.
They're never gonna take me
as one of them.
I don't really want to be.
You don't have to impress
these idiots, these leeches.
You're twice the person
they'd ever be.
Yeah, but so are you.
I mean, you fought a demon dog.
And these people think
that they're better than us
because they have whales
on their shorts?
What do you say we find a way
to piss off some rich kids?
I like the sound of that.
Give me that.
Wait, Astra, no, no, no.
You don't have to do this.
I am done listening to you.
Fine, then don't listen to me.
Listen to yourself.
Come on, you know this isn't right.
Yeah, that's the thing,
I don't know that.
Where I'm from,
I had to fight to survive.
This is all I know.
This is what life has made me.
I am not gonna change.
Blimey, no, we don't want you
to give up who you are.
Look, when I joined the Legends,
I was a punk.
All right? And there wasn't a rule
that I couldn't break.
And guess what? I still am.
I just don't need to hurt people
to survive anymore,
because I have them.
Fine, so I don't burn down a house.
But what if I never wanna dress
as a moose,
or sit through one
of your interminable team meetings?
Then we've still got a place for you.
Did you come to party down?
No, we've come
to get the Chalice and you.
- Come on, Nate, you can't stay here.
- Sure, I can.
Dion says
as long as he has followers,
he has the power to run this place
and grant people that cup.
Thought that'd be useful information
for you.
Can't really remember why.
Either way, I'm very important here,
so excuse me.
Shotgun Nate!
- Shotgun Nate! Shotgun Nate!
- Wait.
Shotgun Nate!
The Olympians feed off devotion,
right?
So that means that Dion
only has his followers
for as long as they worship him
as the party God.
So, if we take away
all these followers from him,
that's it, the Chalice is released
from his grasp.
Okay, but the party
isn't slowing down.
No, but there is one way
to get college kids to leave a party.
Oh, wait, no, no, please don't say...
And that is to throw
an even bigger party.
Which means.
- What is wrong with you people?
- Come on.
The Deltas
have got to out-party Dionysus.
I am still in Hell, aren't I?
Come on.
I can't believe it.
Delta's very first house party.
You know, I'm actually excited.
I get it now.
Parties aren't just
about getting drunk.
They're about building community.
This is so much better
than just some frat party.
Yeah, it would be
if anyone were here to see it.
- So, where is everybody?
- You know what? I think I know.
I don't know why we thought
we could out-party Dion.
You know what? Let's not give up yet.
Why not?
We have drinks, games, music.
We did everything
we were supposed to,
and no one came.
That's right.
We did everything
that we were supposed to.
But maybe we should ask ourselves,
what would Astra do?
If you really want to win,
it is not enough to be good
at your own game.
You also have to take
out the competition.
So, I am talking...
- sabotage.
- Yeah.
All right, what's the plan?
First, we take Dion out of play.
Now, I scoped out his place
when I was gonna burn it down,
and I have an idea.
'Sup, Charlie?
- Big D!
- Yeah.
Now that I got my team out
of your hair,
how about we get
a fresh keg and celebrate?
I like how you think, Shotgun.
Once he's out,
we mess with his party.
Anything we can do to kill the vibe.
Hacking into Dion's accounts and...
Buh-bye, party playlist.
Hey. Who cut the music?
What the hell is this?
Then we take out his booze.
And this is where
all the magic happens.
So, are these all lagers?
I'm sorry, bro.
No hard feelings, yeah?
Dad, now!
And now the keg is tapped.
So, final phase, hijack the party.
Hey, guys, I heard there's a rager
at Delta Chi Sigma.
So, what are we waiting for?
Let's go party.
I gotta say it,
you Legends do know how to party.
Rory, are you able
to lift the Chalice yet?
It's still not giving.
That doesn't make sense.
All of his followers are here.
Cool little trick you pulled
back there.
Gotta appreciate a good stunt.
Still, I heard there was a party
that I wasn't invited to,
and that hurts.
We're getting that Chalice, Dion.
As long as I have my followers,
my Chug Cup isn't going anywhere.
And bros are bros for life.
Bros are bros for life!
- Bros are bros for life!
- Hey!
Your reign on this campus is over.
I challenge you...
to beer pong.
You do know I'm undefeated
in all my years on campus, right?
Yeah, but it might be pretty hard
to hold on to all your followers
once they watch me demolish you.
So come on, D-Bag.
What do you say?
Winner takes all.
Dartmouth rules.
You know I can't say no
to a challenge.
Stupid whimsy. You're on.
But if I win,
Delta House gets shut down.
No sorority and no Chug Cup.
Yeah!
You sure about this, babe?
Because, you know, you can't see.
Oh, I've played some beer pong
in my life.
And plus, superpowers, remember?
The game is beer pong.
Now, sink a ball into a cup
and the other player drinks it.
And to make it even more fun,
body saves are fair game.
So remember, everybody,
the first player to clear
the other's cups takes it all.
Now, opponents, please shake hands.
May the best player win.
Whatever.
And pong!
Chug!
Okay.
Chug! Chug! Chug!
Chug!
Yes.
This point wins it.
All right. Let's do this.
I'm sorry, dude.
Yes!
Our winner!
We gotta give it to her.
Wait, wait, wait.
What happened to Bros for life?
I...
Come on. I know you wanna say it.
- I will not.
- Come on.
Then I will.
Go, sisters!
Got your cup.
- Yeah!
Best father-daughter weekend ever.
I can't believe that actually worked.
Yeah, you'll get used to it.
We couldn't have done it
without the three of you.
Yeah, thanks for sticking with us
even when we were right gits.
It's been real, ladies.
I'm sorry this chapter
of Delta Chi Sigma
has to come to an end.
Oh, it's not over.
We're gonna keep Delta House going.
- What?
- After the party,
I applied for a house on Greek Row.
Fitting in is hard enough.
So many people telling you
what to do and what to wear.
Now there's a space for people
to figure it out for themselves.
Thanks to you guys.
I get it. You're welcome.
- All right, ladies.
- Oi.
- What?
- One for the road?
Go.
Deltas.
- We'll miss you. We'll miss you.
- Say no to drugs, kids.
- Don't do it. It's not worth it.
- Yeah.
I need a nap.
You guys earned the good stuff.
You won the Chalice and, with it,
immortality for a day.
All right, guess it's time to chug.
To Behrad and to your mum.
Well, it's actually quite a lot
of responsibility, really.
And that is a lot of wine.
Why don't we all just drink from it?
I mean, who says there only has
to be three Fates, right?
Yeah, we could
all use the Loom together.
Yeah, you're not alone in this, love.
Yeah, immortality sounds pretty epic.
Let's drink.
Let's all do it, then.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Yeah, I'm not gonna drink,
super haram,
but I trust all of you to bring
my baby brother back.
Here goes nothing.
Oh, hey.
That's it.
Well, not exactly, bro.
You are all glowing.
Oh, must be the moisturizer
you recommended.
My skin feels tighter.
Literally, you're literally glowing.
Guys, we did it.
Come on, let's go and use that Loom.
And remember, no looming anything
that'll ruin my party.
Not that you would, Clotho.
- I can tell you're still chill.
- That's right.
Later days, Shotgun.
Later days, Dion.
You guys got some trippy art here.
- This cane was yelling at me.
- Yeah.
I'll take that. Nice one, love.
Sounds like someone's had
too much to drink.
Let's get you out of here.
- Bye.
Wow, I miss it.
Hello, traitor.
Just the woman I wanted to see.
Don't bother trying to win me back.
I don't need you anymore.
When you asked for my help
killing John Constantine,
I warned you,
you would be in my debt.
Well, honey,
I'm calling in the favor.