RIP: In 2166,
an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately,
my plan is opposed
by the body I had sworn
my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered
as legends.
GIDEON:
Previously, on Legends of Tomorrow...
RIP: His name is Chronos.
He works for
the Council of Time Masters.
Chronos was clearly sent
to bring me in.
SARA: The Lazarus Pit brought me back,
but it left me
with this need to kill.
Sara. Sara, don't!
(PANTING)
I'm dangerous.
Up until two months ago,
I was a barista, not some
damn winged demi-goddess.
Be the person, the woman,
- the warrior you were meant to be.
- (SCREAMS)
That wasn't so bad, was it?
Walk in the park.
Where are we now?
Washington, D.C.
The year is 1986.
We've landed
at the height of the Cold War,
in a world poised
for nuclear annihilation.
We've traveled here
because I have a new lead
on Vandal Savage's location.
Yes, Gideon managed
to intercept this telefax
concerning Savage's
last known whereabouts.
Tele-what?
It's like an email, on paper.
Wow. That's totally useless.
Dude, this whole thing's
crossed out.
Yeah, redacted
by the US government.
Which is why we are here
to steal the original file on Savage
back from those
who are tracking him.
Uh, that's the...
RIP: Now, now.
Don't worry. We are cloaked.
You want us
to break into the Pentagon?
Sounds awesome.
It sounds crazy.
What's the plan?
Oh, the fabricator will fashion you
the necessary
Pentagon credentials.
Ooh, and don't forget
our G-man disguises.
I always wanted to be a spy.
Now, the file we're after
is kept in
a secure records room.
In order to gain access,
we're gonna need to "borrow"
a magnetic keycard.
Because this is so much easier
than just shrinking down
and stealing it.
Let me show you how it's done.
Old school.
(GASPS)
You okay, ma'am?
I wasn't watching
where I was going.
- Thank you.
- Just doing my job.
That's a nifty little trick.
Really?
We're trying to save the world,
and you're lifting wallets?
It's called multitasking.
(BEEPS)
The records room
has closed-circuit cameras.
We need a diversion.
RORY: Someone call my name?
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Double or nothing says I put
this punk on the pine wood.
Yeah, I'll take a piece
of that action.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah!
- (CHEERING)
SARA: We got the file.
RIP: Okay, now for the tricky part.
All personnel are subject
to search
upon exiting the Pentagon.
Firestorm will divert the power
long enough for you to exit.
Ready when you are.
(GRUNTS)
FIRESTORM: All clear.
PROFESSOR STEIN:
What did you do, Jefferson?
I warned you about
the electromagnetic pulse.
Now, you've touched
a neutral wire,
causing the power
to pass through us.
You mean pass through me.
If you knew anything about
alternating current power--
- Grey?
- Yes, Jefferson?
Shut up.
(GRUNTS)
(ALARM BLARING)
The alarm.
This is a restricted exit.
Sorry. We must've gotten lost.
I'm gonna need to see
your keycard, ma'am.
- We have a Code Seven violation.
- (GRUNTING)
We have a slight problem.
(GRUNTING)
It's been fun, fellas. Back!
Where is that smoke coming from?
We've got the file.
What the hell
does Kendra think she's doing?
(YELLING)
Good question.
(GRUNTING)
Oh, wonderful!
We've got a demi-goddess
who's gone completely berserk!
Abort. I repeat, abort.
Get back to the ship right now!
FIRESTORM: Roger that.
I meant use the door!
But while you're at it,
can you help return
our winged avenger to her cage?
RAY: Instead of dwelling on
what went wrong,
let's, you know,
focus on the positive.
What are you talking about?
That was awesome.
PROFESSOR STEIN: In the same way
that tsunamis, earthquakes,
and other natural disasters
are awesome.
We got the file on Savage.
Despite the hiccup
with the alarm.
Oh, so it's my fault now?
You know,
maybe if you weren't always
yammering away in my head,
I could actually focus.
You have access to 60 years
of knowledge and experience.
Why not just take
advantage of that?
Because it's my body on the line
out there, not yours.
Hey! It's not your fault.
Everything would've been fine
if Big Bird over here
hadn't freaked out.
- Excuse me?
- Enough!
There is plenty of blame
to go around.
Now, fortunately, Gideon was
able to generate a low-end EMP,
which erased all
the Pentagon's magnetic media.
Like security footage.
Look, you're just lucky that
the Department of Defense
likes to keep incidents
like this under wraps.
Gideon, any luck
with our purloined secret file?
Please, say yes.
GIDEON: Yes, Captain.
According to the Pentagon,
Savage has defected
to the Soviet Union.
So, the most powerful evil
the world has ever known
has just gone red
at the height of the Cold War.
And now he's gonna help them
cook up something
that kills the future.
Gideon, set a course
for the Soviet Union.
GIDEON: Captain, we've just crossed
into Soviet airspace.
Don't worry, Jefferson.
We are moving far too fast
for anyone to track us.
I'm afraid that's not true.
Someone is tracking us.
- I thought the ship was cloaked.
- It is.
Boba Fett's back.
Chronos must've followed us
when we made the jump
from the '70s.
MAN: Sir, we have a lock
on the Waverider.
CHRONOS: Prepare to fire.
GIDEON: He's closing fast.
Captain, what would you
like me to do?
Slow down, drop our cloak,
and make as much
noise as possible.
Oh, that's like top three
on the list of things
we definitely shouldn't do.
Just trust me.
We run out of gas or something?
GIDEON: Chronos is still in pursuit.
Weapons systems tracking.
Look, if this is your idea of
trying to lose him, then maybe--
RIP: Aha! The Soviet Air Force
to the rescue.
Now, let's see how badly
Chronos wants to follow us.
Wow! It's a MiG-21.
No one's ever been this close
to one before.
Are you quoting Top Gun?
Maybe.
GIDEON: I've got heat-seeking missiles
closing at a distance
of less than a mile.
Which is why
I need you to cut the engines.
Whoa, wait, don't we need
those to land?
I said, "Cut them," Gideon!
(ENGINE POWERING DOWN)
GIDEON: Missiles are now targeting
something else.
Chronos.
RIP: I suggest you all
strap yourselves in.
This could be
a bit of a bumpy landing.
GIDEON: Initiating
emergency landing protocol.
- How's it going, Gideon?
- There's not much more I can do.
Elevation is
5,000, 4,000, 3,000...
When I said "bumpy," I meant
prepare for crash landing.
GIDEON: Good news, Captain.
Despite our rough landing,
the ship is still
fully operational.
Welcome to the USSR, gentlemen.
If it were up to me, they would
revoke your pilot's license.
They are more than welcome to,
considering I don't have one.
Did you get anything on Savage
from the Pentagon file?
It appears our friend has been
quite busy since
we last saw him.
- "Svarog"?
- "God of fire"
in Slavic mythology.
A secret project
the Soviets are working on.
And considering
Savage's involvement,
most likely some sort of weapon.
Valentina Vostok.
Graduated top
of her physics program
and then just
dropped out of academia.
To help develop
Savage's new weapon, no doubt.
The Cold War is up for grabs,
and this Vostok is the linchpin.
I say we put two in the back
of her head and call it a day.
(SIGHS) We have no idea
who this woman is
or what her effect
may be on history.
She may be the next
Madame Curie, for all we know.
She's working for Savage.
That's all we need to know.
She probably has no idea
who's backing her research.
Just let me approach her
as a scientist,
and we'll see what she knows
about Savage's weapons program.
It's 1986, you're American
and you don't speak Russian.
She'll have you pegged
as a spy in a second.
RIP: Perhaps I can help with that.
Ingestible translators.
They attach to your larynx
via neural interface.
Swallow them,
you can speak and understand
any language spoken to you.
PROFESSOR STEIN:
How do you turn it on?
Gideon, switch him into Russian.
(GULPS)
Go on. Say something.
(SCOFFS)
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
Wait.
I'm still speaking English.
I'm speaking Russian now,
aren't I?
Now you're annoying
in multiple languages.
RIP: Gideon, switch him
back to English.
Now, according to Vostok's file,
she's a big fan of the ballet.
She has box seats at the Bolshoi
and attends every performance.
GIDEON: It seems the final performance
of Le Roi Candaule is today.
Dr. Palmer, you will engage
Vostok at the ballet,
whilst you, Mr. Snart,
you're gonna be his wingman.
Aye.
Better go bone up
on Vostok's CV.
I guess I'll bone up
on the ballet.
Gideon, bone me.
We have a problem.
All right, you have to be
a little bit more specific.
It's Kendra.
She's completely unstable.
You saw her at the Pentagon.
Psycho priestess Chay-Ara
took over
and clawed a guard's eyes out.
Perhaps Kendra just needs
a bit of time.
Remember, it was her first time
out on the field
since Carter's death.
Well, Carter's not gonna be
the only dead body on our hands
if someone doesn't get her
under control.
You know, perhaps you're right.
And it just so happens
I have the perfect candidate
for the job.
No. No, I was not
talking about me.
And yet, I can think of no one
better suited to the task.
I'm not a fan of feelings.
If Kendra needs someone
to talk through her grief with--
Kendra needs someone to help her
get her warrior side
under control.
I imagine you,
above anyone else,
know how to do that.
This is a bad idea.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I got eyes on Vostok.
She's headed straight
for you, lover boy.
All right, gentlemen,
everything's looking good
from my end.
Proceed.
Miss Vostok?
Simon Huntzberger,
University of Moscow Physics Department.
I'm not interested
in talking to a student.
If you want a lecture,
come by office hours.
I'm actually a fellow scientist.
I read your paper
on applied physics
in nuclear fission.
Perhaps if you allow me
to take you to dinner,
we can discuss in detail.
Damn, that was cold,
even by Russian standards.
SARA: Heads up!
- What the hell is this?
- Warriors train every day.
Sorry, but I'm not in the mood.
Sorry's not gonna help
that guard
that you defaced
at the Pentagon.
Two months ago, I was a barista.
I had no idea I had some psycho
hawk-goddess inside of me.
And then I meet Carter,
and he convinces me
to let her out.
And now that he's gone...
I can't control it.
So thanks for the offer,
but I won't risk
letting that monster out again.
That monster inside of you,
it's not gonna go away.
You have to learn
how to control her.
And how exactly
do you expect me to do that?
Let's find out.
(GRUNTING)
- GIDEON: Temporal anomaly detected.
- (BEEPING)
Chronos.
The Russian jets
damaged his ship.
He's still alive?
He went down
just outside Moscow city limits.
RIP: Mr. Rory,
how would you like to accompany
me on a little mission?
Will I get to use my gun?
A near certain likelihood.
Lead the way, Captain.
SNART: You struck out, Raymond.
Maybe I should take
a crack at her.
I think we may have gotten off
on the wrong foot.
- I don't mean to bother you.
- (SCOFFS) Too late.
But as an investor,
I'm in a position
to fund your research.
That is why I wanted us to meet.
SNART: Easy, Raymond.
You're gonna spook her.
I think it's important to know
who's funding your research.
Don't you think?
For instance, Project Svarog?
Sorry. Is this man
bothering you?
Don't trouble yourself.
I'm not a damsel in distress.
Good.
Because I'm not a white knight.
(BELL RINGING)
It seems intermission is over.
We wouldn't want
to miss Queen Nisia
dancing naked with the nymphs.
My favorite part of the ballet.
But I've seen it so many times.
Perhaps you wouldn't mind
walking me home instead?
- I hate nature.
- (SHUSHING)
Thirty meters.
Chronos must be hiding out
in the trees.
DRUCE: Is that any way
to treat an old friend?
Time Master Druce?
How on earth did you find me?
You haven't exactly been subtle.
Can I waste this guy?
Could you give us a moment?
You said I'd get to use my gun.
Mmm.
What a colorful team
you've assembled for yourself.
- I thought that you were--
- Chronos?
He was killed in the crash,
I'm afraid.
I was sent
to scuttle his Timeship,
lest it be discovered
by the Soviets.
And you left
a temporal anomaly--
To lure you out of the cold,
as it were.
You've turned your back
on the very institution
you were meant to serve.
Our job is to protect time,
thereby protecting all life.
I am trying to save the world
from complete destruction.
You and your band of rogues
have run rampant
throughout history.
This is why we work alone, Rip.
A team is a liability,
you've proven that.
They keep you
from making the tough choices.
I am here
because the council refused
to make that tough choice.
Well, they can sometimes be slow
to realize the obvious,
but I've been authorized
to offer you a deal.
- (SCOFFS)
- End this foolish crusade,
return with me
to the Vanishing Point,
you'll be acquitted
of all charges.
And in a few hundred years,
we may even be able to fix
the damage you've caused.
And what about my team?
They will be returned
to their own timelines unharmed,
which is more than I can say
for Carter Hall.
You were one
of my brightest pupils
and, by far, my favorite.
Will you at least
consider my offer?
I'll consult with my comrades.
Please do, Rip.
Then meet me here in an hour.
And if I don't?
Then you are beyond my help.
That's a pretty sweet deal
Timecop offered you back there.
Well, I see,
we can add eavesdropping
to your criminal résumé.
Maybe you should start thinking
more like a crook.
Your friend is planning
on killing you.
Time Master Druce is one
of my most trusted friends.
Besides, if he wanted
to do me any harm,
why didn't he do it just now
when he had the chance?
Because he wants you to bring
the whole team with you.
And that's not gonna happen
'cause I'm taking a pass.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Are we done here yet?
If you wanna harness your power,
you need to learn
to control your fear.
Yeah, well, you've been training
for half your life
to be some
cold-blooded assassin,
so I really don't think
you understand what it's like.
Before you can control it,
you have to accept
that it's a part of you.
(GRUNTS)
- Ease up, will you?
- You gotta channel your anger.
Sara, stop!
Push down your emotions.
Focus on your opponent.
Kendra?
Sara. Sara, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Sara! What are you doing?
It's me!
(GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
Are you sure
you don't want your coat back?
I can't believe
how you're not freezing.
Oh, I love the cold.
And ballet.
So what is it about the ballet
that you love, Valentina?
The combination
of grace and strength.
Pushing the body
to its breaking point.
It's a thing of beauty.
My apartment.
You know,
this time of night, it's colder
than a Siberian winter.
Sounds perfect.
Though I'm sure
we could heat it up.
Sadly, I have business
elsewhere this evening.
Well,
if this is good-bye...
You enjoy the show, Raymond?
I think I've got frostbite
in some not-so-fun places
from waiting out here.
Did she tell you what kind
of weapon Savage is building?
Didn't come up.
Such a romantic evening,
I didn't want to spoil the mood.
So, other than
a steamy goodnight kiss
and a possible case of
hypothermia, we've got nothing.
I wouldn't say that.
It's Valentina's security badge
for a place
called Luskavic Labs.
Whatever weapon she's building
for Savage, we'll find it there.
I guess I should just be happy
you didn't swipe her wallet.
So, uh, what happens?
You hand over the ship,
turn yourself in to the Time
Masters, and the rest of us--
Will be returned to your
former lives in January 2016.
It will be as if you never left.
Aside from the fact
that Starling City
might be a part of the USSR,
thanks to our efforts.
All the more reason
to consider the offer.
The Time Council will do
everything within their power
to correct the mistakes
that we've made.
But they still haven't
changed their mind
- about stopping Savage?
- Well, according to them,
he's part of
the natural course of history.
Terrible as that course may be.
Look, I'm not saying that this
offer is without its downsides.
If we abandon our plan now,
then I still lose
my wife and son.
So, why throw in the towel?
I thought you said this mission
was bigger than any one of us.
Yes, but if you remember,
when I first recruited you,
I wasn't entirely forthright
about my motivations,
or about how
(SIGHS) dangerous this mission would be.
Carter Hall knew the risks
before he signed on.
Mmm.
Well, for the rest of you,
it's now time to decide
whether the future
is worth fighting for.
I cannot tell you
how pleased I am
to see you, Hunter.
I finally came to my senses.
You were right, as always.
I've risked the lives
of my team.
I've endangered
the very fabric of time itself.
I only hope you can forgive me.
All will soon be
made right again.
CHRONOS: Hello, old friend.
I'm so sorry
it had to turn out this way,
but the council cannot risk
keeping you alive.
Such a shame.
I won't be able to tell Mick
he was right.
- Mick?
- My colorful friend
who was convinced
you were planning on killing me.
Your friends seem to have
abandoned you, but no matter.
Chronos will track them down.
Can't believe you brought this
stooge to do your dirty work.
I never had you pegged
as a coward, Druce.
DRUCE: In that case,
I promise to stay here
to ensure that your punishment
is carried out properly.
I wouldn't want you
to die alone.
Who says I'm alone?
(GRUNTS)
What a wuss!
PROFESSOR STEIN: This is not the time
to show off.
It's best if we attack
from a covered position.
I'm through playing it safe.
This time, we do things my way!
- (GRUNTS)
- (BEEPING)
Run, punk, run!
Jefferson?
Chronos' blast forced us
to separate.
I didn't see where he landed.
Jax!
Jefferson!
All right, no need to shout.
I'm right here.
PROFESSOR STEIN: There you are.
Thank God, you're okay.
Why didn't you answer
when I called you?
Did it not occur to you
I might be worried?
Look, I just got a little lost.
We need to get him
to the MedBay, now.
Oh, gentlemen, I trust everything
went according to plan
at the Bolshoi?
Piece of cake. Made contact with
Vostok and swiped her badge.
Thanks to me. Pretty boy
just froze his ass off.
(GROANS)
- What happened to him?
- Chronos.
- Jax here was--
- Almost got himself killed.
We need to get you
to the MedBay.
RORY: Ah, the MedBay,
where a morphine drip awaits me.
Now just try and take it slowly.
Don't bother telling him
what to do.
He'll just do the opposite.
Oh, yeah, it would be my fault
that I got hurt.
Because I didn't listen to you
and your infinite wisdom.
I am sorry, Professor.
Exactly.
It seems this partnership
of ours has become untenable.
Partnership?
No, this is a dictatorship.
One in which
you get to call all the shots,
and I get to take all the shots.
Do you think I like
seeing you hurt?
Don't act like you actually
care about me, man.
I'm just a life support system.
I didn't even want to come
on this stupid trip.
- You kidnapped me.
- Oh, this old tune.
Did you ever stop to think
that I actually had a life
back in 2016?
I almost forgot,
a promising career
as an auto mechanic.
I had a mom,
a widow.
What happens to her if something
happens to me in 1986, huh?
She's just going to think
that I left her,
without even saying good-bye.
Man, do you have any idea
what that does to her?
We've all made sacrifices!
But can't you see
that this mission,
stopping Savage,
is bigger than any one of us?
I am so sick of you
using that tone.
When are you going to learn
you are not my father?
I'm sorry you lost him
at such a tender age,
but if your father
were here right now,
he'd be saying what I'm saying.
Just grow up, Jefferson!
The future of the world
is at stake!
And if you insist
on getting yourself killed,
as terrible as that might be
for your mother or me,
who incidentally would also die,
I am more concerned
with the billions of people
who will die
because of your arrogant,
adolescent ego!
Okay.
Please, don't say it.
I was cruel and unjustified,
and I said those things
just for the sake
of hurting him.
Why aren't you telling
that to Jax?
I had to hurt him, Raymond.
It's the only way
I can get through to him.
I've tried everything else.
Well, he's just a kid.
So was Ronald,
and look what happened to him.
Your former half of Firestorm.
Yes.
(STAMMERS)
I can't go through this again.
I can't lose another.
The reason I'm constantly
lecturing Jefferson
is because I'm the one
who brought him along,
and if something happens,
I'm the one
who has to go back to 2016
and tell his mother
that her little boy
is never coming home.
And I would rather die
than do that.
Ooh, that looks sore. What happened?
Maybe you should ask the lunatic
you put in charge
of training me.
Actually, I was hoping that the
arrangement between you and Sara
might be mutually beneficial.
You mean you knew
about this bloodlust thing?
Well, it's the captain's job
to know everything on his ship.
- (SCOFFS)
- Look, Sara went through hell
when she was resurrected.
I was hoping
that you'd be able to
coax out her human side
from the darkness
of the Lazarus Pit.
Why me?
Well, after 4,000 years
of reincarnation,
surely you know a thing
or two about rebirth.
KENDRA: Heads up.
Let's go.
"A warrior trains every day,"
remember?
I'm not a warrior.
And I tried to kill you the last
time we did this, remember?
"Tried" being
the operative word.
You wanna know my theory?
No.
I think your problem
is the opposite of mine.
I need to learn to embrace
my inner hawk goddess,
but you, you need to learn
to embrace your human side.
And what if that side
of me is gone?
What if she doesn't
exist anymore?
Well,
only one way to find out.
What, are you baiting me?
No,
I'm training you.
Come on.
Are you scared?
(GRUNTS)
Here we are. Luskavic Labs,
the secret facility
where Vostok works.
So, what's the plan?
Simple. We use Vostok's
credentials to enter the lab
and find out what she's building
on behalf of Savage.
Reconnaissance in a laboratory.
Finally, my kind of mission.
No, no, no, hang on a minute.
Jefferson's still recovering
from his injuries.
This is hardly a job
for Firestorm.
Let him rest.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(GUN COCKS)
I am Dr. Gregor Gavrilov
of the State Council of Science,
and I am here
to inspect the facility.
PROFESSOR STEIN: I'm in and heading
to the basement.
Here's hoping the key
that Mr. Snart stole
off Valentina works.
Oh, my God.
I know what
Vostok is working on.
She's trying to build me.
Hang on. What do you mean?
I mean, Savage has spent
the last decade
trying to level the arms race
against our team.
"Operation Svarog,"
the Slavic god of fire.
Of course, he and Vostok
are building a Soviet Firestorm.
They've already built
a thermocore.
Professor, need I remind you
this is
a reconnaissance mission?
It's only a matter of time
before Vostok figures out
how to stabilize
a Soviet Firestorm.
I'm not leaving without it.
It's the key
to building others just like me.
Yes, but perhaps you should
wait for the rest of the team.
They're on their way.
Are you familiar with ultra-high
energy cosmic rays, Captain?
The radiation released
inside this chamber
will kill anyone other than me.
Look, despite your impermeability
to nuclear energy,
you're still quite vulnerable
to bullets!
I just need someone
to take the core offline,
so I can remove it safely
and shield it.
RAY: I'm all over it, Professor.
(GRUNTING)
We're all over it.
PROFESSOR STEIN:
Remember, Dr. Palmer,
that shutting down
the core incorrectly
can lead to the creation of--
Strangelets, black holes
and uncontrolled fusion reactions
that consume the universe.
See, I was listening
during class, Professor.
How we doing, Boy Scout?
Uh, point of fact,
I completed all 21 merit badges,
including nuclear science,
so I'm an Eagle Scout.
Oh, we got a problem.
Valentina's headed towards
the core containment unit.
The radiation Stein's
about to unleash,
if she opens that door--
We're here to stop Savage
from building
a nuclear-powered superhero.
Saving some commie broad
ain't on the agenda.
Even if the radiation doesn't
kill her, Savage will
the second he finds out
the lab's been sabotaged.
Look, we got to get her
out of here.
Who's going to shut down
the core, Raymond?
I skipped that merit badge.
Raymond, why is the thermocore
still running at full power?
I'll handle the core,
you handle Valentina.
You're willing
to risk the mission
for a woman you barely know?
"Be helpful to others."
It's the Scout motto.
Thirty seconds. I'll get Vostok,
you kill the power for Stein.
And, Raymond, promise me.
(BEEPING)
(CORE POWERING DOWN)
Bad idea.
What are you doing here?
Believe me, I've been asking
myself the same question.
That night at the Bolshoi,
it was you who stole my keys.
And your wallet,
but it was nothing personal.
What the hell is that man doing?
He has no idea
what the core is capable of.
Relax. He's the one
who invented it.
I'm the first person
to have ever seen
cosmic radiation
with his own eyes.
You know,
let's keep it that way.
Snart, you better keep Valentina
out of the core
containment unit.
You used me.
You work
for American government.
I'm wanted
by the American government.
Does that count?
Look, I may be your
white knight, just this once,
but that weapon
Savage has you building,
he's creating
a nuclear-powered monster.
- (CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
- (GUN CLICKS)
I know.
It was sweet of you
to think of me
as a damsel in distress,
but I'm not the one
who needs rescuing.
Don't flatter yourself,
sweetheart.
I'm not the sentimental type.
No, but your partner,
the physicist
with the big brown eyes, is.
VOSTOK: Turn the core back online.
You will turn it back on,
or I will put a bullet
in your friend's head.
Don't you dare.
She's gonna shoot me
whether you do it or not.
That may be true,
and you can take that gamble
if you like.
It's only his life you wager.
Almost there.
SNART: I'm not joking, Raymond.
Don't you dare push that button.
Raymond, what's going on?
The core just went back online.
Sorry, Professor.
I had to do it.
You idiot.
I can still remove it.
I just hope I can absorb
the excess power.
No, do you have any idea
the kind of energy-- (GRUNTS)
Should have listened
to your friend.
JAX: What the hell
are you doing, Grey?
Jefferson?
You are not Firestorm.
You're just a stubborn old man
who's about to make
a really stupid decision.
Wait. Is this what it's like
when I'm in your head?
I apologize, dear boy.
It is rather distracting.
Your body cannot handle
this alone.
I appreciate your concern,
but you were right.
I've risked your life
enough times.
Now, it's my turn.
No!
(GRUNTS)
He's too weak.
JAX: He'll never get out
of there alone.
(GUNS COCK)
VOSTOK: Professor Stein,
your comrade here tells me
you know quite a bit
about this project of mine.
Very good.
You and I have much to discuss.
What are you waiting for?
You forget how to
use that thing?
My employer, Mr. Savage,
would very much like
to meet you,
and the rest of your friends.
Careful what you wish for.
- HEAT WAVE: This is where the party's at?
- (GASPS)
(GUNSHOTS)
(GRUNTING)
RIP: Mr. Snart, can you hear me?
Do not let Vostok leave
with that thermocore!
Get the hell out of here!
What are you waiting for?
Go, go!
(GUNSHOTS)
Now might be a good time
to send in reinforcements!
Mick and Stein just got pinched
by the Russkies!
You're gonna have to get out
of there right now.
You're hanging us out
to dry, Rip. I need backup.
I'm afraid our only option
is retreat.
What about my partner?
Well, until we devise
our next move,
Mr. Rory will have to
fend for himself.
Remember the mission.
If the Soviets get
that thermocore back,
your partner will not be
the only one who dies.
(GRUNTS)
You better kill me now.
If I ever get my hands on you,
I'm gonna get all Rocky IV
on your ass.
(GRUNTS)
I'm gonna remember that,
comrade.
We must leave now, Colonel.
There's still one more intruder,
and he has the thermocore.
We don't need it now.
We have something far better.
(PANTING)
Thank God
you managed to grab it!
Where was my backup, Captain?
Half the team is gone
because of you.
And if I'd have sent
the other half in to save them,
they'd be captured, too.
And where would we be, hmm?
Savage would have
both halves of Firestorm,
a dead Kendra
on top of a dead Carter.
Everything he wants.
It would be the end
to our little crusade
and, most likely, the world.
So, before you pull
that trigger,
ask yourself,
what would you have done?
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
That is a pretty cold
calculation, Rip.
Almost criminal.
Except we criminals have a code.
You never leave
one of your own behind.
We will get them back.
Now, if Savage even hopes
to create a Firestorm,
first, he's gonna need
a new one of these.
A thermocore?
Let me get this straight.
You had Kendra and I training
for the next mission,
when we should've
been out there helping them.
We will help them.
Now, our next mission
is to get our compatriots
back from Vostok.
Who's to say
they're not already dead?
Vostok needs the professor alive
in order to rebuild
the thermocore.
And Ray and Rory?
Savage will keep
them alive, too.
As leverage.
He'll torture them
if Stein tries to hold out.
Well, we have to pray
that he does.
If Savage's goal
is to create his own Firestorm,
then Stein himself is the key,
the missing piece of the puzzle.
And if Vostok figures out
how to turn
Stein's powers against us,
then...
I'm afraid the world
is beyond saving.
Stein is a lot tougher
than he looks.
I mean, it'll take a lot
to break him.
That's the good news.
RIP: The bad news is that
our compatriots are being held
in an impenetrable Soviet gulag.
Get a good night's sleep.
You and Dr. Vostok have much
work to do in the morning.
My companions from the lab,
what did you do with them?
Don't worry. They're alive.
Whether they remain that way
is entirely up to you,
Professor.
English - SDH