The Time Masters were an organization
charged with protecting history
from rogue time travelers,
but they were destroyed.
Under the leadership of Rip Hunter
we have taken up their mantle.
Sara Lance, former member
of the League of Assassins,
Dr. Raymond Palmer... The Atom,
The Arsonist... Mick Rory,
and Firestorm... The merged super form
of Jefferson Jackson
and myself, Martin Stein.
We are the only ones left
to protect history.
We are The Legends of Tomorrow.
Oh!
Sorry! My bad!
What the hell is going on out here?
Sorry, sir, he broke through the
security cordon downstairs.
Only because they wouldn't let me up
without an appointment,
but how does a regular guy
get an appointment
with the Mayor anyway?
Heywood, Dr. Nate Heywood.
I'm... here to talk
about Sara Lance, Ray Palmer,
and the rest of the Legends.
I think they're all in trouble.
Thank you for not
having me arrested back there.
Those security guards
really overreacted.
You know, one of 'em tried to Mace me.
Dr. Heywood, I only
agreed to give you five minutes,
which was three minutes ago,
because Ray and Sara
are friends of mine,
but I don't know the
first thing about any Legends.
Of course you do,
because you're the Green Arrow.
- Excuse me?
- Huh?
- We're done here.
- Look, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to drop a
bomb on you like that,
it's just, I've
exhausted all my normal avenues,
and you're the only person left
who won't think I'm crazy.
Are you sure about that?
I'm a historian.
I specialize in deductive
historical reconstruction.
In layman's terms, I'm a time detective,
which I really don't have to be
to look at a calendar to see
one week after you came to this city,
Robin Hood showed up.
You said that Sara and Ray are...
Traveling throughout time
with the other Legends.
"Legends" is what they call themselves.
Now, for the past six months,
I've been noticing
subtle changes to
history... Almost imperceptible.
Actually, if it wasn't
for a friend of mine
who's a quantum
physicist, I wouldn't have been able
to detect the subliminal alterations.
The point being, I think
your friends are responsible.
You're looking at me like
you want evidence.
Evidence, okay, an illuminated
manuscript
from 1216 depicting a knight...
Looks a lot like
your friend Dr. Palmer...
Same nose and and chin.
Erratic text describing a woman
in white with a bo staff.
Uh, hieroglyphic from Mesopotamia
depicting an albeit crude ship
that flies through the
air and disappears.
Let's skip to the part where
they're in trouble.
UFO sighting, New York City, 1942,
multiple witnesses report
a flying machine
diving into the Atlantic, which matches
not only the
Mesopotamian hieroglyphics but...
The part where they're in trouble!
Contemporaneous with the sighting
were multiple reports
of an underwater detonation
of an atomic bomb!
Now, the government has denied this.
You said 1942.
- That's three years before...
- Before the atomic bomb
was supposedly invented, yes.
I told you history was changing.
Dr. Heywood, if the Legends' ship
met an A-bomb,
they're not in trouble...
They're dead.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
_
We're closing in on your
coordinates, Dr. Heywood.
Are you seeing the sonar
readings of the sea floor?
Either that's a really weird-looking
rock formation...
or the wreckage of a time ship.
If the Legends
went down with the ship...
Where are the bodies?
The ship's keeping him in stasis.
How do you know that?
Oh.
My name is Oliver Queen
and my preference is
to not break your arm,
so I want you to calm down
and tell us what happened to your team.
You wouldn't believe
me even if I told you.
All I remember is being knocked out
by that skinny, little Englishman.
Very embarrassing.
I know that Sara told her father
she was leaving to protect history.
Why?
Why does history need protecting?
Because the idiots
who were protecting it...
The Time Masters, were blown up.
So you and the Legends took over?
Mm.
Chasing down time criminals
and fixing the parts of
history they screwed up.
Aberrations the captain called them.
We were chasing them
for about six months
without a problem.
Well, the occasional problem.
I knew we were all in trouble
when Rip made us put on blouses
just to save the King of France.
I look like an idiot.
I rather like the style of les
Mousquetaires de la garde.
- You would.
- Can we concentrate, please?
King Louis XIII is scheduled
to meet an untimely end
at the hand of Cardinal Richelieu's men
at any moment.
Roger that. I have eyes on the King.
Whatever you do, do not let
him out of your sight.
But if today's when he's supposed to...
You know, with the queen, I...
Raymond, without that consummation
there will be no
Louis coutures, no Sun King,
and no golden age of France.
Which means by extension
no Madame Curie,
no Louis Pasteur.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I get it,
history will be totally screwed,
but I don't have to
be there for the actual...
you know, consummation, do I?
It's beautiful, Your Grace.
As is yours. Who gave it to you?
My sister.
You speak of her as if she is gone.
I hate to see a lady
so beautiful so sad.
Your husband...
Enjoys the company of
his male courtiers.
Why should I be denied
similar... pleasures?
Sara...
I need to know that the Queen is secure.
Meantime, I believe
I've identified out assassins
and I'd wager those aren't
just swords on their hips.
Ah, yes, that would explain
the aberration.
My love, there is no need for you to...
knock.
Sorry to spoil the mood.
Where the hell's Sara?
Ha!
Everyone back to the ship!
That's easier said than done.
Grey, meet me on the north
side of the house!
It's actually a
chateau. What's your plan?
You'll see!
Oh, you've got to be kidding.
Oh, bloody hell.
That was the last assassin.
What did we say about using powers
and future tech, Dr. Palmer?
Well, yeah, but they started it.
Don't look at me.
I left my gun on the ship
like a good little Boy Scout.
What's going on?
Who are you people?
I believe the Queen is waiting for you
in her bedroom.
And I'll bet she's all
warmed up for you.
Shut your mouth, Jax, or
I'll cut your eyes out
and feed 'em to you.
I believe our work here is done.
Wait, how'd you go
from the court of Louis XIII
to the bottom of the Atlantic Ocean?
You said you wanted to
hear the full story.
We do, just some of us have lives
that we'd like to get back to.
We got ourselves in trouble
by visiting a time
we were told not to.
- 1942?
- Mm.
Who told you not to go to 1942?
Some guy in a hood named...
Rex Tyler.
Said if we set foot in 1942
we'd be all screwed,
and then he just vanished.
Okay, if he told you not to go to 1942,
then why'd you go?
Put another successful mission
down in the books.
Where are we off to next?
Gideon and I have calculated
a 96% likelihood
of another aberration in Bhopal, 1912.
Why can't it be Aruba, 2016?
For real. We've been going non-stop
for the past six months.
Nobody wants to address the fact
that Cardinal Richelieu's men
were armed with laser guns?
Clearly provided to them by
a time pirate or some-such.
Ah, Grey's right. We need
to find out who so...
You can get another chance of
destroying the very history
that you're supposed to be protecting?
Ah, I knew I forgot something...
The part where Rip tells us
everything that we did wrong.
As in seducing the Queen of France
just before she's supposed to conceive
the country's
greatest hope for the future?
- She seduced me.
- All wrong,
as in violating our policy
of not using super powers
in front of people?
They had laser guns.
At least I didn't screw up this time.
Ahem.
Stealing's not screwing up.
Another successful mission, Captain?
Yes, well, it seems I don't share
our team's definition of success,
but let's see if our labors came
to a certain fruition, shall we?
Well, that was fun.
I'm in no mood for a lecture, Sara.
Too tired from dishing 'em out?
Replacing the Time Masters is
an enormous responsibility,
Sara, and one which I fear
our team is ill equipped...
Gideon, are we under attack?
Negative, that was a shock wave
generated rat by a time quake.
A what?
A disturbance in the temporal zone
caused by an unusually large aberration.
You never mentioned a time quake before.
I've never
experienced one before. Gideon?
The shock wave's point of origin
was New York City, 1942.
That's not... possible.
Wait, what wasn't possible?
What?
You said you and the Legends
discovered an aberration
in 1942, what was it?
My guess is it involved Nazis.
You could say that.
The krauts nuked New York City in 1942.
Wow, someone just blew up New York.
During World War II.
Think we can all guess
who that someone is.
Nazis. I hate Nazis.
Aided by some sort of
time traveling ally, obviously.
Wait, does that mean the Allied
forces lost the war?
In which case, why aren't we
speaking German right now?
Because we're in the temporal zone.
And because it takes time
for the consequences
of an aberration... even one
as cataclysmic as this one,
to ripple throughout time.
So how much time do we have to stop it?
Isn't traveling to that particular time
precisely what Rex Tyler
told us not to do?
Well, what's the alternative?
We let New York blow up?
It's not like there are
Time Masters left to stop it.
Miss Lance is right, we are history's
last line of defense.
I like the sound of that.
I'd rather die than speak German.
Best case scenario, let's assume
that Mr. Tyler is wrong
and we all end up not dying in 1942.
What if, in endeavoring to
save New York, we make things worse?
What could be worse
than a genocidal fascist
nuclear-armed super power?
Relax, Captain.
We got this.
Gideon, I need you to pull
up everything you can
on the target in 1942.
I assume that by
"target" you mean Damien Darhk.
You are finally getting the hang
of this whole revenge thing.
All right, so we know that
he was alive during 1942,
so we just need to know where he is.
According to a 1942 FBI file,
the target was spotted here.
Hope I'm not interrupting.
No, just reading up on 1942.
You've been spending a lot
of time down here lately, alone.
Am I not allowed in the library?
Ah, you just never
struck me as a book worm.
I'm just making sure that you're not
holding onto anything.
I-I know a thing or two about grief,
so if you ever want
to talk about Laurel...
Then I know where to
find you. Thank you.
Miss Lance. Any luck pinpointing
the epicenter of
the temporal aberration?
No.
Perhaps these news reports
will prove useful.
Oh, that's good news,
even though we get nuked,
we still win the war.
Look at the date, Dr. Palmer.
In this version of history
World War II lasts
two more years.
And claims 12 million more lives.
Including Albert Einstein.
Actually, Einstein went missing
just prior to the attack on New York.
Wait. W-wait.
Perhaps these two events
aren't merely coincidental.
Think about it, a Nobel Prize
winning physicist goes missing.
And miraculously,
the Germans get the bomb
three years ahead of us.
They must've kidnapped Einstein,
forced him to build them an A-bomb,
which means the only way
for us to fix the aberration...
Is for us to kidnap him first.
Yes! Ha!
Gideon, please chart a course
for New York City, 1942.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe I'm going to meet...
Albert Einstein.
I can't believe you're
making me stay on the ship.
Mm. I'm asking you to stay
on the ship, Mr. Jackson.
While the rest of you
get to have all the fun
battling Nazis.
You're the only one that I trust
to give the time drive
a long overdue tune up.
And build the time library
and modify the bridge
and half the other 100 things
you've been getting me to do.
All right, give me your tools then.
- What?
- Pack up your tools
- and give 'em to me.
- Why would I do that?
Well, I'm gonna give 'em to Mr. Rory
to see if he wants to
be the ship's mechanic.
You see, that's not funny.
Quite right, because in the event
that we can't stop
this nuclear explosion,
a fully functioning time drive
is going to come in handy.
_
So how do we find Einstein in
a city of 7 million people?
Well, we just look for the physicist
with the crazy white hair.
I mean the other one.
According to Gideon, there's
a cocktail party
at Columbia this evening.
Cocktail party?
Means booze. Where is it?
At Columbia, I just...
Why does no one ever listen to me?
Hey, where you going?
I have a grandfather that's in the FBI.
I figured I'd check in
in case we need backup.
Oh. Good plan.
Hey!
Where do you think you're going?
Follow Sara, in case she needs backup.
Oh, God.
Take me to Conway and 5th.
Oh, jeez.
Never been to a nerd party before.
You mean a physics symposium.
- Nerd party.
- Keep your eyes open.
We're sure to be in the
company of German spies.
Th-th-that's him.
Good evening, ladies.
The greatest mind
the world has ever known.
I am merely
demonstrating Newton's third law.
"For every action, there is
an equal and opposite reaction."
Ha ha! I like him.
He's a pig.
I just found our spies.
- Them?
- Notice their uniforms.
The stitching on the lapels,
it's exquisite.
- You mean to say fake.
- Mm-hmm.
Surprise. Surprise.
How long have you been following me?
How long have you been following Darhk?
Shut your mouth, Ray. We got company.
Guten Abend, mein Herren.
- Are they speaking...
- German.
The extraction team is on the move.
Let me talk, I speak "physicist."
Oh, Herr Professor,
I'm so sorry to interrupt.
- Who are you?
- My colleague and I
were just having a rather
spirited debate
about your theory of relativity.
Perhaps you can help us settle it.
I was this close to getting them both
to come back to my room.
Well, what about your wife?
The one who died or the one
who divorced me 30 years ago?
Come on, it's time to go.
_
You don't have to speak
German to know what "uranium" means.
So what?
Even Einstein can't build
a bomb without fuel.
Darhk must be the one
supplying the Nazis.
Damien Darhk murdered my sister in 2016.
If I take him out here in 1942...
You save her.
I've been waiting six months
to get this son of a bitch.
You're gonna have to wait
a little while longer.
We gotta let him go.
Until we get our hands
on the uranium he's selling,
New York City's hanging in the balance.
I really hate you sometimes, Ray.
What do you two think you're doing?
We have to get you out of here,
your life is in danger.
This is why I never travel
without my security detail.
Help! I'm being kidnapped!
We might not look like it,
but we're the good guys.
Why should I believe that
you are really a physicist?
Because for every action...
there's an equal and opposite reaction.
So how'd it go with Einstein?
Depends on who you ask.
But apparently the professor
has one hell of a right hook.
Seriously? Grey punched him out?
Yeah, he's sleeping it off in the brig.
So can we get the hell out of 1942 now?
It looks like. Gideon?
I'm afraid not, Miss Lance.
But without Einstein's
help, the Nazis...
Still manage to destroy New York City
with an atomic blast.
The historical
aberration remains unchanged.
How is that possible?
The Nazis must've gotten the bomb
from someone other than Einstein.
Guten Morgen.
What is this? Some sort of prison?
What am I doing in here?
Good question.
I'm sorry, I never had the opportunity
to introduce myself.
I'm Professor Martin Stein,
just like "Einstein" minus the "Ein."
There's just so much I'd
like to discuss with you,
such as your paper
on unified field theory.
I have not yet published
my paper on unified field theory!
Who are you? Why have you abducted me?
The guys at the party wanted you to make
an atomic bomb for "ze Fuhrer."
No.
Not even a man as mad as Adolph Hitler
would want to create
such a terrible weapon.
You yourself once said
that two things are infinite...
The universe and human stupidity.
And you are living proof of the latter.
He just called you stupid.
Now, open this door and let me out!
We will, soon. I promise.
We saved you from the Nazis.
The least you could do
is help us save New York.
From what?
From some theoretical attack?
Some eventuality that not even
I could have predicted?
The only way you...
Mein Gott.
_
Yes, obviously you know.
I deduced it, Herr Doktor.
Perhaps you could
deduce how the Germans managed
- to create a nuclear bomb...
- Atomic.
When you are the only man on Earth
capable of performing such a feat.
Ja. That is correct.
I am the only man.
Wait a minute. You saying
there's some lady
out there that can make an atomic bomb?
Wunderbar. Why am I talking to him
when you are clearly
the brains of the operation?
You ex-wife is also a physicist.
Without Mileva's help,
I would still be working
as a patent clerk in Vienna.
So, while we were busy
safeguarding Professor Einstein...
The Nazis were busy kidnapping his ex.
Her name is Mileva Maric,
she's a fellow nuclear physicist.
Who, let me guess,
had no one guarding her.
Yes, Einstein's
collaborations with Ms. Maric
were a closely guarded secret
between the two of them.
A secret that the Germans
apparently knew,
so unless we can determine
where they're keeping her
while she manufactures their bomb...
If I had to guess,
I'd say she's with Damien
Darhk's uranium.
Damien Darhk? As in...
The man who murdered your sister.
How is Damien Darhk
even alive in 1942?
Thanks to the
Lazarus Pit, he hardly ages.
Sara's kind of an expert
on Damien Darhk.
- Drop it, Ray.
- I'm sorry,
but while you were all saving Einstein,
Sara was off on her own
secret side mission
to kill Laurel's killer in the past.
And I suppose you never thought
about saving your fiancée?
Yeah, of course I did,
but I never did it,
because it's against the rules.
What rules?
We're not Time Masters,
there are no rules.
Well, if there were, there'd
certainly be one
about lying to your team.
Listen to yourself.
Look, we get it, you're perfect.
Always the Boy Scout,
aren't you, Raymond?
Yeah, well, I could say the same thing
about you being an assassin.
Well, if we're being honest,
then let me get something
off of my chest.
Let's all just take a
deep breath, shall we?
You think that
you're such a big hero, Ray?
Without that fancy suit
you're nothing but a
self-righteous rich guy.
Maybe you're right...
but without my suit
there's no way of finding
Einstein's ex-wife,
or Damien Darhk for that matter.
Sorry, what are you saying?
That anyone who spends a lot
of time around uranium...
In this case Damien Darhk...
Picks up trace amounts
of radiation, which my suit can track.
And lead us straight to
the Nazis' nuclear bomb.
Beautiful work, Mileva.
Dr. Einstein should never
have let you get away.
I did what you want. Now let me go.
Actually, we still have need of you.
This thing didn't exactly
come with an owner's manual.
Get her and the bomb onboard.
We can't allow them
to get that bomb onboard.
- What about Mileva?
- Don't worry, Doctor,
we'll be sure to keep her safe,
but we must secure the nuclear bomb...
- Atomic.
- About to be placed
aboard a Nazis submarine.
This is no time for subtlety.
Agreed.
Let's make sure we all follow the plan.
Let's just get this done.
Step away from the lady and the bomb!
Final warning!
Schnell! Toten sie!
I love roasting Nazis!
Mein Gott!
We need to get Miss Maric to safety!
Sara!
Get down.
Interesting technique.
League of Assassins, am I right?
I've been waiting a long time for this.
Long time? For what?
- To kill you.
- Try to you mean.
Dr. Palmer, let's take precautions.
And disable the bomb? Already on it.
Uh, guys, a little problem here.
Suit's not as radiation-proof
as I thought.
Sara! Fall back!
Uh, guys, actually a big problem.
Haircut! Watch out!
Mick, look out!
Fall back!
Sara!
Mr. Rory's injured, Dr.
Palmer is incapacitated,
we need to fall back now!
Firestorm, cover Dr. Palmer and Sara.
Okay, Mick's on the mend
and Einstein and his ex
are safe and sound
with the security detail.
Thank you, Jax.
But the Nazis still have the nuke.
What are we doing leaving New York?
Because the Nazis still have a nuke,
which we saw being loaded
onto a U-boat.
They're gonna hit
New York from underwater.
Yeah, I'm tracking the uranium signature
recorded by Dr. Palmer's
suit, but before we engage the Nazis
I need you to make these modifications.
Really? Is now the time
for me to be playing mechanic?
Look, I know that you consider
the chores that I've been assigning you
to be a waste of time,
Jefferson, but believe me,
they're more than just an exercise.
What's the subliminal variance
of the quantum manifold?
- Two microns.
- And if one wanted
to divert power from the axial array?
Can't be done, you'd have to go
through the clavian adjunct.
Mm-hmm.
All of the stuff
you've been having me do,
you've been teaching me
about the Waverider.
I'm a time traveler, Jefferson.
I spend most of my time
thinking about the future,
specifically my own, and...
it occurs to me that
that future might not involve
me being aboard this ship,
and I need someone
to know its secrets in my absence.
Hmm, nice try, dude, but
you're not quitting on us.
What's a "Timescatter"?
Hmm? Uh, a last ditch option,
and one that I pray we
will never have to use.
Ah. We going swimming or something?
I'm tracking the Nazis U-boat.
Where is it now?
It's close.
_
They've knocked out our
telemetry, Captain.
- What's going on?
- As you can see, the Waverider
is ill suited for underwater combat.
I'm trying to bypass the
tertiary subsystem array.
Make it fast, haircut.
Yes!
Is the weapon ready?
Yes, Herr Darhk.
Fire!
What was that?
They're not firing on us.
It's the nuclear bomb.
Atomic.
Whatever it is, we gotta stop it.
I fear that there is only
one way to do that.
Okay, I don't know what
you wanted me to do,
- but I did it.
- Excellent work, Jax.
- What's going on?
- I am piloting us
on a collision course with the torpedo,
Now, with any luck it will
hit us before New York City.
How is that lucky?
Can the Waverider handle the blast?
Honestly, I have absolutely no idea.
Which is why... I'm doing this.
Where is everybody?
The appropriate question is when.
Other the last few months
I've implemented a safeguard
in case of a catastrophe. A
high burst of temporal energy
has scattered our team
throughout history.
I knew you never liked me.
I'm afraid, injured as you are,
you wouldn't survive
the rigors of time travel,
which is why... I'm doing this.
Gideon, how much time do we have?
30 seconds, Captain.
Gideon?
I'm here, Captain.
You always are.
Okay, there's just one question
that you haven't answered.
Where's Captain Hunter?
I don't know. Must
have time-scattered himself
like the rest of them.
Guess I gotta play hero and find them.
Do you even think this ship still flies?
I don't see why not. Fridge works.
I don't have time to time travel,
but if your team is stuck in history,
who better to help find
them than a historian?
This guy?
Without Dr. Heywood
you'd still be in stasis.
Ah. Good point.
Library, this way.
Hey, wait. Time out.
This was supposed to
be a salvage mission.
Who are you kidding? You've been waiting
your whole life for a chance like this.
Well, I-I did some digging, but I think
I finally got a lead on Ray Palmer.
Uh-huh.
Are you, uh, sure you know
how to fly this thing?
Let's find out.
Maybe you should slow down?
Maybe you should shut up and strap in.
I can't believe this.
We're about to travel through time!
Did I tell you about the side effects?
What side effects?
Oh!
Mick! Buddy!
- How'd you find me?
- I didn't.
Pretty did.
Is he okay?
Side effects of time travel.
Speaking of, you're never gonna believe
where the rest of your team ended up.
This festival is boring.
Bring me my wizards!
My liege, how may we entertain you?
Do you wish to gaze into my
magic mirror, Your Majesty?
I grow bored of your tricks.
Off with their heads.
- What?
- You little brat.
This is incredible. An actual
medieval execution?
I never imagined I'd
see this with my own eyes.
Who... Who's that?
The new guy.
- New guy, duck!
- Hiyah!
I'm Dr. Heywood, I heard
so much about you.
Hey, how about we get to know each other
- back on the ship?
- Okay.
But first we have to find Sara.
Vile witch!
You have corrupted
the women of our village!
In my defense, they were
happily corrupted.
Hang the witch! Hang the witch!
You must be Sara Lance.
Oh! whoa, whoa, it's okay. He's with us.
Hey.
Is she always this violent?
I'm sorry, but so far I haven't
been able to detect
any historical alteration
that would indicate
Mr. Hunter was stranded in a time.
Uh, why don't we ask Gideon where he is?
Who's Gideon?
Greetings, Dr. Heywood.
I am the ship's
artificial consciousness.
Gideon, we need you
to tell us where Rip is.
I'm afraid I have no idea,
but I would be happy to play
his final message for you all.
Final message?
Sorry for stranding
you all throughout history,
but it was the only way to save you.
Well, you know what they say,
Captain must never abandon his ship.
Well, neither shall I abandon hope
of seeing you all again
someday, somewhere in time.
As flawed and unruly as
you are individually,
together you are the best crew,
the best team a captain
could ever hope for.
So...
stick together.
And remember,
history is yours now, my dear Legends.
Good luck.
So, what do we do now?
We drink.
It's not like we were
exactly Time Masters, even with Rip.
But I think he knew that one day
we might have to do this without him.
And we all heard his
message. He wanted us to keep going.
Weave to keep going.
There's a rogue time traveler
out there somewhere.
Yeah, a time nemesis whose idea of fun
is helping Damien Darhk and the Nazis
blow up New York City.
What's to stop them from
going back in time
and kidnapping Einstein
and his ex-wife again?
We can't be everywhere at once.
But you can safeguard the Einsteins.
Safeguard the Einsteins?
How?
By making one slight
alteration to history.
_
We'd like to talk to Mr. Einstein. CIA.
He means OSS. This is related
to the Manhattan Project.
You're headed to Columbia
University, right,
- for the symphony?
- Symposium.
- Same thing.
- Once you're there,
we're gonna need you
to publicly announce
that Miss Mileva Maric
has been your silent partner
for over 30 years.
You see, acknowledgment
of Mileva's contributions
is the only way to keep her safe.
Besides, it's the right thing to do.
Don't be a jerk.
Today I want to tell you about
a very special woman,
my longtime collaborator, Mileva Maric.
What does that mean?
Krauts won't be able to get to her?
Yes, and then people won't say,
"Hey, you're a regular Einstein."
They'll say, "You're
like one of the Einsteins."
That's so crazy.
I can't believe we just changed history.
No, Dr. Heywood, we saved it.
You promised no trouble, Herr Darhk.
And you promised me competency.
Perhaps we'll have
better luck with the next bomb.
That's cute, but
there won't be a next bomb.
You see, my partner wants
to move on to other things.
But your partner isn't here, is he?
According to who?
Hello, Eobard.
Mr. Darhk.
Ah, how'd it go with Einstein?
Good, until someone
gives the Confederate Army
machine guns or breaks
Mozart's fingers, or...
One aberration at a time.
Hey, remember that thing
that I said before
about you being a...
Billionaire Boy
Scout? You weren't all wrong.
Yeah, but... you're more than that.
Thanks.
And we'll get justice
for Laurel, Sara, promise.
What do you guys say we get outta 1942?
Not until you answer a few questions.
We're the Justice Society of America.
And you're coming with us.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --