In 2166, an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan
is opposed by the body
I'd sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future, my friends
may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered
as legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
I was her.
Tragedy or heartbreak.
That's how it always ends
if the man's not Carter.
Time Master Druce?
You and your band
of rogues have run rampant
throughout history.
This is why we work alone.
A team is a liability.
The Time Masters have issued
Omega Protocols on all of us.
- They've sent the Pilgrim.
- Who's the Pilgrim?
The Pilgrim is the Time Masters'
most deadly assassin.
She's hunting our younger selves.
Kaylex Druzan,
you have been found guilty
of time piracy in the first degree...
and sentenced to death
via Omega Protocol.
The Pilgrim has made contact
with your younger self.
This will all be over quickly.
Well done.
Here's your next assignment.
These individuals
have manipulated the timeline
without authorization
on multiple occasions.
You are hereby ordered to hunt down
these individuals' younger selves
and eliminate them.
This isn't my element.
- It's mine.
- Just keep a weather eye open
for the Pilgrim.
Gideon calculates a 97 percent chance
that she will attack
your younger self
in this exact time and place.
Roll it.
Young Rory's not in there.
But we found his parents.
They're dead.
Then where the hell is he?
Come with me if you want to live.
I always wanted to say that.
- That's younger you?
- What'd you tell him?
That we work for a secret
agency called A.R.G.U.S.
- I think he bought it.
- Course he did.
He's an idiot.
Hey, no offense, but do you
really think it's a good idea
to leave him unsupervised?
You're right. Have fun.
You seem calm.
You mean considering
a temporal bounty hunter
is trying to murder
our younger selves?
I was gonna put it a little more
delicately than that, but yeah.
I think at some point, you just learn
to live with a sword over your head.
Either you're getting better
or I'm getting lazy.
So it seems like you decided
to ignore the advice
from Old West you
about not being with Ray.
Ignoring her advice about Ray
was your advice, remember?
Don't listen to my advice.
- So did you tell him what she said?
- Oh, sure.
"Hey, Ray, by the way,
the woman I met in 1871 was me.
And she told me our love
was doomed to fail
because you're not Carter."
- So that was a no?
- Look, Ray and I are happy together.
We should be able to enjoy that
before I have to drop
the whole doomed love affair thing
on his head.
Yeah, I mean, who wants
a relationship based on honesty
and communication?
Believe me.
A relationship based
on an ancient Egyptian curse
doesn't work much better.
Mr. Rory, how are you feeling?
I mean, your younger self.
Jax is watching him.
That young man,
you, just lost his family.
You might want a shoulder to cry on.
I don't cry, Professor.
Oh, and Haircut,
thanks for saving me.
You're welcome.
You know what I don't get
is why doesn't the Pilgrim
just go back a week earlier
and kill younger Rory then?
'Cause the Omega Protocol
calls for precision.
Multiple attempts from the Pilgrim
could do irreparable temporal damage.
Which means she's only got one shot
at killing each and every one of us.
And we only have one shot
to extract your younger selves
from the timeline
before she pulls the trigger.
Sir, based on the temporal wake
generated by the Pilgrim's time ship,
I calculate a 96 percent likelihood
that she is heading
to Starling City circa 2007.
Pilgrim is targeting Miss Lance.
- Name?
- Lance.
Sara Lance.
This is ridiculous.
Come on. I thought it was
Take Your Daughter to Work Day.
Yeah, if I was in grade school.
"Daddy, I'm doing a paper
on the criminal justice system.
I want to see what it looks
like on the inside".
Well, I didn't mean
inside a jail cell.
Too bad, 'cause that's the next stop
on our little tour.
I think you're enjoying this
a little too much.
Honey, it's the dream of every father
to keep their daughters
locked up until they're 30.
Maybe even 40.
What the...
Daddy!
Get out of here. Get out of here!
Go, go, go!
- God, she's...
- Quite the badass.
I put her in the cargo bay
with mini you,
told them both to stay put.
The less they know
what's going on, the better.
You sure you want to leave
daddy's little girl with that punk?
Even before the League of Assassins,
I knew how to handle guys like you.
Has Gideon figured out
the Pilgrim's next target yet?
- That's peculiar.
- Peculiar or bad?
Gideon, run another scan
for the whereabouts of the Pilgrim.
I'm sorry, sir.
The timeline shows
no temporal distortions.
I seem to be unable
to track the Pilgrim.
That doesn't sound good.
No, it's quite the opposite.
Without a way to track
the whereabouts of the Pilgrim,
she could target any one of you
at any point in time.
Gideon was tracking
the Pilgrim's temporal wake.
I didn't think it was possible
to conceal one's movements
through time.
Well, it is if the Time Masters
are on your side.
How does this all work?
If she can travel to any place
at any time,
she could be killing any of us
right now.
- And if we die in the past...
- We die in the present.
Wow. So interesting.
How long does it take
for what happens in the past
to affect the present?
Could I be dead right now
and not know it?
Maybe I am dead right now.
- Hello? Can anybody hear me?
- No.
Look, the important thing
is not to panic.
Somebody's playing Russian roulette
with our younger selves.
Why would we panic?
Well, there are a few exceptions.
Kendra's ability to reincarnate
means that it would do the Pilgrim
no good to target her.
And as a former Time Master,
to remove me from history
would be quite dangerous
to the timeline.
Well, that's convenient.
- And what's that supposed to mean?
- Nothing.
It just occurs to me you've never
told us about your past, Rip.
And I don't trust a man with secrets.
Look, the less information
you have to offer on me,
the less valuable you are
to our now numerous enemies.
Like I said, convenient.
- Are they fighting?
- This is not a fight.
It's merely an exchange of ideas.
No, not you. Them.
She slapped me.
The little weirdo said that he liked
the way that I smelled.
I'm usually a lot smoother,
but I'm sort of freaking out
right now.
You, hands to yourself.
The next time,
hit with a flat palm.
And you...
you're not her type.
Now, do I need to separate you two?
No.
Hey, when do I get to go home?
You're safer here. Trust me.
Well, where is here?
And why do you look like me?
Please, will you just tell me
what the hell's going on?
Look, it's safer for you if I don't.
And we look alike, because...
because we're like family.
And I need you to trust me.
Look, my dad,
he's got to be freaking out.
If he ever lost me...
He won't lose you.
Ever.
I promise.
Hey.
Did you know that Rip has
a secret stash of vintage cereals?
Fruit Brute was always my favorite.
Are you okay?
I'm a little on edge.
You know, we've been
through a lot together,
and you've never quite resorted
to eating sugary cereals.
Look, I've spent a lot of my life
thinking about the future.
And now, I have to think
about the past,
which is sometimes the present.
And...
the point is,
do you know where I go to
when things get crazy?
Which for us is always.
I go to those two years
in Hub City,
when it was just you and me,
and it felt like we had forever.
Yeah.
That's what kept me grounded.
In fact...
seconds before Rip
and the team came back,
I was about...
Ray!
What's wrong?
Oh, my God.
Gideon, we need help!
What's happening to him?
He is suffering
from severe internal injuries.
Who's doing this?
A deep scan
of Mr. Palmer's timeline
reveals a temporal anomaly
on December 19, 2014,
in the vicinity
of Palmer Technologies.
The Pilgrim.
Gideon, get us to that location now!
- Who are you?
- I'm no one.
We have that in common.
We need to get you to cover.
What is that thing? Who is she?
Who are you?
No time to explain.
No.
Rip and the team
are saving you in the past,
and I'm here now.
However long we have,
I want to spend it with you.
My suit.
It works.
Mr. Palmer's vitals are stabilizing.
They did it.
Actually, I think you get most
of the credit.
I couldn't miss spending
the rest of our lives together.
I meant it, Ray.
I love you.
I guess you found the ring.
The ring?
Kind of a strange way
to get engaged, but...
I'll take it.
What the Pilgrim did, the way
she turned our attacks back on us,
it was as if she was reversing time.
It's called
temporal micromanipulation.
The ability to control time
in one's immediate vicinity.
We are lucky to have
saved Dr. Palmer.
So basically we have no idea
who she's going after next.
We know it's not Rip
because he doesn't have a past
to go back to.
Gideon, prepare
for multiple time jumps.
Plot points here, here, and here.
My birthday? Why are we...
The only way to ensure
you're not harmed in your past
Is to abduct ourselves as newborns,
thus removing ourselves
from our future timelines.
It's brilliant.
- It's morally questionable.
- It's suicidal.
If we take too long
in getting them home
Then history is altered.
There won't be a home to go back to.
You'll disappear from the minds
of everyone who's ever known you.
You mean, my own mom
won't even know me?
My wife.
Yeah, and my...
Oh, yeah.
I don't have anyone.
Sure as hell beats dying.
Hey.
- How's Ray?
- Fine.
His younger self is in the hospital,
so our Ray is healing rather quickly.
You know, you don't seem
too happy about it.
I'm not unhappy. I'm...
I'm engaged.
- What?
- Yeah.
Ray proposed to me while he was...
You know what, it's a long story.
But you said yes.
At the time.
I... I never thought about marriage.
I didn't think I was able
to think about marriage.
I don't know what to do.
That's hard.
Do you like babies?
Yeah, but that sounds
like doubling down to me.
I need your help.
And then I'll help you figure out
what you should say to Ray.
Okay.
Let's go.
All right. This is just like
any other mission.
The mark may be a newborn,
but it might as well be a diamond
or a microchip.
You know what? You're starting
to sound like Snart.
Okay, which one is Snart?
Look for the one with horns.
Found him.
Great, grab him. Let's go.
Well, hello, baby Snart.
Look at you.
Kendra, come on.
We don't have time for this.
Look.
Oh, look at those little cheeks.
You are the cutest little baby
in the world.
Poor kid.
He's gonna have a rough life
ahead of him.
Good thing we're kidnapping him.
What are you doing?
I'm getting us out of here.
We don't even know where here is.
Identity confirmed.
Sara Lance.
Let's go.
Where do you think you're going?
Give me that. Inside.
Is that a baby?
Yes, and you guys
are in charge of him.
- Wait, I...
- You made five grand
last summer babysitting.
You'll be fine.
- No, I don't do babies.
- You do now.
Think of it as a thank you
for saving your life.
You better not drop my future
criminal partner.
Otherwise you're in trouble,
comprende?
We've got Mr. Snart's younger self.
Next stop is you, Professor,
and you, Mr. Jackson.
How strange to imagine,
holding one's infant self.
Actually, none of you should
participate in your own abductions.
Let's call it paradox prevention.
It's almost worth the risk.
To experience how our own fathers
must have felt the day we were born.
Yeah, well, not my dad.
He shipped out before my mom
went into labor.
Yeah, he died two weeks later
in Somalia, so...
- I'm so sorry.
- Yeah.
I think I see the head.
Look at that.
What do you think of Jeremy
as a name?
Oh, I think he looks more
like a Martin.
You guys asked for a doctor, right?
Yeah, how would we?
He means that we were
on our way to the hospital
and we saw your automobile.
Yeah, and this little munchkin
needs a checkup.
Prenatal care, it's very important.
He means postnatal.
We'll take him straight
to the hospital.
We'll meet you there.
What about my wife?
It's somewhat disconcerting
that my father
would give me up so willingly
to two complete strangers.
Well, the 1950s was a much
more trusting time.
Trust me, I lived then.
- He's not in Somalia.
- Huh?
We need to hold off
on taking Baby Jefferson.
I need to find grown Jefferson.
But Rip said that we...
I doubt very much that giving the boy
a moment with his
soon to be dead father
will do the universe any harm.
What are you doing, Gray?
Trust me, Jefferson,
there's someone here
I really think you should meet.
Go talk to him.
And say what?
Speak from your heart.
Go.
You were supposed to be shipping out.
How do you know that?
Oh, right.
My transport got delayed.
I told my CO my wife's giving birth.
He got me a pass and a Jeep.
And I made it. I saw him.
My boy.
Which one's yours?
Oh, oh, no, I'm, I'm not a dad.
I just...
I'm here for my family.
Well, I hope you get to experience
this for yourself one day.
Imagining all the things my boy's
gonna be when he grows up.
How do you know?
'Cause he's my son.
Jefferson Jackson,
remember that name.
He's destined for great things.
I've got to go.
Will you give the nurse
a message for my wife?
You're leaving already?
Be AWOL if I don't.
I just want her to know
that I saw my son,
and that I couldn't be
more proud and happy.
And tell her I'll be home
as soon as I can.
Can you do that?
Wait.
I got to tell you something.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Appreciate that.
We're here.
- Where is here?
- Come, I'll show you.
Again, where is here?
We need a safe harbor
to keep your younger selves.
I've been waiting.
It's good to see you.
It is good to see you too, Mother.
Don't forget to take your boots off
before you come back in.
Oi!
Off you go.
So, this is where Rip plans
on keeping our baby selves.
If all goes according to plan,
we'll only be here for a few minutes,
then presumably never remember.
When's the last thing
anything went according to plan?
I don't think there was a last time.
I really would sit up if I were you.
She'll kill you
if she catches you slouching.
Don't be fooled by appearances.
That woman is as tough as nails.
Funny how you never mentioned
having a mother.
Adoptive mother.
Now, can I interest any of you
in some more tea?
Thank you.
So, Michael.
- Michael?
- That's me.
My birth name.
The Time Masters insist
on the adoption
of new identities
for their protection.
How do you know so much
about the Time Masters?
I work for them.
Oh, don't worry.
My true loyalty is to my children.
Thank you. The Time Masters
fill their ranks with children,
orphans pulled from throughout
the course of history.
When Michael arrived at the Refuge,
he had nothing
but the clothes on his back.
There's a reason
it's called the Refuge,
and a reason that it exists
in a secret location in history.
The Time Masters will never
think to look for you here.
Thank you for your assistance.
Look, I know I make a gorgeous
baby, but I should warn you.
You've got your hands full with me.
I assure you,
you're not the first tough case
to arrive at my door.
Where'd you find the match?
You can always find them.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Not as beautiful as a whole house
going up in flames, though.
- It was an accident.
- Sure it was.
You don't know me.
You think I wanted to kill my family?
I think you fell in love
with your dad's lighter fluid.
with the flames dancing around.
But then you realized
you couldn't control them,
and you ran
without waking your family.
The only thing you were concerned
about was your own skin.
Now, while I'm gone,
there better not be any accidents.
If there is,
I'm gonna come looking for you.
I'm gonna kill you.
You sound just like my dad.
I couldn't quite bring myself
to leave this place just yet.
I've made you something
for your travels.
Some mince pies for your friends.
My friends.
They're the people
whose relationships
with their friends and family
I've put at risk to save my family.
- You think you've been selfish?
- I do, yes.
What a load of old codswallop.
I've always known that you were
brought to me for a reason, Michael.
That you were ready for great things,
but you won't accomplish
anything by wallowing.
So for goodness' sake, pull yourself
out of it and get the job done.
And what about you?
I have put you in terrible danger.
You don't honestly think I'd let you
go away with my best serving dish
if I didn't think
I'd see you again, do you?
I can manage quite happily
with a house full of 10-year-old
Time Masters.
So I think I can perfectly deal
with the adult version.
- Go on!
- Yes, yes. Thank you.
Jefferson?
Hey.
What's up, man, we good?
Oh, please.
We share a psychic connection.
I know how you're feeling,
and I'm sorry.
I thought affording you time
with your father
would lift your spirits.
Yeah.
II thought so too.
I just...
I should have said something.
I should've told him about
what happens to him in Mogadishu.
- I could've saved him.
- You don't know that.
It's highly unlikely
you could've said anything
that would've changed his fate.
My whole life,
everything good I ever did,
every report card,
every touchdown,
in the back of my mind,
I always wondered,
what would my dad think about this?
Hey.
Hey, I was just on my way
to the bridge.
No, wait. Wait, please.
I didn't mean to be a lurker,
but I heard you and Sara talking.
And I get it.
You thought I was dying.
You told me what I needed to hear.
And it worked.
So if you need a reason,
a way to let me down easy...
Ray, no.
I want to be with you.
It's just that I know
that we can't last.
- Says who?
- Me.
The woman I met in 1871...
was me.
And she warned me
that it would end in heartbreak
if I ever tried to be with someone...
Other than Carter.
God, this is just too complicated.
No, it isn't, really.
I mean, if I make you happy,
if being with me makes you happy,
then you can be happy.
Or you can choose to listen
to some former version
of yourself who believes in curses.
When you decide, let me know.
Everyone please report
to the main deck immediately.
What's going on?
Gideon has intercepted
a transchronal beacon.
Gideon, show them.
This message is for Rip Hunter.
I'm going to make this
very quick and very simple.
If I can't find you...
I can find those you love.
Anna?
- Dad!
- All of them will suffer
and die because of you.
Your family, friends,
anyone you've ever cared about.
Unless you surrender
your younger selves to me.
So she can erase you all
from history.
If it's of any comfort,
you won't feel a thing.
As for your loved ones,
I cannot promise the same thing.
Gideon, I take it
that the Pilgrim's transmission
included a carrier frequency
through which she can be contacted?
Yes, Captain.
Hail her, please.
What are you planning to do?
- Captain Hunter.
- Look, I'm gonna make this easy.
I already have.
The lives of your team's nearest
and dearest for their younger selves.
And I'm gonna counter that demand
with an offer of my own.
I will surrender myself
if you spare the lives of my crew
and their loved ones.
A noble gesture.
But worthless.
My directive is to eliminate
your entire team, not just you.
Yes, well,
I'm not talking about me now.
I'm offering you me in the past.
Rip Hunter before he became
a Time Master.
Eliminate him and this team
will never have been.
If this is some kind of trick...
It's no trick.
Enough people have died
at my expense.
Gideon will send you the location.
And, Mr. Snart, your wish
is about to come true.
You're going to meet my younger self.
- What is this place?
- Neutral ground.
It's a defunct Time Masters outpost.
I thought we were supposed
to be picking up your younger self.
He's being brought to us, actually.
That little boy was at the Refuge.
He's you.
- You got my message?
- I don't approve
of what you're planning.
Not that it ever stopped you before.
Your younger selves
are all still safe and sound.
Thank you.
You're a naughty one.
That's right.
I think it's probably about time
that you left.
Give her hell.
Where's my dad?
On board my ship,
along with the rest.
All in perfect condition,
as long as your captain honors
his end of our bargain.
You'd murder a child?
I'd murder as many children
as is necessary
to accomplish my mission.
Do you know what this will do to
the timeline, killing a Time Master?
In case you've forgotten,
I am sanctioned
by the Time Masters
to do what my former colleague
Chronos here failed to do.
Enough of that.
Let's get down to business.
Where's the rest of your group?
They're around.
I'll be taking the boy.
Before you do that,
we don't believe for a second
their loved ones are on your ship.
A show of good faith, then.
A prisoner exchange.
Send the boy,
and I'll send the father.
Once I have the future
Captain Hunter in my possession,
then I'll release the rest.
- What the hell's going on?
- You don't need to understand.
Only walk.
You are gonna be absolutely fine.
I promise.
As soon as my dad's in the clear,
let's light this up.
Remember, we wait for Ray's cue.
I'm in position.
You wanted to see me?
Have I done something wrong, miss?
Not yet.
Now!
Fool me once.
Now, Kendra!
I was willing to proceed
in good faith.
Now you'll watch those closest
to you die.
Thought you could snuff me out?
You don't know me at all, miss.
Hey, are you okay?
Not really.
Yeah, let me explain.
You poor boy.
I'll take you. Are you all right?
That's you.
Yeah.
I was a cutpurse
from the age of five.
Starved more than I ate.
I knew what I'd do
if she tried to harm me.
Lucky for us,
you didn't forget your roots.
Believe me, Mr. Snart,
I've tried.
There you are.
The Pilgrim may have been dealt with,
but the Omega Protocol
is still in effect.
I'll look after your friends,
don't worry.
Oh, I know you will, Mum.
You did the same for me.
It must be strange for you
to see yourself as you were.
Do you remember the first day
you were here?
Yes, I think
I tried to steal your purse.
God, I was a mean little bastard.
- You were tough.
- I was selfish.
Well, you were surviving.
I was home.
Which is why I know you'll be back.
Here to give me another
"don't burn down the house" speech?
You think by hurting yourself,
it's gonna make you feel better
about the fire?
You don't know anything
about me, man.
Guess again, kid.
I'm you.
What?
That's right.
You're too young to understand.
But understand this.
It wasn't your fault.
I let that flame get out of control,
like you said.
I ran out without waking anybody,
I was just so afraid.
You were just a kid.
I spent my whole life blaming you,
hating you
for something you didn't mean to do.
Why are you telling me this?
You can't change the things you did.
But you can change what you become.
Don't be like me.
Be better.
Clarissa, it's me, Martin.
I'm sorry, you look so familiar,
but I just can't place you.
Spaceship?
What next, Martians?
No, actually, amnesia pill.
Oh, yeah.
This will just wipe
your short term memory.
Of course, it's up to you,
but we don't want to mess
with time too much.
I always knew that you'd end up
caring for people...
protecting people.
Well, I learned it from my dad.
Proud of you, honey.
Is everything all right?
My wife doesn't seem to remember me.
Because until we return
your younger selves to the timeline,
you, none of you
will have ever existed.
But we will return you.
When we left 2016,
I just assumed I would return
to the exact moment I left,
that Clarissa wouldn't even know
I was gone.
So I didn't say goodbye.
And now I fear I will never
have that chance.
You will.
Look, I've told you before
that I am not going
to risk your marriage
in order to save my wife.
I promise you that.
Thank you.
Not even gonna pretend
to understand any of this.
It's pretty crazy, huh?
That was you in the hospital,
on the day you were born.
And earlier, on fire.
Amazing.
- Where'd you learn those moves?
- From my dad.
You know, the day
you were born in the hospital,
I'd never been so scared.
I mean, even in combat.
But now, I know for you to be the man
I see standing here,
I must do something right.
I can't wait to be there
to watch it happen.
Dad, listen.
On September 26th,
you're gonna be deployed
along the K4 circle.
Keep your head on a swivel
for an IED.
You know this because...
You're from the future.
Please. Promise me you'll be careful.
I'll be back soon, okay?
Hey.
Hope you don't mind, my fiancee...
my other fiancee
is in our quarters, resting.
Yeah, no, that's, that's fine.
- Hey, I'm sorry.
- No, really, it's fine.
No, I mean, being at death's door
is not the right time
to pop the question.
Look, when you proposed...
I was so afraid of losing you.
And then facing the Pilgrim,
I realized there is never going to be
a right time for this.
So we should stop waiting
for the right time.
I don't understand.
I want to marry you, Ray.
I mean it.
How's your sister?
She's a tough kid.
How's your dad?
Sleeping off that amnesia pill
from Rip.
Hey.
I might have just stopped my dad
from getting killed in Mogadishu.
I just thought I should tell you
in case there's a time paradox
or whatever.
Well, as I've been saying,
Mr. Jackson, time wants to happen.
Yeah, I know. But I had to try.
And perhaps what time wants
is to see you
and your father back together.
Just pulled younger me's head
from out of his ass.
- I'm not sure it stuck.
- Me either.
Then I saw younger Rip change,
and I thought,
why not give it a shot?
Surprised you didn't advise
your teenage self
to not get on a certain boat.
- Yeah, me too.
- Yak, yak, yak.
I thought we were on a clock here.
Indeed we are.
Time, the history from which
your younger selves were removed,
is beginning to set...
as is evidenced by the change
in Clarissa's memory.
Okay. So how long do we have
'til these changes stick?
No one knows.
Which is why we need to move swiftly
to locate Vandal Savage
if any of your lives
are to be restored to normal.
So how long will it take to determine
a new location for Savage?
Longer than we have.
Fortunately,
there is one place in time
that we know Savage to be.
You said he conquered
the world in 2166.
You also said it was too dangerous
to strike at Savage while he was
at the height of his powers.
That it is.
But with your younger selves
removed from history,
we have quite literally
run out of time.