In 2166 an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately,
my plan is opposed by the body
I'd sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
but if we succeed, they will be
remembered as legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Two years.
You left us stranded in 1958.
I was happy with the life
we built together,
the one I thought would be
our future.
Chronos attacked us.
He sabotaged the ship
and took Snart.
If you're gonna kill me,
you could at least tell me
what's going on.
The Time Masters,
they took me to a place
called the Vanishing Point.
I've spent lifetimes training
by them, being reborn.
Don't kill him.
The Time Masters took one of our own
and turned him against us.
I say we undo their handiwork.
I trust that you're comfortable,
Mr. Rory.
Or do you answer
to Chronos these days?
I don't take orders from you.
I can't believe I ever did.
Well, that's debatable.
I'm calling on you for two reasons.
First, we could use your help.
What's the second reason?
We're headed to 2147
to engage Savage.
Is that the second reason
or the first?
Forget it.
I owe you an apology, Mr. Rory.
I failed you.
I brought you along on this mission
under false pretenses,
in denial of your true nature.
And when that nature took its course,
I asked Mr. Snart to...
deal with you.
My point being,
your quarrel should be with me
and not with him.
Well, if it makes you feel
any better,
I want to kill both of you.
Captain, we've arrived at 2147.
Thank you, Gideon.
Set a course
for the Kasnian Conglomerate.
150 years in the future
and people are still wearing wool?
Man, I hate wool.
Be grateful, Mr. Jackson.
Those living outside the Kasnian
Conglomerate are dressed in rags.
- Conglomerate?
- Yes.
In the year 2080, government began
to give way to corporations.
More like 2008.
According to Gideon,
in two hours' time,
our favorite immortal psychopath
is scheduled to attend a meeting
of the Conglomerate's shareholders.
Oh, sounds exciting.
You think Savage takes over the world
by trading stocks?
What we do know is,
in 20 years' time,
Kasnia is the foothold from which
Savage takes over the world,
so we hardly want to take him
on there.
But if we can figure out
how his actions here
lead to his rise to power,
then we won't need to.
Copy that, Captain.
But if we're gonna be
checking out the future...
We should probably invite
the nerd twins.
You know, I can already hear
what Stan's gonna say about 2147.
The future, it's...
- Fascinating.
- Astonishing.
Well, it was a 50-50 chance
which one he'd choose.
Actually I was going to say,
"Remarkable."
Isn't it?
2147 was considered
the world's zenith.
All of these people have five
good years to look forward to.
Before what?
Before a ruthless dictator named
Per Degaton comes to power,
releases the Armageddon Virus
and most of them end up dead.
Well, that's depressing.
Is that my suit?
That's my suit.
You have been identified
as violating Ordinance 12.
That is how Per Degaton's father,
Tor maintains order in Kasnia.
Doesn't look like progress to me.
Speaking of progress, we need
to get a better lay of the land.
And I need to get a better look at
how they made my suit autonomous.
Well, why don't you take
Martin and Jax with you?
Ms. Lance, Mr. Snart
and I will work on locating Savage.
Tor Degaton holds daily meetings
with his board of directors.
And it's open to the public?
'Course not.
Just Kasnia's shareholders.
I hate to break it to you,
but we're not shareholders.
I'm more of a hard asset man,
myself.
You're clear to attend.
They'll have to wait outside.
Oh, no. This is my accountant
and she is my personal assist...
bodyguard.
Stockholders only.
We've been through this.
I won't put the resolution to a vote.
Sir, with greatest respect,
the situation outside
the Conglomerate's borders
is becoming untenable.
The food riots, climate change.
I am well aware
that the world outside our walls
is descending into chaos.
But causing chaos
cannot be a proper response.
It is not chaos.
It is logic.
The world's population is
unsustainable at current levels.
The herd must be thinned.
So you've argued, Mr. Savage.
But no matter how many times
you choose to press your point,
my decision shall stand.
Vandal.
Oh, my boy.
My father would have you killed
for calling me that.
Oh, I wouldn't want
to chance execution.
Per Degaton.
So how did the meeting go?
Well, your father was being
his usual intractable self.
The problem is, my young student,
to run a corporation is not the same
as ruling a country.
If you're implying that my father
doesn't have what it takes...
Yes, he would have killed me
for that as well.
Well, I suppose I just have to live
dangerously then.
So how are your studies progressing?
He's a teacher.
Tutor, it would seem,
to young Per Degaton himself.
You say that like
it's supposed to mean something.
After the death of his father
in five years' time,
Per Degaton unleashes
the Armageddon Virus,
which decimates
the world's population,
leaving it ripe for conquest.
Per Degaton primes
the world for dictatorship
and then when the time is right...
Savage snatches that power
away from him.
By killing Per Degaton.
Indeed.
Okay, so we don't have what we need
to take out Savage,
but maybe now we can figure out
a way to stop his rise to power.
By depriving him of his springboard,
Per Degaton.
Okay, how do we do that?
It's quite simple, really.
We kill the little bastard ourselves.
To be clear, we're talking
about murdering a child.
Who hasn't done anything to anyone.
Yet, so why don't we pick him off
now,
while the picking's easy?
There's got to be a better way.
How do we even know
that this Per Degaton kid's path
to becoming a world-ruling
dictator is inevitable?
Because in the future that I'm from,
children learn about Per Degaton
in the same way
that children in your time
learn about Adolf Hitler.
What about addressing
the larger societal problems
that would allow
such a despot's rise to power?
We already know what pushes this punk
to the dark side, Savage.
Look, it's not the kid's fault
he's got an immortal psychopath
as his tutor.
If we don't kill the kid now,
Savage will as soon as he's done
using him to take over the world.
If he doesn't build him
into the greatest tyrant
the world has ever known,
Savage can't become the last tyrant
the world will ever know.
Murdering a child in cold blood
just like Savage murdered
your own son.
What's the use in saving the world
if we stoop to his methods to do so?
I'm with Professor Stein.
Okay, fine.
If you all don't have the guts
to kill this kid...
Then removing him from the timeline
might be the next best thing.
Great. We've gone from infanticide
to child abduction.
Progress.
First, we need to devise
how to abduct him
from underneath the noses
of his father's private guard.
And don't forget the army
of Atom robots.
We're going to need
an accomplished thief.
Well, while you're kidnapping
baby Hitler,
Professor Stein and I
will sabotage the robot army.
I call Team Robot Army.
Isn't that a waste of time?
Not for the Kasnian citizens
who are tormented by my technology.
That technology does lead
to Savage's rise to power.
Good backup plan.
Fine, Team Kidnapping.
Go, team.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, yeah. I was just... thinking.
I think I understand.
You do?
Yeah, it's Savage.
He's so close you can sense him,
right?
Yeah.
Do you want to talk about it?
No. Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine.
Okay.
Honey?
I'm home.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Can I fix you a drink?
That would be lovely.
And while you do,
you can tell me what's on your mind.
Really, it's nothing.
You are a terrible liar.
Yes, but... you love me anyway.
Beyond anything I can describe.
And because I love you, I know
when something's bothering you.
It's... it's just a feeling.
Of him?
It's hard to tell.
I haven't sensed Savage's presence.
But you do... or you think you do.
I think it's time for us to go.
I have some vacation time coming up.
We can drive to Coast City
and do some sightseeing.
- A vacation isn't going to fix this.
- I know.
Savage isn't just gonna forget
about us because we went away.
I know.
And he's not gonna stop until...
Mommy?
I can't sleep.
Hey, Slugger.
Daddy.
Come here.
What's wrong?
Nothing. Nothing.
I just love you so much.
I love both of you so much.
No litter. No street crime. No smog.
How soon can we leave?
Keep your eyes peeled.
According to Gideon,
Per Degaton should be passing
through any minute
on his way to gymnastics class.
Are you telling me future Hitler
is enrolled in a gymnastics class?
Yes.
I got eyes on Little Lord Fauntleroy.
I don't see him.
It's because he's surrounded
by Daddy's goon squad.
Northeast corner of the plaza.
Got him.
You sure you don't want
to just shoot him?
It'd be a whole lot easier.
Stick to the plan, both of you.
Now, Ms. Lance.
I'm in position.
It's up to you now, Mr. Snart.
Take the asset! Move back!
Since the introduction
of our latest line
of autonomous law enforcement
officers,
crime has dropped precipitously.
- In fact, it's nonexistent.
- Really?
Well, thank you for showing us
around, Dr. Brice.
It's my pleasure.
We don't get very many visitors
from Central City
ever since the S.T.A.R. Labs
Corporation took it over.
Unless I'm mistaken, your tech
utilizes a dwarf star alloy.
The technology is proprietary,
but yes.
How did you know, Doctor...
Lecter...
Dr. Hannibal Lecter.
So how did you get into robotics,
Dr. Brice?
Oh, well, it's in my blood.
Robotics have been
a passion of my family
ever since my great-great-great-great
grandfather founded this company.
Is that...
Oh, my God.
Huh, weird.
You look just like him.
Yes, I look just like...
Yeah, that's... that's pretty weird.
I can't believe it.
I'm like the Werner Von Braun
of robots.
The who?
The Nazi scientist
who invented the V2 rocket,
built it using slave labor,
then used it to level London.
Except my robots will one day be used
to level the entire world.
Ray, dude, do you not think you're
focusing on the wrong thing here?
I mean, you have a kid
you didn't even know about.
Had a kid.
In this particular time period,
his offspring would be
long since dead.
Thank you, as if I wasn't already
feeling bad enough.
How is it even possible
that I'm someone's
great-great-great-great grandfather?
Before we left in 2016,
the only person I was...
Having sex with?
Ghosted me the week before we left.
She died?
No, no, ghosting.
It's where you pretend to be dead
by not answering somebody's text.
What a strange age for dating.
You think maybe she didn't reply
to your text because...
She knew she was pregnant?
No wonder my kid started the company
that manufactures evil robots.
If I'd never left 2016, my child
would have had a loving father
and Palmer Tech might not have gone
on to build a robot army
that Savage uses
to conquer the world.
Bit of a stretch, don't you think?
Either way, I was someone's father
and didn't even know it.
- Hey.
Are you okay?
Fine. I'm fine.
You don't look fine.
I'm just a little... peckish.
Peckish?
It's nothing a little energy bar
won't fix.
I'll see you.
Edith and Joseph Boardman?
Our new names.
Joe Boardman is a good name.
And besides,
I've never kissed an Edith before,
but I certainly think
I can get used to that.
And what about all this?
How do we explain to our son
why his mother and father keep
moving every couple of years,
changing their names, looking over
their shoulders at every turn?
I don't know why we thought
we could do this again.
Do you think we're selfish?
To have a family?
Because when Savage finds us...
- He won't.
- He always finds us.
Maybe this life is different.
Do you honestly believe that?
Look...
All I know is that Savage is not the
only thing that's immortal, my love.
So is this.
What do genocidal maniacs
dream about, I wonder?
He's imagining himself
baking cookies with his mother.
- Wait, you can monitor our dreams?
- Of course.
For example, last night,
you had a rollicking fantasy
involving a young nurse.
Okay, Gideon, enough.
Gideon, check the timeline
to make sure
that the kidnapping of the boy had
the desired effect upon the future.
Oh, dear.
I'm afraid you'll be disappointed
with the results.
What do you mean it did nothing?
I mean, that kidnapping Per Degaton
had a nominal effect
upon the timeline.
Maybe we need to dump the little brat
somewhere he can't get into
any trouble, like the Stone Age.
No matter where and when
you sequester him in the timeline,
Savage will still rise to power.
But Rip said this kid's
like a baby Hitler.
Yes, I also said
that time wants to happen
and such a world-changing event
like Savage's rise to power
can't be stopped merely
by kidnapping his young pawn.
So we're back to plan A?
Snuffing the kid out in his sleep?
Let us not forget that this kid
will one day be responsible
for billions of deaths,
including those of my family.
Say that you do stop Savage
and save the lives of your family.
Will you be able
to look your own son in the eye
knowing what you did,
so he could live?
When the alternative is that
I shall never see him again.
I got a better idea.
Instead of us arguing about
whether we should kill him,
or where and when to dump him off,
why don't we just talk to him?
Savage has spent years
corrupting his mind.
It's not too late
for Per Degaton to change.
Says who?
Says someone with two tours
with the League of Assassins
and a case of bloodlust
under her belt.
Finally, someone who's willing
to do a man's job.
Not why I'm here.
It's almost funny how you guys
keep parading in here
like it's some kind of confessional
or something.
It's also not why I'm here.
Okay, I'll bite.
Everybody's out there arguing
about whether or not
we should kill this kid,
'cause no one thinks he can change,
which made me think of you.
You know no one thinks
you can change.
That's why you're in here.
The only reason
I'm in here is if I get out,
I'm gonna give Snart some payback
he's not walking away from.
He saved your life.
He wussed out on killing me,
not the same thing.
He marooned me.
It's not like he had many choices.
You know, while you were busy selling
us out to a homicidal time pirate,
Leonard and I almost died.
He was thinking about you,
told me about your partnership,
your friendship.
Did it make you weepy?
You think it's gonna make me weepy?
He's your friend, a loyal one.
You should know that.
Well, thank you.
I'll work it out with him
as soon as I can.
Oh, killing a kid,
not very hero-like.
Mr. Degaton.
For the last 50 years,
everyone inside the Conglomerate
has submitted biosamples,
so they can be tracked
and monitored at all times.
But these three...
Are not from the Conglomerate,
nor are they even
from the last 50 years.
How do you know?
Long story.
What's important is that
I can get your son back.
How do you know
they haven't killed him already?
Because I know the people
who kidnapped him
and they are weak...
squeamish in matters of death.
Who are you?
That's an excellent question.
What was that?
That was our jump ship taking off.
How could Per Degaton have escaped?
Gideon, who else is on the jump ship?
It's being piloted by Captain Hunter.
Who just turned off his transponder.
Sounds like someone
doesn't want us following him.
Why?
Because Rip doesn't want us
stopping him.
Stopping him from doing what?
From killing Per Degaton.
Okay, just think about this.
Where could Rip be taking
Per Degaton?
Jump ship's got a range of 8,000m,
so... anywhere.
It doesn't matter
where he's taking him.
All that matters is what he's gonna
do to him when he gets there.
Rip is not a murderer.
To Captain Hunter,
this isn't about a killing.
It's about saving.
Saving?
His son's life for Per Degaton's.
Rather simple if cold-blooded
calculus for a father to undertake.
Do you know who I am?
- My father is going to...
- Thank me?
I imagine there's a sizeable reward
for your safe return.
Relax.
You'll soon be home.
Come on, honey. We got to get moving
or the train is going to leave
without us.
Where are we going?
We are going on a little trip.
Just think of it
as one of your adventures.
The bad man found us,
the one that you and Mommy talk
about when I'm asleep?
Why is Vandal Savage chasing us?
It's time that he knew.
Come on.
Can you keep a secret, Aldus?
There's something... special
about your mommy and daddy.
We've known each other
for a very, very long time
and loved one another
since the day we met.
I already know that story.
You know part of that story.
Have you ever heard of a place
called Egypt?
Well, it all began
during the rule of Ramses II,
when late one night a big,
magical meteor
smashed into the Temple
of Horus, the hawk-god.
- Hey, you okay?
- Hey.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I was just thinking.
What are you thinking about?
Let me into that
4,000-year-old mind of yours.
The flashes I've been having,
they aren't of Savage.
They're of Carter.
And they're not just memories.
They're feelings too.
Oh, well, I get that.
It must be really weird feeling like
you're cheating on me with him.
No, Ray.
I feel like I'm cheating on him
with you.
I'm sorry.
No, it's... it's okay.
I mean,
I knew what I was getting into.
The last 206 times you fell in love,
it was with the same guy.
I guess this isn't a great time to
talk about what's been bothering you.
You're not the only perceptive one.
So what's wrong?
Turns out that I had a child
I didn't know about back in 2016
and here in the future,
my great-great-great-great
granddaughter
creates the army of robot Gestapos
that Savage will one day use
to destroy the world.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want you
to think less of me.
Ray, how could I ever think
less of you?
Well, now that we've got
that off our chests...
What does that mean for us?
No luck finding our homicidal
captain?
Gideon's still searching,
but I have a feeling Rip's not gonna
be found if he doesn't want to be.
So what are you doing down here?
Don't you think you at least
owe him a conversation?
We had our conversation
while he was Chronos
and he made his feelings
about me very clear.
And what about your feelings?
About you?
About Mick.
I don't have any feelings about Mick.
Look, it didn't seem that way
when we were dying in
the engine room of hypothermia.
Look, if you want to ease
your guilty conscience,
that's your business.
But he's still the same
son of a bitch he was
when you all wanted me
to put him down.
I wasn't the one
who mentioned marooning, Rory.
You did.
It's obviously still weighing
on your conscience.
So stop being an ass
and go deal with it.
This isn't Kasnia.
I thought a neutral site
would be best for this.
For what?
Exchanging me?
Did your father ever teach you
to swim, Per Degaton?
No, I imagine he had someone
do it for him, didn't he?
You're hardly lacking in tutors,
are you...
such as Mr. Savage.
What are you talking about?
My son Jonas
always wanted to learn to swim.
I promised him that I'd teach him,
but there never seemed to be... time.
My son never learned to swim,
because he was killed.
So... you brought me here to kill me.
I brought you here to save my son's
life, your life in exchange for his.
I'm sorry.
No, you're not.
You're not sorry
because you're not going to kill me.
I have to.
To save my wife and son, I have to.
I don't expect you to understand.
It doesn't matter if I understand.
I can see it in your eyes.
You're not going to do it.
You're like my father, weak.
Vandal Savage has taught me
many things,
including what a killer looks like.
You're not a killer.
Your tutor has taught you well
despite his ill intentions.
Vandal loves me.
Oh, he wants to use you as his pawn
and ultimately, he will betray you.
No. No, he wouldn't.
I've said to myself time
and time again
that there is nothing that I wouldn't
do to save my wife and son,
but now I know that there is.
My reticence to kill you,
Per Degaton, is not weakness.
It is goodness.
And if there is a shred
of goodness inside of me,
then I have to believe that there is
a shred of goodness inside of you.
Be the man that your father
wants you to be,
not the man Savage wants you to be.
Savage, he's coming.
Gideon?
Tor Degaton's forces
have surrounded the ship.
I'm afraid our shields
will not be able to sustain
continued bombardment.
You're afraid?
Here's an idea.
Why don't you fire back?
I would, except...
The flying robots already
targeted our weapons systems.
We don't need weapons.
He's right.
We have super powers.
I think this is yours.
I'll draw their fire.
You handle the ground troops.
Ray, are you all right?
So this is what it feels
like to be last year's model.
They're too fast.
We have to find another way.
Forget about them.
We'll hold off the robots.
We'll take out their command center.
Who are you?
Yeah.
Ray, hurry up.
I can only hold them back
for so long.
Where did you get your suit?
Look, if you don't let us disable
your evil robot army,
then the whole world
will be destroyed.
They're designed to bring peace.
I know.
I designed the robots.
What?
I am your great-great-great-great
grandfather.
The guy you have a bust of
in your lobby,
father of the robotics industry.
You're trying to tell me
that you're Sidney Palmer?
Sidney?
Wait, the bust in your lobby
is of my stupid brother?
Of course.
He must have gone to work for
Felicity in 2016 after I vanished.
He allowed my tech to be perverted
by the defense industry.
That is so Sidney.
So that means that she's not...
I'm not a father.
So we still need your help
disabling the robots.
And why should I believe you?
Because if you have even a drop
of Palmer blood in your veins,
you'll do what's right.
Looks like Raymond was able
to sabotage his robot army.
Which means mopping up the rest of
these guys shouldn't be a problem.
Oh, it will be a problem.
What do you want?
I want to exchange this woman's life
for your captain, Rip Hunter.
I have a better idea,
her life in exchange for his.
Your son will be returned to you
as soon as you guarantee
our safe passage.
Don't do it, father.
If you let them go now,
they will only come back for us
in the future.
It's your choice.
Your son is right.
We should kill them all.
Put down your weapons!
No, father.
Let my son go
and I will let you leave in peace.
You have my word.
Better find yourself a new mentor,
kid.
What do you want?
People seem to think
we should have a heart-to-heart.
We don't have hearts.
Where does that leave us?
I've got a dozen reasons
for killing you.
You've got a dozen
and one for killing me, so...
All the talk in the world
is not gonna change a thing.
Exactly, here's my proposal.
I open this cell,
we let our fists do the talking.
When I kill you...
You take the jump ship,
make your escape,
live out the rest of your life
anywhere you like.
And if you kill me, well,
it's better than being
locked up in this place
like some kind of circus freak.
I take that as a yes.
Sound the bell.
Hey.
You don't have to knock.
It's your room too.
Yeah, I know.
It's just... things have been weird.
Since I told you I had a love child
that I didn't really have,
or since you told me
that you're still in love with...
You know what I love about you, Ray,
is you always manage to find
the bright side.
And no matter what,
you never give up.
So please, don't give up on us.
I'm not giving up,
but it's hard to ignore the math.
You and Carter have
spent lifetimes together
and in each one,
you've fallen in love.
So why would this lifetime
be any different?
Well, I never met you before.
Look, Ray, Carter is my past.
You are my future.
Vandal.
Oh, I didn't expect you up
and about so soon.
My father wanted me to rest,
but I wanted to resume my studies.
Oh, good boy.
So... where should we begin?
Well, I was thinking Greek mythology.
Do you know the tale
of Oedipus Rex?
He was a prince of thieves
before his father exiled him.
Why?
Well, because the king was a coward.
He had heard a prophecy that one day
his son would take his crown,
so he bound his boy's feet
and tossed him into the woods to die.
What did the boy do?
He did what he had to do.
And one day, the prophecy came true
and the prince became a great
and powerful king.
Though it wasn't easy.
Great things are never easy.
Unfortunately, our interactions
have done nothing to halt
Per Degaton's rise to power.
If anything,
we've merely cemented it.
In fact, the virus,
which wasn't supposed to be
unleashed upon the world
for another five years...
I'm sorry, Father.
Will now be released
in a matter of days.
As you all know,
our former chairman's chair
is in the Conglomerate
passed to his son,
who due to his age elected me
to act as his proxy.
First order of business,
I would like to revisit our
discussion
concerning the population crisis
beyond the Conglomerate's borders.
As we all know,
we already have a solution.
Did I do the right thing, Gideon?
Not committing murder is generally
considered the right thing, Captain.
In this instance...
I wonder.
We had a deal, Mick.
Kill me and you walk.
It's what you wanted, isn't it,
to get off the team?
I don't know what I want anymore.
Truth is, it doesn't matter.
What are you talking about?
Whether I stay or leave, I'm dead.
We're all dead.
Since I failed to bring you in,
the Time Master's want to
bring me in
and this time, they're not
gonna take any chances.
They're called the Hunters,
mercenaries
and unlike me, there isn't
a human part left in them.
So they want to lock us all up
in the Vanishing Point?
The Hunters do one thing, kill,
whenever, wherever
and they'll stop at nothing
'til every single one of us
is erased from the face of history.
Do you have any suggestions as to
how we might outsmart them, Mr. Rory?
Run.