How will we be remembered?
Will it be for saving the world, twice?
No. We're the team who broke time.
That's right.
History has been torn to shreds.
Which means it's up to us
to put it back together again.
Piece by piece,
fixing the so-called anachronisms
before we get torn to shreds.
So please, don't call us heroes,
we're Legends.
Zari Tomaz?
Previously
on Legends Of Tomorrow...
Come with us if you want to live.
That's enough, Zari!
You're not going anywhere without us.
My brother had powers
because he wielded this.
He fought against A.R.G.U.S.'
injustices, so he was hunted.
We all were.
- Come with us.
- What would you rather do?
Hide from A.R.G.U.S. your whole life
or time travel?
- Whoa, Lily!
- I'm pregnant.
Congratulations.
Hello?
What's your name?
Mine's Ray Palmer.
5219! I repeat, we have a 5219!
Subject on the move,
lock down all exits!
Code Red! Engaging lockdown protocol!
He went this way.
Got him.
He's headed for the lab!
Can't let you go in there, Raymond.
You're not gonna hurt me.
I'm just a kid.
And if you want to make it to adulthood,
you'll start seeing
the reality of the situation.
So, why don't you calm down,
and we'll have ourselves a nice chat?
There you go.
Now come with us.
What makes a hero?
Is it powers? Strength? Bravery?
No.
A hero is forged
by his or her relationships.
Our bonds of brotherhood or sisterhood.
That is why I'm taking you all
through the 10-step
team-building process
I perfected at Palmer Tech.
Step one. Part one, icebreakers.
Dude, we've stuck on a ship
that has one bathroom.
I think we know each other well enough.
And your timing couldn't be worse,
given that we are being chased
by a water-wielding assassin
and the Time Bureau.
We need to grow as a team.
First up is "Two Truths and a Lie."
It's gonna be fun.
Lie.
I haven't started yet.
Look, I know you guys
probably think this is lame...
Truth.
But we have a new crew member, and it
is important for Zari to bond with us
not only as team members,
but as individuals.
Yeah, well, I'm no hero,
and I'm not a member of any team.
Besides, I already
have you all figured out
The old guy wants to be anywhere
but on this ship.
These two have some
will-they-won't-they thing going on.
Rory's been drunk since breakfast,
Jax is wondering if I'm single,
and your ship's still mad at me
for doing a teeny hack
on her subsystems.
Now, what's this about one bathroom?
I've informed her repeatedly my
subsystems do not require an upgrade.
- Guys...
- You're right, Haircut.
This is gonna be fun.
Let's just skip to step two.
Trust Falls.
Now, to demonstrate,
Mick, who hated me when we first met,
will fall trustingly into my arms.
All right. You promised me good coin
for doing this.
And you said you weren't
gonna say that out loud.
Well, just lean back and let go.
'Cause I'm not going anywhere, buddy.
What the hell?
Gideon! What happened to Ray?
According to public record,
Mr. Palmer died in 1988.
Wait. Ray's dead?
He better be.
How could Ray be dead?
He was just right here.
And, well, he owes me money.
Gideon, you said Ray died in 1988?
Mr. Palmer went missing
on October 31, 1988.
They recovered the body two days later.
He was found in the woods, dead.
Only eight years old.
If Ray disappeared on Halloween,
then we'll just go back
before whatever happens happens.
Gideon, get us to October 30, 1988.
Wait, are we time traveling?
You better buckle up.
Arriving in 1988.
I should've said, there're
some really strange side effects.
Buddy! Hey! You're alive!
Aw, man. I Love you, man.
Me, too.
And always ready for a bro-hug.
I'm in the paper.
And I'm dead?
Not yet.
We're in 1988,
the day before you disappeared.
Okay.
Well, I guess the fact
that I'm still here
means temporal permanence hasn't set in.
Which means we can still save my life
and enjoy 1988 while we're at it.
Trust Ray to find
the bright side to dying.
Uh, are you sure this is right?
That sweater's totally awesome.
How do I look?
Honestly, like you're being
strangled by a Muppet.
I can't believe
people used to wear this stuff.
Hey, speak for yourself.
I look good in any era.
I can't wait to show
you guys my home.
First, we have to go to Pizza Master,
best slice in town.
Then we have to go to Video Village.
I can't tell you how much
of my allowance I spent there.
So you're always this positive,
even when you're dead.
How can you pretend
like everything's okay?
I'm not pretending, I believe it.
I've found that if I can trust in myself
I can believe everything's okay.
And it usually is.
It's called positive thinking.
Give it a shot.
Is he for real?
School's almost out. You ready, kids?
Yeah, let's motor.
Mmm. This is amazing.
Blue skies, smiling kids,
an actual white picket fence.
I think it's actually a trellis, but...
Yeah, same thing.
Oh.
Wow. There I am.
Thanks for the pop quiz, Mrs. Garvin.
It really reinforced some fundamentals.
Yeah, that's definitely you.
Oh. Okay, now whoever's targeting me
could be anywhere,
so keep a look out for anything unusual.
Hey, guys, here I come.
I mean, little me's coming at you.
Catch up with me on Main Street?
And, um... Keep me alive.
Got eyes-on. Ready to make a move.
Though it looks like
you're taking a detour.
Did you frequent the Ivy Town
Newsstand as a boy?
Yeah, I must be picking up
the new issue of Scientific American.
I was more of a National
Geographic boy, myself.
Once a geek, always a geek.
Well, whoever's after me
could be there, so...
Yeah, we'll stick on him.
Okay, I got somebody
checking out magazines
and one shopkeeper.
I could knock this place off
with a water pistol.
Okay, new mission,
keep me away from Mick.
I don't want today to be the day
I descend into a life of crime.
Well, Haircut, looks like it's too late.
Wait, what does that mean?
You're by the candy bars...
Well, get me away from there.
That stuff's poison!
- Yeah, that's not all.
- Wait, what does that mean?
You're shoplifting.
Wait. What?
Damn, Haircut, you had balls.
I've never stolen a thing in my life.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, you have now.
I'm proud of you.
Little you's on the move.
Well, stop him! Me.
Stop both of us!
I'm no rat.
Ready at the home front.
See, now, this? This is a time machine.
I got eyes on little Ray.
We've got a hostile incoming.
What is it? Assassin? Time Bureau?
Almost as bad.
Bullies.
Hey, Palmer. Let's play.
No, that's just Gus and Ty.
We were friends.
Very funny, guys.
You want me to rough 'em up?
Nah, they were just kidding.
Give that back! Come on!
- Give that back!
- Here.
I'm beginning to think
maybe they weren't kidding.
Boring. Let's go, Ty.
I can't believe
he thinks we're actually friends.
Bye, guys.
Guess kids are mean in any time period.
We circled the neighborhood,
checked the yard. It seems normal.
Scary normal.
Maybe young Ray died of boredom.
No, something's up. Something's wrong.
Look, maybe it's the candy.
Maybe I overdose on high fructose
corn syrup and food coloring.
Or maybe your killer aborted
when we showed up.
Let's get back to the ship
and check the historical record.
Give me a minute.
Dinner time.
Got you gummy bears,
licorice, Nougat Nummies.
Wait till we go
trick-or-treating tomorrow.
There's a whole lot more
where that came from.
I'm talking to someone in my room.
Knew you were hungry!
Coast is clear, Gumball.
You can come on out.
Guys? I think I know what kills me.
It's a Dominator.
So... Aliens are real.
Yup. And those ones
are called Dominators.
They're nasty, too.
Capable of telepathy,
advanced technology,
and the fun one,
- tearing people limb-from-limb.
- Great.
The last time we faced them,
they almost wiped out meta-humans
and made us to fight each other.
And worse, fight together.
And now little-me kidnapped one
and is treating it like a house pet,
which would be cool if it wasn't deadly.
Maybe the baby Dominator hasn't
developed all of its abilities yet?
The infant of the species
has the strength of the adult
with none of its discretion.
It can also
mind-control subjects at will.
How can you not remember
befriending an alien?
Because I didn't.
It never happened to me.
The Dominator is an anachronism.
- It's time-displaced.
- Right.
So we have to get that baby Dominator
out of Ray's bedroom
and back to where it belongs.
And how are we supposed to do that?
Uh, well, it should be easy.
All we have to do is
sneak into my house tomorrow,
when my mom's at work and I'm at school,
and kidnap the Dominator.
I even know where the spare key is.
Like stealing candy from a baby.
But not as fun.
Yo. Where were you, man?
You missed the team meeting.
Oh, you finished already?
I was just on my way,
but I can ask Gideon to debrief me.
Uh, psychic connection, so I know
you're hiding something.
I have no idea what you're referring to.
Zari was right.
You don't actually want to be
on the Waverider, do you?
Don't be ridiculous.
I am as committed to this mission
as I've ever been.
What's going on?
Grey's keeping some sort of secret.
You want to know what's going on?
Well, do you know
what's going on with him?
I have my suspicions, yeah.
And, uh, I have my ways
of extracting information.
Home sweet home.
- Wait.
- What? What is it?
No shoes on the carpet.
I guess we can probably
let go of that now.
- Yeah.
Oh, man, never thought
I'd be here again.
My brother Sydney and I
used to fight over this thing.
He always wanted to play Tecmo Bowl
and all I wanted to do
was play Legend of Zelda.
Yeah, the only video games we had
were military training simulations,
but, yeah, that sounds hard for you.
Our record player.
Hey, who's "Billy Joel"?
What? Piano Man? River of Dreams?
Really? Wow.
You really did live in a dystopia.
No time to waltz down
memory lane, Ray.
Find the Dominator and get out of there
before anyone sees you all grown up.
Dude, I didn't know
you were a Billy Joel fan.
What's your favorite album?
Everyone says The Stranger,
but for my money Nylon Curtain,
his Beatles tribute album,
is super-ambitious.
Let us know when you're heading out.
We're ready for retrieval.
Whoa. I never thought
I'd be back in my room.
Guys, we're in my room.
It's in the closet.
Okay, no sudden movements.
Ugh. Leave it to young you
to see the best in that thing.
Though you were pretty lonely.
What? I wasn't lonely.
I was just choosing
to focus on my studies.
This is probably
just my scientific curiosity
- getting the better of me. Again.
- Great.
Popcorn's ready.
Aren't you supposed to be in school?
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah, this is a problem.
No. Yesterday shoplifting,
today I'm a truant.
This thing is turning me into Rory.
Young you is on the way.
Hey! No! Get off me!
No. I am not a toy.
Stop that. Toys are our friends.
I don't remember you.
Hmm.
Come on, this is my favorite.
It's 1:30 already. It's morning!
Yes. And what a lovely morning!
Good mornin'
We've talked the whole night through
Good mornin'...
Is that music?
Yeah, Singin' in the Rain.
Only the best musical ever.
Not as good as Fiddler on the Roof.
I loved that show.
What?
We got a new problem.
You know anyone
who owns a green station wagon
with fake wood-paneling?
What's my mom doing home?
Dude, you never mentioned
your mom was hot.
Why would I ever mention that?
Good mornin'
We've gabbed the whole night through
Good mornin' to you
Nothing could be grander
Than to be in Louisiana
In the mornin'...
Raymond Coswell Palmer!
You have to hide.
Where are you, Raymond?
Why did I get a call saying that you
didn't show up to school today?
- Mom?
- I'm sorry, Mom. I was sick.
Sick.
No kidding. Of course you're sick.
Sick from eating all of this candy.
You can forget
about trick-or-treating tonight.
Guys, the Dominator's getting angry.
Somebody needs to distract my mom.
Fine. I'll take one for the team.
Raymond, this is
the second time this month
that I've had to leave work for you.
First you're starting a fire
in the science lab, and then what?
Now you're sitting at home,
skipping school?
School is boring.
I already know all the answers.
Too bad. You're going back.
So, grab your stuff. Let's go. Come on.
What was that?
Yeah, now would be great, guys.
What now?
Is there a cougar on the premises?
Excuse me?
Animal Control.
One of the neighbors said
that they heard some strange noises
coming from your home.
So that's what he's been up to.
Yeah, we just got done wrestling a bear
and saving, like, a bus-load of kids.
They were super cute.
We just need to come in
and take a look around.
Sure. Come on in. Whatever you need.
- Thanks.
- Whatever.
It's my son.
He's always sneaking out
into the woods, bringing back strays.
Don't worry. We've seen it all.
Yeah. I just wish Ray would
make normal friends, you know?
I mean, he would rather
spend his time with his animals
and movies or his weird inventions.
Sometimes I worry that he just
gets lost in his own head.
Hey, I hope kid-you
didn't hear all that.
She always said she liked my inventions.
- Captain Lance?
- What's up?
I am detecting the approach
of another Timeship.
What if the assassin followed us here?
We need to plead for clemency with
the Time Bureau and ask for help.
Whoever's here could be tracking us.
Stay off the comms.
I'm gonna check it out.
You keep watch here.
I'll be watching very, very closely.
They know about you.
We need to go.
No one cares about me anyway.
Oh. You need a friend.
Uh-oh.
Whoa! No!
Come on.
Oh, no. I've got a play date.
Zari, stay with me.
I don't want to spook the Dominator
or traumatize my younger self.
I should've stayed in 2042.
Ray, hold on.
How do you know my name?
It's a long, mostly-irritating story.
The only thing that matters is,
I'm here to save your life.
No. You want Gumball.
Well, you can't have him.
And I thought grown-up Ray was annoying.
Listen to me, kid. You don't want
to be alone with that thing.
You don't know him. We're friends.
Your friend is gonna kill you!
If I don't do it first.
What's going on? This about Grey?
You said the Professor's been acting
all squirrelly about where he's been.
Squirrelly?
Yeah, when you're on the run,
someone usually cracks.
Burns the crew to save themselves.
Burns the crew how?
Cutting a deal with the Time Bureau.
You think Grey's ratting us out
to the Time Bureau?
The old man wants off the boat.
Thinks we're in too deep.
- Yeah, but he wouldn't do that.
- Really?
Then who's been boosting the Jumpship
while we sleep?
Gideon.
I believe Mr. Rory
is alluding to the fact
that someone has erased
the Jumpship's travel log.
Someone's been sneaking off the ship
and snitching to the Time Bureau.
And if there's one thing
I hate more than pigs, it's a rat.
How far could he have gone?
He's just a little kid.
Maybe if you hadn't stayed
to flirt with Ray's mother...
First of all,
I didn't flirt with Ray's mother,
I merely charmed her.
Can't help that I'm charming.
Wait. Are you jealous?
Nathaniel, I just think
we should keep it simple.
Friends.
Like we were
before all of this happened.
And that was still fun, right?
Right, if we just had a Timeship.
We could go back to where
we never even lived together.
Nate, don't.
And that Swedish bed
we never quite assembled.
I believe it was called a Doubledroff.
- Just erase their...
- Shh. Nate!
I'm getting something this way.
The mobile team
is setting up a lab now.
We need to find the Dominator
before it finds us.
- What about the kid?
- He comes with us.
We can't have this getting out.
Looks like a false alarm.
No sign of the Time Bureau here.
Gideon says the Professor's been
spending a lot of time down here.
Whoa.
The last time I was down here
this place was just a storage room.
Looks like the Professor has been
busy behind our backs.
So what? He's a professor, man.
That's what professors do.
They invent stuff. Stuff like...
Like what?
Like this.
Best bet is this is some sort
of radio transmitter
that communicates through time.
With the Time Bureau.
Can't believe it.
Grey really is a traitor.
Kid, I know you're in there.
Oh, good. You found us.
You shall not pass!
There's no time for make-believe.
You are in actual danger.
Step down, you knave.
Zari, think like a kid.
You just have to play along.
I'm...
I'm here from a neighboring kingdom
to speak to Sir Galahad.
And?
Sir Gumball.
And Sir Gumball.
Yeah, good. That's good. Keep going.
It's an honor, my lieges.
Got him! I repeat,
subject has been located.
You lied to me!
No, I didn't.
- Hey! Let him go!
- You're coming with us.
Leave me alone! Leave us alone!
No!
Careful. The Dominator's sedation
is wearing off.
Don't worry. This little fellow's
not going anywhere.
It doesn't need to go anywhere.
Using its telepathic powers,
even a juvenile could control us
at its will.
Force us to set it free
or do each other in.
I've seen it before.
This will suppress its neural impulses,
neutralizing its powers...
As well as preventing it
from communicating with its mother,
the Queen.
We have the girl in a storage room.
And the boy is in questioning now.
Get him to tell us everything he knows.
Where he found the creature
and how long he's had it.
Then what do we do with him?
Make it so he can't tell anybody else.
- You mean...
- Mmm-hmm.
This Queen, if the baby
can control our minds,
what is she capable of doing?
Mental projection,
supplanting thoughts and sensations
into its victim's mind.
Also known to protect their young
at any cost.
You know what I'm looking for.
A breath mint?
Dermatologist recommendation?
Reese's Pieces?
All right! Your kid!
You're looking for your kid.
If you let me go, I'll help you.
Your species cannot be trusted.
Look, I want to help you. I do.
You can't find him without me.
Agreed.
Going somewhere, Professor?
I don't have time to explain. I'm taking
the Jumpship whether you like it or not.
Mick, come on, man.
I just souped this baby up.
Jefferson, please, I need you
to help me get out of 1988.
Help you?
After you've been lying to me.
You've been sneaking out on us,
you erased the jump logs.
You're working with the Time Bureau.
What? Never!
What's in your back pocket, Professor?
It's a trans-temporal communicator.
So you can talk
to your Time Bureau friends.
No, so I can talk to my...
Hey, Dad!
My daughter.
Oh. And all you guys.
Hey, Lily.
Dad, I think it's time.
We're heading to the hospital now.
And you're gonna be here, right?
How can I miss the birth
of my first grandchild?
Good.
This baby's coming.
Okay, I will see you there. Bye, Dad.
I took the Jumpship back to 2017
so I could give Lily
the other communicator.
And you wiped the jump-logs. Why?
Because I wanted you to know
that I was committed to you
and to the team.
I made the decision to stay,
and I needed you to know
that I meant it.
Clearly, my subterfuge has robbed me
of the chance to be
at the birth of my grandchild.
No. We can take the Waverider.
What about the rest of the team?
I'm sure they'll manage.
You're serious?
Grey, it's your first grandkid.
Why would you think
I'd want you to miss that?
Come on, man. Let's go.
What's going on? Where's kid Ray?
They're interrogating me. Him.
Code Red! Engaging lockdown protocols!
Let's go.
So why don't you calm down, and we'll
have ourselves a nice little chat?
There you go.
Come with us.
You're real.
Fire!
Go, go, go!
We gotta move.
They won't stay down long.
We can't leave without Gumball.
Look, that thing is not your friend.
It may be cute and cuddly now,
but sooner or later,
it's gonna turn on you.
Gumball wouldn't do that!
We can save him, I know it.
Look, Raymond,
I get that you're lonely,
and that you're just trying to cope,
but, buddy, you can't live
in a fantasy world forever.
- Ray...
- Look, trust me.
I understand that it hurts
to learn that the world
isn't as perfect as you want it to be.
But sooner or later,
you have to start facing reality,
otherwise, you're going to end up
getting yourself killed.
Hey.
Listen to us.
We're going to save your friend
and make it out of here together.
All right?
Because that's what brave knights do.
Right, Sir Galahad?
Let's do it.
Ugh.
Where are you, guys?
Not sure exactly.
Looks like they turned the rec center
into some kind
of government research facility.
We're on our way to save
the baby Dominator.
- What?
- It's a long story.
Well, that story's about to get
a lot more interesting
because its mom just landed,
and she's looking for him.
Wait. The Dominator has a Mominator?
And it gets worse.
I think she might have read my mind.
Wait. What did she see?
Well, she was looking for her baby.
The last time I saw him was...
At my house.
My mom's home. If the Queen finds her...
Don't worry. We won't let that happen.
I'll keep watch for the Queen,
you check on Ray's mom.
Okay. How do I look?
Kidding.
Animal Control. Again.
Back to check out my crawl space?
Your who?
Oh.
So, what's your excuse this time?
Family of possums?
Come to wrestle a bear?
How did you make a family of possums
sound so sexy?
Well, you found your animal right here,
but good luck controlling her.
Who's there?
Mrs. Palmer?
But if you're here, then...
Wow. You are very powerful.
You have no idea.
Trick or treat!
Ray's Mom, it is an honor
just to be nominated...
We both know it's too late to stop this.
Well, maybe if we just
get to know each other...
Get away from him, you bitch!
I knew it! You're jealous!
No. She's messing with your mind.
She's making you see things.
Nate, that is not Ray's mother.
Don't be ridiculous.
Of course it's Ray's mom.
Who else would it be?
Oh! I kissed a Dominator.
And I liked it.
What's the matter?
Don't you think I'm pretty?
Hey! Over here!
Super-ambitious album.
Sara, we found the Queen.
Whoa!
Awesome costume.
I'm almost back to the ship.
I'll fly to you,
try to lure her onto the brig.
Oh, crap.
"Oh, crap" what?
All right, on to Plan B.
Let's say somebody stole the Waverider.
What if we give the Queen
what she wants
and just hope she goes in peace?
You mean the baby? I'm already on it.
Gumball!
Don't move.
Step away. You have no idea
what that thing is capable of.
We're taking it with us,
no one needs to get hurt.
Can't let you do that.
I don't think you want to do that.
You should really lower your weapons.
I...
I can't...
He's controlling them.
- Ray, turn it back on.
- No.
No? What do you mean "no"?
It'll hurt him.
He'll hurt all of us.
He wouldn't do that.
Can't believe I was this stubborn.
Look, if you don't listen to me,
we're all gonna die.
Good mornin'
We've talked the whole night through
To you
Good mornin'
Sunbeams will soon shine through
Good mornin' to you
Good mornin'
It's great to stay up late
Good mornin' to you...
So we should go, right?
Yeah.
I told you he wouldn't hurt anyone.
You're right. I should have trusted you.
I'm sorry for the tough love.
Good mornin'
Good mornin' to you...
Let's go.
...the movie show
the future wasn't bright
But came the dawn
The show goes on
And I don't wanna say good night...
Man, you guys are really good.
- Ray!
- Yeah, but they were...
- Good morning!
- Yup.
Good mornin'...
Quick. I'm sure those agents
are already coming to their senses.
Hey, we can use those.
Those aren't ours. We can't steal.
Ha! I knew you were a good kid.
But, uh, let's just make an exception
just this once.
Guys, we've got the baby.
And we've got the Queen,
and she's trying to kill us!
Let's hope everyone gets here
at the same time.
Or else, we're gonna have
one angry alien momma.
We're gonna make it.
- It's okay we borrowed the Waverider?
- They'll be fine.
We're never gonna make it!
It went this way.
God, I hope this works.
Hey, Gumball.
Mominator incoming!
I'll take her. This one's personal.
She put me in a cocoon.
Just like E. T.
- What's E. T.?
- "What's E. T.?"
Go ahead.
You have to go now. You need your mom.
But we'll still be friends.
I'll be all right.
I have people here to take care of me.
And I wouldn't have found them
without you.
Go on, go on, little buddy.
Go to your mama.
See you later, Gumball.
I'm not crying.
I just have, uh, alien goo in my eye.
Yeah, me, too.
Now I'm gonna go brush my teeth forever.
Wait. Why?
I'm so glad
I could be here
to welcome you into this world.
I'm sure it's overwhelming,
and I'm sorry to say,
it doesn't really ever go away.
But this place
is also full of wonders.
Wonders that I'm discovering even now.
Hey.
I'm sorry, man.
You almost missed this because of me,
because I didn't trust you...
No, I should have been...
I should've been honest with you
from the beginning.
You're as much a part of this family
as Lily and Clarissa
and now, this little guy, Ronnie.
It's perfect that you're here
with us right now.
Mr. Rory, on the other hand,
is inexplicable.
- I thought we should celebrate.
- Oh.
One for you.
- One for you.
- Thank you.
- And one for you.
- Mick, dude, come on, man. Not the baby.
Cute.
- What happened?
- Possums.
It's mating season.
They got all in your vents.
So, um, we got rid of them.
So you're saying
one of Ray's strays didn't do this?
Your son?
No, no, no.
And, uh, don't worry, I'm sure he'll
grow out of that eventually, you know.
And I think you're doing
a really good job with him.
Yeah. So, can we go now, please?
Yep.
I can't believe
you made out with my mom.
Look, man, it was the '80s.
You did the right thing, you know.
Letting him go.
He was my only real friend.
We were supposed
to watch the movie together.
I felt alone for a long time.
So long that I just figured
that's how things were gonna be.
But turns out there were people
out there for me
that I didn't even know I wanted.
You'll find your people, too. I promise.
You just have to keep believing
that things will be okay,
even when it's hard.
Will you watch the movie with me?
My ride's here, but maybe next time.
Besides, shouldn't you be out
trick-or-treating?
Me and Gumball were gonna go together.
Besides, I can't eat
all that candy anyway.
Hey, look at Palmer.
- What are you supposed to be?
- I'm the Atom.
That's like, the coolest superhero ever.
The Atom? That's a stupid name.
Actually, I think it's pretty clever.
Cool costume.
I can't believe you guys talked me
into wearing this.
How do you fight in these things?
Who are you guys?
We're his friends.
These guys are your friends?
Cool.
Hand the candy over.
And your allowance.
You know, in my time,
the FDA outlawed all of this.
Guess they got my letters.
Hey, do your missions
always go this poorly?
No. No.
There was this one time where we...
You know, actually, yes, they do.
Well, can't wait for the next one.
Which means we should probably get
to know each other.
So, Two Truths and a Lie.
Seriously?
Are we team-building right now?
Number one.
Back home, my friends
used to called me "Z."
Number two. I got a copy of Zelda
on the black market
and never beat that final boss.
Ganon.
And number three.
I love musicals.
Z, we're watching Singin' in the Rain.
I'll go get the popcorn.
Hey. Movie night! Wanna join us?
Man, I got some work to do.
Actually, I want to ask you something.
Yeah, shoot.
It's just seeing Stein
with his grandkid earlier,
I mean, we're his family,
but this isn't his home.
- Not anymore.
- Yeah.
But you two are inseparable.
Like, literally.
That's what I need your help with.
I want to break up Firestorm.