RIP: In 2166,
an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately,
my plan is opposed by
the body I had
sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered as legends.
Previously, on
Legends of Tomorrow...
Savage has kept his movements
hidden throughout history. But--
Professor Aldus Boardman
is the world's leading expert.
ALDUS: Savage was an Egyptian priest.
CARTER: Kendra and I reincarnate.
ALDUS: And every time he kills you,
it passes to him.
That's what maintains
his immortality.
GIDEON: Professor Boardman has
sustained severe internal injuries.
A hundred years from now,
your lives have minimal effect
on the recorded timeline.
You lied to us.
CARTER: I don't give a damn
about being a legend,
as long as we end Savage
once and for all.
So how do we find this guy?
And, we've arrived.
Gideon, if you wouldn't mind
camouflaging us
as an Alpine meadow, perhaps.
What're you complaining about now?
It's not like we time-jumped.
I hate flying. Especially in...
Whatever this thing is.
Where exactly are we?
We're still in 1975, right?
Indeed. October 19th, 1975.
On the fjords of Northern Norway.
Sounds like a vacation.
Which we can take as soon
as the threat of Savage
has been neutralized, Mister Snart.
That's Aldus' notebook.
Now, he theorized
that Savage might be here.
And, if he's right,
and if we can capture Savage,
then at least Professor Boardman
didn't die in vain.
Can't we just go back
and save Aldus?
He was our son.
Look, I'm sorry.
We can't go back and change events
in which we participated.
Time would fold in on itself,
creating a temporal vortex.
Which sounds way cooler than it is.
Forgetting physics for a second,
shouldn't we figure out
what Savage is doing in Norway?
According to Gideon, there's a large
meeting of terrorists and fringe groups
looking to buy illegal arms.
Now, that sounds like a vacation.
Arms dealers and terrorists
aren't exactly our kind of people,
but they're the next best thing.
Well, looks like you and your lapdog
get to earn your keep.
I'm no one's lapdog, birdman.
So, what exactly does one wear to
a black market arms bazaar, anyway?
The Waverider has
a fabrication room
which can fashion temporally
indigenous fashion.
You've got a room
that makes clothing?
Doesn't everyone?
All right. First thing we need
to do is work up a plan.
Got a lot of experience
infiltrating criminal gatherings?
Didn't think so.
I'm calling the shots.
Actually, I'm in charge,
in case any of you've forgotten.
No, I remember. I just don't care.
Do I need to remind any of you
that I am a Time Master?
Making discrete alterations
to the timeline is what I do.
So we're not going to
charge into the past
like a bull into a china shop.
Half of what you've told us about
the mission turned out to be lies.
None of you have ever encountered
Vandal Savage before.
I have.
And I am telling you now,
you are making a big mistake.
(SCOFFS)
Already did that when we trusted you.
Back soon, Captain.
Looks like they're checking
credentials. And we don't have any.
We got this. Trust us.
Excuse you.
IDs.
You don't look like
an "Amhad Ahmed Izz-Al-Din."
I'm Arab on my mother's side.
Is there a problem?
I don't like delays.
Do you know who we are?
My associates and I are
the operational arm of "Scimitar."
The Lombardo Square bombing, 1963.
Murder of Henri Tyran, Canada, 1970.
Koenig Airport Massacre, 1971.
Bottom line,
you don't want to doubt me.
You're a special kind of crazy.
I like it.
We're in.
So, why don't I
get to play terrorist?
SNART: This is just a kidnapping.
No need for your nuclear fireworks.
Savage'll be one of the buyers.
Once we get eyes on, hang back.
We'll boost him
once this is all over.
Any sign of him?
- No.
- He's not here, boss.
Let's get Ginger and
the Professor and move out.
MAN: If I could
have your attention...
Thank you all for coming.
I promise,
it will be well worth your time.
Seems we were wrong about Savage.
He's not one of the buyers.
He's the seller.
This is a variable-yield
nuclear warhead,
capable of producing a blast
equivalent to one megaton of TNT.
Shall we begin our bidding
at $100 million?
- (GUNSHOT)
- One hundred million.
- Do I hear 105?
- (GUNSHOT)
- One hundred and ten?
One hundred and fifteen?
Is everything all right, sir?
They're here.
That group.
Where are they from?
Appears we've drawn some
unwanted attention. We need to bid.
Fire your gun in the air.
That's 125.
What's happening?
It's what's not happening
that is the concern.
- Nobody else is bidding.
- Sold!
Congratulations, Professor.
You just bought yourself
a nuclear weapon.
Well, well,
we seem to have a new player.
Well, you seem a bit "academic."
How'd you get in here
and who are you?
As of a few seconds ago,
I'm a nuclear power.
Yet, I don't know you
or your organization.
And I know everyone.
- Hey, back off.
- Watch your tone.
- Is there some sort of problem here?
- Yeah.
The Master Race here
is starting to bug me.
We're just gonna get our nuclear
warhead and be on our way.
Not without paying first.
Once we've validated
that the warhead's operational.
Personally, I find it highly unlikely
that you were able to accumulate
enough fissionable
material in this era
to fashion
a workable nuclear device.
This era?
Figure of speech.
I've got a feeling
you guys might
want to get those
helmets of yours on.
Change of plans.
I'll provide a 25% discount
to the organization which
brings me the heads of these men.
Can I burn some stuff now?
I wish you would.
(GRUNTING)
- Now would be a good time.
- Yeah. To kill you.
I wasn't talking to you.
(SCREAMING)
Savage.
Prince Khufu.
As always, the fashion plate.
And, your better half...
This ends here and now, Savage.
You're coming with us.
I doubt you can apprehend me
and stop a nuclear explosion.
- You screwed that up pretty good!
- I had it handled.
I like how you actually believe that.
Um, we've got a nuclear bomb here.
Ray! What did you do?
I didn't do anything!
It must have a failsafe!
Professor, Jax, we need you!
PROFESSOR STEIN: You have to get
to a minimum safe distance.
Okay, what now?
PROFESSOR STEIN: We wait
for the warhead to go off.
At which point,
you're going to have 0.06 seconds
to absorb the massive release
of atomic energy.
Your plan sucks.
You know that, right?
PROFESSOR STEIN: Concentrate, Jefferson.
(SCREAMING)
Well, I'm really glad
you were the one calling the shots.
I had it under control
until the Professor started
picking fights with the PLO.
You let your ego
endanger our entire mission.
No, Mister Rory's temper
got completely out of --
I thought we were friends, Professor.
At least, there's one less
nuclear bomb on the planet.
(CLAPPING SLOWLY)
Hear, hear. You all deserve
a hearty congratulations.
Not only did you
fail to capture Savage,
but you exposed yourselves
and your powers to him,
giving away the element
of surprise for now and all time.
Well done, team!
We don't need
the "element of surprise."
We know he's here in Norway.
So let's find him.
Unfortunately, we now have
larger problems than Savage.
If only you'd have
listened to me
about the dangers
of upsetting the timeline.
What are you talking about?
While you were busy saving
Norway from nuclear annihilation--
You're welcome, Norway!
Savage sent one of his cronies
back to the site of the arms sale.
Anyone care to guess what he found?
Oops.
I'm unversed in
modern American colloquialisms.
Is "Oops" slang for--
Yes, Doctor Palmer seems to have
thrown a spanner in the works
- for the entire timeline.
- Come again?
Armed with Doctor Palmer's
future technology,
Savage's engineers develop a weapon
far more destructive
than anything here in 1975.
This is Central City in 2016.
At least it was.
I'm not sure what neo-fascists
who took control of it
are calling it these days.
There must be a way
to correct this somehow.
Fortunately,
Gideon is just showing us
a forecast of the future
you've all created.
Time is like cement,
it takes time to become permanent.
In this case,
until Savage's team have worked out
the mystery of your future technology
and molded it to their own ends.
And, when they do, what you see here
is no longer just a forecast.
This...
This is history.
Where is he?
His body, I mean.
There's cryo-storage in the MedBay.
I promise we'll get our son
a proper burial once we have a chance.
It's still so weird
to hear you call him that.
But even though it was in a past life,
it feels like something's missing.
I know.
What's that?
I found it in his pocket.
I've seen this knife before.
This is the knife
that Savage used to kill us.
In our first life.
So thanks to Raymond leaving
a piece of his suit in the past,
the rest of us don't have
a future to go back to...
Unless we do something
to change this course of events.
The future will become immutable.
Exactly how much time do we have?
Until Savage's weapons team
reverse-engineer your tech.
We're talking 1970s terrorists
with 21st century weapons?
And since we don't know
where Savage went...
We don't have to find Savage,
we just have to find
the other piece of my suit!
Which shrinks
because it's made of an alloy
which mimics the intra-molecular
compression of a dwarf star,
thus emitting Alpha particles.
So we just need to
be able to track them.
Fortunately,
Alpha particles are highly trackable.
Yet unheard of in the 1970s.
It's like we're trapped
in the Stone Age.
I will have you know that
I was researching Alpha particles
when you were eating crayons!
So to track that piece of Raymond's
super-suit we just need to talk to--
Me. 25-year-old me, rather.
You two are just in time.
Show them, Kendra.
Aldus was carrying this
when he was killed.
It's a newspaper article
about an Egyptian dagger.
The one Savage used to kill us.
In Central City,
we learned that
objects associated with
the night of our deaths,
can also be used to kill Savage.
According to Aldus' notes, the dagger
needs to be wielded in conjunction
with an incantation inscribed on it.
Well, what does this incantation say?
I don't know.
I can't read the language.
It's okay. I'll help you remember.
- Splendid. Now, as for the dagger...
- You need someone to steal it?
Okay, fine. Whatever. I'll do it.
Article says that it was purchased
by some rich Russian douchebag
named Sasha Mahnovski.
- I'll go with you.
- I already got a partner.
Who I trust even less than you.
Look, you're more than welcome
to go with him,
just don't take along
your future-tech.
Oi! Where do you think you are going?
To break into my old lab and
bring us back the particle tracker.
Fine. Perhaps you should take
Jefferson and Sara with you
to act as your intermediaries.
Interacting with yourself
in the past
can have catastrophic effects
upon the future.
Fascinating. Let's go.
GIDEON: Setting a course
for the United States, Captain.
People actually wore this crap?
People smoked
a lot of pot in the '70s,
it clearly had a deleterious effect
on the fashion of the era.
Let's just hurry up
and get that particle tracker
so I can get the hell
out of these go-go boots.
When we meet my former self,
it's imperative
that we don't let on
we're from the future.
So, let's just be cool.
Oh, my God.
Look.
I had forgotten how handsome I was.
My hair, it's so thick and silky.
Do I know you?
No, no. I... I'm Professor Musk.
Elon Musk.
And these are my two lab assistants.
Hi. I'm Marty.
Are you sure we haven't met before?
It's a very interesting question.
Suffice it to say,
I'm familiar with your work.
That's actually why we're here.
To see you.
You're a leading expert
in Alpha particles?
(CHUCKLING) No, I'm "The" leading expert.
Well, we were hoping to pick your
brain about your area of expertise.
Physics?
Which are you interested in?
Applied or theoretical?
That is just the thing.
I can't decide.
I love them both!
Cool.
Well, let's go spark a "doobie"
and rap about physics.
Lead the way, Marty.
Uh...
Are you sure that's actually you?
(CHUCKLING) Oh, man.
Concentrate, Kendra.
You know how to read the inscription.
At least, you used to know.
Yeah. Well,
my hieroglyphic is a little rusty.
GIDEON: Lapidary hieratic, actually.
An ancient language
lost to the ages.
Don't you know how to read it?
It was a language known
only to the clergy.
GIDEON: If we only had a Rosetta Stone.
I might be able to--
Well, you are our Rosetta Stone.
Just close your eyes.
Think of it as meditation. I need
you to relax, and open your mind.
In order for you to remember
how to kill Savage,
I need you to let your mind float.
Back through
your hundreds of previous lives.
Your name is Chay-Ara,
and you are a priestess
in the temple of Horus.
(GASPS)
What? What is it?
Us.
We were together.
Like, "together" together.
Well, I have been telling you
that you and I should be destined...
What are you doing?
What part of "destiny"
do you not understand?
The part where I have to stop
thinking for myself.
The group that disrupted
the arms auction...
Any idea who they were?
A man in a robotic suit,
weapons that shoot ice and fire...
Suffice it to say,
they're not from around here.
I would assume the future.
- That's impossible.
- So is immortality.
Besides, how else
do you explain
technology beyond
anything we've seen?
What can you tell me about it?
It contains a miniaturized
missile guidance system
capable of delivering
high-explosive ordnance.
You have 24 hours
to reverse-engineer it.
It could take weeks,
months to figure out the circuitry!
It looks simple enough to me.
You just press this button here.
I said 24 hours.
I suggest you all get to work.
SNART: I'm seeing motion-detectors
on the ground floor,
hardware on the doors
looks standard-issue.
- I can't see any smoke alarms...
- Just stay close.
I saw at least three armed guards
on the perimeter.
All right, boss.
- What the hell are you--
- I recognize the security system.
My parents had the exact one.
I'll have the access code cracked
and security disabled
before you can say
"breaking and entering."
There. We're in.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Why's that?
Because you just
tapped into a dummy box.
Which means
those guards are going to be here--
Quicker than you can say
"rookie mistake."
Hands up.
Huh.
- So, who wants a hit?
- Yeah, man.
I believe you told me
you're trying to quit.
None for you, silver top?
I don't partake in cannabis...
Anymore, that is. In fact,
perhaps you should take it easy.
Ah, it helps me think better... Dad.
Mmm-hmm.
Yes, but what about the long-term
health consequences?
Speaking of which, you might want
to lay off the saturated fats.
So...
Alpha particles...
Exciting stuff.
Too bad detection is at least
a decade away.
More like two decades.
But I've worked up
a little something.
Science is all about
the future, right?
I've developed
a prototype particle tracker.
Cutting edge. Probably gonna
mint me a million dollars.
Wow!
A whole million?
Be right back.
I think I've got some chocolate
chip cookie dough in the fridge.
I cannot believe that that is you.
Seriously.
I had no idea you were ever cool.
I wasn't cool.
I was an arrogant little snot.
- Was?
- What are you doing?
Looking for my younger self's
particle tracker.
Keep an eye on the door.
And, when I get back,
stop flirting with me.
You're the one flirting with me.
Look, what's the big deal?
I mean, young you isn't married yet,
so technically it's not cheating.
October 1975...
This is right when I meet
my future wife Clarissa.
So obviously, we wouldn't want
my former self tempted
by a sexy assassin from the future.
Aww... You think I'm...
Do not finish that sentence.
Found it.
Is there a trick
to opening the case?
Aah...
What are you doing?
Let's grab the dagger and let's go!
Raymond, you don't break into
a candy store and steal one gumball.
You guys grab the goodies,
I'll find the safe.
What do you think you're doing?
This is what we came here for.
No, it's what you came here for.
Take your hand off me.
I'm not gonna let you
jeopardize another mission.
I'm done asking politely.
This is my mission.
And I'm gonna listen to a guy who's
spent half of his life in prison?
(BUZZER SOUNDING)
Great.
Now, we're both going to prison.
(GASPS)
Eureka.
I remember building this.
It's like déjà vu all over again.
Put that down.
Excellent job watching the door.
What're you doing?
Oh, just... What is this?
Something you shouldn't be
fooling around with.
It's very interesting looking.
How about you cut the crap?
To which crap are you referring?
I hold two PhD's
and I'm working on a third.
I'm a five-time winner
of the Carlin Award.
My point being, is I don't
believe either of those kids
you're hanging around
with can even spell "physics."
You know, I'm beginning to like
the younger gray less and less.
Either you tell me what the hell is
going on or I'm calling campus police.
I'm not supposed to tell you.
It could cause, well, trouble.
We're here to interview you for a
profile in next month's Wells Journal.
The Wells only profiles
Nobel candidates.
An exception is being made
in light of your obvious brilliance.
I know a photograph of this device
would make a spectacular cover.
If we could just borrow it
for a few hours.
Thanks.
But that's two years of my life.
I'm not letting you
walk away with it.
Stay back.
That was taking too long.
You just knocked me out.
That beautiful brain
struck unconscious!
The only way to shut you up.
What're you doing?
We have to go.
I have to make sure I wake up in time
to go to this Faculty Mixer tonight.
One of the professors
is bringing his niece,
AKA my future wife.
Let's go.
(BUZZING)
What the hell happened?
It was this idiot's fault.
I told you we shouldn't
have brought him.
Agreed. But we got bigger problems.
I need you to
find the fuse box and--
Trigger a system default.
This ain't over.
How did you know how to do that?
When I was a kid
my dad brought me along on jobs.
I had little hands,
I could get into tiny spaces,
do whatever he needed me to do...
Like, rewiring a security system.
In another life you could have
been an electrical engineer.
I guess I dodged a bullet.
You think I want to be like you?
You make being a tech billionaire
sound like a bad thing.
You spend all your time and money
inventing a super-suit,
and what do you do with it?
Fly around like some
incredible shrinking schmuck
trying to save the world.
And robbing banks for a living.
I suppose that's more important?
It's sure as hell more satisfying.
Thinking like that
is what makes you a criminal.
No, it makes me a survivor.
And there's going to come a day
when you wish you were, too.
Here.
You flip the solenoid,
saves you the trouble of rewiring it.
I take it back, Raymond.
You're not completely
useless after all.
I wanted to apologize.
I'm not afraid of my past.
I'm just unwilling to believe
that you are my future.
And the more you keep repeating
that we're destined to be together,
the more I want to prove you wrong.
And maybe that makes me childish--
No. It doesn't.
Not at all.
Look, 4,000 years is a long time.
And maybe
I've been taking us for granted,
expecting you
to fall in love with me
because that's what you've done
in the last 206 lifetimes.
But, you're right,
it does not make us destiny.
More like probability.
Look, Kendra.
You don't have to love me
in this lifetime.
As many lifetimes as it takes.
I know you're worth the wait.
All right, well,
let's try this again.
You know what to do.
Your name is Chay-Ara,
and you are a priestess
in the temple of Horus...
You're giving me
a knife as a present?
Your conceptions of romance
require some adjustment I think.
It's sacred.
I was told that only a high priestess
could read the inscription. It's--
A poem.
And though my soul departs the Earth
I count my days 'til my rebirth
I will wait across eternity
For my love to come back to me
The knife...
You gave it to me.
And, the inscription, it was a poem.
A love poem, which promises...
Promises what?
That we'd be together forever.
PROFESSOR STEIN: Perhaps,
I really am genius.
My younger self's tracker led us
straight to Savage's lab.
Reading's at 96.6%.
It's definitely down there.
- Be right back.
- What? Wait, wait.
Shouldn't we handle this?
I mean, you look pretty stoned.
I could be unconscious and
I'd still be able to kick the ass
of a few rent-a-thugs from 1975.
I do see
why I found her so attractive.
- Looking for this.
- Yeah.
And you all have a lovely evening.
(THUD)
Huh.
Looks like Rory found the fuse box.
RORY: We got a slight problem.
The owner just came home.
You're not gonna believe who it is.
We meet again.
Oh, I'm grateful for another opportunity
to kill you.
I've never saved the world before.
Feels good.
We should've picked up some donuts
on the way back.
My God. My ring.
When you knocked me out,
I must not have woken up
or did and decided
not to go to the Mixer.
Clarissa...
Holy crap.
Now do you want to tell me
who you are and where you're from?
Stop struggling.
I've had 4,000 years of training in
every hold and pressure point known.
But you already know that, don't you?
That I am immortal.
I'm going to kill you anyway.
That's a promise.
Oh, what have I done to
deserve such enmity?
No, let me rephrase that.
What have I done to you?
Perhaps you have targeted me
for something I've yet to do.
You traveled here
from some point in the future.
Catches on fast, this guy.
Visitors from another time.
You won't be so happy
when the rest of the team shows up.
And knocks that
smug grin off your face.
Oh... Why wait?
A communications device
of some sort, I imagine?
Please.
Contact your friends.
I'm looking forward to seeing
at least two of them again.
Unbelievable.
Is that a tachyon manifold?
Hey. How did you find us, man?
You think I couldn't build
something to track my own tracker?
Do you have any idea
what you have done?
What I've done?
You guys knocked me out.
Which we wouldn't have had to do
in the first place
if you weren't
such a monumental jerk!
Okay, can I just... Yeah.
You watch him, Sara.
Yo, you need to calm down and
you need to stop yelling at yourself.
- His arrogant curiosity--
- Yeah.
He's curious and too smart
for his own good.
But I'm sure you can relate.
You're just pissed
you didn't see it coming sooner--
That's not it.
Although you are correct
in observing my ire is self-directed.
It's a rude awakening
when one realizes that
despite decades of what one thought
was maturation and experience,
you haven't really changed at all.
That same arrogance I derided
in my younger self
was on full display
at the weapons bazaar.
Over 60 years on this planet,
and I have learned nothing.
I think you're being
a little too hard on yourself.
Which makes a nice change from
you always being hard on me, but...
Yeah, you're arrogant.
But you're also smart and kind,
and selfless.
I mean, you wanna make the world
a better place
and you're willing to risk everything
to make that happen.
That... That is not a bad guy.
And neither is this one.
Meeting Clarissa was one of
the great moments of my life.
And meeting you was another.
You are a fine young man,
Mr. Jackson.
Come on.
Can someone, please,
tell me what's going on?
You didn't say anything to him.
I figured we screwed up
the '70s enough.
What are you talking about?
Are you saying that you're from--
Don't say another word.
Don't even think it.
You are to get off this ship.
Post haste.
Wonderful.
Another unauthorized passenger.
That worked out
so splendidly last time.
- Sorry, he was just leaving.
- I'll show you out.
So have we met before?
In a manner of speaking.
Have a wonderful life, Martin.
I mean that sincerely.
I'm not even going to ask.
GIDEON: Captain Hunter, we're getting
an incoming communiqué.
Mister Snart on
Mister Rory's comm unit.
On speaker.
SNART: I'll make this short.
The owner of the mansion
we burgled is Vandal Savage.
He's really interested
in meeting you guys.
Especially our feathered friends.
- They have the dagger.
- And Savage has them.
Doesn't matter.
Just get me close enough
and I'll do what needs to be done.
GIDEON: I have their coordinates.
Let's do this.
Your friends are cowards.
They'll be here.
They are taking too long.
They need an incentive...
Oh!
The burning man.
I don't just burn, pal.
I blast things, too.
- Are you okay?
- I'm pissed.
Stand back.
It's all good. Savage is down.
Savage is not defeated
by earthly means.
Well, I hit him with a nuclear blast
so, you know, not that earthly.
Go get that son of a bitch.
Are you ready to end this?
We've only been waiting 4,000 years.
We got company.
Friends of Savage.
You'll be needing this.
Don't leave any pieces of it
behind this time.
(SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE)
The Amon dagger.
Of all the knives I've collected
across the centuries,
that was my favorite.
(GRUNTING)
And though my soul
departs the Earth...
(SCREAMING)
Such a beautiful poem.
I remember it well.
As you can see, I can make
the dagger do its work without it.
Carter!
This was your lover's blade.
It must be her hand that wields it.
Something to consider
in your next life.
(YELLING)
Carter.
It's okay. You're gonna be okay.
I will wait...
Through eternity...
Please just save your strength.
Come back to me.
No.
Murderer.
(YELLING)
I am not a murderer.
I am a force of nature.
A servant of fate.
I enable destiny.
I love you, Chay-Ara.
I always will.
(GROANING)
But we are both tortured
by this circle of death
we are imprisoned by.
Carter...
He's lost.
Get Kendra before Savage recovers.
Come on.
We can still kill this bastard.
Kendra is the only one who can.
We gotta go.
Kendra needs medical attention.
Gideon, get us underway as soon as
Firestorm and the Atom are onboard.
Get her to the MedBay now.
I assure you, Doctor Palmer, there's
nothing more you can do for her.
- You can't let her die.
- I don't intend to.
GIDEON: Sharp force injury resulting in
rupture of several major blood vessels.
Her pressure is currently
82 over 30 and stable.
I will begin by
irrigating the wound
and cauterizing it to prevent
any further hemorrhaging.
Thank you, Gideon.
Carter! Carter!
Gideon, if you wouldn't mind
administering a mild sedative.
No! No!
I didn't get to tell him...
I didn't get to tell him
it came back to me.
I finally remembered how I felt
about him in our past lives
and I didn't get to tell him.
I didn't get to tell him
- I felt the same way.
- (RIP SHUSHING)
- How is she?
- Stable, I think.
Sara told me about what's happening
with your wife. I'm sorry.
I'm so seduced by the prospects
of time travel, of adventure,
I never stopped to consider
the consequences
of what we were undertaking.
Gideon has managed to stabilize
Ms. Saunders' condition.
But another time jump
could aggravate her injuries.
- So we're stuck in '75?
- For the time being, yes.
Given that, can I have
a moment of your time, Martin?
There's something
that I would like to show you.
Of course.
Apparently, it's true that the guilty
return to the scene of the crime.
Oh, don't be so maudlin.
Look at your hand.
- How--
- I contacted your younger self
and encouraged him to attend
the Faculty Mixer.
Turns out, one of the professors
brought along his niece.
You risked the timeline for me?
Hardly seemed fair for you
to sacrifice your wife
in order to save mine
from Savage's future.
The one thing that
time travel teaches you
is that time changes,
people don't.
A painful realization
I've recently come to.
I have traveled countless ages
into the future,
we're still asking ourselves
the same question.
Why are we here?
I believe that we're here to learn,
Martin.
Be glad that you still can.
Thank you, Mr. Hunter.
- How is Kendra?
- The same.
So, what now?
Now...
Now, it's up to you.
To do what, Rip?
Last I checked,
every time we try to do anything,
it all goes to crap.
Once again,
I must disagree with you.
Thanks to Miss Lance,
Dr. Palmer's future technology
is no longer in the hands of
Vandal Savage's
black market weapons designers.
But it didn't do anything
to change the fate of your world.
No.
Vandal Savage will still
rise to power in the year 2166.
And your family will still die?
So, what you're really asking is,
do we want to fish or cut bait?
Return to 2016
and live out the rest of our lives
as insignificant losers or...
Make another play
at becoming legends.
Figure out how to end Savage
and save the world.
Preferably, without causing
any more nuclear explosions.
Savage has my attention.
Look, we didn't know
Carter from Adam.
But if you take out one of my
crew, you're gonna pay the price.
Well, surely,
Captain Hunter has a sound plan.
- What about you?
- You're asking me?
I didn't give you much of a choice
the first time, did I?
Well, I say we kick Savage's ass.
For Carter.
So, Captain,
where are we going next?
English SDH