Previously
on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
- It's a dragon egg.
- You're possessed.
- Ray's gone.
- I've taken over his body.
If Neron wanted John dead,
he would have killed him
on the spot.
I need you to open up
a doorway to hell.
It's to bring someone here
from the other side.
Tabitha.
- I'm sorry. It wasn't me.
- It was my nipple.
- Save me!
- As you wish.
I'm not leaving Mona behind.
Do you really think
that everyone in hell
deserves to be there?
This is your opportunity
to make things right.
I'm gonna save Ray.
Honey, time to go.
Come on, honey, let's go.
We're gonna be late.
Zari? You better not
be eating the Halva.
No, Mommy.
Zari Jaan.
Dessert's not for
after breakfast.
What?
It's only a kick.
Behrad must be anxious
to meet you.
Now go put your shoes on
so I can take you to school.
You might just want
to soak it all in.
Violent people are pouring
into our country...
illegal immigrants,
terrorists, meta-humans.
Politicians promise
to keep you safe
but they've been
hiding the truth.
There's a dangerous new threat
already within our borders.
Hi, I'm Ray Palmer.
Yes, that Ray Palmer...
former CEO of PalmerTech.
And I am here to warn you
that creatures once thought only
in legends and fairy tales
are real.
Yes, folks, monsters are real,
and they walk amongst us.
And they will stop at nothing
until they destroy humankind.
Interested in learning more?
Then join me at PalmerX 2019,
where the power is in
the Palmer of your hands.
I don't care if Neron's
wearing my best friend's face.
- I want to punch him.
- Get in line.
Ogres are big softies... that
one wouldn't even hurt a fly.
Neron's been a step
ahead of us for too long.
- We need to play offense.
- Agreed.
Sorry, what are we agreeing to?
Look, it's time for us
to fight back.
We're retaking the Bureau.
Gideon, pull up the blueprints
at the Bureau
and start fabricating
and arsenal.
- Right away, Captain.
- Look, Gary has bonded
with the Fairy Godmother,
and while he might be an idiot,
she is not to be underestimated.
Mick, Nate, you think
you can handle Tabitha?
- Granny's dead.
- Good.
Ava and I will handle Neron.
Yeah, I want a crack at him.
It's my bureau he's running
his operation from.
Not to be a buzzkill,
but even John and Nora
couldn't out-magic Neron.
- I just felt a kick.
- Oh, I want to feel!
Right now the smart play would
be just to bide our time.
Wait for John-o to return
with Ray's soul.
Shockingly,
I agree with Charlie.
- I love you, little Wicksty...
- Oh, I felt it!
I told you, it's kicking.
Okay, can you guys stop being
dragon-baby crazy right now?
Look, this commercial is proof
that Neron
is up to something big,
and we need
to stop him
before it's too late.
Captain, I have an incoming
communication from Nora Darhk.
- Put her on.
- Sara?
- Talk to me.
- What's your status?
I'm tired of skulking
around air ducts.
I'm going after Mona.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- We're gearing up
for an assault.
Hold your position.
- Hey!
- Too late.
- Wait, where's Gary?
- In Ava's office...
getting real comfortable.
Mmm.
Oh, Fairy Godmother?
Yes, my pet?
I want to dig deeper
on my next wish.
- Excellent idea.
- What do you have in mind?
Well...
we've already redecorated
my office.
I now have three nipples
because a spare never hurts,
and...
Perhaps you could make
a wish regarding the Legends?
You want me to wish something
for them?
I'm talking about revenge.
- Oh.
- They lied to you, Gary.
Promised you could be
an interim Legend.
One wish, and you can send them
all to hell
with John Constantine.
Speaking of John,
you think he's all right?
That warlock sent thousands
of demons to rot in the pits.
I think he's well
and truly screwed, dearie.
Does this mean we're straight?
I got a more important
collection to make.
Who is that guy?
That, my friend,
is John Constantine...
in the flesh.
Congratulations, Mona.
I have selected you
for a very special assignment.
That's okay, Ne-Ray.
Can I call you that?
I'm okay here.
You see, before Nate's father
decided he wanted to be
P.T. Barnum,
we were working together.
Training monsters
to do our bidding.
Actually, I worked extensively
with your dear friend Konane...
I mean...
Your dead friend Konane.
- I found Mona.
- Hurry.
Copy that.
This seems like overkill.
The Legends never included me
in their pizza parties...
or asked me to play
Dungeons & Dragons.
Make them suffer, Gary.
I can make them do
whatever you want.
I just wanted to be
part of the team.
As soon as Ava opens the portal,
we go in firing.
Time to burn some freaks.
I wish...
Opening a portal
in three, two, one.
No.
Welcome to book club.
Why, you little...
I'd be careful how you speak
to my charge.
Gary, why are you doing this?
Because I would like
to discuss...
"The Collector."
Forget the book, Gary.
You helped a demon
take control of the Bureau.
What happened to
the Bureau creed?
Oh, I could ask
the same about you.
Article 27?
Hmm?
A supervisor must never show
favoritism?
You started a book club
with another employee.
Gary, Mona is being tortured
right now.
Neron said he's trying
to protect
humans from monsters.
You saw Mona gnaw off my nip.
- She did you a favor.
- Okay, um...
maybe we should just reschedule
until after we've read the book?
Oh, Fairy Godmother?
- Oh, no.
- Wait.
- Ow.
- Book was terrible.
Oh, my head.
That's the spirit.
- Sara, Ava, come in.
- Where are you guys?
- Hey, Nate.
- Can't talk right now.
Are you talking to Nate
on comms?
Tell him I say hi.
Gary says hi.
And we are at book club.
Move on to plan B.
- What's plan B?
- I only listen for my name.
I assume it's like plan A,
but, you know, with less people.
Well, without the Captain
and the clone,
the Bureau's a suicide mission.
Mick's right.
We need to sneak into PalmerX,
do some recon,
find out what Neron is up to.
Now that sounds like a plan Z.
- Mmm.
- Hey, baby.
Hey, you looking
for a good time, handsome?
I'm always looking
for a good time, love,
but, uh, regrettably,
my time here is limited.
Maybe you can help me.
I'm looking for broker
in the soul trade.
He goes by the name of Masher.
I might know something.
Well, this here is holy water.
Now, you can use this
to burn the skin
off any demon tosser
who messes with you.
Uh-uh-uh.
Masher likes to hang out
at the strip club
after trading is done...
John.
How do you know my name?
Oh, I know who you are.
Half of demonkind is searching
for John Constantine.
The holy water?
- Oh, this?
- Nah, this is just whisky, love.
Sure, our protagonist
was keeping people
hostage, but...
that's only because he never
received love as a child.
Aah!
They don't want you
in their book club, Gary.
Doesn't that make you angry?
Make a wish, and they will pay.
- You're right.
- They don't want to spend time
with Gary Green,
lowly Time Bureau agent.
But they would love
to spend time
with Gary Green...
Captain of the Waverider!
Welcome aboard, Captain Green.
Thanks.
I have no quarrel
with you, dear.
You didn't send me to hell
like John Constantine
and the Legends.
Yes...
I was in hell for 327 years.
And what was my crime?
I sprinkled a little magic
over Salem,
trying to help a girl
who's mother
was accused of witchcraft.
Okay, well, you're out now.
Why help Neron?
Neron rescued me in hell.
What can I say?
True love bloomed.
I know what you're thinking...
he's so much older than me.
Sometimes you
have to look past age.
You know, in another life,
I think you and I could have
been friends.
- Toodles.
- Wait, what?
Ray?
Without all
of the idiotic tendencies.
Make a move on me,
and Mona dies.
Ray is good and strong.
He can fight his way
back from hell.
Who do you think
is having a worse time in hell?
Ray, or your father?
Turns out Daddy dearest
isn't so tough.
I hear Damien Darhk is going
stark raving mad in the pits.
Why am I here?
Well, you and John
tried to kill me... nearly did.
If the doofus
in the skin suit I'm wearing
hadn't have interrupted,
I'd have been obliterated.
I spent many nights
just dreaming
about how I was going
to get my revenge.
And then it came to me...
what better punishment
than making you sit front row
to all of the fear and rage
I'm about to unleash
on the Earth,
all while in the body
of the man you love.
Now...
Smile for the cameras.
- Mr. Palmer!
- Are monsters real?
What's tonight all about?
Now, all of your questions
will be answered soon.
- Oh. Excuse me.
- What's wrong with you?
Well, you know,
a room full of people
fearful of magical creatures
just makes me a little bit
fearful, all right?
The worst part is,
Ray loves tech events.
Good evening, D.C.,
and welcome
to PalmerX 2019.
Now, you're all
probably wondering,
what in the heck is Ray Palmer
doing back in the public eye?
Well, folks, for the past
two years I have been hunting
magical creatures.
Hang with me here.
I have created an exosuit
capable of combating
the most ferocious
of their kind.
What a douche.
- But I can't do it alone.
- I need your help.
I need you to help me
find these creatures...
creatures that may be hiding
right here amongst us.
Now, everyone take out
your smartphones.
Better be PalmerTech.
I have created a small,
simple app,
that will change the world.
And I want you all
to download it right now.
The app is called Eyes.
Now, on Eyes, you will be able
to share real-time,
life-saving monster sightings.
Share them, and I will be there
to save you.
Remember, the power
is in the Palmer of your hands.
You really expect us
to believe monsters exist?
I thought you were going
to offer us proof.
- Thank you, Cindy.
- You are absolutely right.
Here is your proof.
Now, this may look like
a helpless hipster
who should be working
at a bookstore,
but believe me, she is something
altogether more dangerous.
- Masher.
- John?
Yeah, yeah, all right,
keep your hair on.
No need to tell the whole
bloody club.
Oh, buddy, now I know you're
out of your mind.
- What are you doing in hell?
- I'm here to save a friend.
His soul belongs to Neron.
Cheers, love.
He's paying.
Nobody gets into Neron's
soul vault without his say-so.
Except the Triumvirate,
and I have a plan
to deal with them,
but first, there's a hunch
I need to confirm.
What's Neron trading at?
He's steady, but I'll let you
in on a little secret.
His stock is about to rise.
I'm talking a massive
soul collection on Earth.
You know what that means?
Neron is finally making his play
for the throne of hell.
Oh, cheers, Masher.
I can use that.
Be careful, John.
Not every demon
you've sent to hell
is as forgiving as I am.
Yeah, don't I know it.
You're dead, demon hunter.
I was going to be
a demon proctologist,
but the pay wasn't as good.
- Hold him.
- Oh!
Oh, Calibraxis.
Hey, looking good, mate.
- You grow your beard?
- John Constantine.
I'm really going to enjoy
watching you breathe your last.
I invoke a parlay.
I demand to speak
to the Triumvirate.
I'm a demon, not a pirate, John.
I thought you understood
the rules.
Well, you little maggot,
as long as I'm alive,
then the Triumvirate
can pass me around
like a little sparrow
amongst the cats.
But as soon as I die,
you dim-witted dick,
then my soul belongs to Neron,
and then the Triumvirate
lose out
on all the tasty little bits
of torture
that they've got planned for me.
So you've got two choices:
You can either kill me
and royally piss off the old
bags that run this place,
or take me to speak
with the Triumvirate.
I'm detecting
a fugitive alert... stop it...
at the Inquisition,
Captain Green.
Oh, I don't do torture.
- Could've fooled me.
- Hey. Play nice.
We have to distract Gary
while the B team
is plan B... ing.
Would a fairy at the
Great British Bakeoff
suit your fancy?
Shall we, uh...
keep calm and pastry on?
I'll plot a course, Captain.
Get it?
"Keep calm and pastry on"?
Good one, Cap.
- Hilarious.
- Thanks, guys.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Take a good,
long look at her... Mona Wu.
You saw her on the street,
you wouldn't think twice.
- Come on, Mona.
- Don't give him what he wants.
But she has a strange
and violent condition...
brought about
when she fell in love
with a repulsive creature.
I feel like a bridge scene
should have more people.
Oh, no, we love
three-people bridge scenes.
Yeah, otherwise we just
end up standing around all day.
Oh, that's why
Mick's always grumpy.
Come on, Mona.
I promised
these fine people a show.
Let's not keep them waiting.
Shift now or end up
dead like Konane.
Folks, proof
of the world's
very first werewolf.
That's what we're missing...
the boys!
- No.
- Yeah.
Fairy Godmother?
- Z.
- B.
- She made him disappear!
- Well, well, well...
what do we have here?
More magic in the audience?
She's one of them!
- He's right.
- I am.
- She's a witch.
- Witch. Witch.
Witch, witch, witch!
Witch, witch...
- Don't worry, folks.
- The witch won't get far.
Not as long as everyone
downloads the Eyes app.
Share your sightings.
We'll find the witch.
It's only a matter of time.
Sara, you guys okay?
Yeah, we're fine, as long
as we keep placating Gary.
I guess Charlie and Z
are our last hope.
- Great, we're toast.
- Welcome to hell.
Good evening,
this is your captain speaking.
Just...
What?
We'll be cruising at
a high altitude
on our way
to save a bakeoff in Britain.
- Whoo, yeah.
- Yeah.
Gary, is that
the Kid Steel costume?
Uh-huh.
You like-y?
Why would anyone wish
to be a sidekick?
- Close your legs.
- Oh, he's such an idiot.
What?
Nothing,
they're just teasing you.
- Oh.
- You're my Gar-bear.
We're gonna have so much fun.
Okay?
#EyesApp is trending on Twitter
below Kanye's surprise album
and a cat getting a bath.
- Mm.
- How many downloads?
Only 2,000, Mr. Palmer.
News cycle is so fast
these days,
it's hard to
cut through all the noise.
But a monster attack
on the capital
will dominate
the headlines for weeks.
And then what?
More people will download
some app?
That's your big plan?
Why, yes, it is.
Ah! My love.
Would you please
escort our guest
to a cell?
Let's go, dearie.
Neron didn't say which
containment cell to put you in.
Why are you helping me?
Because you're a fellow witch,
and I think
we can help each other.
Mona?
How do you feel?
I've been better.
Remember, I'm just
a "Fairy Godmother" away.
Trust me, we'll be safe here.
Where are we?
My childhood home.
I thought you grew up
in a dystopian city, Z.
You had a pool?
In a couple years,
A.R.G.U.S. will use people's
growing fear of meta-humans
to seize control.
Of course, it didn't help
that we were Muslim.
We were forced to move
to a ghetto district in 2021.
Humans are so easy
to manipulate.
I mean, you just show them
a scary ogre
or a dangerous meta,
they just go barmy.
Haven't even been able
to get into the Eyes app yet
because the terms
of service are so long.
No one bothers reading those.
- It's a demon app.
- I'm gonna read the fine print.
I can't believe
it's just us left.
I mean, you and I both knew
from the start
that it was madness
to storm the Bureau.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
Z?
In New Orleans,
John said Neron needed more
souls to take over hell.
Here it says in exchange
for the service,
the user agrees to forfeit
their eternal soul
to the demon Neron.
What, you're saying that anyone
who downloads the app
is going to hell?
Yeah.
Oh, that is mental.
This little fairy was causing
quite the fray
around the soufflé.
I think I know
just the place for you, madame.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm gonna kill him.
Hey, Z, Charlie, please tell
me you have something.
Well, we figured out Neron's
app is a way to collect souls.
- That's crazy.
- Yeah, it gets crazier.
To drum up fear and increase
downloads of his app,
we think he may be planning
a monster attack.
Okay, well, we'll stall Gary,
but you got to get every single
one of those monsters
out of the Time Bureau.
I was afraid
you were gonna say that.
- Who are you talking to, Sara?
- What?
Gary! Baby, bubby, bubelah.
There's a whole big
world of problems.
You know, Neron
and your Fairy Godmother,
they're not really
your friends, but...
Do you know
who your friends are?
These guys.
Huh?
Are you trying to schmooze me?
Feels good, right?
Uh, actually,
it feels a little false.
- Gary!
- You are our friend.
I mean, would we lie
to an interim Legend?
Ah, you see, that's just it,
because I'm not
an interim Legend.
You just promised me that
to use me as bait.
- Pfft.
- You know what, Gary?
It's a little hard to feel
sorry for you
when you're holding us
all hostage.
You're not getting it.
This whole time,
Tabitha has been trying
to use me to hurt you.
All I wished
was for us to hang out.
I was trying to protect you.
I get it.
I'm not cool.
But I don't deserve
to be treated like a joke.
So, now...
now the joke's on you.
- What's he talking about?
- Oh, Fairy Godmother!
Yes, my pet?
Mick thinks he's a tough guy,
but I think he's a big baby.
And Nate, who's never been
bullied a day in his life,
welcome to my high-school years.
And, Sara and Ava,
the cool girl
and the class president,
you know what I want you
to do for me?
Dance!
Five, six, seven, eight.
Faster!
Gary, stop it!
Charlie,
I get that you're scared,
but the team is counting on us.
I'm not scared. It's just,
breaking the monsters
out of the prison
is a multiple-person job.
- You can be multiple people.
- Look, Z, yeah, I can,
for a second, and you know what?
It takes its toll.
Now, I could end up
back in prison
or even worse, dead.
- When A.R.G.U.S.
- came for my family,
my brother,
Behrad, told me to run.
And I did.
I've never forgiven myself.
You won't either.
We can't change
my family's future,
but we can save their present.
Zari Jaan, make sure
you take your shoes off
before you go in.
- I know.
- Charlie?
If I die, I'm gonna come back
and haunt you.
I would love a ghost friend.
Come on.
Cool.
Greetings, Satan,
first of the fallen.
It's been a long time, John.
Belial.
We've been looking forward
to hearing the bunk
you're pedaling.
And Beelzebub.
Not as popular, but you were
always my personal favorite.
This is a waste of our time.
I take it you've noticed
a certain demon's stock
has been on the rise.
Neron's been doing
very well for himself.
Neron is trying to take
control of hell.
And let me assure you,
his method for collecting souls,
it won't be to sign
on the dotted line in blood.
He's, uh, young,
by your standards at least.
And let's just say,
he means to disrupt the system.
If we interfere with Neron,
we'll look weak.
Well, that's precisely
where I come in, Bubby.
And what do you want
in exchange?
Not your own soul, I hope.
I'm here for the soul
of Raymond Palmer.
You let us two leave hell,
and I pledge to you
that I will dedicate all
of my crafty, wicked ways
to thwarting Neron
and securing your reign.
Are you really here
for Raymond Palmer?
We thought there was another...
A young girl whose life
you destroyed.
Astra.
Yeah, well, you know,
I didn't want to be too greedy.
But, yeah, I'll take them both.
Both of them?
That is greedy.
But if you were to choose,
well, then
that's a different matter.
John, help me.
John, you're here. You got
to get me back to Earth.
- Please, John.
- They're hurting me.
Make up your mind, John.
This offer won't last.
John?
- Astra?
- It's following me!
Make it go away!
Come here, I've got you.
You can't have her!
You can't save her.
- You can't have her!
John, get me out of here!
I'm sorry.
I choose...
Astra Logue.
Stick to the plan, Charlie.
You mean the plan
where I need to rely
on my shoddy shape-shifting
to portal creatures one by one
out of their cells
and on to the Waverider,
where Gary may or may not
wish them to Kingdom Come?
Yep, that plan.
This isn't you, Gary.
Why are you being so cruel?
Please!
Stop! You're killing them!
I don't do mime, dearie.
- Just stop!
- Everything!
As you wish...
- Ooh.
- Ugh.
Huh.
- Mona?
- Hey, wake up.
Hey, Nora.
Hey.
Oh, you're still here.
I'm book club forever.
Book club forever.
Oh, Fairy Godmother!
Uh, I have to pop off
for a second, Gary.
I thought we were going to
play Settlers of Catan later.
Don't be silly.
We're not friends.
Oh.
I am so sorry, Gary.
I took you for granted.
I never,
ever should have let you
do my dry cleaning
or work overtime without pay.
I mean, that's illegal anyway.
I'm so sorry.
I still want to kill you.
Gary, when Rip first
recruited the Legends,
he picked the people
that were insignificant
to history...
the original losers.
You don't have to be cool
to be a Legend.
And maybe we forgot that
somewhere along the way, but...
- you are one of us.
- Now, come on, Gary.
Ray and Constantine are both
stuck in hell,
and you can help them.
Just use your Fairy Godmother
powers for good.
Save her.
Sadly, my hands are tied.
But if you become Mona's
Fairy Godmother,
she could wish to be healed.
How do I do that?
If another witch
takes the wand...
You'll take my curse...
but with it, all of my power.
Nora.
Nora, no.
No...
Oh, it worked.
Quick, Mona.
Make a wish.
Wow.
Uh, Fairy God-Nora,
I wish to be safe
on the Waverider.
Oh, how I've missed me.
Sadly for you,
when you took on the wand's
power and responsibility,
you also took on its charge.
- Gary?
- I'm afraid so.
Fairy Godmothers are prisoners.
Their magic is dependent
on whiny humans
and their petty demands.
You lied.
Obviously.
Toodles.
Excuse me.
- Oh. Marilyn Monroe?
- Why, yes.
I seem to have
gotten a little lost.
Can you help me get back home?
Of course, ma'am.
Let me just program in a year.
- Ah. Yeah.
- Uh...
Thank you, sir.
- Oh, my love!
- My love.
Uh, still no luck with Nora?
- No.
- Oh.
Well, she'll take
your curse soon.
After all,
you are very convincing.
Well, I better head back.
Evil deeds to do and all that.
No.
Well, that was bloody close.
I'm at the first cell.
Anytime now, Z.
Okay, just give me one second.
The public doesn't always
know what's best for them.
So tonight we will release
the Minotaur
and scare them into accepting
our protection.
It is done, mon amour.
How do I look?
But you were just...
Oh, the shape-shifter.
Can someone sound the alarm?
Charlie, Tabitha and Neron
are onto you.
Yeah, I figured.
You need to get out now.
Open all the doors,
turn off the force fields.
I'm not leaving.
Are you waiting
for an invitation?
It's a bloody jailbreak!
I mean, there are pros
to trusting your apologies
are sincere, and cons.
Maybe I'll make a list.
Gary... Gary,
just go with your heart.
Oh, Fairy Godmother!
- Nora.
- Oh...
Go find John and help him
rescue Ray from hell.
Oh, fiddlesticks.
- Wait, wait!
- Gary!
Gary, you dick!
Oh.
- Come on, you lot.
- Get a move on.
You don't have to tell me twice.
Faster, sassy!
You're all right, little one.
Oi, ogre.
Catch!
Charlie, you're out of time.
- Z, get out of here.
- See you on the other side.
I'm going after Mona.
Mona.
Come on, my love.
Let's get you out of here.
- Ugh. I hate shape-shifters.
- Break her neck.
Patience, mon amour.
Get Mona.
No!
Looks like things ain't going
so well for you, Neron.
You wanted a monster
to attack D.C.
Now we have every single
monster...
in one.
You promised me
you'd take me to see Astra.
Patience, John.
I made a pledge to you,
and I expect you
to keep your end of the bargain.
What the hell
are you playing at?
John?
John, is it really you?
- Yes.
- Yes, Astra, love.
It's me.
It's me. This is Johnny.
Thank God...
God? You know better
than to thank Him.
Astra?
John is here to take you
back to Earth.
You're welcome to go.
- Yeah. It's all right, love.
- It's me.
No.
Wait.
Hold on.
What do you mean no?
Looks like the deal
is null and void.
Neron is a thorn
in our side, John,
but torturing you...
is too much fun.
John?
It's following me.
Make it go away!
Please!
John, het me out of here!
Astra, love.
- This isn't you.
- Oh, of course it is.
Or would you rather I stayed
that terrified little girl,
crying and waiting
for you to come and rescue me?
I would have been waiting
a long time.
I am so, so sorry, love, but...
this place, it's twisted you.
If anything...
it's made me more like you.
Right, John?
You're not like me.
You're not.
You chose wrong.
You should have saved
your friend.
- Hey, watch it!
- Back off, freak!
It's like a demented Noah's Ark.
What about Charlie?
It's my fault.
I'm the one that convinced her
to risk everything.
Hey, don't go down that road.
We'll do what we always do.
Yeah, forming stupid Beebos.
Hey, where are you going?
Well, after everything,
I just figured
you wouldn't want to
have me around anymore.
It's all hands on deck, Gary.
Yeah.
We're gonna need all our
friends to defeat Neron.
Aye, aye.
You all right?
Not really.
I'm glad you
and Wicksty are okay.
What happened?
Oh, my God.
Hi.
My name is Zari.
Greg, move your head.