PROFESSOR STEIN:
Time travel is real,
and all of history
is vulnerable to attack,
which is why we must travel
through time to stop the spread of
these so-called Time Aberrations
and to erase their damage to history.
We are a team of outcasts and misfits,
so please don't call us heroes,
we're legends.
PROFESSOR STEIN:
Previously, on Legends of Tomorrow...
Thank you, Mister...
Hex. Jonah Hex.
Temporal Aberrations cause these things
called timequakes.
If there was a way
of locating their epicenters,
maybe we'll be able to fix the Aberrations
before they happen.
Hello there, wanderer.
Don't see many folks around here.
Been a while since this old mine turned up
anything worth taking.
Then I guess I'll be on my way.
And let you be on yours.
Oh, ain't you heard?
I'm the one
that does the letting around here.
- Or do you need a reminder?
- Wait.
I know things about these mines.
Things I can't tell you if I'm shot.
Oh, you'll tell me,
or I'll shoot you otherwise.
Now lower that iron and start talkin'.
The ore in there, it's rare and powerful.
More powerful than gold.
And how would you be the one to know that?
I can show you.
With your permission.
Found it using this.
There's enough in that mine
for the both of us.
We're the only ones who know.
We could be like partners.
Hmm. Give it here.
Nice doing business with you, partner.
What's with bad guys and ancient amulets?
Any idea why Darhk wants this?
All I know is it's never a good idea
when your nemesis starts accessorizing.
- And he's teamed up with a speedster.
- What's a speedster?
Someone with super speed.
It's how Darhk escaped.
The energy of the Speed Force
grants the speedster
chronokinesis, temporal manipulation.
English, Professor.
It means that his running real fast
lets him time travel.
I'll be in my room.
Martin, I need you to gather
everything you can on speedsters.
And Nate's right.
This amulet looks a lot
like the one we recovered off the Nazis.
- There's got to be a connection.
- Let me guess.
I'm on library duty.
JAX: We're dealing with a speedster here.
How long are we gonna
keep this secret from them, Grey?
Come on, future Barry's message.
Yes, I know what
you're talking about, Jefferson.
And we have been through this.
Barry implored us not to share any...
You okay?
I'm fine, it's just a headache.
You would tell me
if something was up, right?
'Cause if we start keeping things
from each other...
I just need to rest.
Saving history can be
extremely wearing on the body.
I'm thinking this amulet dates back
to Late Antiquity
and is Judeo-Christian in origin.
Great.
Is that great?
Well, I can't find
a reference of it anywhere.
Like, none.
Historically speaking, this doesn't exist.
Well, this is right in front of us,
so I'd say it does exist.
And we know that Damien Darhk
and this speedster
are willing to kill for it.
SARA: Sounds like you got
some more homework to do.
- What?
- I just thought becoming a superhero,
I would spend less time in the library
than my old job, that's all.
RAY: Well, research skills
are a kind of super power.
And you can turn to steel, so you got two.
Saved by an Aberration.
Ooh, what's the Trouble Alert say?
Look, I told you, don't call it that.
The timequake's epicenter
is Liberty, Colorado, 1874.
Ha! Back to the Wild West.
You guys were in the Old West?
Yeah. Town made me sheriff.
That's cool.
All right, well,
I will go tell Jax and Stein.
Who wants to tell Rory?
- Not it.
What?
Okay. I'll do it.
I don't know how to use 'em,
but I'm wearing spurs.
I remember my first time in the Wild West.
I drove a real-life desperado out of town.
- That's cool. Mmm-hmm.
- And that was my hat, thanks.
Hmm.
That's cool.
RAY: What's this?
Oh, uh, that's nothing, don't open it.
You don't have to open...
You opened it.
RAY: Did you draw
your own superhero costume?
No. Absolutely not.
Yeah, I did.
And I only did because when I steel up,
my clothes stretch out
and they fit all weird.
And besides, don't I deserve a suit?
I mean, am I just the research guy here?
Look, I know what it's like
to be a rookie.
Just, uh, follow my lead
and you'll be fine out there.
Well, I know a few things
about the Old West.
Like, for instance...
Nobody says "Howdy."
- Uh-huh.
- And you know how to ride a horse, right?
- Yeah, I can figure it out.
- Ah.
This loaded?
Yes, it is.
- Ooh.
- Yeah.
DR. HEYWOOD: Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Guys, I think my horse is broken.
Where's the professor?
Uh, he's feeling a little off.
More whiskey for me.
MAN: Yee-haw!
Sounds like a commotion of some kind.
Hold back, let's get a better look.
HEAD BANDIT: Look at him up there, boys.
Oh! It's a hanging.
Is that Hex?
You know that man?
We gotta help him.
Well, we gotta take his crew out first.
- They look armed.
- Don't worry, guys.
I got this.
What?
Well, well, well, you look a lot less mean
with that noose around your neck,
don't you, Hex?
You think this is finished?
Looking pretty finished to me,
don't you think, boys, huh?
You son of a bitch!
You might wanna slow down there.
Because these here parts
ain't big enough for the...
Five of us.
- Who the hell are you?
- What he said.
HEAD BANDIT: On second thought,
I don't give a damn!
Hold still, Hex.
Nice shot.
DR. HEYWOOD:
Now you get on that horse
and you ride till you feel like
you can't ride any further,
then you ride some more. Now, go on, get.
Go on. Whoo!
Face.
What?
Nothin'.
Oh, hell.
They're back.
Saved by a filly.
Ain't that the damnedest.
A simple thank you would suffice.
How'd you know I needed savin'?
Because we got an alert
that history was being changed,
and the coordinates lead us
to your hanging.
Well, I guess it's nice
to know that I matter.
Leaving already?
I didn't get to shoot anyone.
I need a drink.
Where's Rip?
He's MIA.
Damn.
How the hell do you miscreants manage
not to get yourselves killed without him?
Ms. Lance has been serving as captain.
But she's a lady.
You are a lady, right?
You know I could take your life
just as easily as I saved it.
Ooh. Fiery.
Whoever breaks her is in for a wild ride.
Too bad this filly is into other fillies.
Mmm. You don't say.
So, how did you end up in the noose?
I was collecting a bounty on a pissant
by the name of Quentin Turnbull.
- As in Turnbull Country?
- Never heard of it.
That's because it's not supposed to exist.
This book has changed
since the last time I saw it.
- Check this out. Gideon.
- GIDEON: Right away.
That's a map of the United States
from 1876.
SARA: All right, who's Turnbull?
Two-bit, yellow-bellied cattle rustler.
Who controls all the land
west of the Rocky Mountains.
Looks like we found our Aberration.
Am I supposed to have the faintest idea
what the hell this means?
It means that we need to stop Turnbull
from taking over the West.
Looks like you got yourself
a posse, partner.
JAX: Where is everybody?
JONAH: Ever since Turnbull set up shop
six months ago,
everyone's been run out of town
or made to work in the mine.
Mine? What kind of mine? Gold?
JONAH: Hell if I know.
Nobody's been mining for gold
in these parts for half a century.
Listen to me. "These parts."
I sound like I'm a cowboy.
He's pulling something outta the ground
that's making him rich.
Turnbull also owns this saloon.
The hotel, the laundry and the whorehouse.
The answer's no, Mick.
Turnbull's got an office above the saloon.
He's also got about a dozen men
making sure nobody gets close to him.
I think I know how we can.
Mick.
Why don't you mosey on in there?
Have yourself a good time.
If you insist.
Not sure I understand your plan.
You just set a match to a powder keg.
And if Turnbull doesn't want
his saloon to burn down,
then he's going to have to
come out of his office and deal with it.
Better yet, get your boy
to get in a fight with Turnbull
and bring him out here on the street.
Amaya, your job is to make sure
Rory keeps his pistol in his pants
until he's outside the saloon.
Clearly, I drew the short straw.
So, what you want us to do?
Reckon I can post up nearby
with a long gun.
- Are you chewing tobacco?
- Mm. Tootsie Roll.
Get rid of your hats and your guns.
What? I thought we were supposed to be
some badass cowboys.
You guys wanna know how
Turnbull went from being a cattle rustler
to running his own country?
I'm gonna need you
to infiltrate his base of operations.
As what?
Y'all are tax collectors?
We're here to go over your books
and make sure everything's in order.
And we're in a bit of a hurry, so, uh...
Yes, we're on the next train
back to Washington, D.C.
Well, there ain't no train to Washington.
The pass won't be open till spring.
He means mule train.
- Mmm-hmm.
- This guy.
How'd I go from desperado to accountant?
Well, at least Mick's having fun.
Stuck here doing research
while everyone else is out drinking.
It's like high school all over again.
Shot.
Make it two.
You're with him?
Unfortunately.
Guys, I think I found something.
According to this ledger,
Turnbull is stockpiling some kind of ore
in a nearby mining camp.
And you are?
I work for Mr. Turnbull.
Who are you?
My friends and I are with
the Internal Revenue...
Uh, Mr. Turnbull don't like no taxmen.
Well, nobody likes paying taxes,
but they are an essential part
of the federal government's...
Mr. Turnbull don't like
the federal government neither.
Is that why
he's trying to start his own country?
Well, now, see, Why'd you have to go
and say something like that?
Now I got to pump some lead into you,
so you don't go blabbing
to the wrong person.
Hey, hey, would you shoot an unarmed man?
I think that's a yes.
So, what's your history with Turnbull?
JONAH: Come again?
Well, you said that you had
dealings over the years.
I can tell a vendetta when I see one.
I'm kind of an expert
when it comes to revenge.
Is this what it's like
working with a woman?
You just sit around
and talk about your feelings.
Well, if your feelings
are what almost got you hung, then yeah,
I'd say they are worth talking about.
Not in my century.
DR. HEYWOOD: Now that we've got
outlaw outfits, it's time to
find out what Turnbull's stockpiling
at his mining camp.
Or we can do the responsible thing
and head back to the ship
with the rest of the team.
You're joking, right?
Time to cowboy up.
Ah!
- Another blackjack.
- Must be my lucky day.
- You're cheating.
- I'm winning.
Sweetheart, that's for you.
I'll see you around.
Piano man, play something else.
I've had more fun at a funeral.
Bartender!
And who might you be?
Name's Turnbull.
Never heard of him.
That's my name on the sign
in front of the saloon.
Or can't you read?
So, it's your money I'm winning.
Well, that's interesting.
I'd say your luck has run out, partner.
You just going to stand there
and make threats?
Or are you gonna back it up?
SARA: Amaya, what's going on in there?
You wanted Rory to start a fight?
I'd say your plan's working.
JAX: Man, these clothes smell like ass.
People didn't wash in the Wild, Wild West?
RAY: Well, we're criminals, remember?
It's important to smell the part.
DR. HEYWOOD:
Game faces, boys. We got company.
I don't recognize you three.
That's probably 'cause of
our new bandanas.
This one off his rocker?
RAY: You could blow his brains out.
Only he doesn't got any.
DR. HEYWOOD: Nice work.
Gideon, let's run
the neuro-imaging scan again.
There must be something you missed.
GIDEON: The odds that I misdiagnosed
your condition are infinitesimally thin.
The algorithm programmed
into my medical diagnostics system...
Please just do it.
As you wish, Professor.
Biometric scan reveals all brain functions
are within normal parameters.
Physiologically,
there's nothing wrong with you.
Are you implying that my symptoms
are psychosomatic? Because...
Please.
I need you to run the tests again.
- Oh, my God.
- What is it?
It's dwarf star.
One of the rarest minerals
in the universe.
How does this help Turnbull
take over the West?
I used dwarf star to power the Atom suit.
The piece I had
was the size of your little finger.
There's enough potential energy here
to power the entire Wild West.
Or blow it up.
Question is,
how does Turnbull even know what it is?
I bet you
this has something to do with it.
It's some sort of tracker,
definitely not from the 1800s.
Probably stole it from a time pirate.
- We got to get this out of here.
- Yeah.
Oh.
I should have mentioned it's also
the densest material in the universe.
Let's get the rest of the team.
Amaya, it's been forever.
What the hell is going on in there?
The plan's caught something of a snag.
Explain.
Well, it's hard to.
But Mr. Rory and Mr. Turnbull...
like each other.
SARA: What? What happened
to Rory starting a fight?
I think it's more likely that him
and Turnbull get matching tattoos.
Then they told me to put my hands up,
and my pants fell down
because of all the loot I was carrying.
You see, that's what them damn fools
in government back in Washington
don't understand,
that men like you and me,
we wasn't meant to live in cages.
Hell, that's why our forbearers
busted away from England to begin with,
so we could be free.
And that's what Turnbull Country
is all about.
It's about keeping the Wild West wild.
I'll drink to that.
Hey, have some of that.
Are you gonna sit around
while those two bend elbows?
- What are you doing?
- I'm gonna collect my bounty.
Whether you like it or not.
Stick to the plan, Jonah.
Your guy on the inside
ain't sticking to no plan.
Why the hell should I?
AMAYA: Sara? What do you want me to do?
Brace yourself.
Turnbull!
Well, if it ain't
the great Jonah Hex himself.
Whoo! You've got quite a pair
to walk into my establishment like this.
You're like a cockroach, hard to kill.
I'm taking you in,
alive or dead.
Your choice.
I choose dead.
Actually, Jonah...
I'm glad you decided
to pay me this little visit.
You see, I've been...
working on a little something.
It seems that ore that I discovered,
well, it's got special qualities.
Let's party!
Come on!
Why do you guys get to have all the fun?
We just got back from Turnbull's mine.
Reason for the Aberration?
He's digging up dwarf star.
Get back to the ship.
That's right, run,
you yellow-bellied cowards!
Finally some excitement.
Mick, no!
And here I thought you and me
was gonna be friends.
I don't have friends.
- AMAYA: Nate? Nate, are you okay?
- Yeah.
- I'm the man of steel, remember?
- Oh, my God.
Gideon, prepare to run diagnostics.
What's to run? I've been shot.
GIDEON: The bullet has lodged itself
between several of
Dr. Heywood's internal organs.
How's that possible? He's made of steel.
SARA: Because it wasn't a normal bullet.
It was dwarf star.
GIDEON: I estimate
his chance of survival at 51%.
Would it kill you to say,
"Better than average," Gideon?
We had a plan. You went off book.
Now, you're gonna cut the crap
and tell me what the hell is going on
between you and Turnbull.
I don't answer to you, Ms. Lance.
It's Captain Lance.
And if you did answer to me,
Nate wouldn't have gotten shot.
Now, I know you don't like
taking orders from a woman.
But you're gonna like getting
your ass kicked by one even less.
I've been after Turnbull
for eight years now.
I almost got him twice.
He wants to see me pushing up daisies
just as bad
as I want to see him do the same.
Because of what?
There's a town in Oklahoma.
Goes by the name of Calvert.
Turnbull and his men were harassing it.
They hired me to fight back.
Calvert. That's the town
that Rip left in the lurch.
My little rebellion made other towns think
they didn't need to pay protection money
to Turnbull and his gang.
So, one night,
Turnbull gathered every man,
woman and child in Calvert.
Locked us in a church, set it on fire.
Somehow, I escaped.
The Lord saw fit
to leave me with this souvenir.
What the hell am I telling
a woman this for?
You'd never understand.
Wrong.
Like I said, vendetta is kind of my thing.
I've got a Turnbull,
and he's still out there.
Well, here you are with a Timeship.
Been there, tried that.
Killing Darhk would create
ripples in history that I can't control.
But there are things that I can control.
I can help you capture Turnbull.
Even though I screwed up?
Been there, too.
I'm starting to think that screwing up
is just an essential part of surviving.
So, how's your headache?
Oh, it's fine.
Nothing a little aspirin couldn't help.
Funny, that's not what Gideon told me.
What's going on?
And don't lie
because you know I can always tell.
All right, while you were away,
I had a vision.
A vision? Like a hallucination?
It's possible it could merely be
a side effect from multiple time jumps.
Whoa. Grey. Grey.
JAX: Grey?
That is not a reaction to time travel.
What did you just see?
A woman.
Someone I've never met, but her face,
it keeps flashing in my mind,
like I'm having memories of a stranger,
but she's not really a stranger.
I haven't the slightest notion why.
Trying to work out your frustration?
Something like that.
What happened out there today?
You lost control.
Says you.
That man back in town, the drinker,
the gambler, the animal
that wants to watch the whole world burn,
that's the real me.
I happen to know a thing or two
about animals.
They're not vicious by nature
unless they're attacked.
If you're trying to tell me
to tell you some sob story
about how horrible
and painful my life is, forget it.
I'm no victim.
Sara's told me all the things
that you've done for this team.
And you don't sound like an animal
who just wants to watch the world burn.
They like to pretend I'm part of the team,
that they have me on a leash.
No.
Hmm?
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Some superhero.
Maybe I am better suited for the library.
Ow.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
You had no idea that Turnbull
laced the bullets with dwarf star
or that you're even vulnerable to it.
When I was a kid,
there was this bully, Shane Blocklin.
And one day, I decided
I'm going to stand up to little Shane.
Long story short,
he breaks my nose in two places.
But from that point on, I was, uh...
I was different.
I was afraid.
And then I meet you guys,
and I get these superpowers
and I say to myself,
"Nate, you don't have
to feel afraid again."
Well, maybe now you know how I felt
after you destroyed my Atom suit.
When we were out fighting with the Shogun,
without my suit, I was afraid.
Well, you hid it well.
It's because I realized that weakness
or not being invulnerable
is what makes me a hero.
There's no bravery without fear.
That was a really good
inspirationalspeech.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
Well, I have a few other aphorisms
in my back pocket.
Like, uh, "Courage is the mastery of fear,
not the absence of fear."
Strength is...
You know what, buddy? You nailed it.
Sorry. Got a little carried away
with my train of...
That's it!
I think I know how
Turnbull's gonna make his own country.
When I saw how much dwarf star ore
he had in that mine, I started to wonder,
how could he transport
such a heavy shipment?
- He'd have to use...
- The railroad.
The railroad.
Okay. Get to the part where we care, Ray.
I think he's gonna use the railroad
and the dwarf star to... Wait for it.
I don't want to wait for it.
Close Summit Pass.
- DR. HEYWOOD: Oh, my God, Ray is right.
- Thank you.
Summit Pass connects east and west
via railroad.
But not if Turnbull uses this magic...
- Dwarf star?
- Yeah, to blow the thing up.
Well, if he destroys the pass,
there's no way of transporting
soldiers and supplies from the East Coast.
The US Army is effectively
locked out of the West.
So, it's simple.
We just stop Turnbull
from blowing up the pass.
SARA: Yeah, it's simple.
You don't have a suit,
you just had invasive surgery,
Stein's out of commission.
We'll think of something.
"Courage is the mastery of fear,
not the absence of it."
Yeah. What about Turnbull?
That train goes boom,
he's not gonna be on it.
I overheard one of his people saying
Turnbull just called
for a meeting at his mine.
You, Jax, and Ray stop the train.
The rest of us, we'll deal with Turnbull.
You sure about this?
Of course.
This isn't my first rodeo.
I wanted to say that.
RAY: There's our train.
Loaded with enough dwarf star
to punch a hole in the mountain
and cut off the pass to the east.
How do we stop a moving locomotive?
We don't.
I do.
I think.
- So, what do you think?
- I think I liked him.
There's three of them for every one of us.
Hex and I will draw their attention
while you two go make sure
Turnbull can't pull any more dwarf star
out of the ground.
We'll need about five minutes
to plant enough dynamite to seal the mine.
About time we got to light something up.
Just light the fuse and run,
don't stick around for the fireworks.
Yeah, yeah.
All right, I got a plan
to get us close to Turnbull.
You ready to follow my orders this time?
Aye, aye, Captain.
- Good. Now put these on.
- Hmm.
Quentin Turnbull.
Who's asking?
I heard you're looking for someone.
Jonah Hex.
Well, hell, looks like I'm gonna
have to kill you for the third time.
I'm impressed, boy.
Jonah, Jonah, Jonah.
Back in the belly of the whale.
The lily-livered whale
who kills women and children.
Oh, no, that was before. I've changed.
I got purpose now.
Matter of fact,
why don't I show you what I'm working on
so you know why you died.
You come along too, boy.
Anyone who can bring in Hex
always got a place on my crew.
Nate, what are you doing, man?
- Hold on.
- Keep your distance.
JAX: What are you going to do?
I'm going to cut 'em off at the pass.
I've always wanted to say that.
RAY: You can't get in front
of a moving train.
You said it yourself,
there's no bravery without fear.
Which is good
because I am scared as hell right now.
Yah!
TURNBULL: Colt Single Action Army,
the gun that won the West.
Some folks like to call it The Peacemaker.
Only I don't much care for peace.
Yeah, thanks to what I pulled out
of this mine,
I got my own weapon now.
Something that's gonna tip the scales.
Win the West back
for the folks it belongs to,
the outlaws.
- Okay. I'm in position.
- RAY: And out of your mind.
JAX: You couldn't even stop
a bullet made with that stuff.
That train is loaded with dwarf star, man.
You guys aren't helping.
You've got a whole minute
to get out of here.
You mean we have a minute?
That's what I meant.
Should we tell them about the minute?
- No.
- Good.
I was hoping you were going to say that.
Who's next?
Mick, we gotta go.
Mick, now.
Put the animal away.
Okay.
Hell, those bullets ain't nothing.
Wait till you see what I got now.
Now, get on in there.
You ain't no man!
You burned down Calvert.
You murdered all those people.
For what?
For power?
Go on, get it over with.
Alive or dead?
Alive...
You lucky son of a bitch.
I got this. I got this. I got this.
I got this, I got this, I got this,
I got this.
DR. HEYWOOD: Did you see that?
Did you see that? Tell me you saw that.
- Yo, that was badass, dude.
- Totally badass.
- You all right?
- No.
But I stopped a train.
JAX: I think he's good.
Whoo!
I stopped the train!
RAY: Whoo!
It's a mighty fine job you did back there,
Captain.
I'll drink to that.
So, now that you have your man,
what are you going to do with him?
Turnbull? If I had my way,
he'd be in for a long, painful demise.
I'd let him bleed out from the gut.
But I'm gonna turn him over
to the authorities.
So you don't have to worry
about your Aberration.
Only territory
Turnbull's gonna be claiming
is a cold, dark prison cell.
Then our work here is done.
You do a mighty fine job
bearing a burden few men can deal with.
Good thing I'm a woman then.
Yes, ma'am.
I best get Turnbull.
Collect my bounty.
Now, you try to stay out of trouble.
Not likely.
I wouldn't imagine so.
AMAYA: It really is beautiful.
It's no wonder that human beings
have worshipped fire for millennia.
Fire gives us life,
but also has the power
to destroy everything in its path.
Your point?
Or are you gonna keep talking
in metaphors?
Yeah, I know what a metaphor is.
But don't tell them.
You were right.
The animal who wants
to watch the world burn,
that is who you are.
But it's not all that you are.
Your point?
Don't deny the animal.
But don't let it control you either.
I can help you.
Believe me,
I know a thing or two
about controlling wild beasts.
JAX: Oh! There you are.
So I've been thinking
about your memory flashes,
manopause moments
or whatever it is you want to call 'em.
I got a theory.
What if when you interacted
with your younger self in 1987, you...
Inadvertently changed my past,
so that my memories from my new life
are supplanting the memories
from my old life,
thus creating temporal dissonance.
Yeah, that's exactly what I was thinking.
That's a brilliant theory
which I happen to share with you,
but it doesn't explain...
Who the mystery lady is.
Or that I'm fairly certain.
I love her.
Man, Clarissa is gonna kill you
when you get home.
Assuming there even is a Clarissa
to go home to.
Hah!
Hey. Heard you were looking for me.
Oh, yeah. Uh, I just want to thank you
for saving all that dwarf star ore.
I have enough to power 20 Atom suits now.
That's cool, man. So, we all get one?
Actually, there's something
I've been working on
before I start building a new exo-suit.
Hmm.
It's not exactly what was in your drawing,
I made a few improvements.
- Shut the front door.
- Yeah.
I figured you earned it,
Steel.
Cool name.
Hey, you guys done broing out?
I mean, uh, not really, but...
- We can.
- Good.
Because our friends back in 2016,
they need our help.