How will we be remembered?
Will it be for saving
the world twice?
Nope! We're the team who broke time.
That's right...
History has been torn to shreds.
Which means it's up to us
to put it back together again,
piece by piece,
fixing these so called anachronisms
before we get torn to shreds.
So please, don't call us heroes.
We're legends.
Previously on Legends Of Tomorrow...
I told you I was leaving to create
an organization to replace
the Time Masters.
- Fifteen minutes ago!
- For you.
Forming the Time Bureau's been
the work of the last five
years of my life.
They're undependable,
unpredictable. Dangerous.
My decision to leave
had nothing to do with you.
I could feel myself losing control.
The animal was in charge, not me.
Tel me what we're facing here.
That information is a need-to-know.
Welcome back, Kuasa.
This is A.R.G.U.S.
Anti-meta-human curfew is in effect.
Citizens, please stay in your homes.
HQ, this is transport
X-one-seven.
En route to facility.
Copy,
X-one-seven.
Standing by to receive prisoner.
What the hell?
Code 99.
We have a Code 99!
So there's this theory
that the phrase,
"bring home the bacon,"
started in a town in Old England.
Bacon was awarded to any man
who can truthfully say
he and his wife had
not argued that past year.
Same cannot be said
of you and Ms. Jiwe, however.
No, because I'm eating bacon.
- But since you asked...
- I didn't.
It is a little awkward.
I mean, I am a little resentful...
Please. If you need to discuss
this with someone, I would suggest...
- Amaya.
- Yeah, I know.
We should talk things out, but...
Amaya.
Acute arachnoid somnambulism...
This really is fascinating!
Oh, my God.
She's having a dream she's a spider.
We got to wake her up
before she crawls into the engine.
Amaya!
You're not supposed to wake
a sleepwalker,
especially when they're
stuck to the ceiling!
Why not? Amaya!
That's why.
Are you okay?
I... I was having a nightmare.
And in the process, summoned the
ashe of a spider. Astonishing.
No, Martin, it isn't.
What if I summoned a rhino and I
crashed through the hull of the ship?
Or a lion and I mauled someone?
Well, if the victim was Mr. Rory,
I imagine...
It's gonna be okay.
We're going to figure out what's
going on with you and your totem.
What do you think I've been trying
to do for the past six months?
In my experience, there is no problem
that cannot be solved by the rigorous
application of science.
It's a mystical totem, Martin.
I believe
we should start in the Med Bay.
Please, please, come with me.
Come with me.
Code 99.
This is Agent Gary Green.
Seattle, Washington, 2042.
I just witnessed a female meta
of unknown origin.
- She killed everyone.
- Hey.
What's going on?
We intercepted a distress call from
one of Rip's Time Bureau agents.
Why? Actually, forget it.
- I don't care.
- It's the dweeby one, Gary.
Still don't care.
Yeah. I got to go with Mick
on this one.
Why should we help those ass clowns?
I mean, that's not our job.
Hopefully that little time dweeb
learns his lesson.
Agreed. But the last time I checked,
we help people who are in trouble.
I don't.
Something feels off
about this place.
Yeah. Like, where is everybody?
Martial law. It's a police state.
- How do you know?
- I can smell pigs.
He's right. All the cars on the
street are military.
More pigs. Get down! Get down!
It's A.R.G.U.S. A covert paramilitary
organization.
Yeah, but, it seems
they've forgotten how to be covert.
The signal we intercepted
came from over there.
Right. Should be here somewhere.
Gary? Gary!
- Gary!
- Oh, no, she's going to kill me.
- The chick from your distress call?
- Agent Sharpe.
She hates you guys.
Well, feeling's mutual.
Look, you said there was a female
meta killing everyone.
What's going on?
Well, this is classified
Time Bureau business.
Open your mouth and say some words.
I guess you're gonna have
to decide who you're more afraid of,
Agent Sharpe or Mick here?
Uh...
The Bureau got a ping
on some unregulated time travel.
But when I got here, the person
I was supposed to arrest...
Was a meta-human
who had no problem murdering people?
Her powers let her control water.
A human squirt-gun? Big deal.
No, you guys really have no idea
how dangerous this woman is.
Dweeb's right.
That chick's dangerous.
She just blew through those pigs
like it was nothing.
I actually fought someone with water
powers like this a few years ago.
It was not very pleasant.
But why would
a time-traveling meta-human
come to 2042 to kill a bunch of
A.R.G.U.S. agents?
She didn't.
She came here to kill their prisoner.
Well, looks like she struck out.
Something tells me our assassin
doesn't give up so easily.
- You got a plan, Captain?
- Why?
We saved Four-Eyes,
mission accomplished.
And "Four-Eyes'" mission was to
prevent the anachronism.
You mean, stop the water witch
before she kills whoever
was in the back of that truck.
Gideon, scan A.R.G.U.S.'s logs,
see if you can ID the prisoner.
I can do
better than that, Captain.
I can project the prisoner's
most likely destination.
Even better.
UNITE - A.R.G.U.S. MAINTENANCE
LAW IS ORDER - ENLIST
Zari Tomaz?
Come with us if you want to live.
Yeah. Used that one once.
Come on. Let's get out of here.
Yeah. I don't know who you are
or what you're doing,
but you're gonna lead
A.R.G.U.S. right here.
Don't worry. We can protect you.
Who's going to protect you?
This is A.R.G.U.S.
Sara Lance, Nathaniel Heywood,
Raymond Palmer, and Mick Rory...
You are listed in the Meta-human
Registry as missing.
You are hereby under arrest for
violating the Anti Meta-human Act.
Anti-Meta-human?
Yeah, meta-humans have been illegal
since 2021.
- Didn't you guys get the memo?
- No.
ARREST MODE
ANTI-METAHUMAN ACT VIOLATION
Well, nice to meet you. I'm out.
Wait, your life is still in danger.
- Remain where you are.
- Ditto. Bye.
Detainment units have been notified.
Hate to destroy futuristic
technology, but...
Stand down!
Don't move.
You are surrounded.
Come to the right. Move.
Under the Meta-human Act
of 2021, you are under arrest.
On the ground. Hands behind your
head. Final warning.
Do as they say.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- That's an order.
I don't suppose I
get to call my lawyer.
- What?
- I wanted to shoot someone.
All right,
let's get back to the Waverider,
see if we can get a line on Tomaz.
Why?
I'm pretty sure she just told us
to screw off.
That doesn't change the fact that
there's a rogue time traveler
- trying to kill her.
- I can see why.
Let's go.
There's nothing to worry about.
Gideon can't find anything
medically wrong with you.
I told you, Martin. My problem is
mystical, it's not scientific.
Believe me, mysticism
is merely science
that hasn't been understood yet.
Hey. Did you figure out what's wrong
with her?
- I'm sitting right here, Nathaniel.
- I suggest we consider
a new battery of tests.
I don't think that's...
To check on an
overactive hippocampus.
Latent chromosomal imbalance,
not to mention temporal dysplasia.
I asked Jax to adjust
Gideon's diagnostic algorithms...
There's no "algorithm" for what's
wrong with me.
It's my totem.
It's the legacy of my ancestors.
Great.
So let's go talk to your ancestors.
We're on a time ship.
This totem means
I protect my village,
not mess with its history.
What's her problem?
Side effect of temporal dysplasia,
I suspect.
Hey. How you feeling?
Like I just understood what you
meant by the term "mansplaining."
I take it
from Nathaniel's premature return,
you didn't have
much luck with Ms. Tomaz?
That was interesting.
Turns out, Zari's a bit of a...
Not very nice person.
Apparently it's illegal
to be a meta-human in 2042.
You know what I don't get? A.R.G.U.S.
- In 2016 they weren't...
- Idiots.
Well, I was gonna say
"They weren't
"trying to control the city
with killer drones," but...
Any authoritarian organization
always goes bad. Always.
Which means it's only a matter of
time before Rip and his Time Bureau
turn into the Time Gestapo.
In case you've forgotten,
the Time Bureau only exists
to clean up your time mess!
Which now includes an at-large
time-assassin and a fugitive hacker.
Is that your way of thanking us
for rescuing you?
Gideon, do we have a location
on Zari yet?
Negative, Captain.
I'm afraid Ms. Tomaz has stepped up
her efforts to remain undetected.
Damn, I can see why.
Look at this rap sheet.
Burglary, larceny, grand larceny,
identity theft,
trespassing, digital trespassing,
meta-human smuggling, conspiracy...
Impressive.
Multiple religious infractions...
- What do you mean?
- Zari is Muslim.
And apparently religion is illegal
in 2042.
Rory, if you had this much heat
on you, where would you go?
My bar.
What have they done to my bar?
Too much, Ray. Too much.
What? I look like
I just robbed a bank.
Or a costume store.
There she is.
You run, scream or sic one of those
drones on us, I'll light you up.
You got that, missy?
- Are you guys stalking me?
- Not me.
But for some reason
my boss has a bee in her bonnet
about protecting you
from that, uh, water bitch.
Not you, sweetheart.
Yeah, I can take care of myself.
Is that right?
That why your're in this bar
looking to hire muscle?
Look, you can trust us, okay?
We're the good guys.
Uh...
Don't be fooled by our disguises.
- Good guy
- It's her.
Let's get out of here.
Come on.
Ah. A pool party.
Cute tricks.
Get her to the ship.
You guys have a ship?
Is it a big ship?
How about a diversion, Rory?
Who wants to fight?
Go!
Okay, this is almost amazing.
What do you mean "almost"?
Don't worry, you'll be safe here.
- Who's the woman that's after you?
- No idea.
Any idea why someone would want to
kill you?
Yeah. I can think of quite a few,
actually.
Look. If we're going to help you,
you need to start
being more straightforward.
What is she doing here?
Uh, water woman was trying
to kill her, so we're protecting her.
This is technology you are not
allowed to see.
Civilians are not
allowed to know about time travel!
You guys are time travelers?
- Nice one, Gary.
- Okay. That's on me.
Uh, but still, our job
is to prevent the anachronism,
which means capturing the assassin,
not the target!
I can't believe it...
You guys are
time-traveling superheroes?
Yeah. We've actually
saved the world. Twice.
Not that we're counting.
Really? You saved the world?
- Twice?
- Then why does it still suck?
Uh, just for the record, dealing with
that messed-up police state of yours,
that's on our to-do list, so...
But after we capture the
person trying to kill you.
And we need your help to do it.
Oh. I get it.
Since you have no way
of tracking this water psycho,
you plan to use me as bait, right?
- Right.
- Okay, I'll help you.
On one condition.
You help me break my brother
out of the A.R.G.U.S. facility
where they're holding him.
Prison break?
- I'm in.
- No, no, no.
They're not helping you
because they're still helping me.
Guys, this mission has
gone way off the rails as it is.
Zari's brother is not the priority.
If you really want my help,
then that's my price.
Guess we're breaking into
an A.R.G.U.S. prison.
Okay. So I've been doing
some research.
Turns out there is a root
from your region of Zambesi
that's known for its
spiritual healing properties.
- The Layoga root.
- That's the one.
It's a powerful hallucinogen.
Yes, and people use it to go on
vision quests.
Oh. So you admit that my problem
might be mystical in nature?
Well, if you say it's
mystical, then it's mystical.
Anyways, I was having a chat
with Gideon
and it turns out our favorite
talking super computer...
Uh, is really great at synthesizing
pretty much anything.
No.
Please tell me you didn't.
We recreated the Lyoga root
extract right here on the ship.
I mean, Gideon did most of the work.
I pushed some buttons.
Nate, this is a really bad idea.
A single miscalculation
could be lethal.
Which is why I did a quality
control test on myself first.
What? You already took it?
Yeah. I had to make sure it was safe.
So far, pretty good.
Um, the tongue, getting a little numb.
But, um, you should drink it now
so we peak at the same time and place.
Okay.
Well...
Ah...
Right. We should be sitting down
for this.
And the room should be dark.
Gideon?
Okay... So what do we do now?
Believe it or not,
this is my first vision quest.
- Do we chant?
- No.
- We stop talking.
Close your eyes. And just breathe.
Breathing in.
Breathing out. Breathing in again.
Nate...
Sorry.
- Rory, don't.
- Just a little?
Maybe later. Which way?
My brother is in the East Wing Annex.
The blueprints Gideon downloaded
said the control panel
is this way.
You guys open the cell.
Let's go talk to your brother.
Oh, no.
Hey. How's it going?
There's no maintenance scheduled
here till tomorrow.
Really? We got a call that,
uh, something was broken...
Yeah? What?
Your nose.
It says here my brother's being
held in cell 4587.
You guys got a location
on the other security console?
Yup. All clear.
All right.
Which cell do we need to open?
It's room 4587.
Okay. I'm on it.
Wait a minute...
You mean everybody
locked up in here is a meta?
Looks like A.R.G.U.S. is conducting
experiments on them.
Guys, open the cell now.
I can do a lot better than that.
What are you doing?
CELL LOCK STATUS
What does it look like?
UNLOCKED
Let's go.
I thought you were just going to
open her brother's cell.
You didn't see
what we saw on the monitors.
A.R.G.U.S. is experimenting
on these prisoners.
Hey, where's Zari?
What the hell's going on?
I thought this was
just about grabbing your brother.
Yeah, about that... Sorry.
- Sorry for what?
- There is no brother.
There is no prison break.
It's a heist.
You used us.
We bent over
backwards to help you.
As lies go, this was a
pretty white one.
This used to be my brother's.
And now it's mine.
Oh, my God.
- Nate.
- You're not supposed to talk.
Nate, look.
Not supposed to open my eyes either.
Oh!
I think I'm starting to peak.
Amaya?
You okay?
Oh, boy.
Where's Zari?
Go, go!
Hold it.
Knock yourself out.
Showtime.
Uh, Nate, buddy,
we need you to bring
the Waverider to us. Now.
Um...
Stay.
Uh...
Okay. Um...
Yeah, I can do that.
My face. My face.
This room is huge.
Okay.
Pulling up the
anchor, raising the sails!
Full speed ahead!
That's enough, Zari.
You're not going anywhere without us.
Is that right?
- That's a cool getaway.
- Don't worry. I'll follow her.
Where's Pretty?
Nate, how are we doing with
that rescue?
I'm giving her all she's got,
Captain!
The ship can't take
much more of this!
Actually, Dr. Heywood,
the engines are still idling.
Then why does it feel like my face
is peeling off?
Yo, are you high or something, man?
You have no idea.
Gideon, take command of the ship.
I'll arrange a rendezvous point.
Let's get out of here.
Where's Stein anyway?
I believe he's checking
on Ms. Jiwe.
She seems to be experiencing a, well,
unusual side effect,
and as for Mr. Heywood, he's...
We've got bigger fish to fry.
Ray, do you have eyes on Zari?
Yep. I'm on her tail.
Not literally on it...
I'm following her posterior
from a respectable distance.
I can't believe
she played us like that...
That whole sob story
about her brother?
Just an excuse to get her hands
on some magical necklace.
When we find that chick
I am going to kill her.
- I like her.
- Uh, when you say "kill her,"
- what you really mean is...
- Kill her, and slowly.
No, no, no.
We have to restore the timeline.
Which means getting Ms. Tomaz
back to the A.R.G.U.S. black site,
where she belongs,
and tracking down your time-assassin.
Oh. And cleaning up the prison debacle.
Don't worry, Gary. We got this.
Geeze Louise. This disaster keeps
getting bigger and bigger, and bigger.
What are you doing?
Well, I hate to say it,
but Gary's right.
We've got to put Zari
back in the bottle.
Look, she's not exactly my favorite
person either right now.
But you didn't see
how it was back there,
the way A.R.G.U.S. was treating
those people.
She played us, Jax.
We're lucky that it's not us
in that prison instead.
She had a water witch travel
through time to hunt her down.
I mean, did Zari really act
any differently
than you would have
in that situation?
I'm just saying.
Do we really want to be the people
who put her back in a meta prison?
Is that who we are?
I can see through my hand.
Are you on drugs?
Your face! I want your face.
Okay, buddy, not a good idea.
Gideon?
As I was trying to tell you,
Mr. Heywood is under the influence
of a hallucinogenic compound.
To help Amaya with her totem
problem. Okay?
It's totally safe. People in her
village do it all the...
It's safe, I think.
As for Miss Jiwe,
professor Stein
helped her to the medical bay.
Get him to his quarters now.
Give him some water
and maybe his fidget spinner.
Ah.
I told you, bro. Let's go.
- Come on.
- Cobra.
All right. All right.
Amaya.
What is this place?
You are in the world between worlds.
Who are you?
I am your blood.
I am all who have
come before you.
I can feel the fear inside you.
It is a burden
that weighs heavy on your heart.
My totem, I can feel it
growing stronger.
I fear that I'm losing
control over it.
You can't stop the forces of nature.
No more than you can
stop a charging stallion.
You must learn to run beside it.
Why is it getting stronger?
The totem's strength grows
when the threats that you must face
become more powerful.
But you cannot face
this new threat alone.
You must find the girl.
She needs your protection.
Do not fail this new totem-bearer.
Do not resist your power.
Trust in it.
Zari...
Look, I don't want to fight,
but we got to go,
we can't stay here, it's not safe.
I don't understand.
They're not here.
Nobody's here.
They were supposed to meet me here.
This was supposed to be our Jannah.
"Jannah"?
It means "sanctuary" in Arabic.
My brother had powers because he
wielded this.
He fought against
A.R.G.U.S.'s injustices.
So he was hunted. We all were.
The night we were leaving,
A.R.G.U.S. raided our house,
killed my brother.
And took the only part that's
left of him.
That's how you got caught.
Trying to steal it the first time.
Yeah. I couldn't let A.R.G.U.S. keep it.
With my brother gone,
I needed its power to help me protect
my parents, but...
- Maybe they got away.
- Where?
Can't you see there's nowhere left
to go? This was our last hope.
Zari, I'm sorry about everything
that's happened to your family.
But we really have to...
Sara, the water woman just showed up
and she looks pretty grumpy.
Like, kill-anyone-
that-gets-in-her-way grumpy.
Send us your coordinates.
We're on our way.
What's going on now?
Unidentified ship approaching,
Captain.
- A.R.G.U.S.?
- No, Captain.
It's the Time Bureau.
I don't understand.
How does the Time Bureau
know where we were?
Gary!
I'm sorry.
I know you said you could handle it,
but you guys can't handle anything.
I should go.
Sara Lance.
I see
that you and your team
have managed to get yourselves
in over your heads... Again.
- Chill, lady.
- We're just trying to help.
By starting a prison riot
at the A.R.G.U.S. facility?
When are you going to learn
that the Legends should not be
interfering with Bureau affairs?
Maybe when you stop
screwing things up.
Perhaps it's best not to antagonize
someone on such a large timeship.
I don't care what Gary says.
We don't need backup.
Sara! I need backup!
Sara!
Where are you guys?
Interesting.
It sounds like one of your team members
has stumbled sideways
into finding our assassin.
Yes, that's rather our style.
Just give us his coordinates, we'll
be happy to save him for you.
You know these guys are going to hand
Zari back to those A.R.G.U.S. bastards
who are gonna do
god knows what to her.
And if you don't comply,
we would also
be happy to scatter
you all into space.
Did you just shoot at us?
I am not screwing around.
Give us those coordinates!
The next one will not be a warning,
Miss Lance.
I knew we shouldn't have trusted
that Time Dweeb.
Just give her what she wants!
Fine.
I'll uplink their
coordinates to you now.
You got to be kidding me.
- Ready?
- Ready to receive.
Whoa. They're gone.
I can see that, Gary! Track their
signature and follow them!
That was easier than I thought it'd be.
Is this what you're looking for?
So you do have it.
But are you capable of using it?
What are you offering for the totem?
I can give you
what you really want, Zari.
What you want more
than that little trinket.
I can give you revenge.
Revenge on A.R.G.U.S.
They targeted you and your family.
Turned you all
into fugitives and criminals.
They should die.
And in exchange for your help,
I give you this?
You can't control this power.
It wasn't meant for you.
I can free you from this burden
and help you getjustice
for your family.
Maybe picking a fight with the Time
Bureau wasn't the best stratagem.
Yeah. Well, they fired on us first.
And if they continue to do so,
we will sustain critical damage
in less than five minutes.
Four minutes.
- Well?
- I guess I have to say...
Sorry.
Come on, Ray! She's too much for us.
We got to move.
And she tastes terrible. Whoa.
- What's happening?
- Time Pukes
are shooting at us.
At least you seem to be feeling
better, Ms. Jiwe?
Yeah. Nathaniel's plan
while ill-advised, was beneficial.
Quiet.
The marshmallow's are talking.
Get to the Jumpship.
Get a fix on Ray's position
while Stein and I
keep our Time Bureau friends busy.
Not you, Space Ranger. Sit.
I really love this show.
Gideon, status.
The Jumpship has been deployed.
I don't believe our pursuers noticed.
Oh, dear. I'm afraid our rear deflectors
have been completely lost, Captain.
Sara, please.
You still have enough time
to arrange a détente
with the Time Bureau,
a compromise, if you will.
Sorry, Martin. I don't compromise.
Would you please help me talk some
sense into her?
I don't like broccoli.
Gideon, divert everything
to our forward shields.
You guys might want to hold on.
Gideon, hail the Time Bureau.
- What are you doing?
- Being true to who we are.
My team doesn't roll over
on their own.
Zari Tomaz is not one of your own.
Either way,
we're not gonna let you, A.R.G.U.S.,
or anyone else put her behind bars
for who she is.
So you'd rather kill your team
and mine?
Collision in ten seconds, Captain.
Last chance, Ms. Lance.
Sara, this is madness.
Change your course!
I'm good.
Impact in three... Two... One...
Are we dead?
Did we die?
The Time Bureau vessel
jumped away.
Gideon, make sure
they're not following us.
Professor, you all right?
Nothing that a cup of tea won't fix.
One cup of Lyoga root tea
for the professor coming up
'cause you're my best friend.
What made you change your mind?
Thought about what my brother
would want me to do.
Weren't your friends
supposed to be coming to rescue us?
- Good point.
- You had your chance.
I was willing to offer you
a compromise,
but now I have to kill you.
I'm afraid we can't
let you do that.
If anyone's going to kill Haircut,
it's me, lady.
Thanks, Mick.
- Pleasure.
- You think you can stop me?
Trust in it.
What are you doing?
Trusting it.
How?
Stay down. I can do this all day.
I would kill you...
But I'd just be killing myself.
All right, Gideon,
how are we doing?
Our time-jump from Jannah
remained undetected, Captain.
I think we can safely say
our Time Bureau problem
is... Oh, bollocks.
- Perhaps I spoke too soon.
- What is it?
Incoming transmission
from Agent Sharpe.
Put her on.
Oh.
Hey, Ava.
How was your day?
You do realize that that little stunt of
yours could've destroyed us both.
You tried to kill us first.
No. I tried to warn you first. But
you don't take warnings, do you?
Now you're starting to get it.
Well, this isn't a warning.
It's a promise.
If I ever track you down again,
you and your band of idiots
will be exiled to the dawn of time.
Whatever leniency
Hunter gave you is over.
What a bitch.
You took the words
right out of my mouth, Gideon.
Plot a course to 2042.
Hey. How're you feeling?
Yeah. Much better.
And you?
I thought the hangover I got
drinking with P.T. Barnum was bad.
Hey. I wanted to thank you.
I've gotten a handle on
my totem again.
That's great.
You can at least try
not to sound so disappointed.
It's cool.
I just thought you were
staying on the ship
because your
totem was out of whack,
and now
that it's back in whack...
I can't go.
This whole experience
has made me realize
that my fate is entwined
with someone else's.
Zari's.
Well... Sara said we're
dropping her back off in 2042.
We could've dropped you off anywhere.
Why this dump?
With Jannah gone...
- This is home.
- Oh. Well...
You got a lot of heat on you.
I can handle heat.
Thanks.
Wait.
It's not safe for you here.
There's no reason to suggest that
sorceress won't return for you.
Well, it's not like
I have any other options.
That amulet...
It's not an amulet.
It's a totem.
Like mine.
We're bound together, somehow.
In a way that I have
yet to understand.
Come with us.
That's all nice and weird, but...
Totems, they guide us
in strange ways.
What if yours guided you to us?
What would you rather do?
Hide from A.R.G.U.S. your whole life
or do something really stupid,
like time travel?
- I'm not a superhero.
- Neither am I.
Good.
You can't pedal forever,
you little nerd!
Where are you, nerd?
I think he went down this way.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
Wait, he went down here.
Down here.
Hello?
Hi.
What's your name?
Mine's Ray Palmer.