In 2166, an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan is opposed
by the body I'd sworn
my allegiance to, the Time Masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes.
But if we succeed,
they will be remembered as legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
I'm a Time Master.
Making discrete alterations
to the timeline is what I do.
Half of what you told us about
the mission turned out to be lies.
Lewis Snart, convicted of larceny,
armed robbery.
You and your entire family
are criminals.
Things are complicated with family.
The Lazarus Pit brought me back
but it left me with this
need to kill.
You're Princess Chay-Ara,
I'm Prince Khufu, and we're lovers.
I know you're worth the wait.
Aah!
Well, I say we kick Savage's ass
for Carter.
For Carter.
Who are you?
The man who's here to kill you.
We've arrived in Leipzig, Germany,
the most current location
for Vandal Savage.
And by the way, Captain,
you are urgently needed
in the MedBay.
I thought she'd stabilized.
As did I.
Carter! Where's Carter?
He's gone, Kendra. I'm so sorry.
Gideon, turn that bloody noise off!
- Yes, Captain.
- What happened?
Saunders appears to have had
a complication.
Are you...
I know, what kind of complication?
How could you leave him?
- Is she...
- MedBay gave her a sedative.
But obviously, her condition
is worsening.
Pieces of the dagger have
apparently broken off
and are... as we speak,
en route to her heart.
Can't we just time jump
into the future
where they got the stuff
that can fix her?
This ship is from
that very same future
and has, thus far, been unsuccessful
in saving her.
Kendra wouldn't survive
the time jump anyway.
I pay attention.
To sum up, Carter Hall is dead,
the girlfriend's not too far behind.
Vandal Savage is sitting pretty in
1975, which we're all now stuck in.
That how the plan supposed
to work, Rip?
Obviously not.
But the mission is simple.
We... we stop Vandal Savage here
in the past...
and we save the future.
Simple don't mean easy, Captain.
Oh, I never said it was.
The benefit of being
a Time Master is that
the length and breadth of history
gives one perspective.
I've seen darker days.
I've seen men of steel die
and dark knights fall.
And even then, I accomplished
my mission no matter what.
Gideon, what is our status?
When theWaverider was attacked
by Chronos,
the Jumpship was damaged.
Unless you make repairs,
we will be unable to...
Wait, wait. Jumpship?
It's a small expeditionary vessel
at the belly of the Waverider...
you're a mechanic!
You have a look at it.
Auto mechanic.
Uh... spaceship.
Okay, if you've got a set
of wrenches,
I'll see what I can do.
What about the rest of us?
Do we just sit?
Capital idea, Mr. Rory.
You're not nearly as thick
as most people say.
Thick...
does that mean stupid?
Is that your son? He looks like you.
Sorry.
Trained by League of Assassins,
sneaking up on people
is kind of our thing.
I'd like to be alone for a moment.
You don't actually have a plan,
do you?
And that speech wasn't about
convincing us.
It was about convincing you.
Didn't work, did it?
Not particularly, no.
Hence my desire to be alone.
So we can't kill Savage.
Oh, I see you've grasped the concept
of immortality. Well done.
Maybe we could slow him down.
Now, Ra's al Ghul taught me
a thing or two
about fighting powerful adversaries.
If you can't kill your enemy,
weaken him.
If you can't cut off his head...
take his heart.
Mr. al Ghul was quite the poet.
Back at the weapons auction,
Savage was trying to sell his nuke.
Money is power.
Take away Savage's fortune
and he's just a regular guy
with a really long lifespan.
It certainly would set his plan for
world domination back a few decades.
So, where does Vandal Savage
keep his money in 1975?
The broken knife fragments are moving
through her circulatory system.
And if you'll notice these,
they're closing in towards her heart.
So what do we do?
The fragments are miniscule.
Even the ship's technology
isn't capable of neutralizing them.
Fortunately,
there's a technology onboard that is.
The atom suit.
I can shrink down,
slip into her bloodstream
and use the photon canons
to vaporize the knife fragments.
You'll be pushing the suit's limits.
We should run some tests, make sure
this is the best plan of action.
This isn't the ivory tower,
Professor.
- We don't have time...
- Listen to me, Raymond.
- I'm not your student anymore.
- You were never my student!
Just because you don't remember me.
If... if you had been my student,
I'd have taught you the principles
of using scientific analysis,
not this bravado.
There isn't time. I'm going in.
Gideon! Where's Savage's money now?
Dr. Boardman theorized that Savage
entrusted it to the Bruemberg Group,
the oldest bank in the world.
I'll go tell the rest of the team.
That won't be necessary.
I'm going alone.
I can't have any more blood
on my hands.
Except for your own?
You can't go in there without backup.
Look, I brought you all with me
under false pretenses.
Carter would still be alive
if I hadn't have convinced him
to come.
No one's on this ship that doesn't
want to be here.
But I can't risk the whole team.
Fine. Just me.
And if it helps,
I'm not giving you a choice.
I'm going with you to that bank.
Somebody say bank?
Your services aren't required,
Mr. Snart.
This is purely reconnaissance.
We know how to case banks.
We're practically bankers.
Except we take the money out.
Yes, and when I need someone
to steal something,
you'll be the first to know,
I assure you.
Listen, Englishman.
I'm getting bored being stuck
on this tin can.
And when I get bored,
I make bad decisions.
Now, now, now.
We're all on the same side here.
My hot-headed friend
and I just want to be helpful.
That's all.
Duly noted.
You should have let me punch him.
Yeah, then we wouldn't
have gotten this.
You ready?
Yes.
All right, where am I headed?
You're exiting the tracheal artery.
You should see the first fragment.
No sign of it. Did I miss it?
It's the size of an iceberg.
It seems highly unlikely
that you could miss it.
That's probably what they said
on the Titanic.
Think I found it.
Looks like all those years of playing
Asteroids is about to pay off.
Her vitals are improving.
It seems to be working.
There's still 19 more fragments.
Raymond?
Raymond, you're... you're not done!
I'm losing core containment.
Plot me a course out of here. Now!
Hey
Time is truly wasting
There's no guarantee
Smile is in the making
Excuse me.
We'd like to deposit some family
heirlooms.
I'm sorry, we're a private bank.
We don't secure valuables worth less
than ten million dollars.
Well, I'm sure this will suffice.
Doubloons from the wreck
of the Esplinade.
They've been appraised
at ten million dollars...
apiece.
Fight the power
Fight it
Such a pleasure.
You won't regret your decision.
The Bruemberg Group is known
for its discretion.
I'm sure there'll be a fair deal
of paperwork to sign.
Not too much.
We like to cut through
the red tape here.
Let me get this to one of our safe
deposit boxes
and I'll get my secretary to move
in on this paperwork.
Interesting.
There are records here referring
to something called the Vessel.
We have a problem.
Yes, I know, none of Savage's funds
are in this bank.
I'm working on locating this Vessel,
but I'm not sure I'll do so
before our new friend returns.
To kill us.
The receptionist had a silenced
Beretta under her desk.
The guards,
South African mercenaries.
You can tell by the initiation burns
on their neck.
And our new friend here
has calluses on his right hand
consistent with being
Kuroda-trained swordsmen.
- How do you know?
- Because I have the same calluses.
Which means they've probably figured
out that we are not Rockefellers
who just came into their inheritance.
Oh, don't be so alarmist.
Calluses are hardly definitive proof
of anything. But there's...
Pretty sure they made us.
Well, if this is how you treat
your customers,
we might just have to take our
business elsewhere.
I thought I specifically said
no weapons!
You can thank me later.
If you're looking for someone
That you can keep
Exactly how many knives do you have?
Seems you brought a knife
to a swordfight.
And if you want something
That's 20 years deep
Baby don't even try
Maybe lift you a little bit higher
I got the fire!
Sara.
Sara! Sara, don't!
We didn't get anything
from the computer!
We need him alive!
What the hell happened back there?
You know I'm a killer.
That's why you put me
in your little group.
I didn't witness just a killer
at work, Sara.
What I saw was an animal.
You are the last person on this ship
to judge anyone!
This is not judgment, Sara.
It is concern.
I thought you knew
how I was resurrected and...
and what it did to me.
I know you were restored
by something called the Lazarus Pit.
Well, apparently, there's a downside
to being brought back to life.
My friend Thea calls it a bloodlust.
And I think that's being too generous
and so is calling me an animal.
I'm a monster.
Ha! Nice ride!
Yeah. It can hit a Mach 3in a walk.
Pretty cool.
How'd you know so much about it?
Little thing called an instruction
manual.
Did you read the part about
how to fly this thing?
Maybe... Why?
We're gonna take a little sojourn
to Central City.
There's a priceless jewel that needs
to be freed from captivity.
You want me to help you steal
something?
No, man. I'll pass.
Not exactly asking, Jax.
Wow. Carter is dead.
Kendra is this close to joining him
and Vandal Savage is still alive
and out there doing God knows what.
And all you can think about
is stealing some diamond?
It's an emerald.
Is there anything you think about
other than yourself?
Yes. Money.
No. I'm not helping you guys steal
anything.
So if you want to shoot me,
then shoot me.
Can I shoot him?
You got a pair on you, kid.
I respect that.
So no shooting.
Look, you don't actually have
to help us steal anything.
We just need to get to Central City.
We'll be there and back before
anyone knows we're even gone.
Man, even if I wanted to help,
and I'm not saying that I do,
this thing's got a security lockout.
We need an access key.
You can't tell me you don't wanna see
what this baby can do.
I believe I've determined a way
to more efficiently track
the fragments still inside
Miss Saunders body.
Next time you'll be better prepared.
There won't be a next time.
Can't you fix the suit?
It's not the suit.
Raymond, you...
you mustn't be discouraged.
We're scientists.
We learn from failure,
and we keep going.
Kendra isn't a lab experiment.
She's a person.
I know.
You need to have confidence
this will work.
Well, I don't. I can't save her.
Based on what evidence?
Are we not empirical thinkers,
Dr. Palmer?
Exactly how many people
have you lost?
One.
Who did you lose?
Someone close to you?
Who was she, Raymond?
For someone who doesn't remember me,
you sure have a lot of personal
observations to offer.
Fine.
Don't talk to me, but fix the suit.
It's the only chance
that poor girl has.
I'm gonna make this very simple
for you, Mr. Blake.
You tell me where Vandal Savage
is hiding his fortune
and we will let you leave
here unmolested.
Vandal Savage...
is that the name you know him by?
Let's assume so, yes.
And what is your name?
Gareeb?
- Will you give us a moment?
- Gareeb?
It's a legend passed down
for 4,000 years.
When my master was first
bestowed the gift of eternal life,
an enemy tried to kill him.
Every myth has its monster,
it's devil.
For those of our order,
it's him, the Gareeb.
I'd stop talking now if I were you,
mate.
If I were you, I'd run.
Your friend has already failed
to kill my master once.
He won't be able to protect you.
In fact, I highly doubt he's ever
been able to protect anyone.
What did he mean
you already tried to kill Savage?
Leave it be, Sara.
- No, if you want us to do this...
- Yes, okay!
Yes, I... I had the chance
to kill Savage once before.
I had him dead to rights
and I hesitated.
Get off me! Aah!
I asked you a question.
Who are you, Gareeb?
Killing is never easy,
especially for a good man.
But the man killed my wife and son
and God knows how many
other wives and sons,
and yet I couldn't...
Your killing people doesn't make you
a monster, Sara,
but having the chance to avenge your
family and not taking it...
that does.
Let's try this again.
Back for more.
Where's Savage's fortune?
Now, I'm particularly interested
in this thing called the Vessel.
The Vessel is my master's most
treasured possession.
Excellent, and where can we find it?
The Greyhill Building.
There's a gathering tonight
in celebration of it.
And clearly you want us to go
so we can get ourselves killed.
Clearly.
What is the Vessel?
It's the remains of Prince Khufu
of the Middle Kingdom.
I believe you know him
as Carter Hall.
What is Savage going to do
with Carter's body?
Well, there's only one way
to find out, isn't there?
Gideon, locate the Greyhill Building
and set a course.
Wait. We have a plan.
Going after Savage's fortune.
Yeah, well, not anymore!
I won't let Carter's remains be
desecrated by that monster.
I won't let him win again.
And when Kendra wakes up,
and she will wake up...
she can give her soul mate
a proper farewell.
Then let us at least go in
with the rest of the team.
Gideon!
Sir, Mr. Snart, Mr. Rory,
and Mr. Jackson
are no longer aboard the ship.
That's what I call a clean heist.
And thanks for not setting
the museum on fire, partner.
And you, thanks for
being our getaway driver.
Speaking of,
let's get the hell back to the ship.
Oh, one more stop.
What are you talking about, boss?
1629 Handley Avenue.
What's on Handley Avenue?
It's where we grew up.
That's why you wanted to steal
the Maximilian Emerald.
Mick, enough.
You wanted to give it to your old man
so he wouldn't go to jail
trying to steal it for himself.
Your father was a thief too?
And unfortunately,
not a very good one.
Didn't Rip say something about not
messing with the timeline?
You could accidentally blink yourself
out of existence.
You're screwing with history here,
man.
Yeah, well, history screwed
with me first.
I know how it feels.
What?
To have a crisis of confidence.
As unlikely as that might seem,
I know.
It was 2002. I was teaching
quantum mechanics
and I had one particularly gifted
student.
He was able to solve
the Ehrenfest Theorem
in less than an hour.
He was quite frankly the only student
in all my years of teaching
who ever made me feel inferior.
That student...
was you.
You were... exceptional.
And suddenly, just like that,
you remember having me in your class.
I always remembered.
I just enjoyed taking you down
a peg or two.
And why tell me now?
Because I cannot for the life
of me reconcile that...
cocksure student I remember
with a man
who believes he doesn't have what
it takes to save Miss Saunders' life.
Who did you lose, Raymond?
My fiancée, Anna Loring.
She was killed two years ago
in a Starling City siege.
Right in front of me.
I couldn't have stopped them.
I couldn't do anything.
My leg had been broken.
I couldn't get to her.
I could only watch...
as they broke her neck.
I built this suit because
I promised myself that night
that I would never be powerless
to save anyone again.
So when a fragment broke free
and damaged my suit, I...
panicked.
Froze.
Raymond, you couldn't save Anna...
but you can save Kendra.
I believe it.
I believe in that student.
I just need him to believe it, too.
Let's do it.
Ah, Mr. Blake. Welcome.
I take it Mrs. Blake is out of town?
That's a very pointed observation.
If you're going to find the vessel,
you'll need my help.
No, I think we're quite good
without it.
Sara?
I came down for a glass of water.
I'm Leo.
Are you friends with my daddy?
Kind of.
I think my daddy's sleeping.
Can I tell you something, Leo?
It's important.
Don't ever let anyone hurt you.
Ever.
Not here...
and especially...
not here.
No matter what, you always have
to look out for yourself.
Okay?
You understand?
I think so.
You get the hell away from my boy,
you son of a bitch.
Why don't you go on up to bed?
Go on.
Talk fast, or you take a bullet.
What are you doing in my home?
A favor for you.
Watch it.
Relax.
How the hell did you get...
Two days from now, you try
to steal this and you get arrested
and you spend five years
in Iron Heights.
What are you talking about?
Cut the crap.
We both know if I go down
to the basement right now,
I'll find floor plans
for the Central City museum.
Let's just say I've saved you
the trouble...
and from being arrested.
How do you know all this?
The same way I'll know
if you even think
of raising a hand to your wife
and son.
I know who you are.
I know the man you become
and it's all I can do to keep from
ending you right here, right now.
But if I do, that means
my sister's never born
so you get a pass.
Your sister?
Looks like you didn't write yourself
out of the timeline.
- Looks like.
- But?
I don't know, I just thought
maybe things would feel differently.
The Englishman says it takes time
for time to change.
What were you trying to change?
My dad was never Father of the Year
but at least he never raised
a hand to any of us.
Until he went to prison,
which now he won't.
Let's get out of here.
Maybe we should have had Blake
show us around.
Perhaps there's a less conspicuous
way for us to do reconnaissance.
May I?
I'm not much of a dancer.
I'll lead, then.
Well, for a monster, you dance
quite gracefully, Miss Lance.
- Don't make fun.
- I know, I'm not.
Nor do I consider you a monster.
All I see is someone who is tortured
by an appetite
that she cannot control.
There's no magical cure
for what's wrong with me.
Of course, there is.
It's called being better.
When my family was killed,
I thought there was no way
I could go on...
but I did.
The truth of our existence is that
we're all blessed and cursed
with the drive to move forward.
Live the next day.
To get better.
And you will too, Sara.
Well, maybe I can start by managing
not to kill these guys.
They're scarred up like our friends
at the bank.
South African mercenaries.
Why didn't you say so?
Ladies first.
This area's restricted, folks.
I'm just looking
for the ladies' room.
Oh!
Hope you have a plan
to get him out of here.
Yep. There's a maintenance elevator
leads to a loading bay.
I'll have Gideon fly
the Waveriderdown.
I just wish we knew what Savage
was gonna do with Carter's body.
Why not stay and find out?
Ah, the Gareeb.
Mr. Blake has told us
so much about you.
I've located three fragments.
Okay, I see them.
Damn, they're big.
Remember, the initial blast
will create smaller pieces.
You'll need to...
How does Jax put up with having
you in his head?
I believe he finds my presence
rather comforting.
I doubt that very much.
Targeting system's overloaded.
Focus, Raymond.
Remember, you can do this.
It's not the suit.
It's you that Kendra needs right now.
Well done,
just one more fragment to go.
I see it. It's the biggest one yet.
You did it!
Well done.
I... I couldn't possibly
be more proud.
Well, maybe if you actually
remembered me being your student.
Right around the subclavian artery,
I remembered something.
How I figured the solve
to the Ehrenfest theorem...
two years after I was in your class.
Why did you tell me you remembered me
when you didn't?
Because you needed a push.
So all that stuff about me being
exceptional?
Was probably true.
The fact of the matter is...
I had many exceptional students
over the years.
I couldn't possibly remember
them all.
I was pretty amazing.
If that were true, I suspect
I'd have given you a higher grade.
I meant tonight.
Oh, yes.
On that score, I cannot disagree.
What are you planning on doing
with Carter's body?
Oh, you'll see.
Mr. Blake informs us that you were
hoping to steal our master's fortune.
But while money has its uses,
it is not the source of his power.
Then what is?
Let us show you.
Hym nu setta, rash mun setta.
Our numbers are legion.
All drawn to the man
who is immune to death.
Wealth is not power...
belief is.
Hym nu setta, rash mun setta.
Hello, Gareeb.
How long has it been?
4,000 years?
You look well.
When you and your friends
attacked my estate in St. Roch
I was afraid I wouldn't get
the chance to meet you once again.
Well, if there's something
that I've learned in 4,000 years...
it's patience.
And this time, I only had
to wait one short day.
You're probably wondering what my
plans are with your friend's body.
I already have his life's essence,
but his blood still has its uses.
Hym nu setta, rash mun setta.
Jack the Ripper showed me
the virtues of severing
the carotid artery.
Hym nu setta.
Okay, what's this now?
Hym nu setta, rash mun setta.
Centuries ago,
I discovered that although
immortality is mine alone...
I can share a taste...
with my faithful.
Help them to live an extra 100 years
or so.
Hym nu setta, rash mun setta.
Hym nu setta...
Hum nu setta, rash mun...
They're in trouble.
She appears to be hallucinating.
Rip... Sara... You have to save them!
Vandal! And Carter!
The Greyhill Building!
Carter! Rip! Sara!
Gideon, search Greyhill Building.
I've already searched for it
on behalf of the Captain,
who's there now with Miss Lance.
What? They left without us?
It's a mansion several miles away.
Apparently, there's some
sort of private event.
How the hell could Kendra know
that they're there?
You have to save them!
- What's going on?
- I don't know!
When we first met,
I asked you who you were.
Remember?
That was the wrong question.
I should have asked you "Why?"
Why did you seek to kill me?
What could I have possibly
done to deserve
that hatred I see burning
in your eyes.
Did I take something from you?
Someone?
Get your hands off that.
Ah, your wife, I take it.
Oh, she is lovely.
The boy has your eyes.
I'll be sure to keep
their picture close.
I don't remember killing them...
yet.
It seems like I have a lot
to look forward to.
Gideon, get me Jefferson.
Mr. Jackson is not aboard.
Oh, don't tell me...
He's with Mr. Snart
and Mr. Rory on the Jumpship.
I'm patching you through.
Jefferson?
Jefferson, where are you?
Well, it's not a short story.
There's no time!
Gideon will upload you coordinates
to the Greyhill Building.
Rip and Sara are in danger.
We're on our way, Professor.
This is a perversion.
No, this is the power
you have no hope of defeating.
Everyone here is sworn to live
and die at my command.
Why?
Because to them, I am a God!
I pity you.
You have no idea what it's like
to have people willing
to follow you up to the gates
of Hell!
Actually,
I have a little bit of an idea.
Let's get this party started!
Here's our invitation!
Well, this is different.
I didn't have him pegged
as the Eyes Wide Shut type.
Aah. Go! Here!
You came!
We're a team!
Next time, remember that.
Enough!
Get Carter's body out of here.
- Sara!
- I got this.
- Go! I'll deal with Savage.
- Good luck with that.
This is for Miranda and Jonas.
At least I know their names now.
Miranda and Jo...
Jonas.
I will heal...
and then, I will rise...
and I'll simply wait.
I... I am looking forward
to meeting them.
Sara. Sara.
Sara!
Gideon, I need a check
of the timeline.
Vandal Savage.
The timeline is unchanged, Captain.
You know better than anyone
that Savage is immortal.
He cannot be killed through
conventional means.
Which is why I need you to work
on finding out
where history records seeing him
next.
How is she?
Better.
Thank you for what you did
for Carter.
Believe me, it was a team effort.
As was, apparently, your recovery.
Well, actually,
I did most of the physical work
and Professor was there
for emotional support.
You're welcome.
Now, if we could just figure out
a way to wrest the Amon Dagger
out of Savage's hand into yours.
I don't think I'm exactly up to
taking him on right now.
No, but you will be...
and we'll help you get ready.
Maybe you didn't understand me.
I asked for the new timeline, Gideon.
This is the new timeline.
Two days from now,
your father will be arrested
trying to sell the Maximilian Emerald
to an undercover police officer.
Stupid son of a bitch.
He'll be sentenced to five years
in Iron Heights.
Despite your intervention,
his future remains unchanged.
Hey, you tried to save him.
That's got to count for something.
Turns out it doesn't.
Come on.
Where are we going now?
To say good-bye.
The other day, I tried to find some
words of inspiration.
Words that would restore hope to us
in the wake of our losses.
But, it is all of you
who have inspired me.
Beginning with Professor Boardman
and then with Carter,
their heroism is...
an inspiration to us all.
And a reminder that one person
acting alone can't save the world.
Come back to me.
Thank you.
Both of you.
We're sorry for your loss, Kendra.
I believe Anna would be proud.
As am I.
Gideon, ready us for takeoff.
Whoa, are we being chased
or something?
No, but I imagine that right about
now,
the museum has realized
that their prized emerald is missing.
You want me to say I'm sorry?
Sorry, I don't do sorry.
Which is fine, Mr. Rory,
because you are owed the apology.
I should have told you all before
that this wasn't my first attempt
to vanquish Vandal Savage.
But the reason I failed before...
was because you didn't have
all of us.
Obviously, Dr. Palmer and I had our
hands full tending to Miss Saunders.
But now that she's back
on her feet...
We're back to full strength.
Or as strong as we can be
without Carter.
Quite true.
But, there is no point in us
continuing any further.
Unless we are all
and... myself included...
committed to working in concert.
You don't ditch us,
we won't ditch you. Deal?
Sir, I've completed my review
of the timeline.
I calculate a 98 percent likelihood
that Savage reappears in 1986.
Chart a course, Gideon.
Guess we're headed to the '80s.
Better break out your
parachute pants.
What the hell are parachute pants?