- In 2166, an immortal tyrant
named vandal savage
Conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
And stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately,
my plan is opposed
By the body I'd sworn
my allegiance to--
The time masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
But if we succeed,
They will be remembered
as legends.
- Previously
on "legends of tomorrow"...
- You need to learn to embrace
your human side.
- And what if that side of me
is gone?
What if she
doesn't exist anymore?
- No, this is a dictatorship.
You get to call all the shots,
And I get to take
all the shots.
- The most powerful evil
the world has ever known
Has just gone red at the height
of the cold war.
- Valentina vostok?
- She's trying to build
a soviet firestorm.
- Your comrade here tells me
you know quite a bit
About this project of mine.
- You're hanging us
out to dry, rip!
I need backup!
- Half the team is gone.
- I'm gonna remember that,
comrade.
- You and dr. Vostok have much
work to do in the morning.
- Incredible.
This is the exact formula
For the thermocore that's needed
to build a new firestorm.
How did you manage to arrive
at something
That took decades to produce?
- But here's what
I don't understand.
The firestorm matrix
is unstable.
The thermocore reacts
exponentially
To the rate of fission
in the host body.
- Well, fortunately, dr. Wells
developed the quantum splicer
To address that very problem.
I-I'm so happy to see
that you're taking an interest
In my work.
- What can I say, sir?
Nuclear physics is my passion.
- "sir"?
The cisco I know never dwelled
on formality.
What's more,
your hair is different,
Your wardrobe neat,
your comportment gentlemanly.
- Oh, yeah, you like?
I just subscribed to "gq."
- Huh.
A snide attempt at humor...
Almost cisco-like.
Almost.
- What are you implying?
- What I am stating
unequivocally, sir...
Is that you are not cisco,
Which means I am not
in s.T.A.R. Labs.
Furthermore, I will never,
Never give you the formula.
[tense music]
♪
- Bravo, professor stein.
- [gasps]
What cocktail of hallucinogens
have you given me, doctor?
- Don't worry.
I would never dream of damaging
that beautiful mind of yours.
I simply want to open it.
Finish the formula, and these
little games of ours can stop.
- You'll never trick me
into giving up my research.
And since you also
cannot kill me
And destroy any hope of creating
a soviet firestorm,
I would like a hot shower
And a change of clothes.
- And I thought I gave
a good speech.
- I'm sorry.
Have we met?
- 11 years ago,
You bought a nuclear warhead
off me in norway.
And then you and your
time-traveling friends
Tried to kill me.
Just like me,
you haven't aged a day.
- I have a good hairdresser.
- [chuckles]
In my long life,
I have met some
Of the most skilled
interrogators in history, but--
But since we are
in the soviet union,
Let me tell you a story
about a friend of mine--
Joseph stalin.
He became quite skilled
at breaking a man--
Carefully aimed strikes
to the bridge of the nose,
Along the shoulder blades,
And right underneath the chin.
Stalin gave me this
as a gift.
- So it's
to be torture, then?
Get on with it.
- No.
Nothing so prosaic
for you, professor.
There are infinite ways
to break a man,
And I have
an infinite amount of time.
- Firestorm
is my life's work.
I will never allow you
to pervert it
In pursuit
of global conquest.
♪
- This is going to be
so much fun.
♪
[exciting music]
- Jefferson!
Jefferson!
- Jax?
What are you doing in here?
Hey, are you all right?
- [gasps]
[panting]
Yeah, I, uh--
I haven't been able to sleep
the past two nights.
- I prescribed mr. Jackson
some mild medication.
- Which don't seem to be doing
a damn thing.
- What's wrong?
- Ah, it's stein.
They started in on him again.
He's scared to death.
I-I can feel it.
He's trying to be strong, but--
- we're gonna get him back.
Ray and rory too.
I'm sure captain hunter
has a plan.
- [groans]
it's my fault he got captured.
If--if he wasn't trying
to protect me,
He would have never
gone in there alone.
- It's gonna be okay, jax,
I promise.
- You don't know what kind of
place they got him locked up in.
- Labor camp number 54--
Formerly known as the koshmar
or "nightmare" gulag.
Built in the 18th century--
- Can we skip past
the wikipedia crap
And get to the good stuff,
like how to break in?
- Perhaps you didn't register
that as a question, gideon.
- I understood, but in
its 200 years of operation,
No one has successfully
escaped from--
- No offense, gideon,
But I never met a building
I couldn't break into.
- Well, I hope you're right.
Savage knows
that stein created firestorm,
But if he finds out
that he is firestorm--
- Always savage with you,
isn't it?
My partner's in prison too.
- And ray.
- Yeah, whatever.
The point is you didn't lift
a finger.
- You know damn well
it was never my intention
To get them thrown into a gulag,
but I had no other option.
Besides, I doubt that it's
mr. Rory's first time in prison
Or second
or, I imagine, tenth.
- All right, arguing is not
Gonna bring the team back
any faster.
And rip's right.
Criminals usually do feel
more at home in prison,
And they know it
better than anyone else.
- So?
- So what if the key
to breaking in
Is asking someone who's been
in and out of soviet prisons
Their whole life?
- And who might that be?
- Are you familiar
with the bratva?
- Ooh, the russian mob?
In 1986, they would have ruled
the criminal underground
Inside every prison.
[tense music]
♪
- Your tattoo.
It stands for
"menia ispravit rasstrel,"
If I'm not mistaken.
In english, it translates to,
"execution will reform me."
- What brings you
to the banya, little man?
- The name's rip.
I understand
that you're familiar
With the koshmar gulag.
- We need to break
into that prison.
And can you make it fast?
I despise the heat.
- A man by the name
of vandal savage
Runs a secret operation
out of it--
A prison within a prison,
if you will.
- I've heard of this savage.
He has no respect
For my country's
rich criminal traditions.
- So you'll help us?
- You men have no tattoos.
And a man who has no life story
cannot be trusted.
Igor!
Andrei!
♪
- Don't all volunteer at once.
[grunting and blows landing
in distance]
- Igor and andrei
seem to be a bit preoccupied.
Now, about that gulag...
- No matter.
In this life,
a man fights for himself.
[neck cracks]
- Perhaps you'd like this one.
- He's all yours.
- [yells]
- So you like
having vandal savage
Run his evil empire
from your country?
- As much as a pig enjoys
being christmas dinner.
- Help us, and we will destroy
his entire operation.
[knock at door]
- I just took out six men.
You guys couldn't handle one?
- You killed my men?
- They're not dead yet.
And neither are you,
assuming you help us.
- My organization runs
black-market goods into koshmar.
- Three of our, uh,
well, comrades
Are being held there
by savage.
- Koshmar is not a hotel
for petty criminals.
If your friends are there,
They must be insane,
ruthless animals.
- Hey. Howdy.
How you doing?
- What the hell are you doing?
- Just being friendly.
This must be where they keep
the vips.
- This is prison, jackass.
There are no vips.
- Some of these guys
have been here for a while.
Hey, maybe this guy knows
where stein is.
- [speaking russian]
- The only thing you should be
worrying about, pretty,
Is lasting the night.
- Stein needs help.
He's in real trouble.
- Newsflash, so are we.
- [speaking russian]
- Think they'll
bring us blankets later?
- Now, according to yuri,
This is where his men
have access.
Got it?
- This isn't my first
prison break.
- We got it covered.
- So how can we help?
- By staying on the ship.
We don't need
any more casualties.
Besides, mr. Snart and sara
have got it covered.
- Whoa, man.
Why does it feel like
We're on the jv team
all of a sudden?
- What you are is one half
of everything savage needs
To change the face
of the cold war.
And you are the only person
who can kill him.
- Yeah, so you can't just--
- I am not going to gift-wrap
the two people
In the world that savage wants
the most.
- We should get going.
- Oh, ms. Lance,
could I borrow you for a moment?
I have something that might
help you out with the mission.
- So what did you really want
to talk to me about?
- Gideon, will you please show
ms. Lance the projection of 2016
Should our rescue mission fail?
- I'd be happy to, captain.
- So this is what will happen
to russia
If we don't get stein back?
- Not russia.
This is star city.
The rest of world
doesn't look much better.
- That's impossible.
- Not if stein creates a stable
firestorm for the soviets.
Here in 1986,
they're already perilously close
To creating a prototype.
Listen to me, sara. Everything--
everything we've tried
To achieve so far
could be lost.
And not only will my family die
150 years from now,
But your family,
your city...
Your entire 21st-century world
will suffer.
♪ ♪
- That's why we're gonna
get stein back
Before vostok can break him.
- Well, I-I hope so,
but we need a contingency plan.
- What are you saying?
- I'm saying that if at any
point throughout the operation
It becomes clear
that martin is...
Beyond our reach...
- You want me to kill stein?
♪
- Impressive how many weapons
you can fit in that outfit...
And how much stupidity raymond
can squeeze into this one.
- The plan is to save him too,
not just stein and your partner.
- Oh, I'm gonna save raymond,
all right,
So I can beat some sense
into him.
And what about you?
- What about me?
- Clearly I'm not the only one
with a side mission.
What did rip keep you
after class to talk about?
- He just wanted to go over
a few details of the plan.
- He wants you to take out
the old man, doesn't he?
It's the obvious play.
It's also heartless.
- The plan is to save stein.
And if, for whatever reason,
we can't,
Rip showed me what will happen
to my home in 2016,
To our families.
If stein breaks,
the damage is irreversible.
- Been on a lot of heists,
and even when things got rough,
I never took out one
of my own.
- Well, this isn't
a bank heist.
- First, he left my partner
twisting in the wind.
Now he's gonna have you ice
old silver-top.
We're all just pawns, sara.
Come on, I'm the crook,
you're the assassin--
- He's not just asking me
to kill.
He's asking me to save
the future.
And if, for whatever reason,
we can't save stein,
Then I'm gonna do
what needs to be done.
- Huh.
It's just like scout camp.
[chuckles]
man, the food was terrible.
There was one time they gave us
salisbury steak--
- You ever stop talking?
- What I wouldn't give for
a little salisbury steak now.
Hey.
Ray palmer.
- Put your hand down.
- He might know where vostok
is keeping the professor.
- Shut up and eat.
- Do you know if there's
any other place
Where they keep prisoners here?
We're looking for a friend.
- There is a place.
They send you there,
you never come back.
You can hear the screams
all night.
- This place, where is it?
- Who said you could eat?
- Hey, he's not hurting
anybody.
- Who is this american
with the pretty teeth?
Must be a comedian, da?
- I'm sure we can handle this
like adults.
- [chuckles]
[crowd cheering]
Sooka!
[crowd continues cheering]
- I brought you something
to eat, professor.
- If this is a bribe,
I politely decline.
- So stubborn,
so proud...
So american.
- You've already built
a thermocore,
So just build another one.
It'll only take you
eight to ten years.
- You thought that, what,
your friends stealing
The thermocore
would save the west?
[ominous music]
♪
As if I would only build one.
We're so close, professor.
All I need to learn now is how
to stabilize the thermocore,
And my dream of creating
a nuclear man will be achieved.
- To what end?
If you launch
a soviet firestorm,
The United States will have
no choice but to retaliate.
Both countries
will be annihilated.
- And out of the ashes,
we will rise stronger...
Just as we did
when the nazis invaded.
But america is weak...
With your big mac,
mtv, movie-star president.
- Do you really think
vandal savage cares
About the cold war?
He's just using you, doctor.
- Do not think of insulting
mr. Savage in front of me.
♪
- Hey, what's wrong?
- Something's changed.
Grey thinks
we've abandoned him.
He's starting to lose it
in there.
I can't take this.
- We've got to tell rip.
- The guy who benched us?
He'll just tell us
to sit tight.
No, I hate feeling
so helpless.
This is exactly what it was like
when I blew out my knee.
I could barely walk,
recruiters stopped calling,
My mom always crying.
[sighs] I just wish
there was something I could do.
- Wait.
Your connection with stein,
it goes both ways, right?
- Yeah.
- So maybe we can send him
a signal.
- Grey did tell me about
this one time he and ronnie--
Get a knife.
You need to cut me.
- Tell me how
to stabilize firestorm.
- If einstein had
the opportunity,
He would have traveled back
in time
To prevent the creation
of the atomic bomb.
How can I in good conscience
lead the world
To the invention of something
far more destructive?
- You don't really have
a choice.
This toxin, it's not lethal,
But it will make you wish
that it were.
[suspenseful music]
- Are you sure about this?
♪
- So, professor...
Would you like to talk,
or would you prefer to scream?
- Do your worst, doctor.
- [speaking russian]
- Hey, pyro, what was that there
back in the yard?
- Just your typical
prison alpha.
He didn't like you
threatening his reputation.
- Not that.
I mean you sitting there
While I was getting
my ass kicked.
- None of my business.
- None of your business?
None of your business?
We're...
Supposed to be a team.
- The only team I'm on
is mine and snart's.
Besides, you had
that beatdown coming.
- Oh, well,
I can't sit back
And watch an old man
get pushed around.
- Then you're a bigger fool
than I thought.
[tense music]
♪
- These are the ones I want.
Remember me?
♪
- Identification papers.
- Yuri the bear sent me.
- Remember, we get stein first.
- And if the plan fails,
you'll kill him.
You want my advice?
- No.
- Don't use your gun.
Do it with your hands.
Do it while you're looking
right into stein's eyes.
- You're talking
about a member of our team.
- I just don't want you
to forget
Who we're talking about.
♪
- Thank you.
Valentina has failed
to make you talk.
Now it's my turn.
♪
- Colonel, let's begin.
- So are you still planning--
what did you threaten before?
To go all "rocky iv" on my ass?
- [laughs]
I've changed my mind.
[electricity crackles]
[both grunting]
[panting]
Ivan drago lives at the end
of the movie.
Ha--
[both grunting]
[both screaming]
[electricity crackles]
[both grunt and pant]
- Isn't he supposed to ask us
some questions?
- They don't care
what we got to say.
We're just part of the show.
- Stein.
Professor, we're okay.
Don't tell these bastards
anything!
[electricity crackles]
[both grunt and scream]
- If you think I have a
sentimental attachment to them,
You are as foolish
as you are mad.
- You held up longer
than expected.
[electricity crackles]
[both scream and grunt]
But if 4,000 years of life
has taught me one thing,
It is patience.
[suspenseful music]
- When I get out of here--
- That is your mistake--
Thinking that you'll
get out of here.
- Hey.
Can I get some water in here?
Something to drink?
I'm a little thirsty.
A sandwich would be nice--
a little turkey and mayo.
They have mayo in russia?
No.
[scoffs]
At least in america,
you get a last meal.
This communism really sucks.
- What are you doing,
boy scout?
- Yes, boy scout,
what are you doing?
- Nothing compared to what I did
to your mother last night.
- You have quite
a mouth on you.
- So does she.
[screaming]
- Enough!
You're killing him!
- That's it?
- Oh, but the colonel will think
that we are cheating him.
- I'll tell you
how to stabilize firestorm.
Just let them live, please!
- So how does it feel
to be dead again?
- Take the next left.
- You can't be
down here, comrade.
- I was ordered to take
this corpse to the incinerator.
I wouldn't do that
if I were you.
Dr. Vostok used him for one
of her smallpox weapons trials.
♪
Highly contagious.
- All right, this duct
should take us to solitary.
We get to stein--
- yeah, I'm not going.
- That's the plan.
- That's rip's plan.
My priority is mick.
- Fine.
Forget it.
So much
for your code, crook.
- Anytime, assassin.
- Of all the dumb things
I've seen in my life,
You getting that guy
to beat on you takes the cake.
- You're welcome.
- You think you proved
something back there?
- Proved
I wasn't scared.
- Proved you make
a great piñata.
He could have beaten you
to death.
- There are some things that are
more important than survival,
Like standing up
for what you believe in,
Your principles,
your team.
There must be something
you're willing to die for.
- The perfect score.
- Well...
Only difference between us
is how we define "score."
- I'm sorry
to inform you, captain.
The probability
of the United States
Losing the cold war
has risen to 99%.
Star city,
the seat of the resistance,
Is predicted to fall in 2003.
- Come on, sara.
♪
- You mentioned
The quantum splicer earlier,
professor.
Your friends are counting on you
to make the right decision.
- I have eyes on stein.
- The future is cementing.
You must extract stein
before he enters the lab!
♪
[man shouts indistinctly]
- kill her!
- What's happening,
ms. Lance?
- I couldn't rescue stein.
- Have they moved him
into the lab?
- Yeah, where savage
has every guard
In the gulag watching him.
- Well, if that's the case...
- I know what I have to do.
- The formula for stabilizing
firestorm, professor.
- This may surprise you,
but in my youth,
I longed to visit russia.
I was obsessed
by your culture--
Rachmaninoff,
dostoyevsky, tolstoy.
- Stop stalling.
- It's a shame I-I never got
to see it before the collapse.
- What sort of nonsense
are you talking about?
- In 1991, your economy fails,
and your empire crumbles.
But the truth is the world
is better off.
In my time, crooks and thieves
rule your country,
Desperate to hang on to power
and the riches
They divide
amongst their cronies.
My country
is by no means perfect,
But at least we are free
to criticize our government,
Vote in fair elections,
and love whom we choose.
I, uh, hate to break this
to you, dr. Vostok.
You are on the wrong side
of history.
- For now.
But you will help us
change history.
Proceed.
- Gideon,
are you able to detect
The professor's
life functions remotely?
- Yes, captain.
His pulse is still strong.
- Yeah, not for much longer.
- Rip, jax and I need
to talk to you.
- Now is really not
a good time.
- Yeah, this will only take
a minute.
I know you think
you can't risk losing us,
But that's assuming
we'd fail.
- And we won't.
I'm not afraid anymore.
I can do this.
- And I don't got
to be firestorm
To be a part of this team.
- Look, I am not prepared
to risk anyone else.
Ever since--
- carter?
His death wasn't your fault.
- I know.
But stein's will be.
- All I got to do
is touch him,
And we can fly
out of there.
- Yeah, once you've scaled
a 50-foot fence
Topped with razor wire,
gotten past eight sharpshooters,
And entered a gulag full
of the most dangerous criminals
In the u.S.S.R.
- Okay, so you create
a distraction,
And I'll fly jax in,
and no one will see us.
- Listen...
You're playing chess without
all your pieces on the board.
- Maybe you're right.
- So that's a "yes"?
- You call that a flame?
- Ah.
Nice costume.
- Got one for you too.
Wakey, wakey.
Time to shrink...
Or not.
Let's go.
- What about him?
We can't ditch him.
He won't survive.
- Two guards walking
out of here--not suspicious.
Two guards carrying him out--
suspicious.
- He took a beating for me.
- Raymond would take a beating
for a total stranger.
Mick, if our time in the can
taught us anything,
It's we look
after each other.
It's you and me, right?
- So, if we enter here,
we can cut the circuit breaker.
- Shutting off all the power.
- Distracting the guards and
giving us time to save our team.
- The probability of this plan
being successful--
- There is a 15-second window
Where the sharpshooters
on the tower
Aren't covering the breaker.
- Which means that somebody
would have to run 120 yards
In less than 12 seconds.
- Given mr. Jackson tore his
anterior cruciate ligament--
- Have a little faith,
gideon.
You can do this.
I know you can.
- It's done.
- You know, I've never seen
a theorem so simple,
So poetic before.
With this, I can decelerate
the subject's rate of fission
And decrease
core body temperature.
Yet something's missing.
- I'm telling you,
that is the equation--
Everything you need to build
a quantum splicer.
[both grunt]
- "we're coming"?
Explain.
- I cut myself.
- Impossible.
You've been monitored
ever since your arrival here.
So, unless some--
So, unless someone else was cut,
yet it appears on your body...
- That's preposterous.
- No, no, no.
You are somehow connected
to the burning man.
That's how you were able
to absorb
The nuclear energy
at luskavic.
- You are mistaken.
- No, you didn't only create
firestorm.
You are one half
of firestorm.
- That's ridiculous!
- Bring the core online.
And to think, all this time..,
You were the missing link.
- Listen to me.
It is extremely rare to find
two people who are compatible,
And without the splicer--
- Have you ever merged
With a woman before,
professor?
I think you and I are gonna make
a wonderful firestorm.
[tense music]
♪
- What the hell
are they doing?
- What I should have done
from the start--
Helping rescue stein.
- What about the time line?
- I have a plan.
Forget about the fail-safe.
- Isn't it a little late
for plan c?
- Not if jax can reach
that circuit breaker.
- I can't believe you're risking
your life for this idiot.
♪
- Okay, okay.
You got this.
12 seconds, open field--
done it a million times.
[exhales sharply]
[exciting music]
[knee pops]
ah!
Ah!
[panting]
♪
Barry allen who?
[alarm blaring]
[overlapping shouting,
locks slamming]
- Electromagnetic locks.
- We're dressed as guards.
- Run.
♪
- Everyone back in your cells!
- Enjoy your new cellmate!
[laughs]
- No!
- That door leads
to the loading bay.
From there, you can get
to the jump ship.
- Hey, mick,
this is a strange kind of hug.
- Where are you going?
- I got something to do.
♪
[dramatic music]
- Mr. Savage, I need to get you
to the helicopter.
- Make sure the professor
enters the reactor.
His nuclear-mate is waiting
for him.
♪
- Take the core to full power.
[machinery whirring]
[core crackles and hums]
♪
- There seems to be a riot
going on.
You might want to reconsider
your orders.
- Vostok knows stein
is the other half of firestorm.
She's trying to merge
with him.
♪
Rip, once stein is inside
the reactor,
He will become
soviet firestorm.
Do you copy?
♪
I have the shot.
- Sara, don't do it.
- I don't have a choice.
It's the only way
to save star city,
The future.
- That's how a killer thinks.
And that's not you anymore.
♪
[core crackles and hums]
- Our energy...
♪
It yearns to be whole,
professor.
- Uh, without the splicer--
Aah!
Without the splicer,
you'll never be able to control
Our nuclear reaction.
You have to listen to me,
dr. Vostok.
Unless we un-fuse,
you'll end up killing us both!
♪
[devices beeping]
- Rip hunter must be a fool
To send you into my arms.
Come with me, chay-ara,
And I will find a way
to prolong your life.
We will live together
in eternity.
- No.
- No?
[gun clicks and hums]
- My answer
will always be "no."
♪
- Go.
- You want to kill me again?
Doesn't this game ever get
too old for you, gareeb?
- It's captain hunter,
if you don't mind.
- Oh.
- I'm here to make sure
you never build a firestorm...
And for my watch, actually.
You stole it from me
during a pagan blood ritual
Back in 1975.
♪
Ring any bells?
Ah, ah.
Slowly.
♪
- I have no desire
to kill you.
I want you alive.
I want you to see
the world burn.
I have looked so often
at your wife and son
These last 11 years--
Miranda and jonas,
Their faces etched
into my mind.
And when I finally get
to meet them,
I will let them know
that you and your friends
Are responsible
for their suffering.
- Not if I see you first.
♪
[device beeps]
How's it going up there?
♪
Sara?
Sara, are you there?
- Now you're on the comm?
We need to get out of here.
♪
- Whoa! Don't shoot!
Grey's in there!
- Lot of good
it would do anyhow.
- Man, screw this!
- What are you doing?
- I'm getting stein back.
- We'll cover you.
[gun powers up]
♪
- I know you're in there, grey!
- And he's begging for you
to save yourself.
- I wasn't talking to you.
[wincing]
I was talking
to professor stein.
- [chuckles]
- Your mind is stronger
than hers, grey.
I get it. I know why
you've been so hard on me.
You're trying to protect me.
You don't want to lose me
like you lost ronnie.
And that's why I know you're not
gonna let her kill me.
'cause I've had you inside
of my head,
And I know what a tough,
old son of a bitch you can be.
So you got to fight her,
because you and me,
We're firestorm, grey.
You and me!
♪
- [grunts]
jefferson!
You okay?
- Yeah, you?
- Yeah.
- Not for long.
- I tried to warn her.
Without the splicer and myself,
Her nuclear powers
are dangerously unstable.
- [screams]
- It appears dr. Vostok
is having a bit of a meltdown.
It's--it's fascinating.
- I think what he means
to say is "run."
- I'll have the jump ship
Waiting just beyond
the main gate.
♪
- [screaming]
["we'll meet again"
by vera lynn plays]
♪
- Courtesy of yuri the bear.
- How did you even have time
to steal this?
- There's always time
to steal.
- Thank you.
And just so you know,
I know you're more
than just a thief.
- You took a beating for me.
We're even.
End of story.
- Well, thank you.
- More drinking,
less feeling.
- A toast to the first time
We haven't completely ruined
the time line.
- Please tell me
that's true, gideon.
- The projections of the future
are back to normal.
- I'll drink to that.
- To rip.
To things not going
according to his plan.
- To the captain.
All: To the captain.
- All right.
- Hold on, jefferson.
You're not quite 21.
- Yo...
- In 1986, the drinking age
in russia was 12, so...
- Well, perhaps we can
let it slide this one time.
After all,
you were the hero today.
You saved my life.
- Oh, that?
That was no biggie.
- Having merged with an insane
russian scientist,
I now know how lucky I am
to have you as my partner.
- Partners.
- Stein doesn't know,
does he?
That I almost killed him?
- That I advised you
to kill him.
- It's funny.
When I was
in the league of assassins,
Failure to follow through
on a hit was unforgivable,
A thousand times
worse than death.
[sighs]
maybe I'm losing my edge.
- Or gaining a new one.
The fact that you didn't pull
the trigger speaks volumes.
You know, the safe move was
to kill martin
With the cold war hanging
in the balance.
I would like to think
it was your humanity
That stayed your hand.
- I'd like to think that too,
but I had some help.
[loud boom]
- What was that?
- We have been struck
with an explosive projectile.
- No kidding.
- Everyone get strapped in now!
We're in the temporal zone.
I don't understand.
No one should be able to--
[loud boom]
- You were saying?
[dramatic music]
- A scan of the vessel
Suggests that it is
the bounty hunter chronos.
- Oh, man,
this guy has impeccable timing.
♪
- He appears
to be following us.
♪
Firing countermeasures.
Countermeasures effective.
- Have we lost him?
- Yes, but not his missile.
Our aft shield
is gravely compromised.
- Initiating
evasive maneuvers.
♪
- Ah!
The vodka was a bad choice.
- Impact in three, two, one.
- [grunts]
- [screams]
- Sir, we've just been
knocked out of the timestream.
- What does that mean?
- It means we're crash-landing
In place and time.
♪
[ominous music]
Gideon, camouflage the ship.
This doesn't look like
the type of place
We want to linger out
in the open.
♪
- That looks a lot like
a palmer tech building,
But why does it have
a smoak logo on it?
- Wait.
This is star city.
I thought you said
the time line was safe.
- Yeah, star city was intact
in 2016.
This...
This is 2046.
- Don't move!
[gun clicks]
- oh, thank god.
- I said don't move.
♪
- It's me.
It's sara.
- Hey, oliver, look,
I-I know it's been a long time,
but don't you remember
That rip hunter recruited us
to become legends?
♪
- I never heard
of any legends.
- Greg, move your head.