- Hey.
- I have Mace, jackass.
Oh, it's you.
Listen, uh, sorry I didn't make
your thing last week.
I was stuck in Hell.
Don't sweat it, I didn't miss you.
Right.
Your mom said I could have the weekend.
Maybe we could bond, do stuff.
Come on, I'm trying.
All right, what is our father-daughter
weekend gonna look like?
I got tickets to the roller derby.
Should be lots of blood and cleavage.
I... I just remembered I actually
have a big history test on Monday,
so I can't. I gotta study.
Study. Mmm.
Very important, study. Yes.
Right.
What's that?
- That's a time machine.
- Is this...
Can I see it?
I thought you had to study.
Uh, well, it could be useful
for a history test.
Basically, this bucket of bolts
can travel anywhere in history.
We can catch a show
with The Ramones or Sabbath.
- Some Lita Ford of The Runaways?
- That, too.
You know, I have been fighting so hard
to get you out of Hell
and you are finally here.
I bet you're the only one on this ship
who's happy to see me.
Oh, nonsense.
As far as this sorry lot are concerned,
as soon as anyone stops
trying to murder them on a weekly basis,
they're best friends.
Either way, I am gone
the second Charlie uses that Loom
- to bring my mom back.
- Yeah.
What's she doing?
She said she wanted to get
into the right headspace, so...
- Huh.
- I totally get that.
There's nothing like a 20-second
meditation micro-sesh to zen out.
Did we miss the weaving?
I hope we didn't miss the weaving.
- Whoa! Gary, what... You have a dog?
- What?
We don't have dogs.
This is not a dog place.
I have a letter from my therapist.
We don't have therapists either.
Well, we should.
Going to Hell
generated a lot of anxiety.
Well, this says
this is his emotional support animal.
- It's signed and everything.
- I don't have time for this.
I've named him Gary Junior.
- Oh! He's made a tiny tinkle.
- Ew.
He isn't ship-broken.
Junior!
He's usually a very good boy.
Everyone, watch your step.
Oh!
Chasing tail now, are we, Gary?
That's a first.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, don't...
- Ah, bollocks.
Gary!
All right, almost ready.
I think. It's been a few millennia.
Okay, so, who's gonna
get the first weave?
- Her mother.
- Behrad.
Behrad first, John.
Yeah, look, uh...
Well, I, uh...
I made a promise to Astra, love.
I'm with Zari.
Behrad.
Who's Behrad?
I did not come back from Hell
to take a number and wait my turn.
He is my brother and he's part
of the team that found the rings.
We're getting him back first.
Okay, stop, stop.
Everybody, stop arguing.
You're all gonna get a chance.
But Sara's in a coma.
Charlie's gonna weave her out first.
All right, enough! Come on, guys.
This is exactly why I should have
left the damn thing broken.
Okay, I'm gonna choose. It's Behrad.
Now, goggles on, and let's get going.
Okay.
The ring of Clotho,
the maker of threads.
And extremely rad dresser.
The ring of Lachesis,
the weaver of destinies,
and a manipulative control freak.
And the ring of Atropos,
the cutter of threads,
and a heartless psychopath.
I see Behrad's thread.
But it's a bit of a tangled mess.
It's probably
because of all the time travel,
but I think it'll be all right.
All right.
Gideon, status.
Gideon?
Still assessing the damage,
Ms. Sharpe.
Running on backup power.
I'm sorry, Z.
- What happened?
- It didn't work.
- Okay, so we try again.
- I said it didn't work.
I've never tried to use the Loom
without my sisters.
I guess I need them.
Then let me try it.
Lachesis said she was preparing me
to be a Fate. Maybe I can...
Yeah, go ahead if you wanna
burn up from the inside.
Okay, what are we supposed to do?
Right now, we're just gonna sit tight
and try to fix the ship.
Well, that's great.
I could do some research
back at the house,
see if there isn't another way
to harness the rings.
I could use another set of eyes.
Yeah, I'm not going anywhere
until Behrad's back.
Wait. So, I left an empire in Hell
for "sit tight,"
for "do some research"?
Not good enough.
Apologies,
but no one's going anywhere.
The energy burst
created an anti-chronotomic field.
Time travel functions are offline.
So, no Jumpships, no Time Couriers?
- All out of commission.
- Great.
We're stuck.
Why are the lights out?
The ship better not be broken.
Unfortunately, I am.
I was damaged in an explosion
caused by the Loom of Fate.
You're kidding me.
I promised the kid we'd time travel.
Now she's gonna fail her exam.
Nope, it's fine. I'll be okay.
We have to find you a room to study in.
Um, did the computer
just say "Loom of Fate"?
Things are really bad, baby.
Ship's broken.
The Loom backfired and almost
killed Charlie. Everybody's bickering.
The chances of getting Behrad back
have never felt more slim.
We could really use your vision.
I could really use you.
Oh, my God, Sara, you're awake.
Ava?
I can't see anything.
Gideon, what's wrong with her eyes?
Unfortunately, Ms. Sharpe,
at my current power levels,
I am unable to offer a prognosis.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry? What are you
talking about? She's blind.
Reroute some power, Gideon.
Do something.
Ava, shh. It's okay, all right?
It's probably just temporary.
What if it's not? Lay back.
Who knows what else
is wrong with you.
Sara?
You were startled when we touched.
What happened?
Nothing.
Are you hiding something from me?
Always.
Come on, Sara.
Babe, it was just a weird reaction
to waking up from a coma.
Whoa, no, no, no, no, no. Where do you
think you're going? You can't see.
I trained in a blindfold for weeks
in the League of Assassins.
And nobody knows
how to fix the ship like I do.
Except for maybe Ray and Jax.
And Rip and Stein.
I guess Behrad's not bad either.
But you know what? None of them
are walking through that door,
so let's go.
So, what did I miss?
Oh, nothing much, actually. Just, uh...
Hey, Mick.
Hi.
Oh, uh, Lita, this is Sara Lance,
the captain.
Sara, this is Lita, my kid.
Oh! Uh...
Nice to meet you.
It's really cool
that there's a woman in charge here.
Uh, what, sorry?
I just said that it's really cool
that there's a woman in charge here.
- Uh-huh. Uh, yes.
- Good... Good to see you.
- Yes, it is.
- Come on.
What are you not telling me?
There's a kid on the ship?
I...
And a dog? Ava?
Gary has an emotional support animal.
He had a signed letter.
- That's not a thing.
- I don't know, baby. Come here.
Is that Behrad?
He sounds like a pretty nice guy.
Were you two close?
No. But we were starting to be.
I only just learned about
this big life he was living
and then I lost him.
But I'm getting him back, so...
Yeah, about that.
I think I might have a way to do it.
I'm listening.
You know, I think I'm probably good
for my test tomorrow.
I'd kind of just like to
look around the ship.
Uh, you got to hit the books.
Punched him.
Elbowed him.
Ooh.
Made out with her.
Okay, smart guy.
We're studying the French Revolution.
I've heard of it.
So, I have to compare and contrast
the American Declaration of Independence
and the French Declaration
of Rights of Man and Citizen.
Right.
So, does anybody on the ship
know history?
I know a guy.
Did I hear someone say the Declaration
of the Rights of Man and Citizen?
Hi. Dr. Nathaniel Heywood.
I specialize in deductive
historical reconstruction.
Now, while technically I am a doctor,
you can call me Professor.
Or Steel because...
I turn into it.
Whoa.
You're the coolest professor
I've ever met.
Most likely, yeah.
All right.
Let's study.
Well, we can't study
without snacks, right?
Gideon makes the best snacks.
Really? Can we have Ants on a Log?
Okay, Ants on...
Mick, can you be an absolute peach
and run to the Fabricator for us?
Now, what's happening with your sight
is a mystery, love.
Are you experiencing any more effects?
No, nothing.
Oh, well, we'll just have to
wait and see then.
And there is one other matter
to discuss.
Astra Logue is on the ship.
What?
Ava?
Uh, sorry, babe, but there was just
never a good time to tell you.
She was only supposed to
be here temporarily
and then the Loom didn't work.
She cannot be on the ship.
I mean, what if...
What if she goes on a stabbing spree?
A stabbing spree? Well, that seems
a little excessive, honey.
Look, she's made her choice.
She decided to throw in with us.
- Now, why would you doubt her word?
- Look, I don't know, okay? It's just...
It's a feeling.
John, I need you by her side 24/7.
Fine.
What if Charlie just wasn't warmed up?
She tried to reweave the most
complicated thread right out the gate.
What if she tries with an easier thread?
One that hasn't been complicated
by, well, time travel.
Like your mother's?
Exactly.
If she succeeds
on an easy thread like hers,
she might be ready
to try Behrad's again.
The thing is,
if it comes from me,
they might not buy it.
But if it comes from me...
they just might.
Again, I do apologize
that the Fabricator
is not functioning, Mr. Rory.
Oh, man. Must have been damaged
in the explosion.
Oh! Ants on a Log?
Are those for sharesies?
My kid.
Oh.
I see what's happening here.
You're new
to this whole parenting thing.
You know what?
I think you need some advice
from the Papa Gare.
Parenting is about doing the crap work.
No matter how degrading,
and never, ever once
hearing a word of thanks.
But you'll know in your heart
that they appreciate it.
Even if the thought
never crosses their mind.
Isn't that right, Gary Junior?
Oh.
Duty calls, as they say.
Crap work.
What is that?
Okay.
I've removed panel 16-QW45G.
Mmm.
No, I'm pretty sure I said 16-QW45T.
No, you said "G."
- No, 16...
- Okay. Yep. Finding T.
Sara?
Caught a case of blindness, I hear.
Yeah, and while Gideon's down,
I'm stuck like this,
but it's no big deal.
No big deal?
Right, you're the first mortal
to ever see a god's true form
and live to tell the tale,
and that is no big deal.
It's no big deal.
So nothing else
has been happening, right?
There's no other side effects?
Look, I know you're not
being honest with me, Sara.
I just wanna help.
What is she talking about, babe?
Look, it's nothing, okay?
I just...
I didn't wanna upset anyone.
What's so upsetting?
When I touch somebody,
I see people stabbed to death.
But it's probably
just some subconscious fear
that's being kicked up by the coma.
It's like a... It's a nightmare.
You've lost one kind of vision,
and you've gained another.
Sara, you're seeing the future.
Look, they're just nightmares, Charlie.
This can't be the future, all right?
- It's not possible.
- Why?
You're a Paragon of Destiny
who got radiated by godly light.
Why is it so impossible that you've
gained the gift of foresight?
Because we don't all die.
"We"? What do you mean, like,
we die in, like, 50 years,
or we die with me
wearing this exact outfit?
Option two.
- It's got to be Astra.
- Charlie.
Would you stop with the Astra thing?
She saved our lives in Hell, okay?
I'm not gonna just assume the worst.
What, that she's
some manipulative psychopath?
Well, she just tried to manipulate me
into coming in here
and begging Charlie
to use the Loom again, so...
Okay, well, that's not a crime.
Guys, the rings.
They're gone.
I found this in the trash chute.
Okay, that is a crime.
Gidget, play back internal monitoring
of the parlor, please.
My internal monitoring
subsystems have been disabled.
I'm afraid we have a saboteur on board.
Okay. Now I'm starting
to assume the worst.
Well, this was inevitable, wasn't it?
First thing that goes wrong,
and you all point the finger at me.
You know what, Astra? Slow your roll.
You wanted the rings
and now they're missing, so...
You're the only person
who doesn't belong on this ship.
Happily.
Look, I was with her the whole time,
all right? She never took the rings.
And besides, how is she supposed
to have sabotaged Gideon, eh?
We have no idea, John.
That's why she's here
and not out the airlock, okay?
- Come on, babe.
- Sorry, Astra.
You just spent too much time
with my sisters to be trusted.
I was shown more hospitality
in the deepest pits of Hell
than on this ship of fools.
Yeah, just sit tight, all right?
I got just the spell
to track this saboteur.
I never should have trusted you.
Did you really, though?
Or did you just run out of
other options?
Then there's Zari.
She's from the future.
She's supes cute,
and she can control air.
- What?
- Yep.
Ants on a Log.
Everybody here has a superpower.
Do you have a superpower?
I have this.
Your gun?
Uh, yes.
Your superpower is that you shoot a gun?
It shoots fire.
No, I know. I don't like any guns.
Why not?
I marched in protest of them.
Do you know how dangerous that thing is?
Well, that's the point.
Lita...
You know,
if it wasn't for your pops here,
we wouldn't be able
to travel through time.
Mick keeps the lights on.
Lights are off.
Oh, it's an unfortunate coincidence.
However, Mick funds this whole operation
through the simple act of stealing.
Oh, didn't you go to prison
for stealing?
Isn't that why you missed my childhood?
Damn it, Mick.
Sometimes they're just souvenirs.
Like, Mick, did you happen to steal
any French Revolution souvenirs
from Marie Antoinette?
Say yes.
Yes. Yes. Yes, I did.
Really? Can I see them?
Really?
Come with me.
Not bad, Nate. Not bad at all.
Mmm.
Not bad, Mick. Not bad at all.
Well?
Yeah, definitely sabotage.
Yeah, thought so.
Ooh. What happened here?
Hmm, we have a saboteur.
Hmm. I think I know who it is.
Oh, come on!
Oh, hello, Zari.
Hello, Astra.
Look, I'm sorry you are locked up.
Well, at least we have that in common.
We also both lost a relative
who we want back,
and got screwed when the Loom failed.
One of us
more than the other.
Okay, I know John is out there
trying to prove your innocence,
but we both know
how much you wanted those rings,
so why not just give them back?
Oh, wait. I see now.
You think you're here to interrogate me,
but that's not why you're really here.
No, that's literally why I'm here.
You're here because you've got Nate
wrapped around your finger,
and you thought you had John
wrapped around your finger, too...
but you don't.
What are you talking about?
When we were choosing
who to weave first,
he picked my mother.
Not Behrad.
You think you clocked something
between John and I,
and now you're using it
to manipulate me.
Wow.
You are devious.
So are you.
So why don't you use
that devious little brain of yours
and figure out
who really took the rings?
You think you can repair
the security cameras to find our thief?
Maybe, but...
whoever did this left a lot of damage
and not a lot of clues.
Ah, it seems we've all arrived
at the scene of the crime.
Well, this crime, anyway.
You know, we could, um...
We could just work together
to find our ring thief.
And how can I hope to defend Astra
by teaming up with her accusers?
We're all looking for the truth, John.
Yeah, well, some of us
can just see the situation
a little more clearly than others.
You okay?
- What's wrong?
- I...
It was me.
I kill everyone.
Baby,
you are an amazing assassin, okay?
But you're blind
and now you've warned us.
The idea of you killing everyone is...
Arrogant? Delusional? Just plain rude.
Yeah, and you're not
that kind of person.
Something is going on with me,
all right?
I went from seeing you all dead
to being the one responsible for it,
and I don't know why.
Look, you have to figure out
what is going on.
And until then,
I cannot be trusted, all right?
So promise me, no matter what I say,
you will not let me out of here.
Okay, I promise, honey.
I love you, all right?
We're gonna get to the bottom of this.
Just please take a breath.
And what exactly
are we getting to the bottom of?
I have no idea.
She has lost her damn mind.
- Don't touch anything.
- Copy that.
Whoa.
You really like to steal.
Don't tell your mom. Here.
This belonged to the headless lady.
So, I really dig the whole
Scrooge McDuck aesthetic,
but why not put your money in a bank?
Bank?
Too easy to rob.
Hold on, all of your money is here?
What if somebody robs this?
Let them try.
What about compound interest?
Okay, how much money is in here?
Uh, million? Billion.
And in ten years,
how much is that gonna be worth?
The same. It's gonna be worth the same.
If you invest it,
it'll be worth way more.
Sounds complicated.
What if you take the time machine
back to the start of the New York
Stock Exchange and invest it all then?
We could go and buy Manhattan
in the 1600s.
We can invent Bitcoin.
We can become partners
in getting freaking rich.
What the hell?
Room's off-limits.
So we're finally connecting,
and you're shutting me out?
You're a terrible father.
What are you doing?
Looking for footage of you
stealing the rings.
It doesn't exist.
Besides, I thought
the cameras were sabotaged.
I'm hacking the backup feed.
You hack?
Mmm, not so much me,
but a version of me that used to exist.
Do you think I could talk
to this other version of you?
Maybe she'd trust me.
Shush. She wouldn't.
You know, you could gain trust
the normal way by being trustworthy.
Well, things are getting crazy
out there. Sara just locked herself up.
Is locking someone up
her solution to everything?
She had a vision that she killed us all.
Oh.
Great. So I'm exonerated? I can go?
Mmm, no, you're staying in time-out
until we find out where these rings are.
Huh. Speaking of which,
backup feed is up.
Oh, my God!
Charlie, why'd you take the rings?
Mate, that wasn't me.
I mean, it was. But it wasn't.
Ooh. That does not look good for me.
You disabled the cameras?
Are you two in cahoots?
- No.
- No, obviously not.
Why would I hack into footage
that incriminates myself?
I don't know.
I just destroyed the Food Fabricator.
Which makes no sense 'cause I love food.
And let me guess,
you don't remember that either, eh?
No.
Oh!
I am guessing
you also don't remember that.
I can't believe that
I flushed the Loom of Fate.
Well, it's all right there
in the surveillance footage
Gideon apparently records
of our bathroom.
Ew.
Well, clearly you're all the culprits,
which, obviously, exonerates me.
No. Still no.
Yeah, this could all be mind control.
You think I'm behind it?
Yeah.
Who's there?
It's Papa Gare to the rescue.
Damn it, Gary,
what are you doing in here?
Oh, don't worry, I'm not gonna
let you out. I'm not a crazy person.
No, I'm serious.
You cannot be in here, it is not safe.
Well, neither is solitary confinement.
Gary, what are...
- What?
- Which is why,
after careful consideration,
I decided...
...you need my emotional support dog
more than I do.
I mean... I guess...
I guess it is kind of comforting.
Just promise me you'll treat him
like the little angel he is.
Kill him.
Wait.
Who... Who said that?
Said what? Gary Junior, stop barking.
Gary can't hear me.
Now, kill him.
Good girl. Now, kill them all.
Which is why...
...after careful consideration,
I've decided you need
my emotional support dog more...
Wait, wait.
Oh, my God, it's the dog!
Your dog... Your dog is a demon,
and it's gonna tell me to kill everyone.
But you know what?
I am not gonna listen.
I'm not gonna listen, dog.
I'd appreciate it
if you didn't raise your voice.
Gary Junior's a very nervous pee-er.
Hey!
- Hey, where is everyone?
- Sara, Sara, Sara, hey, hey.
Oh, bollocks. How did you escape?
Hey, look, I figured it out.
It's Gary's dog.
He's gonna make me kill everyone.
Okay, babe, just calm down.
You told us not to listen
to anything you say. The dog?
Look, I know, but just listen.
I can prove to you
that I am telling the truth, all right?
I had a vision that I killed Gary,
and then, in real-time, I saved him.
And the fact that he is alive right now
proves that I am not lying.
You were right
to lock yourself up, love.
Listen, I know that I sound crazy,
but you just take me to that dog
and you will see that I am not.
Gary, where is Gary Junior?
No idea.
He ran off shortly
after she screamed at him.
What? I was saving your life.
- From who?
- From me!
Okay, enough.
John, stay with Sara.
Gary, let's go find the dog.
Yes. Teaming up like old times.
Ew. Whoa. Gross. Can you wash
your hands first, please?
Okay.
Hmm, that's weird.
What the hell
is Gary Junior doing there?
Wait, go back to the other footage.
There. Zoom out.
Look, he's there every bloody time.
Oh.
Junior, here, boy.
Where are you?
He's not ship-broken,
he doesn't come when called.
Where the hell did you get him?
I don't wanna say.
Gary, my girlfriend's gone crazy,
and I'm looking for a dog to prove it.
I am beyond mad.
- Fine.
- Hmm.
I rescued him.
Oh.
From Hell.
You adopted a Hell Hound?
Well, when you say it like that...
I saw him when we got Astra.
He was all alone, I felt bad for him.
Oh, my God.
Sara was right.
This dog is making us go crazy.
This is absurd.
This is more absurd than
that StabCast I did on the Son of Sam.
Uh, wait, uh...
What does "Son of Sam" mean? 'Cause I...
I feel like Gary Junior
kept saying that to me in his barks.
What? No. It was a guy in the '70s
in New York. He killed a bunch of people
and later said
that a dog made him do it. Oh, my God!
You adopted Son of Sam's demon dog.
Oh, my God.
At least I didn't buy from a breeder.
Whatever he says, don't listen to him.
All I hear is annoying barking.
All I hear is
why I should murder you all.
And he's making some very good points.
- Nate.
Nate... No.
Whoa.
Hey, hey, hey!
Was I trying to murder you
with the stool?
- Yeah.
I am so sorry, guys.
What the hell are you doing?
It's a whistle only dogs can hear.
Why are you doing this to us?
Because I hate hats.
I hate stupid ties.
And I hate Gary.
But I rescued you from Hell.
From Hell?
Wait, are you working
for my sisters?
Uh, no, sweetheart.
I'm the Canine of Chaos.
I was gonna have you
murder each other,
but now I'm gonna kill you myself.
Whoa.
Get to the dais.
Don't let me out now!
Where'd he go?
What's that?
Yeah, it looks like
we owe you an apology, love.
Wait, that was Junior?
Let's just say
Gary has some explaining to do.
Come on, let's go stop this bloody thing
before it kills someone.
Gary, your hand's on my...
Just move it.
Sorry.
- Ow, Gary, that hurts.
- Sorry.
Gary, your hand is still on my...
No, I think that's me.
You can leave it if you're comfortable.
- It's... It really doesn't bother me.
- Can I put my hand back?
- Man, shut up, Gary!
- No.
Why are you all acting like I brought
the Son of Sam's dog here on purpose?
- That's who that demon is?
- Yeah.
- Let me out. I will get rid of him.
- How?
- You still don't trust me, do you?
- No.
Ava, just let her out.
If we'd listened to her
in the first place,
we wouldn't be in this
hot, uncomfortable mess.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Astra, I...
Uh, yeah. Hey, I think you accidentally
put the force field back up.
I think she knows.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh, come on!
You gotta be kidding!
You really shouldn't mess with someone
so comfortable with torture.
Lita. Open the door.
Go away, Becky.
I know what it's like
to be mad at your parents.
I lit mine on fire.
But... Let's talk about it.
We have nothing to talk about.
This is taking too damn long.
- We have to find that dog.
- Yeah, don't I know it?
And I could really use
another set of eyes. No offense.
Wait, wait, wait. What if we can use
my vision to search the ship?
- Yeah?
- Give me your hand.
Is it working?
- We have to get to the library.
- Come on.
Come on, open the door.
Lita!
Get away from her, you mangy mutt!
You idiot. I was born from fire.
What did you do?
I told it to attack me.
But at least I've got you
to protect me.
John, I'm blind.
But you're not deaf.
Now what?
To send the demon to Hell,
I need to know its true name.
Well, I'm pretty sure
it's not Gary Junior.
His name is Marchosias.
Astra, you dick!
No!
All right,
that should do it, Gideon.
We back online?
I'm happy to report
all functions are restored.
- Oh, my God!
- Ooh. You smell that?
- What...
- Ugh.
Gideon, what is that smell?
Gideon, did something die
in your ventilation system?
No. It's me.
I had to scour every inch
of the waste disposal unit,
but I found the rings.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Just... Just hold on.
Ugh.
Thanks, Gary.
Yeah, getting the rings was tough,
but fair punishment
for letting a Hell Hound onto the ship.
It's all right. All is forgiven.
You were obviously mind-controlled.
- I wasn't.
- Huh?
I just thought he was really cute.
- Of course you did.
- Yeah.
Well, this has been
very traumatic for me,
so, um, once the Time Couriers
came back online,
I, uh, got myself another
emotional support animal.
- You what? What?
- Oh, come on.
- What is it?
- It's a wittle wabbit.
- Oh! Babe, it's actually really cute.
- What?
I've named him Gary Junior Il.
Please tell me he's not from Hell,
though, because I'm gonna have to...
No, no, I wouldn't
make that mistake again.
- Okay.
- No, I got this wittle guy
from a mysterious carnie
who warned me
never to feed him past midnight.
Is one of those for me?
No. You're too young.
Oh, so, now you obey the law?
Never.
You're my kid, my responsibility,
and I only want what's best for you.
I was a little harsh before.
It's okay. You saved my life.
It's... It's no excuse. Let me explain.
Ah.
"The life of a criminal
is a life of misery.
I've spent years in jail
thanks to some red leather freak
- so fast that I couldn't..."
- It's okay, it's okay. I get it.
You just don't want me
to suffer in the ways that you have.
Should I, um, stop reading?
We have a common interest,
and I thought we could bond over it.
But I understand why we shouldn't.
Right. I'll, uh, take you home.
Why? I thought we were
spending the weekend together.
You wanna stay?
Yeah. Today wasn't so bad...
Dad.
Hmm.
- Roller derby tomorrow?
- No, absolutely not.
- The mall?
- Definitely no.
I see you're
making yourself comfortable.
You looking for John?
No. I am looking for you.
Why?
We're not friends.
I only saved your entire team
because it helped me.
And I only told Ava to let you out
because it helped us.
So we're even. We're the same.
No, girl, you released
Encores onto the world
just to get your own way.
So we're not even.
We'll keep using each other
till it stops suiting us.
I am comfortable with that.
Well, I'm not.
I don't know, let's see
if we can be more than that.
Come on, let me show you around
this weirdo ship.
I'm good.
Not planning on staying long.
But you get points for trying.
Okay.
So, I was thinking maybe later
we could try...
Try blindfolding you?
Stop reading my mind
or it's gonna get...
- Awesome?
- Oh.
Okay, let's just fix you up.
Come on, baby.
Okay, Gideon, do your thing.
Scan complete.
I do not detect any abnormalities
in Captain Lance's ocular region.
What do you mean, no abnormalities?
- Gideon, she's still blind.
- I'm sorry,
but there's nothing I can do.