- [alarm blaring]
- [gasps]
- [beeping]
- [speaking Spanish]
[muffled explosion]
- [electrical crackling]
- [grunts]
- [thud]
- [gasps]
[alarm blaring]
Gideon, what is it?
[Gideon] I didn't sound the alarm.
It was Mr. Rory, I believe.
Hey.
Zari.
Oh. You're not used
to my nighttime makeup.
I mean, no makeup.
Sorry to ruin the illusion. [sighs]
No, you, um...
You look just like her.
Oh.
You mean the other Zari.
Yeah.
I could change my hair if it would help.
Help what?
Whatever's happening down there.
- It's not my fault.
- Mmm.
- I was sleeping.
- Yeah.
It's natural.
Whatever you say,
Steel.
[hip-hop music playing]
[Mick over PA] Move your butts,
people, need you on the bridge.
All right, all right.
Got to finish my last set.
Is he doing all right, Gideon?
[Gideon] Mr. Tarazi
asked me to formulate
an ingestible gelatinous
cannaboid compound to help him sleep.
You make marijuana candy?
Sometimes I wonder if they're
ever gonna let me back into Texas.
[Agent Sharpe yawns]
Rory, what time is it?
[Gideon] Technically, time doesn't exist
in the temporal zone.
Thank you, Gideon.
I mean it's early.
I got a hit on the alien
that kidnapped Sara.
Why the hell didn't you wake me?
Um... Remember that sketch I drew,
the, uh, squid face?
I thought it was chicken wings.
Well, Gideon helped me find this photo
buried among some old KGB files.
A report about a crashed space alien.
It was redacted until Putin was ousted
from power in 2044.
"Redacted, ousted"?
Where are these words coming from?
I know words.
Look, uh, thanks for cleaning me up.
- [grunts]
- Thank you.
Oh, you even smell nice.
Gang, great news. Rory got a lead
on the alien that took Sara.
Hmm, shocking, honestly.
Hmm.
The pod we are looking for is picked up
by military forces
at 0600 hours,
sits en route as we speak.
The plan, rendezvous with it here.
Any questions?
En route, rendezvous...
[speaking French]
What?
This is great, Mick,
but shouldn't Gideon do the coordinates?
[Mick] Already set, numbnuts.
Wait, shouldn't we stop by John's,
pick up him and Astra?
- [thud]
- [all exclaim]
Let's move, it's a two-klick hike
through a thick jungle.
I love the intensity, but just a little
heads-up would be nice.
[Spooner] Okay, hold up.
I thought this was a time machine.
Why not bring us back an hour earlier?
Y'all can change out your PJs.
Oh, girl, we don't ask those questions.
[theme music playing]
Damn it, we forgot Behrad.
What did I tell you
about the Legends buddy system?
That hippie burnout
wouldn't want no part of this action.
Okay, Rory, what's the plan?
Cover me.
With what? I'm wearing slippers.
- [grunts]
- [gunshots]
Commie son of a bitch tried to shoot me!
Think it was a bad idea
letting Rory run point?
Eh, we've had messier missions.
- [grunts]
- [screams]
[horns honking]
[men grunting]
[both] Let's go.
[screams]
[engine starts]
[Spooner] I'm in, let's go!
Why is everyone shooting?
Oh, they started it!
[Mick] Time to check on the loot.
We're not bank robbers, Rory.
Wouldn't guess it by our use of guns.
Right to bear arms,
that is my Second Amendment privilege.
The right to tell you guns suck,
that's my first.
We're not gonna shoot the alien.
We're gonna talk to it.
What if it doesn't want to?
- Well, we roast it.
- Okay, just open the crate, Rory.
Huh. This alien pod's
different than the last one.
That's because it's not an alien pod.
It's a warhead from a Soviet SS-4
medium range ballistic missile.
Uh, Rory, where are we?
Uh, some island in the Caribbean.
Wouldn't happen to be Cuba,
would it, Mick?
Tell me you didn't take us to 1962.
Why, what happened?
- Oh.
- Oh!
You dropped us in the middle
of the Cuban missile crisis.
- And helped us steal a nuke.
- So?
This is the moment in history
when Americans and Soviets
came to the brink of nuclear war.
If we even sneeze...
Okay, nobody move.
It could be Armageddon.
But we can still find the alien
that'll help us find Sara.
You remembered to cloak the ship?
[telephone ringing]
Yes.
I see. Let him in.
Mr. President.
If this is about
the missiles down in Cuba,
I've been briefed.
The nuke's the least of our problems.
These photographs were taken
on the latest U-2 pass over Cuba.
[President Kennedy] What is that?
Mr. President, it would appear
that the Soviets have a new bomber.
Gideon, what's the latest in D.C.?
[Gideon] JFK just called for an
emergency meeting of his top advisers.
That's what I get for letting Rory
run point in a Cold War.
- It's all good.
- Is it?
JFK delivered
a master class in diplomacy
during the Cuban missile crisis.
How do I know this? Because I wrote
my doctoral thesis on it.
You want to go to Washington.
[accented English] With your permission,
- I'd love to throw the ball...
- Lose the accent.
- Way to wear that suit.
- [in normal voice] Thank you.
Aw, thanks, girl.
What happened to your totem?
Oh. Old one clashed.
- You want to go to Washington.
- Yes. I spent a lot of time on this.
Ah, morning, team. What did I miss?
Nate and Zari will make sure
that JFK doesn't start World War Ill.
The rest are chasing down
a displaced space alien in Cuba.
- Cool, I'll just be...
- Nah, you will just be with me.
Let's go. Come on.
Go see the Kennedys.
Good news, Captain, we found the pod.
It's on its way to Fidel Castro's
not-so-secret bunker.
Wow. You found the alien
using your powers?
No, CB radio.
[man speaks Spanish on radio]
[speaks Spanish]
[Mick] Mmm-hmm.
Right, easiest way in is here.
I'm guessing four guards.
- We blow the place to...
- Okay, I'll take it from here.
They won't let you
walk through the door.
It's exactly what they're gonna do.
- Let's go. Come with me.
- Why do you keep grabbing me?
Look, Captain, authoritarian leaders,
secret bunkers, nuclear missiles.
I'm not feeling the energy
of this mission.
Too bad, I need your energy.
Can't afford starting a nuclear war.
Hey, I'm just trying to help you
find your girlfriend.
Help me by getting the missile back
to the people that we stole it from.
- Wait, the Russians?
- Defeats the purpose of stealing.
Our job is to protect history.
Remember that next time.
[indistinct chatter]
[speaks Spanish]
[in English] Where are you going?
Sorry. We got turned around.
Is there another entrance?
Who is your companion?
Oh, uh... She's...
[in Russian accent]
I am Dr. Yevgania Shostenko.
At ease, comrade.
Who are you here to see?
Um... That's classified.
It's cool. We can come back later.
Oh, no, please. We enter now.
What kind of doctor are you?
Um...
[clears throat softly]
The kind who specializes
in extraterrestrial creatures.
Why didn't you say so?
Follow me.
We're supposed to give the nuke
to the Russkis, right?
Well, those ain't Russkis.
Um...
Permission to shoot a way
out of a sticky situation, Captain.
No, absolutely not.
We don't need
an international incident. Do you copy?
[Mick] Uh-huh.
Is that a yes grunt or a no?
[Mick] Uh...
That's what I thought.
Just let me do the talking, okay?
Sorry.
We, uh, found this rig in the jungle.
We're getting it back
to our Soviet comrades.
It's a stolen missile.
We'd hate for a nuke
to fall into the wrong hands.
I must take it
to El Comandante.
- El who?
- Fidel frigging Castro.
Sir, wouldn't the Soviets prefer
that we return it to them?
You don't understand.
The North Americans
have started a mutant invasion.
You will follow us.
Did you not hear my order?
Lead the way, comrade.
How does this help history again?
Captain's orders.
I liked it better
when you were in charge.
[engine starts]
- [Nate] I can't believe we're here.
- [Zari] Let's focus.
What's the plan?
Uh, I'm going to try to get into JFK's
inner circle by pretending to be
an international relations expert.
This way I could keep his finger
off the red button.
Okay, what about me?
Um... [exhales]
- You could pretend to be my...
- Secretary.
Bingo!
[in Southern accent] Yes?
The boys could use a fresh pot.
Oh. Right away, sir. [chuckles]
Who's the egghead?
[President Kennedy] Do I know you?
[Nate clears throat, chuckles]
Uh...
I doubt it.
Dr. Nate Heywood.
Harvard? Class of 1940?
Yes.
Go crimson!
Well, you can always use
another Harvard man in the huddle.
Isn't that right, there, Bobby?
Class of '46. Nice to meet you.
Uh, Nate Heywood.
[Bobby] Let me introduce you
to the brain trust.
We have Secretary of Defense.
Robert McNamara, Class of '39.
Nice to meet you.
Secretary of Treasury Douglas Dillon.
Class of '31.
Pleasure.
Now that the reunion's over,
we could get back to business.
General Kilgore here wants me to upgrade
our nuclear readiness to DEFCON 3.
This photograph shows the Soviets
have some sort of space-age bomber
parked off the coast of Florida.
[grunts]
[softly] Damn it, Mick.
- What do you think, Mr. Heywood?
- Me?
I, uh...
It's a spaceship.
It's probably made out of
plastic and plywood.
What did you say
your area of expertise was again?
- You know, Mr. President...
- Call me Jack.
Wow.
Jack, this reminds me
of the 1942 Princeton game.
Refresh my memory, son.
I was too busy fighting a world war.
Thank you for your service.
It was a 0-0 tie, a defensive stalemate.
Neither team put the ball in the air or
got close enough to kick a field goal.
Terrible game, both sides lost.
But when we're talking
about lobbing nukes at one another,
that is the only way both sides win.
[nurse] He's over there, right here.
Okay.
Ah. Just in time,
comrade doctora.
The anesthesia is working, and we're
ready to begin the vivisection.
Uh, the what?
The vivisection.
Oh. Oh, yes.
Uh, but first, can I have shot of vodka?
As they say in my country,
it steadies the hands.
No, there is no time.
El Comandante wants to know how we can
best kill these mutant invaders.
[Agent Sharpe] Okay.
Then, uh, let the vivisection begin.
[Behrad] Hey, uh...
- Team Pow wow.
- Hmm?
You're gonna kill the only alien
who can lead us to Sara?
No. I'm stalling
so I can come up with another plan.
[Behrad] Okay.
[Agent Sharpe] Okay.
[Behrad] I should have
mentioned this before,
but I do not like blood.
[Agent Sharpe] Relax, everyone.
I am just going to make
a tiny little incision. Yes?
[breathing shakily]
[Agent Sharpe] It's just a little
tiny bit of blood.
[Behrad gagging]
Okay, it's okay. Everybody relax.
It's, uh, perfectly normal.
[gas hissing]
[exhales heavily]
This area is restricted. Come back here!
Let me see.
I didn't realize it was you, sir.
- No worries.
- Let me show you to the bunker.
Fidel will be glad you're here.
[door opens]
Comandante, look who's here.
It's your old friend Che.
Wait. You think I'm Che Guevara?
I never said I was Che.
Then who are you?
I am Che's cousin, Jay.
[kisses]
Jay Guevara.
Just as your cousin
and I fought Batista's men.
You and I will fight
the CIA's mutant army.
Wait, you mean the alien?
Sent to kill me, no doubt.
It's like the Bay of Pigs
all over again,
except this time we've been invaded
by squids from space.
Sir, I have an Ambassador Popov
on the phone.
Ambassador, what a pleasant... Attack?
What attack?
You lost a nuclear missile?
What do you mean, stolen?
It sounds like you've been drinking,
so call me when you've sobered up.
What did he say?
Never believe it.
Russian ambassador just accused us
of attacking Cuba with...
A steel man.
- Is that...
- At least it's a good photo.
[Nate] Steel man?
This is even faker than the spaceship.
This is clearly a super-yoked guy
in silver body paint.
Actually, I have reason
to believe that it's real.
DARPA initiated a program
to develop a serum
that could turn a soldier's
flesh into metal.
It appears one of their
test subjects has gone rogue.
Why didn't anyone tell me
about such a program?
Eisenhower didn't think you boys
had the stones to deploy such a weapon,
but the good news is,
the weapon has been deployed for you.
But, sir, if the Russkis think
we sent a steel soldier
to sabotage their missiles,
they might do something stupid
and launch 'em.
What do you suggest I do?
We launch a preemptive strike
against Cuba.
We take their little island
out of the equation.
Mr. President, this reminds me
of the '39 Yale game...
Well, you are the quarterback, Jack.
You're calling the shots.
Take us to DEFCON 3, General.
[whispering] Yay, one less DEFCON.
[whispering] That means that
we're one step closer to nuclear war.
Well, that makes no sense.
- [gas hissing]
- [all laughing]
- [Agent Sharpe] Can I tell you a secret?
- Sí, sí.
I'm not really Russian.
- Are you a North American spy?
- Worse.
I'm a clone from the future. I snuck
onto the base to steal the alien.
[both laughing]
I don't even know
why I'm still talking like this.
Get comfy. I'll be right back.
You know, the CIA had a secret plot
to try to put a bomb
in one of my cigars once.
Not cool.
But now,
I have a secret weapon of my own.
A nuclear missile.
I'm so done being a pawn
in this game of chess
between the Americans and the Soviets.
If Cuba is attacked by squids,
I will wipe Washington
off the face of the earth.
Ooh!
Candy? [grunts]
- I have never seen this brand before.
- They're not for everyone.
[quietly] Strap in, dude.
[all snoring]
[Mick and Spooner grunting]
[soldier chuckling]
Fidel will decorate you two
as heroes of the Republic for this.
Great! I'll be sure to put
that one in my trophy case.
[high-pitched ringing]
Headache? That time of the month?
Very funny.
No, I'm being serious.
My daughter. She has the same thing.
Oh. That's very sweet of you, then.
- But it's not my period. It's the alien.
- [high-pitched ringing]
[alien grunting]
I think my powers are getting stronger.
It's almost like I can hear it talking.
What's it saying?
[alien screeching]
Don't wake up. Please, not now.
Oh, it is pissed.
We gotta find Ava.
[roars]
[screeching]
I don't wanna hurt you, all right?
I... I need to know
where you took my girlfriend.
[grunts]
[snarling]
[Mick] Let's get out of here.
[Fidel Castro] If I can force
the Soviets out of Cuba,
then all the missiles will be mine.
Would you mind if I played
you a song, Comandante?
I would have you killed if you didn't
play me a song, Jay Guevara.
[laughing]
[strumming guitar]
[playing soft melody]
[singing]
Well, I've been smiling lately
Dreaming about the world as one
And I believe it could be
Someday it's going to come
Oh, peace train sounding louder
Glide on the peace train
[vocalizing]
Come on the peace train
Peace train, holy roller
Everyone jump on the peace train
[vocalizing]
Come on the peace train
Yeah, yeah
[inhales deeply]
Oh, I must call Kennedy at once.
He and I are brothers,
just like you and I are brothers.
We are all humans,
placed on this one fragile planet.
And the only way forward is
love!
[laughing]
[screeching]
How about another tune?
I told you that thing
was sent to kill me!
If it's war the Americans want,
it's war they shall have!
Prepare the missiles
for launch immediately!
[groans]
Oh, damn it!
We forgot Behrad, again.
[grunting angrily] Sí!
Guys, I thought you might like
an update on El Comandante.
Wait, you're with Fidel Castro?
We're super tight. The problem is he
thinks the alien was sent to kill him.
- Why would he think that?
- It tried to kill him.
Report back to me as soon as
the missile has been fueled.
Oh, and also, he's preparing
to launch a nuclear missile at D.C.
- Why does Castro have a nuke?
- 'Cause we gave it to him.
- You said no shooting.
- I said... [gasps]
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, this is not happening.
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
Let's hope that cooler heads
are prevailing in D.C.
One of our boys flying over Cuba
reports a missile being fueled.
Has Khrushchev lost his mind?
It appears that the missile is no longer
in the Soviets' possession, sir.
Huh. Castro's got it.
History is not
supposed to go down like this.
Say there, Jackie,
how would you and the kids feel about
getting out of town for a couple days?
Uh, I think Jack's starting to crack.
Is Hyannis Port within the blast radius?
There is no time for this,
Mr. President.
If those Russkis catch us
blinking now, we're through.
What if this is just
a big misunderstanding?
What if those Russkis want us
to hit Cuba so they could hit us?
Those clever commie bastards.
Our only defense is to attack the USSR.
Jack, that is insane.
Take us to DEFCON 2.
Yes, sir.
Sir, maybe I can help.
My secretary can type
120 words a minute.
This way, we could get
the bombers in the air faster.
I thought
you were just another pretty face.
Oh, my gosh.
[Zari clears throat]
This is a direct order
from the President of the United States
to the entire Strategic Air Command.
I've never seen someone type
with just their thumbs.
I want every B-52 we have headed towards
their primary targets
in the Soviet Union.
Should we lose contact
due to a first strike from Cuba,
it should be considered
a direct attack from the USSR.
Full retaliatory measures must then
be taken without any further orders,
because we'll all be dead.
[typing]
- Did you get all that, sweetie?
- Oh, every last word, sir. [chuckles]
Guys, why is Fidel
starting World War Ill?
[Agent Sharpe] He thinks
you are invading Cuba with aliens.
[sighs] Look,
Behrad's trying to cool him down.
Comandante.
You have a phone call.
It's Che Guevara.
[Fidel Castro] Hello, old friend.
Yes, I know. The news
is very scary at the moment.
Oh. [chuckles]
Yes, I wish you were here, too.
But I have a comrade-in-arms right
next to me who's the next best thing.
- [explosion]
- [soldiers grunt]
Tell the CIA
to call back their squid soldiers
or else I'll launch the nuke.
Oh, my God.
[exhales]
- Sounds like you're up, Rory.
- I thought I was in the dog house.
That's when we were trying
to finesse the situation. Plans change.
- You want us to kill the alien.
- We don't have a choice.
Spooner, help him track it.
We need to deescalate the situation
and get history back on track.
Screw history! You kill the alien,
you kill any chance of finding Sara.
If we don't,
Castro starts a nuclear war
and Sara doesn't have
a home to return to.
I do not have time
to game this out with you, Rory.
- We will find another way to find Sara.
- Right.
Lot of big brains in this ship.
I'll just stick with what I know.
Shouldn't have cleaned me up.
I'm better off doing what I do best.
Being a goon, killing people.
Yes.
It's exactly what I need.
Right. At least I know
what I'm here for.
[sighs]
Alien's gone.
- [high-pitched ringing]
- No, it's still here. I can sense it.
Base is wide open. Why would
the stupid thing still be here?
It's not stupid.
It's looking for something.
It wasn't right for Ava
to try to pin this all on you.
- I don't give a rat's ass.
- You were just trying to find Sara.
I was pretending to be somebody I'm not.
You're going to go back
to being a dumb drunk, that it?
Yes.
[alarm blaring]
Is that...
[alien grunting]
What's it want with the nuke?
- [high-pitched ringing]
- I think it wants to get away from here.
Like, off this planet.
Wait here.
Hey, dummy.
[snarls]
You really think you're gonna
hitch a ride home on that thing?
It's a missile.
[roars]
[Mick groans]
Go ahead, eat me,
but you're not gonna get home.
[Spooner] Let him go!
I know you understand me.
Put him down or I blow your ass away.
That thing is not a spaceship.
But lucky for you, I've got my own.
[screeching]
Keep talking. It understands you,
it just doesn't trust you.
You're not as dumb as you look.
[snarls]
The alien wants
its own spaceship, not yours.
[grunts]
[choking] I can take you to it.
But under one condition.
You help me find my friend.
[grunts]
[roaring]
[garbled grunting]
She's asking you a question.
She?
Yeah, she wants to know
what kind of fuel the Waverider uses.
Sounds like we got
a long trip to find the captain.
Comandante?
- What are you doing?
- What does it look like?
You want to start World War Ill.
You will kill all of us.
[beeps]
[alarm whooping]
History will absolve me.
[Zari] Call for you, General Kilgore.
Thank me?
What for?
What three-day weekend?
And who all received that order?
The entire Strategic Air Command?
Should've known that
- she was too good to be true.
- Whoa!
This secretary has been
countermanding your order, sir.
If Fidel Castro launches that missile,
you have only got seven minutes
to order a counterstrike
against the Soviet Union.
I thought you said
all our B-52s are still on the ground.
As much as it pains me
to have to ask the Navy for help...
What is that?
That is a nuclear football.
Sir, that allows you to contact the
nuclear submarine captains directly
and order an all-out
strike against the Soviets.
Jack, they don't want
a nuclear war any more than you do.
[machine clacking]
There's a report
of a missile launch from Cuba.
Clock is ticking, sir.
Somebody get me Premier Khrushchev.
- This has to be a mistake.
- You want to negotiate?
They were right about you. You are soft.
Well, if you don't have the guts
to stand up to those commies,
I guess I'll have to do it myself.
- You take one more step...
- Or what?
[President Kennedy] The steel man.
You're damn right.
But Jack, I didn't go rogue.
I'm here to protect the world
from guys like him.
I'm guessing your accomplice here
ain't quite so bulletproof.
Come on.
Boys, huddle up. Huddle up.
Okay.
We gotta get that
nuclear football back, boys.
Hey, Bobby, what was that play
we ran against Dartmouth back in '39?
Guess we don't need you anymore.
Rude!
[Kilgore] Thirty seconds
for the safeties to be released.
All we gotta do is
to keep that football
out of the hands of those
lily-livered Harvard boys.
Okay, crimson on three.
[men] One, two, three, crimson!
Hike!
[all grunting]
This is fun.
- [back cracks]
- [groans]
My back!
[groans]
[distorted] No!
[grunts]
[Nate] Intercepted!
Whoo!
[both panting]
To tell you the truth, sir...
this football belongs in your hands.
[machine clacking]
The missile's headed straight for us.
It'll be here any second.
The safeties are off.
You still have time to strike back.
This game ain't over yet, Mr. President.
It's not a damn game.
Whoever launched that missile,
it was a mistake.
If you strike back,
they're going to strike back at us.
That's why it is called
mutually assured destruction.
Clearly you do not
understand the concept.
Listen, Jack,
just because we're about to die
doesn't mean that we have to take
the whole damn world with us.
You're right.
I'm spiking this football.
[sighs in relief]
[Zari] Um...
Are we about to die?
Yeah. [sighs] But at least
we gave it the old college try.
Well, I ain't going out without a fight.
[grunts]
[sighs]
[rumbling]
Take that, you commie bastards!
[rumbling dies down]
Um...
I think we can let go of our hands.
You did it, Jack!
You saved us all!
[laughs]
Luck of the Irish, I guess.
- Come on, buddy, get in there. Yeah.
- Nah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah! Ah!
[all cheering]
Go crimson!
[Gideon] Captain, I'm detecting an
unusual level of radiation on the ship.
Rory.
Are you sure it's safe for us
to be carrying plutonium around?
No.
[yelps]
[grunts]
Oh, uh... This is not how it looks.
[sighs] I know. I owe you an apology.
You saved the entire world
from nuclear Armageddon, Rory.
- Well, I, uh... I had help.
- Yeah.
[grunts, clicking]
It doesn't say much, does it?
Oh, she does. You'd be surprised.
- Did you say "she"?
- Mmm-hmm.
Huh.
So what's the plan?
[Mick] Well, she's hooking some kind
of turbocharger to the Waverider.
Why would she help us?
I promised her I'd help her
find her ship.
Okay.
Do you trust her?
- No, it's why I'm going alone.
- Al...
- Uh, no, but that...
- But no.
You said your job is to protect history.
I also said your job
wasn't to think for yourself.
But had you listened to
any of my orders,
we'd have absolutely
no hope in finding Sara.
So, I...
[sighs]
I guess you got this.
Stop saying nice things.
You just bring me back my girl, okay?
Hmm.
Good luck, big guy.
Sorry, what happened to the ship?
It should be somewhere around here.
[sighs] God, these shoes are killing me.
And this stupid hair.
I look like her again, don't I?
I hate that I'm a reminder
of everything you lost.
You're not.
I mean, I guess at first.
But now?
Now you just remind me of you.
- Wasn't there a Waverider here?
- Hmm.
- [Nate] Hey!
- [gasps]
Well played, gang. How'd you manage
to avert nuclear Armageddon?
- Sports analogies.
- Pot gummies.
- Ah. Very on-brand, both of you.
- Thank you.
Hey, where are Rory and Spooner?
That son of a bitch stole our ship.
Well, very on-brand, Mick.
[Nate] Oh, come on.
Thank him for stealing
the warhead out of the missile
that Fidel launched on D.C.
- Thanks, Mick.
- [Zari] Hmm.
Oh! And who made a deal
with the alien to take it to its ship
as long as it took us to Sara.
- So he stole the ship?
- But it's...
Sorry, my phones were on that ship.
So was my...
Oh, thank God.
How are we gonna catch aliens now?
So, so sorry, but where
are we going to live?
- [both] Constantine's house.
- John's.
Sweet. I could use a little R&R.
All of us under the same roof
with John and Astra.
Could be a real bonding experience.
- He's gonna hate it. Let's leave.
- Okay.
Damn. Rory had the right idea...
Hmm? Hmm?
[Agent Sharpe] Nobody wants your drugs.
[sighs] Mom.
Listen up. Before we start
this little journey of ours,
let's get a few things straight.
Keep your slimy tentacles
off my stash, understand?
[grunting]
That better be a yes.
[grunts]
If you're going to run
your ugly mouth off this whole trip,
we're gonna have problems.
I was just asking if you had
anything stronger on board.
Don't mind if I do.
[exhales]
Here's to long journeys.
[theme music playing]