GIDEON: This season,
on Legends of Tomorrow...
RIP: I've assembled you all
because I need your help.
The future of the world
is in peril
because of Vandal Savage.
DRUCE: You've turned your back
on the very institution
you were meant to serve.
RIP: The Time Masters.
They refuse to take action
against Savage
because he didn't pose
a threat to the timeline.
DRUCE: The Oculus not only gives us
a window into time,
but the ability to shape it.
RAY: If the Oculus is what
they're using to control us,
then, we need to destroy it.
(YELLING) Shut it down!
There are no strings on me.
He traded his life for ours.
He was a hero.
GIDEON: Unfortunately, Vandal Savage
has already succeeded
in murdering Miranda and Jonas.
ATOM: Savage still has Carter
and Kendra.
This is a Timeship.
A little gift from our friends.
I no longer need
to rule the world.
I now have the ability
to change it.
RORY: What are we doing back here?
Savage has a Timeship
courtesy of the Time Masters
and the timeline is unclear
due to our destruction
of the Oculus, meaning--
Savage is lost to history.
Which is why
I've brought you all home.
Mission's not over, man.
Jax is right. We've lost Savage before.
We'll find him again.
And then what? We have
no way of killing Savage,
particularly now that Kendra and
Carter are in his possession.
Assuming that they're still
alive, which is highly unlikely.
So that's it?
We're just giving up?
I'm on my way to the Refuge
to retrieve your younger selves
and return them to the timeline.
It will be as if you never left.
You think that we can just
return to our old lives,
and then pretend like
none of this ever happened?
That might be a tad difficult.
I had to bring you back to
May 2016, not January 2016.
Great. So what you're saying is
for the last five months
my mom probably thinks that
I'm dead. Thanks a lot, man.
Why?
Why the change of plans, Rip?
If you're getting back on that ship,
we get back on that ship.
In truth, I never left it.
I'm sorry
for all that I've asked of you
and that it all came to nothing.
I wish you all well.
I never liked that guy.
Hello? Hello?
Dad!
Hey.
- Hi, Daddy.
- Baby.
When did you get back?
I just got back.
I tried calling,
but nobody was answering.
I was at Laurel's
but she wasn't there.
Where is everyone?
It's Damien Darhk.
He's causing problems.
Good to know nothing's changed
in five months.
Dad?
What's wrong?
Is everything okay?
No, baby.
You're starting to scare me.
Damien Darhk was in prison,
and he escaped.
And everyone tried to stop him,
but your sister...
Honey, she, um...
No, Dad, no.
I'm sorry, baby.
- No. Dad. No.
- Come on, I got you.
(SOBBING)
I got you.
- (GRUNTS)
- (ALARM BLARING)
You idiot, we were in the clear!
BROOME: He was going after us.
On foot!
You shot him and wasted ammo.
Cops are coming.
You wanna yell at me some more
or should we both
get outta here?
RORY: Neither.
(YELLS)
MAN: Hey, Mick.
Oh! It's me. (CLEARS THROAT)
It's Ray.
(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
I thought we should talk.
Drive.
You didn't waste any time
getting back to your old habits.
I like stealing stuff.
It makes me feel good.
Do you ever think that
maybe you weren't meant
to do this anymore?
What do you want, Haircut?
To apologize.
Sort of.
For Snart.
I was the one who
was supposed to die
and I can't help feeling--
It wasn't your fault.
It was his.
Son of a bitch never did
anything without a plan.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe he wanted this.
What are you doing
with your hand?
Maybe he wanted us to.
you know, be partners.
I think I'm gonna be sick.
I think Snart knew.
He knew that I'd keep
an eye out for you
and you'd keep
an eye out for me.
While doing what?
What we haven't finished doing.
"What was
H.G. Wells' childhood nickname?"
- Bertie.
- (SIGHS)
Incredible. You've gotten
every answer correct tonight.
Since when did you become
such a history buff?
I guess I've developed
a passion for it recently.
During your sabbatical?
You hardly ever talk about it.
Martin?
I know, I'm-- I'm sorry.
My sabbatical was, um...
I left some
very important work unfinished.
The ship's not gonna
be here, Grey.
We saw it take off, remember?
Yes. And doing so
would've left...
Quantum signature.
That's what
I've been trying to tell Mick.
Radio beacon.
Quantum entangler.
Boring.
When do we
get in contact with Hunter?
PROFESSOR STEIN:
Ms. Lance, are you all right?
How do we get
the Waverider back here?
Hi, Daddy. We miss you.
MIRANDA: And love you.
JONAS: (CHUCKLES) And love you.
GIDEON: Captain, I'm sorry to interrupt.
Tell me you've located Savage.
No. But we have received
a transmission
from 2016 Star City.
I don't understand.
It should've worked.
Did you account
for sub-space interference?
It's the first thing
I thought of.
Did you adjust for
temporal polarity?
Raymond, you insult me.
Can you reach the Waverider
or not?
- We're working on it.
Actually, guys,
I think it just worked.
Ha!
I thought I made my intentions
perfectly clear.
And we wish to be equally clear
about ours.
Do you mind?
Just checking to see
if you're real this time.
JAX: You're not ditching us again.
When the mission's over, then
we can all go our separate ways.
And this mission is not over.
Yeah, just curious
how much headway you've had
tracking Savage
without all of us.
None.
But neither have I got
myself into bar fights
in 1975 and the Old West,
put dwarf-star technology into
the hands of terrorists,
or got myself turned into
a scary bird monster.
We get your point. Now get ours.
That ship's not taking off
without us. You got that?
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Halt!
Please, don't shoot!
Don't shoot!
What the hell are you doing
out here, lady?
I was being held captive.
- By Nazis?
- No. Worse.
- Your helmet...
- What about it?
I've seen it before.
Paper. Do you have paper?
Something to write with?
- Lady, I think you're in shock--
- Please!
Yeah.
So if it wasn't Nazis,
who were you running from?
I need your helmet. Now!
(GASPS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
I'm sorry, my love.
But this game is not over yet.
Despite my wishes
to pursue Savage alone,
it seems
that you're all intent on
seeing this thing through
till the bitter--
RORY: Oh! Speaking of "bitter."
You knew.
You dropped us off five
months later because you knew.
Knew what?
You knew
that Laurel was gonna die.
And now you're gonna
take me back
and I'm gonna save my sister.
- I'm afraid that I--
- You should be afraid.
I can't allow you--
I don't care about the timeline!
You're taking me back now.
Look, Sara, I'm sure there's
a valid reason why Rip didn't--
Stay out of this.
What the hell, Rip?
Mr. Rory,
take Ms. Lance to sleep it off.
Not to dismiss
what just happened,
but we do have to find Savage.
Assuming that Kendra and Carter
are still on his Timeship,
he could--
Be anywhere in time and space.
Well, that narrows it down
a lot.
Sorry.
- Was this always over here?
- No, it lives over...
- Did you put it there?
- No, man.
Did you?
Dude, it's just a helmet.
- Chronometric repositioning.
- What?
Temporal changes can,
on occasion,
reverberate through
the timeline,
physically moving an object
from one place to another.
- Gideon.
- GIDEON: Yes, Captain.
Plot a course
for Saint-Lô, France, 1944.
- Why then?
- Because that's where Kendra is.
JAX: How's that possible?
She sent us a message
through time.
Go ahead. Say it.
Astonishing.
(GRUNTING)
(SAVAGE CHUCKLES)
I brought you some company.
Oh! He might be
a little disoriented,
after the way
he came out of stasis.
I know you.
SAVAGE: Oh, you remember her?
Well, at least his mind
isn't fully gone.
Hey, stay away from him!
I'm going to kill you.
You've had 4,000 years to do so
with no success.
What are you doing?
Your blood
is the key to unlocking
the Thanagarian technology.
"Thanagarian"?
The alien species which gave
the three of us our powers.
They sent three meteorites containing
technology beyond human understanding.
When they are activated
by your blood,
I will be able to erase
time itself,
and travel us back to 1700 BC.
No! No!
SAVAGE: I will begin
my immortal life anew.
Only this time,
I won't be content
to whisper
in the ears of powerful men.
This time,
I will be the one with the power.
I will be a God.
Please try very hard
not to kill me.
Rip, please take me back.
SARA: I need your help.
I need to save my sister.
And you know that
I would do this for you, Sara,
but I just can't.
I have never asked you
for anything.
And you, of all people,
should understand.
You have tried everything. We...
We have tried everything
to save your family.
And I would not wish the pain
of that failure upon anyone.
I would rather live
with that pain than this.
That's just the thing, Sara.
Look, if you were able
to try to save Laurel,
then you wouldn't be
alive at all.
Fine. I don't care.
When we left, when I recruited you...
(STUTTERING) We altered the timeline.
Now, had it remained the same,
then Damien Darhk would've...
He would've killed
not only you and your sister,
but your father as well.
(STUTTERING) But, Rip,
if we go back
and we take the team...
The outcome would
be exactly the same.
You don't know that.
I'm afraid that I do.
- No. There's gotta be a way.
- Uh... (SIGHS)
Rip, I have to be able to
do something.
I'm so sorry.
(SOBBING)
Look, I can't...
I can't do this
without my sister. I can't--
Oh, yes, you can.
You are one of the strongest
people I have ever met, Sara.
(CRYING)
Laurel... Laurel may be
beyond your saving,
but Kendra and Carter,
they might not be.
GIDEON: Captain, we are prepared to make
the time jump to 1944.
We're on our way, Gideon.
GIDEON: We've arrived in Saint-Lô.
No sign of Kendra yet, but
I have located Vandal Savage.
And he does not seem
to be alone.
(IN GERMAN)
(LAUGHS)
(EXCLAIMS)
- (GUNS FIRING)
- (SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
SAVAGE: Get them!
Keep Savage
and our Nazi friends occupied.
Gideon has detected
a temporal signature
consistent with a Timeship.
If Kendra and Carter are alive,
that is where they're gonna be.
FIRESTORM: Yeah, I see it.
(YELLING)
- (GRUNTING)
- (SWORD CLINKING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
- Jax!
- You miss me?
(GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
Is he still nuts?
No, he's okay.
Take this to the ship.
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
What the hell was that?
PROFESSOR STEIN: You transmuted
the molecular properties of the rifle.
What does that even mean?
Okay. Let's get out of here.
(HAWKGIRL GRUNTS)
Kendra's down!
Rip, we're kind of
outnumbered here!
Fall back!
Staying here to fight Nazis
is exacerbating the damage
that we have already done
to the timeline.
- But Kendra--
- Is alive, thankfully.
And we will rescue her
in due course.
I hope.
So this is a spaceship?
It's a Timeship. But, yes, it
does also travel through space.
You've seen it before, Mr. Hall.
That used to be my name.
Carter Hall?
There really is
rather a lot to fill you in on
and we really
do not have the time.
- What about--
- RIP: Kendra.
Yes, we need your assistance
in locating her and Savage.
Perhaps we can start with what
Savage was doing in 1944.
He said something about, um,
Thanagarian technology...
"Thanagarian"?
The Thanagarians are a race
of extraterrestrials.
He also said that
this "technology"
was actually three meteors.
GIDEON: Captain, I have surveillance
footage which might be relevant.
Thank you, Gideon.
JAX: I've seen that rock before.
Savage had one of those in 1958.
He took our blood.
He said he would use it
in a ritual to erase time,
take the world back to 1700 BC.
What are you doing?
Come on, man.
We gotta try it again.
That thing that we did
in World War II?
- It's called "transmutation."
- Yeah.
PROFESSOR STEIN: It's a similar process
by which our uniform
materializes when we merge.
But at the moment,
we need to focus on figuring out
what Savage is planning.
Come on. Just the once.
Is that Raymond
and Kendra's lucky vase?
I don't know. I just
found this junk lying around.
Come on.
Don't you think that turning
something into something else
might come in handy?
All right. One time only.
Okay, just the once.
All right.
(EXHALES)
PROFESSOR STEIN: You need to focus,
Jefferson.
Why do you always say that
like I'm not focusing?
Just do what you did before.
Before, we had a Nazi trying
to kill us. This is just a vase.
(SIGHS) Come on.
(SIGHS)
I never thought
I'd utter these words,
but I think we need a Nazi.
Not funny.
Look, the reason
I keep telling you to focus
is because transmutation
is a literal function
of mind over matter.
Dude, this sucks.
Why do I always gotta
be in the driver's seat?
Don't despair, Jefferson.
This is only our second attempt
at transmutation
and you know what they always
say, "The third time's a charm."
What?
The third time.
Three rituals.
I think I know what Savage
is planning to do.
(SCOFFS)
PROFESSOR STEIN: I've figured out how
Savage plans to erase time.
I believe he intends to detonate
each of these meteors
in a different time period.
How can you destroy the world
three times
in three different times?
You can't. It would create
a temporal paradox.
Which would result
in a time-quake
that would return the Earth
to the point of the first
chrono-thermic reaction.
Ancient Egypt.
JAX: Okay, it's official.
This is
the craziest bad-guy plan
in the history of bad-guy plans.
I don't think
that sanity is a yardstick
by which Vandal Savage
can be measured.
Okay, so which time periods
are we talking here?
You said Savage
was in possession of
one of these meteorites in 1958.
PROFESSOR STEIN: That was a year
of a rare alignment
with the Earth and Thanagar.
Evidently, he got hold
of a second meteorite in 1944.
Which would be useless
to him in a year
where the Earth and Thanagar
weren't in alignment.
Now, if my math is correct,
and trust me, it is,
the next two years that Earth
and Thanagar are in sync
are 1975 and 2021.
But Savage still has to do this
in three different time periods?
That's the beauty of immortality,
Jefferson. He can.
PROFESSOR STEIN: He can literally
be in three places at once.
It can't be...
It can, thanks to time travel.
And it's because of time travel
that I know you're here.
You're out here tonight
because you've felt an imminent
presence of something.
Uh, a meteorite?
And I am going to give you
a use for it
which will give us the power
to rewrite destiny itself
and change the course
of the entire world.
So if Savage plans on blowing up
the world three times,
- how do we stop him?
- We don't.
PROFESSOR STEIN: We kill him.
CARTER: How?
We've always known that only
you or Kendra could kill Savage
using items exposed, as you
were, to the meteors' radiation.
Now, the radiation
works both ways.
It gave Savage
his immortality, but--
It also makes him vulnerable.
PROFESSOR STEIN: And Savage is about
to unleash the radiation
from three meteorites
in three different time periods.
Triple the exposure.
Yes. Which should be sufficient
to render Savage mortal.
And then all we've gotta do
is kill Savage three times.
Indeed. Gideon can navigate
the Waverider
and we can split
into teams of two.
One in 1958, one in 1975,
and one in 2021.
Open it.
Did you know that this is
one of the original meteorites
which fell upon
the Middle Kingdom?
Drawn from the ground
after millennia,
straight into Nazi hands.
The object that has bound
the two of us together
for 4,000 years
has the power to take us back
to where it all began.
But this time,
I will be the pharaoh, and you--
Will hate you.
Like I've always hated you.
(LAUGHS)
Patience, Mr. Hall.
All our teams
need to act simultaneously.
I think that's a comet
or something.
SAVAGE: It's a meteorite,
point of fact.
I was drawn to it as well.
When can I kill him?
ATOM: We have to wait for
the meteorite to go critical.
When's that?
ATOM: When he starts the ritual
at all three time periods.
Um, we got a nuclear bomb here.
SARA: Professor, Jax, we need you!
Oh, man, I forgot
how much of a badass I was.
(CHUCKLES)
Look.
MAN: What do you mean,
you don't have the money?
I was going to
sell a nuclear warhead,
and pay you out of the profit.
Things changed.
You expect me to just hand
the meteor over for free?
(GRUNTING)
No, I expect to
take it from you by force.
(HISSING)
(CHANTING INDISTINCTLY)
Oh!
I think that's our cue.
(SCREECHING)
Really? These guys again?
Now.
(GRUNTING)
Keep them occupied.
You ready to show these fools
what's really good?
You have no idea.
I'm glad we're past the point of
worrying about the timeline.
(GRUNTING)
Carter!
(SCREAMING)
Oh, you're too late.
A Time Master is never late.
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Rip!
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
- (SWORD CLINKING)
- (GRUNTING)
(CHOKING)
You can't kill me. I'm immortal.
Guess you haven't
heard the news.
Goodbye, my love.
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
You can feel it, can't you?
Things are different this time.
(GROANING)
You're mortal.
But yet my death does not save
the lives of your family.
I may die,
but you will live knowing that
you failed to save the lives--
(SCREAMS)
Never speak their names again.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Do something, RoboCop.
I'm on it. I've got a little
trick I've been working on.
(LAUGHS)
PROFESSOR STEIN:
It's up to you now, Jefferson.
Grey, listen, if we're gonna do this,
we gotta do it together.
It's gonna take the two of us,
all right?
- PROFESSOR STEIN: You're right.
- Okay.
Come on, Grey.
(STRAINING)
Oh, man, you got my boots wet.
- PROFESSOR STEIN: Jefferson, you did it!
- We did it, man.
Gideon, take us back to Rip.
(GRUNTS)
Damn it! I wanted to be the one
to kill him.
Again, I mean.
Um...
I don't think
our problems are over yet.
I'm on it.
On what?
It's not working.
PROFESSOR STEIN: The radiation buildup
is too progressive.
I got this.
I don't understand.
I must be all out of power.
What happens
if only one of these goes off?
Time will remain intact.
The world, not so much.
Okay, guys, let's
fly this thing out of here.
To where? We would never get it
far enough away.
Maybe the Waverider can.
Rip, we need to-- Rip?
Rip, what are you doing?
I'm flying the Waverider into
the sun with the meteor onboard.
SARA: And you on it.
I guess this is goodbye.
It's been a pleasure, Captain.
Likewise, Dr. Palmer.
JAX: But you brought us all
into this, man.
Which is why I'm doing this
alone, Mr. Jackson.
I'll have no one else
die for my choices.
This isn't gonna
bring Snart back.
I don't wanna lose
another friend.
I appreciate that, Mr. Rory.
RIP: I must say, it's been an honor
to serve as your cap--
(STATIC)
MIRANDA: Rip.
JONAS: Daddy?
Miranda?
I... Where...
GIDEON: I'm still here, Captain.
I know you are, Gideon.
May I share something with you?
I'm not ready to die.
Me neither.
Which reminds me, is our solar
array still functional?
In fact, it's operating
at an efficiency rate
of 12,000%.
Transfer all available power
to the time drive,
get ready to eject the meteor
and pray that we have enough
power for one last jump.
What happens
if only one of these goes off?
Time will remain intact.
The world, not so much.
Okay, guys, let's
fly this thing out of here.
To where? We would never get it
far enough away.
Maybe the Waverider can.
Rip, we need... Where's Rip?
SARA: And the meteorite.
Will somebody please tell me
what just happened?
Rip?
Sorry if I gave you all
a fright.
SARA: What happened to the meteor?
I flew it
into the heart of the sun.
Well, I angled the ship
to eject the meteorite
before impact
and then time-jumped away.
You could've been killed.
Should've been. You're a moron.
(LAUGHS)
Now, who fancies
a return trip to 2016?
I can't believe it's over.
Well, for some of you, yes.
My journey, it seems,
is only just beginning.
How does that work?
Savage is three times dead.
The Time Masters are no longer
a going concern,
due to our destruction
of the Oculus.
Someone needs to be responsible
for protecting the timeline.
Who better
than a former Time Master?
And any of you
who'd like to join me.
I should stay
and help you with Darhk
and get justice for Laurel.
QUENTIN: That's happening,
honey, with or without you.
I promise.
Now, listen, I can't
pretend to understand
this time-travel thing,
but it sounds important.
So is family.
(SNIFFLES)
I wasn't gonna
go the first time.
Then Laurel convinced me.
And now I'm gonna
do this for her.
(SIGHS)
Well, she'd be proud of you.
How do you know?
Because I am.
"What German loanword literally
means 'the desire to hike'?"
"Wanderlust."
A word which could also be used
to describe
that look in your eye.
What look in my eye?
Martin, we've been married
for 28 years
and you're still a lousy liar.
Now, about this
new sabbatical...
I've decided
to decline the invitation.
But I think you should.
(STUTTERING) I think it's important--
Clarissa, I'm not leaving you.
That's final.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
- Hey, Grey.
- What are you...
Oh, I'm so glad
that you could make it, Jax.
What are you up to?
Well, we had a nice, long talk
this afternoon,
- didn't we?
- Yeah.
Oh, my God!
This is an intervention.
Yeah, you could
kind of call it that.
Listen, Grey,
you were meant for more
than sitting around,
answering trivia questions about history.
Me, you, Firestorm...
We're made for changing history.
This is my life.
And your life will be waiting
for you when you get back.
You really want me to do this?
I could never forgive myself
if I kept you from it.
My husband, the superhero.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Why are you
looking at me like that?
I wasn't sure you'd make it.
You left me a message, I came...
What of it?
I just wanted to talk.
You and I,
we've done a lot of thieving,
a lot of cool stuff,
a lot of fun.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Anyway, I just wanted to make
sure I said something important
that wasn't left unsaid.
Mick, I don't do touchy-feely.
If you got something to say,
say it.
This wasn't a good idea.
You're the best guy I ever knew.
You may not think you're a hero,
but you're a hero to me.
You got that?
Yeah, I got it.
See you around.
You okay?
Fine.
So, did you tell him?
That he killed himself
to save our destinies?
If it's any consolation,
I can always bring you back to
this particular time and place.
I'm fine. Just let it be.
RIP: A full complement. (LAUGHS)
To be honest, I had my doubts
that all of you would be willing
to throw in with me
for a second go.
- Well, actually--
- We're not coming with you.
With Savage gone, we wanna start fresh.
See what happens.
I give it three months. Tops.
Look, I just...
I wanna say thank you
to all of you.
- Ray, I--
- No.
This is... It's meant to be.
I wish both of you
nothing but the best.
Be safe.
See you guys around.
Every time they do that,
I get hungry for chicken.
So, shall we?
(WAVERIDER APPROACHING)
- Is that...
- The Waverider.
Another Waverider?
Whatever it is,
it's not slowing down!
Get down!
What the hell's going on?
To be honest, Mr. Jackson,
I have absolutely no idea.
Is this 2016?
Is this May 2016?
Yeah.
You're exactly
where you said you'd be.
Do not get on that ship.
If you do, you're all dead.
Says who?
Says you, Mr. Rory. You sent me.
I'm sorry. Who exactly are you?
My name is Rex Tyler.
I'm a member of
the Justice Society of America.
English - SDH