Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Neron must be looking
for a new vessel.
Nora.
- Nora?
- I don't like Nate.
- That would be wrong and...
- He likes you.
Why don't you talk to Nate,
tell him how you feel?
Mick's writing a Sci-fi
romance novel.
- Rebecca Silver?
- Nom de plume.
Nearly cost her own life,
but she killed that bloody demon.
You're letting the cold in, man.
We found something, sir.
But it's hard to explain.
Don't stand there like a fool,
spit it out.
Something was encased
in the ice,
- and it appears to be...
- Gold.
Well, careful, sir.
It's...
incredible.
I haven't the foggiest what it is.
I know exactly what it is.
My greatest discovery.
Yeah, that's what they all say.
Oh, hey, ladies.
Is he any trouble?
Slam dunk.
Honestly, with Neron gone,
catching fugitives
has never been easier.
I thought it was gonna take all week.
That's great, it means you won't
have to miss book club tonight.
That's right.
Book club.
Smells like somebody
hasn't showered
since birds were letters.
That's a hieroglyphics joke.
Nice.
Buddy, don't talk
with your mouth full, am I right?
Mummy's are the biggest dummies.
Hey, you big dummy, mummy,
got your containment cell all set up,
and we upgraded you
to a king size sarcophagus.
Oh, and would you like a wake-up call
from the front desk in,
I don't know, about a thousand years?
Nice.
All right, cool.
- Bye.
I mean, what the hell was that?
- On it.
- Yeah.
Z, how's it going?
It's going super awesome.
How are you and Nate?
Good.
Nate Dog?
It's... it's going totally great,
in a super platonic way.
Then why you guys being so weird?
It was that awkward, huh?
Even the mummy thought
it was awkward.
Look, I mean, you like him, right?
Yeah, I think so, but I don't know
what the next step would be.
Oh, that's easy
you just jump his bone.
What if I do that
and I screw up our friendship.
Look, Z, sometimes for the good
of the relationship,
you have to put yourself outside
of your comfort zone.
For instance,
I am going to read 500 pages
of some trashy novel
by tonight for Ava.
And look, with Neron gone,
now's the time for us
to get our personal lives into order.
I will help you.
Please don't.
Relationship expert.
I showed him my locket, explaining,
I keep the ones I love in here,
close to my heart.
Gustavo replied, "I keep the ones
I love in my freezer,
close to my microwave."
He had a devilish sense of humor
that I found irresistible.
Hey, Ray.
I was just reading
our book club book to Nora.
Oh, that's really nice, Mona.
Ray, are you okay?
You look like you haven't slept
in days.
Oh, yeah,
I've been having weird dreams.
How is she?
No improvements, but no setbacks.
- Any news from Constantine?
- Nothing yet.
Well, I'm sure he'll find a way
to bring her back.
I'll leave you two alone.
I brought you some more flowers,
because when you do wake up,
I want you to know that
your life is gonna be beautiful
from now on.
What the hell?
What's happening?
Ray, what are you doing
with the pillow?
You smothering,
you're smothering her?
Not groovy.
Not groovy at all.
What just happened?
What are you doing?
Why did you try to smother Nora?
Are you losing it, Ray?
Oh, I don't think you're crazy, Ray.
Let's chat, just Ray and Neron.
Neron?
No, no, you're, you're dead.
You're dead, this, this isn't real.
- This isn't real.
- Not real?
This is, this is all in my head.
- Okay?
- Ray.
Oh, wow, this place is a mess.
Hey.
Containment Level bathroom
is sort of my crying spot.
- Not now, Gary.
- Okay.
Okay.
You're a reasonable man, Ray Palmer.
So I'm going to make you
a reasonable offer.
Give yourself to me freely.
No.
No, this conversation is over.
You leave me no choice
but to make you kill
someone you love.
You... you made me try to kill Nora,
but why?
Because if you murder
someone you love,
your soul will be mine.
What is happening?
Oi, Mick, fancy a brew?
Laundry.
Oh, sorry, sorry.
I'll be in the science doing lab.
Nobody bother me or my hand.
Haircut.
What's all this ruckus?
- Hey.
- Hey, I got it.
Is this fan mail for Rebecca Silver?
No, it is not.
- Here, give me that.
- What...
"An invitation for Rebecca Silver
to reveal her identity
at Romanti Con 2019 for $20,000."
Rebecca doesn't do Cons.
Now, Mick, I realize
that you don't like people
knowing that you moonlight
as a romance novelist, but...
Do I look like
a romance novelist to you?
Oh, listen, don't you get mad at me.
Now this is an easy score,
and we're gonna get that money.
Twenty K.
How?
Well I'll be Rebecca, mate.
Okay.
Page one.
Will have to wait.
All right, people, we've got a hit.
New York City, 1933,
the Adventurers' Society.
Shut the front door.
What's the Adventurers' Society?
It's a club for archeologists
and explorers.
It's basically the coolest place
in history.
Guys, this is gonna be awesome.
Nate, you're running point
on this one with Zari.
- For real?
Sara, we did not discuss this.
Look, relax,
it's just a cleanup job.
They'll do fine.
Okay, find the fugitive,
bring him in,
preferably in one piece.
Now scram.
Yep.
You're willing to risk
an entire mission
to play matchmaker?
I sure am.
Honestly, I'm getting
a "just friends" vibe.
I bet you 20 bucks
they hook up on the mission.
I will take that.
You and I running this mission
won't be weird at all.
- Yeah, it's gonna be super chill.
- Yeah.
And just because
Sara and Ava are busy,
doesn't mean everybody else is.
Yes.
Let's rally the troops.
Raymond, we got a legit
Time Bros mission.
What? Time...
Time Bros, that's us.
Look, I just... I got some stuff
I am doing here.
Come on, put the "schmience" away.
We got a magic blip.
Look, right now it's just
me and Zari.
And if I'm being totally honest,
it's a little awkward between us.
So I could really use my wingman.
I was doing some
interesting stuff here.
It's something
that has to do with me.
Busy working on a vaccine
for Ner... Ner.
- For what?
- Ner...
You all right?
- I got it.
- You, you do... you do?
This is about Nora.
I'm sitting here going
on and on about me and Zari.
I'm not even thinking about
what you must be going through.
I am sorry for being a bad friend.
Bring it in.
What kind of punk ass hug is that?
Bring it all the way in, Raymond.
Hug me.
Look, whatever you're working on,
you're gonna kill it.
You're gonna absolutely murder it.
- Ray.
- Yeah, I just, sort of
sometimes like to do
a pre-mission message, you know?
Just to limber up before
we get out in the field.
Little too much?
Yeah.
Well?
Say hello to Rebecca Silver.
Try these.
Perfect.
Nice getup.
So you guys heard
we're headed to the 30s?
- No.
- Well, you are.
Sara put Nate and me in charge.
Oh, you and Nate finally gonna...
Stop, stop.
Okay, guess what?
You're on the Waverider,
so you're going.
Jumpship's got a full tank,
though, yeah?
Do you have somewhere to be?
Oh, best you don't pry, love.
Just like I'm not asking
about that naughty little number
Sara left behind for you to wear.
Check your closet.
- Rory, do you wanna maybe...
- Plans.
Okay.
I can't believe everyone else
bailed on the mission.
More Adventurers' Society for us.
All right, let's do this.
- Allow me.
- Thank you.
I... I know these costumes
are totally ridiculous.
You... you... you look absolutely.
Yeah, ridiculous.
Apparently it's all part
of a cover story Sara gave me.
I'm someone named Marion Ravenwood.
Wait.
Wait a second.
Well, it says here
I am Dr. Henry Jones Jr.
Professor of archeology,
expert in the occult,
and how does one say this?
Obtainer of rare antiquities.
It's Indiana Jones.
Yeah.
Sara set us up.
What's that?
Adventurers' Society,
everyone else unavailable
for the mission,
dressing up like your favorite movie,
it's all a set up to send us
on the perfect date.
I totally get if you wanna go
back to the ship.
Or...
we can see where
this mission takes us.
We believe in the summer sun
Neon rays, I'm gonna get me some
Golden light come shine
On everyone
Oh, Mick, we're gonna make
a killing off of these people.
Does Rebecca Silver belong
in sci-fi erotica or cyber erotica?
Rebecca Silver defies all categories.
Excuse me, you are?
It's me you should be
talking to, actually.
I am Rebecca Silver.
And I do not appreciate the tone
that you're taking with my bodyguard.
Oh, goodness, Miss Silver,
the Recluse of Romance.
We are honored
that you will be making
your first public appearance
ever with us.
You look exactly as I dreamed.
I'm just here for the check, really.
Of course, and you will get it
after your public appearance,
Q&A, and book signing.
Oh, chitchat with a bunch of weirdos
dressed as some ridiculous
alien queen they all want to bang.
No problem.
Number one, Garima is a warrior.
Number two, you're being rude.
Rude?
That's rich coming from you.
You're the rudest person I know.
You don't get it.
You need training.
What time's the Q&A?
In two hours.
Good, we'll be there.
Let's do this.
Okay, page one.
Is this on audiobook?
They say your life flashes
before your eyes when you die.
But what if in that moment,
you finally see everything
life's been trying to show you?
That's how I discovered
that a killer was amongst me.
I should've known
something was amiss that night.
I was returning from hot yoga
to my sensational cliff side home,
matcha green tea smoothie
in hand,
when I noticed my door
was slightly ajar.
I entered wondering if my dog walker
or cat sitter or personal shopper
or astrologer had failed to close it.
That's when I heard him say,
There's something
I've been meaning to kill you.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Ladies and gentlemen, please.
My esteemed colleagues,
the honor of having my flag retired
is only rivaled by the honor
of sharing my latest discovery.
To retrieve it required
not only besting the frozen wasteland
of the Arctic,
but also the physical limitations
of the human body itself.
But for the sake of exploration,
I prevailed.
And so, without further ado,
I present to you,
Gordon Gilchrist's
Golden Mystery Egg.
Now, Vincent.
In the words of Ray and Mike Tyson,
I think we found our "myth-tery" man.
Come on, science.
Something's happening.
I can feel my hand again.
No, no, no.
The infection...
is spreading.
Gideon, where in the timeline
is John Constantine?
His last known whereabouts
were in 2019 with Gary Green.
Would you like me to connect,
connect...
What are you doing to me, Dr. Palmer?
Gideon?
What?
What are you...
We can't have anyone spying
on us now, can we Raymond?
You're all alone now.
Well,
it's you and me.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I'll just... I'll just do this
the old fashioned way.
- Hello.
- Gary, hi.
Ray Palmer here.
By any chance, have you spoken
to Constantine lately?
Worried about Nora, huh?
Yes, but no.
I'm... I'm calling
on a more personal matter.
Say no more.
I will be right over.
What? No, no, no Gary.
No, Gary.
How can I help?
Oh, no.
You hear something?
There's a guard.
Okay.
Don't worry, I can talk
my way into anywhere.
Excuse me, my good man.
Can you point me
to the nearest facilities?
I have an urgent need to,
relieve my bowels.
Let's go.
We are crushing this mission,
by the way.
No classic Legends mishaps
and only one historically
insignificant nobody received
blunt force trauma to the head.
And now we get our prize.
Wait.
Trip wires.
This is gonna require one of us
to squeeze through these trip wires,
maneuvering our bodies
in unexpected ways.
Are you asking me to do that?
No, I'm asking you to hold my coat.
When I wrote, "Uncaged Desire,"
I was trying to uncage my own desire.
A desire to, to...
to... oh, bollocks.
- What's the next bit, again?
- To feel life, not just live it.
You still don't know Rebecca.
Well, I know you and you're Rebecca.
Your primary mode of communication
is grunting like a caveman.
Besides, I mean, Rebecca Silver
is whoever we want her to be.
These people, they don't know
anything about her.
What are you talking about?
They read her books,
they read her letters.
Her letters?
Do you answer your fan mail?
I just thought all this
was a big laugh at their expense.
Well, it's not.
Careful.
The hell?
It's papier-mâché.
Oh, my God.
She did this all for us.
It's all a set up.
- No.
- Yeah.
- You think?
It was a fake Magic-O-Meter alert.
Sara concocted this whole thing.
- I bet you they're actors too.
- Yep.
"Gordon Gilchrist"
with that ridiculous facial hair?
- The only that's missing, Nazis.
- Yeah.
What did you do with the egg?
The real egg?
Oh, wow, she really went all out.
- Hey.
- Oh, there you are.
I was beginning to think
you weren't gonna make it.
This is a interesting choice
of venue.
We can't have book club without Nora.
It takes all three of us
for a book club quorum.
Very sweet.
- Cheers, babe.
- Thank you.
All right, so, who do you guys think
is the real killer?
Because I have my theories.
Oh, my God, this can't be real.
- I have to go now.
- What?
You just said that book club
requires all three of you.
It's Rebecca Silver.
She's revealing her identity
at Romanti Con tonight.
Rebecca Silver?
The sex-positive novelist
reinventing feminism.
Yeah, we know who she is.
Make sure you take lots of pictures.
Oh, my God, thank you.
I can't believe
I'm going to be breathing
the same air as Rebecca Silver.
Okay, so.
What did you think of the book?
Oh, you wanna keep doing book club?
Babe, we don't have to,
we can just forget it.
I thought it would be nice for us
to be able to do something abuse.
It's so sweet, thank you.
I didn't read the book.
- What?
- Sorry.
Seriously?
Honestly, I... I usually just
drink rosé and let Mona go on and on
and use it as a mini-vacay
for my brain.
Well, it was actually
a really good book.
Wait, wait, wait, you... come on.
I can still drink rosé,
and you can go on and on.
Come on.
- Come on.
- Okay, fine.
So, I think the real killer
was the dog walker.
- No.
- Yes.
I mean, all that pent-up frustration,
and she treated him like a doormat.
You can't help me.
I need Constantine.
Well, I may not be
a master of the dark arts,
but I am an intern of the dark arts.
You're interning for Constantine?
Yeah.
He's letting me study
his spell books,
if I water his plants while
he searches for a cure for Nora.
But besides,
what other options do you have?
Come on, tell the Garebear
what ails ya.
I... I don't know how to explain it,
but it feels like,
like there's something inside of me.
Oh, yeah, you know,
there's a beautiful singer
inside of me,
but no one's ever gonna meet her.
No, no, Gary.
No, Gary, this is bad.
This is very bad,
and I don't know how to get it out.
Indigestion.
I know just the spell.
I'll have your pipes
cleared out in no time.
Let me just look it up.
Oh, good thing it's not a demon,
because if it was,
you wouldn't be able to tell me.
A weird rule
that keeps the victim silent
all the while trying to murder
a loved one
in order to seal in
the demonic possession forever.
- Why did you just stab yourself?
- I didn't
- You're possessed
- Yes.
I... I can help.
Where is the egg?
Take it easy, Hitler Youth.
The egg's broken,
it was a crappy prop.
The real egg.
Do not anger me.
Look, this was a good effort.
Like really good,
but we've done Nazis before.
But, like, real Nazis.
So, if it's okay with you,
I would rather just...
pull the plug on this.
- Yep.
- My friend here is a surgeon.
Oh, nice.
He will kill you until you tell me
where the real egg is.
Yeah, let's tell Sara we're onto her.
Yeah.
- Hello.
- Hi, Sara, Nate and Zari Here.
First of all, well played.
Yeah, setting up this whole adventure
for us to go on a date
was way over the top.
But in the same breath, very sweet.
And if I were to give a note,
the Nazis were just, like,
a tad too much.
What are, what are you talking about?
Are they in the same theater troupe
as Ava's parents?
- What?
- Sara, drop the act.
Nazis killing us
with throwing daggers?
- Come on.
- Listen to me.
Look, I did purposefully
put the two of you
on a mission together,
but this is a real mission.
Not a game.
Those are real Nazis.
And now, young lady, you die.
- Sorry, Nate.
- For what?
- You okay?
- Yeah,
it was actually really intense.
See, they took care of things
on their own.
And they were clearly
about to hook up.
- No, they weren't, wait.
- You owe me 20 bucks.
Were guys about to hook up?
- It was definitely on the table.
- No, no, no
- See?
- Come on, it doesn't matter.
- I told you.
Okay, now that you know
it's a real mission, where's the egg?
Yeah, and where is Ray?
Isn't he supposed to be
quarterbacking on this?
Ray?
Ray, come in.
Nate, buddy,
don't go back to the ship
under any circumstances.
You okay, buddy?
Yeah, just, cleaning up
a storm over here.
I don't want you to trip
and break your neck
on the mopped floors.
Okay, bye.
Bye. Okay, that was weird,
even for Ray.
We should check on him.
You go check on Ray,
we'll handle the egg.
I'm sorry that our first date
got ruined by Nazis.
Who says it's ruined?
Okay, what do we know?
We found an egg, but it was fake.
Someone stole the real one.
Hey, what about that
Gordon Gilchrist guy?
He's the one who found it,
so I don't know
why he would have stolen it.
Although, I sort of think
his poor assistant Vincent
did most of the work.
- Wait, that's just like book.
- It is?
The book from book club.
Vincent is the doormat.
Look, it's always the doormat.
It was the dog walker in the book,
and now this Vincent guy's mad
that he didn't get any credit.
So we find Vincent, take the egg,
and wipe everyone's memories.
Easy.
Ray, Ray.
Remember, if you kill a loved one,
Neron will take over.
Oh, well, here's the thing, Gary.
I... I like you, but...
Yeah, got it.
Ol' Gare.
Not loved by the Legends,
bottom of the pecking order
at the Bureau.
Constantine's plant sitter.
Always the butt of the joke.
Gary, it's not like that.
It is like that, Gary.
No one appreciates you.
They all think you're a fool
that they can use
whenever it's convenient for them.
But I respect you,
and I see your potential.
Neron?
Gary, don't listen to him.
He's trying to trick you.
A demon can't renege on the deals
they make.
So you can believe me when I say
I can make you whole again.
Whole?
Rebecca, first let me say
that your novel,
"Uncaged Desires,"
was a sexual epiphany for me.
I can't say that I'm surprised.
My writing does have that effect.
But how did Officer Daphne
free Tank Tremors?
Can prison guards release inmates
just because they're in love?
Oh, well, you see that
was a metaphor.
After all, aren't we all in our own
prisons of desire?
Rebecca, in "Heat Waves,"
who is the unnamed villain
who's stalking Garima?
- Charlie?
- What is a villain?
Is it just someone
with a different point of view?
What's really stalking Garima
are the choices that she made.
So,
you're the real
Rebecca Silver, huh?
Hi, yes.
I mean,
that is what I have embroidered
on my satin pillow cases.
Okay, then.
I have a question
about your novel, "Raw Hides."
When Captain Cash Harvey
fights the Prairie Bandits,
why does Nasgowa stow away
in his Conestoga wagon?
Well, you see,
that is also a metaphor.
That is not a metaphor.
She really did it,
and she died because of it.
The real Rebecca Silver would know.
I am the real Rebecca Silver.
I have tea with lemon.
I have a really small dog.
You're a fraud.
Where's the real Rebecca?
Right, go to hell,
you stinking mouth breathers.
Where's the real Rebecca?
- Where's the real Rebecca?
- Quiet.
Give me that.
Nasgowa chased Cash for one reason.
It's the same reason humans
have gotten together
since the dawn of time.
It's why people like you
come to conventions
and dress up
as your favorite characters,
why a man
sits behind a desk, typing,
pouring out his heart...
why...
an author,
a writer, replies to fans.
It's connection.
Human connection.
I am Rebecca Silver.
You... you are Rebecca.
I'd recognize that wisdom anywhere.
I would've come sooner, Nora,
but have you any idea how hard it is
to acquire a phoenix's tail feather?
I didn't.
All right.
By the power above and below,
I call you on you, Nora Darhk,
to return to this plane
and rise reborn.
Come on, love.
Come back to me, come on, love.
Get Neron.
No, no, no, it's all right,
love, it's all right.
He's gone, you did it.
- No.
- He's gone.
He has Ray.
Ray?
Gideon, where's Ray?
Nate, you shouldn't have come.
Ray, what's going on?
You should leave.
You can't let me get near...
Ray, what are you saying?
You been acting so weird lately.
- Thought we are bros.
- It's not me.
No, see, it's N...
It's Ner...
What's near?
- Somebody's nearby?
- No.
All right, people, gather around.
Vincent?
What's the meaning of this?
I found it.
- Hand over the egg.
- I should get credit over it.
The egg is my accomplishment.
It belongs to me.
Everyone's memory of the egg
is about to be erased,
so don't get too bent out of shape.
Not so fast.
Finally, the egg is ours.
Oh, man, these guys.
I'm Ray, the wrist of me isn't.
Nate, you have to get out of here.
- You have to leave.
- I won't leave you buddy.
Okay, you got possessed by Neron.
You have to go.
He's gonna make me kill you.
No, because I believe you, Raymond,
are stronger than he is.
Nate, I'm so sorry.
Why... why are you hitting me?
Can't, stop.
We're bros.
We are bros.
No, no.
No.
Okay, I give up.
I give you up,
do you hear me, Neron?
I give up.
Spare Nate and I'll let you,
I'll let you have me.
Just promise me you won't hurt him,
and I won't resist.
Deal.
It's nice to have a willing host.
But a promise is a promise.
We gotta get the egg
On it.
Okay, I got you.
See them whip skills?
Yeah, give me an idea
for a date night.
Oh, come on, now, don't be shy.
You're a little late, Johnny.
I've sort of taken over jolly
old Ray.
So you've lost a step.
That's the thing about mortals.
They age so quickly.
But don't worry, Johnny.
I won't let you die of old age.
Yeah, well,
I might be a little older, mate,
but I've picked up a few tricks
along the way.
- And that one's from Marie Laveau.
- Cute trick.
But we both know you won't
be able to hold it for long.
You're a parasite.
And I will separate you
from Ray Palmer.
Oh, Gary.
Where have you been?
I was hiding in the lab,
then I heard noises.
Yeah, well, go and get
my steam trunk.
and we can exorcise this demon
right now.
Damn it, Gary, now is not the time
for you to be standing around
like some hapless idiot.
I can't hold this bastard forever.
Do it now.
Demands a lot from you,
doesn't he, Gary?
But what has he ever done for you?
I, on the other hand,
brought you a gift.
Go ahead.
Open it.
No, no, no.
Oh, don't accept anything
from him, Gary.
My nipple.
Gary, listen to me, that part of you,
it belongs to hell now.
All right? Don't let it seduce you.
The same way John seduced you
into being unicorn bait?
It's beautiful.
Oh, it's curse.
Now back away from it,
you bloody fool.
It belongs to you, Gary.
Come on, Gary, think about
what you're doing, all right?
Don't give in to its temptation.
How'd I do?
Time dweeb.
The hell are you doing here?
- What do I do?
- Shut up, Gary.
I'm tired of being a doormat.
Gary, no.
Well done, Mr. Green.
I'm whole again.
All systems back online.
So, Zari, some big moves back there.
Yeah, you were really brave.
Thanks.
So why are you scared
to make a move on Nate?
Nate.
What happened?
- Where is he?
- Who?
Ray.
Neron's got him.
Sara, hey.
We got you a collectible
Romanti-Con tote bag.
Who died?
Yeah, what's going on?
I have some bad news.
- I told you, I'm fine
- She's stable, Director.
- Thank you.
- Ava, you shouldn't be here.
You should be scouring every second
of the time line for Ray.
Agents are on it as we speak.
Oh, why did he do that?
Look, I know
you've been through a lot,
but I need your help.
My help?
Why?
Because no matter how many agents
I send after Neron,
none of them can do what you do,
none of them,
have the powers you have, Nora.
And I trust you.
Nora Darhk, I am asking you
to face another demon,
but this time I am asking you
to face it
as a member of the Time Bureau.
Let's do this.
You haven't recovered yet.
We gotta track down Ray.
You will when you're better,
I promise.
You don't just throw a man down
with these sort of injuries.
- It's mean-spirited.
- Don't be a baby.
- Does this hurt?
- Yes, Zari.
It all hurts.
Well, where doesn't it hurt, Nate?
Here?
Yeah.
I guess there's an upside
to getting pummeled.
You know how I never let anyone know
what I'm really feeling?
It's kind of your thing.
That's how I feel, Nate.
I feel the same.
Gideon?
What kind of egg is that?
I believe, Dr. Hayward,
it's a dragon egg.
Of course.