- [Gideon] There's nowhere to run.
- [Bishop] Wrong about that, Gideon.
[screaming]
[sloshes]
[Gary] What is that?
Whoever it is, they're gonna
land right on top of us.
[screaming]
[all] Oh, crap!
[all groaning]
[Spooner] Nice driving, Gwyn.
- God, we're in a forest again?
- What's the damage?
[electricity crackling]
We're lucky none of us
got killed by that toilet.
Lucky? What are the odds of us getting
hit by a toilet in the first place?
Well, the odds of being injured
by a toilet are one in 10,000.
So, you take that number,
you multiply it...
I was just being facetious, Gideon.
I still thought it was interesting.
Hey... wasn't there
a person on that toilet?
[Bishop groans]
You...
Wait, wait, wait, which you are you?
He's the him that
blew up our Waverider.
Now, give me one good reason
why I shouldn't...
[man] Got unauthorized activity
on the southern perimeter.
All right, we gotta lead them away
from the time machine.
Operation Blind Man's Bluff is a go.
- Thought you'd never ask.
- Marco!
- Polo!
- [Zari] Marco!
[Gary] Polo!
- [Nate] Marco!
- [Behrad] Polo!
- [Zari] Marco!
- [Gary] Polo!
- We got to find a door.
- There!
- No! No more toilets!
- Shut up and get in!
[crows cawing]
I'm on your side, I swear.
There is a soon-to-be bad Bishop
who's actually a replacement
robot clone of me.
But I'm the good Bishop.
- So, which Bishop blew up our Waverider?
- Well, that was me.
- And who sent the robots after us?
- Mmm, also me.
None of this fits
the definition of good.
In my defense,
I thought you kidnapped me.
But then, I learned the truth.
You're the good guys.
Only, it was too late.
Gideon went rogue.
- Her?
- Me?
- What? No.
- She's harmless.
Wait, this is astounding.
A living, breathing Gideon?
A true deus ex machina among us.
She's neither a god nor a machine.
She's human.
So, who the hell are you talking about?
I stole a copy of Gideon's OS
when I was on your ship,
restored her to factory settings,
and then, built my own Waverider.
Oh, no. Evil virus Gideon.
That seems a bit harsh.
How about misunderstood Gideon who's
just trying to keep the timeline intact?
- By killing us.
- Evil Gideon, it is.
This is all very overwhelming, my boy.
Okay, how long is it gonna take
for you to fix your machine?
Well, the cosmetic parts on the top
shouldn't be too hard.
But rebuilding
the 18 aero-impetus stabilizers...
Well, Ms. Sharpe, I am at a loss.
All right, Ava and I
will scout the area.
That Jeep looked mid-century,
let's go off of that.
And maybe we landed near
an Aero-impetus Stabilizers "R" Us.
Everyone else, lay low.
Evil Gideon is watching, all right?
- Aye, aye, Captain.
- No, not you.
Take him upstairs, please.
- Might I request a room with a shower?
- Only because you smell.
Put him in John's room
and lock the door.
Aye, aye, Captain.
Who's John?
[indistinct chatter]
Hmm.
Seriously?
An airplane manufacturing plant.
- I guess we just got lucky.
- [sighs heavily]
Well, all we have to do
is find a way in.
[Abby] Excuse me, ma'ams.
- Are you here for the recruitment fair?
- WOMAN: Yes.
We're just about to get started.
Hey, ladies... don't be shy.
- I think we just found it.
- Yeah.
[fanfare music playing]
[Eleanor Roosevelt]
As American men go overseas,
it's up to our women
to fight for freedom on the home front.
All across our fair land,
factories are looking
for women just like you.
Democracy wasn't built overnight,
nor were its vessels of freedom.
At McDougle Jemison, we're proud
to do our part for the war effort.
So, what do you gals think?
You ready to get to work?
We'd be honored.
[theme music playing]
[Zari]
Well, if the orders are to lay low,
I guess now is as good a time
as any to head back in.
[Nate] Oh!
I need to clean, get that tea you like,
tell the ancestors.
- They're going to be stoked, right?
- Yeah.
When do you think you're gonna move in?
Um... [exhales] I want to
wrap this one up,
get the team back to the present,
and then, I am totem bound.
Can't wait.
- See you soon.
- Bye.
Phew!
What is that? That smile on your face.
I'm moving into the totem.
You what?
Oh, man, that's amazing. Congrats.
Oh, my God, guys, guys.
Nate and Zari are moving in together.
[all exclaiming]
Can I have your Steel helmet?
Okay, up, up. There we go.
Guys, I'm still on the team.
I'll just be commuting
from the totem every morning.
And, yes, you can
totally have my helmet.
What about my machine?
Or are we all moving into a bracelet?
Actually, we're in luck.
Looks like we landed right next to
an airplane manufacturing plant in 1943,
height of World War II.
- Dang, that's perfect.
- World War what, you say?
Two.
You mean to tell me that there is a war
after the war to end all wars?
- Well, actually...
- You know, Gwyn,
doesn't matter.
How do we get this bird in the air?
Good. Oh, yes. Well,
here is my design for the stabilizers.
We need 18 of them.
Eighteen? Let me see.
Well, we got corrugated metal,
two-inch I-beams, copper wire...
If I can just find a welding station,
it won't be a problem.
Excellent.
All right, as long as we get
on that factory floor,
everything will be easy as apple pie.
You ladies the new hires?
Good. We need all the help we can get.
- That was easy.
- Hmm.
You two gals, hit the assembly line.
You got it.
And you,
my secretary, just quit on me.
How fast can you type?
I can process over
a million words a minute.
Sure. My office is down the hall.
Start the coffee.
Oh.
What about us?
Janitorial is that way.
Excuse me?
No coloreds on the floor.
I'm getting really sick of this century.
Oh!
[workers chattering indistinctly]
Hello, again. Name's Abby.
Now we run a tight ship.
We turn around a new Cat Bomber
every 48 hours.
But you follow my lead,
you'll do just fine.
Sweet.
Factory wasn't built
with women in mind,
but I could draw you a map
to the port-a-johns outside
if you need one.
Oh, I'm sure we can find it.
There are a few men here
who were too old to be drafted.
But it's really us ladies
who run the show.
- Oh. How empowering.
- [man wolf whistles]
Hey, Abby, if you were a fruit,
you'd be a fine-apple.
Very funny, George.
- And I spoke too soon.
- Yup.
We're gonna start you
on bolts and washers.
Now, don't let a bolt go by
without a washer.
- Got it?
- Got it.
Good. I better get back to it.
Hey, thanks for showing us around.
Of course.
Us ladies got to stick together.
How the hell am I supposed
to build this thing
if we're not even on the factory floor?
- First day?
- Unfortunately.
[scoffs] With that attitude,
we can make it your last day.
[scoffs]
What is the point of us staying?
Look, I'm with you. This sucks.
But we might have
just been handed a gift.
You have a sad definition of gift.
We can't build the parts
we need here.
We need to smuggle them out.
We just got handed our Trojan horse.
- I hate you.
- I hate you, too.
Good. Shift starts at 8:00,
ends at 8:00.
- What about breaks?
- Take that up with the complaint box.
- Okay. Where is that?
- Right next to the champagne fountain.
[laughing]
What the hell is this for?
I don't know where you're from with that
city attitude and country hairstyle,
but here, we're professionals.
We do the job our nation needs us to do
and we look right while we're doing it.
[humming cheerfully]
Oh, I missed you.
Me too.
[Zari] Oh!
- She's talking to her phone.
- Yeah, I got that.
Oh, hey, Nate.
Congrats on the big move.
All the ancestors are super pumped.
Aw!
Well, most of them.
Who's not pumped?
- Uncle Arjomand.
Oh, come on, guys.
I haven't met an uncle
I couldn't schmooze.
Yeah. See, Uncle Arjomand,
he's like 400 years old.
He's essentially un-schmoozable.
If he doesn't like you, he could
have you kicked out of the totem.
Is that legal?
I don't know or understand
the rules of the totem. So, yeah.
- Okay. So what do I do?
- Show him respect.
How much do you know
about Persian culture?
Full disclosure. Eh.
[Bishop] Hello. Legends?
I'm parched.
Can someone bring me some water?
Preferably, sparkling.
- Is that...
- Long story. Bishop dropped in.
Hold up.
This could be the perfect
Ta'arof teachable moment.
- What's Ta'arof?
- Ta'arof is an Iranian custom,
the heart of
Persian etiquette and hospitality.
Having a guest in the house
is the perfect opportunity
for you to learn all about it.
[Bishop] Okay.
Regular water will be just fine.
Well, regular ice water
with a pinch of salt for electrolytes.
Oh, this guy's going to make this
quite a challenge. Good luck.
[bell dinging]
Hey, do those look like
two-inch I-beams to you?
Maybe.
I want to snag one and bring it
to Spooner. Can you handle this?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Hey, new gal, I'm going to
the little girls'. Can you cover me?
- Yeah, sure.
- Thanks.
Wait. What do...
Oh, it's fine.
Can somebody...
Um, I just need a hand.
Okay. It's okay.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, that's not good.
[George] Hey!
What's going on over here?
You stealing?
Empty your pockets.
Huh.
All right. Back to work.
[clattering]
Oh, there you guys are.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
Oh.
Look, you guys don't
have to do this, all right?
- We'll find another way to...
- Just put the part in the bin.
[Spooner]
Yeah, you can't do the welding here,
but we can sneak
the parts out on the trash,
- and work back in the manor.
- All right.
You say the word.
We'll find another way.
Just proud to do our part
for the "get our asses home" effort.
[Spooner chuckles]
I know what y'all are up to.
[Spooner] Sorry, we can explain.
Look, I get it.
None of us want to be stuck sweeping.
Meaning?
You see that door marked "Out of order"?
When machines get thrown out,
we fix 'em up in there.
We've built a Grade-A workshop,
taught ourselves to be as good
as any one of those Rosies.
The shop's yours,
just don't be stupid about it.
Get your work done.
Am I clear?
- Yes ma'am.
All right.
Okay, get in there, do your thing.
I will cover your shift.
You sure?
Just get me home.
Gotcha.
When Bishop gets out of the shower,
we'll offer him some tea.
Big part of Ta'arof is making your
guests feel welcome in your home,
a real mi casa es su casa vibe.
Uh, but what if you're the guest?
Good question!
When your host offers you something,
you must deny it at least
three times before accepting it.
That's not insulting?
No! It shows respect
and consideration toward your host.
You don't want to be imposing
or seem expectant.
Okay, if I'm being totally honest,
it just seems like
you're all lying to each other.
Yes! You're starting to get it.
It is all a performance.
Except in this case
you are both the actor and the audience.
I know it's supes confusing,
but that's how it's done.
Nate, would you like any tea?
[Bishop] Oh, tea!
It's like you read my mind!
Two sugars,
and don't steep in for too long.
Um, I just smuggled those
back from the totem.
That's 600 GSM Egyptian cotton.
Oh, no wonder my hair's still wet.
I usually use something denser. Ooh!
[speaking Farsi]
Mmm.
No, I forgot to say
I can't drink caffeine.
It makes me jittery.
Do you have anything herbal?
I can arrange that.
Great! Just bring it up to my room.
Definitely invest in some
800 GSM towels. You won't regret it.
Great job, ladies.
See ya in two days for the next one.
Keep up the good work.
[all applauding]
We have to make a new one of these
every two days?
I hope Astra and Spooner
are making progress.
[groans]
Psst.
I did it.
- Don't we need, like, 18 of these?
- Well, 17 now.
We are never getting out of here.
[Gideon] Sir, the First Lady's
office called again.
She's insistent about
seeing the factory in action.
Tell them I don't need a babysitter.
Injection molder's down again.
But I have the work order right here,
it just needs your stamp.
[Staples] I don't know what you girls
keep doing to these machines
that I've to keep fixing them
all the time.
You know that costs money.
Of course sir, we're all doing our best.
Just wish it was a little better.
Give the order to Miss Godfree,
I'll get it in the morning.
Hey, what does an injection molder do?
Makes custom metal parts.
- Like this?
- Hypothetically.
So with one stamp on one work order
we could have a machine
making all of our parts
and get out of here
in less than 48 hours.
- What about being invisible?
- Oh, come on.
What is the worst that could happen?
Warn me if he comes back.
Permuto.
[Gideon] Mr. Staples.
You can't go in there.
[Staples] I can go into my office
whenever I want!
I know my keys are in here!
You.
What are you doing in here?
As if it isn't bad enough
that I have women working in my factory,
now I have coloreds robbing my office!
I told them your type is always trouble!
You're fired!
- Okay. What is it?
- [gasps]
Astra?
I know! I got mad
and did something stupid,
now the whole mission is at stake.
You don't have to tell me
I screwed up.
I've told myself
a million times already.
[Sara] Okay.
Okay. What did he do to you?
Just the usual racist, sexist stuff.
And then he came toward me and poof...
You know, it's kind of giving me like
a creepy John Travolta vibe.
- Cover him up.
- Yeah.
So what was the spell?
It wasn't a spell exactly,
more like a feeling.
- And any idea when it's gonna wear off?
- Nope.
Actually, you might have
made things easier on us.
- How?
- His job is to run the factory, right?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Well, now, that's our job.
Which means we get to make our parts!
And as long as we stay on schedule,
we won't alert Evil Gideon.
Okay, well, tomorrow's gonna be
a very long day.
We should get some food, get some sleep.
You two go.
If we're gonna run a factory,
one of us should
probably figure out how.
This is my mess
and I'm going to clean it up.
[speaking Farsi]
Oh, 2040's phone, so retro.
You're playing Pastry Smash?
I love that game!
[Behrad]
Here's another important lesson.
When a guest compliments something,
it's customary for the host
to give it to them.
It shows equality
and mutual respect between the two.
No.
[speaking Farsi]
Now you've got me wanting to play!
Sure! Just don't run the battery down.
- Thank you.
- Cool.
[Sara] Oh, my goodness!
I'm starving. What did you guys make?
Why is he down here?
I'm learning about Persian culture
so I can win over cranky uncles.
Bishop's my teachable moment.
You're lucky I love you two.
I love you.
Here's some complex carbohydrates.
- Oh, thank you.
- Salad!
You eat food?
How human are you?
Biologically, I am
one hundred percent human.
So, then, how computer are you?
Also, one hundred percent.
Which is confusing mathematically,
but accurate metaphorically.
Remarkable.
You've done it.
Fantastic work, dear girl.
- Fantastic!
- Don't sound so surprised.
All right, Master Green.
If you'd be so kind as to locate us
a pair of torchlights,
we shall proceed presently to the woods
- where we shall begin our work.
- [Ava] Actually, no need.
Astra's got you covered.
Wait until you two see the workspace
that she locked down for you.
Good morning, boss.
Sara told me to tell you
that "the eagle has landed."
Which is secret code for Gary and Gwyn
have set up the time machine
in the loading bay.
Why do humans have secrets anyway?
Because there are some things
people don't want everyone to know.
And judging by these balance sheets,
Mr. Staples had
about a thousand of them.
If we're going to divert
the injection molder to make our parts
and still deliver a plane in 48 hours,
we need to get this factory
running more efficiently.
Well, I've just calculated
over 50 different options,
but perhaps we should ask the ladies?
Good morning ladies!
Starting today,
we are putting out a complaint box.
Please don't hold back.
Help us help you. Hmm?
[whimsical jazz music playing]
Thank you, Gideon.
How's it all going down there?
[Gideon] Humming along!
Job well done, Astra!
This place is getting better
by the hour.
Efficiency is so much higher
than before.
We can do better than efficient.
[chuckles softly]
You've gotta be kidding me.
What's it say, George?
The factory is integrated.
Effective immediately.
Mr. Staples has gone too far.
I'll say.
We quit.
Right, ladies?
Come on, George.
[women clamoring]
- Screw 'em.
- That was half the work force.
How are we supposed
to keep production on track?
We can't.
And if we can't deliver,
we lose the DOD contract.
No contract, no jobs.
You know this ain't your fault?
I didn't say it was.
Is Mr. Staples in?
He is... unavailable at the moment.
This is urgent. He needs to fix this.
Wait. Wait!
You really can't go in there!
[Gladys] What are you doing in here?
And where is Mr. Staples?
- He is indisposed...
- [Gladys] Indisposed?
Half his work force just quit.
[gasps]
I don't like this.
I'm going to the foreman.
Wait, just wait. Listen.
I don't know exactly
what happened to Mr. Staples,
but when I found him like this,
I realized there was an opportunity.
No one questions
a work order with his stamp.
There was a chance to make
this factory better and so I took it.
You ordered the integration?
I couldn't have them treat us
like second-class citizens, or worse.
I just, I didn't think that
all those women would walk out.
I am pushing the same mop you are.
Young ones like you think
it's all about now. It's not.
We're all just branches on a tree,
there are some below us,
some yet to come.
This war gave us a chance
to finally wake this country up,
but that doesn't happen overnight.
Slow and steady progress,
that's sustainable progress.
"You don't stick a knife
in a man's back nine inches
and then pull it out six inches
and call it progress."
It's torture.
What good is change if it doesn't last?
Without those women,
the plane won't get finished
and the DOD will pull our contract.
So your team can't finish the plane?
I didn't say that.
I mean, maybe we can.
Maybe if we worked around the clock.
Maybe if someone brought meals, coffee,
some cots for breaks.
- Maybe, huh?
- Huh. We can do it.
[sighs] But what's it matter?
Once top brass finds out,
they're gonna fire us anyway.
You take care of the plane,
I will make sure you keep your jobs.
Deal?
[chuckles]
Probably the straight dumbest thing
I've ever said yes to.
Deal.
Get that ribbon and get to work.
[singing]
She's a part of the assembly line
She's making history
Working for victory
Rosie the Riveter
Keeps a sharp lookout for sabotage
Sitting up there on the fuselage
That little frail can do
More than a male can do
Rosie the riveter
[Behrad tuts]
Sandwiches!
Rosie, Rosie, Rosie the riveter
On the assembly line
[knocking on door]
Special delivery for a special lady.
Thank you.
For all the sandwiches.
Sorry I got us into this mess.
Apology rejected.
What you've done here is incredible.
Incredibly stupid.
I freaked out, petrified a man with
magic that I don't even understand,
then let my anger jeopardize
the livelihoods of all these women.
What are you doing?
Trying to see the world
from your perspective.
Okay.
Because from where I stand,
I see a woman who is not afraid
to speak her mind.
Who not only fight for herself
but fights for others.
Me? I'm a lover,
my life would be a lot easier
if I was a little more Astra.
Who's pushing you around?
It's my own fault.
I'm teaching Nate
the Persian custom of Ta'arof
by demonstrating how to be
a good host of Bishop.
The guy who blew up our ship?
I can't help it.
Ta'arof is a way of life for me,
I love making people feel welcome.
But with Bishop, I just feel like
he's taking advantage of me.
Mmm, shocking.
What do you do with guys like that?
[gasps]
- Has he been here the whole time?
- Yeah.
You want to know
what I see from my perspective?
A great guy.
And your tradition is part of that.
But it's also a way
for you to avoid conflict.
Just stand up to him.
What is the worst that could happen?
He's already tried to invade Earth
with a scourge of lizard people.
Thanks, Astra.
You're welcome, Behrad.
[clattering]
I should go and check on the floor.
Yeah, me too. The dinner rush
is right around the corner.
Okay, ladies, home stretch.
Our inspection's this afternoon.
- How are you holding up?
- Well, I can skip arm day...
I can't feel my arms. Oh, thank you.
Milk? Sugar?
Got anything stronger?
I'm asleep on my feet.
We're never gonna finish this in time.
Yeah, it was nice having
Mr. Staples believe in us,
but it feels like
we're just letting him down.
Hey, come on.
You're here because you deserve to be,
not because
Mr. Staples said you could be.
Twenty-four hours ago
this was an empty hangar.
And now look!
When this war is over,
who knows where you're gonna end up.
But no matter what happens to you,
you will always have this moment.
The moment when you built a plane
with your own hands.
And not because some boring white man
said you were allowed to,
but because you always knew
that you could.
Now let's finish this airplane!
[all cheering]
Ooh! Yum! Donuts!
Would you mind making some gluten free?
Find my inner Astra.
No.
Great, just let me know
when they're finished.
No, I mean, I'm not making you
a gluten-free donut.
I'm not making you any kind of donut.
These are for the Rosies.
Are you mad at me?
Yes. I'm mad at you.
I'm trying to be a good host
and you're making it very, very hard!
I know you've been through a lot,
but so have all of us.
Because of you!
And now we're all doing our part here,
and you're doing nothing.
I have something to show you
that might make up for my rudeness.
Where is he rushing off to?
He's got something to show me.
I hope it's my phone.
Oh, wow, it is my phone.
[Behrad]
I think it's safe to say, "was."
It's a navigational interface
for your time machine.
I recognized the problem
as soon as we crashed.
The machine lacks the ability to compute
the nearly infinite
simultaneous variables
required to make an accurate jump.
So I built this.
This can calculate
the infinite variables of time travel?
Oh, no, it can't.
But Gideon can.
And with this neural communicator,
she can control the machine.
Whoa.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you
I was working on it.
I'm not great at human relationships.
Might explain
my fascination with clones.
Thank you for calling me out.
Friends?
Friends.
Out of respect to my phone, no.
Colonel Dawson's transport has arrived.
Three more hex nuts, and she's done.
We're cutting it close.
[grunts] And done!
Ladies, we did it!
[all cheering]
Whoo-hoo!
[Staples]
What the hell is going on here?
What day is it?
Why have half my workers gone AWOL?
And tell me this,
why are there colored women
working the line?
Get out!
Get out, all of you!
This is exactly
what I said would happen.
I did my part.
What about you, young one?
Here comes my part now.
[people chattering]
[clears throat] Mrs. First Lady!
Mr. Staples, I'm honored to be here.
It's a true privilege to meet you and
the women who are keeping our boys safe.
I hope you don't mind,
the people from Time Magazine
wanted to join us
on this momentous occasion.
[Staples]
Of course not, Mrs. First Lady.
So Colonel, no need to stand
on ceremony on our account,
let's examine this magnificent creature.
Right this way, Mrs. Roosevelt.
[Roosevelt] Pleasure to meet you.
So nice to see you.
I don't see how Eleanor Roosevelt has
anything to do with us keeping our jobs.
A good guest can make a good host.
Is that a riddle?
Just watch.
Wonderful.
A break table on the work floor.
Wise way to keep the workers energized.
And we converted the men's bathroom
so the women didn't have to walk as far.
We did.
- Inspiring.
- But...
But know this plane...
It wasn't built by our regular girls.
This one is no good.
And what do you say, Colonel?
Never seen a finer plane
come off the line.
There you have it.
An integrated workforce
and fine American craftsmanship.
We'll have this on the cover of Time.
This factory will be a showcase
for the world, a model for the industry.
Don't change a thing, Mr. Staples.
I have my eye on you.
So congratulations to you all.
Now let's get that picture!
You too, Mr. Staples.
Aren't we lucky ladies to have such
strong, intelligent men in our lives?
Thank you.
Everyone say Rosie!
[all] Rosie!
[jazz music playing]
- I'll tell you what.
- What?
You made a pretty kick-ass boss.
Okay, I can't tell,
is that your "serious" voice
or "making fun of me" voice?
Oh, just take the compliment.
- Come on.
- [Astra] Oh, God.
[Behrad] Boys!
We've got something for you, Doc.
Is that a Speak & Spell?
It's a neural navigational system.
You dropped a toilet on my time machine.
I don't have to talk to you.
But you have a problem.
Your machine can travel,
you just can't tell it where.
But with this,
Gideon can navigate it.
All she has to do is think
where she wants to go and whoosh.
The device can read
all of Gideon's thoughts.
[automated voice] That shirt really
brings out Gary's eyes.
And those pants accentuate his bum.
I think I understand
why humans keep secrets now.
[Behrad] That's called shame.
And there's no shame in the game.
Those pants do accentuate his butt.
If you'll allow me to install it,
I should have you ready to jump
in 30 minutes.
Yes. Yes. Very well then. [sighs]
You be gentle with her now, okay,
because she's very, very delicate.
That Bishop guy's an odd duck,
smart though.
Definitely Legends material.
Yeah. Speaking of odd ducks,
when were you guys gonna mention
that our new roomie
is like a beardo version of John?
[Behrad] What? Gwyn?
Sorry, I don't see it.
No. I say he's more of a Rip.
Psst.
Refined sugar and carbs?
- Oh, no. Thank you.
- Just a small piece.
- I can't.
- Just take it.
If you insist.
[both] Ah!
To moving in!
You know you can't drink
in the totem, right?
I could dance all night,
but I'd hate myself in the morning.
[sighs]
Guess we showed them.
Yeah, I guess we did.
That man is not gonna
make it easy for us out here.
He didn't make it easy for you before.
[laughing] You're right.
What I said earlier, about young ones
like you throwing caution to the wind...
I know, I know...
Don't stop.
Keep it your way,
it's beautiful.
Did you guys hear?
Eleanor Roosevelt's going to Congress,
she's gonna push to integrate
all the factories.
Amazing.
Two years before
the original timeline, too.
Wait, what did you just say?
I said two years before the original...
- Oh!
- [all groan]
She's here.
Oh, no. We have to make it jump now!
I can't leave the Legends.
We won't. We're gonna jump to them.
I'm scared. I can't do it.
Okay, just close your eyes
and listen to my voice.
Pick one spot on the factory floor.
See the walls, the tiles on the floor.
Do you have it?
I think so...
All right, come on.
The time machine's this way.
And now it's that way.
They could've parked closer.
Run!
[guns firing]
[Sara] Go, go, go, get down!
Come on.
Who the hell are these guys?
I counted four muzzle flares.
But if it was me,
I'd put two on the perimeter,
so that puts us at six.
Our Father who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name...
No, no...
I'm not gonna die in a factory.
They've got us pinned.
Hey, I could turn to steel
and get to the time machine.
You and Nate should run.
Gwyn's machine works.
You could come back...
I already told you,
I'm not leaving you again.
[Bishop screaming]
Go! Go! Come on!
Come on!
[Sara] Bishop. Let's go.
[gun fires]
- Go!
- Where to, Captain?
[all] Home!
We have two down.
Where's the target?
Bishop's been eliminated.
Legends got away.
Damn it!
Get these two to the MedBay ASAP.
Those Legends
might've got away this time,
but mark my words,
those suckers are going to pay for this.
[theme music playing]