[Nora] Previously on
Legends Of Tomorrow...
[Neron as Desmond
whistling "Pop Goes the Weasel"]
[Constantine] Neron must be
looking for a new vessel.
Nora!
- [groans]
- [screeching]
[Ray] Nora?
I don't like Nate.
That would be wrong and...
- Nate likes you.
- [Mona] Why don't you talk to Nate?
Tell him how you feel.
[Nick] Mick's writing
a sci-fi romance novel.
- Rebecca Silver?
- Nom-de-plume.
[Constantine] Nearly cost her her life.
She killed that bloody demon.
[dog barking]
[whistling "Pop Goes the Weasel"]
[wind whistling]
You're letting the cold in, man.
[boy] We found something, sir.
But it's hard to explain.
Don't stand there like a fool.
Spit it out.
Something was encased in the ice.
It appears to be...
Gold.
Careful, sir.
It's... incredible.
I haven't the foggiest what it is.
I know exactly what it is.
My greatest discovery.
[mummy snarling]
Yeah. That's what they all say.
Oh, hey, ladies. Was he any trouble?
Slam dunk. Honestly, with Neron gone,
catching fugitives
has never been easier.
I thought it was gonna take all week.
That's great. It means you won't
have to miss book club tonight.
- That's right. Book club.
- Mmm-hmm.
Whoa! Smells like
somebody hasn't showered
since birds were letters.
That's a hieroglyphics joke.
Ha! Nice.
[mummy snarling]
Oh, buddy, don't talk
with your mouth full, am I right?
Mummies are the biggest dummies.
Hey, you big dummy mummy.
Got your containment cell all set up,
and we upgraded you
to a king-size sarcophagus.
Oh, and would you like a wake-up call
from the front desk in,
I don't know, about 1,000 years?
- [both chuckling]
- [Nate] Nice.
[Zari clears her throat]
All right, cool.
- Bye.
[mummy snarling]
I mean, what the hell was that?
- On it.
- Yeah.
Z, how's it going?
It's going super awesome.
- How are you and Nate?
- [mummy snarling]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Ah!
Nate dawg... It's going totally great,
in a super platonic way. [clears throat]
Then why are you guys being so weird?
[sighs] It was that awkward, huh?
Even the mummy thought it was awkward.
Look, I mean, you like him, right?
Yeah, I think so. But I don't know
what the next step would be.
Oh, that's easy.
You just jump his bones.
What if I do that
and it screws up our friendship?
Look, Z. [sighs]
Sometimes, for the good
of the relationship,
you have to put yourself outside
of your comfort zone.
For instance,
I am going to read 500 pages of some
trashy novel by tonight, for Ava.
And look, with Neron gone,
now is the time for us
to get our personal lives into order.
I will help you.
Please don't.
Relationship expert.
[Mona] "I showed him my locket,
explaining, 'I keep the ones I love
in here, close to my heart.'
Gustavo replied, 'I keep the ones
I love in my freezer,
close to my microwave.'
He had a devilish sense of humor
that I found irresistible."
Hey, Ray!
I was just reading our book club book
to Nora.
Oh, that's really nice, Mona.
Ray, are you okay?
You look like you haven't slept in days.
Oh... Been having weird dreams.
- How is she?
- No improvements.
But no setbacks.
Any news from Constantine?
Nothing yet.
Well, I'm sure he'll find a way
to bring her back.
I'll leave you two alone.
I brought you some more flowers
because when you do wake up,
I want you to know that your life
is going to be beautiful from now on.
What the hell?
What's happening?
Wait. What are you doing
with the pillow?
Are you smothering her?
You're smothering her?
[grunting]
[gasping]
Not groovy.
Not groovy at all.
[sighs] What's happening?
What are you doing?
Why did you try to smother Nora?
Are you losing it, Ray?
Oh, I don't think you're crazy, Ray.
Let's chat.
Just Ray and Neron.
Neron?
No, you're dead.
You're dead. This isn't real.
This isn't real.
Not real?
[electricity crackling]
This is all in my head.
This is all in my head, okay?
[Gary] Ray!
Wow, this place is a mess.
Uh... Hey, um...
Containment-level bathroom
is sort of my crying spot...
- Not now, Gary!
- Okay, okay.
[sighs]
You're a reasonable man, Ray Palmer.
So I'm going to make you
a reasonable offer.
Give yourself to me freely.
No. No, this conversation is over.
- [grunting]
- [chuckles]
You leave me no choice
but to make you kill someone you love.
You made me try to kill Nora.
But why?
Because, if you murder someone you love,
your soul will be mine.
[gasps]
What is happening?
[sighs]
Mick, fancy a brew?
Laundry.
[electricity crackles]
Sorry! Sorry.
I'll be in the science, doing lab.
Nobody bother me, or my hand.
[Mick] Haircut!
- What's all this ruckus?
- [Mick grunts]
- [Charlie] Hey!
- [Mick] Hey, I got it!
- Is this fan mail for Rebecca Silver?
- No.
It is not. Here. Give me that!
An invitation for Rebecca Silver
to reveal her identity
at RomantiCon 2019 for $20,000.
Rebecca doesn't do cons.
Now, Mick, I realize
that you don't like people knowing
that you moonlight
as a romance novelist, but...
Do I like look like a romance novelist
to you?
Oi, listen, don't you get mad at me.
Now, this is an easy score,
and we're gonna get that money.
20K. How?
Well, I'll be Rebecca, mate.
Okay. Page one...
[beeping]
...will have to wait.
All right, people, we've got a hit.
New York City, 1933.
The Adventurers Society.
Shut the front door!
What's the Adventurers Society?
It's a club
for archaeologists and explorers.
It's basically the coolest place
in history.
Guys, this is gonna be awesome!
Nate, you're running point on this one.
With Zari.
- For real?
Um...
Sara, we did not discuss this.
Look, relax. It's just a cleanup job.
We'll do fine.
[Agent Sharpe] Okay.
Find the fugitive,
bring him in, preferably in one piece.
Now scram.
- [Nick] Hmm.
- [Zari] Yeah.
[Sara sighs]
You're willing to risk an entire mission
to play matchmaker?
I sure am.
[Agent Sharpe] Honestly, I'm getting
a "just friends" vibe.
I bet you 20 bucks
they hook up on the mission.
I'll take that.
You and I running this mission
won't be weird at all.
- Yeah, it's gonna be super chill.
- Yeah.
[Nate clears throat]
And just because Sara and Ava are busy
doesn't mean everybody else is.
Yes. Let's rally the troops.
Yes.
Raymond, we've got a legit
Time Bros mission.
What? Time... Time Bros, that's us.
Um... Look, I just...
I've got some stuff I'm doing here.
Come on, put the "schmience" away.
We got a magic blip.
Look, right now, it's just me and Zari,
and if I'm being totally honest,
it's a little awkward between us.
So I could really use my wing man.
I'm just doing
some interesting stuff here. I...
It's something that has to do with me.
Busy working on a vaccine for...
N...
- For what?
- [straining]
Are you all right?
- I got it.
- You do?
This is about Nora.
I'm sitting here, going on and on
about me and Zari,
I'm not even thinking about
what you must be going through.
I am sorry for being a bad friend.
Bring it in.
What kind of punk-ass hug is that?
Bring it all the way in, Raymond.
Hug me.
Look, whatever you're working on,
you're gonna kill it.
You're gonna absolutely murder it.
- Ah, Ray?
- Yeah, I just sort of
sometimes like
to do a pre-mission massage, you know?
Just to limber up before we get out
in the field. [grunts]
[Ray sighs]
- A little too much?
- Yeah.
Well, say hello to Rebecca Silver.
[grunts]
Try these.
[Mick grunts]
Perfect.
[chuckles]
Nice get-up.
So you guys heard we're headed
to the '30s?
No.
Well, you are.
Sara put me and Nate in charge.
Oh, are you and Nate finally gonna...
Boom, boom.
Stop, stop. Okay.
Guess what. You're on the Waverider,
so you're going.
Jumpship's got
a full tank though, yeah?
Do you have somewhere to be?
Best if you don't pry, love.
Just like I'm not asking
about that naughty little number
Sara left behind for you to wear.
Check your closet.
- Rory, do you want to...
- [Mick] Plans.
Okay.
- [people chattering]
- [laughter]
[Nate scoffs]
I can't believe
everyone else bailed on the mission.
More Adventurers Society for us.
[sighs] All right. Let's do this.
- [man] Allow me.
- [Zari] Thank you.
I know. I know. These costumes
are totally ridiculous.
[stammers] You look absolutely, um...
yeah, ridiculous.
Uh, apparently, it's all part
of the cover story Sara gave me.
I'm someone named Marion Ravenwood.
Wait.
Wait a second.
Huh. Well, it says here
I am Dr. Henry Jones Jr.
Professor of archaeology,
expert in the occult.
And how does one say this?
Obtainer of rare antiquities.
How...
It's Indiana Jones.
Yeah.
- Sara set us up.
- What's that?
Adventurers Society, everyone else
unavailable for the mission,
dressing up like your favorite movie,
it's all a setup
to send us on the perfect date.
[gulps]
I totally get
if you want to go back to the ship.
Or we can see where
this mission takes us.
[upbeat music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
Oh, Mick, we're gonna make
a killing off of these people.
Does Rebecca Silver belong
in sci-fi erotica or cyber-erotica?
Rebecca Silver defies all categories.
Excuse me. You are?
It's me
you should be talking to, actually.
I am Rebecca Silver.
And I do not appreciate the tone
that you're taking with my bodyguard.
Oh, goodness, Ms. Silver.
The Recluse of Romance.
We are honored that you will be making
your first public appearance ever
with us.
You look exactly as I dreamed.
I'm just here for the check, really.
Of course. And you will get it
after your public appearance,
Q&A, and book signing.
Oh, chitchat with a bunch of weirdos
dressed as some ridiculous alien queen
they want to bang.
[chuckles]
No problem.
Number one, Garima is a warrior.
- Number two, you're being rude.
- Rude?
That's rich coming from you.
You're the rudest person I know.
You don't get it. You need training.
What time's the Q&A?
In two hours.
Good. We'll be there.
[sighs]
Let's do this.
Okay. Page one.
Is this on audio book?
[narrator over earphones]
They say your life flashes
before your eyes when you die.
But what if, in that moment,
you finally see everything
life's been trying to show you?
That's how I discovered
that a killer was amongst me.
[increases playback speed] I should have
known something was amiss that night.
I was returning from hot yoga
to my sensational cliffside home,
matcha green tea smoothie in hand,
when I noticed my door
was slightly ajar.
[increases playback speed]
I entered, wondering if my dog walker
or cat sitter or personal shopper
or astrologer had failed to close it.
That's when I heard him say,
"There's something
I've been meaning to kill you."
[man] Ladies and gentlemen.
Ladies and gentlemen, please.
My esteemed colleagues,
the honor of having my flag retired
is only rivaled by the honor
of sharing my latest discovery.
To retrieve it required not only besting
the frozen wasteland of the Arctic,
but also the physical limitations
of the human body itself.
But for the sake of exploration,
I prevailed.
And so, without further ado,
I present to you
Gordon Gilchrist's golden mystery...
egg.
[people chuckling]
Now, Vincent.
[all gasping]
In the words of Ray and Mike Tyson,
"I think we found our Myth-tery man."
Come on, science.
Something's happening.
[panting]
I can feel my hand again.
[chuckles]
No, no, no.
The infection...
is spreading.
Gideon, where in the timeline
is John Constantine?
[Gideon] His last known whereabouts
were in 2019 with Gary Green.
Would you like me to connect?
- What are you doing to me Doctor...
- Gideon? Gideon?
What?
[beeping]
We can't have anyone spying on us now,
can we, Raymond?
You're all alone now.
Well, it's you and me.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I'll just do this
the old-fashioned way.
[grunts]
Aha!
- [cell phone ringing]
- [grunting]
- Hello.
- Gary, hi. Ray Palmer here.
By any chance,
have you spoken to Constantine lately?
Worried about Nora, huh?
What? Yes, but no.
I'm calling on a more personal matter.
Say no more. I will be right over.
What? No! No, no, no, Gary.
- No, Gary.
- [crackling]
How can I help?
Oh, no.
You hear something?
[door opening]
- There's a guard.
- Okay.
Don't worry. I can talk my way
into anywhere. [clears throat]
Excuse me, my good man. Can you point me
to the nearest facilities?
I have an urgent need to
relieve my bowel.
Let's go.
We are crushing this mission,
by the way.
No classic Legends mishaps,
and only one historically insignificant
nobody received
- blunt force trauma to the head.
- Hmm.
And now we get our prize.
Wait.
Trip wires.
This is going to require one of us
to squeeze through these trip wires,
maneuvering our bodies
in unexpected ways.
Are you asking me to do that?
No. I'm asking you to hold my coat.
When I wrote Uncaged Desire,
I was trying to uncage my own desire.
A desire to... To... To...
Oh, bollocks! What's the next bit again?
To feel life, not just live it.
You still don't know Rebecca.
Well, I know you, and you're Rebecca.
Your primary mode of communication
is grunting like a caveman.
[grunting]
[sighs] Besides, I mean, Rebecca Silver
is whoever we want her to be.
These people,
they don't know anything about her.
What are you talking about?
They read her books.
They read her letters.
Her letters?
Do you answer your fan mail?
[scoffs]
I just thought all this
was a big laugh at their expense.
Well, it's not.
[exhales]
Hmm.
Be careful.
What the hell?
It's papier-mâché.
Oh, my God.
She did this all for us.
It's all a setup.
- No.
- Yeah.
- You think?
It was a fake magicometer alert.
Sara concocted this whole thing.
- I bet you they're actors, too.
- Yeah.
Gordon Gilchrist,
with the ridiculous facial hair.
- The only thing that's missing? Nazis.
- Yeah.
[gun cocking]
What did you do with the egg, huh?
The real egg.
Oh, she really went all out.
[Nate chuckles softly]
[Zari chuckles softly]
[door opens]
- [Sara] Hey.
- [Agent Sharpe] Well, there you are.
I was beginning to think
you weren't gonna make it.
This is a...
interesting choice of venue.
We can't have book club without Nora.
It takes all three of us
for a book club quorum.
Very sweet.
[Mona chuckles]
- Cheers, babe.
- [Sara] Thank you.
All right. So who do you guys think
is the real killer?
Because I have my theories.
[cell phone dings]
Oh, my God. This can't be real.
- I have to go, now.
- [Sara] What?
You just said that book club requires
all three of you.
It's Rebecca Silver.
She's revealing her identity
at RomantiCon, tonight.
Rebecca Silver?
The sex-positive novelist
reinventing feminism.
Yeah, we know who she is.
Make sure you take lots of pictures.
Oh, my God, thank you.
I can't believe I'm going to be
breathing the same air
as Rebecca Silver.
[squeals, giggles]
[door opens]
- Okay, so...
- Hmm.
What did you think of the book?
Oh, you wanna keep doing book club?
Babe, we don't have to.
We can just forget it.
I thought it would be nice for us
to be able to do something of yours.
Aw!
That's so sweet, thank you.
- I didn't read the book.
- What?
- Sorry.
- Seriously?
Honestly, I usually just drink rosé
and let Mona go on and on
and use it as a mini-vacay for my brain.
Well, it was actually
a really good book.
Wait, wait. Come on. I can still drink
rosé, and you can go on and on.
- Mmm.
- Come on. Come on.
Okay, fine.
So I think the real killer
was the dog walker.
No.
Yes, I mean,
all that pent-up frustration.
She treated him like a doormat.
You can't help me. I need Constantine.
Well, I may not be a master
of the Dark Arts,
but I am an intern of the Dark Arts.
You're interning for Constantine?
Yeah.
He's letting me study his spell books
if I water his plants
while he searches for a cure for Nora.
But, besides, what other options
do you have?
Come on. Tell the Gare-Bear
what ails you.
I don't know how to explain it,
but it feels like there's something
inside of me.
Oh, yeah. You know, there's
a beautiful singer inside of me,
but no one's ever going to meet her.
No. No, Gary. No, Gary. This is bad.
This is very bad,
and I don't know how to get it out.
[snaps fingers]
Indigestion. I know just the spell.
I'll have your pipes cleared out
in no time.
Let me just look it up.
Good thing it's not a demon
because, if it was,
you wouldn't be able to tell me.
Weird rule that keeps the victim silent,
all the while trying to
murder a loved one
in order to seal in
the demonic possession forever.
[grunts]
Why did you just stab yourself?
I didn't.
[gasps]
- You're possessed.
- Yes!
I... I... I can help.
Where is the egg?
[both chuckle]
Take it easy, Hitler Youth.
The egg's broken. It was a crappy prop.
The real egg.
Do not anger me.
Look, this was a good effort,
like really good.
But we've done Nazis before,
but like, real Nazis.
So, if it's okay with you,
I would rather just... [clicks tongue]
pull the plug on this.
- Yeah.
- [man] My friend here
- is a surgeon.
- Oh, nice.
He will kill you until you tell me
where the real egg is.
- Uh, let's tell Sara we're on to her.
- Yeah.
- [beeps]
- Mmm.
- Hello.
- [Zari] Hi, Sara. Nate and Zari here.
Uh, first of all, well-played.
[Nate] Yeah, setting up this
whole adventure for us to go on a date
was way over-the-top,
but, in the same breath,
very sweet.
And if I were to give a note,
the Nazis were just like a tad too much.
What are you...
What are you talking about?
[Nate] Are they the same theater troop
as Ava's parents?
- [Sara] What?
- Sara, drop the act.
Nazis killing us with throwing daggers.
Come on.
Listen to me.
Look, I did purposely put the two of you
on a mission together,
but this is a real mission,
not a game.
Those are real Nazis.
[Nate] Whoa!
And now, young lady, you die.
[Zari sighs]
- Sorry, Nate.
- For what?
[grunting]
Wow.
- You okay?
- Yeah, that was actually really intense.
[door opens]
See, they took care of things
on their own.
And they were clearly about to hook up.
- No, they weren't. Wait.
- You owe me 20 bucks.
Uh-uh! Uh-uh!
Were you guys about to hook up?
- It was definitely on the table.
- No, no, no, no.
- See. I told you.
- Come on... It doesn't matter.
Okay, now that you know that
it's a real mission, where's the egg?
Yeah, and where is Ray?
Isn't he supposed to be
quarterbacking on this?
[groans]
Ray? Ray, come in.
Nate, buddy.
Don't come back to the ship
under any circumstances.
- [Nate] You okay, buddy?
- [Ray] Yeah.
Just cleaning up a storm over here.
I don't want you to trip and break
your neck on the mopped floors.
- Okay, bye.
- [Gary exclaims]
Bye. Okay, that was weird, even for Ray.
- We should check on him.
- You go check on Ray.
We'll handle the egg.
Um... I'm sorry that our first date
got ruined by Nazis.
Who says it's ruined?
[Agent Sharpe squeals softly]
[clears throat] Okay, what do we know?
We found an egg, but it was fake.
Someone stole the real one.
What about that Gordon Gilchrist guy?
He's the one who found it,
so I don't know
why he would have stolen it.
Although I sort of think
his poor assistant, Vincent,
did most of the work.
- Wait. That's just like the book!
- It is?
The book from book club!
Vincent is the doormat!
Look, it's always the doormat.
It was the dog walker in the book,
and, now,
this Vincent guy is mad
that he didn't get any credit.
So we find Vincent, take the egg,
and wipe everyone's memories. Easy.
[Gary] Ray. Ray.
Remember, if you kill a loved one,
Neron will take over.
Oh, well, here's the thing, Gary.
I like you.
But...
Oh...
Yeah.
Got it. Old Gare.
Not loved by the Legends.
Bottom of the pecking order
at the Bureau.
Constantine's plant sitter.
Always the butt of the joke.
Gary, it's not like that.
It is like that, Gary.
No one appreciates you.
They all think you're a fool
that they can use
whenever it's convenient for them.
But I respect you,
and I see your potential.
- Neron?
- Gary, don't listen to him.
He's trying to trick you.
A demon can't renege
on the deals they make.
So you can believe me when I say
I can make you whole again.
"Whole"?
Rebecca, first, let me say
that your novel Uncaged Desires
was a sexual epiphany for me.
[Charlie] I can't say
that I'm surprised.
My writing does have that effect.
But how did Officer Daphne
free Tank Tremors?
Can prison guards release inmates
just because they're in love?
Oh, well, you see, that was a metaphor.
After all, aren't we all
in our own prisons of desire?
Rebecca, in Heatwaves,
who is the unnamed villain
who is stalking Garima?
- Charlie?
- What is a villain?
Is it just someone
with a different point of view?
What's really stalking Garima
are the choices that she made.
So you're the real Rebecca Silver, huh?
Hi. Yes.
I mean, that is what I have embroidered
on my satin pillowcases.
- [all laughing]
- Okay, then.
I have a question
about your novel Raw Hides.
When Captain Cash Harvey
fights the Prairie Bandits,
why does Nasgowa stow away
in his Conestoga wagon?
Well, you see, that is also a metaphor.
That is not a metaphor.
She really did it.
And she died because of it.
The real Rebecca Silver would know.
[Charlie]
I am the real Rebecca Silver.
I have tea with lemon.
- I have a really small dog.
- You're a fraud.
- [all gasping]
- Where is the real Rebecca?
[all chanting]
Where's the real Rebecca?
- Where's the real Rebecca?
Right, go to hell,
you stinking mouth-breathers.
[all gasping]
Where's the real Rebecca?
[all chanting] Where's the real Rebecca?
Quiet! Give me that.
Nasgowa chased Cash for one reason.
It's the same reason humans have gotten
together since the dawn of time.
It's why people like you
come to conventions
and dress up
as your favorite characters.
Why a man sits behind a desk, typing,
pouring out his heart.
Why an author,
a writer, replies to fans.
It's connection.
Human connection.
- I am Rebecca Silver.
- [all gasping]
You are Rebecca.
I'd recognize that wisdom anywhere.
[all cheering and applauding]
[sighs]
I would have come sooner, Nora.
But have you any idea how hard it is
to acquire a phoenix's tail feather?
I didn't. All right.
[exhales]
[chanting]
By the power above and below,
I call on you, Nora Darhk,
to return to this plane and rise reborn.
Come on, love.
Come back to me. Come on, love.
[gasps]
- [Nora grunting]
- [chuckling]
Neron...
No, no, no, it's all right, love.
It's all right.
He's gone. You did it.
- No.
- He's gone.
He has Ray.
Ray?
Gideon, where's Ray?
[hissing]
[Ray] Nate, you shouldn't have come.
Ray, what's going on?
You should leave. You can't let me get...
Ray, what are you saying?
[panting]
You've been acting so weird lately.
- I thought we were bros.
- It's not me.
Don't you see? It's near...
- What's near? Somebody's nearby?
- No.
[groaning]
[Sara] All right, people. Gather around.
Vincent? What's the meaning of this?
- I found it.
- Hand over the egg.
- I should get credit for it.
- The egg is my accomplishment.
It belongs to me.
Everyone's memory of the egg
is about to be erased,
so don't get too bent out of shape.
- Not so fast.
- [grunts]
Finally, the egg is ours.
Oh, man, these guys.
[groans]
I'm Ray. The rest of me isn't.
Nate, you have to get out of here.
You have to leave.
I won't leave you, buddy.
[Nate] Okay, you got possessed by Neron.
You have to go.
- He's gonna make me kill you.
- No, because I believe you,
Raymond, are stronger than he is.
[groans]
- Nate, I'm so sorry.
- [coughs]
Why are you hitting me?
Can't stop.
- We're bros.
- We are bros.
[panting]
[grunting]
Okay, I give up. I give up.
You hear me, Neron? I give up.
Spare Nate, and I'll let you have me.
Just promise me you won't hurt him,
and I won't resist.
[panting]
[Neron as Ray] Deal.
[laughing]
[sighs]
It's nice to have a willing host.
But a promise is a promise.
[people screaming]
- We gotta get that egg.
- On it.
[grunting]
Okay, I got you.
[sighing]
- See them whip skills?
- That gave me an idea for date night.
Hmm.
Oh, come on now. Don't be shy.
You're a little late, Johnny.
I've sort of taken over jolly old Ray.
[exhales]
- I see you've lost a step.
- [chuckles]
That's the thing about mortals.
They age so quickly.
But don't worry, Johnny.
I won't let you die of old age.
Yeah, well, I might be
a little older, mate,
but I've picked up a few tricks
along the way.
[chanting]
[chuckles]
That one's from Marie Laveau.
[Neron as Ray] Cute trick.
But we both know you won't be able
to hold it for long.
You're a parasite.
And I will separate you from Ray Palmer.
Oh, Gary. Where have you been?
I was hiding in the lab.
Then I heard noises.
Yeah, well, go and get my steam trunk,
and we can exorcise this demon
right now.
Damn it, Gary. Now it's not the time
for you to be standing around
like some hapless idiot.
I can't hold this bastard forever.
Do it, now.
[Neron as Ray] Demands a lot from you,
doesn't he, Gary?
But what has he ever done for you?
I, on the other hand,
brought you a gift.
Go ahead. Open it.
[Constantine] No, no, no.
[Constantine grunting]
Don't accept anything from him, Gary.
[gasps]
[chuckling]
My nipple. [gasps]
Gary, listen to me. That part of you,
it belongs to hell now.
All right? Don't let it seduce you.
[Neron as Ray] The same way John
seduced you into being unicorn bait?
- [Gary groans]
- [all screaming]
[neighing]
It's beautiful.
[Constantine] It's cursed.
Now, back away from it, you bloody fool.
[Neron as Ray] It belongs to you, Gary.
[Constantine] Come on, Gary. Think about
what you're doing, all right?
Don't give in to his temptation.
How did I do?
[Mick] Time dweeb!
What the hell are you doing here?
- What do I do?
- [both] Shut up, Gary.
I'm tired of being a doormat.
[panting]
Gary, no.
Well done, Mr. Green.
I'm whole again.
[powering up]
[Gideon] All systems back online.
So, Zari, some big moves back there.
- Yeah, you were really brave.
- Thanks.
So why are you scared
to make a move on Nate?
[door opens]
Nate.
[groaning]
What happened?
- Where is he?
- [Zari] Who?
Ray.
[panting]
Neron's got him.
[sighs]
Sara, hey!
We got you
a collectible RomantiCon tote bag.
- Who died?
- Yeah, what's going on?
I have some bad news.
- I told you, I'm fine.
- [doctor] She's stable, Director.
- Thank you.
- Ava, you shouldn't be here.
You should be scouring
every second of the timeline for Ray.
Agents are on it as we speak.
Why did he do that?
Look, I know you've been through a lot,
but I need your help.
[chuckles] My help?
Why?
Because, no matter how many agents
I send after Neron,
none of them can do what you do.
None of them have the powers
you have, Nora.
And I trust you.
Nora Darhk, I'm asking you
to face another demon.
But this time, I'm asking you to face it
as a member of the Time Bureau.
Let's do this.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
you haven't recovered yet.
[clears throat]
We gotta track down Ray.
[Zari] You will,
when you're better. I promise.
You don't just throw a man down
with these sorts of injuries.
- It's mean-spirited.
- Don't be a baby.
- Does this hurt?
- Yes, Zari. It all hurts.
Where doesn't it hurt, Nate?
- Here?
- Yeah.
Here?
I guess there's an upside
to getting pummeled.
You know how I never let anyone know
what I'm...
really feeling?
It's kind of your thing.
That's how I feel, Nate.
I feel the same.
[egg squelching]
[exhales] Gideon?
What kind of egg is that?
[electronic whirring]
[Gideon] I believe, Dr. Heywood,
it's a dragon egg.
Oh...
Of course.
[theme music playing]