[Zari] Previously on
Legends Of Tomorrow...
That's my mom.
There's no loophole where I can
save my family and not screw up history.
I'm so sorry, Z.
What the hell is going on here?
This is my dad, Hank.
Hello, John.
[Constantine] The knuckle bones
of a martyred saint.
They act as a divining rod able
to detect the presence of beings
not belonging to our world.
Where did the unicorn go?
Ah! Sent that bastard
straight to hell, didn't I?
You need to be part of a team.
No. I would rather bloody
top myself than move in with you lot.
People around me get killed,
or far worse.
[sighs] Bollocks.
[Sara] How's our magical
upgrade going, Ray?
[Ray] Almost done, I think,
though they never covered
how to interface time seismographs
and enchanted bones
in the IVU Ph.D program.
Ah.
Well, that should do it.
My peers would say that science
and magic don't mix.
But to them, I'd ask,
"Have you seen The Fifth Element?"
Am I right?
IVU sounds like a real party school.
[Sara sighs] I hope this works.
We need a way to pinpoint
magical threats on the timeline.
I mean, who knows
what kind of creatures are out there
wreaking havoc on history.
- Like, uh, vampires.
- Gremlins.
Aswangs.
Cannibalistic Filipino werebeasts
with proboscis-like tongues.
I've been doing some research
just in case.
I thought that's why we had Constantine.
Yeah. About that,
Constantine is...
Tired, hungover
and in need of a stiff one.
[trunk thuds]
Dealer's choice as to
what that's a euphemism for.
He's here.
Yeah, I meant what I said
about joining you lot,
but then, I pictured that same lot
squaring off against
some of the manky buggers
that I've come up against,
and I thought, "You know what?
You're right."
You're all bloody doomed without me.
One Aswang will take you down
without breaking a sweat.
[laughs] New Legend alert.
I better go update the chore wheel.
[Constantine] Whoa, hang on, sunshine.
I'm not a bloody Legend.
I'm merely offering my services
as a consultant,
and, as such, I have some stipulations.
I don't do silly costumes.
I expect full benefits.
And I require no less than
two weeks paid vacation.
- Vacation?
- Paid?
Easy.
[whirring]
Hey, it worked.
[Zari] Will you look at that?
We already got a...
Do we have a special name
for these magical fugitives?
Well, I was thinking, since they're
mysteries involving mythical beings,
we could go with "Myth-teries."
"Fugitives," it is. What does it say?
Salem, Massachusetts, 1692.
First day on the job, and you're
taking me to the bloody witch trials.
Well, I hope you're feeling
morally superior
because we are getting
our Puritan Purit-on!
That was too much, right?
[Constantine] I'm telling you,
your machine is clearly buggered.
There's nothing magical
about Puritan New England.
I know. I was there.
But it could all be different now.
Oh, come on. If a creature landed there,
why would it idle in the absolute
worst possible place for magic.
People of Salem are paranoid
and petty. And besides,
every magical creature knows
that, if you wanna get weird,
you go to New York.
Then we need to find it before it flees.
All right, well, I agreed
to help you save history,
not take part in
your little role-playing adventures.
Call me if you find anything.
If he's staying, I'm staying.
Besides, no fun in Puritan times.
The Church banned
burning people at the stake.
[Sara] Well, they didn't
actually burn people.
That was the Middle Ages.
The Puritans used the gallows,
but, yeah, sure. Stay.
You know, I actually miss having
someone Natesplain history to us.
- Me, too.
- [Ray] Speaking of which,
I wonder how Operation
"Dinner with Dad" is going.
Thanks.
Good steak.
So what do you do for work these days?
Little bit of this, little bit of that.
You?
Same old, same old.
Sir, your credit card was declined.
I, um... I must've given you
the wrong one. [clears throat]
Here you go.
And this one expired in 1953.
And I don't know why I still carry it.
Do you accept Athenian tetradrachm?
Notgeld? Is that...
Nathaniel. I've got this.
Guess the deductive historical
reconstruction business
is a little slow this time of the year.
Yeah, and I see it's still paying off
to be a Beltway Bandit.
Really, Nathaniel?
That's how you wanna end this?
After we connect over a nice dinner.
Have we?
All you've talked about was the steak.
What the hell else
am I supposed to talk about?
If you'd rather just sit there
and silently judge me...
Oh, like you're not
doing the same thing.
Of course I was, Nathaniel.
I put you through grad school
to what? To collect rare currency?
Then maybe I should follow
your example, right?
Make a fortune wasting tax payers' cash
on some secret government projects
that you can't even explain.
It puts food on your plate.
How's that for an explanation?
I don't need your money.
As a matter of fact,
I don't need any of this.
Of course. Running away again, huh?
I'll see you in another two years.
[sighs]
I forgot my leftovers.
Nathaniel...
Ah, poor bird
Take thy flight
High above the sorrows
Of this sad night
Good morrow. Good morrow.
Not the friendliest bunch.
[Sara] Tone it down, Ray.
This isn't a fun time period.
- These hats say otherwise.
- Just try not to stand out.
Salem isn't exactly
welcoming of outsiders.
You know, just like every other
time in history.
They're just worse at hiding it.
[crowd chanting] Witch! Witch! Witch!
[man screams] Witch!
Wife of Satan, confess your sins!
Tell now, what saw thee
for grounds of accusation?
I saw her, Reverend Parsons,
dancing in the woods.
- Bare as the day she was born.
- [crowd gasps]
Jane Hawthorne,
what say you to this accusation?
I have done no harm. I swear it.
But this man says he bore witness
to your witchcraft.
She has lain with the devil.
[Jane] I would never.
Not with the devil.
Nor with any man
since my husband's passing.
Much to your frustration, good sir.
[Reverend] Goody Hawthorne.
You are hereby under arrest
and accused of witchcraft!
Your trial will commence
on the morrow.
And if thou be convicted, we will
purge your kind from our community.
You cannot do this!
My daughter needs me!
Prudence!
Mother! [grunts]
Have mercy! Please!
[crowd chanting] Witch! Witch!
Burn the witch!
Witch! Witch! Witch!
Well, there are definitely
monsters in Salem.
Just not the magical kind.
[crowd chanting] Witch! Witch! Witch!
- Witch! Witch! Witch!
- [crows cawing]
Crows. That's ominous.
Despite the gothic association,
the American crows actually are very...
[screaming]
Never mind.
[crowd clamoring]
[crows cawing]
The witch! She commands them!
Remove her from here,
and let's go! Go!
[Jane struggling]
It couldn't have been her, could it?
Whatever it is,
it looks like we were right.
There is magic in Salem.
All right, let's give this thing
a whirl, shall we?
Gideon, do us a favor and mix us up
some ingredients
so I can restock
the old apothecary, will you?
Out of my way.
I need some mustard.
Yeah, yeah.
I'll be just a minute, mate.
Now, be a doll, Gideon, and mix together
a pinch of possum's tail
with three ounces of frog's testes.
[knocking on door]
Open the door! I need to take a leak!
[exclaims]
- What's that smell?
- Spell book.
Bound in human skin. It gets a bit
rank if you don't soak it in water.
Get out of my chair, you weasel.
I'm watching the football.
The game's on already, mate.
You want a marmite crumpet?
- What did you call me?
- You know,
you need to simmer down
a little bit, sweetheart.
You see, I don't like to share
my space any more than you,
- but here we are.
- And why are you here?
Hey. Sorry to break up the bonding
session, but we found our fugitive,
and we think it's a real witch.
Well, a real witch must be
off her trolley to hang around here.
Well, we just saw a woman command
a murder of crows,
and now I know why they call it that.
Well, Jane was bound, gagged,
and taken away.
Those birds were just protecting her
from that mob.
I say more power to them.
And I agree with you in theory,
but we still have to remove that power.
Gideon, what do you have
on Jane Hawthorne?
[Gideon] On October 29th, 1692,
Jane Hawthorne's execution was
at the center
of what came to be known as
"The burning of Salem."
[Ray] On the day she hung,
all of the people of Salem
spontaneously combusted.
The whole town was set ablaze.
Sounds like my kind of woman.
Well, the incident was enough
to convince the public
that witches were real.
Whatever it is,
Jane's at the center of it.
Hang on a minute.
You said that she was gagged.
- [Sara] Yeah.
- Did any of you actually hear her
cast the spell?
[inhales sharply] You see,
spells are a verbal game, maties.
Was there anyone else there?
Someone who would wanna protect Jane?
- Prudence.
- Her daughter.
A malevolent demon has attached
itself to the child,
and the mother is being blamed.
I've seen it a million times over.
Easy, peasy, lemon squeezy.
Let's get to it, shall we?
Well, look who's started to care.
But I am not wearing a costume.
I'll see you later, big man.
[door closes]
[Agent Sharpe] Gary?
Is that you?
Did you sleep walk to work again?
Oh, my God!
What is wrong with you?
Nate? What the hell are you doing here?
And why aren't you wearing pants?
I can explain. And thank you
for not mentioning the shower cap.
- Pretend I did.
- Coconut oil.
Makes my hair more buoyant.
- Really? I should try that.
- Mmm-hmm.
And the pants situation?
Well, I decided
to extend my trip to 2018,
and I may possibly be living
a little bit at the Bureau.
You couldn't spring for a hotel?
Well, here's a fun fact
about staying in the present.
It costs money.
And as a Legend, your salary is
the friendships you make along the way.
Gotcha.
And you?
I know you love paperwork, but...
Oh, yes. I'm presenting my budget
to the Department of Defense tomorrow.
Rip was always good at
schmoozing the bigwigs.
It was never really my thing.
Now, with this whole magic initiative,
we're gonna need even more money.
I can help. I'm great at schmoozing.
- [stammers] Oh, no, thank you.
- What? Why not?
I need a place to stay.
You need a wingman.
It'll be fun. We can hang out.
We can get into adventures...
Okay. Okay. You know what?
Let's do it.
Just put some pants on.
Hey.
You just got schmoozed.
Look at her. She doesn't have anyone.
Soul, soul, soul cake
Please, good missus, a soul cake
All right. Let's move.
[Prudence] Please, good missus
A soul cake
An apple, a plum, a peach
Or a cherry
[crow cawing]
Any good thing to make us
All merry
One for Peter
One for Paul
Three for He
Who made us all
[rustling]
Why dost thou follow me?
Hi, Prudence. We're just here to help.
You're strangers.
I have no need of your aid.
Now, be gone with haste!
John.
[chanting]
- What magic is this?
- Look, it's gonna be okay.
[evil laughter echoes]
[Constantine] Agent of the damned.
Show yourself, you fetid creature!
Show yourself, you cursed beast!
Reveal your hideous form!
[magical glissando]
Hello.
What in the Disney hell is this?
[laughs] You gotta be kidding me.
That's your monster?
Monster? Why, I'm nothing of the sort.
I am a Fairy Godmother, and I mean
only to make dreams come true
because a dream is a wish your heart...
Don't say another word.
Constantine, please tell me
you have something for this.
This is, uh, new.
Prudence, this is your Fairy Godmother?
It is. She protects me.
- By hurting other people.
- Not at all!
I only want to help little Prudence.
For you see,
- there are times the world is scary.
- [enchanting music playing]
Times the world is bad.
But when your Godmother's a fairy...
There's no reason to be sad
Is that music?
So fear not if things
Don't look to be
The way that you preferred
Just make a wish
And look to me
I'll sing these magic words
Shut up!
I didn't want her to stop singing.
Ah, to hell with this.
- [chanting]
- Oh, my.
You don't want to do that.
And why wouldn't we?
Because Prudence and I share a bond.
If you send me to hell,
she goes right down with me.
These people want to send us to hell.
You don't want to go to hell,
do you, dearie?
No.
Would you like me to make them go away?
As you wish.
We'll start with some tree roots
Up from the ground
Prudence, you don't need her!
Then summon some birds
What a beautiful sound
Okay, you can stop singing now.
And just as they gather
Over your head
[crows cawing]
[Sara] Prudence!
You don't have to do this!
I'll tell them "Attack!"
And you'll all end up...
We're here to save your mother!
[Fairy Godmother]...dead!
Godmother, wait.
Release them.
As you wish.
[magical glissando]
[all groan]
But I'm at your call when you need me.
You gotta admit, though,
that was a catchy tune.
- [Prudence] Where am I?
- Some place safe.
Just until we can get you home.
I've seen many wonders these past days.
And I believe you, like Godmother,
were sent by the Lord.
The answer to our prayers.
Here. It's a donut.
[video game music playing]
- [Beebo] I love you.
- [Mick shudders]
Many wonders indeed.
All right, guys.
Remember the three C's of pitching.
Confidence, charisma...
Oh, crap.
That's my dad.
- Wait a second. That's your dad?
- Yeah.
This must be one
of the secret government projects
he can never tell me about.
I can't go in there, Ava.
I will make this worse.
Come on, Nate.
You're family. How bad could it be?
Oh, last time I saw him,
I insulted his life's work,
and literally said,
"I don't need your money."
- Oh. Okay, that's bad.
- Mmm-hmm.
[Agent Sharpe] Look,
I cannot do this alone.
- You don't have to.
- Thank you.
Gary, you know
my part of the pitch, right?
Okay, okay. Maybe I can do this alone.
No, look at this guy.
He's got confidence.
He's got charisma. He's got...
Crap. I got my arm stuck
in the poster tube.
- [sighs]
- [Gary] Ah!
Ava, I know my dad, okay?
You're not gonna want to go
in there without backup.
Fine. Gary, you're in.
All right, Director Sharpe.
Let's give them
the old ham and eggs.
[sighs]
Damn it!
The Godmother was telling the truth.
We can't send her to hell without
sending Prudence down with her.
Bloody Fairy Godmothers
are like parasites
who feed off their hosts.
Their magic, it only works
at the whim of their charge.
The girl will have to reject
the Godmother.
Who's gonna give up that kind of power?
Especially in her situation.
We just have to give her what she wants.
If we save her mom,
she won't need the Godmother.
Z, we can't.
I checked the historical record.
Jane Hawthorne was executed as a witch.
That was canon before the Fairy
Godmother affected the timeline.
We can't change that.
So we're just gonna let them do it?
Sara, this is exactly what it's like
where I'm from.
The tribalism, scapegoating,
persecuting someone
just because they're different,
while other people just stand by
and do nothing.
I don't want it to go down
like this either, Z.
I'm sorry, but we don't have a choice.
Look, I promised her
that I would help her.
Well, you made a promise
that we can't keep.
The priority here is separating
Prudence from her Godmother.
That's how we're gonna save more lives.
So, in the meantime, we just let her
think we're saving her mom.
- [sighs]
- Great.
- [man] Stop at once! Whoa!
- [explosion]
[sword fighting in distance]
- I'm here to save you, Jane.
- Who art thee?
We need to go. Now.
No.
Look, I get that you're scared,
but I can protect you.
You need to trust me. Come, please.
I believe you mean well.
But I cannot go.
These people are insane.
They're gonna kill you no matter what.
They are afraid.
[Jane] And fear brings out
the worst in all of us.
Therefore, I must forgive them,
for they know not what they do.
Well, at least one of you Puritans
gets the point of that book.
If I disappear now,
others will pay for my cowardice.
And I will not allow
innocents to suffer.
What about your daughter's suffering?
Her powers.
Think about how your actions
are going to affect her.
She is the only one of whom I think.
I made her swear to me
that she would never use
her power henceforth.
As long as she heeds my command,
my Prudence will live.
But what kind of life is it going to be,
where you died
and she couldn't protect you?
That guilt is gonna follow her
her whole life.
She'll end up mad at herself
and mad at the world.
Please. We have to go.
My daughter is strong.
In time, with God's love,
she will let go of these burdens.
Jane, don't do this, please!
- [man groans]
- [man 2] Fetch the Pastor at once!
Thou must go with haste!
[man 3] She lifted him high!
[man 4] Head for the jail!
Quick! With haste!
You shall not flee
your punishment, witch!
Your trial awaits.
Useless piece of...
[Fairy Godmother laughing]
I know you're there, you old bat.
Why don't you show yourself, eh?
We'll have ourselves a little chat.
A simple "please and thank you"
would do, my pet,
[chuckles] although it has been
quite amusing watching you prattle on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, all right, Granny.
You've had your fun.
Now it's time to let go of dear Prudence
and be on your merry way.
All I want is to make the world
a happier place.
And you got her mother thrown
in the bloody clink.
And what about that bloke
who had his eyes
pecked out of his skull, eh?
That man was a liar.
They're all liars!
And simple-minded pests like that
must be taught a lesson!
Ooh, pests. Intriguing choice of words.
Before Prudence, all the girls
I helped were just take, take, take.
"I want a new dress, Godmother."
"I want to go to the ball, Godmother."
So I gave and I gave,
no matter how absurd the request.
I mean, who would ever choose
to wear glass slippers?
Imagine the blisters!
And what did I get in return?
A thousand years locked away
in a dank and miserable dimension.
So it was humans who put you away, eh?
Hell, it serves you right,
you bitter old nag.
You don't want Prudence happy.
You want her raging.
That's how you settle the score.
By using a child's anger
to rain down hellfire
on those poor bastards out there.
Hellfire, you say?
Not a bad idea.
Ta-ta, my pet.
My Prudence will be needing me soon.
[sighs]
[Hank] And what situations require
our continued funding, Director Sharpe?
Sir, do you remember when dinosaurs
took over downtown Los Angeles,
or when a telepathic gorilla
tried to kill Barack Obama?
You know that I don't.
[Agent Sharpe] And that's
because we did our job.
The timeline was in complete
shambles, but I'm proud to say
that we finally put things
back into its proper place.
So, your job is done?
What are all these people
still doing here?
You see, the timeline is very fragile.
There's always a threat
of one kind or another.
And now, there's magic.
- Magic?
- Yes. You see, last year,
there was a time demon named Mallus.
Malice. But we're not gonna...
[Gary] And in order to kill him,
the Legends broke his prison,
which surprise, surprise,
released an unknown number
of other dangerous magical beings
all of whom got spat out
across the timeline
and now, must be hunted down
and sent to hell.
- Did I miss anything?
- No, actually.
You know, I've had to oversee some
really far out projects in my career.
But I can't, in good conscience,
have the DOD pay for a department
that fights fairy tales!
Sir, with all due respect,
you cannot shut us down. Please.
The damage that these supernatural
fugitives can cause is unfathomable.
Director Sharpe, you seem like
a very capable leader.
Now, you say there's magic out there.
And I say that I need proof.
- Well...
- [Gary] Here's proof.
- A unicorn ate my nipple!
- [gasps]
- Right.
- Um...
I'm shutting this place down.
Gary, put it away!
[Sara] Have you guys seen Z?
- With the witch.
- Prudence isn't a witch.
- Not that witches are bad.
- Prudence is alone. I just checked.
Gideon?
[Gideon] Miss Tomaz gave me
explicit instructions
not to tell you
that she was leaving the ship.
That can't be good.
Stay with the kid.
Don't piss her off.
Where the hell are you, Z?
And Io, she called upon her master
to set her free!
And t'were it not for these
brave men, she might've succeeded.
And now,
before your very eyes,
- the mark of the devil upon her flesh!
- [crowd gasping]
[whispering] That's
a birth mark, you jerk.
Watch now as I attempt
to draw blood from Satan's brand!
It will not bleed.
[Jane screaming]
[groans]
[exclaims]
Back! The word of God
shall be my shield!
[woman] The Lord has mercy!
[crowd exclaiming]
It's the witch! Stop her
before she destroys us all!
[Zari] Stop it! She didn't do anything!
[crowd exclaiming]
Why can't you idiots
see what he's doing?
He's convincing you to kill
your neighbors for imaginary crimes!
If you're looking for the real source
of evil in this town,
it's him!
Witch. Witch! Another witch!
Remove that cursed bauble from her.
[man] Let's stop her!
[choking]
[all choking]
[coughs]
What the hell am I doing?
Take her! Now!
I'm sorry.
No!
The Devil's hold over these witches
is stronger than we've ever faced.
Hanging them will not suffice.
They must burn!
[crowd shouting] Burn! Burn! Burn!
[straining]
[Fairy Godmother] You feel that,
don't you, dearie?
Something is amiss.
I worry for my mother. I thought
she'd be rescued by now.
It does seem odd.
You were promised
by those strange visitors
that she would be saved, were you not?
Curious then,
that they have not delivered.
Shall we see what the delay is?
- Can you do that?
- I can do anything, sweetkins.
All you must do is ask.
[Sara] According
to the historical record,
Jane Hawthorne was executed as a witch.
That was canon before the Fairy
Godmother affected the timeline.
We can't change that.
Looks like your new friends lied to you.
They have no intention of saving
your poor helpless mummy.
Now, what would you have me do
about that, my pet?
Oh! Prudence, hold on.
Out of my way, you swine.
[magical glissando]
[pig grunts]
[Fairy Godmother] Ta-ta.
Bloody hell. [chanting]
Shut up!
[muffled groaning]
Stay back!
Come, dearie.
Let's show these nasty villagers
what real magic looks like.
[pigs grunting]
Hey, how'd it go out there?
Well...
You better start packing your things
because he just gave
the entire Bureau an eviction notice.
Did you tell him
about the magical creatures?
Oh, yeah. He's not buying it.
He needs proof.
Oh, that is such a Hank thing.
Maybe he'll believe you,
why don't you just tell him
the truth?
Nate, it can't go worse
than what just happened back there.
Look, I spent my whole life trying
to convince Hank
that I made something of myself.
And most of the time,
I was faking it, okay?
So he's supposed to suddenly
believe I'm a superhero
who fought a unicorn. Come on.
Look, I know it's hard doing good
when it seems like no one notices,
but I've seen the good
that you can do, okay?
And that's why I believe
that you can help us here.
Not because you're Hank's son,
but because you... Look at me.
You are a hero, okay?
Now Gary's seeing him out.
We still have time.
You schmoozed me.
Did it work?
You sure I can't interest you
in a coffee, tea?
- Fizzy water?
- Just the validation.
I think you're doing a great job.
Validation.
Okay.
Hello? Is anybody here?
Gideon. I don't have time for this.
I need proof that magic exists,
and I need it...
[pig grunts]
Hello, piggy. What are you doing here?
[Gideon] I'm afraid that's
no ordinary pig, Mr. Heywood.
Shut the front door.
Ray, that's you?
Slow down.
[pig grunts]
You got turned into a pig,
but you think you'll be better soon
because the team's working on it
as we speak?
Mick got turned too?
Well, where is he?
[pig grunts]
Listen, I know you're
in a situation right now.
But I could really use your help
at the Bureau.
Yes, of course, I'll carry you. Come on.
[crowd shouting]
[Reverend] In the name
of our Heavenly Father,
- let these witches burn!
- [crowd cheering]
Cleanse this town and its people
of this evil
and send these wretched souls
to their master in hell!
You don't have to listen to him!
You know this is wrong!
This woman is your neighbor!
Your friend! She doesn't
deserve this. No one does.
This witch is more dangerous
than any we have faced!
- She wore this cursed stone!
- [crowd gasps]
[crowd chanting] Witch! Witch! Witch!
[crossbow bolt whizzing]
Let the women go.
Light the pyre. Let God's work be done.
Do it, and he's dead.
My soul will live with God
for all of time.
Screw it.
[grunting]
No!
[crowd cheering]
Stop!
[magical glissando]
Free them from the pyre.
Mother! What's wrong with her?
- What did they do?
- She's gonna be okay.
Now, my pet. What shall we do
about that horrid man
who hurt your mummy?
I want him to burn.
[magical glissando]
[Nate] Hank.
- Are you sure this is gonna work?
- No.
Nathaniel? What are you doing here?
I work here. That's right, Dad.
I'm a time traveler.
How do you even know
about the Time Bureau?
What are you doing with a pig?
You want proof magic exists?
Well, here it is.
[pig grunts]
Just give me a minute.
[whispering] Now, Ray. Ray, do it.
What, no? Just come to life.
Prudence, listen to me.
This isn't who you are.
You're a good person.
He tried to kill my mother.
This town, these people.
They've killed so many others already.
They deserve to burn!
And they will pay for their ignorance
but not like that.
How else will they learn, dearie?
If these people aren't taught
a lesson today,
they will go and hurt others
for days and years to come.
You come from the future.
Can you honestly tell this child
that the hearts of men change
in all that time?
Do they?
No, they don't.
People always fear
what they don't understand.
And that fear turns them into monsters.
But we can't let it turn us
into monsters, too.
We have to be better than them.
Be better? What nonsense!
Be stronger, my pet!
Show them the power that you possess!
Make them grovel at your feet
where they belong!
Think of your mother!
Yes, think of your mother.
What would she want you to do?
Get blood on your hands
or forgive them?
"For they know not what they do."
Godmother...
Fire and brimstone, coming right...
I release you.
[gasping]
That's more like it.
Son, I don't know
who put you up to this but...
Oh, yeah. I'm also a superhero.
And this is my friend, Ray.
Oh. Hi, Mr. Heywood. Nice to
finally meet you. [clears throat]
How much money do you need
to ensure this never happens again?
[clears throat] 4.2 billion a year, sir.
Done.
Help!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
You vile, meddling bitch!
[chanting]
And that is for taking my mouth,
you silly old bat.
I was so terrified
of losing you, Mother.
And I you, my sweet girl.
So what now? Am I free?
Yeah, you're free. But you're gonna
need a change of scenery.
Thank you.
Where on Earth are you taking me?
Oh, not on Earth, love.
Where I'm sending you is a touch hotter,
or so I hear.
You intend to send me to hell.
I could be persuaded otherwise.
I'm listening.
You need a host to conduct your magic.
Let's just say,
I'm in need of a miracle.
You want to be my new host?
Tit for tat, dearie.
[laughs]
John Constantine.
Yes, my pet. I know exactly who you are.
I know you're on the run,
and I know who's coming for you.
And believe me, I'd rather face hell
than piss him off!
Well, I am happy to oblige.
[Constantine chanting]
This is your last chance, Granny.
There's no helping you, dearie.
You're more damned than I!
Bibbity bobbity... [screams]
[Gideon] Miss Tomaz has entered
the bridge.
I see that, Gideon. Exit Narc mode.
"Narc mode."
You're not the only one on the ship
who knows how to get Gideon
to do things.
- I wanted to talk to you...
- You don't have to say anything.
I already hate myself.
No, it's not like that. I...
I understand why you did what you did.
I've felt that rage before, a lot.
Well, I haven't.
Turns out sarcasm is
a really great way to hide
some seriously deep-seated anger.
I get it.
And that's all I wanted to say,
is that if you wanna talk to me,
I'm here.
Look.
In 2018, I found my mom.
I didn't talk to her,
but she was right there and...
I couldn't think of a way to save her.
Yeah, it's hard.
I've lost a lot of people, too,
and I still think about saving them.
I don't think that anger ever goes away.
That's okay. You just can't hold it
in all the time.
I'm not really sure
what I'm supposed to do with it.
Well, let's figure it out, together.
And then we formed Voltron-Beebo
and opened a serious can
of whoop ass on Malice,
thus saving the universe
for the second time.
So this is what you've been doing
with your life the past two years.
Wow, Nathaniel. You did it.
You finally found a useful
application for that history degree.
Still not letting it go.
Take the win, son.
You've done good here.
I look forward to working with you.
- Dinner, Friday?
- Yeah.
Here you go. Parking is right this way.
Did you hear that?
That's 4.2 billion. Hell to the yes!
Meet me uptown, Ava Sharpe.
Mmm.
- Okay, that was terrifying.
- Yeah.
But clearly effective. Thank you.
Anytime. Always happy to help.
- How about tomorrow?
- Hmm?
Now that I have $4.2 billion
burning a hole in my pocket.
You said you could use some income.
I could use a guy like you around here.
Think about it.
Clothes. Check.
Non-cloven digits. Check.
Portal home.
Check.
After you, my friend.
Um...
You go ahead.
I'm gonna stick around
a little while longer,
give dinner with dad another go.
Oh. Okay. Yeah. Great.
So we'll see you for the next one.
Absolutely.
- Okay.
Okay.
[theme music playing]