Please!
Vandal Savage.
An evil dictator blessed
with immortality.
He has achieved what no one
in human history ever has.
He has conquered the entire planet.
What's your name, son?
Jonas.
Your mother was brave,
just as your father was foolish.
Which are you?
So you take after your mother, huh?
Or not.
Caesar.
Hitler.
Per Degaton.
Rank amateurs compared to Savage.
His forces have already
claimed the lives of billions.
And if we possess
the means to stop him
and again do nothing...
then their blood is on our hands.
As a Time Master of long standing,
you seem to forget.
Our responsibility
is to protect the timeline,
not humanity.
You wish to engage in the very
sort of manipulation of time
that we are sworn to prevent.
And yet, if we allow humanity
to perish
at the hands of evil,
then what universe
are we custodians of?
What if, in trying
to save the world from Savage,
you make it vulnerable to
another, more terrible despot?
We are not warriors,
Captain Hunter.
We possess no army.
And I'm not asking for one.
Just a single time ship...
and your permission
to change history
before Vandal Savage
puts an end to it.
I'm not appealing to you
as Time Masters...
but as humans, please.
Grant me the authority
to change the timeline
just this once.
How did the council meeting go,
Captain Hunter?
Exactly as expected, Gideon.
- So we are proceeding?
- Indeed.
Prepare the Waverider for takeoff.
Set a course.
United States.
Star City. January, 2016.
The early second millennium A.D.
The golden age of gasoline engines,
online pornography,
and those silly little smartphones.
What are we going to retrieve,
Captain?
Oh, not what.
Who.
I need you to pull up some files,
Gideon.
The eight men and women
who'll be joining us
on our little crusade.
You usually prefer
to work alone, Captain.
This time, I'll need a team.
First recruit, Dr. Raymond Palmer.
Also known as the Atom.
This feels good,
being back in the field.
Not that this is a field, but...
Ray, are you up for this?
Oh, too late to turn back now.
Huh. Someone removed
the central processing unit.
Are you sure?
I designed the computer's CPU,
so, yeah, pretty sure.
Well, HIVE would only
remove it if they knew...
You had me shrink down and fly
into their secret computer lab?
My night's about to get
a whole lot worse, isn't it?
Oh, you can take them.
They have guns.
You have a super-suit.
It's time to start growing.
This is gonna get a little rough.
Oh, I am not one of your adversaries.
Next recruit, Sara Lance.
Former member of the League
of Assassins, also formerly dead.
Miss Lance?
Join me for a drink?
I have come quite a long way
to meet you.
Firestorm, the merged super-form
of one Jefferson Jackson
and Professor Martin Stein.
Caution, Jefferson,
83 percent of the chemicals
in this factory are combustible.
Yeah? Tell that to Rambo.
Thought I told you to be careful.
What's the use of sharing
my intelligence if you won't listen?
Stop bossing me around
like I'm one of your
snot-nosed undergrads.
- Excuse me.
- Who are you?
Kendra Saunders and Carter Hall.
The latest reincarnations
of Hawkman and Hawkgirl.
Kendra.
- You, my love, almost got us killed.
- Thank you.
Your flying is still clumsy
- like a bird just out of the nest...
- Well maybe that's because
up until two months ago,
I was a barista,
not some damn winged
demi-goddess.
Have you two considered
couples counseling?
I hear it's quite popular
in this century.
There seems to be an error, Captain.
These candidates,
Leonard Snart and Mick Rory,
are a pair of criminals.
- There's no error, Gideon.
- Drop your weapons!
Oh, fry, you little piggies!
A minivan?
Really, Snart?
Cops'll never hassle a dad
buying diapers
in the middle of the night.
- What the...
- Watch it!
What a headache!
Stein?
What the hell are you doing here?
I'm as ignorant as you, for once.
Where are we?
Why don't you ask the dude who
knocked us out and kidnapped us?
British dude with a flashy thing?
- Ring any bells?
- The name's Rip Hunter.
I'm from East London.
Oh, and the future.
Nice to meet you, Rip.
Oh, while you were incapacitated
I may have tampered
with your weapons.
I've assembled you all
because I need your help.
The future of the world is in peril
because of a man by the name
of Vandal Savage.
That can't be.
We destroyed him.
Yeah, the Green Arrow
and Flash helped us do it.
And therein lay the problem.
Unless you or Mr. Hall
deliver the death blow,
Savage can be restored
from but a single cell.
What the hell are you talking about?
Vandal is immortal.
Kendra and I reincarnate.
Yeah, I've done that.
And what the hell does
this Randall guy got to do with us?
Vandal.
In the future, he will employ
the evil he's perfected over
his long life
and the power he has amassed
throughout history
to finally... conquer the world.
I've been tasked with assembling
an elite team to stop him.
- How?
- To travel through time.
To capture Savage
before he grows into
the monster he becomes.
You got the wrong guy.
- "Hero" ain't on my resume.
- Or mine.
I know it's difficult
for you to fathom.
But where... when I'm from...
the year 2166,
you and everyone on this roof
aren't just considered heroes...
You're legends.
Legends?
I... I hate to nitpick
but doesn't a legend have to be dead?
Yeah, see, that's a
deal breaker for me.
So I'm gonna pass.
It's dangerous for any of you
to know too much
about your own futures.
But I am here because each of you
as individuals,
is destined for greatness.
I could get behind that.
And, because if you don't follow me,
this is what is in store
for your world
150 years from now.
I could have chosen
any time and any place.
Of all the people who ever lived,
I chose you eight.
I certainly hope
that you won't let me...
and the world, down.
If your answer is yes, meet
me at this address in 36 hours.
- I had that.
- I know.
It's fun to watch you kick and punch
and skewer bad guys, but...
I need a minute of your time.
I'm sure Captain Hunter
will return me
to the moment I left. But I thought
you know, just in case, someone
should I know I was gone.
We went up against Savage.
He does not go down easy.
That's why Hunter's recruited a team.
A team that includes
Leonard Snart and Mick Rory.
So, what do you know
about Captain Hunter?
He's a Time Master
from the 22nd century.
It's a little hard to Google.
So you know nothing...
and yet you trust him?
I'm as trusting as you are cynical.
Well, I'm cynical
and it's difficult for me
to trust anyone.
But that has kept me alive.
I died once.
At least, the world thought I did.
You know what happened?
Nothing.
All the money, all the buildings,
all the inventions...
the world didn't care.
My life, ultimately, didn't matter.
Rip is giving me the chance
to help save the world.
I have to take it.
Keep your head on a swivel
while you're at it.
206 times.
Savage has killed both of us
206 times!
Yeah, and I'm not too eager
about making it 207.
So what?
You just going to run away?
We've tried that before.
Look, I know you don't remember
your past lives yet.
But I remember so much of it.
God, if you only knew
how I loved you
and how much...
How much it hurt every time
he took you away from me.
Have you ever stopped to think
that maybe, just maybe,
we can't actually beat him?
But this time, we wouldn't
be facing him alone.
And, we almost defeated him
with help before.
Yeah, almost.
Kendra, this is our best chance
to stop him forever.
The woman I've loved for millennia
wouldn't be scared of it.
Look.
Past lives we'd fight, argue.
A lot.
But, we'd settle matters as warriors.
What?
Like I beat you...
and you give up this plan
to follow Hunter?
Yeah. Except you won't be able
to beat me.
But you can absolutely try.
Winner gets to decide, little lady.
I remember when you told
Mom and Dad
that you wanted to go to
sleep away camp.
This'll be a little different.
Time travel.
I can't believe we're talking
about it like it's something real.
I know.
I think you should go.
Laurel, I died.
I'm still picking up those pieces.
The Lazarus Pit brought me back
but it left me with this...
need to take.
To kill.
I'm dangerous.
After you died,
I needed a channel for my grief.
I found it in becoming
the Black Canary.
I found it in you.
For me, being the Canary
was never that positive.
Then don't be the Canary.
Do what Oliver's been doing.
Do what this Rip Hunter
is offering you
the chance to do and...
Be a hero in the light.
Be the White Canary.
Where did you get this?
I have a resourceful friend
named Cisco.
Where's the mask?
You don't need it anymore.
You've lived in the shadows
long enough.
I can't believe you're thinking of
hooking up with the Englishman.
We're thieves. Crooks. Criminals.
I have no desire to save the world.
Especially a hundred years
after I'm dead.
He said across time, Mick.
What about the years before?
Before fingerprints
and surveillance cameras
and DNA analysis.
Why did we become criminals?
Because we hate working
and we love money.
We could steal the Mona Lisa
straight off Da Vinci's easel.
Snatch the Hope Diamond
before it was discovered.
This is everything we got into
thieving for in the first place.
More than everything.
You want me in? I'm in.
But I'm not gonna be anyone's hero.
Jefferson, it's imperative
we remain together
for our powers to work.
In case you haven't noticed,
I'm still getting used
to the whole powers thing.
And now that's you're adding
time travel to the mix...
Do you have any idea
what an extraordinary
opportunity we've been given?
A chance to get murdered
by an immortal psychopath.
No thanks.
Look, I'm a 20-year-old
auto mechanic.
The world is better off without
me trying to save it.
I don't understand your decision.
But, I respect it.
Perhaps I can persuade Mr. Hunter
that he needs my knowledge
as a physicist
and not my abilities as Firestorm.
So I propose we have a toast...
to my grand and solo adventure.
To saving the world.
Knock yourself out.
You took the words
right out of my mouth.
Professor!
This is the place.
I think we're being punked.
- Do people still say "punked"?
- No.
I see your buddy threw himself
a going away party.
Yes, I believe he drank something
that didn't quite agree with him.
You don't look too happy
to be here.
Perceptive.
Well, I see you've all decided
to come.
Well then, we can be on our way.
I ain't footing it anywhere.
A Time Master's sacred charge
is to do no harm to the timeline.
Can you imagine what a time ship
would look like
in, say, Victorian England?
Holographic indigenous
camouflage projection.
Indeed.
It's called the Waverider.
It's been my ship for over a decade.
Shall we?
Excuse me, would you mind?
Thank you.
I bet it uses ionic propulsion.
I doubt that very much,
given that even advanced technology
wouldn't be able to sustain
an ionic reaction.
It's possible if you stabilize
the quantum flux.
You know, we actually covered
this before, Professor Stein,
when I was your student,
many moons ago?
Perhaps you remember my paper
on subspace field mechanics?
I don't remember you, Mr. Palmer.
Whatever you roofied him with,
I'd like some.
I did not roofie him.
Oh, I ain't judging.
I have never seen anything
like this before.
Neither have I. And considering
I have 4,000 years
worth of memories,
that's saying something.
How does a vessel of this size
function without a crew?
I don't need one.
I have Gideon.
Welcome aboard.
I am Gideon.
An interactive
artificial consciousness
programmed to operate
this vessel's critical systems
and aid Captain Hunter
in his mission.
Captain?
Gideon's been working on
helping me locate Vandal Savage.
I thought you said he's pretty
active in the 22nd century.
Perhaps engaging Savage
at the height of his powers
isn't the best strategy.
Indeed.
Unfortunately, Savage
has kept his movements
hidden throughout history.
Not even Gideon can determine
where or when we can find him.
But, I have the next best thing.
The man who can.
Professor Aldus Boardman.
Professor Boardman is the
world's leading well, only...
expert on Vandal Savage.
We're gonna pay him a little visit.
Course plotted
for St. Roch, New Orleans.
- St. Roch?
- October 17, 1975.
I suggest you
all strap yourselves in.
Temporal navigation isn't
something one wants to be
standing up for.
Time travel.
Cool.
Some of you may experience
some slight discomfort.
In very rare instances,
there will be some...
bleeding from the eyeballs.
I'm sorry, what?
The human body is used
to time unfolding linearly.
Jackson, I'm so glad you're awake.
I didn't want you to miss this.
Miss what?
What the...
Oh, no. I wouldn't unfasten
those if I were you.
Get me off this...
whatever this thing is!
Good luck explaining this.
I did him a favor.
He doesn't look all that grateful.
Just hang on and remain calm.
All your worlds are about to change.
Seriously.
- That was insanity!
- God!
That is some serious
Darth Vader going on there.
Chronos to Command.
I am closing in
on Captain Hunter's position.
Hey, what you doing there, bro?
I am determining whether you
are integral to the timeline.
Okay.
You are not.
Oh, I should have mentioned it
before.
Nausea is one of the
side effects of time travel,
along with...
Vertigo.
I can't see.
And temporary blindness.
Oh, it should only last a minute.
After all, that was a mere jaunt.
The further back in time you go,
the worse the side effects.
- Better?
- It's all relative.
Good.
I can't believe you kidnapped me.
- Hey, I want to go home.
- Good news, then.
2016 will be around in 41 years.
Now, you three, feel free
to make yourselves comfortable
back here on the ship,
while the rest of you
are coming with me to find
Professor Boardman.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
- You're benching us?
- I thought we were a team.
This mission doesn't require
your particular skill set.
Yet.
Meaning you don't need anyone
killed, maimed, or robbed.
Precisely.
Sure it's a good idea
to leave these two
unsupervised on a time machine?
Hey, haircut.
Deafness wasn't
one of the side effects.
We better hurry up.
Professor Boardman will die
in less than 24 hours.
What's the point in cutting it
so close?
Because if he's destined to die,
then he doesn't have a timeline
for us to disrupt
and his impact on the future
will be minimal.
How brilliant.
And depressing.
How does he die?
Oh, he's found dead in his university
from unknown causes.
Come on.
- Are you coming?
- I'll stay put.
You'd rather stay with them?
They didn't drug me.
Point taken.
This is unbelievable, 1975.
Imagine all the wondrous
applications of this technology.
A chance to witness
the construction of the pyramids,
the end of the dinosaurs.
I've never been to 1975.
It's rather colorful.
So, where can we find
Professor Boardman?
In his lecture hall.
No matter who you are
Shining bright to see
What you can truly be
You're a shining star
Oh, man. We're too late.
This is... I'm... I'm sorry.
You.
Both of you.
You know who we are?
I've been studying you my whole life.
Ever since, as a child
I first heard the story of Chay-Ara,
High Priestess of Horus,
the Hawk God,
and her lover, Price Khufu.
I hoped and prayed
this day might come.
Well, then, looks like
we've come to the right place.
I'm sorry. Who are you?
A fellow historian,
here to discuss another passion
of yours...
Vandal Savage.
There's no way of telling your story
without telling his also.
Okay...
Why does this stupid station
play nothing but reruns?
Don't even bother trying to explain.
Am I the only one on this ship
who could really use a drink?
I say we go get weird in the '70s.
Excellent idea.
I got the perfect outfit.
Perhaps Captain Hunter
was unclear
with his instructions
to remain onboard.
Shut it, metal mouth.
Oh, you're not quite ready
to run with this crew.
Sorry, kid.
Wait, you're just gonna
leave me here?
I said I'd take care of you.
4,000 years ago...
Vandal Savage
was an Egyptian priest
secretly in love with a priestess.
You.
Or, rather...
you in your first life.
But you were in love with another.
Prince Khufu.
Savage, or Hath-Set as he
was then known,
learned of the affair and was
consumed with jealous rage.
You believe me yet?
Which drove him to murder you both.
And prayed for the hawk god, Horus,
to damn the objects of his hate
for all eternity.
But Chay-Ara had a prayer of her own.
That Horus would protect them
forever.
But another life was bound
to theirs by accident.
Savage's.
That's why he wants us both dead.
My theory is that the three of you
were exposed to the same
radiation by the meteorites.
We all share the same power.
And every time he kills you,
it passes to him.
That's what maintains
his immortality.
That's impossible.
Unless the meteorites
contained a mutative element.
Like the particle accelerator
that caused your powers.
But without evidence,
you're asking us
to take you at your word?
It's not my word.
It's theirs.
But you still don't remember me,
do you?
We knew you in our past lives.
You've told me your entire story,
stretching back through the ages.
But when I first knew you,
it was after World War I
and your names were Joe and Edith.
Edith Boardman.
Wait, I... we were related?
I don't remember you. I'm so sorry.
Don't be.
You always warned me
that if I ran into you
in your next life,
you might have forgotten me.
That's us at the World's Fair.
You're just as beautiful
as I remember you.
Mother.
How old were you when...
You two were murdered?
Ten.
My whole life, you taught me
to be careful.
To keep moving,
always one step ahead of Savage.
But after tracking you
for 4,000 years,
he'd gotten good.
He found us
in the middle of the night
at a fleabag motel in North Carolina.
You hid me in the closet,
made me promise
that no matter what I heard,
I'd stay put.
And I did.
Sorry to interrupt your family time
but we were hoping you could
tell us a bit more
where to locate
Savage's present whereabouts.
He hides in the shadows,
never drawing too much attention.
But every lifetime,
placing himself near
the seat of power,
sowing seeds of destruction.
Who remembers
the name of the man
who whispered in the ear
of Gavrilo Princip,
and convinced him to start
World War I?
Why? What does he get out of that?
The more the world is focused
on destroying itself,
the less it notices an immortal
psychopath in its midst.
With the ultimate goal
of subjugating the entire planet.
He killed your parents,
Professor Boardman.
Something tells me you know
where to locate Vandal Savage.
I have an educated guess.
Dollar beers.
You got to love the '70s.
Who wants to listen to some
Captain and Tennille?
My mother played it.
A lot.
Wow, you guys are really far out.
- You want to dance, Leonard?
- You go right ahead.
I'll watch.
- Love will keep us together
- Suit yourself.
Think of me, babe, whenever
Some sweet talking girl comes along
Can I help you?
How about you join me
in the parking lot?
Tempting, but you're not my type.
But your lady, on the other hand,
well, she looks just my speed.
Maybe you didn't understand
my request, bitch.
Son of a...
I got this.
You belong to me now
Ain't gonna set you free now
When those girls start hanging around
Talking me down
Hear with your heart
And you won't hear a sound
Now I could stand for a little help.
'Cause I really love you
Stop, I'll be thinking of you
Look in my heart and let
Love keep us together
Whatever
I love the '70s.
Gideon. That is your name, right?
How may I help you?
I assume this ship has a,
autopilot or something?
- You assume correctly.
- Great.
In that case, I'm a need you
to take me back to 2016.
See, me being here?
It's all a big mistake.
Captain Hunter told me
you'd try to do this.
And he also told me not to
listen to anything you say.
Well, you are a computer.
You have to listen to me!
You seem overwrought,
Mr. Jackson.
If you'd like to go to the MedBay,
I'd be happy
to prescribe you a sedative.
I do not need another roofie!
What was that?
A thermite grenade.
It seems someone is trying
to breach the hull.
His name is Chronos.
He's a temporal bounty hunter.
The ship is taking heavy fire.
I know!
Aren't we supposed to be
invisible or something?
You need to get us
out of here now!
A lifetime of research
on Vandal Savage
that all points in this direction.
This should help you find him
and the vengeance that has
eluded me all these years.
Jefferson... Something's
happening to Jefferson!
We seem to have a little
problem back at the vessel.
There's an intruder.
We really must be going now.
Thank you for everything.
Wait.
We can't just leave him here.
We have to get back now.
You said he's going to die
in 24 hours.
And we can stop it.
Are either of you a Time Master?
I didn't think so.
I've spent years studying
the implications
of chronological alteration.
Good for you...
but we're not going anywhere
unless our son's coming with us.
Why is Chronos attacking us?
Perhaps Captain Hunter
is best suited to answer that query.
Fire photon torpedoes
or something!
Only Captain Hunter is authorized.
Where is Captain Hunter?
Dr. Palmer, please tell me...
I didn't leave my exo-suit
on the ship?
Okay, but I'd be lying.
Who the hell is this guy?
Is that a laser gun?
Got to get back to the ship
and bond with Jefferson.
Cover me!
Cover me too.
Oh, you crazy old man.
Thank you, Mr. Palmer.
Seriously? It's Dr. Palmer.
Get down!
We need to merge!
We go out for one lousy drink
and you guys somehow manage
to pick a fight with Boba Fett.
- Aldus!
- We'll get you out of here!
You're doing good.
Professor Boardman has sustained
severe internal injuries.
Prepare the MedBay to receive
Professor Boardman
and get us out of here!
Course heading?
Anywhere but here!
Our cloaking shield and aft entrance
have been significantly
compromised, Captain.
Yes, I can see that, Gideon.
Station us in the temporal zone
while I work on repairs.
Temporal zone?
Yeah, it's essentially a time limbo.
We can hide out there for a bit.
Another temporal jump would risk
revealing our position.
A time limbo? Astonishing.
Oh, there's something you people
don't know about time travel?
That's surprising, isn't it?
Considering none of you have
ever time traveled before.
Bringing a family member
from the past onto a time ship?
Breaking out and carousing
around the 1970s?
We've barely begun,
and already this is the worst,
unmitigated disaster of my career.
I see why you got the hots
for that one.
My son is hurt because of you.
Who attacked us?
Something of a long story.
Better tell it fast, Rip,
'cause it doesn't look like
the lady's in a patient mood.
Neither am I.
His name is Chronos.
He works for
the Council of Time Masters.
My former employers.
I thought you were a Time Master.
As I've expressed,
time's not a linear thing.
At some point I was, in fact,
a Time Master.
Will you people please
stop hitting me?
Start telling the truth!
I relinquished my position
as a Time Master
when I commandeered the Waverider.
Chronos was clearly sent
to bring me in.
- You lied to us.
- Of course I lied to you.
I needed your help you all
barely said yes as it was.
What about the "legends" part?
Oh, you lied about that too,
didn't you?
I chose you all because
a hundred years from now,
your lives have minimal effect
on the recorded timeline.
I needed your help without
disturbing the history of 2166.
So, we're
like the opposite of legends.
Give me one good reason
why we shouldn't kill you.
Ditto the arsonist.
Because Gideon wouldn't
listen to your commands
and you'd be stuck here forever.
Great. So we're not
an elite team of heroes
on a sanctioned mission,
sent to rid the future
of its most horrific bad guy.
Just a collection of nobodies
who time really doesn't
give a damn about.
I didn't lie
about the mission itself.
Or the brutality
and ruthlessness of Savage.
Or my need for your help.
I don't imagine
you're the kind of guy
who quits his job
and takes on this kind of threat
for altruistic reasons.
So Rip, why don't you tell us?
What did Vandal Savage
do to you?
The Time Masters discourage marriage.
They urge against procreation
even more.
A Time Master should be free
of any personal entanglements
that might compromise him.
But...
I fell in love
and we had a child.
A boy.
Jonas.
Savage killed your family.
He slaughtered my family.
And thousands of other families.
And that body that I swore
an oath to serve
turned a blind eye.
They continue to turn a blind eye.
I won't.
The last thing that my child
saw in this world
was that monster's face.
You can be damn well sure
that when Savage dies,
the last face he sees will be mine.
I understand,
given the circumstances,
if you wish to return home.
We can make the jump
once the repairs are done,
if and when
Professor Boardman stabilizes.
I think we all need a little time
to consider our options.
Just get some rest.
There's something
I've wanted you to have.
It's around my neck.
It was my mother's.
Yours.
It's beautiful.
I remember it.
Thank you.
Rip wouldn't have allowed me
to bring Aldus onboard
- if you hadn't said so...
- Of course.
Chay-Ara...
sorry.
Kendra.
No, it's okay.
Chay-Ara is fine.
Seems an apology is in order.
What I did was wrong.
I should never have forced
you to come along.
But, for me, the opportunity
to travel through time...
see the mysteries
of the universe revealed,
notions I've spent my whole
life studying...
Please do not geek out on
quantum physics right now.
Mr. Hunter was offering
grand adventure.
And at my age, you never know
how many adventures
you have left.
Hey...
I saw your 40-yard dash onto the ship
with that Chronos guy
shooting at you.
I think you got plenty
of adventures left.
Yes, perhaps you're right.
Back home. As Firestorm.
What if I don't want to go home?
Yet, I mean.
Why the change of heart?
You ever play football?
Yeah, I didn't think so.
Anyway... the best feeling
I ever got from being on the field
wasn't when I made a great play
or we won some game.
It was when one of my teammates
took a tackle for me
and I knew they were gonna
make sure I was safe,
that nobody got to me.
Watching all of you rush back
to the ship,
even those two knuckleheads,
to take on Chronos?
Made me feel the same way.
I like being part of a team, man.
Me too.
Watch it!
Sorry.
What's the point of us even
giving this a second thought?
Rip has already seen the future.
He knows exactly what's in store
for each of us.
Might as well have stayed dead,
'cause the world doesn't need
any of us.
You're just a lost assassin.
You're just a pair
of good-for-nothing criminals.
I can live with that.
Well, I can't.
Can't live with somebody
putting a cap on my destiny.
Spent my whole life
working to be something greater
by becoming something smaller.
Then, some guy
comes along and tells me
that being the Atom
is as insignificant
as an actual atom.
That's not what he said.
Rip said that in his future
we're nobodies.
But this mission
is about changing the future.
I mean, if we have the power
to change the world...
don't you think we have
the power to change our own fate?
For better or for worse.
That's a very good point.
What do you think, Gideon?
I calculate
a less than six percent likelihood
that they decide
to go on with the mission.
I meant about the repairs.
And there has been another
unfortunate consequence
of Chronos's attack.
- Care to hear about it?
- Not really.
He's gone.
Our son... or, our son
from our previous life.
It's all too confusing.
I'm very sorry.
Actually, you don't
get the blame for this.
This was my fault.
If I hadn't insisted
on bringing him back here,
he might have died peacefully,
in his sleep maybe.
Don't torture yourself
with recriminations.
One of the great lessons
of time travel
is that many things
cannot be changed.
Time wants to happen.
Chronos, even Vandal,
won't be the only enemy we face.
Very often, it will be time itself.
Whether it wants to happen
or not,
we're gonna change time,
erase Savage's future,
and earn our rightful place
in history.
Dr. Palmer is correct.
We may not be legends
in your time, Captain.
But we are going to decide
our own fates.
I don't give a damn
about being a legend,
as long as we end Savage
once and for all.
I can get down with that.
And our malcontents?
I like killing people.
We're in...
for now.
So how do we find this guy?
Professor Boardman
had a theory about that.
I've already had Gideon
plot a course.
You know what this is?
An instrument to make this world
a better place.
History teaches us
that the cause of humanity
is only advanced through strife.
There's no Renaissance without
the Dark Ages.
Man had no interest
in splitting the atom
until World War II.
I'm just trying
to make this world
a better place...
one war at a time.