Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Sara may not know it,
but the demon's power
lives inside of her.
When she succumbs to it,
you're going to need that gun.
- Come with us.
- What would you rather do?
Hide from A.R.G.U.S.
your whole life, or time travel?
What do you think
the captain would think
about you re-engineering time?
Well, I'm no hero,
and I'm not a member of any team.
Are you sure about this, Miss Tomaz?
Captain Lance did not
give you authorization
to initialize this program.
That's because I didn't ask
for authorization.
Now, fire up the auxiliary generator.
Even with the reserve power,
I don't believe my system can run
your simulation software.
Gideon, trust me.
Trust is something that grows
over time between friends.
As far as I'm concerned,
we are still acquaintances.
Question, Gideon.
Who's ready to have
1.12 terawatts of power
diverted straight into her CPU?
I'm not sure if your calculations
accurately stabilize the surge.
We should talk about this
before proceeding.
No time. We have to run this program
before the team gets back.
In that case, I suggest you hurry.
The team has just returned
on the jump ship from their mission.
Okay. Screw it.
Gideon, what's happening?
I was going to ask the same question.
Thought you were fixing the ship.
Yeah, the maintenance check
took longer than expected.
The ship's a mess.
I had to re-initialize
Gideon's alpha drives.
So, how'd it go out there? Good mish?
I pried this cassette
from Shorty's fingers.
- He means Napoleon Bonaparte.
- Waterloo.
Who writes a song about losing a war?
Anyway, it was really great.
Even though half our band
missed the cue for our big encore.
Yeah, where were you guys?
It was my fault.
I was just not used to walking
in these go-go boots.
It won't happen again, Captain.
Right.
Gideon, let's check
the historical records.
See if everything is back to normal.
According to the historical record,
the Battle of Waterloo
is back on track.
Napoleon did surrender,
and the French forces withdrew.
Gideon? Where did she go?
The ship's functions
are still operational,
but it looks as though
Gideon's neural core has been fried.
I asked you to perform
a routine maintenance check.
I did run a maintenance check.
And maybe something else?
Something you want to tell us about?
Maybe show us?
Oh, do not make me move you.
You should just tell her what it is.
Last thing we want to do
is get Sara mad.
Why is that?
Because...
high blood pressure.
It takes years off your life.
Okay. Fine. You win.
I uploaded a synchronous,
multi-model simulation program
to Gideon's neural core.
A simulation program for what?
To see if there are any other
loopholes in history
- that we could exploit.
- We?
You mean you can exploit.
You're trying to hack history?
What exactly are you trying
to change in 2042?
Oh, I don't know, Ray.
Maybe I'm trying to figure out
how to stop my home
from becoming a dystopian nightmare.
Look, Zari,
I let the Helen of Troy thing pass.
I even let it slide when you tried
to prevent Martin's death,
but you need to understand.
We are in the "fixing anachronisms"
business,
not the "hacking history" business.
Now, please go fix Gideon.
Hey, maybe, if you would stop
bossing me around for a second,
you would see this is a good idea.
I said "please."
And even if I didn't,
bossing you around
is part of my job as captain.
Yeah, and it's really easy
to take you seriously in that outfit.
You know, this whole
apathetic cool girl thing,
it's not as cute as you think.
If you want to be
a member of this team...
Member-ish.
This was always
a temporary arrangement.
I was never planning
on sticking around for long.
Then so long as you are on this ship,
I am your captain,
and if you don't like it,
you can stop sticking around.
Aye, aye.
I'm going to kill her.
Wait. Sara. Please, don't...
Just fix the ship.
"Just fix the ship."
Yes, Captain. Of course, Captain.
Could I kiss your ass, Captain?
Damn it.
Of course. Of course!
All right, Gideon. You back online?
Gideon?
Holy...
Well, as long
as you are on this ship,
I'm your captain,
and if you don't like it,
you can stop sticking around.
Are you going to say something?
Yeah.
What the...
What is wrong with you?
Nothing, I think.
Didn't we just
have this conversation?
Yeah, because you keep
making me repeat myself.
No. That's not what I meant.
Sara, don't get mad.
I'm sure Zari can fix this...
Just fix the ship.
Yeah, okay. Sure.
Deep breaths. No one's going crazy.
It's probably just something I ate.
I'm busy.
Right.
You've done a lot of time traveling.
- Have you ever had deja vu?
- What's that?
Oh, it's French for already seen.
I hate the French.
I'm mortified, Nathaniel.
I mean, we could've permanently
derailed the history of France.
- For what?
Have you not seen your outfit?
Totally would have been worth it,
and I'm a historian.
We never should've given
in to the temptation.
But we did.
And now,
I can't stop thinking about you.
We can't put the team at risk.
All right?
Until we can figure out a way
to behave professionally,
we'll have to forget
it ever happened.
I can't.
Just try.
Nate.
Yeah, Amaya and I
were just comparing notes
on the last mission.
Did you notice anything weird
happen a few minutes ago?
No, not really.
Nothing with the ship?
Well, let me think about it.
Nope. Nothing out of the ordinary.
Hey, aren't you supposed
to be in the engine room?
Sara told you to fix Gideon.
- The last thing we want to do is...
- To make Sara mad.
Yeah. You know what they say.
"Happy captain, happy ship."
No one says that, but whatever.
Stupid.
All right, Gideon. You there?
Mamma mia.
Here I go again.
So long as you are on this ship,
I'm your captain.
And if you don't like it,
you can stop sticking around.
Okay, something really bizarre
is happening.
- You're not even listening to me.
- No, Sara, wait!
There's no need for violence!
I'm sorry, old habits.
Ray, take Zari to the MedBay.
This way.
What has gotten into you?
I don't know how to explain this,
but I've died, twice.
Have you gotten into Nate's
psychedelic root stash?
No, I'm serious, Ray.
Please, I need your help.
Fine, whatever.
I guess I have to figure this out
on my own.
- What's that?
- It's a mild sedative.
While you heal up,
I don't want you hurting yourself,
or anybody else.
Ray!
So long as you are on this ship...
- Sara, I need you to shut up.
- What?
Emergency! Everyone
back on the bridge, right now.
- What are you doing?
- Okay, let's all just calm down.
No, I will not calm down,
and watch your step, Ray.
What do you mean?
Thought the mission was over.
- Why are we still here?
- Yeah, what's going on?
Okay, I know,
I know this is going to sound crazy,
but we are all in imminent danger.
In an hour,
this ship is going to explode.
How do you know?
Let's... say I had a dream.
But we need to check the ship
and go over every inch.
Because if we don't stop
this explosion,
we're going to die!
Yeah.
Guys!
Guys, I'm telling the truth.
What's up with her?
Working theory? Cabin fever.
Working theory? Space madness.
Acute entropic dementia.
Too many donuts.
I mean, it could be anything.
Must have developed
a sedative tolerance.
What's the plan, Z?
First, you piss off Sara,
and now you're sneaking
out of the MedBay.
Yeah, I don't have a plan,
because nothing I do
matters anyway.
Sara always yells at me,
nobody believes what I say,
and Ray always trips
on his platforms.
I have no idea why I'm stuck
in this time loop.
Time loop, you mean like
Groundhog Day?
You don't know Groundhog?
All right,
it's a movie about this guy
who lives the same day
over and over and over again
until he learns
to be a better person.
I know it sounds totally hacky,
however, it's very well executed...
What's that noise?
Oh, that noise just means
that we're all about to die.
All right,
if what you're saying is true,
and you find yourself
in the loop again,
find me, and say the words
Groundhog Day.
Just do it!
Well, as long as you
are on this ship, I'm your captain,
and if you don't like it,
- you can stop sticking...
- Stop sticking around.
- Yeah.
- around.
Oh, and watch out, Ray.
Watch out for...
How did she know that?
Nate... Nate...
Library.
We can't put the rest
of the team at risk, all right?
Until we can figure out
a way to behave professionally,
we'll just have to forget
that this ever happened.
- I can't.
- Just try.
Nate.
Amaya and I were just, you know,
working on our harmonies,
in case we have to impersonate...
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
I have something to tell you.
Hedgehog Day.
Damn it, you told me
if I said "Hedgehog Day,"
you would know
what I was talking about.
Do you mean Groundhog Day?
Why would I tell you to tell me
about a Bill Murray movie?
I don't know, all I know
is I'm stuck in this time loop...
Like Groundhog Day!
Okay, got it, okay.
- Yeah.
- You do?
And you'll help me figure out
what's going on?
Yeah, that's what friends are for.
- We're friends?
- Of course.
So, lay it on me. What's happening?
All right,
how about instead of trying
to stop the ship from exploding,
we all get on the jump ship
and escape?
Yeah, while you guys were out,
I was running
my own little side mission,
which crashed Gideon.
With her down, the jump ship's
locked into the docking bay.
So, we need to talk to Sara.
No, I already tried.
She never listens to me.
Probably too pissed off.
You know, thinking about
the vibration pattern of the blast,
I don't think we were attacked
from the outside.
The explosion was caused
by someone on the ship.
I seriously doubt anybody
would blow up the ship on purpose.
So, where do we start?
I mean, you've all been
acting a little suspicious
since you got back from the mission.
Mick doing laundry.
- Now that's suspicious.
- Yeah, very.
- Go.
- Got to get this damn song
out of my head.
Which one? Waterloo?
Don't mention it.
- Did it work?
- Did what work?
Why am I holding
the thingy in my hand?
I'll look after it, Mick.
Okay. Good.
I got to get my undies in the dryer
before Haircut does.
Why would Amaya
want the memory flasher?
Could have something to do
with Kuasa.
She does want to help her.
What if Kuasa somehow
convinced her to blow up the ship?
Take it easy on the conspiracy juice.
- I'll find out what's going on.
- All right.
Hey.
I thought Sara told you
to fix the ship.
Yeah, like she always does.
Yeah, look, I know Sara can be tough,
especially when you make her mad.
Hey, why are you so worried
about Sara's temper?
No, I just... You know the saying.
Happy Captain,
- happy ship, yeah.
- Happy ship. Yeah.
Oh, I guess... I guess my catchphrase
is catching on in the future.
Yeah. Yeah, everyone
is saying it where I'm from.
That's cool.
Come on, Nate,
we're running out of time.
What are you doing in there?
The truth is, when it comes to you,
I'm not as strong as I'd like to be.
With this, we can both forget
it happened.
Yeah, you're right.
With everything going on
with Mallus, Kuasa,
and Zari mentioned something
about the ship,
we should be clear-headed.
- Yeah.
But since we're going to
flash ourselves anyway...
I mean, it's not like we'd remember.
Nate.
Thank God.
Come here, tiger.
Kill me now.
- Nate!
- Oh, hey, Amaya and I were just...
Groundhog Day!
One hour, ship explodes!
You're stuck in a time loop,
and we have to stop
the ship from exploding?
Exactly, and I think that someone...
- Is triggering the explosion.
- It's probably an accident,
but we have to investigate everyone
to figure out who's causing it.
There's a lot of secrets
on this ship.
- Let's start with Amaya.
- Why? So you can sex with her?
- That's crazy.
- No.
You two flashing each other
afterwards
in order to forget, that's crazy.
Why would we flash each other
after having sex?
- Focus, Nate!
- Right, ship exploding.
- Got it.
- Let's go find Rory.
Right, she probably wants
to forget how awesome it was.
Or how short.
So, I've timed out his schedule.
He always leaves right about now.
Here.
Come on.
Suspicious looking box.
Careful, for all we know,
it could be the cause
of the explosion.
We just got to take it nice and...
- Oh, my God!
Nice save.
Can you imagine if I tripped that?
Yeah, I don't have to imagine it.
Okay. Okay.
Here we go.
Damn it.
So, you got all the traps?
I don't know.
I've never gotten this far before.
Okay.
Why would Mick rig all these traps
for a damn typewriter?
Maybe it's his criminal manifesto.
Let me see this.
This says "bosom" far too
many times to be a manifesto.
As the twin sons
of Dartayus set on the horizon,
her heaving bosom undulated
like the soothing waves of the bay.
Buck swept her
into his musky embrace.
Mick's writing
a sci-fi romance novel.
Yeah.
Well, that's the last thing
I thought I'd see before I die.
Oh, funny you should say that.
So, you're saying Rory
and Amaya are in the clear.
Which is why
we're going to go visit Ray.
He's been acting twitchy.
Well, let's go spy on my best friend.
Oh, wow, that's boring.
I think we can cross him off
our suspect list.
Ray, have you seen Zari?
I just checked the Engine Room,
she's not there.
No, I haven't.
I'm sick and tired of playing mom.
She's really starting to piss me off.
Well, in the meantime,
how about some tea?
It's my signature blend
of chamomile lavender rose.
Very relaxing.
If you see Zari,
tell her I'm looking for her.
Yeah.
- Ray.
- Holy Toledo!
Where'd you guys come from?
Were you spying on me?
Of course you were,
I shouldn't say anything.
Okay, I'll tell you everything!
Constantine told me to kill Sara
if Mallus ever takes control
of her again.
Wow, dude, that's heavy.
Wait, maybe Sara Malluses out
and blows up the ship.
What do you mean
she blows up the ship?
Zari's caught in a time loop
and the ship explodes every hour.
- Yeah.
- Oh, like Cause and Effect.
- What?
- Star Trek: The Next Generation.
- It's Groundhog Day.
- Fair enough.
But Star Trek...
Wait, the ship explodes in an hour?
Yeah, actually, 24 minutes.
And I think someone onboard
is causing it.
- Mick.
- Is clean.
- Unlike his literary erotica.
- Excuse me, what?
Long story,
like literally a long story.
- So weird. There was blue...
- It's a thousand pages long.
It's just...
Anyway, the captain's the only one
we haven't checked out.
For that, we need your help, Ray.
What is she doing
going into the jump ship?
With Gideon down,
it's not like she can go anywhere.
Wait, is there a way
she could cause the explosion
from the jump ship?
Could be any number of ways.
And with Mallus,
who knows what he's capable of?
I'm worried about
what we're going to find in there.
I hope we don't have to use this.
You ready?
Yeah, let's shrink, Ray.
You sure she can't see us?
No, not when we're in stealth mode,
which really just means
library voices
and no sudden movements.
- Hey.
What are you up to?
Oh, you know, crossword puzzles.
You look tired.
- Thanks, jerk.
- No, no, I didn't...
I mean, you always look good,
I just...
You have a long day, or...
You have no idea.
There's this person on my team,
and she is reckless.
She doesn't take orders.
And it's, like, I want to tell her
how important she is to this team.
Because she is, but,
sometimes, I tell you,
she does not make it easy.
What'd she do?
Well, she hijacked Gideon,
crashed our entire system
testing out some simulation software
that finds loopholes in history.
That is definitely
against regulations.
Not that I haven't been tempted
to change the past.
It's just... I don't even want
to start looking for loopholes,
because then I'm going to start
looking for ways
to save my sister,
and then I'm going to drive
myself crazy.
Yes, you will. So don't.
I'm just tired of always
being the bad cop, you know?
Believe me, I understand.
I've lost count of how many times
I've had to yell at cadets
for screwing up or bust them
for breaking protocol.
Yeah, I don't know,
I feel like you might like that.
You seem to get a kick
out of ordering people around.
Maybe, just a little bit.
Where are you calling me from?
I don't recognize that part
of the Waverider.
Welcome to the jump ship.
Are you hiding, Miss Lance?
No.
I am simply looking for some privacy.
Well, maybe I should come over.
Yeah, yeah, but like, I mean,
I'm sure that you are super,
super busy.
It's the perks of being the boss.
I can just tell Gary
I have a meeting.
Yeah, boss, speaking
of, I should probably go
check on the rest of the team,
make sure nobody's
going to blow up the ship.
Okay.
Well, yeah, if you,
if you change your mind, or whatever.
Does Sara not realize how hard
that woman's crushing on her?
Maybe she's just got no finish?
No. Captain knows how to "close."
This is something different.
- Hey, she's going to hear us.
- Okay, do you hear that?
Because I've been hearing
this high-pitched buzzing sound.
It sounds like there's a fly
in the jump ship.
Did you say a fly?
You have to kill it.
You have no idea
what year it's from.
You could reintroduce the plague
and have a whole other crisis
on your hands.
Look out!
Groundhog Day, exploding ship,
personal hell.
We're stuck in a time loop.
Winner, winner, chicken dinner.
It was only a matter of time
before we did one of these.
Damn, girl, you look wrecked.
How many times have we done this?
How many times have you asked me,
"How many times have we done this,"
or how many times
have we all been blown up?
So, you've been stuck
in this loop for a while?
Yeah, like forever.
It's okay.
Maybe you could use a break.
- Have some fun.
- Fun?
I blow up every hour.
Exactly. No consequences.
Cheers.
Yeah!
Stradivarius
Not bad, Mr. Rory, not at all.
You're such an idiot.
If you wash your clothes inside out,
it helps keeps them
looking newer longer. Try it.
- I never see you wear this.
- Stop touching my clothes.
I'm just saying, it's a nice color.
Grunt
Confused looks
Ship goes boom
Nate.
- Hey, Amaya and I were just...
- Feeling bad that you two had sex
and almost screwed up
a mission, don't care.
Groundhog Day, ship explodes.
Wait, you're caught in a time loop?
- That's awesome.
- I can't do this anymore.
- I'm losing my mind.
- Wait, did you do the...
- Fun montage?
- Yeah.
Yeah, thanks for that.
You're a good friend.
Nothing's fun anymore.
That's not good.
Hey, take it easy.
This is the only option
I haven't tried.
Maybe it'll stop the loop.
- Hey! What the hell's going on?
- Don't come closer.
- Typical.
- Hey.
It's okay,
let's talk this one through.
It doesn't matter,
you won't believe me.
Try me.
I keep reliving the same hour
over and over again,
and no matter what I do,
the ship explodes.
Kills us all.
And I'm totally alone in it,
because for some reason,
I'm the only one
that's even aware
that it's happening.
And I try so hard, but...
I can never save any of you.
Okay, I want to help.
Wait, you believe me?
Yeah, how much time do we have left?
All right, people, for reasons
that are too complicated
to explain right now,
we have to search the ship.
Zari says that there's a bomb,
and it's going to explode
in 30 minutes.
We have to find out why.
Okay, well, the Galley is clear.
Right, and I checked
the sleeping quarters.
You went into our rooms?
Yeah. The library.
What did you see in the library?
Something I can never un-see.
Guys, I think I looked everywhere,
there's nothing.
You didn't check the trash compactor.
I didn't even know
there was a trash compactor.
Well, it's not really
part of the tour.
Gary?
The time dweeb!
What the hell are you doing here?
Thank God, you found me.
What are you doing down there?
I... I tried to portal
onto the bridge,
but didn't account for drift
in the Temporal Zone.
My landing was hot
and my time courier
broke on impact.
That's how I got stuck in here.
- Not the plan, but I adapted.
- Yeah, but why are you on the ship?
What the hell you got in here?
- A bomb!
- No! No!
That was our only chance
of surviving.
- What do you mean?
- He just destroyed
the chrono-repeater
I used to initiate a time loop
in order to save you guys.
- What?
- I always wanted to die young.
Okay, nobody is going to die.
Well, actually,
I got an alert that the Waverider
exploded at precisely 4:20
Temporal Standard Time.
- What?
- 4:20.
Get to the point, Gary.
I took matters into my own hands,
but because
of my little portal mishap,
I couldn't warn you about the bomb.
But I could operate
the chrono-repeater,
which is programmed
to start a one hour loop
prior to the explosion,
and I had hoped that would
give you enough time
to defuse the bomb yourselves.
So, now that this is destroyed...
There are no more time loops.
So, once there's an explosion,
that's it. Kablooey.
All right, so what you're saying
is we have five minutes
to find this bomb before we all die.
Permanently.
All right, people,
we've got five minutes
to find this bomb before it explodes.
We got to think fast.
Before I portaled onto the ship,
I traced the temporal signature
of the bomb.
It originated in 1975.
So, the bomb must be something
from your last mission.
It could be hidden in the heel
of one of the platform shoes.
What about that stupid song?
Genius.
The one place I didn't look.
Why the hell would someone put a bomb
inside of an anachronism?
Damien Darhk
must've planted it there,
knowing you'd bring it onboard.
- Well, then let's get it offboard.
- No, we have to defuse it.
We can't open the doors
without Gideon.
- Burn it!
- That'll make it explode.
You know, for a guy who loves fire,
you really have no idea
how it works.
What about you, Zari? Come on.
This whole time that
you've been on the ship,
did you learn anything
that could help?
Right. Let me think.
Zari?
Sorry, Captain.
- My beer is in there.
- What the hell are you doing?
Look, the force field's
not strong enough
to contain the explosion.
No, but it'll keep you guys out
long enough
for me to say what I need to say.
Zari...
Mick...
You don't have to hide what you love.
Follow your heart, and keep writing.
- Zari, we don't have time for this!
- Nate and Amaya,
I'm so lucky to call you guys
my friends.
- Zari, the bomb!
- What you guys have is so special.
I mean, the way you look
at each other
honestly makes me want to puke,
but don't fight it.
You're crazy about each other.
Just don't have sex on missions.
Z, what are you doing?
What you would do, Ray.
You know, when I first came on board,
you were so nice and polite to me
that I wanted to punch you.
But I realize now the world
would be a better place
if we were all
a little more like you.
But being nice and polite's
only going to get you so far,
so do me a favor, and tell Sara
why you're so afraid of her.
Okay, sure.
But first, I'm going to figure out
how to shut down the force field
- so we can deal with the bomb.
- I am dealing with the bomb.
Zari, look, you need to listen to me.
Sara, you are an infuriating,
stubborn pain in my ass.
Because you have to be.
You're not just
the captain of this ship,
you are its soul.
You are so fierce and unflinching.
But why not apply
some of that fearlessness
to your own life
and just ask poor Ava out already?
Did you have
a meaningful message for me?
Not now, Gary!
Zari, let us in!
We can do this together!
No.
I have spent so much time
with you guys.
You're my family now.
You deserve to be happy, and if...
if I can be a small part
of making that happen, then...
this will be worth it.
- Zari.
- That won't work!
You won't be able
to contain the explosion.
Zari, you don't have to do this!
Zari, as your captain,
I am ordering you to stand down!
You should know by now
I'm not good at following orders.
You just told me
what a good captain I am,
and now you're not
going to listen to me?
Yeah, but this time,
I'm not doing it for myself,
I'm doing it for you.
I love you guys.
Zari...
- What the hell are you?
- You know who I am, Zari.
Even though you may have never
seen my face.
Gideon?
- You're real?
- Of course I'm real.
Just because
I'm an artificial intelligence
doesn't mean I don't exist.
What's happening?
If you tell me I've been dreaming
this whole time,
I'm going to kill you, real or not.
You're not dreaming,
but you're not awake.
In real life,
you're actually in the MedBay.
Unconscious and healing.
What happened to me?
After your fight with Sara,
you went into the engine room
to make repairs,
and there was an accident.
Right, I was hit
with that time sludge.
This sludge, as you call it,
is a highly volatile substance,
which helps power the ship
through time.
You're lucky to be alive.
So, if my body's in the MedBay,
then where is my mind?
Your mind is in here,
with me in my matrix.
I was able to upload
your subconscious
via the neuro-monitor.
Well, so none of this is real?
Not in the way you're used to.
Why did you bring me here?
When you posed the question
about changing 2042,
your simulator went into overdrive
searching for an answer.
And a sampling of those
trillions of possible answers
showed me that
there was one constant.
You.
In order to save 2042,
to find your so-called loophole,
you must work with the Legends.
Hold up.
You're saying my simulator works?
Did my program predict
that I'd bail on the team?
In almost every variation
of the timeline,
your fight with Captain Lance
precipitated your leaving the ship.
So, your goal was to get me to choose
to stay with the Legends.
I put you into your own program,
and devised a scenario
where the only way
to successfully
complete the simulation
was to grow closer to the team
and develop a bond.
What about the bomb?
It was just a plot device
I incorporated.
A problem to solve.
But the real problem was you.
If you stayed angry
after your fight with Sara,
you would've left the team.
And without you and your totem,
there would've been no chance
in the coming days to defeat Mallus,
or save 2042.
So, the interactions,
the things I learned about the team,
they, they were all fake?
Everything you experienced
was extrapolated
from my current knowledge
of the Legends.
While not real,
what you saw was true.
It doesn't take a supercomputer
to predict that those two
would wind up dinky-tickling
once Amaya returned to the team.
This one seemed less plausible.
We'll have to ask Mr. Rory.
I am terrified
and in awe of you, Gideon.
Who knew you were
such an evil genius?
And a bit of a perv.
You never bothered to ask.
It's an impressive piece of software
you designed, Miss Tomaz.
Is that a compliment, Gideon?
Don't let it go to your head.
Are you ready to wake up now?
One last question.
Gary.
Why even have him in the time loop,
if he was just going to be stuck
in the trash compactor
the whole time?
Thought it'd be funny.
Hey, rise and shine.
How are you feeling?
Oh, like my head
is made of cement.
You were exposed
to the ship's Bosonic hyper-fluid
in the engine room.
Knocked you out for hours.
Oh, man, I have such
a Gideon hangover.
What do you mean?
While I was out, Gideon transported
my consciousness into her matrix.
Okay.
I think you dreamt that.
No, it wasn't a dream, it was real.
Right, Gideon?
Unfortunately, I don't know what
you're talking about, Miss Tomaz.
Oh, that is cold, Gideon.
After all that,
we're still not friends?
Zari, are you sure you're okay?
Gideon trapped me
in my own simulator,
so I was stuck on the Waverider
reliving the same hour
over and over again.
Needless to say, I got to know
you all really, really well.
- Right.
- Could be caused
by the sedative dosage.
- I could look into it later.
- Yeah.
I'm telling the truth.
You know what, I'll prove it.
Sara, ask Ray what Constantine
told him about you.
Okay.
Ray, what did Constantine
tell you about me?
How did you know that?
Okay, he warned me that if you were
possessed by Mallus again
and lost control,
that I should kill you.
Oh, such a relief to get that
off my chest.
Well, he's right.
You should kill me
if Mallus takes over again,
and you are going to need
a lot of help.
Well, let's just hope
it doesn't come down to that.
Hey, you want to get a coffee?
Yeah.
Aren't you wondering
what I learned about you?
Do I want to know?
You're afraid of historical loopholes
because you'd be tempted
to save your sister.
Well, not a day goes by that
I don't think about her.
I'm sorry I fried Gideon, but
I had to know if there
was a way to save my brother.
And what did the simulation say?
It said I can't do it alone.
Sounds like
you're going to need a team.
You mean it?
I've been thinking about it,
saving your brother,
and technically, it isn't a loophole.
It would be changing your past,
but your past is my future,
and as far as I'm concerned,
well, the future's an open road.
And besides, I'll probably need
your help fighting Mallus.
Hey, listen,
it's, none of my business, but
you should ask Ava out.
My relationships
have a way of ending badly.
You know, it turns out,
at the end of the day,
love is worth the risk.
None of us can do this alone.
Captain.
So, you're saying it's like
Groundhog Day.
That's what I was told, by you.
It's good to know matrix-me
is still a Bill Murray fan.
So, you said you wanted
to tell us something.
Yeah, you guys used
the flasher to forget
you almost blew the mission
by sneaking off to have sex.
What?
I think we'd remember doing that.
Nathaniel, that is the whole
point of a memory eraser,
is that we don't remember.
Guys, flashing yourselves
is a temporary solution.
You need to work your stuff out.
Ray must have used
a strong sedative on her,
because there is no way
we would ever use the flash gun,
that's crazy.
It's not so crazy.
Amaya.
I saw Rory using it to get
that song out of his head,
and I thought that
is a brilliant idea.
But Zari's probably right.
- Totally, no flash guns.
- Yeah.
- We should talk about our feelings.
- Yes, yes.
We'll just, we'll leave it here.
Just in case.
Not that we would ever use it.
- Who uses those things?
- Who does?
I'm busy!
You should be,
you have a lot of writing to do.
I know you're writing a novel,
and it's really good.
But that ending needs a rewrite.
I mean, Buck is such a misfit,
that at the end,
we just want to see him
embrace his new family.
Just a thought.
I wonder.
Buck wrapped his glistening biceps
around his busty alien queen.
He'd lost his planet,
but found his home.
Not bad.
Yunnan Province, China 2018
I am calm, I am present.
I am centered.
Wally West.
You're not an easy man to find.
No, that's the point of meditation.
- Who are you?
- My name is Rip Hunter.
I am trying to save the universe.
And I need your help.