The Legends of Tomorrow
are everywhere.
Since they defeated a demon with
the help of a dragon on national TV,
they've become a worldwide obsession.
Sure, we've all been mesmerized
by the global phenomenon
known as "Legends Mania."
Yum.
And the Oscar for Best Picture
goes to...
But who are the people beneath
those supersized public personas?
What are they like
when the spotlight is off?
I'm Kevin Harris,
and my documentary film crew
is the first ever
to be granted unfettered access
to their lives
and their ship, the Waverider.
So, strap in, because today,
we meet the Legends.
So, why don't we start
with just a brief introduction?
And let us know what we're doing today
on the Waverider.
Uh, yeah.
Hi, I'm... I'm Ava Sharpe.
After Congress shut down
the Time Bureau,
Sara went off to help Oliver Queen...
...and, uh, I had to fight to keep
the Waverider from being impounded.
Bad luck that the senator
chairing the committee was
the same person
we almost killed last year.
Senator Wellington, I know the Time
Bureau may have been compromised...
...but you must allow the Waverider
to continue patrolling the timeline.
Ms. Sharpe, how do we know
these so-called "Legends"
can be trusted with time travel?
Oh, there's simply no transparency.
Which is why you all are here.
Right? To show everyone what we do.
What could go wrong?
The Waverider
was surprisingly quiet
because half the team
was away on a mission.
Oh, the crossover.
Yeah, had to take a rain check.
See, when you are a superhero/
amusement park impresario...
.../historian that rises from the dead,
your dance card tends
to get pretty full.
For two full minutes, I was not alive.
That changes you, man.
Don't get me wrong, I love fame.
No one says no to you about anything.
Hey, man, that's a cool hat.
Can I have it?
But still, something doesn't feel right.
Oh, sorry.
Hang on.
There we go.
Hi, I'm Behrad Tarazi.
I guess you probably think I'm some kind
of awesome future man
since I'm from 2044.
My literal birthday was yesterday,
which is pretty wild, man.
That's me. Hey, baby Behrad.
Be easy and go with the flow.
Like Wu-Tang Clan and Bruce Lee.
I mean, now, that we're no longer
D-list superheroes,
we can just go where we want.
Do as we please.
Why have I stuck around?
Tell you the truth,
I have no bloody clue.
I am bored as a post, ain't I?
Gids, I'm nicking the Jumpship,
all right?
I'll see you when I see you.
The Jumpship is fully totemed.
She's a mad old bat,
that one.
Hi, I'm Mona Wu. I'm a Kaupe.
That's basically like a werewolf,
but Hawaiian.
I'm also a literary agent for...
...romance novelist Rebecca Silver,
who is secretly Mick Rory.
Jeez, Peter, take me out on a date first
before you try to... You know.
Basically, what I do is,
I sell movie rights,
get book advances,
that kind of stuff.
You're telling me that
you don't have a single dollar
for a Rebecca Silver book advance?
Okay, now you're not
just disrespecting me,
you're disrespecting my client!
Not now!
Pay up, or I will thrash you!
Hi, I'm, uh, Gary Green.
Um, if I had to sum myself up
in two words, they would be, uh...
fully forgiven.
A lot of things happened last year
that you could misconstrue
as potentially maybe being my fault.
But thankfully, everyone agrees that
at worst, I was just a hapless rube
who got manipulated by
the forces of hell to betray humanity.
Uh, I had a Fairy Godmother named Nora,
but we separated amicably
after she granted me
my heart's deepest wish.
Gary, what the hell are you doing?
Come on. We got bigger fish to fry.
Nora made me Constantine's apprentice.
Gary!
Call me!
So, uh, how does your girlfriend
feel about the documentary being made?
Actually I haven't told Sara
about the documentary yet.
I just think it was a little awkward
over the phone.
It's... it's better to spring it on her
when she gets back from the big mission.
Okay, big smiles, everyone.
And nobody mention Oliver Queen.
Why?
Because he died.
Shouldn't have done the crossover.
- Surprise!
- Yay, team!
- Yeah.
Bros!
Orange drink or limeade?
Alcohol.
Hey, love. Welcome back, baby.
Mmm.
- What is going on?
- Before you object, let me explain.
The only way that I could stop Senator
Wellington from cutting off our funding,
was to be clear and transparent
about our process.
Get it?
So, you're shooting a documentary
about the Legends?
Not me per se...
Hi, Captain Lance. Huge fan.
Uh, I'm the director, Kevin Harris.
You can call me "Kev."
Uh, just carry on, do what you're doing.
We're not even here.
That's Kev. He's got it under control.
And what if I wanna talk about
something in private?
It's not a problem. That's what
the confessional interviews are for.
Oh. Okay, so I can...
I could just say it to the camera.
- Sure.
- My girlfriend, she's lost her mind.
She just...
She really probably needs a nap.
She gets a little sleepy
after a long mission.
Um... Oh, Mick!
Why don't you tell us all
what you do on the ship, huh?
I steal stuff.
Get out of my way, you putz.
Okay.
He's just joking. Uh, Ray!
Who else saved the multi-verse?
Oh. Uh, well, the Flash, Supergirl,
- Batwoman...
- Cool.
- Yeah.
- What, no Superman?
Couldn't have been that big a deal.
Oh, no, no, Superman was there.
He's very handsome.
- It's good to have you back, buddy.
- Yeah.
Hey, we're missing someone.
Where's Charlie?
Took the Jumpship for a joyride.
Oh, a joyride to check the timeline.
Right? It's called a time scout.
Now, who wants to visit
the temporal zone? Shall we?
Guys, I'm still outside!
I'm still outside!
Don't leave me!
Hi, I'm Ray Palmer. The Atom.
This documentary is an exciting
opportunity for me to improve my image.
A lot of people still confuse me
for the demon
who possessed me
and opened up the gates of hell.
His name was Neron,
and he is no longer with me.
Or inside me, or...
I really wish that you could
meet my girlfriend Nora.
Uh, but she works
out of town a lot, internationally.
She's got a lot of global clients.
Kids mostly.
She is a Fairy Godmother.
There's something behind you.
Is this a Timequake?
See? I knew the timeline was
still in jeopardy. What do we got?
Time pirates? Time terrorism?
Time sex tourism?
Wow, Ava.
You could be a supervillain
if you applied yourself.
Gideon, what's the point of origin?
It appears my Jonah Hex has...
Beebo loves... loves you.
Gideon may have a virus.
Doesn't she make everything work?
We are perfectly safe.
Guys, that was a Class 5 Timequake!
That is so dangerous.
Okay, guys, let's just try to
keep our composure, shall we?
I've triangulated the Timequake
to 1917 St. Petersburg, Russia.
Let's go and shrink the problem.
- Uh...
- Not good.
I'm developing a catchphrase?
Executing time jump now.
No, Gideon,
we're not taking a film crew to...
Imperial Russia. Yeah, great.
This is great, Ray.
All right, Legends,
put on your babushkas
because we are rushing into Russia.
And now, you're copying my thing.
Totally.
I just got really excited.
Okay, listen, babe,
this may seem like a problem,
but let's turn it into
a proble-tunity, huh?
Maybe a party-snake
is just what the doctor ordered.
Uh, what's a party-snake?
"Sneak." Party-sneak.
The wonder of time travel
is allowing our cameras
to capture some of the first
color images of Imperial Russia
as we ride along
on the Legends' patented party-sneak.
Turns out
it's more of a fun funeral-sneak.
Who died?
Grigori Rasputin,
aka The Mad Monk.
Equal parts mystic advisor
and manipulative hornball.
Rasputin was
notoriously hard to kill.
It took cyanide, a gun,
and drowning before he stayed dead.
Um, guys...
we sure he stayed dead?
Rasputin came back from the dead,
and it caused a Timequake.
Ugh, this is the kind of problem
that I can wrap my head around.
So, I need you guys
to forget about
this documentary film crew
and focus on the mission at hand. Yes?
Yes, we need to minimize the mishap.
Oh, right,
that's good, because
saving the day
is what the Legends do best.
- Ava, you're in my shot.
- Oh, sorry.
Gideon, what does
the historical record say?
Perhaps time loop... time loop
released him from Marion Ravenwood.
Of course!
Okay, B-money, with me.
We're gonna fix Gideon,
get our guests back to 2020.
Mona, Nate, Ray,
I want you three researching Rasputin.
Figure out
what his next move's gonna be.
Okay? Let's do it.
Hey, Ray, sorry.
But just...
Hey...
- is everything okay with Sara?
- Oh, um, I don't know,
but I do know that Oliver's death
was pretty tough on her.
Yeah.
Maybe you should write Sara
a condolence card.
That's actually not a bad idea.
I guess I could
put my thoughts and feelings into words
on a card.
What if more baddies started coming back
throughout history?
If they do,
we can call 'em "evil do-overs."
"Villa-agains."
I like "Encores."
- Mmm...
- It's a good idea.
- We could take a vote. Like a team vote.
- Okay, let's vote.
- Encores.
- Villa-agains.
Encores.
- Mmm...
- Don't be a jerk about it.
Encores!
Meanwhile, back in New York,
Constantine and Gary
were doing some soul searching.
We're here with
the great mage John Constantine,
responding to an urgent call
regarding the supernatural.
Oh, bloody hell, Gary.
You know I must have been off my rocker
when I made you my assistant.
- Mr. Constantine.
- It's what the card says, love.
It's my son, Edgar.
I came home late from my shift,
usually he's up playing video games...
All right, love, there you go.
Now, why don't you let me
take a look, eh?
- What's wrong with him?
- His PJs, for starters.
Do people really wear
matching pajama sets?
Yes.
John, wait!
Masher?
- Masher, is that you possessing the lad?
- Glad to see you escaped hell.
Yeah, I could say the same
about you, mate.
Demon's gotta have his fun.
Yeah, well, I could murder a pint
right about now.
- Fancy a drink?
- You're buying.
You've got it. Let's go.
Uh, excuse me, greatest of warlocks,
but what about Edgar's mother?
Good thinking, G-man.
We'll take the fire escape.
What distable do you wix,
Captain Cat? What distable...
Easy on Gideon, Cap.
What are are you wixtable
Captain Cat... Captain Cat?
Is everybody just
trying to get on my nerves today?
Camera crew shows up and, what,
nobody can act like themselves?
The spotlight does weird things
to people.
But hey,
you know I'll always be my true self.
Oh, yeah? Your true self?
Don't your parents think
you're in business school?
I am a tangled web.
Enough about me.
How are you doing with Oliver
and everything?
I'm fine.
No worries,
we don't have to talk about it.
But...
I made you something.
Oh, please don't be a condolence card,
'cause those are always super awkward.
Nah, hopefully, something better.
It's you, Ollie, and Laurel.
B, this is actually...
It's really sweet.
Thank you.
My condolence card wasn't awkward.
"Dear Sara,
I'm sorry the vigilante you slept with
when he was already
dating your sister died.
Some say it's better
to have loved and lost,
but I hope you never loved him at all."
Sara and I aren't the type
to give each other cards, anyway.
I'd rather do something for her,
you know, like fix this
Rasputin situation and get the Legends
the heck out of Russia
before they screw something up.
Uh, you can cut the last part
of that out, right?
Apparently, when Rasputin cured
the Tsarina's only son,
the two fell madly in love.
I think if Rasputin realized
how much the Tsarina loved him,
he would wanna settle down with her,
lead the kind of quiet life
that doesn't disturb history.
Maybe Rebecca Silver's next series
could be called Russian Nights.
So, the St. Petersburg elite hated
Rasputin's influence over the Tsarina.
So the Tsar's own nephew,
a prince by the name of Yusupov,
he spearheaded the assassination.
Ray,
what if old Grigori came back,
- to settle the score?
- To settle the score.
We need to stop Rasputin
from killing Yusupov.
I'm going to deliver
a love letter to Rasputin.
I'm gonna kill Rasputin.
- You in?
- Yep!
Rasputin and I are two wandering souls
who got a second chance at life.
He shouldn't waste his encore
on revenge. Damn it!
What?
Mona was right. "Encore" feels better.
It does. Plus, with my new Atom cam,
everybody can watch us fixing history
without any bloodshed.
And Yusupov's dead.
New plan.
Trespassers!
Whoa, hey, whoa!
Don't... don't shoot. You either.
Um...
What do you want?
I'm here to interview Rasputin.
Grigori! Razzmatazz!
Do people call you "Griggy"?
There's just been
a slight misunderstanding.
Um, your monk friends here think
I'm here to kill you,
uh, when really,
I just would like to chat.
Oh, this? This is, uh, my camera crew.
We're producing a news reel
about your startling return.
After all, you're not a big deal
until you're a big deal on camera.
Grigori Rasputin. Monk. Mystic.
It is hard coming back to life.
I think, "What will make me happy?"
So, I killed the man who killed me.
But am I happy? Eh...
I'll give you Yusupov. He had it coming.
But let's talk big picture, Griggy.
- You rose from the dead.
- Mmm-hmm.
That's wild.
Nate, what are you doing?
Now, you're in my shot.
To be honest with you,
I'm here to find out
what makes you tick.
Are we killing folks?
Or chilling with folks?
Sorry, Nate, this one's for Sara.
I got your back, Nate.
Size small, standing tall!
What the...
- Ray!
- Hey! Ow.
Get outta there!
Rory, you're up.
Mona's here.
Of course she is.
Hi, guys, I forged a letter
that's gonna save history.
That's for Rasputin.
Hmm, not bad.
Nice use of "musky embrace."
I learned
from Rebecca Silver.
Well, you learned from the best.
You know, your aura is quite strong.
I get that a lot.
I rotate hair products.
Like me, you too
have experienced a miracle.
God brought you back to life.
But there's something missing.
I sense a hole in your heart.
There. Right there.
You once loved someone,
but you have forgotten.
Allow me to hypnotize you,
and I will help you recover
everything you have lost.
Don't even
think about it, Nate.
Thank you, Rasputin,
but I'm gonna have to say yes.
100%, let's do this.
As Nate's party
was about to get started...
...Constantine's was coming to an end.
It's not right bringing a kid in here.
Oh, piss off, you puritan twit!
I've gotta ask, Masher.
Has she done it?
I don't know what
you're talking about, John.
Don't be coy with me.
Has Astra released
the worst souls from hell onto Earth?
What can I say?
The girl's all grown up
and making money moves.
The question is,
what are you gonna do?
I don't need to do anything about it,
all right?
My life is settled right now.
I'm not gonna stir up
a hornet's nest of trouble
because Astra Logue wants to
break the glass ceiling in hell.
Is that so?
You smug git.
Right then...
- Sorry about this.
- No. At least let me...
You're a bastard, John.
- Where's my mom?
- Gary!
Yes, Master of the Dark Arts.
Hail the Waverider, will you?
- We need to warn the Legends.
- Uh, but what about Edgar?
Ah, you know, give him the usual.
One taxi and a lollipop coming up.
I see you, you creep.
What? What do you want?
You want my confessional?
All right. Come here,
I'll give one to you.
I confess that I hate this doc.
I confess that
I don't want to be a celebrity,
and I confess
that if you don't get that camera
- out of my face...
- Captain!
I think Gideon is suffering
from phantom data.
Do you want me to come back later?
No. You should stay.
Stay with me, hang out. Let's get lit.
Questionable timing,
but should I get my stash box?
Yes, you should.
Captain,
I have an incoming Bollywood.
Sara,
what's with the connection?
Gideon has a bug, and we're trying
to get buzzed. What do you want?
Uh, listen up, all right?
Some of the most evil souls
in all of history
are being raised from hell.
- Did you hear him? He said "hell."
- Get out.
Relax, Nathaniel.
Focus on my voice and this bauble.
Now, drop into
the deepest part of yourself.
Quivering flesh go here...
That's good.
And what if we've already run into
one of these Encores?
How do we kill it?
You can't.
Not with the chit
to their soul still in hell.
Where's Ava? Tell her I said hi.
I see a woman in the shadows.
Walk to her.
She's beautiful.
Silky raven hair...
...eyes you could just
stare into forever...
And she's stuffing her face with donuts.
God has spared Rasputin again!
Kill her!
Rory!
Nate, I'm coming for you, buddy.
Nate, snap out of it.
- I remember her, Ray.
- Who?
I don't know her name,
but she was on the ship with us.
Mission's blown.
We need to retreat.
I'm not done with you, you rats!
Good thing Sara's not watching this.
So, you guys decided to go off
on your own and face Rasputin?
I thought I could calm him down.
I thought I could make him fall in love.
And I thought I could,
you know, assassinate him.
None of that was ever going to happen.
He's fresh out of Hell.
- Well, let's kill him, then.
- You... you can't!
Look, John said that he can't be killed
while the chit of his soul
is in hell, or...
Whatever that means.
Look, Sara, we're really sorry.
We thought we could
make things easier for you
by... by taking this off of your plate.
And risking your own necks?
Look, I already have
one dead friend on my plate,
I'm good there.
And you know,
none of you self-absorbed megastars
even bothered
to ask me how I was doing.
Look, Sara, I...
I told them not to mention Oliver, okay?
I thought you wouldn't
want to be reminded.
Reminded?
What...
Did you think that I could just forget
that my friend died?
No, I...
Look, I know things have been
crazy around here.
Crazy around here?
You still have no idea
what I saw out there.
What did happen?
Countless Earths died.
I became a Paragon
and traveled back to the Big Bang.
We restarted the universe,
and now, no one even remembers
what we've changed.
- It's a lot to process.
- Yeah, I know.
So, you could see why I want to
talk to my friends about it,
and instead, I get cameras
in my face.
"Agent Sharpe
lacks a delicate touch
and is extremely deficient
at relating to people."
That is straight from
my Time Bureau personnel review.
Pretty harsh.
I wrote that review.
Yeah, of course I'm bummed
that we let Sara down,
but I am glad I got to meet Rasputin.
Little help?
I mean, the guy
got in my head and laid a bomb.
- He freaked your bean, huh?
- Oh, yeah.
He also told me about the mystery woman
that I was in love with before I died.
I know it sounds crazy, but it just...
It feels right.
Sounds like you got
some soul searching to do.
Wanna watch How Stella Got
Her Groove Back again?
No, my groove feels fine.
You think I have either split memory
or partial amnesia?
That's like what's happening
with Gideon.
Her memory is processing
what I thought was phantom data,
but maybe it's real data
from a different timeline.
Either you're a computer who caught
the same virus as Gideon...
Or, when we fixed Heyworld,
we changed the timeline.
Damn, we deducted the hell outta that.
I have to tell Sara.
Wait. Five minutes. Five minutes.
Stay on the inversion table.
Your back's gonna thank me.
Okay, so clearly, we shouldn't
have avoided asking Sara about Oliver,
but in my defense,
I was desperately afraid
I was gonna say the wrong thing,
you know?
I don't know what she needs, and
everything I try seems to make it worse.
Hold on, Behrad, so, you're saying
Gideon's glitching
because we fractured time?
Look, at least we didn't break time.
We just sort of dinged it up.
Hello?
What is on the feed?
- Is this thing on?
- Yes, we're rolling, Mr. Rasputin, sir.
Good. Get out.
Now, what was it that man
with the hair product said?
Yes.
"You're not big deal
until you're big deal on camera."
You are going to make me big deal,
Mr. Kevin Harris.
They left the director behind?
I've invited my dearest Tsarina
and her family over for dinner.
Tonight
will be a night
that you can remember.
That... that doesn't sound right.
What?
The... the laugh.
You need to nail the laugh
before we kill the Romanovs
and take the throne.
It's a work in progress.
How about this...
He's gonna kill the Romanovs.
Making him an immortal Tsar.
We can handle this.
We can? What about the team?
Shh. They're not thinking straight,
and their cover's blown.
Look, this is up to you and me, B.
We're gonna stop
this assassination alone.
Yes.
What's this?
Is this a smudge on this goblet?
Every detail must be perfect.
Tonight, I am dining
with the Imperial Family.
Take it back.
They are going to love the tea cakes.
I've laced them with cyanide.
Hello? Kevin? Right here.
- Your guests have arrived.
- The Romanovs are here!
Welcome.
It is such a shame that
your daughters could not attend.
I know how much they must have missed
their Uncle Rasputin.
Word of your death
sent them into mourning,
but none were so heartbroken as I.
Oh.
Music!
How did you manage to survive
being poisoned, shot,
and thrown into the river, Grigori?
Oh, I have a very hearty constitution.
Damn it.
The Red Wedding's about to start,
and I don't see the tea cakes anywhere.
All I see is cookies.
Tea cakes? My favorite.
The cookies are the tea cakes.
What is the meaning of this?
Forgive me, sire, I saw a bug.
Grigori, what is going on?
What have you done?
Oops. I think we forgot the cameraman.
That's Kevin, the director.
He's really more of an auteur.
We should get out there.
Sara clearly wants to handle this alone.
But are we gonna let her?
Go.
Nicholas, Alexei, come.
Wait!
You will stay exactly where you are.
For years, I have flattered you both,
our subjects adore you,
the army needs you,
and look at the state
of our beloved Russia.
Hey.
Let me guess, you're the only one
that can save it.
- Not today, Grigori.
- Who are you?
No matter. Perhaps I didn't give
an adequate demonstration of my bauble.
Attack this serving wench!
Come on, Behrad, snap out of it.
Rasputin.
The Grand Duchess Anastasia is here.
No. Anastasia, run!
So glad you could join our soiree.
Me, too.
Hey.
You're going to have to
do better than that!
Sorry.
Come on, follow me. Go!
Move it!
Didn't hurt.
All right, this way.
You're gonna hide to be safe.
Look, Sara, I...
wish I was the person
who could say the perfect thing...
Behind you.
But, listen, I'm just...
I'm not that person, okay?
Emotions are hard for me,
and I don't even know what
restarting the universe means.
Behind you.
Listen to me.
Whatever happened to you, okay?
Whatever happens to you,
I wanna be the person
that's there for you. Okay?
I'm here for you, Sara.
Ava, that was perfect.
Oh, sorry to, uh,
ruin the moment, ladies,
but we have a problem.
Come on.
Kill the Imperial Family!
Guys, come on,
we don't need to use violence here.
Ray!
Sara, think of something.
Hey, Grigori! It's your big moment.
Don't you wanna ham it up
for the cameras?
Oh, yes.
I'm Grigori Rasputin,
and I'm unkillable!
Guys? Where am I? What happened?
Don't think, Ray. Just enlarge.
Why's it so dark in here?
Am I in a lake? A...
A lake that smells like perogies?
Ray, do it. Get big now.
Embiggify!
Your atomic number is up!
Now, Ray!
Size...
matters!
Oh, no, what did...
What did I do?
You found your catchphrase, Ray.
- What the hell?
- Raw meat.
The question is,
did you get the shot, Kevin?
Uh, yeah, I got it.
You know, I chalk it up
to saving the timeline.
History has to be saved,
and sometimes, you have
to take some people out, I guess.
The public is gonna love this ending.
- It's only missing one thing.
- Hmm?
Saving history turned out
to be a messierjob
than anyone had anticipated.
To keep Rasputin from reforming,
the Legends stored his remains
in a series ofjars
that had previously been used
for condiments.
You might have thought
travelling through time
would be a way to find the answers
to life's great mysteries...
but it turns out,
sometimes, you just find more questions.
But one thing is true
in any time period,
it's being there for the ones you love
that makes the journey worthwhile.
Hear that applause?
This movie is not even gonna begin
to satiate the Legends craze.
You know what this is?
This is a TV show.
I'm talking cameras on every mission.
Sara, you okay? You look nauseous.
Yeah, she's fine. And when you go
out there, just... just be yourselves.
- But, you know, bigger.
- Like, bigger how?
Just act heroic.
You guys have
a real Bad News Bears vibe.
It's not doing you any favors.
Now that you're big-time,
people expect you to put on a show.
So, you're asking us
not to be ourselves?
This guy gets it. Let's do this.
Hi, everybody.
We are the Legends...
...and we just wanted to say thank you
for watching our film.
We hope that you enjoyed it.
Of course, uh,
none of it was real.
No, way! It's not real?
Excuse me? Uh, she's joking.
No, I'm not. Come on, time travel?
It's the biggest hoax in history,
am I right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I mean,
it's obvious that this is all fake.
How could Rasputin speak English?
You told me it was
temporal linguistic dysplasia.
I mean, if we had so much as coughed,
our modern germs would have
wiped out half the population.
Why wouldn't we just find baby Hitler
and make him wrestle baby Stalin?
Think about it.
The special effects
were kind of questionable.
Shut up!
It's not real.
All right, everybody,
I guess that just means don't believe
everything you see on camera.
Yeah, it was all
just a big fake spectacle,
just like Heyworld last year.
We are all a bunch of frauds.
Big frauds, everybody.
- You guys ruined my movie.
- Yeah, sorry.
This is for the best, right?
Maybe, maybe not. I don't know.
I feel like I'm supposed to say that.
We're better off.
Fame messes with people.
We still have that money problem.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Mick?
I steal things.
Whoa. Is that a Faberg egg?
Mmm-hmm.
- What's that worth?
- Fifty million.
Whoa!
Careful with that, babes.
John, what...
What are you doing here?
I heard your movie premiere was in town
tonight, so, I thought I'd pop in.
Well, just make yourself at home, then!
Why can't he ever
just be normal?
What are you doing?
Yeah,
I need to borrow something.
Rasputin wasn't an isolated incident.
Not isolated?
What do you mean?
- Okay. Hey, whoa! No, no, don't do it...
- Don't!
I'm plumbing into this.
Wait. Are you trying to go back to Hell?
Soul become my soul,
flesh become my flesh.
Hades, firstborn of Cronus,
I call upon you.
Hey, John, there's gotta be another way.
I'll return when the sigil is complete.
John?
You take care, you lunatic.
I always do, love. I always do.
You know,
sometimes what happens on this ship
really would be hard
for an audience to follow.
That love letter you wrote,
it was good.
Very good.
Gee, thank you, Mick.
This means so much coming from you.
Listen, um, I'm giving up the writing.
It's getting in the way of my thievery.
So, I'm handing the Rebecca Silver
novels over to you.
Someone deserving.
Me?
This is... This is so much.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure. That's why I'm saying it.
There's a novelist inside you.
There's more inside of me
than just Wolfie?
Yes. That's right.
Well, it was great living with you
on the Waverider.
- What?
- Yeah, I... I can't stay here to write.
I need to be free.
I need to fall in love and break hearts.
I can't do Rebecca Silver justice here.
But... But I...
But you tried writing on the ship
and ran out of ideas?
I mean, frankly, Mick,
your latest novel Carjacked,
it sucked.
But don't worry. Rebecca Silver
is about to have her comeback.
You'll see.
You were my favorite.
How's it going, Gideon?
The phantom memory scrub
is proceeding without a hitch.
The flaws only go
as far back as the last two years.
Oh, it feels good
to get my thoughts straight.
Good work, Gidi.
- I'm turning in.
- Good night, B.
- Don't stay up too late, Nate.
- You got it.
- Dr. Heywood?
- Mmm.
I have encountered a glitch
during the Heyworld event.
Show me.
Nate...
if you're seeing this,
we altered my future at Heyworld.
I don't know where I'll be
or who I'll be, but...
I know that I love you.
Find me.
Gideon! Gideon, who was that?
Play it again.
Memory scrub complete.