Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Thank you for notifying us
of Detective Hunter's whereabouts.
Now the Legends
are free to fly the skies?
The Time Bureau
has bigger things to worry about
than a bunch of idiots.
Mallus is getting stronger,
Captain Lance.
There is a war coming
and history needs you to be ready.
- Do I know you?
- No, no.
I'm Marty.
So, you're Leonard Snart's
doppelganger?
No, I'm Leonard Snart,
but you can call me Leo.
I'm asking you to let me die,
so that you may live.
Sleigh bells ring
Are you listening?
In the lane
This is the last store
in town with the Beebo dolls,
Clarissa, I... I promise.
I am not leaving
without one for Lily.
Professor Stein, Merry Christmas.
And a Happy Hanukah to you, Chuck.
Every kid needs a Beebo doll, right?
So it would seem.
I got one! I can't believe I got one!
I don't suppose you can tell me
how many Beebos you have back there?
Plenty. Don't worry about it.
That was the last one.
Actually, we just ran out them.
- But you just said...
- I'm sorry, folks.
We are expecting
a new shipment in February.
February?
Five-year-olds don't wait
until February.
Wait! There's one more Beebo
right there.
Move!
Think, Marty.
Distance of about 6m.
Allowing for air resistance.
Breathe in, hold...
Eureka! I've got it!
Beebo, loves you!
Get him!
Barbarians!
Oh Hanukkah, oh Hanukkah
The festival of joy
A holly day, a jolly day
For every girl and boy
Great Scott.
Barbarians?
Gideon said
that you wanted to see me.
Come in. Have a seat.
You comfortable?
I know the Legends
have lost a friend.
I've been there.
I wanna help you guys
through the grieving period.
Oh, that's...
that's very sweet of you.
I wanna give you the chance
to get anything off your chest,
anything at all.
What would you like to say...
to Professor Martin Stein?
I... I think that everyone
copes in their own ways.
It's clear the Legends
are ill-equipped to cope at all.
This way? This is wrong.
Actually, there is one question
- I never got to ask Marty.
- Great.
When I reduce
the Waverider's coefficient
of sinusoidal depleneration,
it seems to inversely hyper-celerate.
Let's hear it again.
What would you like
to say to me, Nathaniel?
Still a little too nasally.
Remember, you speak very precisely.
This is therapy, not acting class.
Nice! That's the right level
of frustration.
That's very Stein.
Now just do it with the puppet.
My goodness, you're really
working out some rage issues
with Professor Stein.
No, I just hate puppets.
All right, I am,
I am putting the puppet away.
I get it now.
That wasn't the best tactic.
Look, Jax. I think that you,
even more so than the others,
must be in pain about this.
He died so I could live.
- End of story.
- It wasn't your fault.
I should never have given him
that Firestorm cure.
I should've been strong enough
for both of us.
I...
All right, you know, no.
We're not doing this.
What was that?
An Anachronism caused a disturbance
in the Temporal Zone,
which created a Timequake.
And this is where Marty
would've said, "Fascinating."
All right, everybody,
I know you're sad,
so this is what we're gonna do.
I want you to take all
of your feelings about Martin
and put it in a box,
and then, I want you
to close the box,
and then,
you're gonna lock the box.
Well, that sounds healthy.
Maybe not,
but we got a job to do.
Gideon, the Anachronism, please.
Level 12?
Level Ten didn't do it justice.
Leif Eriksson's Vikings
set up a colony
in the New World around 1000 A.D.
Little known fact,
the Vikings "discovered"
the Americas
492 years before Columbus,
but due to Eriksson's
adoption of Christianity,
the Vikings decided
to pack up their bags
and head home.
Sorry, Gideon, you were saying?
In this version of history,
the Vikings stayed
and conquered all of North America,
or as it's called now, New Valhalla.
- Cool hat.
- How many beers is that?
It's not even noon yet.
You have a problem, Mickey.
I don't have a problem.
Now shut up.
All right, let's go.
I don't think the Legends
are ready for the field.
Listen, Leo,
kicking ass is how we heal.
I don't like it, sister.
This land is bountiful.
But these people,
these Skraelings,
they're skilled warriors.
We should not challenge them.
It's time to return home
to Greenland.
Brother, this continent is vast.
Who knows how far west it goes,
and what riches it has to plunder.
It is our destiny to conquer
all of New Valhalla.
That's Leif Erikkson
and his sister, Freydis.
Yeah, this moment
has huge historical significance.
It determines whether or not
the Vikings leave North America,
which, for me,
is very exciting 'cau...
You okay, man?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
Let's just stay on mission.
Okay.
The Christian monks
say that endless war
means our people
will never know peace.
It is what the Blue God
has demanded, brother.
The Anachronism isn't a weapon.
Guys, we're dealing
with some kind of Blue God.
Found him.
Is that...
Martin?
Martin's the Anachronism.
They used his genius
to conquer the New World.
Just... Hey, it's supposed to be
a stealth mission.
Damn it!
Jax, back into position now.
Jefferson?
What are you doing here?
- I... I haven't seen you since...
- 1987.
Don't worry, Martin,
I'ma get you out of here.
Wait!
No, no, no, no, no!
Hey.
- You all right?
- Most certainly not!
Look out!
I haven't had a bath
or a change of clothes
for over a week.
I... I could've died.
- Was it something I said?
- No, nothing. It's fine.
We just gotta get out of here
before the rest of the clan comes.
No, no, no,
wait, wait, wait, wait.
- We have to go back.
- Go back for what?
- My Beebo.
- What the hell is a Beebo?
As in Cuddle Me Beebo?
It's a Hannukah gift for Lily.
We're not going back
for some damn toy!
You don't understand!
That damn toy is gonna
change history!
The four-eyed man has escaped.
No matter.
We still have our God.
Beebo hungry.
And our God hungers for battle!
Beebo! Beebo! Beebo! Beebo!
All right, let me get this straight.
So, the Vikings think
that Beebo is a God,
Beebo as in,
"Wah, wah, Beebo love you"?
As preposterous as it sounds,
that obnoxious toy
is the only reason I survived.
The Vikings who found me
in the woods
were about to kill me,
when Beebo spoke.
It... it was like a, a spell
was cast over the barbarians.
Here, this should warm you up.
- Earl Grey?
- With a little bit of brandy.
My favorite.
Thank you, Jefferson.
It does make sense.
Norse mythology is filled
with creatures like Beebo:
trolls, gnomes, tumptens.
Okay, sure, but thinking he's a God
who wants them
to conquer the New World?
You see, at first,
the Vikings thought that
only I could make Beebo talk.
But it soon became clear
that my translations
were not what Lief's sister
wanted to hear.
Freydis usurped my position
and twisted Beebo's words
for her own agenda.
All right, sounds like
we gotta go get that Beebo,
and send the Vikings packing.
Zari, can you take young Stein
to where he can get cleaned up?
Come on.
I... I can help him,
'cause I've got nothing else...
It's okay. Zari's got it.
Mart... Marty. Mar... Martin...
you're looking young and lively.
- Good to see you.
- You too, Raymond.
One question: Where's me?
- You...
- At peace.
With your family for the,
for the holidays.
I almost forgot.
Happy Hannukah.
I'll drink to that.
That's disgusting.
What's wrong with this beer?
Man, can you believe Sara?
She doesn't trust me
around young Stein.
So you're saying
you weren't planning on
warning Martin about him dying?
Okay, fine. But come on, man.
Grey dies, and then, all of a sudden,
his younger self
gets displaced in time?
Yeah, I know. It's crazy that
we keep bumping into ourselves.
- Yeah.
- I mean, Ray and the baby Dominator,
- and Sir Stein and his killer stash.
- Mick's dad.
I mean, this can't just be
a coincidence.
What if this is fate's way
of saying we should step up?
That we can actually improve things?
Martin made his choice, Jax.
We should be
honoring his sacrifice,
not trying to undo it.
Yeah, but it's Grey.
I mean, how can we not tell him?
Because what if
knowing about his death
makes young Marty choose not
to create the Firestorm matrix
or meet you
or step foot on this ship?
He never would've wanted you
to risk the present
to save him in the past.
And how exactly do you know
what he would've wanted, Ray?
You weren't psychically
connected to him for three years.
Gideon!
The beer tastes like sewage water.
Was that a question, Mr. Rory?
Don't get smart, lady.
I adjusted the fabrication settings.
The Waverider's now a dry ship.
No alcohol allowed.
You son of a...
You said your drinking
wasn't a problem.
If you can go a couple of days
without booze,
you've proven your point.
A couple of days?
- Forty-two hours?
- Forty-eight.
So, I checked the lunar calendar,
and today is Yuletide.
Oh, like Christmas?
Well, before Christians rebranded it,
wreaths, trees, elves were
all Norse traditions first.
And tonight, Leif is throwing
a huge Yuletide feast.
Which is the perfect cover for us.
Oh. We could dress up
as Norse Gods
and order
them to head back to Greenland
or face our wrath!
- Worst idea you ever had.
- That's a terrible idea.
Incoming transmission
from Agent Sharpe.
Put her on.
Agent Sharpe,
it's been awhile, thankfully.
- Captain Lance.
- Let me guess,
you saw that there's
a Level 12 Anachronism,
and you're calling
to lecture me on everything
that we're doing wrong.
No.
- Okay, yes.
- Hmm.
But I also heard about Martin Stein,
and I'm calling
to express my condolences.
Well, thank you,
but my team and I,
we have it under control.
I hope so, because the Legends
fixing a Level 12
under normal circumstances
would be a Beebo Day miracle.
Did you just say Beebo Day?
December 25th, Beebo Day.
When families exchange gifts
and sing silly songs
and discover that they can no longer
live under the same roof?
Beebo Day's part of
the Anachronism, isn't it?
- Yeah.
-Yeah, never felt right.
This Anachronism is cementing fast.
And to be honest, my team is still
pretty raw from losing Stein.
We could use an outside perspective.
Are you asking for my help?
No.
Okay, yes.
All right.
What's the plan?
You ready to see
the Legends in action?
The goal is to do this peacefully,
without action.
There's a first time
for everything, I guess.
Hail, Leif son of Erik.
I, Nathaniel Henryson.
Hail, Nathanial son of Henry.
A Yuletide surprise.
Are you sure this is wise, brother?
We know nothing about these people.
We brought booze.
Tell me of your clan.
You certainly are an odd collection.
We're from all over.
But we stick together
the best we can.
Although, recently,
we lost a brother.
That can be difficult.
I've lost far too many
men and women in my own clan.
It has made you soft, brother.
Let's not fight
in front of our guest, sister.
As far as strategy goes,
this would not be my first pick.
Why not? They welcomed us in.
We get Beebo, we get out.
The Bureau has rules
about fraternizing with the locals,
and these costumes are ridiculous.
Nah, you look good.
- Give me that!
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No booze means no booze, Mickey.
- Stop calling me that.
- You have 35 hours left.
Can you handle it?
Are you ready to admit
that you have a problem?
You're the problem!
There you are, you little bastard!
Beebo thirsty.
You dare to steal from our God?
He's not gonna drink it.
Our Gods do not tolerate
such insolence.
Beebo will decide your fate.
Anyone have eyes on Beebo?
Short, blue, looking for cuddles?
Yep, we're working on it.
Here we go!
By Odin's Spear, you bested us.
Beautiful,
and they can hold their mead.
Tell us...
which of these clansmen
are your husbands,
and we'll kill them.
I'm not really the husband kind.
Perfect! Me neither!
All right, you guys said if we won,
you'd take us to see your Blue God.
Two out of three.
Fellow warriors...
Our guest has been stealing
mead from the Blue God.
And now,
our God will render judgment.
Beebo! Beebo! Beebo! Beebo!
Beebo! Beebo!
How judge you, Beebo?
Beebo hungry.
Our God demands justice.
To the pyre!
Nate and Amaya, you're on Beebo.
Everyone else, let's make sure
Rory doesn't get burned alive.
Freydis, it's Yuletide.
Let's not ruin it.
More wood, so bright Odin
can see it from Valhalla.
Is it weird that I find her hot?
Weird, but then again,
not surprising.
Leo, can you
take care of the fire?
Copy that, Captain Lance.
I thought you said this was
an undercover operation.
Well, blowing your cover
is half the fun.
Into the flames!
Now.
It's a sign!
Beebo does not want
our clansman to be burned.
The Blue God has shown mercy.
I luh-luh-love you.
- I accidentally squeezed him.
- He's so damn huggable.
Unhand him or die!
I am leaving myself wide open,
and you can't land a single punch.
Yeah, I'm just warming up.
Let's up the stakes then.
Loser takes the other's chores
for a month.
Deal.
I know what you're trying to do,
by the way.
- What's that?
- Tying to distract me.
I'm also trying to beat you.
Is the distraction working?
- I still wanna warn Grey.
- So do it.
I would've warned my brother,
if I had the chance.
- Yeah, but Sara...
- Just 'cause she's the Captain
doesn't mean you have to do
everything she says.
Yeah, no, I know, but we're not...
Jefferson, there you are.
- Game over!
- Come... come on!
- I'm scary good at this.
- You're just okay.
Forgive the interruption,
but I would very much like to return
to my Clarissa and Lily,
with or without
that wretched Beebo.
Oh, yeah, sure.
I'll take you in the jumpship.
Yo. This is your chance.
Find some loophole,
like I did with Helen of Troy.
You can save your friend's life.
Nathaniel!
Beebo, likes to play!
Nate! Nate! I'm open!
Bee...
I hate puppets.
Beebo want cuddle...
I know how much
you wanted to believe, sister,
but Beebo's a false God
full of false promises.
We are Vikings.
This is our land to conquer.
It's time to go home
and abandon this colony.
It seems the Old Gods
have abandoned us.
Well, looks like the Legends
have saved Odin Day.
Odin Day?
Wait, you mean Christmas?
Doesn't ring a bell.
I thought
we fixed the Anachronism.
My name is Odin,
ruler of Asgard.
Damien Darhk...
You know this guy?
- And his daughter.
- See?
I told you the Norse God
costumes would work.
Bow to the King of the true Gods!
He has left Valhalla
to lead you into battle.
Together, we will conquer
the New World.
Mick, no, we're outmatched.
Let's go.
Kneel before Odin, brother.
That was unexpected.
I mean, not the Darhks showing up.
They seem to enjoy altering history.
- You retreating.
- Well, Vikings are one thing.
If we're gonna tangle
with the Darhks,
we have to get our heads on straight.
I, for one, am glad
you're treading cautiously.
We've arrived safely
in the Temporal Zone,
but I'm afraid the Anachronism has...
Let me guess, it's worse.
Thank you, Gideon.
Another Timequake.
We are not letting America go Viking.
Ava, can you call
the Time Bureau for backup?
Wait, wait, wait,
are we really that desperate?
Yeah.
Well, the last time
we faced Nora Darhk,
- she put Sara in a coma.
- Right.
- I'll speak to Director Bennett.
- Thank you.
Wow, that's quite the getup.
Where's Martin and Jax?
They're on their way
back to Central City.
Gotta get Martin home
for the holidays.
You've been awfully quiet, Jefferson.
My bad. I've just had some...
some things on my mind.
It's good to be home.
I can't wait to see
Clarissa and Lily.
Listen...
this is gonna sound crazy, okay,
but you need to open this letter
on November 28th, 2017.
I've seen "Back to the Future,"
Jefferson,
that mockery of time
travel that Clarissa adores.
I don't suppose this letter
has anything to do with my future.
This letter could save your life.
Then I categorically refuse
to take it.
You know the dangers
of trying to improve history.
No, no, this, this is your future.
And your past.
Give me a little credit.
I... I know the team was lying
when they said I was visiting
family for the holidays.
Then take the damn letter
and stop being so stubborn.
Think about your family.
This letter is a loophole.
Nothing changes until
November 28th, 2017.
Please.
Okay, Jefferson.
Thank you.
Hello, friend.
Looking for booze?
I'm not your friend.
You almost died back there,
and I know you're craving a drink.
That's why it's so important
to resist!
You have to stop numbing yourself
to fear and pain.
That's when the true
transformation begins!
Mickey!
You're right. You're right.
I... I apologize.
That... that was his name.
Your Earth-X doppelganger
was my best friend.
We grew up together
in the Resistance.
And when he died, I...
I was devastated.
But seeing you made me realize,
I was a long way from acceptance.
I didn't come onboard
just to help you process your loss.
I came so I could process mine.
Was that guttural sound
your response?
- To what?
- My heartfelt confession.
I don't care. I wasn't listening.
Well, the Mick Rory I knew did care,
and he did listen.
He was the kindest,
most selfless person
I've ever met.
A far cry from the crude, alcoholic,
oafish waste of space before me.
I'm a disappointment?
Well, the Leonard Snart that I knew
was a cold, ruthless criminal,
who didn't say boo
about my drinking,
because he knew
I could get the job done!
I don't like you. You don't fit in.
Why don't you go back to
that Nazi hellhole you call home?
Well, if that's how you feel,
then I'll leave,
as soon as we return from Vinland.
- Good.
- Good!
Are we clear, Agent Sharpe?
Crystal, sir.
Please tell me you have good news.
I'm afraid Director Bennett
doesn't believe this mission
is the best use of our resources.
So what, the Time Bureau
is just gonna let the Darhks
run around and change history?
The Time Bureau's in disarray.
Ever since Rip
was sentenced to prison, we...
Wait, Rip is in prison?
He was hardly convincing
at the tribunal,
raving about Mallus,
completely unapologetic.
And in his absence,
Damien Darhk has recruited
even more allies.
Gideon, can you pull up
what Director Bennett
showed me, please?
Grodd survived Vietnam.
Darhk secured him
a means of time travel.
Of course.
Darhk and his daughter
are just too powerful.
They have magic
that we don't understand.
We've lost scores of agents
trying to fight them.
So what? What does that mean?
That you're just gonna
throw in the towel?
We can't afford
to lose anyone else.
- And I can?
- No, I mean...
Do you have any idea
how hard this has been on us?
I really am sorry, Sara.
Director Bennett has ordered me
to return to the Time Bureau.
Screw his orders.
I need you here.
Look, I know Darhk
is personal for you,
and you're the last person
to back out of a fight,
but you asked me to give you
an outside perspective.
If you're concerned
about the safety of your team,
leave Vinland.
This is not a fight
the Legends can win.
Hey.
- You rang?
- Yes.
Heard you took young Stein
back to 1992.
- Yep.
- How'd it go?
He's just glad to be home.
Okay, here's the deal.
Backup is not coming.
The Time Bureau thinks
the Darhks can't be defeated,
and they're probably right.
Leo asked us to talk
about our feelings.
Well, my feeling
is that history needs us
to stop the Darhks.
But after losing Stein,
I can't lose anyone else.
I need you guys to take
the Waverider and leave.
Not without you.
You can't face Darhk alone.
I have a plan.
I'm here to speak to Odin.
Let her pass.
My father will enjoy killing you.
You've come alone.
I'm here to make you an offer.
Oh, this ought to be good.
Leave now, and I'll let you live.
No.
Hold up.
Your plan sucks.
- Pretty's right.
- Well, I can't do nothing.
Yeah, but you can come up
with a better plan
that, like, doesn't get you killed.
Okay, Z, what's your big plan?
Well, first of all,
you don't enter the Longhouse
by yourself.
My father will enjoy killing you.
You've come alone.
Not exactly.
And then, Darhk will have
some sort of quip.
Something evil,
but not too mustache-twirly.
What, are you gonna huff
and puff till you blow my house in?
What's the matter?
Performance anxiety?
So far, this works,
but it doesn't solve
our Nora problem.
And what about
the rest of the Vikings?
Odin is under attack!
Defend him,
if you wanna see Valhalla.
You're gonna need backup.
Listen, Sara,
just don't let Grey's death
teach us the wrong lessons.
Either we do this together
or not at all.
Gideon, plot a course for Vinland.
What, are you gonna huff
and puff till you blow my house in?
What's the matter?
Performance anxiety?
Odin is under attack!
Defend him,
if you wanna see Valhalla.
Halt.
It is I, Beebo,
risen from the grave.
Like Christ himself.
Yeah...
Yes, Jesus is
the one true God, which...
doesn't mean science
or evolution isn't real.
Anyway, you need
to return to Greenland,
which will soon be melting
thanks to global warming,
which is also real.
Like a little fire?
How 'bout a little ice?
Nora.
They killed the Valkyrie!
Nora!
Not this time.
Sara Lance.
Who's there?
Who are you?
What is this place?
I am Mallus.
Soon I will be free,
and your world will know
unendurable pain.
You came back.
It's like you said, you needed me.
Well, your timing is impeccable.
It's a Christmas miracle.
Yes.
There is nothing physically
ailing you, Captain Lance.
Told you. I'm fine.
You also told me
you visited an alternate dimension.
Well, it wasn't my first time.
Sara.
Tell me exactly
what you saw in there.
Look, I don't know, okay?
It wasn't about what I saw.
It was about what I... felt.
It was an absence of feeling
no warmth, no love, just a void,
and the only thing filling
the void was...
Mallus.
It seems Rip was right
to be obsessed with him.
I need to tell the Bureau.
Well, aren't you afraid of getting
in trouble for disobeying orders?
It was worth it.
See ya again.
Gideon, how's the ol' timeline?
Records show that
history has been restored.
New Valhalla
is North America again,
and the only war Beebo has incited
is in shopping malls
across the nation.
Sounds like our work here is done.
Gideon, you're sure there are
no other changes to the timeline?
If you're referring
to Professor Stein,
he still died in 2017.
I'm sorry, Jax.
Wait. I... I just don't understand.
The loophole,
it... it should've worked.
That letter told him exactly
how to protect himself
on the day he died.
What happened?
He must not have read it.
Oh! Hey, Lily!
A little birdie told me
you wanted one of these guys.
Beebo! I love him!
Happy Hanukah.
Clarissa, you remember Jefferson.
- You haven't aged a day.
- Neither have you.
Can I get you some Earl Grey?
Yeah, sure.
Come on.
I think I know why you're here.
Come in.
The letter, you never read it.
That's because I already burned it.
What?
I was tempted, to be sure.
I thought a lot about that date.
November 28th, 2017.
I'll be 67 then.
I'll have had adventures,
watched my daughter grow up,
and I'll have made a friend,
who was willing to risk far,
far too much for me.
No, I... I am trying to save you.
You need to let me go.
We both know you shouldn't be here.
I... I may have a life ahead of me,
but to you,
- I'm a ghost.
- No, no, to me...
I'm not gonna cheat death, Jefferson.
None of us live forever.
And yet, I clearly live
a wonderful life with many chapters.
And if I had one wish,
it, it wouldn't be for me
to prolong my life.
It... would be for you
to live yours,
and to have all the happiness
you deserve.
Okay.
Goodbye, Grey.
Goodbye, Jefferson.
Did you try to change his fate?
Didn't work, so...
I'm sorry, Jax.
Me too.
If I stay on this ship,
I'll never be able to move on.
What do you mean? Like...
you wanna leave?
You, you can't leave, Jax.
No, you're, you're not leaving.
You're a part of this team.
Yeah, and I always will be,
but right now...
this is something I gotta do.
I need a different kind of adventure.
Is this what you really want?
Yeah.
I would order you to stay,
but I know you'd just disobey me
and follow your heart,
like you always do.
Hey.
Can you do me a favor?
Don't tell the others until I'm gone.
I don't do goodbyes.
It's... it's not my thing.
Yeah, yeah. Totally, I get it.
Okay.
- Surprise!
- Boo!
You didn't really think
we were just gonna let you
sneak out of here
without saying goodbye.
Yeah,
we can't celebrate the holidays
without the whole family.
Happy Yuletide.
Jingle bell, jingle bell
Jingle bell rock
Well, I think we made
an impressive team out there.
Reminded me of old times.
L'chaim.
Jingle bell, jingle bell
As you can taste,
I reprogrammed Gideon.
I should not have
tried to change you,
and I'm sorry, Mick.
To the ones we lost,
or left behind.
Speech.
- Speech, speech, speech.
- Oh...
Okay, all right.
When Grey first dragged me
onboard this ship,
I thought it was the last place
that I wanted to be.
I mean, you were all
a bunch of screw-ups,
B-list superheroes,
washed up bank robbers, no offense.
- It's true.
- But the thing is,
when you get
a bunch of broken pieces,
and you put them all together
the right way,
they make something new.
And suddenly,
they don't feel so broken anymore.
And I'm pretty sure
that's what a family is.
So...
I don't know what happens next,
but I know I'll always have
a family here with you guys.
- That's right.
- Damn right, little brother.
Always.
Cheers.
Well...
it's been an honor, Captain.
Come here.
Hey.
I'm sure it's only gonna be
a matter of time
before some Aztecs with jetpacks
invade Central City, so...
And the honor's been all mine.
It's been a long time, love.
John?
Now, let's see,
the last time we met,
I saved your soul.
Now there's something
you can do for me.
Look, I'd love to help,
but your timing is terrible.
This won't take long.
You see,
there's a demon out there.
It's possessing a little girl.
And that demon,
he knows your name.
Beebo, loves you!