[Sara] Previously on
Legends Of Tomorrow...
An unknown number of other dangerous
magical beings got spat out
across the timeline and now
must be sent to hell.
[speaks other language]
Your shapeshifting days are over,
sweetheart.
- No!
- Is that a Kaupe?
[Agent Sharpe]
This is a prison, Mona.
And they are our prisoners,
not our friends.
People around me get hurt,
killed or far, far worse.
But you can't mess with your past.
[Constantine] Des.
[people chattering and laughing]
Order up!
Last one.
Oi, oi. Wake up, John-O!
Piss off, will ya!
Oh, not today, you lying geezer!
- What the...
- You said that my shapeshifting days
- were over.
- You call that abomination
shapeshifting, do you?
Well, if I can shift at all,
that means your spell is reversible.
You see, that's where you're wrong,
sweetheart.
There's no taking it back.
Smart man like you, John-O,
you can figure it out.
Yeah, well, mortal life
is full of disappointments.
Best get used to it, love.
[clicks tongue]
It's all right. That's all right.
You know how I survived
in the prison dimension?
Trading favors.
Now, sooner or later,
you're gonna need something from me.
[Constantine chuckles]
Then we'll talk, chum.
[scoffs]
[Sara] Thanks for staying
at my place this time.
I love sleeping next to you.
I just wish that your place didn't
mean sharing a bathroom with...
- Beer.
- Yes, Garima.
Beer, it's the only word
Rory taught her.
Wait, Rory's still using Brigid's
diary?
That thing is an ancient
magical artifact.
Yeah, but it keeps him happy.
Sara, be reasonable.
You can't let Rory keep the diary.
I see you've met Garima.
What she lacks in vocabulary,
she makes up for in personality.
And everyone knows that a happy Mick
is better for the entire ship.
- Whoa!
- Oh!
- Killer 'stache!
- Interesting.
[Ray] You think? I had Gideon stimulate
my hair follicles to grow it overnight.
I read in one of Nora's letter's
that she had a thing for mustaches.
Sorry, but how are we all being
so blasé about the diary?
What if Rory goes
from writing sci-fi to horror?
Do you want killer clowns running
around the ship?
The only killer on the ship is
the amount of sugar in this cereal.
"Big Easy O's"?
They taste like beignets. So sweet,
it makes your lips pucker.
Oh, there's a quiz on the back.
"Who is the most prolific
serial killer in the United States?"
Ted Bundy. Although in my opinion,
John Wayne Gacy had way more victims
than he confessed.
What?
Everyone has their hobbies.
Sorry, Ava, but according to this
not so kid-friendly cereal,
the answer is New Orleans' own
Marie Laveau.
What?
A high-profile female serial killer?
No, I would have heard of her.
The box is wrong.
Unless... Gideon.
[Gideon] You are correct, Captain.
It appears a fugitive
is on the loose in New Orleans
in 1856.
According to local lore,
there were a series of murders
perpetrated by a criminal
who could walk through walls.
Sounds like we're going mind huntin'
in the Big Easy.
Gideon. Plot a course.
[grunts]
[groans]
Unbelievable.
You just ran into my car, Ear Muffs.
But... Your car...
The scratch will easily cost you
a couple of hundos.
- You want me to pay for it?
- Yes.
No worries, sir,
I can have the money tomorrow.
They really need to stop giving
delivery girls drive-ons.
I'm actually Assistant Coordinator
of Creature Upkeep.
[elevator dings]
[winces]
Ahoy, matey. [chuckles]
It seems to be pirate day
once again, ya scurvy wench.
[both] Arr!
Don't be late again, or Ava will
give you another peg leg.
- Okay.
Hey, Catch a Predator, what was that?
Well, that,
my fellow rebound artiste,
- was flirting.
- Gary, that was not flirting.
- No.
- What do you mean? I made extended
eye contact, picked up on some
personal information,
and then I negged her.
Don't tell me you're falling for this
like Neanderthal misogynistic
dating advice?
You're a modern man surfing
the sexual spectrum.
Just be cool and ask her out.
Or, I'm just spit-balling here,
you can ask her out for me.
[scoffs] This isn't high school.
Oh, sorry.
High school's a bit
of a trigger word for me.
Wow, you are really broken.
Okay, look, I will...
[clears throat]
I'm not gonna ask her out,
but I will do some recon.
You'll be my time-bro wingman?
You do things like that and it makes
it very hard to help you, Gary.
[Sara] All right, Legends, next stop,
New Orleans.
We have a fugitive serial killer
and it's a weird one.
It says here that all of the victims
were wealthy blonde ladies...
...stabbed to death
inside their locked bedrooms.
- Spooky.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Blondes killed in locked rooms...
That's the MO of Mike the Spike.
Am I gonna find a murder board
in your closet?
[Constantine]
New Orleans is a crap town.
Although anything's better than
that tush tickler.
This?
Well, the cops pinned it on voodoo
priestess, Marie Laveau...
...one of the only women of color
with power living in 1856.
- Surprise, surprise.
- You stole my diary, weasel.
You mean the one that you knicked
from my trunk? That one?
Gentlemen, gentlemen,
I mustache you both to calm down.
Out of my way, otherwise I'll knock
that fur ball off your lip.
I confiscated the diary.
It's Time Bureau property now.
Don't worry, Rory, Garima will always
be right where she belongs.
In your imagination.
Garima.
Rory, look, I'm sorry,
Ava was just doing her job,
which is exactly
what the rest of us need to do.
Ray, Mick, we're going to protect
the fugitive's first victim,
Ms. Didi Charbonnet.
She's hosting a party this afternoon.
John, I need you to talk to Laveau.
Find out how she's mixed up in this.
I'll go with him.
Yeah, I love me some voodoo.
Great. Zari, you're on their mission.
You can just say the B-Team.
No, there's no...
There's no such thing as B-Team!
But there is such a thing
as an A-Team.
Laissez les bon temps rouler!
[speaking French]
Wow, this doesn't even look
like America.
Oh, it's not. This is New Orleans, baby.
Have you been here before?
After London,
the best city in the world.
I mean, just look
at this hodgepodge of humanity.
It's a perfect place to
pick a face and just have some fun.
[laughing]
John.
- You okay?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's just, uh... [clears throat]
This city just brings back memories,
is all.
[melancholy jazz playing]
Monsieur Constantine,
will you come with me, please.
[laughing]
Yeah, I'm not really not
in the habit of going home
with strangers, mate.
At least not recently.
[groans] Not again.
[gasping]
Oh, no.
This is not good.
[grunting]
Bloody New Orleans!
[gasping and coughing]
[sighs]
Priestess Laveau.
Cheers, love, you saved me
the trouble of finding you.
It was a little bit theatrical
to be honest with you,
but then again, I do appreciate
a flair for the dramatic.
[speaking in French]
[groans]
You have something of mine.
Oh, I have no idea what you're on about.
I felt its presence as soon
as you arrived in New Orleans.
This medallion honors Saint Marron,
the patron saint of runaway slaves.
Now, what do you know about bondage,
mon cher?
Buy me a pint in the local pub
and I'll tell you all about it, love.
You don't have to say a thing.
I'm back, and it is time for me
to cook you a breakfast.
One full English, coming up.
Hey, Johnny.
[blues music playing]
Des, you have to leave town.
This thing that's after me,
it's no ordinary demon.
This medallion has been in my family
for generations.
It's imbued with a protection spell.
Take it, Johnny.
As long as you promise to leave town.
It's just until I get this mess
sorted out, all right?
- All right.
[gasps]
My great-great-grandson,
he must have loved you
to give you my medallion.
Did you love him?
[jazz band playing]
Does anyone have eyes
on the fugitive's first victim?
[Agent Sharpe] Annoying blonde
in the middle, that's Didi Charbonnet.
Good. Stay with her.
[Agent Sharpe] According to Gideon,
the murder's going to happen
within the hour.
What kind of fugitive stabs a woman?
[Mick] I know a woman I can stab.
Rhymes with Shmava.
Rory, play nice.
[Agent Sharpe] Don't worry,
I can handle myself against the cretin.
- [Mick] Whatever, man-pants.
- Hey.
Look, I know you're mad at Ava
right now, but she's right,
the diary is not a toy.
Garima helped me write.
Would you just try to be nice to her,
please? For me?
[Sara] Guys, keep an eye on
the creepy ginger by the door.
[Ray] Copy that.
And a possible fugitive alert.
Gideon, we can't find John
and he's not on comms.
Mr. Constantine has refused
to wear his communications device.
Stupid blighter.
However, Captain Lance requested
I fabricate a tracker
in every pair of his undershorts.
- Cheeky little minx.
- Okay.
Great, as soon as you trace him,
send us his location.
Tell me what happened to my Desmond.
A demon, Neron...
Des was collateral damage.
Just go ahead and curse me,
'cause I bloody deserve it.
Why would I curse the man
who could save the last of my line?
You don't understand, Des is gone.
No amount of magic
can bring him back.
[gasps]
Save my kin.
Let him go!
Nice rescue, loves,
but Priestess Laveau and I
were just having a little chat,
weren't we?
Now, to our business.
Have you sensed any other magic
in your city
besides my own and theirs?
I've sensed a spirit. A Dybbuk.
And like you, from another time.
What's a Dybbuk?
It's a dislocated soul
of a dead person.
Someone so wicked that their spirit
never crossed over.
[Ray] Sara,
I don't think he's a fugitive.
I think this guy's
just looking for the bathroom.
[girl sobbing]
What's going on?
This doll... [sobbing]
He's going to kill my mama.
[Ray] This doll?
Sara, is it possible that
our fugitive killer
is a possessed doll?
Horror movie 101.
Hello, dolly.
[girl screaming]
Wrong doll, you dick!
Well, we best be going then.
If we don't catch this Dybbuk,
then the good people of New Orleans
will blame you for its mayhem.
I believe
this belongs to you,
Monsieur Constantine.
Guys, this fugitive we're looking for
is an evil spirit.
Crap. Damn it, Ray,
where the hell are you?
Ray.
[girl sobbing]
What happened?
[sobs]
Sara, any sign of the fugitive?
I think we may have
a Chucky situation here.
What does that mean?
I reckon the Dybbuk is in a doll.
Rory, Ava, Sara needs backup.
A word.
I'm all ears.
You still want your powers back?
Come on then.
All right. Come on, big guy.
Sara, I had the weirdest dream.
I was attacked by a... Doll!
I'm gonna kill you, Goldilocks.
[both grunting]
[laughs]
[screaming]
You're late.
[groaning]
It's still moving.
Kill it!
No, no, no. We need to question it.
Find out if it's
really Mike the Spike.
Who are you?
Your worst nightmare.
[laughs weakly]
[growling]
Aloha, I brought you some meat.
[sighs]
[growling]
[sniffing]
Oh, my cut. Um, I stupidly ran my bike
straight into this guy's car door.
No. No, he didn't look
before he opened the car door.
[growling]
I know. I know.
I shouldn't have to pay,
but I don't want to lose
the world's best job.
You're a really good listener,
you know that?
[Mona chuckles]
[growling]
What happened?
Did someone hurt you?
So how does helping you
make me a shapeshifter again?
Well, it's simple, really.
If I never meet Desmond,
then this demon scum that's after me
doesn't hurt him,
which means my guilt-ridden ass
never joins the Legends
and doesn't turn up to London
to give you a magical lobotomy.
Simple.
The me from five months ago
is having a drink in there,
and I'll recognize you as Amaya.
All you have to do is play the part.
American accent, stick up my bum
and in love with Nate.
Do me a favor, just make sure
I get out of there before I meet Des.
All right. I'll meet you back
at the Jumpship, John-O.
All right, Charlie-O.
Good luck.
- John? As I live and breathe.
- Amaya.
- Nice barnet, love.
- Thanks.
Last I heard, you were in Zambesi.
Where's Nate and the rest of the crew?
Nate, my boyfriend, and my crazy gang
of best friends.
- Oh, it is such a long story.
- Right
But a really good one.
How about I tell you all about it
- over a glass of Chardonnay?
- Chardonnay.
- Barkeep...
- No, no, not here.
I know a better place.
All right, well, you owe me dinner.
- That is a fair price.
- All right, got it.
Order up!
[door opens]
Hey, Mona!
How's life like in the Time Bureau?
Settling in? Dating anyone?
Good. Great. Yes, I mean,
there is someone.
Lay it on Nate.
I think it might be inappropriate
'cause I work here.
And he's here, too.
Wow!
Exactly.
I think I know who you're talking
about and trust me,
he has a crush on you, too.
- He does?
- Mm-hmm.
I swear, I was just imagining it.
We don't even, like, speak
the same language.
Well, he does have a unique way
of expressing himself.
I'm afraid people would think
it was weird. I mean, that hair...
Maybe he just needs
the right product.
What about the man meat?
Um, what about it?
I think he's, you know,
had some.
It wouldn't surprise me. I mean,
it's 2018. I don't judge.
I should probably forget about it.
No. Carpe datum.
- What have you got to lose?
- My job.
I will make sure you're not fired
for following your heart.
Okay. I'll do it.
I'm gonna let him know
how I feel. [laughs]
[Sara] One thing I learned
from the Chucky movies
is the doll always comes back.
Gideon, how's the timeline?
History is on track and Marie Laveau
lived a long and celebrated life,
inspiring an Emmy-nominated portrayal
by Angela Bassett.
See, Rory killed the Dybbuk.
Which is unfortunate because
now I have to explain to Mr. Heywood
why I'm bringing him a seared doll
instead of a magical creature.
Well, at least we get to find out
why they call it the Big Easy.
Did you happen to notice
that Rory robbed that party blind?
- I believe it.
- I don't understand
why you enable his bad behavior.
At the Bureau, we would fire
people for lesser offenses.
At the Bureau, you don't have to eat,
drink and sleep with your team.
Point taken. It's just that this is
supposed to be a professional
- operation, babe.
- Look, deep down, Rory's a good guy.
- And honestly, a friend.
- I get it.
- You run your team, I'll run mine.
- Thank you.
Speaking of, I should get back
to the Bureau.
How about you stay for dinner?
I could use a shower.
[scoffs softly]
It's not like that thing's
going anywhere.
[grunts]
So, when are these changes to history
going to set in?
'Cause now I've got some big plans.
I'm actually thinking of Vegas first.
Time takes a moment to cement,
or so I'm told enough by Sara.
But, don't worry, love, we'll have
you shapeshifting again in no time.
John-O, you all good?
We stopped me from meeting Des
tonight, but now, I meet him
a few days later instead.
We have to go back.
[Gideon] I'm afraid
returning to New Orleans
is impossible, Mr. Constantine.
And why is that?
Because I know
you two are up to something.
And as much as I hate babysitting,
I hate being played even more.
Gideon, bring them back
to the Waverider.
They have some serious explaining
to do.
[sighs]
There's one thing
you need to understand,
is that I don't go in for all
that love crap.
Romance is for little girls,
crying into their pillows,
not for a devious tosser like me
who knows the score.
Then six months ago, I met him.
Desmond.
Our first night was like
a second liner marched
into my useless heart and breathed
some life into it again.
Desmond knew who I was,
exactly what I had done,
and he didn't care. So I was all-in,
rented an apartment.
And then, this demon shows up.
Neron.
Wanted me to help him usurp
the triumvirate ruling hell.
Well, he must have had something
on you to expect that.
The deed to my soul.
When I die, the bastard owns me.
And he's already worked out lots
of excruciating torments
for yours truly in the inferno.
So, naturally,
I told Neron to piss off.
Naturally.
I begged Des to run.
I knew that Neron would use him
against me.
Johnny!
[screaming]
The bloody fool didn't listen.
Till Neron dragged Des to hell
because of me.
I didn't think there was a way
I could save him.
That's the thing about
time travel, right?
There's always a way.
[scoffs]
I joined the Legends thinking I could
outrun my guilt,
but being back in New Orleans,
I realized,
I was just taking
the coward's way out.
So I had to save him.
So now that you know
what we were up to,
do you mind explaining
why it didn't work?
[Zari] Some points in history are fixed.
Maybe John and Desmond
were supposed to meet.
Look, I'm sorry,
I'm going to do everything I can
to find a loophole to save Desmond
and keep history intact.
You do that, love.
[growling]
[door beeps]
I know, an unscheduled visit.
It's good to see you, too.
- [growling]
- [Mona clears her throat]
I brought you something.
O... [chuckles]
[shushes]
[speaking in Hawaiian]
O-Mona
ko'u inoa.
Mo-na.
O wai kou inoa.
- Konane.
"Shining like the Moon."
That's a really pretty name.
Mona.
- Yup. That's me.
- [chuckles]
[sniffing]
[exclaiming in Hawaiian]
"Run and hide"?
- Is someone coming?
- [sniffing]
- [growling]
- [gasps]
Mona.
[alarm beeping]
[roars]
[device beeping]
[heavy metal music playing
on headphones]
Hello, is someone there?
[sighs]
[humming]
[spirit laughing evilly]
Compelling story back there.
Still, you're hardly the kind of guy
to open up,
unless, of course, you were stalling.
Well, you see,
magic has rules just like time travel
and I just so happen to write
the book on breaking them.
So if meeting Desmond
is a fixed point in time,
then I need to go back to
after I met him, stop him
from falling for me.
That's how I save Desmond's life.
History be bloody damned.
[scoffs]
[chuckles]
[exclaims] You went all out.
- The hell is he doing here?
- Leaving.
Wait, wait, both of you.
Please, look.
I roasted a roast.
[Gideon]
Technically, Captain, I fabricated...
Shut up, Gideon.
Ava.
You are my love.
And, Mick, you are my family.
And it would mean the world to me
if both of you would try
to get along.
Please.
So, I was thinking
maybe you two
could find some common ground.
- [laughs]
- For example, Ava, you love to read.
Mick, here, is an author.
Oh, that's something.
I would be shocked if his novel
wasn't sexist and derivative.
It is.
Okay. Well, Mick, you love to eat.
Ava is a fantastic baker,
she makes one mean snickerdoodle.
Fancy sugar cookies.
Snickerdoodles are actually
completely different.
It's a cream of tartar base, but...
Garbage cookies.
That's rich, coming from a man who's
so lacking in personal hygiene
that he had to resort to sleeping
with a three-breasted alien sex toy.
Well, at least, Garima isn't a clone.
Only I get to use the C word.
Too far, Mick, too far. [sighs]
Why do you get to have
a fake girlfriend and I don't?
- Clone.
- Dick.
Hey.
- Any luck?
- I'm sorry, John,
sometimes with history
if you change one thing
it creates a whole domino effect.
- It's all right.
- Listen, I...
I get being tempted
to save someone you love.
The anger and frustration, it's...
John?
Yeah?
- Turn around.
- I'd rather not. [clears throat]
[gasping]
That is the last time I try that.
I thought you couldn't...
You know what, it doesn't matter.
Where is John?
The last time we did something
like this, we almost destroyed
- the entire world.
- All right. Okay. Enough.
How are you planning to find John?
Well, his tracker...
Which you told him about.
Yeah. Ol' John-O's changing
history commando.
You know, I understand why John's
being so colossally stupid,
but what's your excuse?
I'm dying.
What?
Look, every time that I shapeshift,
it's like I'm born all over again.
But stuck in this body
for the first time in centuries,
I'm getting older.
But if John saves Desmond,
then he never joins the Legends.
And I'm immortal again.
Let me get this straight,
you helped John risk a catastrophic
rupture to history,
because you're afraid of aging?
Okay, maybe John succeeds and you
go on your immortal merry way,
but if he fails,
I will personally make sure
you spend the rest of your short,
dreary human life
in the deepest, darkest prison cell
the Bureau has to offer.
- [alarm beeping]
- [roaring]
[growling]
Let's move.
- [roars]
- [door beeps]
Look, I'm sorry, this is my fault,
I shouldn't have forced it
on you and Mick.
He was just stating a fact, you know,
I am a clone.
Oh, it's okay. [sniffles]
Sometimes I just wish I could
be more like you and the Legends.
You know? Loosen up.
When did that happen?
What?
Oh, no, I'll get a broom.
Ava, wait.
[Agent Sharpe]
Are those tiny little footprints?
The Dybbuk is alive.
[trimmer whirring]
[Ray exclaims]
Okay, we shouldn't split up.
Classic horror movie mistake.
Well, we're not exactly helpless.
Fine, I'll go fix Gideon.
And I'm gonna go catch
a serial killer.
You are way too excited about this.
[blues music playing]
[notification chiming]
What the hell?
[cell phone ringing]
[Zari] John.
How the bloody hell did you find me?
John, you have to stop this.
If Desmond isn't dragged to hell,
and you don't join the Legends,
the effects could be cataclysmic.
Neron didn't drag Des to hell.
I did.
- What do you mean?
- When I told Des to run,
he went behind my back,
made a deal to protect me.
In exchange for sparing my life,
Des had to bind his soul to Neron's.
I couldn't send Neron to hell
without sending Des down with him.
Johnny?
Johnny!
[screaming]
[panting]
I killed the man I loved,
and for what,
to buy New Orleans
a little more time.
Neron needs souls to take over hell,
and mark my words, he's coming back
to Earth to get them.
John, we can help you.
Yes, spare the team bit, all right?
I work alone.
- [Desmond] You back already?
- Yeah.
Des, I'm back already.
Hey, Johnny.
Hey, Des.
I'm gonna get some clothes on.
[exhales]
[Mick] It's dead.
The Dybbuk must have found
another vessel.
Is there another doll
on the ship somewhere, Rory?
What the hell was that?
Block the exit.
Okay, so whatever it is, it has tiny
little feet, so it's not that big.
[groans]
You dumb blonde,
it's not size that matters,
it's how you use it.
[exclaims]
[grunting]
Professor Stein!
No. It's Mikey, you dick!
[Mick] Here.
[both groaning]
- Thank you.
- Oh...
Where is he?
[laughs hollowly]
He really is Mike the Spike.
[growling]
[taser clicking]
Stop!
- Where are you taking him?
- You.
I am the Assistant Coordinator
of Creature Upkeep.
It's my job to take care
of magical beings.
[man] Not for long.
- Let him go!
- I'm warning you.
[roaring]
Konane, no!
[groans]
[man] No!
[man screaming]
You have to go.
They'll kill you.
[wheezing]
[grunts]
- You okay?
- Mike's up there.
- Mike the Spike?
- And he's found a new vessel.
- Much, much worse.
- Hold on.
[system powering on]
What could be worse than a creepy
antebellum doll?
[Mike laughing evilly]
Where are the eggs? I thought
you said you were gonna cook?
Yeah, I changed my mind.
I'll finish getting dressed,
then we can go out to eat.
You know,
it's not about the breakfast, Des.
Hmm.
Okay. I see what you're doing.
You know what
your problem is, Johnny?
You don't think
you deserve to be happy.
Des, your feelings for me
are a bloody lie, all right?
See, I just wanted to get you
into my bed.
But I couldn't be bothered
to put the work in
so I used a love spell on you.
Is this a joke?
Afraid not, mate.
Hey, I really care about you.
If there's something going on
in your life, just be honest with me.
Yeah, do you know what,
this thing between us,
it isn't real, it never was,
it doesn't exist.
[sighs]
I put myself out there like this,
and you're playing games?
You should go.
Yeah, you're right. I should.
But this...
This thing between us,
this was real, Johnny.
[door closes]
[sighs]
Sara, do you read me?
John's done something awful.
He hasn't done anything yet.
I'm still stuck in this form.
- [rumbling]
- Uh...
What's that?
[gasping]
[Mike laughing evilly]
Guys, guys, guys,
I have a real emergency here.
[laughs evilly]
Marty!
[groaning]
[laughs evilly] Die, you putz.
I hate puppets!
Suck my...
[Charlie] At last...
[sighs]
Oi, Z, check this out.
I got my powers back.
Don't be mad, I'm myself again.
Whoa! [laughs]
[meows]
Where's Zari?
Zari?
Oh, blimey!
[theme music playing]