How will we be remembered?
Will it be for saving
the world twice?
Nope. We're the team who broke time.
That's right.
History has been torn to shreds
which means it's up to us
to put it back together again
piece by piece
fixing these so-called Anachronisms
before we get torn to shreds.
So please, don't call us heroes.
We're Legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
I would kill you
but I'd just be killing myself.
I want to break up Firestorm
so that you can you go home.
When do we start?
Please allow me to introduce
Madame Eleanor.
We have to stop Damien Darhk
from coming back to life.
Stop this abomination.
You're too late.
- I remember everything.
- Let's go.
You. You there.
Yeah, you don't belong here.
You're supposed to be on Stage 12.
We're about to roll and Mr. Coleson's
already in a real mood.
We already have one actress
gumming the works.
I can't have extras
wandering off too.
We should've been rolling
half an hour ago.
Where the hell's my star?
- Ms. LaMarr is still in makeup.
- You got to be kidding me.
How long does it take a tomato
like that to put her face on?
She's playing Helen of Troy,
not Marie Antoinette.
Holy cannoli, who is that?
That's it.
That look right there.
Can you do that on cue?
Forget Hedy.
This is our star.
What's your name, sweetheart?
I'm Helen.
Helen of Troy.
You are now, toots.
"The face that sold
a million tickets."
All right, people, let's roll!
Oh, hey, Sara.
Sara, I've been searching
for more outliers
in the hopes of finding Darhk
and his witchy friend.
You think having a supercomputer
would helpful.
Watch yourself, Mr. Heywood.
Anyways, there's no sign
of them in the timeline.
What is that smell?
Okay, full disclosure, I haven't left
the library in seven days, I think.
Is it Tuesday? I'm not really sure.
It's hard for me to keep track
of time in a temporal zone.
Shower. Now.
Okay. I'll shower after I find Darhk.
I know how much it means
to you to find him.
Look, we're gonna put Darhk
back in the ground where he belongs,
but not like this.
- Not like what?
- Not like Rip.
He lost perspective
and he got his team killed.
I'm not going to be
that kind of captain.
But I am the kind of captain
that tells you to clean yourself up.
Okay?
Aye, aye.
Thanks to your research, Marty
the nanites I injected
into your bloodstreams
should be locking onto
your respective halves
of the Firestorm Matrix.
I'm only hoping that the polymer
I constructed is strong enough
to transfer your half
from you to him.
Well, a little too much "should"
and "hoping" for my comfort
but then...
What is science if not
the exploration of the unknown?
Ray, I'm telling you right now,
if you kill me
I'm gonna haunt you forever.
Well, just remember,
this was your idea.
If you guys are getting cold feet,
we can call the whole thing off.
Absolutely not.
We proceed with courage
and confidence.
It's time for Jefferson to claim
the power of Firestorm for himself.
I appreciate that, man.
But come on, admit it,
you're gonna miss this a little.
I mean, being a superhero,
saving time.
Not at all.
Were it not for this affliction
my adventuring days would be
long behind me by now.
Time travel is a young man's game.
I'm eager to close this chapter
and embrace the next.
Well, let's set this old man free.
Ray, let's do it.
All right.
Here goes.
Hey, what's... what's going on?
The system seems to be overheating.
- There's too much power.
- Shut... shut it down quickly.
Marty. Marty, you okay?
A little bruised,
Doctor Palmer but I'll live.
- Wait, what?
- Everything hurts.
Look at my hands.
They're white.
And mine appear to be
African-American.
You can just say "black," Grey.
- You're me and I'm you?
Oh, pancakes.
Attention, Legends.
Captain Lance requests
that all personnel
report to the bridge immediately.
I guess we know
where the explosion came from.
- What happened?
- Yes.
Pray tell, Dr. Palmer.
What exactly happened to us?
Because it seems we are in
a particularly precarious situation
that I, for one, have no idea
how to remedy.
Why don't we just merge?
Out of the question.
Absolutely not.
We have switched bodies.
Who knows what else
may have shifted?
Merging now could cause a meltdown
of insurmountable proportions.
We just... we just
can't afford the risk.
You're the Professor and you're Jax.
Switched.
Must be Tuesday.
What's going on?
Well, we seem to have a bit
of a "Freaky Friday" situation.
- I'm Jax.
- And I'm Martin.
Cool.
- So this is why we've been summoned?
- No, actually.
- Okay.
- Tell them.
1937, Hollywood, California.
A beautiful woman
mysteriously appeared
and threw the entire
film industry into chaos.
She apparently was so beautiful
that both Warner Brothers
and K and G Pictures went to war
over her and it got ugly, fast.
Literal backs were stabbed.
People died.
Those Hollywood idiots
probably had it coming.
Maybe but this wasn't
supposed to happen,
so we are going to fix it.
It will be a nice, easy mission
and we'll get our mojo back.
Awesome, maybe now I might actually
get to meet some celebrities.
And how would you even know?
The oldest movie you've ever
watched is some ridiculous farce
called Police Academy."
Don't knock the "Academy," Grey.
Doesn't matter because you two
are a liability like this
and you are staying on the ship.
- Wait, what?
- Oh, fantastic.
Gideon, plot a course for Tinseltown.
You're sad.
Paris has gone off to fight Menelaus.
He may die.
How could you live with yourself
if you lost him?
Cut!
That was aces!
Check the gate. Moving on.
All right, everybody.
You heard the man.
Got a movie to make.
- Let's go, people!
- I got eyes on her.
All right, remember,
We're doing recon only.
Nobody moves on her.
Let's see what we're dealing with.
What can you tell us?
She's really, really pretty.
She looks familiar,
like I've seen her somewhere.
I'm sure she's never heard
that one before.
The gossip I'm hearing is that
this woman is seriously method.
She hasn't broken character
since she got here.
I'm going in.
- Maybe I can talk to her.
- Negative. Recon only.
I don't want to spook her.
She's out of her time.
I am so sorry, miss.
- Are you all right?
- It's nothing. I'm fine.
Hey, watch what you're doing.
You almost took her head off.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, it's really nothing.
- Hey!
- Get lost, you twit.
- I asked the lady a question.
- She doesn't want to talk to you.
Oh, try stopping me, tough guy.
That escalated quickly.
What... what's going on?
There's only one woman in history
who has this effect on men.
She really is Helen of Troy.
- She's on the move.
- Follow her.
What's she doing now?
She's alone now. She looks upset.
What are we waiting for?
Let's grab her.
A kidnapping in broad daylight?
Even we shouldn't be so careless.
Jack, I mean Martin is right.
We have to wait.
What the hell is going on here?
Where's Helen? Well, find her! Now!
Z, you got incoming.
Studio boss is looking
for his new face.
Yeah, so is someone else.
My, oh, my.
Now, the rumors I've been hearing
could not do you justice.
You really are something special.
The name's Eddie.
- Eddie Rothberg, K and G Pictures.
- I'm Helen.
That's right, honey. Don't do it.
Someone taught you not to get
into cars with strangers, right?
Hop in.
Or not.
Rothberg. Helen! Wait! Stop!
Rothberg, you son of bitch!
I'll kill you myself,
you rat bastard!
Did that just happen?
"Paris stole Helen from Menelaus.
And the war began."
I thought the Helen of Troy story
was just a myth.
Well, we've found that myths tend
to have some truth about them
this one more than most.
Helen and her lover, Paris,
set off a ten-year war
that launched thousands of ships
and sent tens of thousands
of men off to their death
all in the name of her beauty.
You make it sound like
it's her fault.
Men always find a reason to fight.
That's not on her.
Depends. How hot is she?
I mean, she's all right.
She's really hot.
Seems kind of little league, right?
I mean, what's the big deal if this
chick gets to make a bunch of movies?
What's the big deal?
Helen is taking over the classics
like an infestation.
What's... what's "Casablanca"
without Ingrid Bergman?
The "Philadelphia Story"
without Katherine Hepburn?
It's... it's inconceivable.
And now this upstart steals
the career-making role of Hedy LaMarr
my boyhood crush.
- Sorry, I'm still adjusting.
- Look.
I've seen the chaos that she causes
with my own eyes.
We need to get Helen
out of the movie business
before anybody else gets hurt.
Gideon, where's Helen now?
I checked the tabloid archives
and it so happens
Edward Rothberg of K and G Pictures
is throwing a gala this afternoon
to show off his latest star.
Which would be the one
and only Helen of Troy.
Well, everybody go
put your best digs on
because we are going
to save Hollywood.
Yeah, until the Kardashians
destroy it.
Finally, a positive side effect
to our predicament.
I'm absolutely giddy at the notion
of attending a 1930s Hollywood gala.
Maybe I'll rub elbows
with Clark Gable
or dance with Ginger Rogers.
You have a little extra
fun for me, Grey.
I'm sitting this one out.
- Why? What's... what's wrong?
- I'm wasted, man.
My joints ache. I feel like
I'm walking under water
and I have to use the bathroom,
like, all the time.
I assure you,
the moment we get Helen
back to her proper time,
we will fix this.
Damn, I look good.
What's wrong? Are you all right?
Can we please go back in time
and murder whoever
invented stockings?
- Any sign of Helen?
- No.
But Ray's becoming friends
with Cecil B DeMille.
That is one remarkable mug,
young man.
And you've never been in a picture?
No, not that I recall.
Well, I'm shooting one next month.
Cary Grant backed out
but this profile of yours
might just have him outdone.
Stick with me and they'll be saying
"Cary who?"
Ray is ready for his close-up,
Mr. DeMille.
- There she is.
- You found Helen?
No. Hedy LaMarr.
The most beautiful woman
in the world.
Not only is she a talented actress
but she is a genius.
Brilliant and beautiful.
- I'd do her.
- Trust you, Mr. Rory,
to take something precious
and debase it.
She's also an inventor.
Her patent on frequency hopping alone
revolutionized the world.
Tuck in your shirt.
Ms. LaMarr.
I just wanted to say I am
one of your biggest admirers.
You are a remarkable actress.
How would you know?
I haven't acted
in any American films.
Now I probably never will.
I came here today
to take one last shot
at making my dreams come true
and meet Mr. DeMille.
But the closest
I'll get to Mr. DeMille
is transferring his calls
at Warner Brothers.
"Operator,
how may I direct your call?"
But surely someone with your talent
will find work as an actress.
Tough luck finding work
when she's in the room.
Who?
Any girl can look glamorous.
She just has to stand still
and look stupid.
Is everyone in position?
Yes.
Thank you.
- Sandwich?
- No.
Ray? Nate?
Rory?
Holy Helen of Troy.
Yeah. That spells hot.
Guys, snap out of it.
We got a job to do.
Hey, check out her security detail.
- The woman's a prisoner.
- Not for long.
We just need to get her alone.
Z?
- Oh, no.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Please excuse me.
- Of course.
Nice.
Ray, suit up and meet us
at the balcony for extraction.
Helen, you have to come with us.
You don't belong here
and you know it.
You must be from Warner Brothers.
Tell Arnold that I'm sorry,
but I left him for a better
opportunity.
Oh, you actually are a good actress.
Yeah, I hear they have a decent
theater scene in Troy.
We should go check it out.
No.
No, the Gods have answered
my prayers by bringing me here.
This place is strange
but I'm learning its rules.
And the first rule of Hollywood is
never discuss business
without your agent present.
I guess she's not just a pretty face.
Everybody get ready to move.
We got to go fast.
Helen, darling,
why don't you run along
and find Mr. Rothberg?
Gladly.
What the hell are you doing here?
Aside from collecting my 15 percent?
You're her agent.
You know that I have
the killer instinct
that this job requires.
I didn't come here to fight.
I came to talk.
And I didn't come alone.
If you don't take me up
on my offer for parlay,
things could get ugly for you
your team and Hollywood's elite.
All right.
Everybody stand down.
Darhk and I have some
catching up to do.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
Poison is a coward's weapon.
And our conflict is
at a brief standstill.
You're from Zambesi?
And your powers-here
do they come from?
I would have thought
you would have been able
to sense one of your own.
You're a totem bearer.
You wanted to talk, so talk.
You know for someone who died
you don't appreciate
the simple things in life.
Me? I'm a changed man
which is why I'm trying to do
this the civilized way.
- Do what?
- Convince you and your friends
to pack up and ship out.
You want Helen to stay.
What can I say?
Anachronisms are good for business.
- You wield the Water Totem.
- In a matter of speaking.
The totem is now part of me.
And you've perverted it.
Totem bearers must
protect the innocent
not use it for selfish gain.
You dare lecture me on selfishness?
You're the one who's turned
her back on her own people
in favor of these bungling idiots.
You know nothing about me.
You really do look lovely.
That color always suited you.
- So are you an actor?
- Yes
well, maybe. My name's Ray.
- And...
- Haircut!
It's time to leave.
Didn't you hear us on the comms?
No, my... my comms aren't working.
Just ignore them. They're being rude.
Let's get back to our private
conversation.
What are you doing?
Get your mitts off me!
Unhand the lady!
Are you all right?
I am now.
How convenient.
Here I was, thinking I was going
to have to convince you
what a mess your team makes of things
and that you'd all be better off
if you just went back
to your old lives
which brings me to my offer.
I will let you all walk...
Unharmed, if you all leave now
and go back to 2017.
Or what?
Or I will kill your merry
band of idiots one-by-one,
saving you for last.
And then you will die knowing
you could have saved them all
if you'd only made the right choice.
- What were you guys thinking?
- They weren't.
Like every man in the room,
they were just captivated by Helen.
Okay, in our defense,
she was very, very, very...
very attractive.
Yeah, I was just admiring
her personality.
So you jackasses decided
to impress her by having a fight?
- Mick started it.
- All right, enough finger pointing.
We need to focus
on the real issue here.
Damien Darhk.
Wait, Darhk was there
and you're still alive?
He didn't want to fight.
He wanted to talk.
And he made us an "offer."
We stop doing what we're doing.
No more Waverider.
No more fixing Anachronisms.
Wait, what does Darhk care
if we fix Anachronisms or not?
I don't know. We didn't have time
to get into his evil agenda.
Well, we've seen what Darhk can do.
Can we even fight him?
Yeah, especially now
that he's walking
with the time caddy
and the water witch.
She's not a witch.
Her name is Kuasa.
And she possesses one
of the lost totems of Zambesi.
Kuasa.
Darhk massacred
those Time Bureau agents
in Victorian London
without even batting an eyelid.
What if we can't take them?
This might be our best offer.
You don't offer a deal unless
you want something in return.
Besides, if he lets us walk,
he's just going to take us
out one by one.
That's right.
We're stronger together.
We know that. Darhk knows that.
All right.
Let's get Helen on the ship.
Nope.
After that party,
you three are grounded.
And I need you and the professor
to figure out why our comms
aren't working.
- You mean me and the professor?
- Whatever.
Amaya.
What's up?
I just wanted to wish you guys,
good luck out there.
Thank you.
Not too shabby. As far as prisons go.
It's the same security
detail from the party.
I guess Helen's still inside.
You really think they'll fall
for this stunt?
Have men gotten smarter
in the past few thousand years?
Nope.
Dude, this is impossible.
I can barely get my hands
inside this console
let alone handle the wiring.
How am I supposed to fix something
if my fingers don't work?
It's called arthritis.
And just so you know,
I don't enjoy being inside you
any more than you enjoy
being inside me.
What did I. Don't be so puerile.
Come on, Grey!
Don't pretend like you weren't having
the time of your life at that party.
I don't catch your meaning.
Telepathic link.
Let's just say I can tell
if you weren't married,
you and Ms. LaMarr
would be doing the nasty
in the past-y.
Nasty in the, I'll have you know
that Ms. LaMarr is my hall pass.
- Clarissa gave you a freebie?
- It was her idea.
Something to spice up our marriage.
She picked Jean-Claude Van Damme,
and thinking the whole
exercise ridiculous,
I chose Hedy LaMarr
never thinking I'd actually
get the chance.
Why, because she's dead?
She's not dead here, you dog.
No deliveries tonight.
Really?
Because I got Mr. Rothberg's
prized horse back there.
Nothing here about no horse.
Well, I don't know what to tell you.
Fine.
Just gonna need to check the back.
Oh, you mean his prize whores.
- Did he just call us...
- Yeah.
Please don't scream.
She said "please." You gonna behave?
Please don't take me away.
I'm sorry but this isn't your home,
Helen.
Do you have any idea what it's like
on the plains of Troy?
This land of Hollywood
is far from perfect
but at least men aren't killing
one another in my name.
Not yet anyway. We got incoming.
Rothberg! You think
you can poach my talent
you no good son of a bitch!
I dare you to come at me,
you dumb bastard!
Why does this always happen?
I truly am cursed.
Hey, this isn't your fault
but you can make it stop.
Come with us.
We can't let those idiots
kill each other.
Protect them.
I'll get Helen out of here.
Hey!
What do you think you're doing
with Rothberg's girl?
Just renegotiating her deal.
Great Zeus.
They're warriors.
Sorry, fellas.
Your new starlet decided
she's better off a free agent.
This vessel-t's remarkable.
Wait till you see her fly.
Gideon, show her what you can do.
Gideon?
What's going on?
Have you figured it out yet?
Socket wrench, Grey.
Does this look like a socket
wrench to you?
I specialize in subatomic particles,
not hand tools.
That's obvious.
Anyway, it doesn't matter.
Comms weren't the only
thing affected.
Half the ship's systems are down...
Crap.
Please tell me we're not
stuck in 1937.
Gideon and other
vital systems are offline.
How is that even possible?
Could be Damien Darhk.
What better way to catch us
than to shut down the Waverider?
It's like parts of the ship
are straight-up vanishing.
Of course they are, Jefferson,
because in this version of history,
those technologies no longer exist.
Wait, what are you talking about Jax?
I mean, Marty.
Can't you see?
This is all because of Hedy LaMarr.
As you know, Dr. Palmer,
technological advances
are cumulative.
They build over time
and it seems her patent...
Is the backbone for half
the Waverider's systems.
And without it,
we're essentially, well...
Screwed.
Where's Hedy now?
She said she was starting a new job
as an operator for Warner Brothers.
Shouldn't be hard to get her
re-signed with Mr. Coleson
now that his "It girl" is gone.
Where are you going?
To get Ms. LaMarr's career
back on track.
You better not just be calling in
your hall pass, Grey.
I don't want to overstep
but may I ask...
what Gods gave you such
incredible powers?
The Gods didn't give us powers.
Well, maybe they kind of
did for Amaya and me,
but the captain's a self-made woman.
Sara trains every day.
She's a total badass.
- She's a captain too?
- Yeah.
It gives me hope knowing
that you come from a time
where women have
the same opportunities as men.
Yeah, I wouldn't say that.
Anywhere must be better
than where I came from.
I spent the last five years alone,
locked up in a tower.
My only view was a distant
battle waging below
men killing each other.
For what?
Me?
And now you want to send me
back to that hellish place.
Warner Brothers,
how may I direct your call?
Warner Brothers, please hold.
How may I help you?
One moment, please.
Ms. LaMarr.
- What are you doing here?
- Mr. Coleson is in the commissary.
You have to talk to him
and get your contract back.
Why do you care so much?
Warner Brothers,
how may I direct your call?
There must be a better way
of switching signals.
There is.
You're meant for better things.
You have no idea the adventures
you'll miss out on
if you don't follow me out that door.
You're crazy.
Sometimes you have to be
if you want to burn bright.
Oh, no.
This is our lucky day.
Wait, you're that talent agent
from the party.
Ms. LaMarr...
Oh, I assure you
I am something far more ruthless
than a Hollywood agent..
If that's possible.
Okay, I didn't actually think
you'd take me up on my offer,
but after my warning,
I thought you people
would at least use the buddy system.
But here you are, all alone,
without your better half
to give you at least
a fighting chance.
You and your insufferable
pontificating...
Wait, wait, wait, excuse me.
Either someone got themselves
a thesaurus, or...
He isn't who he appears to be.
- He's the old one.
- No, no.
You guys switched bodies.
Oh, that is rich.
- You need a minute?
- No, I'm good. I'm good.
Let's kill them.
Grey's scared to death.
I can feel it.
Darhk must have found him.
- We're going in.
- I'm coming with you.
You sure you're up for this, Jax?
- Save Grey? Damn right I am.
- You may want to pee first.
We're not gonna stop to help
you find a bathroom.
Good point.
Me too.
Just don't make it a deuce, Mick.
Yeah, and if you do, flush.
What did he mean
about your other half?
Are you married?
Oh, you mean Jefferson.
Yes, I suppose in a way
we are married too.
- It's hard to explain.
- You're a homosexual.
No, I'm one half of a nuclear-powered
superhero
except the two of us
accidentally switched bodies.
They're here.
- I can feel them.
- Hide, hide.
What is going on?
The captain asked us to keep you safe
until the ship's fixed.
And the only way we can do
that is by saving Hedy LaMarr.
I don't understand any of this.
That's okay. Time travel is...
It's very, very confusing.
With the power out,
we're going to have
to lock the outside doors manually.
Right.
You're leaving me on my own?
Defenseless?
Here.
Now you're not defenseless.
It appears they have us boxed in.
On my signal, run.
What about you?
Look, just focus on getting
yourself to safety
and don't give up on your dream.
Oh, goodie.
The cavalry has arrived.
Oh, how I missed those
whimsical outfits of yours.
Your beef is with me, Damien.
So let's fight.
You and me, League style.
Two swords,
zero magic.
A duel. How quaint.
- Grey!
- But you do realize
I don't need magic to kill you.
Funny...
that's what Oliver Queen said
right before he killed you.
Foolish girl.
I extended my hand to you
in kindness.
Now you've left me no choice.
Let her go.
If it isn't the great protectress.
Whatever you're doing, don't.
Bring it.
What the...
- Grey, Grey, you all right?
- I'll live.
It seems your body's youthful
resilience has its advantages.
- Hedy, I told you to run.
- And I didn't listen.
You must be his other half.
You two need to use your powers.
We can't. It could cause
a catastrophic nuclear reaction.
Everybody could die.
I got this.
You have to become the Nuclear Man.
It's Firestorm, not Nuclear Man,
and we'd have to be crazy to attempt
a "Freaky Friday" merge.
Yes, but yours could be the case
of quantum entanglement,
which means the particles
in your body are mirrored
by those of your atomic companion,
which also means...
That if we merge, we could still
maintain a stable nuclear reaction.
Sometimes you have to be crazy
if you wish to burn bright.
What do you say, Jefferson?
Not bad.
You want those to be your last words?
We agreed no magic.
Oh, no, I agreed
that I wouldn't use my magic.
I couldn't make that same
promise for her.
That's the thing about daughters.
When they see you die at the hands
of one self-righteous hero
they really don't want
to see it happen again.
Your daughter?
The apple of my eye.
This is the famous White Canary?
Bye-bye, birdie.
That's what I'm talking about, Grey!
Come on, drive her back, Grey!
Jefferson,
I don't think I can do this.
In case you haven't noticed,
I'm an old man.
Yeah, true but you got this, Grey.
Come on, Grey! Let's get them, baby!
Nora, darling, I think it's time
we take our leave.
Please tell me Firestein's a thing.
- Oh, my God.
- What's wrong?
I have to pee.
And I do not.
You did it.
You're a genius.
Forming Firestorm has restored us
to our rightful bodies.
Guys!
Guys, we've got to get her
back to the ship.
You're a disgrace
to every totem bearer
who's come before you.
You have no right to wield its power.
I have every right
to this totem and yours.
This totem is my family's.
- Only my blood may bear it.
- And they do.
You gave it to your daughter,
and she was supposed
to give it to me.
But instead, it rests on
my little sister's throat.
That's impossible.
That I am your granddaughter?
What do you know of the future?
I told you I couldn't kill you
without killing myself.
But how?
Kuasa, wait.
I see great things for you,
Ms. LaMarr
and Warner Brothers.
It appears that went well.
Arnold wants me to star
in his next film.
The man was so desperate
after the Greek disaster
I was able to negotiate a pay
bump out of the whole thing.
- Brilliant and beautiful.
- Thank you.
I couldn't have done that
or survived without you.
Oh, it was nothing, really.
Just doing our job
setting history back on course.
- Can you guys hear me?
- Loud and clear.
And the ship's purring like a kitten.
Okay, time to go.
Yes. Yes, we... we must be off.
Well, good-bye.
I actually prefer older men.
Well, I'll be...
You old fox.
Come on, man.
Hey.
How's Sara?
Gideon has placed her in a coma
so that she can heal fully.
We'll be without a captain
for a few days but
thankfully she'll make it.
There's something I need to tell you.
It's something I shouldn't tell you
but it's something you should know.
That Kuasa is Mari's sister
and my granddaughter.
- How'd you know?
- She told me.
I never knew that she even existed.
I don't blame you
for not saying anything.
You were just protecting
the timeline.
I would have done the same thing.
Thank you for understanding.
I can tell you everything I know
but it... it is more complicated
than you think.
No.
We are the protectors of history,
not its editors.
So the less I know, the better.
There, killer.
Oh, my gods. I'm terribly sorry.
I got a bit carried away.
You're pretty good with that thing.
You should keep it.
But this belongs to your comrade.
Yeah, I think she'd be cool
with you having it.
Any of those Trojans get handsy
with you back home
you show them what's what.
Troy is hardly a home.
I don't want to return there.
How can you claim to be heroes,
claim to do good in the world
and yet force somebody back
into a horrible existence?
Okay.
According to the historical record
you disappeared halfway
through the war
but that didn't affect
the war itself.
So I found you a loophole.
Same time that you're from,
just a different place.
I hacked history.
This isn't Troy.
Nope, it's an island
full of warrior women.
It's cool, right?
Won't your comrades be mad at you?
Yeah, yeah, they would be.
But they knew what they were getting
when they brought me on.
Oh, thank you.
You've changed my destiny.
Best thing about this place
no boys allowed.
You'll finally have some
peace and quiet.