[man] Ladies and gentlemen,
we've reached our destination.
Welcome to New York City.
- Taxi!
- [horns honking]
[Gary] Legends, we made it!
[clicks, whooshes]
Legends.
- We made it.
- Thanks, we heard you the first time.
- And every other time.
- I appreciated all your updates.
Thanks.
Uh... Nate and Zari aren't coming?
What are they doing?
Did they say something?
Hoover-Bot's still stonewalling us,
so they're tinkering,
trying to figure out who sent him.
- Why are you so concerned?
- Oh.
I'm not concerned. I'm just, you know,
emotionally invested
in their love story.
[Behrad] I can't believe
we're finally in New York.
We're so close to getting a time machine
and going home.
Okay, first,
we've got to find Dr. Gwyn Davies.
So, let's get a city map, yeah?
Can we also please find some pizza
or something that's not John's whiskey?
Ooh, I saw an ice-cream stand
near the park.
[indistinct chattering]
Mmm. I miss classic New York pizza.
It's all squash blossoms
and cauliflower crust in 2044.
Yeah. Why couldn't
John's manor dimension
have had unlimited Pizza Shack?
Uh, manor dimension? 2044?
Pizza Shack?
Where are you kids from?
Oh, um, we're just tourists from...
Uh, Canada. Eh?
Sorry. How much do we owe ya?
[stutters] You're not Canadians.
[chuckles] The Canadians,
they're good people.
You're outlaws, and I'm gonna stop you!
- Uh-huh.
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshot]
- [Sara grunts]
[groaning]
[Agent Sharpe] Come here. Come here.
- [Agent Sharpe] Careful. Careful.
- [grunts]
[breathes heavily] Okay.
[indistinct conversation]
[Sara] Okay, I'm fine.
I got the map.
Let's just get to the manor.
[digital beeping]
Whatever you're doing back there,
you can't hurt me.
I'm impervious to pain.
Oh, I believe it.
Wow, you mastered that Hoover tech
real quick.
Yeah, well, the code
is the same as the Waverider's.
In fact, see this blue chip?
We have chips like this
all over the Waverider.
So we can confirm that the Waverider
who shot our Waverider
is making the Hoover-Bots,
but the question is still who and why.
Yeah, well, if this computer I stole
from John's attic wasn't so retro,
I would have an answer to that.
I was sent by the United States
government to uphold the law.
- Hmm.
- He still thinks he's the real Hoover?
Yeah, I even put up a mirror
to show him his tech.
He accused me of subversion.
You deserve a break. [clears throat]
[Zari] Donuts?
Where'd you get donuts?
John's attic.
Kidding. Gary stole them off the train.
Ah! Genius!
Oh, my God, Sara!
I'm fine. We got too casual,
forgot the Bullet Blondes
are still front page news.
Not gonna happen again.
Yes, you might be fine,
but I'm finding it
very hard to erase the image of my wife
being shot by a trigger-happy local.
Sounds more like a patriot to me.
Can we mute him?
I can't deal
with his negative energy right now.
Yeah, gladly. [grunts]
[Hoover-Bot]
Sounds like an American hero.
Sounds like some... [inaudible]
[Gary mumbles]
[whispering] So,
have you and Zari talked next steps?
[whispering] No, I don't know what to
say and I don't want to ruin the vibe.
[Gary] You're ruining the vibe
by not saying anything.
This is the last time
I sneak you train donuts.
The hell you will!
You're my donut dealer.
Hey, what are you two whispering about?
Oh, um, the mission, the Bullet Blondes
are still front page news.
We've got to find this Dr. Davies
as fast as we can.
[Sara] He's right.
And we located Edison Labs,
which is where Davies worked
when he came up
with the foundation for time travel.
Great. Just get us his research,
and we'll use our future knowledge
to build what he's come up with.
Then we can time travel out of 1925.
[Agent Sharpe] Wonderful.
While you regain your strength,
I'll go get Davies' research.
Actually, I'm going, you're staying.
What? No way. You just got shot.
Babe, our faces are literally
on the front of every single newspaper.
If someone recognizes us again
and decides to take a shot,
I'm the only one
who's gonna be able to survive that.
[sighs] Fine, but no footprints.
Davies is the father of time travel.
If you mess up his timeline, no amount
of IOUs in the world can fix it.
You got it.
[exhales]
[indistinct chattering]
- Which one's Davies?
- No clue.
Time Bureau manual
didn't have a picture of him.
[grunts]
But if I had to guess, I'd say that guy.
Looks familiar, kind of like Mick,
but with hair.
I'd say more of a young Stein.
But regardless, he's clutching
his briefcase to his chest
like it has something important in it.
- The basis of time travel?
- Mm-hmm. Wait here.
[clears throat] Excuse me, uh,
Dr. Gwyn Davies?
That's Dr. Gwyn Davies.
What is it you want?
I am a huge fan of your work,
and I would just love
to pick your brain over a cup of...
Yes, yes, yes,
I'm not here to socialize, young lady.
I'm here to make some very important
discoveries for Mr. Edison.
- Now, excuse me. Thank you.
- Of course.
- [exclaims]
- Oh! I am so sorry.
Oh, wait,
was that an accent that I detected?
- Good day to you.
- Oh, um...
Keep up the good work.
Did you get it?
Couldn't have been easier.
[theme music playing]
[Spooner]
We've been trying to hitchhike for days
and literally nobody has stopped.
We must get to Dr. Gwyn Davies
by 7:00 p.m. tomorrow,
or the Legends will die.
At our current pace,
we'll get to him in two weeks.
[speaking Spanish]
[vehicle approaching]
Spooner.
[speaking Spanish]
Why can't you
just bring us some good luck, man?
Who are you conversing with?
Is there someone up there?
Hello! I'm Gideon.
Fine. I didn't want to do this,
but you leave me no choice.
[chanting spell]
I just performed a luck spell.
Now, this rock will bring us good luck.
Wait, you can do that?
Obviously, I'm a witch.
Isn't luck just an interpretation
of random occurrences?
How can a spell generate that?
How can a spell generate anything?
- All I know is it works.
- [vehicle approaching]
Spooner...
It works!
[Behrad]
These blueprints are incredible.
It's like Da Vinci's helicopter sketch.
[Sara] Okay,
how long to build the Timeship?
Davies' instructions
are really thorough.
- I'd say four, no, five...
- Weeks?
- Months?
- Uh, years.
Five years?
You're asking us to build a time machine
from scratch in 1925.
[sighs] We're never gonna
get back to 2021.
Look... It's not impossible.
It's just gonna take a little while.
No, you're right.
[exhales] And at least we have
an unlimited supply of booze,
'cause I need to get liquored up.
I totally support that
after you ninja Davies' files
back into his apartment.
You want me to do this now?
Yes. Small footprints, babe.
We can't risk altering
time travel history.
It could jeopardize
our entire existence.
Okay, fine.
- And then I'm getting liquored up.
- Goodbye.
[object clattering]
[snoring]
Now go about your life
and we'll build
your time machine for you.
[chuckles]
[upbeat music playing]
Or you'll build it for us.
[sighs] You guys, his time machine
is literally sitting there,
just begging to be used.
Hold on, we can't use it yet.
According to Davies' notes,
we're still missing one part.
Who's game for a scavenger hunt?
Huh! I love scavenger hunts
because I love giving myself
to all things.
Games.
People.
Did you and Gary hook up?
I won't be mad. I will be confused.
Just checking.
Davies' notes also say
he got all his parts from Edison Labs.
I bet that's where
we find the missing one.
Scavenger hunt just got way easier.
Wait, wait.
I am also dying to get to 2021,
but no footprints, remember?
Babe, I respect your no footprints plan.
And, yes, we could wait five years
for the Tarazis
to build a time machine
that may or may not work. No offense.
- None taken.
- Slightly offended.
Or we could leave a tiny footprint
and get out of here way earlier.
It's not gonna be tiny.
Can you slow down?
We're just trying
to get all the information.
For instance, this is very interesting.
The manual says that Davies
laid the foundation for time travel.
If he built a time machine,
why doesn't it say
that he invented time travel?
Maybe he time travelled somewhere,
couldn't recharge and got stuck there.
Ah, that makes sense.
That's why he never got credit
because no one ever knew he succeeded.
But if we time travel to the future,
we can recharge it.
Plus, we'll pick up some Time Couriers,
and we'll get back,
and we'll return the machine,
and he'll be none the wiser.
Babe, we would have time travel again.
And I know it's a footprint,
but it's a tiny footprint.
It's like a baby footprint,
and everyone loves baby footprints.
[sighs]
The clutch is slipping.
I have no idea what that means,
but I assume it's bad.
- Can you fix it?
- No, there's no time.
And we won't be able
to get out of first gear.
So, the max we can go
is like 20 miles per hour.
How fast do we need to drive
to get to New York?
Well, to prevent the Legends
from blowing up in Davies' time machine
due to electrical overload,
we should maintain a conservative pace
of no less than 55 miles per hour.
Maybe we can, I don't know,
find a mechanic?
There's no need.
We've got our lucky rock, remember?
I'm still not convinced
there's any such thing as luck.
Only the ability
to cope with a statistical universe.
Ah!
You'll see. Watch.
Come on, rock, bring us some more luck.
Good afternoon, ladies.
Name's Erwin George Baker,
but you can call me Cannon Ball.
Cannon Ball?
As in the cross country race car driver?
You've heard of me!
I'm a big NASCAR... I mean, racing fan.
[chuckles]
Well, y'all wouldn't happen to know
the fastest route through Cleveland,
now would you?
I'm actually in the middle
of trying to break my own record,
driving from LA to New York.
Well, I think I made a wrong turn.
New York, did you say?
We're actually on our way there, too.
[Gideon] Well,
the fastest route to New York
is south on Highway 15
till it merges with Highway 40,
then cut through Columbus,
not Cleveland, on the 90.
[chuckling] Oh, dang!
You sure know your directions, miss.
I'll tell you what,
if y'all help me get to the highway,
I'll let you race with me
all the way to New York.
- Shotgun.
- All right!
Come on!
Ah, I love scavenger hunts.
Are we playing teams or head-to-head?
Neither. You're on your own
finding that part.
What are you gonna do?
Make sure that the doc
stays here all night.
We can't have him walking in on us
building his time machine, right?
- How are you gonna keep him here?
- Uh...
Hmm.
[Sara humming]
[Dr. Davies sighs]
[stutters] I told you, I am not here
to socialize, young lady. Thank you.
I beg your pardon?
What do you think you're doing?
You see, this is my desk.
It is not a rubbish tip.
Oh. You didn't hear?
They want your opinion on which
of these projects is best by tomorrow.
[chuckles] Yes.
Who wants it?
Not Edison?
Oh, this came straight
from Edison himself.
- [sighs]
- Oh. And these.
Tomorrow.
What do we have here?
I truly am the world's
greatest scavenger hunter.
[exclaims]
- I should be out there.
- Sara's gonna be fine.
She's a half-alien ninja
in a building full of scientists.
An illegal alien?
You degenerates
are worse than I thought.
Would you just shut up?
You're not even the real Hoover.
You are a robot.
If you'd just tell us who sent you
and who blew up our Waverider,
we could be rid of you.
You can't get rid of me.
I'll hunt you until my dying breath.
[shushes]
I still don't know who sent him,
or who blew up the Waverider,
but I did find a to-do list
in his programming.
- Tax convention at 3:00 p.m.?
- I'm missing that?
You'll pay for this.
Uh... There's an item
that supersedes everything else.
[keyboard clacking]
Oh.
Wait. So, if he's here to kill us,
but he's also here
to replace the old Hoover
and do everything
that the old Hoover did,
does that mean that the person
that wants us dead
is trying to protect the timeline?
Why would someone
who's trying to protect the timeline
want us dead?
Protecting the timeline
is literally our job.
[Agent Sharpe] I don't know,
but any noticeable footprints
and they'll know that it's us,
and they'll come back to finish the job.
Have you seen Dr. Parker?
Um...
No?
You must be new.
I'm Mr. Edison.
Edison? Thomas Edison?
- What's your name?
- Gary Green. [chuckles]
Dr. Gary Green.
Well, Dr. Green, at Edison Labs,
we log out parts
from the parts department.
- Oh.
- Let me show you.
- Who's your supervisor?
- Uh, Dr. Gwyn Davies.
- Davies?
- Mm-hmm.
What project is this for?
Oh, it's the time travel project,
of course.
[man] Front desk.
Have security meet me at Davies' office.
Yes, sir, right away.
[mumbles]
What Edison's asking me to do,
it will keep me here all night.
I suggest you get started, then.
[grunts]
[speaking gibberish]
- Uh, are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm fine. I'm fine.
[continues indistinctly]
- Hey, are you all right?
- Yeah, please, just don't touch me.
Confiscate everything!
No, no, no, no.
Not my work. No!
I've told you,
this time travel is a fool's errand.
But you've been
drafting blueprints at work
and stealing company parts.
Just let me complete it,
Mr. Edison, please.
I beg of you.
You're terminated, Davies.
These men will escort you
off the premises,
and I am personally burning this.
You couldn't possibly understand!
Time travel is my divine mission!
You can't take that away for me!
Take him to Bellevue.
It's apparent he's lost his damn mind.
I'm perfectly sane.
You get your hands off me!
You brutes! Get your hands off me!
- [breathes heavily]
- [door closes]
[engine revving]
[Astra] Put your hand down.
We received calls
from the last 10 towns over
about a speed demon headed this way.
License and registration.
Now, Officer,
allow me to introduce myself.
Name is Erwin George...
I don't care
if you're the pope of Pennsylvania.
License and registration.
We need to get back on the road.
We'll be fine. We've got our lucky rock.
You all need to step out of the vehicle.
I'm taking you in
and impounding your car.
[Astra] Uh, wait, wait.
[grunts] You're making a huge mistake.
Erwin's cross country races
are all over the newspapers.
In fact, he is in the process
of breaking the current record.
Article after article
is being written about it.
Now, you could arrest him
and be forever known as the cop
who arrested a legend.
Or you could let us go and be hailed
as the cop who gave Cannon Ball
a police escort to the county line.
You'll mention my name in the paper?
Absolutely.
Then let's get yous to that county line.
[Astra] Uh, yes!
[Erwin] That lucky rock
sure is something.
- And it is gonna help me beat my record.
- Whoo!
[whooping]
You thinking about Gary again?
Oddly enough, I am.
Please say more.
Actually, Gary and I had
a surprisingly enlightening conversation
prior to your arrival.
That is surprising.
What'd you talk about?
He made me realize
that I've been using your Totem
as an excuse not to take the next step.
[sighs]
I see, we're having that talk.
Hey, listen,
now we don't have to have it.
We've had a really good few days,
and I don't want to ruin it.
No, we... we're always great together.
It's being apart, that makes it... hard.
I know.
I know a way for us to be together,
and it's... this place.
Like here?
Like John's pocket manor dimension?
Uh-huh. Our problem
is that you and other Zari
can't co-exist
without Behrad's head exploding. Okay?
But in this dimension,
time and space doesn't exist.
We don't have to worry about that.
What do you think?
I think it's a great idea.
You seem stunned.
I am... Uh...
We can finally live together.
- Right?
- It's a win.
- Hmm.
Really? A fist bump? It's bigger than...
- Nah, I got jokes.
- You got jokes?
But on a serious note,
I got a surprise for you.
- Another one? [chuckles softly]
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
I saved you a bear claw.
- Who loves you?
- You. [chuckles softly]
[exhales]
I'm trained to read people.
That was a fine acting performance.
Shut up, Hoover. I wasn't acting.
There you go again.
You might get your lies past him,
but not me.
Uh, what day is today?
It's November 7th. Why?
He was planning to use it tonight.
[Sara] No wonder he was so upset.
Okay, but this is fine,
because if we use
the time machine tonight instead,
then history will stay on track.
[Behrad] Co-captains.
Necrian.
I present the world's
very first time machine.
[machine starts]
[exhales]
Wait, Sara, that means...
No!
Where is she?
No, no, no, no!
Wait, they disappeared
when I put this in,
so if I take it out...
[machine stops]
- Why aren't they back?
- Because we caused too many footprints.
God, this is all my fault.
- Okay.
- [sighs]
- Why are we still here?
- I don't know.
But, look, if Ava and...
If they're gone,
then that means
that the Time Bureau never existed.
That means that...
Which means that I never meet Ava.
We need to fix this.
We need to cover all of our footsteps
and make sure that history happens
exactly how it's supposed to.
Stay here and uninstall that last part.
We're not gonna use the time machine?
No, we will,
but we need Davies to install it
and take his maiden voyage
like history intended.
Wait, you're gonna break him
out of a mental institution?
Yeah, I guess so.
Oh, wait, Edison took all of his files.
It's all good, we made a copy.
No, no, no. It's not all good.
It was the originals
that were passed on from history
and it's the originals that inspired
the invention of time travel.
We have to get those back from Edison.
Okay. It's a lot to do,
but it's not impossible.
We have until 7:00 p.m.
- That's a little more impossible.
- [sighs]
Then it's time for all hands on deck,
human and robot.
Hey, you guys muted him.
Can you get him to do or say things?
He has a to-do list.
In theory, I could replace what's on it.
Replace it. We need him
to get Davies' plans from Edison,
and Edison's gonna be more likely
to give the plans to Hoover
than he would to us.
Okay, uh, goodbye
"eliminate the Legends,"
bye-bye "tax convention"...
Don't you dare! I will ruin...
You know, I don't know
why I keep unmuting you.
All right, I'm gonna grab some clothes,
so we can accompany Hoover.
It's shocking how much stuff
John has in that attic.
Hey.
You think he has a lab coat?
[indistinct chatter]
[indistinct laughter]
[indistinct shouting]
[mumbling]
No, no, no,
what the devil are you doing in here?
Getting you out of here.
The fan girl stuff was just an act.
I'm actually a time traveler.
[chuckles] A time traveler?
Is this some kind of sick joke?
Edison put you up to it, didn't he?
The blasphemer!
This isn't a joke, all right?
I'm from 2021.
And I know that
you invented time travel,
and your maiden voyage
is tonight at 7:00,
so I'll get you back to your apartment
so we can use your time machine.
Let's go.
Do you honestly expect me to believe
a word that's coming out of your mouth?
You lied to me.
This is all just more lies.
Come on, you'll see when you get there.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
- No, listen, you don't understand...
- I don't think you understand.
I built my time machine
for a sacred purpose,
and I'll be damned
if I'm letting a two-bit liar use it.
We do not have time for this, all right?
If you don't come with me,
then history...
[stutters] What are you not getting?
You see,
I am not going anywhere with you.
As a matter of fact...
Guards! Help! Intruder!
- Hey!
- [gasps]
[shushes]
Be quiet.
- [shushes]
- Okay.
Now, I will let you go
if you stop screaming.
Do you understand?
I promise.
[gasping, breathing heavily]
Okay, all right, hey, hey.
It's all right, hey, look. Calm down.
You're having a panic attack, okay?
You just need to
focus on your breathing.
Okay.
Okay. [breathing heavily]
Okay, look, hey. Hey.
I'm sorry, okay?
I've been treating you like a pawn
instead of a person,
and it's not fair.
You are a really big deal, all right?
Hey, you invented freaking time travel
and it's because of you
that so many things become possible,
including me meeting my wife.
You married a woman?
Yeah. [chuckles]
Still getting used to saying that.
We just got married.
Look...
I messed up
and she disappeared from the timeline.
And so, now,
I have a sacred purpose, too,
to bring her back.
And the only way that that could happen
is if you come with me,
or otherwise, she could be gone forever.
So please believe me when I say
that I am done lying to you.
I can understand doing anything
to save the person you love.
It's actually why I was trying
to invent time travel.
[clears throat]
So let's do it.
What do you say?
Help me save my person?
If I help you save your person,
you help me save mine.
[sighs] You're only gonna come with me
if I say yes, right?
Mm-hmm. We have a deal then.
Let's get the hell out of here.
- Yes, indeed.
- And wash our hands.
I don't know, Zari.
He's still giving me Terminator vibes.
I hear that, but he's on our side now.
I reprogrammed him to get
Edison's plans, among other tweaks.
Yikes.
Any way to make that less toothy?
Watch this.
After you.
Oh!
I don't understand why
you'd be interested in
Dr. Davies' plans, Mr. Hoover.
Believe me,
they're just the ravings of a madman.
I was just about to destroy them.
Thank you very much, Mr. Edison.
I'm sure you're probably right.
Yeah.
I'm just a little confused, Mr. Hoover.
Why would someone of your stature...
bother to come here?
Unless you have something
more important on your agenda nearby.
I came here for a...
- [Nate clears throat]
- Sir? Sir?
[stutters]
Tax convention at 3:00 p.m.
Mr. Hoover, are you okay?
Yeah. Sir, he's fine.
You know,
he suffers from low blood sugar.
I'm here for a tax Convention.
I'm here to retrieve the plans.
I'm here to r... retrieve the plans.
I'm here for a Tax Convention.
I'm here to retrieve the plans.
[machinery beeping]
[crackling]
Um... [clears throat]
I can explain everything, Mr. Edison.
Great Scott!
- [gasps]
- Oh!
Mr. Edison!
Oh, God!
He's dead.
Oh, my God.
[doctor]
It's imperative that we find him!
[continues indistinctly]
There.
[upbeat music playing]
[Dr. Davies grunts]
- Come on.
- I am a scientist, not an athlete!
We'll just take as much Hoover-Bot tech
as we can.
I can still use it to try to figure out
who sent him here.
Why do you think the Hoover-Bot
short circuited?
He was being pulled
in two different directions
that he couldn't reconcile...
Like our relationship.
Nate, I know I'm not super great
at expressing my feelings,
but I have to tell you something.
You're getting cold feet
about living together.
No. What? No, no, no, no.
Dude, that's literally all I want.
But in the Totem,
not the manor.
No one is more surprised about this
than me.
I found a real community there.
I feel like I'm part of a family.
Somehow, over the last two years...
It feels like home.
[exhales] Okay. Um... [clears throat]
Can I get a little bit of time to digest
what it would be like
living out of a Totem?
Yeah. Completely.
[stutters] This reality
we're navigating, it is insane.
- It's insane.
- Yeah.
- Just take much time as you need.
- Okay.
And, well, there's no rush
on your decision.
We should probably get out of here.
- Yeah.
- Right. [clears throat]
Okay.
[thuds]
Too late.
[both panting]
No, no, no.
We're trapped. We're trapped.
Okay, you're supposed
to be a genius, right?
You can think of a way out of here.
Genius? They think I'm a lunatic...
They think I'm a lunatic.
[doctor] He went this way!
- [yelps] Oh, my God!
- Get back.
I'm as mad as a hatter. I shall cut her.
- Back. Get back.
- Please listen to him. He's crazy.
I swear with all my might, I'll do it!
He's gonna do it!
- [indistinct]
- Get back, I'll do it.
- I will! I will!
- [Sara speaking indistinctly]
- Stay! Stay! Stay!
- He'll do it!
We must clean up my body.
First, we must remove my human body.
I've got to answer the call of nature.
[Gideon groans]
Hey, nice car, mister.
[chuckles]
[grunts]
[bell rings]
You know, we might make it in time,
get to the city
with time for a bite to eat.
- Ah, thanks to our lucky rock.
- [chuckles]
- Oh. I must have left it inside the car.
- [bell rings]
- Whoa, whoa, whoa...
- [engine starts]
[both] Hey!
- Get him.
- No! No! No!
Godspeed, ladies.
Still got time to beat my record.
[bell rings]
Great, we lost our ride, our lucky rock,
and now, Gideon.
Unless you can swim faster
than a blue marlin,
we're gonna lose
the rest of our friends, too.
[machinery beeping]
[sighs] Ooh. There are a lot more of you
than I thought there would be.
This is only half the crew.
Wait till you meet the rest.
Hey, everybody! I'd like to
introduce you to Dr. Gwyn Davies.
Nice to make your acquaintance.
Ah, there she is.
Ah, yes.
My divine mission
is finally coming to fruitions.
Hey, man, I'm Behrad.
- [clears throat]
- Sorry.
I just feel like I know you.
I mean, I've been studying
your life's work,
and chilling in your apartment,
and using your glassware.
I borrowed a glass, by the way.
Hope that's cool.
Uh, hey, is that...
- Oh, yeah.
- [mouths]
Also, uh, Edison's dead.
- What?
- So, there's another Hoover-Bot,
and now Edison-Bot deployed,
but headline,
there's a rogue Waverider after us.
But we did get the plans.
Oh, my files. Thank you so much.
You know, you really do look familiar.
Oh, maybe I just have
one of those faces.
Ray, he looks like Ray.
- My Ray?
- I said a young Stein, but whatever.
We got the plans, we got the doc. B!
[Dr. Davies clears throat]
You got to assemble last part
to get the timeline back on track.
Yes, the final piece of the puzzle.
You ready?
[exhales] Come on, come on.
[machine starts]
- Ava.
- What?
- Oh!
- What happened? Did I disappear?
It worked.
I am so sorry.
I never should have rushed.
I should have listened to you.
No, no, no, it's okay.
What matters
is that we're back together again.
Oh, oh, oh, oh. No, no. No.
This is not a group hug situation?
Right, well, it should be
a bit of a squeeze,
but I'm sure we all can fit.
[sighs] All right.
What do you say, guys?
Ready to go home?
Here, do another luck spell.
Maybe we can still make it.
I can't.
The spell was fake.
Come again?
There is no luck spell. I made it up.
I pretended to do it
to make you feel better
and give you back some hope.
You were at a pretty low point.
Okay, then, how do you explain
where the luck came from?
It came from... us.
Hey, no, think about it.
You felt better
after I did the spell, right?
Gideon convinced Erwin
to give us a ride.
I sweet-talked the cop
into letting us go.
We made our own luck.
And we can keep making it,
but we have to do it fast
because we only have five minutes
to stop them.
Or do we stop everything?
- Let's go.
- [mumbles]
[intense music playing]
- Oh, hello?
- [screams]
- Who the heck are you?
- I'm Gideon.
[scoffs] Well, Gideon,
you got to the count of three
to get out of my new car
or I'm gonna make you.
One, two...
[thuds]
By my calculations, there's still
enough time to save my friends.
With luck.
[engine revs]
Right then, where to?
We need to go somewhere
we can get back to our time machine
and find the rest of our crew.
Tahiti, 2021.
There's a Time Bureau safe house there.
We can go pick up some Time Couriers.
And sounds like a great honeymoon, hmm?
Tahiti would be an amazing honeymoon.
I'm so sorry to interrupt you ladies,
[clears throat] but after you have got
the rest of your friends,
you will hold up your end of the deal,
won't you?
- I always keep my word.
- [Agent Sharpe] Deal?
What do you... What?
You know what? Nope. I don't even care.
It's been a crazy day. I disappeared.
I don't want to know anything.
Don't tell me anything.
Um, you should know one thing.
Um, we also killed Edison.
You what?
Come on, lucky rock.
[Spooner] If you do a lightning spell
to zap this tower,
with as much juice as you can,
it should overwhelm the grid and cause
a citywide blackout, therefore...
Preventing the Legends
from ever turning on that time machine.
I am the master of my fate.
I am the captain of my soul.
[machine starts]
[crackling]
[chanting spell]
- [rumbling]
- [Astra grunting]
[crackling]
[electricity buzzing]
[grunting]
Let's do this.
No!
Astra, I got ya!
[breathing heavily]
[Spooner] Hurry up, move it,
we're almost there!
Go, go, go!
Did we make it?
...and that's how I arrived here.
Oh! Hello, Astra. Hello, Spooner.
[all cheering]
Aw!
[all exclaiming]
How many
bloody time travelers are there?
[indistinct chatter]
Then Astra did a lightning spell.
Yeah, here we are.
Well, how'd you know
the blackout was gonna work?
I guess we got lucky.
[indistinct chatter]
Thought you could use a drink.
Heard you had quite the journey.
Thank you. Mmm.
Save some for me.
Just kidding, I don't drink.
We also have an infinite amount.
[chuckles]
I had my foot on the gas that whole time
and we almost blew up.
And now because we didn't,
the timeline might be off.
Oh, my God.
Hey, what if you fritz out again?
Babe, it's okay. I'm here now.
Seeing you vanish like that, it was...
It's like I saw my entire future
just disappear.
Our whole lives together,
and it's just gone.
And it wasn't the time travel
or the hijinks.
It was like I lost my safe place.
And I lost the cuddles on the couch
and bourbon sunsets on our porch.
- You know we don't have a porch.
- It's okay.
I love bourbon sunsets
on our non-existent porch.
- I love you.
- Love you.
- Hey, power's back on.
- [sighs]
So, Gideon, what was gonna cause
the machine to explode?
The machine requires
a class CR-055 superconductor
that doesn't need recharging.
It can power the machine safely
unlike alternating current.
Unfortunately, it won't be invented
for another 300 years.
Three hundred years?
Well, guys, looks like we're stuck
in 1925 forever.
Oh.
I was supposed to die today,
but by God's will, I didn't.
There has to be another way.
Did... Did you say, CR-055?
A little blue chip
the size of an eyeball?
Precisely. How did you know?
That chip was in Hoover-Bot's head.
[mumbling]
Ah.
Bahoom.
- [grunts]
- Do you have enough room?
Plenty. I'm used to really tight spaces.
Me, too.
[machine whirring]
[thuds]
The other Waverider, it's here.
- All right, punch it.
- Okay.
Tahiti 2021, here we come.
[crackling]
[upbeat music playing]
[Sara] Uh, guys...
I don't think this is Tahiti.
[theme music playing]