Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
It's a dragon egg.
You're possessed.
Ray's gone. I've taken over his body.
If Neron wanted John dead,
he would have killed him on the spot.
I need you to open up
a doorway to hell.
It's to bring someone here
from the other side.
- Tabitha.
- I'm sorry. It wasn't me.
It was my nipple.
Save me.
As you wish.
I'm not leaving Mona behind.
Do you really think that everyone
in hell deserves to be there?
This is your opportunity
to make things right.
I'm going to save Ray.
Honey, time to go.
Come on, honey, let's go.
We're going to be late.
Zari? You better not be
eating the Halva.
No, Mommy.
Zari Jaan.
Dessert's not for after breakfast.
What?
It's only a kick.
Behrad must be anxious to meet you.
Now go put your shoes on,
so I can take you to school.
You might
just want to soak it all in.
Violent people
are pouring into our country,
illegal immigrants, terrorists,
meta-humans.
Politicians promise to keep you safe,
but they've been hiding the truth.
There's a dangerous new threat
already within our borders.
Hi, I'm Ray Palmer.
Yes, that Ray Palmer,
former CEO of PalmerTech.
And I am here to warn you
that creatures once thought only
in legends and fairy tales are real.
Yes, folks, monsters are real
and they walk amongst us.
And they will stop at nothing
until they destroy humankind.
Interested in learning more?
Then join me at PalmerX 2019,
where the power is in the Palmer
of your hands.
I don't care if Neron's
wearing my best friend's face.
- I want to punch him.
- Get in line.
Ogres are big softies
that one wouldn't even hurt a fly.
Neron's been a step ahead of us
for too long.
We need to play offense.
- Agreed.
- Sorry, what are we agreeing to?
Look, it's time for us to fight back.
We're retaking the Bureau.
Gideon, pull up the blueprints
at the Bureau
and start fabricating an arsenal.
Right away, Captain.
Look, Gary has bonded
with the Fairy Godmother
and while he might be an idiot,
she is not to be underestimated.
Mick, Nate,
you think you can handle Tabitha?
Granny's dead.
Good. Ava and I will handle Neron.
Yeah, I want a crack at him.
It's my bureau
he's running his operation from.
Not to be a buzzkill,
but even John and Nora
couldn't out-magic Neron.
I just felt a kick.
Oh, I want to feel.
Right now the smart play
would be just to bide our time.
Wait for John-o to return
with Ray's soul.
Shockingly, I agree with Charlie.
- I love you, little Wicksty...
- Oh, I felt it.
- I told you, it's kicking.
- Okay, can you guys stop
being dragon baby crazy right now?
Look, this commercial is proof
that Neron is up to something big
and we need to stop him
before it's too late.
Captain, I have an incoming
communication from Nora Darhk.
- Put her on.
- Sara?
Talk to me. What's your status?
I'm tired of skulking around
air ducts.
I'm going after Mona.
We're gearing up for an assault.
- Hold your position.
- Hey.
- Too late.
- Wait, where's Gary?
In Ava's office
getting real comfortable.
Oh, Fairy Godmother?
Yes, my pet?
I want to dig deeper on my next wish.
Excellent idea.
What do you have in mind?
Well...
we've already redecorated my office.
I now have three nipples
because a spare never hurts and...
Perhaps you could make a wish
regarding the Legends?
You want me to wish something
for them?
I'm talking about revenge.
They lied to you, Gary.
Promised
you could be an interim Legend.
One wish and you can send them all
to hell with John Constantine.
Speaking of John,
you think he's all right?
That warlock sent thousands
of demons to rot in the pits.
I think he's well
and truly screwed, dearie.
Does this mean we're straight?
I got a more important collection
to make.
Who is that guy?
That, my friend,
is John Constantine...
in the flesh.
Congratulations, Mona.
I have selected you
for a very special assignment.
That's okay, Ne-Ray.
Can I call you that?
I'm okay here.
You see, before Nate's father decided
he wanted to be P.T. Barnum,
we were working together,
training monsters to do our bidding.
Actually, I worked extensively
with your dear friend Konane...
I mean...
Your dead friend Konane.
I found Mona.
Hurry.
Copy that.
This seems like overkill.
The Legends never included me
in their pizza parties...
or asked me to play
Dungeons and Dragons.
Make them suffer, Gary.
I can make them do whatever you want.
I just wanted to be part of the team.
As soon as Ava opens the portal,
we go in firing.
Time to burn some freaks.
I wish...
Opening a portal in three, two, one.
No.
Welcome to book club.
Why, you little...
I'd be careful
how you speak to my charge.
Gary, why are you doing this?
Because I would like to discuss...
"The Collector."
Forget the book, Gary.
You helped a demon
take control of the Bureau.
What happened to the Bureau creed?
Oh, I could ask the same about you.
Article 27?
A supervisor
must never show favoritism?
You started a book club
with another employee.
Gary, Mona is being tortured
right now.
Neron said he's trying
to protect humans from monsters.
You saw Mona gnaw off my nip.
She did you a favor.
Okay.
Maybe we should just reschedule
until after we've read the book?
Oh, Fairy Godmother?
Oh, no.
Wait.
Book was terrible.
Oh, my head.
That's the spirit.
Sara, Ava, come in.
Where are you guys?
Hey, Nate. Can't talk right now.
Are you talking to Nate on comms?
Tell him I say hi.
Gary says hi.
And we are at book club.
Move on to plan B.
What's plan B?
I only listen for my name.
I assume it's like plan A,
but, you know, with less people.
Well, without the Captain
and the clone,
the Bureau's a suicide mission.
Mick's right.
We need to sneak into PalmerX,
do some recon,
find out what Neron is up to.
Now that sounds like a plan Z.
Hey, baby.
Hey, you looking
for a good time, handsome?
I'm always looking
for a good time, love,
but, regrettably,
my time here is limited.
Maybe you can help me.
I'm looking for a broker
in the soul trade.
He goes by the name of Masher.
I might know something.
Well, this here is holy water.
Now, you can use this
to burn the skin off any demon tosser
who messes with you.
Masher likes to hang out
at the strip club
after trading is done...
John.
How do you know my name?
Oh, I know who you are.
Half of demon kind is searching
for John Constantine.
The holy water?
Oh, this?
No, this is just whisky, love.
Sure, our protagonist
was keeping people hostage, but,
that's only because he never
received love as a child.
They don't want you
in their book club, Gary.
Doesn't that make you angry?
Make a wish and they will pay.
You're right.
They don't want to spend time
with Gary Green,
lowly Time Bureau agent.
But they would love to spend time
with Gary Green...
Captain of the Waverider.
Welcome aboard, Captain Green.
Thanks.
I have no quarrel with you, dear.
You didn't send me to hell
like John Constantine
and the Legends.
Yes.
I was in hell for 327 years.
And what was my crime?
I sprinkled a little magic
over Salem,
trying to help a girl whose mother
was accused of witchcraft.
Okay, well, you're out now.
Why help Neron?
Neron rescued me in hell.
What can I say?
True love bloomed.
I know what you're thinking,
he's so much older than me.
Sometimes you have to look past age.
You know, in another life,
I think you and I
could have been friends.
- Toodles.
- Wait, what...
Ray?
Without all
of the idiotic tendencies.
Make a move on me and Mona dies.
Ray is good and strong.
He can fight his way back from hell.
Who do you think
is having a worse time in hell?
Ray, or your father?
Turns out Daddy dearest
isn't so tough.
I hear Damien Darhk
is going stark raving mad
in the pits.
Why am I here?
Well, you and John tried to kill me,
nearly did.
If the doofus in the skin suit
I'm wearing hadn't have interrupted,
I'd have been obliterated.
I spent many nights
just dreaming about how
I was going to get my revenge.
And then it came to me,
what better punishment
than making you sit front row
to all of the fear and rage
I'm about to unleash on the Earth,
all while in the body of the man
you love.
Now...
smile for the cameras.
Mr. Palmer.
Are monsters real?
What's tonight all about?
Now, all of your questions
will be answered soon.
- Excuse me.
- What's wrong with you?
Well, you know, a room full of people
fearful of magical creatures
just makes me a little bit fearful,
all right?
The worst part is,
Ray loves tech events.
Good evening, D.C.
and welcome to PalmerX 2019.
Now, you're all probably wondering,
what in the heck is Ray Palmer
doing back in the public eye?
Well, folks, for the past two years
I have been hunting
magical creatures.
Hang with me here.
I have created an exosuit
capable of combating
the most ferocious of their kind.
What a douche.
But I can't do it alone.
I need your help.
I need you to help me
find these creatures...
creatures that may be hiding
right here amongst us.
Now, everyone take out
your smartphones.
Better be PalmerTech.
I have created a small, simple app,
that will change the world.
And I want you all to download it
right now.
The app is called Eyes.
Now, on Eyes, you will be able
to share real-time,
life-saving monster sightings.
Share them
and I will be there to save you.
Remember, the power
is in the Palmer of your hands.
You really expect us
to believe monsters exist?
I thought you were going
to offer us proof.
Thank you, Cindy.
You are absolutely right.
Here is your proof.
Now, this may
look like a helpless hipster
who should be working at a bookstore,
but believe me,
she is something altogether
more dangerous.
Masher.
- John?
- Yeah, yeah, all right,
keep your hair on. No need
to tell the whole bloody club.
Oh, buddy, now I know
you're out of your mind.
What are you doing in hell?
I'm here to save a friend.
His soul belongs to Neron.
Cheers, love. He's paying.
Nobody gets into Neron's soul vault
without his say-so.
Except the Triumvirate
and I have a plan to deal with them,
but first, there's a hunch
I need to confirm.
What's Neron trading at?
He's steady,
but I'll let you in on
a little secret.
His stock is about to rise.
I'm talking a massive soul collection
on Earth.
You know what that means?
Neron is finally making his play
for the throne of hell.
Oh, cheers, Masher. I can use that.
Be careful, John.
Not every demon you've sent to hell
is as forgiving as I am.
Yeah, don't I know it.
You're dead, demon hunter.
I was going to be
a demon proctologist,
but the pay wasn't as good.
Hold him.
Oh, Calibraxis.
Hey, looking good, mate.
- You grow your beard?
- John Constantine.
I'm really going to enjoy
watching you breathe your last.
I invoke a parlay.
I demand to speak to the Triumvirate.
I'm a demon, not a pirate, John.
I thought you understood the rules.
Well, you little maggot,
as long as I'm alive,
then the Triumvirate
can pass me around
like a little sparrow
amongst the cats.
But as soon as I die,
you dim-witted dick,
then my soul belongs to Neron
and then the Triumvirate lose out
on all the tasty little bits
of torture
that they've got planned for me.
So you've got two choices.
You can either kill me
and royally piss off the old bags
that run this place,
or take me to speak
with the Triumvirate.
I'm detecting
a fugitive alert stop it...
at the Inquisition, Captain Green.
Oh, I don't do torture.
Could've fooled me.
Hey. Play nice.
We have to distract Gary
while the B team is plan B...ing.
Would a fairy at the Great British
Bakeoff suit your fancy?
Shall we...
keep calm and pastry on?
I'll plot a course, Captain.
Get it?
"Keep calm and pastry on"?
Good one, Cap.
- Hilarious.
- Thanks, guys.
Thanks. Yeah.
Take a good, long look at her...
Mona Wu.
You saw her on the street,
you wouldn't think twice.
Come on, Mona.
Don't give him what he wants.
But she has a strange
and violent condition...
brought about when she fell in love
with a repulsive creature.
I feel like a bridge scene
should have more people.
Oh, no, we love
three people bridge scenes.
Yeah, otherwise we just end up
standing around all day.
Oh, that's why Mick's always grumpy.
Come on, Mona.
I promised these fine people a show.
Let's not keep them waiting.
Shift now or end up dead like Konane.
Folks, proof of the world's
very first werewolf.
That's what we're missing the boys.
- No.
- Yeah.
Fairy Godmother?
- Z.
- B.
She made him disappear.
Well, well, well...
what do we have here?
More magic in the audience?
She's one of them.
He's right. I am.
She's a witch.
Witch. Witch.
Witch, witch, witch.
Witch, witch, witch...
Don't worry, folks.
The witch won't get far.
Not as long as everyone
downloads the Eyes app.
Share your sightings.
We'll find the witch.
It's only a matter of time.
Sara, you guys okay?
Yeah, we're fine, as long
as we keep placating Gary.
I guess Charlie and Z
are our last hope.
Great, we're toast.
Welcome to hell.
Good evening,
this is your captain speaking.
Just...
What?
We'll be cruising at a high altitude
on our way
to save a bakeoff in Britain.
- Yeah.
Gary, is that the Kid Steel costume?
You like-y?
Why would anyone wish
to be a sidekick?
- Close your legs.
- Oh, he's such an idiot.
What?
Nothing, they're just teasing you.
You're my Gar-bear.
We're going to have so much fun.
Okay?
#EyesApp is trending on Twitter
below Kanye's surprise album
and a cat getting a bath.
How many downloads?
Only 2,000, Mr. Palmer.
News cycle is so fast these days,
it's hard to cut
through all the noise.
But a monster attack on the capital
will dominate the headlines
for weeks.
And then what?
More people will download some app?
That's your big plan?
Why, yes, it is.
My love.
Would you please escort
our guest to a cell?
Let's go, dearie.
Neron didn't say
which containment cell to put you in.
Why are you helping me?
Because you're a fellow witch
and I think we can help each other.
Mona?
How do you feel?
I've been better.
Remember, I'm just
a "Fairy Godmother" away.
Trust me, we'll be safe here.
Where are we?
My childhood home.
I thought you grew up
in a dystopian city, Z.
You had a pool?
In a couple years, A.R.G.U.S.
will use people's growing fear
of meta-humans to seize control.
Of course, it didn't help
that we're Muslim.
We were forced to move
to a ghetto district in 2021.
Humans are so easy to manipulate.
I mean, you just show them
a scary ogre
or a dangerous meta,
they just go barmy.
Haven't even been able
to get into the Eyes app yet
because the terms of service
are so long.
No one bothers reading those.
It's a demon app.
I'm going to read the fine print.
I can't believe it's just us left.
I mean, you and I
both knew from the start
that it was madness
to storm the Bureau.
Oh, my God.
What?
Z?
In New Orleans,
John said Neron needed
more souls to take over hell.
Here it says in exchange
for the service,
the user agrees to forfeit their
eternal soul to the demon Neron.
What, you're saying that anyone
who downloads the app
is going to hell?
Yeah.
Oh, that is mental.
This little fairy was causing
quite the fray around the soufflé.
I think I know
just the place for you, Madame.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm going to kill him.
Hey, Z, Charlie,
please tell me you have something.
Well, we figured out Neron's app
is a way to collect souls.
That's crazy.
Yeah, it gets crazier.
To drum up fear
and increase downloads of his app,
we think he may be planning
a monster attack.
Okay, well, we'll stall Gary,
but you got to get every single one
of those monsters
out of the Time Bureau.
I was afraid
you were going to say that.
Who are you talking to, Sara?
What?
Gary. Baby, bubby, bubelah.
There's a whole big world
of problems.
You know, Neron
and your Fairy Godmother,
they're not really
your friends, but...
Do you know who your friends are?
These guys.
Are you trying to schmooze me?
Feels good, right?
Actually, it feels a little false.
Gary.
You are our friend.
I mean, would we lie
to an interim Legend?
You see, that's just it,
because I'm not an interim Legend.
You just promised me
that to use me as bait.
You know what, Gary?
It's a little hard
to feel sorry for you
when you're holding us all hostage.
You're not getting it.
This whole time, Tabitha has been
trying to use me to hurt you.
All I wished was for us to hang out.
I was trying to protect you.
I get it. I'm not cool.
But I don't deserve to be treated
like a joke.
So, now...
now the joke's on you.
- What's he talking about?
- Oh, Fairy Godmother.
Yes, my pet?
Mick thinks he's a tough guy,
but I think he's a big baby.
And Nate, who's never been
bullied a day in his life,
welcome to my high-school years.
And Sara and Ava,
the cool girl
and the class president,
you know what I want you to do
for me?
Dance.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Faster.
Gary, stop it!
Charlie, I get that you're scared,
- but the team is counting on us.
- I'm not scared.
It's just, breaking the monsters
out of the prison
is a multiple-person job.
You can be multiple people.
Look, Z, yeah, I can, for a second
and you know what?
It takes its toll.
Now, I could end up back in prison
or even worse, dead.
When A.R.G.U.S. came for my family,
my brother, Behrad, told me to run.
And I did.
I've never forgiven myself.
You won't either.
We can't change my family's future,
but we can save their present.
Zari Jaan, make sure you take
your shoes off before you go in.
- I know.
- Charlie?
If I die, I'm going to come back
and haunt you.
I would love a ghost friend.
Come on.
Cool.
Greetings, Satan,
first of the fallen.
It's been a long time, John.
- Belial.
- We've been looking forward
to hearing the bunk you're peddling.
And Beelzebub.
Not as popular, but you
were always my personal favorite.
This is a waste of our time.
I take it you've noticed
a certain demon's
stock has been on the rise.
Neron's been doing very well
for himself.
Neron is trying to take control
of hell.
And let me assure you,
his method for collecting souls,
it won't be to sign
on the dotted line in blood.
He's young,
by your standards at least.
And let's just say,
he means to disrupt the system.
If we interfere with Neron,
we'll look weak.
Well, that's precisely
where I come in, Bubby.
And what do you want in exchange?
Not your own soul, I hope.
I'm here for the soul
of Raymond Palmer.
You let us two leave hell
and I pledge to you that I will
dedicate all of my crafty,
wicked ways to thwarting Neron
and securing your reign.
Are you really here
for Raymond Palmer?
We thought there was another...
A young girl
whose life you destroyed.
Astra.
Yeah, well, you know,
I didn't want to be too greedy.
But, yeah, I'll take them both.
Both of them?
That is greedy.
But if you were to choose,
well, then that's a different matter.
John, help me.
John, you're here.
You got to get me back to Earth.
Please, John. They're hurting me.
Make up your mind, John.
This offer won't last.
John?
- Astra?
- It's following me.
Make it go away.
Come here, I've got you.
You can't have her.
You can't save her.
John, get me out of here.
I'm sorry.
I choose...
Astra Logue.
Stick to the plan, Charlie.
You mean the plan where I need
to rely on my shoddy shape-shifting
to portal creatures one by one
out of their cells
and on to the Waverider,
where Gary may or may not
wish them to Kingdom Come?
Yup, that plan.
This isn't you, Gary.
Why are you being so cruel?
Please.
Stop. You're killing them.
I don't do mime, dearie.
Just stop.
Everything.
As you wish...
Mona? Hey, wake up.
Hey, Nora.
Hey.
Oh, you're still here.
I'm book club forever.
Book club forever.
Oh, Fairy Godmother.
I have to pop off for a second, Gary.
I thought we were going to play
Settlers of Catan later.
Don't be silly.
We're not friends.
I am so sorry, Gary.
I took you for granted.
I never, ever should have
let you do my dry cleaning
or work overtime without pay.
I mean, that's illegal anyway.
I'm so sorry.
I still want to kill you.
Gary, when Rip first
recruited the Legends,
he picked the people
that were insignificant to history,
the original losers.
You don't have to be cool
to be a Legend.
And maybe we forgot that
somewhere along the way, but...
you are one of us.
Now, come on, Gary.
Ray and Constantine
are both stuck in hell
and you can help them.
Just use your Fairy Godmother
powers for good.
Save her.
Sadly, my hands are tied.
But if you become
Mona's Fairy Godmother,
she could wish to be healed.
How do I do that?
If another witch takes the wand...
You'll take my curse...
but with it, all of my power.
Nora.
Nora, no.
No.
Oh, it worked.
Quick, Mona. Make a wish.
Fairy God-Nora,
I wish to be safe on the Waverider.
Oh, how I've missed me.
Sadly for you,
when you took on the wand's power
and responsibility,
you also took on its charge.
- Gary?
- I'm afraid so.
Fairy Godmothers are prisoners.
Their magic is dependent
on whiny humans
and their petty demands.
You lied.
Obviously.
Toodles.
Excuse me.
- Marilyn Monroe?
- Why, yes.
I seem to have gotten a little lost.
Can you help me get back home?
Of course, ma'am.
Let me just program in a year.
Yeah.
- Thank you, sir.
- Oh, my love.
My love.
Still no luck with Nora?
No.
Well, she'll take your curse soon.
After all, you are very convincing.
Well, I better head back.
Evil deeds to do and all that.
No.
Well, that was bloody close.
I'm at the first cell.
Anytime now, Z.
Okay, just give me one second.
The public doesn't always know
what's best for them.
So tonight we will release
the Minotaur
and scare them
into accepting our protection.
It is done, mon amour.
How do I look?
But you were just...
Oh, the shape-shifter.
Can someone sound the alarm?
Charlie, Tabitha
and Neron are onto you.
Yeah, I figured.
You need to get out now.
Open all the doors,
turn off the force fields.
I'm not leaving.
Are you waiting for an invitation?
It's a bloody jailbreak.
I mean, there are pros to trusting
your apologies are sincere and cons.
Maybe I'll make a list.
Gary...Gary, just go with your heart.
Oh, Fairy Godmother.
Nora.
Go find John and help him
rescue Ray from hell.
Oh, fiddlesticks.
Wait, wait.
- Gary.
- Gary, you dick.
Come on, you lot. Get a move on.
You don't have to tell me twice.
Faster, sassy.
You're all right, little one.
Oi, ogre. Catch.
Charlie, you're out of time.
Z, get out of here.
See you on the other side.
I'm going after Mona.
Mona.
Come on, love.
Let's get you out of here.
I hate shape-shifters.
Break her neck.
Patience, mon amour.
Get Mona.
No.
Looks like things ain't going
so well for you, Neron.
You wanted a monster to attack D.C.
Now we have every single monster...
in one.
You promised me
you'd take me to see Astra.
Patience, John.
I made a pledge to you
and I expect you to keep
your end of the bargain.
What the hell are you playing at?
John?
John, is it really you?
Yes.
Yes, Astra, love. It's me.
It's me. This is Johnny.
Thank God.
God?
You know better than to thank him.
Astra?
John is here to take you back
to Earth.
You're welcome to go.
Yeah.
It's all right, love. It's me.
No.
Wait.
Hold on. What...
What do you mean no?
Looks like the deal is null and void.
Neron is a thorn in our side, John,
but torturing you...
is too much fun.
John?
It's following me.
Make it go away.
Please.
John, get me out of here.
Astra, love.
- This isn't you.
- Oh, of course it is.
Or would you rather I stayed
that terrified little girl,
crying and waiting for you to come
and rescue me?
I would have been waiting
a long time.
I am so, so sorry, love,
but...
this place, it's twisted you.
If anything...
it's made me more like you.
Right, John?
You're not like me.
You're not.
You chose wrong.
You should have saved your friend.
Hey, watch it.
Back off, freak.
It's like a demented Noah's Ark.
What about Charlie?
It's my fault. I'm the one that
convinced her to risk everything.
Hey, don't go down that road.
We'll do what we always do.
Yeah, forming stupid Beebos.
Hey, where are you going?
Well, after everything,
I just figured you wouldn't want
to have me around anymore.
It's all hands on deck, Gary.
Yeah.
We're going to need
all our friends to defeat Neron.
You all right?
Not really.
I'm glad you and Wicksty are okay.
What happened?
Oh, my God.
Hi.
My name is Zari.