[Mick] Previously on
Legends Of Tomorrow...
Your shapeshifting days are over,
sweetheart.
You decided to exploit her
for information
and to help us
track down other fugitives.
I know you're writing a novel
and it's really good...
Taco delivery, my name's Mona.
[Mona] So what's a Time Bureau?
That was supposed to be top secret.
I'm not losing another kid.
[Ray] The magic you used
was pretty powerful.
If magic has him on death's door,
then maybe magic can save him.
I think I know someone who can help.
[oriental music playing]
[all speaking Japanese]
[distant rumble]
[distant screeching]
[gasping]
There's gotta be another way
to fix him, something Gideon missed.
John used magic to save
those kids at camp.
Magic's the only thing that can fix him.
And you really think
Nora Darhk is the answer?
She's the only witch I know.
Can we even find her?
That is the problem.
She has a time stone.
She could literally be anywhere,
any when.
The Bureau can't even seem to find her.
When I was a kid,
there was this one escaped con
that my dad was after.
And everyone assumed
that he had fled the country.
You know where he found him?
Not a block from the police precinct.
You really think she's hiding
in the Bureau's backyard?
Gideon, do a Nora Darhk
facial recognition scan in 2018.
[Gideon] I have located
a potential match.
That's her.
[Sara] Right in the Bureau's backyard.
Great work, Detective Lance.
[Gideon] Captain,
our systems have identified
the presence of a new fugitive.
This one is in 1951, Tokyo.
All right, let's divide and conquer.
I'll take care of Tokyo,
you go find our witch.
Make her fix our warlock.
[Sara] Everybody to the bridge,
we got a fugitive alert.
Mm-hmm.
- Hello?
- [groans]
Anyone hear me?
[Mick] Drat.
Hey.
Closed door means stay out.
Sorry, Sara called a team meeting.
- Were you...
- Yes.
I was watching porn.
On a typewriter?
Hey, no judgment here.
All right...
[woman speaking in foreign language]
Chop chop.
Oi.
Enough shouting.
That my whiskey?
It was.
Oh, well, look who finally
pried themselves away
from their important business.
Look, hobbies are very important.
Right, Rory?
I take my porn very seriously.
Okay, back to work.
In the summer of 1951,
a film crew shot footage
of a monster in Tokyo Bay.
Two days later, the city was destroyed.
We need to get that footage
before any panic sets in
and to capture that monster
before it can do any real damage.
And because we're short-handed,
you're up.
Time to earn your keep.
Well, I didn't ask to be here, ma'am.
But you are a fugitive,
so your choices are help us out,
go back in your cage.
[scoffs] Bloody humans.
All right, fine.
But it's only to stop you blinkered lot
from giving a harmless monster
a one-way ticket to Hell.
At least with me there,
the poor chap gets a fair shake.
I like her, yes, I like her.
As you can see, Mr. Heywood,
the Time Bureau is putting your money
to great use.
We have multiple teams
deployed throughout history
tracking down and securing fugitives.
All trained by your son.
And we only have the most highly
qualified Time Bureau personnel
dealing with... Oh, boy.
[clears throat]
And here's Gary with a live one.
Ah! Say hello to Baba-Yaga.
We caught her trying
to eat Chinese gymnasts
at the 2008 Olympics.
[speaking Russian]
- Sorry about that, sir.
- What did she say?
Just a typical Russian greeting.
[growls]
[Baba-Yaga laughing maliciously]
[Hank] Are you sure this room
is secure enough
to hold these creatures?
It's a temporary arrangement
until our containment facility
is up and running, sir.
And they are heavily sedated,
right, Gary?
Yeah, double doses
of elephant tranquilizer all around.
This way.
[clears throat]
Director Sharpe, it looks like you have
things under control here.
Yes, sir, we sure do.
I'll be seeing you tomorrow
for Thanksgiving.
Your mother's really
looking forward to it
and so am I.
[chuckles] I wouldn't miss it
for the world.
What are you doing
for the holiday, Director Sharpe?
Me? Oh, well, I was planning
on spending it with my girlfriend,
but she's working overtime,
so I'll probably just
be sticking around here, I guess.
- [elevator bell dings]
- You should join us.
It'll be fun, right, Nathaniel?
Absolutely.
- [chuckles nervously]
- Bye, sir.
Yeah, that is if you don't mind
starving all day
while your family slowly
gets loaded and starts fighting
and then your dad gets called
for a "work emergency."
Well, at least your family
are real people.
Mine are actors.
[speaking Japanese]
According to historical record,
the director we're looking for,
Ishiro Honda, should be in this stage.
Well, I'm feeling a little conspicuous.
Just act like you belong.
- No one will question it.
- You.
Coffee. Now.
Yeah, see?
It's all about confidence.
All right, you guys know your cover?
Yeah.
[thunderclaps]
[speaking Japanese]
[clears throat and coughs]
I beg your pardon,
but this is a closed set.
Are you Ishiro Honda the film director?
- Huh.
- Honda-san, pleasure to meet you.
We're producers from K&G Pictures,
we got word of an unusual
animal sighting out in the bay.
We were told you might
have some footage suitable
for our news reel?
- How do you know about that?
- We're from Hollywood,
we know everything.
Gracias.
[Ishiro] You must have misheard.
We were out on location by the sea, yes.
And we saw a whale.
And that was it.
You're sure it wasn't something else?
Something strange?
Perhaps we could take a look
and see for ourselves.
Uh, I'm afraid the footage
was ruined during transport.
I'm sorry.
[Ishiro] It truly isn't possible.
No, the bloke's lying.
Mm. Finally, something we agree on.
- Stay here.
- What?
- Where are you going?
- To find that film.
Oh, not if I find it first.
I have to go now.
Mr. Honda. Mr. Honda.
Could we trouble you for a tour?
Of course.
Please.
When we are on a mission,
I give the orders.
Whose rubbish idea was that?
You are lucky
I am a reformed assassin.
It's quite a remarkable effect.
If we shoot at low angles
with a wide lens,
it feels as though
we are ants in this enormous city.
[distant clang]
That is fascinating.
It's gotta be in his office somewhere.
If I was hiding something, I would
put it where no one else would look.
[grunts]
Like under a bloody bomb.
Genius.
[Mick] It'd look amazing on fire.
Thank you so much for the tour,
if you are ever in Burbank,
be sure to look us up.
[Gideon] I've successfully digitized
the film and it's ready for viewing.
Roll it, Ms. G.
[exhales]
[Sara] What is that under the water?
[monster screeching]
- Whoa.
- [chuckles]
Guys, I think we're gonna
need a bigger Timeship.
[Sara] Okay, what is it?
You're supposed to be
the fugitive expert.
Oh, well, that's no fugitive.
So what? It's just some
other magical monster
that's not supposed to be here?
Maybe you just haven't met this one.
Or maybe if you weren't so quick
to blame us fugitives
for everything, you'd see
the more likely scenario.
That creature is man-made.
It's probably a mutant or something
created by one of the countless nukes
you humans dropped
on the Pacific in this era.
Or didn't you think of that?
Nice try, genius, but if that were true,
we wouldn't have gotten a magic alert,
so why are we here?
Ooh, you're the time traveler,
when don't you figure it out?
[Sara] Okay, Gideon,
scan Tokyo Bay
for any unusual marine activity.
[Gideon] Right away, Captain.
[Sara] Hopefully,
Ray's having better luck.
- [whimsical music playing]
- Huh.
I had a dream like this once.
Maybe more than once.
More mead, wench.
As you wish.
[pouring drink]
Oh, a thousand pardons.
[chuckling mischievously]
- [man] Hmm.
- [sighs]
- Oh. [chuckles]
- [camera shutter clicking]
- [man] Ah.
- [sighs in frustration]
Palmer Tech phone? Huh, great software.
Terrible hardware.
My phone.
Get ye out of my sight, scoundrel.
[laughing]
- What are...
- Oh.
- I'm sorry.
- What are you doing here?
I need your help.
[both yelling]
Chris and Tyson, you two
get back here right now.
Hi, Nate. [chuckles]
- Hey, Patty, this is...
- Hi, uh...
Ava Sharpe. [clears throat] Um...
Hi, Grandma.
That's my grandma, Violet,
do not let her rope you
into playing cards,
it's a lose-lose situation.
And there's my Uncle Rich.
Don't mention Obama.
[Hank] There he is.
- [Nate] Hey.
- Good to see you, son.
Glad you could make it, Director Sharpe.
- Thanks.
- You must be Ava.
- Hi. [laughing]
- Oh, hi.
Thank you so much
for letting me join you.
Oh, of course, we wouldn't want you
all alone on such a special day.
He's into the good stuff.
[sighs] Nate, show her around,
make her feel at home.
- [laughing] Wow.
- Wow.
[both sigh]
Your family seems nice.
Oh, it's still very early.
[Dorothy] Okay, everyone.
- The turkey is almost done.
- Wait for it.
Brining. [chuckling] Yeah. It just has
to sit for another hour and a half
and then I'm gonna pop it into the oven.
So that means dinner is when?
Mm, give or take, six hours.
What?
- [boys yelling]
- [Agent Sharpe] Oh, my God.
- [Patty] Tyson.
- Buckle up, Ava Sharpe.
- [Chris] I'm gonna tell on you.
- [sighs] It's gonna be a bumpy ride.
[Tyson] No!
[elevator bell dings]
Happy Thanksgiving, Mr. Green.
Hi, Mona.
Thanks for bringing me food
on a holiday.
It's literally my job.
Why are you working on Thanksgiving?
What does the Time Bureau do anyway?
[sighs] Oh, it's like Groundhog Day.
Uh, we regulate time zones.
So you got any plans for the big meal?
Heck yeah, I do.
My family's in LA,
so it's just me, instant ramen,
and Bestflix bingeing.
Oh, well, if you want, you could...
Uh, have Thanksgiving with me.
That's really sweet, Mr. Green.
But I don't wanna eat all your food.
Oh, I happen to have
ordered enough for two.
You're vegetarian, right?
[laughs]
[snoring]
[sniffing]
[growling]
[groaning]
Nora Darhk, what the bloomin' hell
are you doing here, eh?
I owed this guy a favor.
She shouldn't be here, mate,
I thought I warned you.
Can you help him?
Gideon's showing strange
marine activity in this area.
Fish disappearing en masse,
seismic tremors.
You need all that just to end up
back where the film was shot?
Just being thorough.
Hm, using fancy toys
instead of your noggins, more like.
You know, I think I liked you
better when you were in a cage.
[Sara] All right, enough.
All we gotta do is draw this thing out.
We shrink it down and we're good to go.
How do you expect us to do that?
What, just summon it
with a friendly call?
"Oi, monster, come up here.
Promise it's not a trap."
Or feed it like that guy.
[grunts]
Isn't that our friend,
the film director?
- Feeding the whales, Mr. Honda?
- [gasps]
You, what are you doing here?
[Sara] You first.
Start talking.
[water gurgling]
[gasps]
What the hell is that?
It's evil.
Truly evil.
I think we found our fugitive
and it's not a monster.
No.
This is something much, much worse.
This, chaps, is no ordinary diary.
It's an agent of Brigid.
Brigid.
The Celtic goddess
of art, creation and healing.
This book has the power
to make the imagination
a reality.
You're not film producers, are you?
No, we are not, but we saw
what was on that film, Ishiro,
and we're here to stop it.
Tell us how you found the journal.
I was out scouting for my film.
- And I found this book.
- You didn't find the book,
it found you.
It's drawn to creative types.
[Ishiro] Once I opened it,
I was flooded with inspiration.
An image that has haunted my nightmares
suddenly came to life on those pages.
And then,
to my horror,
in real life.
I told you,
- this book is evil.
- Whoa, hold on a tick.
Brigid created this book
as a gift to you humans,
to bring your dreams to life,
you turned it into a weapon.
She's right.
I did create something horrible.
- What is this thing?
- [Ishiro] I call it Tagumo.
A giant land octopus.
Capable of destroying entire cities.
When I realized Tagumo had come to life,
I tried to destroy the journal.
But it always comes back.
Of course it does,
the power links you and this book.
It won't be released
until the story of your creation
is played out in full.
[Mick] How did you end it?
You pushed the octopus in a volcano?
Nope.
Tagumo wins.
Tokyo is destroyed.
[sighs]
[Hank] Oh, brother.
[gasps] Richard.
You break it, you bought it, Rich.
[Richard groaning]
Well, this is a disaster.
Hey, no one has killed each other, yet.
Chris, Tyson.
- Dad, have you seen the boys?
- Oh, last I saw 'em,
they were down in the basement.
Playing with Nate's old air rifle.
- [shot fired]
- [both gasp]
- [boy screaming]
- [Dorothy] Ooh!
[Chris] Mom!
Guess they know how to load it.
[Sara] Okay, if we can't stop Tagumo,
then draw a new ending.
Preferably one where no one dies.
[sighs] It's not working.
Like I said, Brigid created that book
to help artists express themselves.
You can't expect him to write
a happy ending
if he ain't had a happy life.
Ain't that right, Ishiro?
You're right.
Every night,
before this journal came to me,
I'd close my eyes,
and be back
in the ruins of Hiroshima.
Choking on ash,
wondering where all the people went.
Not realizing they were all around me,
in my hair,
on my clothes,
in my lungs.
They turned to dust.
Drawing Tagumo
helped me
turn the nightmares
into something I could understand.
A monster.
But now,
I am the monster.
Ishiro, you went through
something truly unimaginable.
We all deal with our pain
in different ways
and you chose art.
And that's beautiful.
Don't blame yourself.
This is not your fault.
[sighs]
So, can you save him?
Life force is the most potent
form of energy in the universe.
And you're like a battery
about to run out of charge.
But you already knew that, didn't you?
Oh, aye.
Then why didn't you say anything?
What?
And help push you off the wagon?
You're clean, Nora,
it's best we keep you that way.
You can recharge him, right?
You don't want me to do that, Ray.
Yes, I do.
- Otherwise, he's gonna die.
- Ray!
My power comes from my father.
It's in my blood,
it's always going to be calling me,
wanting me to give in
and be consumed, but I can't give in.
I won't.
[Gary] Now, this is where
we monitor timezone infractions.
Isn't that a little overkill?
Now here at the Time Bureau,
there's no such thing as overkill.
[creature snarling]
You need to come with me.
Come, come, come.
There's something else
amazing to see right in here.
- Um, why are you...
- Yeah.
- [Mona] Oh! Uh, Mr. Green?
- [knocking on door]
Hello? I think you forgot
to unlock the door.
I'm so fired.
[creatures snarling and growling]
Sorry to bother you but we have
a bit of a situation here.
The prisoners are loose.
- What? How the hell did that happen?
- [groans] Oh.
The tranqs must have worn off.
- Okay, we need to go.
- No, if we leave,
Hank will know something's wrong.
Something is wrong, Nate.
So you want our liaison to the DOD
knowing that we messed up?
- No, I don't.
- What do I do?
- Shut up, Gary.
I got a plan. I'll be back.
No, your family's gonna notice
if you're gone.
Not if I courier back ASAP.
- No.
- Just stall.
- Stall.
- No, I don't even know...
[screams]
Hey, buddy, you okay?
[whispering] This is
the worst Thanksgiving ever.
Yeah, it's scary stuff.
- Yeah.
- But like I said, I have a plan,
so let's go get our hands
on some tranq guns.
- Okay.
- Oh, my God.
- Is that a Kaupe?
- No.
[Kaupe roars]
[Mona screaming]
What the hell is she doing here?
She was supposed to stay
locked in the closet,
I was gonna flash her later.
- Do what?
- That didn't sound right.
Oh, for the love of...
[sighs]
Excellent hiding spot.
Yeah, well, I'm not hiding.
My father sacrificed himself
to give me a second chance.
I don't wanna ruin it
by backsliding into dark magic.
Who says it has to be dark?
John needs a magical transfusion.
Normally, I'd have to drain
someone's life to save his.
Life force is essentially energy.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Well, then I have an idea.
[all cheering]
[Patty] Yes.
Oh, Dot, you have outdone yourself.
I hope you all built up an appetite.
- [Dorothy chuckles]
- Uh...
Care to do the honors
this year, Nathaniel?
- Nathaniel?
- Oh, he's probably just in the restroom.
We should wait for him.
Mom, I'm hungry.
- Me, too.
- Just a little bit longer, boys.
Yeah, I'll go check on him.
Oh, wait, uh, sorry, sir.
You know what we would do?
[chuckles nervously] In my family,
we'd actually go around
and list all the things
that we're thankful for.
What a lovely idea.
I'm thankful I'm still breathing.
Well, I'll go first then.
Uh, I am thankful for so many things.
So many, many things.
[creatures snarling and growling]
I can't believe you guys
have magical creatures here,
this is like the coolest place ever.
[roaring]
Wait.
[both grunting and growling]
I've seen this before.
They're hangry. Those poor creatures
are starving to death.
What does a Kaupe, chupacabra
and a Baba-Yaga eat?
That'd be Hawaiian barbecue,
birria, and veal.
Babies more precisely,
but veal will do in a pinch.
Really?
- I read a lot.
- Wow.
Where are we going to get
all those things on Thanksgiving?
- Everything's closed.
- I'm on it.
No, get back here.
[grunts]
[growling continues]
[sighs] Ishiro can't change the story.
Plan C, it is.
What if we got the book
to bond with another artist?
We could change the story altogether.
Do you see another artist around?
It's not like we can just find
some rando with a paintbrush.
Who knows what they could unleash?
And we're sure there's not
a single artist amongst us?
Why don't we just burn the damn thing?
Hey, why don't you tell
Sara you're a writer?
Because I'm not.
Rory, I read your novel,
as much as it pains me to say it,
you are very, very talented.
Well, it doesn't matter,
I can't write anymore.
Nothing comes out.
You have writer's block.
No, I dropped a deuce this morning.
- Ugh.
- [gadget beeps]
Um, guys...
- [distant rumbling]
- [electricity buzzes]
What is happening?
The Tagumo, it's headed straight for us.
It's moving fast. It's getting closer.
- By land?
- [Zari] It's in the sewers.
[Ishiro] Like an octopus.
Tagumo can squeeze through
the tiniest opening.
It's coming for me.
We're not gonna let that happen.
Rory, Z, keep him safe.
Charlie, with me.
[rumbling]
[siren wailing]
[all screaming]
Well, what's the plan?
You distract it, I'll shrink it down.
What? You want me as bait?
Not bloody likely.
Charlie! Damn it.
[gadget powering up]
[Tagumo roaring]
[roaring]
[grunting]
[screams]
[grunts]
[growling]
Oh.
[grunting]
[screaming]
Get your slimy mitts off of her,
you wanker!
[growls]
[grunts]
Yeah!
Come on over here, you muppet,
come and get me.
- [growls]
- [screams]
[screeching]
Yeah! [laughs jubilantly]
Bloody brilliant!
Aren't you glad that I came back?
[whoops]
Where'd it go?
Sara, how's it going out there?
[Sara] Good news, we shrank Tagumo.
Bad news, we have no idea where it went.
Des...
Nora, don't.
- Don't talk, save your strength.
- No, listen to me, listen to me.
As smart as Ray is, he doesn't
understand what you're about to do.
Choosing a life of magic,
you're either all in
or you're not, there's no half measures.
And you and I both know,
it never leads to a happy ending.
So if you're gonna do this,
you don't do it for Ray,
you don't do it for me,
you do it for yourself, all right?
It's your choice.
It's your choice. It's your choice.
[Agent Sharpe] And I am thankful for
the Whole Paycheck Grocer by my work.
Did you know they have a full bar?
And I think you mentioned everything
the rest of us are thankful for.
So everyone please grab a plate.
[Agent Sharpe] Oh!
- We should say grace, right?
- [all] Grace!
- I'll check on Nathaniel.
- That... Just...
Why couldn't I just tell sober,
grounded stories
instead of indulging in silly monsters.
Sober and grounded is boring.
You had a story to tell and you told it,
you brought that monster to life.
Don't pretend for a second
you're not a little bit proud.
I was so afraid of what people
would think of my creation.
And now that it's here in the flesh...
Story complete.
And I no longer have to fear
what was locked inside my head.
No.
No, you don't.
Pen.
[Ishiro] The ink. It's not disappearing.
Are you ready?
Yes.
I wanna do this.
[electricity buzzing]
[grunting and coughing]
[panting]
Oh, what a rush.
[creatures growling and snarling]
[cell phone ringing]
[whispering] Mona's here with the food.
- Listen...
- [elevator bell dings]
- [all gasp]
- Oh, crap.
[all snarling and growling]
[screaming]
[Agent Sharpe stammers]
Come on out, son, time to eat.
You know, maybe we should
start without him,
I'm sure he'll be out soon enough.
Ha, look at that, maybe he went
to the store to grab some Pepto
for, you know...
I'm going to ask you this once,
Director Sharpe,
what are you hiding from me?
The prisoners have escaped, sir.
My son is alone with those
creatures on the loose?
- You take me there now.
- Sir, it's not safe.
My son is not safe, Director Sharpe.
We're going, end of discussion.
[creatures eating]
[creatures grunting]
What the hell is this?
[Nate] Uh, dinner, the key
to any hangry creature's heart.
We let them fill up and then it's...
[imitates shots] Night-night again.
This time without
the life-threatening shenanigans.
Senor, I couldn't find the Tapatío,
but here's some Sriracha.
[gurgling]
- What are you doing?
- Quiet. I'm concentrating.
Mick is a writer,
the journal has bonded with him.
Bloody hell! That's it, we're doomed.
We cannot stay here.
Tagumo will find us.
[Tagumo growling]
Ishiro!
[growling]
Meet Garima.
Queen of Thanzanon.
[Tagumo screeching]
- Should we help her?
- No, I think she's got it.
[screams aggressively]
[gasps]
[Tagumo growling]
Get it, girl!
[growling]
[screeching]
[Tagumo screeching]
[gasps]
- Whoo!
- Wow.
[Charlie] Yeah!
[grunts and pants]
[crying] It's beautiful.
Hi, I'm Mick.
[Mick grunting]
"With the monster vanquished,
Garima and her beloved Buck
"made passionate love
in the ruins of the city."
[Mick groaning]
Okay, let's go, now.
[Garima grunting]
[Mick sighs]
[exhales]
Where is everyone?
Your compatriots grew tired of waiting.
Hm, sorry about that,
got a bit messy in there.
I'm gonna take this with me.
Oh, please.
It clearly likes you.
Your creation was magnificent.
I was thinking about a fourth boob.
Three was plenty.
Huh. Listen, Honda-san.
Forget about the octopus.
Lizards. Lizards are king.
[speaking Japanese]
[chuckles]
This girl can drink.
Care for a nip?
I know it won't quite
make up for the bottle...
Bottles that I pillaged.
- It's a start.
- [Charlie] Look,
wasn't too keen on what
you were doing out there.
Hunting fugitives,
but if someone's got to play copper,
it is a small comfort
knowing that she has a heart.
Don't tell the others,
they'll never listen to me again.
[chuckles]
[snoring]
I should've known you'd have
an eye for talent.
Just like your old man.
Your creature handler, she's great.
[Nate] Oh, yeah, she's gonna...
She's gonna fit right in.
Hey, look, Nate.
I just wish you'd
told me what was going on.
Honestly, I thought I could put out
the fire before anyone noticed.
Ah. Now I know how you must've felt
all those times
you had to duck out of
family gatherings.
You're the guy they called
if there was a disaster.
And I may have also been looking
for a way to get out of the house.
You old so-and-so.
Sir.
I know what you're thinking,
but I can assure you
that this will never happen again.
You're damn right it won't.
I'm gonna green light additional funding
to fast track the completion
of your containment facility.
Well, thank you so much, sir,
that will help a lot.
And your mother is gonna kill us.
Not necessarily.
Perks of time travel.
We can portal back into
the second after we left.
That's fantastic.
Yeah.
Let's make like a tree and leave.
Hm, not sure that's how it goes, but...
How are you feeling?
Hunky-dory, love.
Hell, in fact I feel like
I have a new lease on life.
How are you feeling?
Better.
Huh.
You know, my whole life,
I always believed my power was evil.
And then my dad died,
and I feared using it.
But...
I saved you, and for
the first time in my life,
my magic doesn't scare me.
Good.
[grunts]
John,
that man I saw.
Who was he?
The past.
Ray.
Hey, cheers, big man.
And now I'm gonna go and satiate
my most wonderful habit,
and have a smoke.
What?
No, no, don't ruin it.
We just cured you.
I can't believe that worked.
- Well, I, for one...
- Always wanna see the best in people.
Even me.
Yeah.
I should be on my way.
- Okay.
Um...
Run as far as you can,
don't tell me when or where,
just go and stay hidden.
But your team will know you let me go.
- Again.
- I don't care about that,
I care about you.
And I want you to be free.
This is the Time Bureau.
Nora, what are you doing?
You gotta get of here.
I can't keep running.
You want me to be free?
Repentance is my path to freedom.
It's time for me to pay for my past.
Nora Darhk, hands up.
Get on the ground.
Get on the ground!
"Garima was as strong
as she was stunning,
"and with her by his side,
"Buck had at last
vanquished his true enemy.
"Fear."
Huh.
[all cheering]
[cell phone ringing]
It's okay, Dad, take it.
Take it.
[Dorothy] Look at this.
Thanks for getting back to me.
I know it's hard to get away
during the holiday.
These creatures are controllable,
I've seen it.
I don't care how much it costs,
we're going to make this happen.
Project Hades is go.
[theme music playing]