Previously on "Legend's of Tomorrow"...
Mallus wasn't the only
prisoner to escape.
Now there's magic.
An unknown number of other
dangerous magical beings
got spat out across the timeline
and now must be sent to hell.
She's a shapeshifter.
- What did you do to me?
- Lobotomy of sorts.
Your shapeshifting days
are over, sweetheart.
No!
She definitely isn't Amaya.
Did you just hear that?
Judy, relax.
There's nothing out here.
Tonight it's just you and me, okay?
Wait a second.
Don't tell me that
the fearless Ms. Lance
is scared of a little horror film.
No, I love horror movies,
and I watched them obsessively as a kid,
so how could I have missed this gem?
"Swamp Thaaaang."
Never heard of it. And
what's with all the As?
Okay, let me look.
Okay, "Swamp Thaaaang."
Apparently there are four As in the name
because it's the fourth
film in the franchise.
The A.V. Club gave it a D-plus, saying,
"The production design is as
lazy as the action staging."
- Harsh.
- Yeah.
"Based on real-life
tragic events that occurred
at Camp Ogawa, Maine,
in the summer of 1995"?
Gideon.
- We're in my room, babe.
- Right.
Speak of the devil.
Sorry to interrupt,
Captain, but I've detected
new magical events in the timeline.
It seems that a number of children
went missing from a summer camp...
Let me guess. Camp Ogawa, Maine.
Precisely.
Looks like the handiwork
of one of our fugitives.
Shall I plot a course to 1995, then?
And while you're at it,
fabricate a mess of bug spray.
I'm on my way.
Well, how about that?
We almost got to spend
two whole uninterrupted hours together.
How about...
you come with me?
Summer camp?
As in bug bites, bunk
beds, and mean girls?
No, summer camp, as in camp fires,
sing-alongs, and friendship bracelets.
Camp's the best. You'll love it.
Pinkie swear.
What are you doing?
It's something you do when you're a kid.
It's like a promise.
What?
Come on. No, pinkie.
- Yes!
- Weird.
This will be a great way
for us to spend some more time together,
and, plus, we get to make sure
that doesn't happen in real life.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
I talked to Nate,
and he's got things
covered at the Bureau.
He and Gary have their hands full
with all the magical
creatures popping up.
Nate and Gary are in charge.
Well, anyways, I'm glad that he's there
because we've got something I
really don't want him to see.
What's that?
Amaya.
It just looks like her.
- Did you say "it"?
- She's a shapeshifter.
We found her in London, 1977.
Hmm. Hello.
- Not much of a talker, I see.
- Oh, she talks.
Go to hell!
Just her way of saying "hello."
Oh, let me out of here, you bastards!
She's still adjusting to her new home.
Maybe it's the food.
But Constantine sent the other fugitives
you encountered to hell, so...
Well, she's not exactly
a bloodthirsty unicorn.
Or an evil fairy godmother.
But you decided to keep
the shapeshifter because...?
Oh. To exploit her for information
about the inter-dimensional prison
that she's been trapped in
to help us track down other fugitives.
That is...
exactly what we are doing.
100%.
Isn't that right, Zari?
Yeah, yeah.
Um, I'm... I'm gathering
that intel as we speak.
Hm. I love the initiative, team.
Yeah.
Gentlemen.
Ooh, Director Sharpe.
Joining us, are we?
- Is that a problem?
- Not for me, love.
Good, because we are
headed back to the '90s
to infiltrate a place called Camp Ogawa.
Oh, sneaking into a
military facility, are we?
Actually, it's a summer camp for kids.
Oh, I loved summer camp.
Everyone used to call me, Kid Counselor.
Bet you took that as a
compliment, too, didn't you, mate?
Well, because of my
leadership skills, obviously.
Right? That's why.
Mm-hmm, yeah.
So, uh, any idea of
what kind of foul beast
we're up against, then?
Well, based on... research
Sarah and I have been doing,
we could be looking for
a swampy monster thing.
According to the timeline,
before the end of summer,
several kids went missing,
never to be seen again.
Well, I happen to know a Swamp Thing.
But then again, Maine is way
too far North for that muppet.
Well, we used to use the buddy system
to make sure everyone was safe.
And this is where Nate
would say, "I'm your buddy,"
and we'd do a fist bump
or a silly jig or...
Well, we are shorthanded,
so I need you to partner up with John.
Oh, don't worry, dreamboat.
I've had stranger bedfellows than you.
But just so you know,
I'm not one to get all
gussied up for a gig, all right?
Oh, they may take my coat,
but you will never take my...
Nope. And lose the tie.
Oh, you have got to be kidding me.
Fine.
One time, but it's only for the kids.
Yeah, that's the camp spirit.
Are these outfits really necessary?
- Girl...
- Come on. Gideon made us
official Camp Ogawa counselor uniforms
using archival photos
so that we could fit in.
What are you guys doing
just standing around?
Hi, we are the new camp counselors.
Sorry to show up unannounced.
Well, Freckles, the name's Paula Cooper.
I'm the director here.
Welcome to Camp Ogawa.
My right-hand man, Chad Stephens,
will show you around.
Chad!
Get over here.
What's up?
Chad, you marble cut of prime beef,
give these new counselors the tour.
Cool. All right, hey,
let's bounce over this way.
I'll give you the 411
on this place, huh?
Yeah.
What we need are snipers
on that ridgeline,
spotters on the ground,
and an exfil site
for when we bag the creature.
Not a bad plan, Sharpie.
I'll put a protection
spell around my perimeter
to keep out the nasties.
Best offense is a strong defense.
- Hmm.
- Mm-hmm.
So, as you can see,
Camp Ogawa is a miserable place,
and Paula runs it like a POW camp.
Not!
Oh, God, not a '90s "not" joke.
It's like comic comfort food.
I'm sorry, I couldn't help
but admire your lanyard.
Did you make that yourself?
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
Yeah, along with 21
required merit badges,
I also went on to get certification
in nuclear science and dentistry.
Oh, snap. I've got
some serious competition
for coolest counselor this summer, huh?
Ah...
What about you? You
got any special skills?
Martial arts.
Ah. Hwah!
Sorry, it's just so fresh.
It's like, Jackie Chan, you know?
I prefer knives and swords.
Right, yeah. Point taken.
- "Point taken."
- Ha ha! Good one, bro.
Anyway, let's head over here, all right?
I'm gonna assign you your cabins.
It's gonna be a heck of a summer.
Okay. He'll grow on you.
Greetings, members of Newton Cabin
I am Counselor Ray,
and the mysterious gentleman
behind you is Counselor John.
Cheers, lads.
Well, today's subject
is wilderness survival,
which includes tracking
and orienteering.
Who's excited?
Well, you will be, okay?
Two words to remember when tracking...
"displacement" and "direction."
Now, Counselor John will demonstrate
the kind of inadvertent
markers people leave behind
while walking in the woods.
And...
Counselor John is missing already.
See how easy it is to get
lost in the woods, gentlemen?
- What's up, Franklin Cabin?
- Whoo!
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
We are in the house. I
am Sara, and this is Ava.
We are your camp counselors.
Now, I was thinking, we
need a secret handshake.
Yeah.
Something really cool that only we know.
- Yeah.
- So cool.
- What are you doing?
- Bonding.
How is that supposed to keep them safe
from what's in the woods?
It allows us to form
a meaningful connection
and them to feel like
they're part of a team.
They aren't gonna be a part
of anything if they're dead.
- Ava.
- We can go back
to the fun and games once
we catch the creature, yes?
All right, ladies...
change in plan.
Today we're going to celebrate
your first day of camp
by using safety and discipline, got it?
Now, when I blow this whistle,
you are to run... not walk...
To your respective beds.
But it's still daytime.
It will feel like nighttime
when your eyes are closed.
Now move!
Very nice.
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm creating a protective
barrier to catch monsters.
- "Monsters"?
- Yeah.
You know, the kind that
slice your stomach open
and eat your intestines for supper.
Getting those kids to bed was
a lot easier than I expected.
You know, I'm really glad I came.
I just feel bad... we're
ruining camp for these kids.
It's such an important time.
Well, I didn't realize
you were so gung-ho
about this whole camp thing.
I was even Color Captain one year.
Hmm?
Summer after eighth grade.
I really stuck it to Suzy Smith
and the Green Team that year.
- Sounds magical.
- It was.
Unfortunately, we're here
to stop magic, my love.
Well, with us guarding their cabin
and Constantine's perimeter,
at least no Swampy Monster
is getting into this camp tonight.
Who's there?
Relax, Lenise. It's just me.
Zack.
So what do you want to do?
Have you ever kissed anyone before?
Zack?
Beautiful morning.
Yeah, sorry to burst your
summer-loving bubble, mate,
but we're missing one
of our young charges.
His name is Zack or something.
Well, are you sure you counted right?
Because based on your whiskey cologne,
- I think you're still drunk.
- No, he's right.
Yeah, a girl is missing
from our cabin, too,
even after I put the
fear of God in them.
Obviously, there's something wrong
with Constantine's booby trap.
Are you off your trolley, mate?
My spell was designed to keep
the monsters from getting in,
not children getting out.
They must have snuck out
in the middle of the night.
Snuck out? Why would they sneak out?
To make out, duh.
Well, I suppose we should
notify the camp director.
Okay, guys, so...
Oh, don't worry about those kids.
They're gonna be just fine.
Uh, shouldn't we mount
a search party or...
They couldn't have gotten too far.
Look, Freckles, this happens every year.
Kids under the influence
of their hormones
go off into the woods at night.
Just watch. They'll eventually
get hungry and tired,
and they'll come back.
Now go out there and do some counseling.
Well, someone gives precisely zero craps
about the safety of our campers.
I guarantee you one of these kids
knows where the other two went.
How can you be so sure?
Because when I was in camp,
we used to hide stuff from
the counselors all the time.
We just need to figure out
how to get them to talk.
Circle of trust creates a safe space
for us to share our
secrets without judgment.
Now, take each other's hands.
- Now I want you...
- Yeah, sorry to butt in, lads.
But, uh, can I have a
word with you for a second?
I want you to meditate
on the word "openness,"
and I'll be right back.
You're interrup...
You're interrupting the flow.
Yeah, well, apologies
to you and your flow,
but all of your psychobabble...
That ain't gonna cut the mustard
with the young ones, mate.
Let me show you how it's done.
Right, then, which one
of you whippersnappers
wants to be hypnotized?
Me, me, me, me!
Alexis, you and Lenise
are besties, right?
We were partners in
last year's talent show.
She didn't show up at
roll call this morning.
I'm worried. Do you know
where she might have gone?
All right, ladies, on your feet.
Report to the front of your
bed, arms by your sides, now.
What is with the police lineup?
This is summer camp,
not boot camp, remember?
You are too soft on these kids.
Children crave authority.
Besides, my way will be quicker.
That's it. Look at my watch.
Now, where did your mate
Zack run off to last night?
He didn't say.
But I hope he didn't go
near the outdoor showers.
Why?
What's by the outdoor showers?
That's where I hid my
Victoria's Secret catalog.
Ah.
Your friend Lenise snuck
out of the cabin last night.
And no one's going anywhere
until I find out where she went.
But the ice cream social
is in, like, five minutes.
Well, then you better,
like, start talking, Kiana,
or you're gonna have to
scrape the bottom of the carton
for what's left.
Last night Zack said something
about meeting someone in the woods.
Where in the woods exactly?
A baseball field.
Only, there's no
baseball field out there.
Well, that's all right. Keep digging.
He kept talking about making
it to first base with a girl.
But who plays baseball in the dark?
She probably went to the
same place your style went.
You could use a makeover,
like, head to toe.
Ms. Tomaz, the prisoner
is growing quite unruly.
Tell her to knock herself out.
Aw. I take that back.
Damn it, not on my watch.
Whoo! Ha ha!
Okay, I feel like we got
off on the wrong foot.
It's just that you're
wearing my friend's face,
and it's a little
unsettling, given your...
general demeanor.
Look...
I didn't love it at
first when I got here,
but I found my place.
You can too.
Take a look in the mirror, sweetheart.
It's not my face that
should be unsettling.
You're the one putting things in cages.
So how many girls
has the missus made cry so
far, or have you lost count?
Ava's interrogation techniques
aren't going to work on them.
They'd rather take their secrets
to the grave than squeal.
Anything with the boys?
Oh, those boys aren't hiding a thing.
They're open books,
if those books were written
by hapless fools, that is.
If I could just become one of them,
another 12-year-old camper,
I could get these
girls to talk like that.
I do believe that you've just sparked
an idea there, Ms. Lance.
End of the road, kid.
In your cage.
Bloke like you doesn't
strike me as a jailer.
I believe we're more
alike than you think.
You look like you've been on the inside.
That's right.
And how do you sleep at night...
hanging out with these
jailer mates of yours?
Alcohol.
Oh, hey. I made an
additional list of suspects
- I want to question.
- Ava...
Look, I know that you just want them
to have fun, all right?
But the fact of the matter is,
there is a monster out there
hunting down these kids,
and these girls are
stonewalling us, okay?
Counselor Ava?
Yes?
I'm ready to tell you
what's really going on.
Go on, honey. Spill the beans.
It won't stop unless you do something.
What won't stop?
The monster that lives under
the dock... the lake beast.
Who's the lake beast?
Years ago, at this very camp,
some mean kids played a prank on a boy,
and he drowned in the lake.
And now every year he
returns to get his revenge.
And so you think the lake
beast took your friends?
They say the only way to make him appear
is to go to the dock alone
and call his name three times.
Sweetie, you are so
brave, and I promise you,
the lake beast won't be
getting anyone tonight, okay?
Guys.
Guys, I think I see a
Northern Saw-whet Owl.
Ray, focus.
Fine. I'll save it for
my bird-watching journal.
Okay, you're in the clear, Ava.
Stupid bird.
Okay, let's get this over with.
Lake Beast, Lake Beast, Lake Beast.
Hmm.
Guys, this feels like a bust to me.
Ah, it was just a bloody prank.
- Oh!
- Go, go, go.
You okay?
Nice night for a swim,
though, eh, Sharpie?
Those girls are...
monsters!
After we left the lake last night,
another one of our campers went missing.
Another one of ours is missing, too.
That makes four in total.
They must have snuck out
to meet up with each other
and never made it back.
Yeah, well, I don't know about you lot,
but I'm not just sitting around here
waiting for the monster
to go and get another kid.
We better split up.
All right, you two check the
woods for the missing kids.
Ava and I... We'll stay watch here.
Hey, wait, buddy system!
I heard about last night.
It's majorly uncool.
Who knew kids could be so mean?
They've been calling me Lake Beast
behind my back all day.
- Excuse me, Lake Beast.
- And to my face.
Okay. Hey, that is enough, ladies.
The joke is over.
It's time for you to behave, or
else your cabin will be banned
from the July Jamboree.
The only way we are going
to get any information
from these girls is to
infiltrate their clique.
How are we supposed to
do that? We're not kids.
Funny you should say that.
Constantine gave me a potion
that would turn us into kids
only temporarily.
You're kidding, right?
Wha... Even if it works, Sara,
I wouldn't have any idea
how to act like a kid
because I've never been one.
All my childhood memories
are fake, remember?
How are we going to find the
kids with that dangly thing?
You know, this ritual usually works best
when someone isn't
yammering in my ear hole.
Well, you want to find the kids,
we got to do it the old-fashioned way.
Study their tracks.
It's a good thing I came prepared,
because one step in the
wrong direction here,
and you'll be traveling
for miles in the wrong...
Damn it, you Nandy Pandy,
I said I need silence.
Oh, you meant right now.
I'm sorry, I thought you meant...
Why are you being such a jerk?
Because you shouldn't even be out here
chasing a magical creature, all right?
It's too dangerous.
Too dangerous?
You're lucky you're out here with me,
because I can keep us alive
on bugs and berries alone.
You know, this has nothing to
do with survival in the wild
and everything to do with
surviving magical creatures
and those who dabble in the dark arts.
I'll have you know, I am no
stranger to the world of magic.
Yeah.
Oh, don't think I haven't
heard how Nora Darhk had you
eating out of the palm
of her wicked little hand.
Oh, I bet she didn't even have to ask
for the time stone, did she?
No, you just gave it away
like biscuits at tea time.
Nora and I have a mutual
respect for each other.
It's not like I was
tripping over myself...
What is that?
No doubt left behind
by the magical beast.
Who sheds its skin
after it eats the kids?
What are we looking for?
Some sort of snake monster?
The answer is in this book.
Is that a magical Audubon guide?
Neat-o.
Mmm.
It's good. What is it?
Hooch. I spent a little
time in a Siberian gulag.
Got a taste for it.
Where I was it felt like 500 years.
Time worked differently in that realm.
Oh, I've been in a lot of
cages, but not a magical one.
What was it like?
The inside of my cage
was a constant battle
between creatures from
your worst nightmare.
I, uh, got to know some of
them better than I wanted to.
It was a dismal and a dark dimension,
like nothing here on Earth.
And I'll be damned if
I'm ever going back.
Well, cheers to that.
Friendship bracelet?
No, it's an "I'm sorry" bracelet.
I shouldn't have run off like that.
It's just that you know I'm not normal,
and I think you hit
a nerve or something.
No, I'm sorry.
I never even thought about the fact
that you'd never been a kid.
- Yeah.
- But this is really good.
Ugh. I confiscated it from Alexis.
See, I'm weird. I...
Do you know that those two
actors who are my parents...
I keep a picture of them
on my desk in my office
just so I can try to
feel a little bit normal.
Yeah, that is anything but normal.
Yeah.
Guys. I think we've ID'd our monster.
Constantine and I found a skin suit
shed by something called a shtriga.
- Come again?
- A shtriga.
It's a vampiric witch.
It feeds off the life force of children.
Bloody brilliant setting
up shop at summer camp.
Ah, there's some good news, sort of.
Uh, it says here the shtriga
feeds slowly off its prey
draining its life energy
over a course of days,
which means the missing
kids could still be alive.
Then it's on you guys to find them.
All right.
Okay, and it's on us
to protect these girls.
Now, I know you think I'm crazy,
but what if the best way to protect them
is by becoming one of them
and lure the creature out?
We'll be the bait.
What if Constantine's
potion doesn't work on me?
There's only one way to find out.
And if it does, I'll be with
you every step of the way.
Show you the ropes.
Teach you how to be a kid.
Pinkie swear?
Pinkie swear.
All right, lights out, everyone!
Hey, that means you, too, Hopper Cabin.
Don't make me come in there.
- Do you feel anything yet?
- Mm...
No.
Maybe it doesn't work.
The pretty lights tell me otherwise.
Hey, what are you two doing in here?
Oh, snap.
Where did you guys come
from out of the blue?
Got kicked out of Clark Cabin
for putting a frog under
Christi Donovan's pillow.
You should have heard her scream.
Cool.
And you?
I was kicked out
'cause I was caught
reading after lights out.
Reading? Lame.
Uh, her counselors only
thought she was reading,
but really she was writing
a letter to her boyfriend.
He lives in France.
This year's counselors are the worst.
Especially Lake Beast.
Yeah, I heard she smells bad.
Hey...
Um, yeah, I heard she
looked really funny
when she fell into the water.
But you're lucky she
didn't catch pneumonia.
That's a very serious illness.
Uh, sure.
You must have had balls
to survive that hellhole.
Did what I had to...
Shapeshifted into whatever monster
would keep the others off my back.
But you know exactly what it's like
pretending to be something
worse than you are to survive.
Well, there's that.
And there's finding someone you trust.
I did time in supermax
with my old partner.
It's harder to plot against a team.
I spent all my time
shapeshifting and running.
I never stuck around
one place long enough
to find anyone that I could trust.
Well, you got to start somewhere.
Hey, it's me, Sara. You
guys still out there?
Sara? Potion actually worked?
You didn't know if it was going to work
before you gave us the potion?
Well, of course I didn't.
I never tested it on humans, have I?
Damn it, John.
Well, just see it like
this... You two have now
turned yourselves into
irresistible shtriga bait.
So any suggestions on
how a couple of kids
can take on a magical child-eating hag?
Well, if you're in a pinch,
you can always try capsicum annuum...
More commonly known as cayenne pepper.
Witches hate the stuff.
But you'll be fine. Cheers, love.
Great.
But where are we going
to get cayenne pepper?
Follow my lead.
The shtriga's lair can't be far now.
Look, a camper must have tried
to hide from the shtriga here.
What are you doing? Oh, a spell?
Yep.
Ah, will-o the wisp.
Little bugger will lead us
to whoever owns that shirt.
Well, go on then, light the way.
Ha! Look at us... A pair
of magical detectives.
Oh, and I was beginning
to think you were all right
till you went and said that.
You know, there are other
dabblers of the dark arts
out there who think that I'm all right.
Referring to Nora Darhk, are we?
You best stay away
from that witch, mate.
Not even your big heart can
keep you safe from someone
who's wrestled with literal demons.
What about you? You're one of us now.
You even dressed up for a little while.
You've wrestled with
demons, and you're good.
Just listen to me, all right?
You know, I had a friend like you.
Someone good, someone who trusted me.
Be smarter than him, all right?
Save yourself, Ray Palmer,
because people like me and Nora Darhk...
we're bloody hell for people like you.
Truth or dare?
Truth.
I... think you meant dare.
Dare?
Dare. I mean dare.
I dare you to sneak out of the cabin
and break into the mess hall.
But to prove that you
didn't chicken out,
you have to bring us something
back from the kitchen.
Ooh.
Well, this must be the place.
Alexis, who would you
rather have babies with?
Jonathan Taylor Thomas or Mario Lopez?
Mm...
I ran into some trouble.
I knew it. She chickened out.
I tried to carry more,
but I could only sneak
out with two of these.
I know you missed the
ice cream social, so...
ice cream social is coming to you.
Rocky road and mint chocolate chip...
You're the best ever.
And I have something just for us.
That's my girl.
Oh, I've seen enough
horror movie trailers
to know this won't end well.
Those films are nothing
compared to the horrors
you might see in real life.
Are we too late?
Uh, we'll need an incantation,
a crystal, and a conduit
to draw their pilfered
life force from the shtriga
and back into their bodies.
Now, just, uh, follow my
lead and do everything I say.
We really needed this.
Camp's been kind of rough this year.
What do you mean?
It's okay. You can talk to us.
We're super worried
about Lenise and Meredith.
We didn't want to say
anything for the longest time.
We thought we'd get in
trouble and ruin everything.
Ruin what?
The midnight meet-up. It's a tradition.
Every summer, girls take turns
choosing guys they like to
meet up with in the woods.
There's a string that
starts near the flagpole,
and it leads out into the meeting spot.
It changes every year.
So they meet up, and what's
supposed to happen next?
Well, you're supposed to have
your first kiss and come back.
But Lenise and Meredith never came back.
We got to be getting close, right?
What was that?
It's way past lights out.
What punishment should
I cook up for you?
Come here, you two.
Get off me, you crusty old witch!
My eyes!
Is she dead?
All right, our team's dealing
with something called a shtriga.
Do you know anything that
could help them fight it?
Oh, a shtriga.
Very intelligent and very deadly.
If you want my help,
it's going to cost you.
Great. Will that come in
the form of another haiku,
or can we expect something
a little more detailed?
What's that? What was that eye thing?
According to legend,
shtrigas are nasty old women,
but the one that I met in prison...
The one that you're looking for...
Is beautiful.
And he's a bloke.
Hmm.
What the hell are you doing?
Hey, you don't have
another bathroom break
for, oh, that's right, never,
since you tried to break my face.
It is now or never.
Fine. Whatever.
Guys, this shtriga thing
is not an old woman.
What's going on out here?
You are looking for a
young, handsome dude.
Are you ready, big man?
On with the show, then.
What did you guys do to her?
We didn't do anything.
Look, it's not safe
for you guys out here.
Okay? You're coming with me.
We can take care of ourselves.
You're coming with me
whether you like it or not.
You think you're so tough?
I don't think it. I know it.
It's working.
It worked.
Ooh, that was worse than a hangover.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Come on, lad, wake up.
Wake up, lad. Wake up. Come on, son.
Damn it.
Bollocks.
I'm not losing another kid.
What are you doing?
John!
John. Come on.
John? Come on, John.
John.
Ugh.
Damn it.
Any of you got... Got a light?
- What happened?
- You saved him.
You saved Randall.
Ah, that's good.
I'm gonna get you back to the ship.
I'm not sure how I'm gonna
get the rest of you out.
We found you guys.
We got worried when you
didn't show up for dinner.
Those kids look famished.
Get them water and electrolytes, stat.
And that gurney we just
made out of rope and wood...
Bring it in.
Had a hunch it would come in handy.
How did you find us?
Displacement and direction,
just like you taught us.
Good job, Toby.
John's potion will be wearing off soon,
and it's back to our normal lives,
where we're only responsible
for babysitting Rory and Gary.
I'd like to thank you
for giving me real childhood memories.
To be honest, these memories
have been kind of awful...
mostly awkward, but...
totally awesome.
I mean, it wouldn't be childhood
without all of the above.
I'm happy it was with you.
And considering all the trouble
those kids went through for a kiss...
I'm guessing no childhood
would be complete without one.
Couldn't help but
notice our magical friend
is not where she's supposed to be.
Oh, she's not?
Rory, do you know anything about that?
You don't pay me enough
to be a stinkin' prison guard.
I don't pay you anything.
Well, I let the fake Amaya go.
Why would you do that?
Oh, in order to...
have an extreme makeover.
Thanks for the shtriga tip.
Well, if you had your
hands full with a shtriga,
I figured you'd need my help
with whatever you plebs face next.
Sounds like a mutually
beneficial partnership.
One condition, though...
I never set foot in
that cage ever again.
Got it?
Mr. Constantine's body is
rejecting my treatments.
His odds of survival are bleak.
John, what you did out
there was pretty selfless.
I told you you were good.
That's not good for you.
Get some rest, John.
Gideon, give him the good stuff.
Oh, Gideon.
That's nice, love. We should party...
He's getting worse.
The magic he used to save that
camper was pretty powerful.
Well, if magic has him on death's door,
then maybe magic can save him.
I think I know someone who can help.
But I have no idea how to find her.
Just one final ingredient.
I trust you'll find that
my potion is magical.
Ugh. You call that soup?
Oh, I-I can start over.
The Ren Fair opens in an hour.
You know what? Forget it.
It's not like folks come to
this tent for the food anyways.
I'm sorry?
They come for the lusty wenches.
I'm...
I'm a witch.
Okay, well, as long as
it's a lusty witch, okay?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --