In 2166,
an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan
is opposed
by the body I had sworn
my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be
remembered as legends.
Previously, on
Legends of Tomorrow...
I am a Time Master.
Making discrete alterations
to the timeline is what I do.
Half of what you've told us
about this mission
turned out to be lies.
Lewis Snart, convicted of
larceny, armed robbery.
You and your entire family
are criminals.
Things are complicated
with family.
The Lazarus Pit brought me back,
but it left me
with this need to kill.
You're Priestess Chay-Ara,
I'm Prince Khufu,
and we're lovers.
I know you're worth the wait.
Well, I say
we kick Savage's ass.
- For Carter.
Who are you?
The man who's here to kill you.
We've arrived in
Leipzig, Germany,
the most current location
for Vandal Savage.
And by the way, Captain, you are
urgently needed in the MedBay.
- I thought she'd stabilized.
- As did I.
Carter! Where's Carter?
He's gone, Kendra. I'm so sorry.
Gideon, turn that
bloody noise off!
- Yes, Captain.
- What happened?
Ms. Saunders appears
to have had a complication.
Yeah, I know,
but what kind of complication?
How could you leave him?
- Is she...
- MedBay gave her a sedative.
But obviously her condition
is worsening.
Pieces of the dagger
have apparently broken off
and are, as we speak,
en route to her heart.
Can't we just time-jump
into the future
where they got the stuff
that can fix her?
This ship is from
that very same future
and has, thus far,
been unsuccessful in saving her.
Kendra wouldn't survive
the time-jump anyway.
I pay attention.
To sum up, Carter Hall's dead.
The girlfriend's
not too far behind.
Vandal Savage is sitting pretty
in 1975,
which we're all now stuck in.
That how the plan's
supposed to work, Rip?
Obviously, not.
But the mission is simple.
We stop Vandal Savage
here in the past
and we save the future.
Simple don't mean easy, Captain.
Oh, I never said it was.
The benefit of being
a Time Master is
that the length
and breadth of history
gives one perspective.
I've seen darker days.
I've seen men of steel die
and dark knights fall.
And even then, I accomplished
my mission, no matter what.
Gideon, what is our status?
When the Waverider
was attacked by Chronos,
the Jumpship was damaged.
Unless you make repairs,
we will be unable to--
Wait, wait. "Jumpship"?
It's a small
expeditionary vessel
at the belly of the Waverider.
You're a mechanic!
You have a look at it.
Auto-mechanic. Uh...
Spaceship.
Okay, if you've got
a set of wrenches,
I'll see what I can do.
What about the rest of us?
Do we just sit?
Capital idea, Mr. Rory.
You're not nearly as thick
as most people say.
Thick. Does that mean "stupid"?
Is that your son?
He looks like you.
Sorry. Trained by
the League of Assassins.
Sneaking up on people
is kind of our thing.
I'd like to be alone
for a moment.
You don't actually
have a plan, do you?
And that speech wasn't about
convincing us.
It was about convincing you.
Didn't work, did it?
Not particularly, no.
Hence my desire to be alone.
Well, we can't kill Savage.
Oh, I see you've grasped the concept
of immortality. Well done.
Maybe we can slow him down.
Ra's al Ghul taught me
a thing or two
about fighting
powerful adversaries.
"If you can't kill your enemy,
weaken him.
"If you can't cut off his head,
"take his heart."
Mr. al Ghul was quite the poet.
Back at the weapons auction,
Savage was trying to
sell his nuke.
Money is power.
Take away Savage's fortune,
and he's just a regular guy
with a really long life span.
It certainly would set
his plan for world domination
back a few decades.
So, where does Vandal Savage
keep his money in 1975?
The broken knife
fragments are moving through
her circulatory system.
And if you'll notice these,
they're closing in
towards her heart.
- So, what do we do?
- The fragments are minuscule.
Even the ship's technology isn't
capable of neutralizing them.
Fortunately, there's
a technology onboard that is.
The Atom suit.
I can shrink down,
slip into her bloodstream
and use the photon canons
to vaporize the knife fragments.
You'd be pushing
the suit's limits.
We should run some tests,
make sure
this is the best plan of action.
This isn't the ivory tower,
Professor. We don't have time.
- Listen to me, Raymond.
- I'm not your student anymore.
You were never my student!
Just because
you don't remember me--
If you had been my student,
I'd have taught you
the principles of using
scientific analysis,
not this bravado!
There isn't time. I'm going in.
Gideon, where's Savage's money now?
Dr. Boardman theorized
that Savage entrusted it
to the Brümberg Group,
the oldest bank in the world.
I'll go tell
the rest of the team.
That won't be necessary.
I'm going alone.
I can't have any more blood
on my hands.
Except for your own? You can't
go in there without backup.
Look, I brought you all with me
under false pretenses.
Carter would still be alive
if I hadn't convinced him
to come.
No one's on the ship
that doesn't want to be here.
But I can't risk the whole team.
Fine. Just me.
And if it helps,
I'm not giving you a choice.
I'm going with you to that bank.
Somebody say "bank"?
Your services
aren't required, Mr. Snart.
This is purely reconnaissance.
We know how to case banks.
We're practically bankers.
Except we take the money out.
Yes, and when I need someone
to steal something,
you'll be the first to know,
I assure you.
Listen, Englishman,
I'm getting bored
being stuck on this tin can.
And when I get bored,
I make bad decisions.
Now, now, now, we're all
on the same side here.
My hotheaded friend and I
just wanna be helpful,
that's all.
Duly noted.
You should've let me punch him.
Yeah, then we
wouldn't have gotten this.
Mmm-hmm.
- You ready?
- Yes.
All right, where am I headed?
You're exiting
the tracheal artery.
You should see
the first fragment.
No sign of it. Did I miss it?
It's the size of an iceberg.
It seems highly unlikely
that you could miss it.
That's probably what they said
on the Titanic.
I think I found it.
Looks like all those years
of playing Asteroids
is about to pay off.
Her vitals are improving.
It seems to be working.
There are still
19 more fragments.
Raymond. Raymond,
you're not done.
I'm losing core containment.
Plot me a course
out of here, now!
Excuse me.
We'd like to deposit
some family heirlooms.
I'm sorry, we're a private bank.
We don't secure valuables
worth less than $10 million.
Well, I'm sure
this will suffice.
Doubloons from the
wreck of the Esplinade.
They've been appraised
at $10 million, apiece.
Such a pleasure.
You won't regret your decision.
The Brümberg Group is known
for its discretion.
I'm sure there'll be a fair deal
of paperwork to sign.
Not too much. We like to
cut through the red tape here.
Let me get this to one of
our safe deposit boxes,
and I'll get my secretary
moving on this paperwork.
Interesting.
There are records here
referring to something
called the Vessel.
We have a problem.
Yes, I know. None of
Savage's funds are in this bank.
I'm working on
locating this Vessel,
but I'm not sure if I'll do so
before our new friend returns.
To kill us.
The receptionist had
a silent Beretta under her desk.
The guards,
South African mercenaries.
You can tell by the
initiation burns on their neck.
And our new friend here
has calluses on his right hand
consistent with being
a Kuroda-trained swordsman.
How do you know?
Because I have
the same calluses.
Which means
they've probably figured out
that we are not Rockefellers
who just came into
their inheritance.
Oh, don't be so alarmist.
Calluses are hardly
definitive proof of anything.
Pretty sure they made us.
Well, if this is how
you treat your customers,
we might just have to take
our business elsewhere.
I thought I specifically
said "no weapons."
You can thank me later.
Exactly how many knives
do you have?
Seems you brought a knife
to a sword fight.
Sara.
Sara. Sara, don't!
I didn't get anything
from the computer.
We need him alive!
What the hell
happened back there?
You know I'm a killer.
That's why you put me
in your little group.
I didn't witness just
a killer at work, Sara.
What I saw was an animal.
You are the last person
on this ship to judge anyone!
This is not judgment, Sara.
It is concern.
I thought you knew
how I was resurrected
and what it did to me.
I know you were
restored by something
called the Lazarus Pit.
Well, apparently,
there's a downside
to being brought back to life.
My friend Thea
calls it a bloodlust.
And I think that's being
too generous.
And so is calling me an animal.
I'm a monster.
- Ah! Nice ride.
- Huh.
Yeah, it can hit a Mach 3
in a walk. Pretty cool.
How do you know
so much about it?
Little thing called
an instruction manual.
Did you read the part
about how to fly this thing?
Maybe. Why?
We're gonna take a
little sojourn to Central City.
There's a priceless jewel
that needs to be freed
from captivity.
You want me to help you steal
something. No, man, I'll pass.
Not exactly asking, Jax.
Wow. Carter is dead. Kendra is
this close to joining him,
and Vandal Savage is still alive
and out there doing
God-knows-what.
And all you can think about
is stealing some diamond?
It's an emerald.
Is there anything you think
about other than yourself?
Yes, money.
No, I'm not helping you guys
steal anything.
So, if you want to shoot me,
then shoot me.
Can I shoot him?
You got a pair on you, kid.
I respect that.
So, no shooting.
Look, you don't actually have to
help us steal anything.
We just need to
get to Central City.
We'll be there and back before
anyone knows we're even gone.
Man, even if I wanted to help,
and I'm not saying that I do,
this thing's got
a security lock-out.
We need an access key.
You can't tell me you don't wanna see
what this baby can do.
I believe I've determined a way
to more efficiently track
the fragments still inside
Ms. Saunders' body.
Next time,
you'll be better prepared.
There won't be a next time.
Can't you fix the suit?
It's not the suit.
Raymond, you mustn't
be discouraged.
We're scientists. We learn
from failure and we keep going.
Kendra isn't a lab experiment.
She's a person.
I know.
You need to have confidence
this will work.
Well, I don't. I can't save her.
Based on what evidence?
Are we not empirical thinkers?
Dr. Palmer, exactly
how many people have you lost?
One.
Who did you lose?
Someone close to you.
Who was she, Raymond?
For someone who
doesn't remember me,
you sure have a lot of
personal observations to offer.
Fine.
Don't talk to me,
but fix the suit.
It's the only chance
that poor girl has.
I'm gonna make this very simple
for you, Mr. Blake.
You tell me where Vandal Savage
is hiding his fortune,
and we will let you
leave here unmolested.
"Vandal Savage."
Is that the name
you know him by?
Let's assume so, yes.
And what is your name, Gareeb?
- Will you give us a moment?
- "Gareeb"?
It's a legend passed down
for 4,000 years,
when my master
was first bestowed
the gift of eternal life.
An enemy tried to kill him.
Every myth has
its monster, its devil.
For those of our order,
it's him. The Gareeb.
I would stop talking now
if I were you, mate.
If I were you, I'd run.
Your friend has already failed
to kill my master once.
He won't be able to protect you.
In fact,
I highly doubt he's ever
been able to protect anyone.
What did he mean you already
tried to kill Savage?
Leave it be, Sara.
No, if you want us to do this--
Yes, okay? Yes, I had the chance
to kill Savage once before.
I had him dead to rights,
and I hesitated.
Get off me!
I asked you a question!
Who are you, Gareeb?
Killing is never easy,
especially for a good man.
The man killed my wife and son,
and God knows how many
other wives and sons,
and yet I couldn't...
Killing people doesn't
make you a monster, Sara.
But having the chance to avenge
your family and not taking it,
that does.
Let's try this again.
Back for more.
Where's Savage's fortune?
And I'm particularly interested
in this thing
called the "Vessel."
The Vessel is my master's
most treasured possession.
Excellent. And where can we find it?
The Greyhill Building.
There's a gathering tonight
in celebration of it.
And clearly, you want us to go
so we can get ourselves killed.
Clearly.
What is the Vessel?
It's the remains of Prince Khufu
of the Middle Kingdom.
I believe you know him
as Carter Hall.
What is Savage going to do
with Carter's body?
Well, there's only one way
to find out, isn't there?
Gideon, locate the Greyhill
Building, and set a course.
Wait, we have a plan.
Going after Savage's fortune.
Well, not anymore.
I won't let Carter's remains
be desecrated by that monster.
I won't let him win again.
And when Kendra wakes up,
and she will wake up,
she can give her soul mate
a proper farewell.
Then let us at least go in
with the rest of the team.
Hmm. Gideon.
Sir, Mr. Snart, Mr. Rory
and Mr. Jackson
are no longer aboard the ship.
That's what I call
a clean heist.
And thanks for not setting
the museum on fire, partner.
And you, thanks for being
our getaway driver.
Speaking of, let's get the hell
back to the ship.
No. One more stop.
What are you
talking about, boss?
1629 Hadley Avenue.
What's on Hadley Avenue?
It's where we grew up.
That's why you wanted to
steal the Maximilian Emerald.
Mick, enough!
You wanted to give it
to your old man,
so he wouldn't go to jail
trying to steal it for himself.
Your father was a thief too?
And unfortunately,
not a very good one.
Didn't Rip say something about
not messing with the timeline?
You could accidentally
blink yourself out of existence.
You're screwing
with history here, man.
Yeah, well, history
screwed with me first.
I know how it feels.
What?
To have a crisis of confidence,
as unlikely as that
may seem, I know.
It was 2002. I was teaching
quantum mechanics.
And I had one particularly
gifted student.
He was able to
solve the Ehrenfest Theorem
in less than an hour.
He was quite frankly
the only student
in all my years of teaching
who ever made me feel inferior.
That student was you.
You were exceptional.
Suddenly, just like that,
you remember having me
in your class?
I always remembered.
I just enjoyed taking you down
a peg or two.
Why tell me now?
Because I cannot
for the life of me reconcile
that cocksure student I remember
with the man who believes
he doesn't have
what it takes to save
Ms. Saunders' life.
Who did you lose, Raymond?
My fiancée, Anna Loring.
She was killed two years ago
in the Starling City Siege,
right in front of me.
I couldn't stop them.
I couldn't do anything.
My leg had been broken.
I couldn't get to her.
I could only watch
as they broke her neck.
I built the suit because
I promised myself that night
that I would never be powerless
to save anyone again.
So when that fragment broke free
and damaged my suit, I
panicked,
froze.
Raymond, you couldn't save Anna,
but you can save Kendra.
I believe it.
I believe in that student.
I just need him
to believe it too.
Let's do it.
Ah, Mr. Blake, welcome. I take it
Mrs. Blake is out of town.
That's a very
pointed observation.
If you're going to find
the Vessel, you'll need my help.
No, I think we're
quite good without it.
Sara.
I came down
for a glass of water.
I am Leo.
Are you friends with my daddy?
Kind of.
I think my daddy's sleeping.
Can I tell you something, Leo?
It's important.
Don't ever let anyone
hurt you. Ever.
Not here. And especially,
not here.
No matter what, you always have
to look out for yourself, okay?
Understand?
I think so.
You get the hell away from
my boy, you son of a bitch.
Why don't you go on up to bed?
Go on.
Talk fast, or you take a bullet.
What are you doing in my home?
A favor. For you.
Watch it.
Relax.
How the hell did you get--
Two days from now, you try to
steal this and you get arrested
and you spend five years
in Iron Heights.
What are you talking about?
Cut the crap.
We both know if I go down
to the basement right now,
I'll find floor plans
for the Central City Museum.
Let's just say
I've saved you the trouble
and from being arrested.
How do you know all this?
The same way I'll know if you
even think of raising a hand
to your wife and son.
I know who you are.
I know the man you become.
And it's all I can do to keep
from ending you
right here, right now.
But if I do, that means
my sister's never born,
so you get a pass.
Your sister?
Looks like you didn't write
yourself out of the timeline.
- Looks like.
- But?
I don't know.
I just thought maybe
things would feel differently.
The Englishman says it takes
time for time to change.
What were you trying to change?
My dad was never
Father of the Year,
but at least he never raised
a hand to any of us.
Until he went to prison,
which now he won't.
Let's get out of here.
Maybe we should've had Blake
show us around.
Hmm.
Perhaps there's
a less conspicuous way
for us to do reconnaissance.
May I?
I'm not much of a dancer.
I'll lead then.
Well, for a monster, you dance
quite gracefully, Ms. Lance.
- Don't make fun.
- Oh, no, I'm not.
Nor do I consider you a monster.
All I see is someone
who's tortured
by an appetite that
she cannot control.
There's no magical cure
for what's wrong with me.
Of course there is!
It's called "being better."
When my family was killed,
I thought
there was no way
that I could go on.
But I did.
The truth of our existence
is that
we're all blessed and cursed
with the drive to move forward,
live the next day.
To get better.
And you will too, Sara.
Well, maybe I can start by
managing not to kill these guys.
They're scarred up
like our friends at the bank.
South African mercenaries.
Why didn't you say so?
Ladies first.
This area's restricted, folks.
I'm just looking
for the ladies' room.
Hope you have a plan
to get him out of here.
Yep, there's
a maintenance elevator
that leads to a loading bay.
I'll have Gideon
fly the Waverider down.
I just wish we knew what Savage
was gonna do with Carter's body.
Why not stay and find out?
Ah, the Gareeb. Mr. Blake
has told us so much about you.
I've located three fragments.
Okay, I see them.
Man, they're big!
Remember, the initial blast
will create smaller pieces.
You need to--
How does Jax put up with
having you in his head?
I believe he finds my presence
rather comforting.
I doubt that very much.
The targeting system's
overloaded.
Focus, Raymond.
Remember, you can do this.
It's not the suit. It's you
that Kendra needs right now.
Well done!
Just one more fragment to go.
I see it.
It's the biggest one yet.
You did it!
Well done. I couldn't possibly
be more proud.
Well, maybe if you actually
remembered me
being your student.
Right around the subclavian
artery, I remembered something.
How I figured the solve
for the Ehrenfest Theorem
two years after I was
in your class.
Why did you tell me you
remembered me when you didn't?
Because you needed a push.
So all that stuff about me
being exceptional...
Was probably true.
The fact of the matter is
I had many exceptional students
over the years.
I couldn't possibly
remember them all.
I was pretty amazing.
If that were true,
I suspect I would've given you
a higher grade.
I meant tonight.
Oh, yes.
On that score,
I cannot disagree.
What are you planning on doing
with Carter's body?
Oh. You'll see. Mr. Blake informs us
that you were hoping to steal
our master's fortune.
But while money has its uses,
it is not the source
of his power.
Then what is?
Let us show you.
Our numbers are legion,
all drawn to the man
who is immune to death.
Wealth is not power.
Belief is.
Hello, Gareeb.
How long has it been?
4,000 years?
You look well.
When you and your friends
attacked my estate in St. Roch,
I was afraid I wouldn't get the
chance to meet you once again.
Well, if there's something that
I've learned in 4,000 years,
it's patience.
And this time, I only
had to wait one short day.
You're probably wondering
what my plans are
with your friend's body.
I already have
his life's essence,
but his blood still
has its uses.
Jack the Ripper
showed me the virtues
of severing the carotid artery.
Okay, what's this now?
Centuries ago, I discovered that
although immortality
is mine alone,
I can share a taste
with my faithful,
help them live
an extra 100 years or so.
They're in trouble.
She appears to be hallucinating.
Rip and Sara, you have to
save them. Vandal. Carter!
Greyhill Building.
Carter, Rip, Sara!
Gideon, search
"Greyhill Building."
I've already searched for it
on behalf of the captain,
who's there now with Ms. Lance.
What? They left without us?
It's a mansion
several miles away.
Apparently, there's some
sort of private event.
How the hell could Kendra
know that they're there?
You have to save them!
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
When we first met, I asked you
who you were, remember?
That was the wrong question.
I should've asked you why.
Why did you seek to kill me?
What could I have
possibly done to deserve
that hatred I see
burning in your eyes?
Did I take something from you?
Someone?
Get your hands off that.
Oh. Your wife, I take it.
Oh, she is lovely.
The boy has your eyes.
I'll be sure to
keep their picture close.
I don't remember killing them
yet.
It seems like I have
a lot to look forward to.
- Gideon, get me Jefferson.
- Mr. Jackson is not aboard.
Oh, don't tell me.
He's with Mr. Snart
and Mr. Rory on the Jumpship.
I'm patching you through.
Jefferson?
Jefferson, where are you?
Well, it's not a short story.
There's no time.
Gideon will upload you
coordinates to
the Greyhill Building.
Rip and Sara are in danger.
We're on our way, Professor.
This is a perversion.
No, this is the power
you have no hope of defeating.
Everyone here has sworn to live
and die at my command!
Why? 'Cause to them, I am a God!
I pity you.
You have no idea
what it's like to have people
willing to follow you up
to the gates of hell.
Actually, I have
a little bit of an idea.
Let's get this party started!
Here's our invitation.
Well, this is different.
I didn't have you
pegged as the
Eyes Wide Shut type.
- Gun.
- Here.
You came.
We're a team.
Next time, remember that.
Enough!
Get Carter's body
out of here. Sara.
I got this.
Go. I'll deal with Savage.
Good luck with that.
This is for Miranda and Jonas!
At least I know their names now.
Miranda and Jonas.
Jonas.
I will heal,
and then I will rise.
Then I will simply wait.
I am looking forward
to meeting them.
Sara. Sara. Sara!
Gideon, I need a check
of the timeline. Vandal Savage.
The timeline is
unchanged, Captain.
You know better than anyone
that Savage is immortal.
He cannot be killed
through conventional means.
Which is why I need
you to work on finding out
where history records
seeing him next.
- How is she?
- Better.
Thank you for
what you did for Carter.
Oh. Believe me,
it was a team effort,
as was apparently your recovery.
Oh, well, actually, I did most
of the physical work,
and the professor was there
for emotional support.
You're welcome.
Now if we could
just figure out a way
to wrest the Amon Dagger
out of Savage's hand into yours.
I don't think I'm exactly up to
taking him on right now.
No, but you will be.
And we'll help you get ready.
Maybe you didn't understand me.
I asked for
the new timeline, Gideon.
This is the new timeline.
Two days from now,
your father will be arrested
trying to sell
the Maximilian Emerald
to an undercover police officer.
Stupid son of a bitch.
He'll be sentenced to five years
in Iron Heights.
Despite your intervention,
his future remains unchanged.
Hey, you tried to save him.
That's gotta count
for something.
Turns out it doesn't.
Come on.
Where are we going now?
To say goodbye.
Uh...
The other day, I tried to find
some words of inspiration.
Words that would restore hope
to us in the wake of our losses.
But it is all of you who
have inspired me.
Beginning with Professor
Boardman, and then with Carter.
Their heroism is
an inspiration to us all,
and a reminder
that one person acting alone
can't save the world.
Come back to me.
Thank you.
Both of you.
Sorry for your loss, Kendra.
I believe Anna would be proud,
as am I.
Gideon, ready us for takeoff.
Whoa. Are we being chased
or something?
No, but I imagine that
right about now,
the museum has realized that
their prized emerald is missing.
You want me to say "I'm sorry"?
Sorry, I don't do sorry.
Which is fine, Mr. Rory, because
you are owed the apology.
I should've told you all before
that this wasn't
my first attempt
to vanquish Vandal Savage.
But the reason I failed before--
Was because you
didn't have all of us.
Well, obviously, Dr. Palmer
and I had our hands full
tending to Ms. Saunders, but now
that she's back on her feet--
We're back to full strength.
Or as strong as we can be
without Carter.
Quite true.
But there is no point in us
continuing any further
unless we are all,
and myself included,
committed to working in concert.
You don't ditch us,
we won't ditch you. Deal?
Sir, I've completed
my review of the timeline.
I calculate a 98% likelihood
that Savage reappears in 1986.
Chart a course, Gideon.
Guess we're headed to the '80s.
Better break out
your parachute pants.
What the hell are
parachute pants?
English - SDH