[Agent Sharpe] Previously on
Legends of Tomorrow...
[Constantine] Some of
the most evil souls in all of history
have been raised from hell.
[Behrad] Nate, Zari. Zari, Nate.
[Nate] Your sister is the secret woman
from the hologram message.
I know Behrad's
been lying to my parents.
I know who you are.
It's time they finally heard the truth.
Guys, meet Zari. She's my sister.
[yells] Help!
Freddy Meyers, you stand convicted
of seven counts of murder,
all occurring on June 2nd, 1989.
You have been sentenced to death
by a jury of your peers.
The State will now proceed
with your sentence.
Do you have anything to say
before your sentence is carried out?
Only...
that I love my mother.
[electricity charging]
- [grunts]
- [sobs]
[sobbing]
[wails] Freddy! [shrieks]
[shrieks] They took my Freddy!
[pop song playing]
[driver sings along]
Ooh, heaven is a place on Earth
They say in heaven, love comes first
We'll make heaven a place on Earth
[thud]
The hell was that?
What the...
[engine revs]
[music blaring]
- [car horn blares]
- [tires screeching]
[groans]
[thud, creak]
Who's there?
[gasping]
[knife plunges]
Going somewhere?
Spare me the send-off, Lance.
I'm leaving before you
and your band of botherers
can suck me into another
world-saving sing-along.
Actually, I was just gonna say
we're still waiting for you to move out.
There's a box in the library
labeled "arcana"
that's been sitting there for months.
I'd avoid touching that, if I was you.
Yeah. Behrad already tried to move it,
and now he thinks he's being haunted
by a forlorn mariner.
And he's right, but I can't stick around
to help the bloke,
I'm off to research
a more lasting solution
to your Encore problem.
[in sing-song voice]
Did someone say "Encore"?
I also said no musical numbers,
so please, don't start.
Listen, I might have a solution
to your problem.
I can't take you with me
on this one, squire.
Where I'm going, I need to walk alone.
With Gary.
Okay. But, look, we're on a Timeship,
and let's be honest,
we're a little past the whole, "Should
we change history?" debate, right?
So, what if we go back
to when the Encores were kids
and reform them before they break bad?
Ray, we're dealing with the villains
of history fresh out of hell.
- They can't just be reformed like your...
- [Nora] Ray, where are you?
Like your Fairy God-girlfriend.
Speaking of which, I think that
your services are required, squire.
Well, look who's finally off the clock.
Oh, no. Not again.
Oh, yes. Oh, yes.
It's the same thing every time.
Kid gets a Fairy Godmother,
what do they wish for?
[laughs]
"You get a pony, and you get a pony.
Everyone gets a damn pony."
Well, maybe next time
you should say "nay."
[blowing raspberry]
Well, right now,
it's all about what you want.
[groans] Oh, what I want is to be done
with this gig.
[sighs]
I know.
But, look, at least with this job,
you have the opportunity
to make people's lives better.
How am I supposed to help kids in need
when these kids don't even know
what they need?
Because, trust me, no one has ever
become a better person with a pony.
Probably true, but, look,
I'm setting the mood.
Gideon, dim the lights,
and play "You're the Inspiration"
by Chicago.
And now, it's whatever you wish, Nora.
[snoring]
Gideon, don't play Chicago.
[Gideon] I wasn't going to, Dr. Palmer.
- [snorts]
- Oh.
You sure being here
doesn't bring back some fond memories?
If I had fond memories of this place,
I'd book a lobotomy.
Okay. Whatever you people do here,
just show me the exit.
I'm due for a content drop.
Oh, and also to tell Mâmân and Bâbâ
you're not really in business school.
But before you do that,
let's make sure you can't do that.
- Look over here.
- Is that a camera?
- Wait!
- [device whirs]
Ugh. I don't want my picture with him.
[whispers] You can't wipe her memory.
All right? There's a timeline
where she was here.
Okay, so maybe her being here,
she'll remember what we did
and who she was.
[whispers] Look, I know Zari,
and there's no way she was
ever anyone but her.
Hey, what's with the Wi-Fi?
I need to clap back
at Blue Ivy on Cat-Chat.
[cat meowing on Zari's phone]
Cat-Chat's the chat app
that lets you clap back...
I didn't say tell me.
[Gideon] Mr. Tarazi and Mr. Heywood,
you're needed on the bridge.
Look, no one wants you out of here
more than I do,
but I need you to stay put
until we finish this job.
[door opens]
Wait. Wait... Are you keep...
Are you taking me prisoner?
- [door locks]
- [inaudible]
I have a sneaker drop,
and I'm supposed to be releasing
a new fragrance for Dragonesque today.
We've been working on this launch
for months.
This is high stakes!
[Gideon] A serial killer has been freed
from hell and is on the loose in 2004.
And somehow the scariest thing
about this mission
is going back to the early 2000s.
[Gideon] A coroner was found dead
while transporting the body
of a famed serial killer.
[gasps] Oh, my God, it's Freddy Meyers,
the Prom Night Slasher.
Come on, guys. I ranked him number five
killer of all time on StabCast.
- My podcast about serial killers. Babe?
- Oh.
[Gideon] As I was going to say,
Freddy killed seven
of his peers before...
At his high school prom in 1989,
he used a kitchen knife,
and he wore a creepy mask.
I actually did a whole series on it,
so none of you open my e-mails, clearly.
[Gideon] And following the murders...
He spent 15 years on death row
before he was executed in 2004.
[Gideon] Which is when
the timeline changed,
starting with the death of the coroner
and the disappearance of Freddy's body.
I don't even wanna think about
what a serial killer would do
with his second act.
Tiffany.
She was the final girl.
[both] The one target
that survived Freddy's attack!
It's informative and entertaining.
It's good.
See? Thank you.
Guys, check this out.
The Central City High class of '89
is planning to memorialize
their fallen peers
at their 15-year reunion
this Friday night.
We have to go. That's where
Freddy will be to finish the job.
Well then, babe,
grab your autograph book...
because we're gonna go catch
a serial killer.
Gideon, take us to 2004.
And order one of these mattresses
using promo code "laceration."
[Sara] We're heading in. You guys keep
an eye out for a crazy masked killer.
The only thing killing it out here
is my wardrobe.
Can't believe I'm here. Seriously.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. [gasps]
This is the lobby
where he stalked his victims.
You guys, he made his first kill
in this cafeteria. [gasps]
- Babe.
- What? What?
Babe, that's the trophy that Tiffany
fashioned into a makeshift weapon.
Why didn't you tell me we were
coming back to my old school?
- You went to school here?
- What?
Mick, this is why you need
to come to team meetings.
Do you remember anything about Freddy?
- Yeah. He was... He was a loser.
- Oh, come on.
Frigging Mick Rory!
Ali, remember?
Is that you, or...
No.
Are you sure? 'Cause you look, like,
exactly like Mick... Mick Rory.
No. My name is Dick.
I'm telling you, Dick,
team meetings work wonders.
It's her.
It's Tiffany.
Tiffany Harper. It's really you.
- Who are you?
- I'm, uh...
I'm Lisa, and this is Kelly,
and you wouldn't remember us
'cause we were losers.
Total zeroes.
I don't.
- Isn't time weird?
- So weird.
- Well, see you inside.
- Thank you.
And... Go, Cavaliers!
- Okay. Go. Keep going.
- Oh, my God!
- [rock music playing]
- Hey, hey!
Hope you're enjoying your reunion
out there.
Keep on dancing, class of '89.
[sighs] No sign of Freddy.
But I got eyes on crudités.
Ooh. Save me some raw broccoli.
[sighs]
I never thought I'd say this,
but I think I've lost
my appetite for broccoli.
[Nate] Guys, Freddy's on the scene.
And he's got his first victim.
- We're ready for him.
- [host] Uh, hello. Hello, everyone.
Welcome back.
It means so much
to see all of you here tonight.
And here to unveil our memorial
to our fallen peers
is our very own survivor,
Tiffany Harper.
[applause]
Uh...
Has anyone seen Tiffany?
Something's wrong.
[crowd gasps]
Of course she makes
a dramatic entrance. [chuckles]
We didn't cover this
in rehearsal, Tiffany.
All right, that's it.
I'm unveiling it myself.
[audience screaming]
All right, everybody. Just stay calm.
Look, he's here. We need backup.
That's him.
Guys, watch out. You're stuck in
a school with the Prom Night Slasher.
[Gary] Master, I'm sorry I'm so late.
I tried a teleportation spell
to get here ASAP,
and now I'm stuck walking backwards.
[recites incantation]
Damn it, Gary. Pull yourself together,
will you? We've got work to do.
And the answers we need
lie behind this door.
What is this place?
Can't say I've ever had anything
as comfy as a home,
but I lived here once.
Not a soul has stepped foot inside
since I left.
What the bloody hell?
[snoring]
Oi!
What are you doing in my house?
- Hey, go on. Get off my stairs.
- [groans]
All right. Who's responsible for this?
And I thought I was the one
with the magic touch.
All right. Everybody out.
You wanna party,
you do it somewhere else, all right?
How did you even
find this place, Charlie?
You told me about it
when you were wasted once.
[Constantine] You found your way here.
You can find your way out.
What is with him, huh?
- What are you doing here?
- Do the Constantine trick again.
All right, everyone. Stay sharp.
The killer could be anywhere.
[sighs] We gotta get everyone
out of here.
[all scream]
Thanks for the heart attack!
Sorry. Swiss Army knife.
Usually solves a jam in a jiff,
but these doors
are telekinetically sealed.
No way in or out.
This place always smelled
like a prison.
Telekinesis. It makes perfect sense.
Killers often act
out of feeling powerless,
and now he has the ultimate power.
- I need to adjust my rankings.
- [Mick] Yeah.
And we need to save Ali.
I mean, the class of '89.
All right. Immortal killer.
How do we stop him?
We can't from in here,
but maybe you guys can.
Look, Ray, it's time to put
your crazy plan to the test.
You gotta go back and fix Freddy.
[school bell rings]
All right. Let's find our future Encore.
Freddy. Hey, Freddy!
Heard you couldn't find a prom date.
Guess your mom turned you down.
[bullies laugh]
Loser.
- Loser.
- Nice job, butterfingers.
Good one, Brad. Yeah.
Losers.
- Brad's such a jerk.
- Oh, it's okay. You don't have to...
It's all right. I got it. Thank you.
Actually, I wanted to ask you something.
Turns out I don't have a date
to prom tonight,
and I was thinking...
Would you go with me?
What? Me... Me, go with you to prom?
Exactly. Meet me in front of school
at 8:00. Don't be late.
[clears throat]
Oy vey. This is bad.
Why would the most popular girl need
a last-minute date, let alone ask him?
She's working with those bullies.
This could be what sets him off.
Okay. We gotta talk this kid
out of his dream date.
Let's rap, Freddy.
Who... who are you guys?
New teachers. Cool new teachers.
And judging by your test scores here,
maybe you should skip the prom
and hit the books.
Turn this A into an A-plus.
Or maybe go to the movies.
1989 is a great movie summer.
- Last Crusade, Ghostbusters Il...
- Yeah. I gotta go, so...
Hey, no running in the hallway.
We're not just your teachers,
we're your pals.
Picture a dark hallway.
Feels like the killer's there with you.
Shafts of moonlight claw at the floor.
Shh!
[quietly] Glowing "exit" sign
you may never reach.
[door rattles]
Come out here, Freddy.
We know you're there.
Yeah. Come on out.
There are gaps in your psychological
profile that you need to answer for.
Babe.
- And we're gonna send you back to hell.
- Yeah!
Did you find a way out?
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
Get back in the gym.
- [bangs]
- [shrieks]
There!
[woman screaming]
[metal crunching]
[screaming stops]
[blood dripping]
Freddy ran off on us.
We need his address.
I got you.
[muffled voices]
[groans]
Nora?
Nora, what's wrong?
I can hear them.
Their... their voices.
Fairy Godmothers
have sort of a special radar
that tunes in to kids' wishes,
and prom night is
a minefield of teenage need,
so when it locks on
to the kid with the deepest need,
I just go straight to...
No, no, no, no, no. It's happening.
Where the hell did you come from, huh?
- Oh, Freddy, uh...
- Huh?
I am your Fairy Godmother.
So...
Please don't kill me?
You're a Fairy Godmother?
- My Fairy Godmother?
- Uh-huh.
Prove it.
You think I'd be wearing this
if I really had the choice?
- Huh?
- So, anything I ask for...
you have to do it.
So, you should really think
about what you want,
especially the consequences.
I already know what I want.
Prom's tonight, and...
- [knock at door]
- [Cathy] Freddy, honey.
- Hide.
- [exclaims]
Hey, Freddy.
You ready, Freddy, for movie night?
I got the Jiffy Pop going.
Actually, Mom...
[whispers] Ray, I'm with Freddy.
Nora. Good! That... That's great.
How is that great?
I'm a serial killer's Fairy Godmother.
This is perfect. Old Freddy didn't have
a Fairy Godmother.
So, if you give him the prom
every kid dreams of,
maybe he won't hurt anyone.
Except this kid's dream
is for everyone to be dead.
[Freddy]...gonna go to prom.
Hmm. Prom.
Wow, Freddy.
Uh, do you need a ride?
Or I could help you with your tie...
You know what, I got it, but...
Love you. Okay, I just gotta go.
Okay.
[door closes]
Now...
Back to my wish.
I'm gonna make it so those kids
never make fun of me again,
because I wish for...
Uh...
A suit.
A suit?
Yeah. If I'm gonna take Tiffany,
I gotta look good.
So, I want a cool suit. Can you do that?
- Yeah, I can do that.
- Okay.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Check it out.
Okay.
Now I gotta show up in style.
- I want a pony.
- Ugh. Seriously, kid?
[whooshing]
Hey, Freddy.
- Hey, Tiffany.
- Wow. Cool suit.
Thanks. Here.
- Thank you.
- Should we, um...
- Yes.
- Okay.
Looks like your plan just might work.
Well, only thanks to you.
Hey, Palmer.
Will you go to prom with me?
Oh, shucks.
All right.
[grunts, gasps]
Whoa, whoa. Hey. Cool it.
- [device trills]
- Huh.
I knew it. You stole our family's totem.
It's not like that. I...
I needed to take it.
You could've just asked for it.
Mâmân and Bâbâ would've given it to you.
What's that supposed to mean?
Oh, you really don't know?
You're never around,
you don't do any work,
and they still treat you
like you're some kind of hero.
If you only knew what I've done,
what I've survived,
without getting any credit...
Not that you'd understand,
'cause you only care about yourself.
Whatever. Don't tell me.
But wait till they see you've turned it
into a stupid stoner bracelet.
- Hey!
- "What up, Z-listers?
Turns out even a sacred totem
couldn't reverse
the sucking void that is my soul."
Hey, screw you.
I'm not a void.
I'm a business.
Not like it works here anyway.
[man] Everybody stay calm.
Once the power's back, we'll get help.
[guest] I am freaked out.
I'm freaked out.
Where do you think you're going?
I'm gonna find a way out of the school.
Look at them,
just waiting to be picked off.
Never fit in with them when I went here,
and I'm sure as hell
not gonna die with them.
I like the way you think.
There's an old vent in the wood shop
I used to sneak out of.
I knew it.
Mick freaking Rory.
Come on.
Let's get the hell out of this school.
You have a husband? Boyfriend?
Girlfriend?
Nah.
No one's waiting at home for me.
Still haven't quite
gotten that together.
Hmm.
And you?
Uh, it's behind here.
Hey.
You ever wonder where we'd be if...
you know,
that prom had gone differently?
Like if we...
Ali!
You'd better be fixing this in '89.
[dance music playing]
So, this is prom.
I know it's lame, but...
No, no, no. Actually, I think I kind of
get the whole nostalgia thing for once.
[DJ] And we're gonna slow it down
for the next one.
So, everyone, grab your sweeties
and get on the dance floor.
[romantic song playing]
I love this song.
Yeah. Me, too.
You know, you're a really good dancer.
Thanks. I...
I watch a lot of music videos.
Aw. They look so happy.
Yeah. But they don't.
So, that's the prank.
She leads him to the center
of the dance floor,
and they drop trash on his head.
Classic Carrie.
Bet these bullies
don't know how that ended.
We got to keep him
from walking in the drop zone.
I... think it's gonna be okay.
- It's a little crowded over there.
- Sure.
- Is this good?
- Yeah.
- Having fun?
- Yeah. Thanks a lot...
Hey, Freddy.
[students exclaim]
Nice suit.
Would suck if it got ruined.
- Brad, wait.
- Come on, Tiff.
This is how the prank
was supposed to go, right?
Prank? What are you talking about?
[chuckles]
He still doesn't get it.
You think she actually wanted
to go out with you?
It was a setup, butt-lump.
[students snickering]
Tiffany, is that true?
No. I mean... not anymore, Freddy.
No. Freddy.
Freddy, it's gonna be okay.
This went from John Hughes
to John Carpenter.
I take it back.
High school sucks.
Come out here and face me, you bastard.
Rory, are you trying
to get yourself killed?
He killed Ali. He's gonna pay.
She wasn't just some girl, was she?
She was my prom date.
We went to the same school together
and kind of had a thing.
Then I went to juvie, but we still
wrote letters to one another.
I was gonna break out
and take her to the stupid dance...
but then I blew her off.
Rory.
What? I was young, stupid.
Mick, look, I'm sorry, okay?
But if this plan works,
then Freddy never becomes an Encore.
Maybe everything that happened
can be undone.
Maybe we can still save Ali.
[sniffles]
- [Nora] Freddy, wait.
- Leave me alone.
- What?
- You don't wanna be alone right now.
How would you know that?
How would you know what I want?
I've spent years
wanting these kids to be my friend,
and I couldn't even make it happen
with a Fairy Godmother!
I cannot wait to be done
with this stupid place,
and I hope they all
get what they deserve.
No. You don't mean that.
- Yeah, I do.
- No, you don't!
Look, I get it.
I have given in to my demons,
I know what it's like
to wanna make the world feel your pain,
but that is not who you are.
I see so much more in you.
Listen.
God, being yourself...
that is a magic stronger than any wish.
Being truly okay with myself...
scars and all,
is how the right people truly found me.
Now, if you had one more wish...
to show all of them
who you really are...
what'll it be?
[song plays, stops]
Uh, how concerned should we be?
I say medium.
- Medium concerned.
- [dance song playing]
We're J. J. Fad
and we're here to rock
[beatboxes]
Rhymes like ours could never be stopped
Hit it!
Supersonic
Supersonic motivating
rhymes are creating
We know you like us girls
so you better get stirl
'Cause we are the homechicks
that are rockin' your world
Supersonic
Supersonic is a word
when people start to listen
Especially bigger people,
they pay close attention
You might not believe it,
you might not even buy it
But when it comes to our lady
(Beat Box), you might even try it
Supersonic
What the...
So, you better listen good
to what we have to say
'Cause when it comes to J. J. Fad
you can get no play
Supersonic
[sighing]
Computer, just tell me...
How many Cat-Chat followers have I lost
since I've been stuck in this dump?
[Gideon] I can't do that, Ms. Tarazi.
It's probably best I don't know.
[sighs]
Wait, does this computer get Internet?
[Zari] So, that computer program
I designed to act
as a temporal beacon...
[Gideon] How did you bypass
my encrypted security protocol?
Oh, just by being a businesswoman,
makeup guru, bad bitch,
and overall genius.
Now, call me a ride, computer.
[upbeat dance music playing]
Hey, you were
really great out there, Freddy.
It takes some real confidence
to bust out backup dancers at prom.
So this gets to be, like, your job,
making things better for kids?
Yeah.
Yeah, it is.
Look, there's gotta be
a bunch of kids out there
that could probably use your help,
and I...
I think I'm gonna be okay.
Thank you, Nora, for everything.
Oh, here's my ride.
Oh, vintage.
Well, at least the computer knows
I like to travel in style.
That was fun.
Yeah, and the night
is just getting started.
I know. Well, we can take my limo
wherever we wanna go.
- After you.
- Thank you.
Mmm-hmm.
[woman giggles]
She booked me a shared ride.
[Behrad] Guys, they fixed it.
Ray's plan actually worked?
Apparently, Freddy's
a really solid dancer,
and he's not gonna go
on a killing spree at prom.
[clanging]
Then who is that?
Die, you bastard!
- [groans]
- Mick!
No, no.
Sara, look.
Cathy Meyers?
She must be the Encore.
They wanted to take my Freddy
away from me.
But when that girl asked him to prom,
I knew I had to kill her
and all of his new friends.
Now I get to finish what I started.
Hey, are you guys getting any service?
I know what you guys are thinking.
Yes, it's me, the dragon girl.
Wait. Why aren't we moving?
Driver, what's going on?
[all screaming]
Close it! Close it! Close the door!
Close it!
[grunts]
You killed our friend.
You killed those kids.
But you're not gonna
get away with it this time.
I won't let anyone stand between me
and my boy.
And you're next. [grunts]
Sara!
- Close the door!
- [all screaming]
[gasping]
[growling]
- [bang]
- [all whimper]
[clanging]
- [grunts]
- Wait, wait, wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Before you kill me...
Just something I don't understand, huh?
How did you get here?
Come on.
Every... every killer has a story.
Why don't you tell me yours, yeah?
After I killed those brats,
my Freddy took the fall.
He wanted to protect me.
But I knew I couldn't live without him.
And I was right,
because he's not the only one
who died the night of his execution.
[groans]
I had a heart attack
right there in Iron Heights.
I died with him!
But then, I was sent back from hell!
Given a second chance.
A chance to bring Freddy home
where he belongs,
a chance to finish the job I started.
And no one can ever take us
away from each other.
[grunts]
[screaming]
Babe, it's happening.
- We're final girls!
- [roars]
[screaming]
- [groans]
- [screaming]
[students screaming]
That's right.
Feel the burn of Dragonesque,
you psycho!
[Zari grunts]
[pants]
Mom?
- Hi.
- What are you doing?
Freddy, I'm doing this for you. For us.
I can't lose you, Freddy.
I can't live without you.
Let me do this, Freddy.
[Agent Sharpe] I can't move.
[both straining]
You don't need them, you need me.
We can get away with this together.
No! No.
I know who I am now,
and I'm not gonna lock myself away.
Then this is for your own good.
[groans]
- They did it.
- [gasps]
Behrad?
Sorry. You okay?
I totally get why you stole that.
Fair enough.
Wow, this was... a lot.
- [siren wails]
- [gasps]
Ma'am, you were in the limo,
is that right?
- Yes.
- Thanks.
I'll be back.
I know she needs help, but...
She was all I had,
and they took her away. [sniffs]
Mmm-hmm.
So, what do I do?
You survive.
Freddy, my upbringing
was only dysfunction.
But dysfunction doesn't get to choose
who you are.
You do.
- You hear me?
- Yeah. Okay.
We should head back
and check on the team,
make sure everything's back to normal.
I know... you're gonna be okay, kid.
Dr. Gideon treating you right?
Pretty cool, huh?
So, this is what you do,
travel around time
and save people using wind? That's...
Well, I wouldn't say "cool,"
exactly, but...
no wonder you're the favorite.
The favorite?
Mâmân and Bâbâ only treat me how they do
'cause they're worried about me.
I mean, I've been in business school
for five years.
You were a self-made millionaire
by the age of 19.
You're right, I am very impressive.
Like, how did you jailbreak
your way out of here anyway?
I was poking around
your weird little screens,
and suddenly
I knew how to hack my way out.
Right.
Yeah, time travel
always has these weird side effects.
Huh.
Well, hopefully it wears off
because I was thinking of
sticking around for a while.
Huh.
I weirdly wouldn't hate that.
[Sara] Hey, guys, we're still in 2004.
Where the hell are you?
You coming?
[upbeat dance music playing]
How about this for a reunion?
[all cheering]
And, uh, what's your sister doing here?
Probably Cat-Chatting. No judgment here.
- Yes.
- Wait.
Where's Mick?
Mick?
- [pop song playing]
- Mick Rory?
Ali.
Hey, Freddy.
Hey, Tiffany. Congrats.
Nora, may I have this dance?
Ah, but of course.
I cannot believe I got to get
an exclusive scoop for StabCast,
and I got to be the final girl.
Well, technically, I never died, so...
Technically, you've died
more than three times,
so just give me this one, babe.
- You are my final girl.
- Mmm-hmm.
Hey, guys.
Photo booth.
- Oh, no.
- Yes!
[music continues]
- [record scratches, song stops]
- Wait. Where's Mick?
[song resumes]
[both moaning]
Wow, Mick.
That's my gun.
[sighs] I thought I told you
to piss off.
Garyjust filled me in
on that business with Astra.
So, why are you drowning your sorrows
instead of doing something about it?
What happened here, John?
Oh, I used to run with a bunch
back in the day.
Became known as "the Newcastle Crew,"
spent most of our misbegotten youth
in this place.
One of them was a powerful witch.
I'm back here to consult with her.
She's through there.
So, what are you waiting for?
Come on. Get off your arse
and go and do it.
Because it's not that easy,
all right, Charlie?
That witch is Astra's dead mother.
Her spirit is waiting
on the other side of that door, and...
none too happy with me.
There are things in my past
that I haven't told anyone.
So, I get the whole
wanting to do it on your own.
But if there was some door that I could
walk through to solve all my problems...
I sure as hell would take that chance.
I call upon Hecate,
lady of keys and guardian of crossroads.
Sever this seal.
By my blood, be open.
Don't look back, John-o.
You got this.
Let's hope you're right, love.
[locks thudding]
[theme music playing]