RIP: In 2166,
an immortal tyrant named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan is opposed
by the body I had sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered as legends.
RAY: Previously, on Legends of Tomorrow...
Sorry we're late.
Aren't you even a little bit
happy to be back on the ship?
I was happy with the life
we built together.
RORY: You think I was hunting
you and your friends
because the Time Masters made me?
They barely had to ask.
Since I failed to bring you in,
the Time Masters want to bring me in.
They're called the Hunters,
and they'll stop at nothing
until every single one of us is erased
from the face of history.
Do you have any suggestions?
Run.
(SHUDDERS)
It's been quite a while
since I time-jumped far enough
to experience side effects. Fond memories.
I can't feel my face.
- Fine feel I.
- Linguistic dysplasia.
That should pass shortly.
Better it now.
(SLURRING) Am I the only one
who can't feel their face?
I can't feel my...
I better not say.
- Mr. Rory appears unaffected.
- What's going on? We time-jump?
Yeah, we time-jumped.
But where to is the better question.
The town of Salvation
in the Dakota Territory, 1871.
I can't believe it. The Old West!
- This isn't gonna work.
- It'll buy us time.
We can hide out here
while the Hunters search
the other Fragmentations.
What if they decide to
check this place first?
You know, feel free to loop
us in whenever it's convenient.
As you've seen, time doesn't
operate as is generally thought.
It wants to happen,
it takes time to harden,
the timeline is unclear
on occasion, constantly in flux.
Hence, the difficulty in locating Savage
throughout history.
Indeed. And one of the other
interesting notions
of time travel is the existence
of Fragmentations.
Temporal blind spots.
Specific places and times
the Time Masters can't see.
The town of Salvation
and its surrounding environs
are located within
one of these Fragmentations.
So, basically,
we're hiding out in the Old West
and hoping your bogeymen
don't find us here.
The Hunters are not bogeymen.
And you better hope they don't find us.
Well, at least not until I get a chance to
"punch a few doggies"
or "bust a bronco" or two.
Not that I condone animal cruelty,
it's just that I watched
a lot of Westerns as a kid.
Alas, you'll have to enjoy the Old West
from in here, I'm afraid.
Oh, come on.
What's the harm in us
just taking a look around?
With this group? Clearly, you
haven't been paying attention.
(SIGHS) If I'm in the Old West
and I don't get to look around,
I'm gonna kick myself.
I could help with that.
I'll keep an eye out.
Don't worry, I'll be a good boy.
(RAY CHUCKLES)
I look just like Wyatt Earp.
Now, the fabricator can make clothing,
but you're also going to need
era-appropriate protection.
This era can get a little, uh, rough.
(CHUCKLES) Oh, six-Shooters?
Actually, most guns of that
time period had hammer blocks.
Thus reducing the number of shots to five.
Now, this should go without saying,
but considering this group,
I am going to say it.
Only use these weapons in the
case of extreme emergencies.
You make it sound like
you're not coming with.
From your duster and revolver,
I'd imagined you as much
an Old West aficionado
as Dr. Palmer.
Indeed I am. But my time is best
spent back here on the ship,
plotting our next move
against Vandal Savage.
Besides, as Mr. Rory said,
"It's only a matter of time
"before the Hunters find us here."
Don't worry.
We're not gonna put down roots.
Yeah, we'll stay out of trouble.
Mmm. How I hope and pray that to be true.
(WESTERN MUSIC PLAYING)
(MAN WHOOPING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
PROFESSOR STEIN: Remember, we're just here
to get the lay of the land.
- No trouble.
- Sure, that'll happen.
RORY: I need a drink.
RAY: Wow. It's a real old-timey saloon.
- (GRUNTS)
- WOMAN: Oh!
- I beg your pardon.
- Not at all, ma'am.
(PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
That tastes like gasoline.
Pretty much. Hit me again.
- (GRUNTS) I'm so sorry.
- It's no bother.
RORY: Time doesn't pass normally
in the Vanishing Point.
It's been years since
I've seen the bottom of a glass.
Years?
- How long were you...
- Chronos?
Never counted. Doesn't matter.
Turns out, it was just another gig anyway.
Doesn't seem like it.
You're different now.
Better or worse?
Don't know yet.
You can handle your liquor. I like that.
I've been on more
than a few dates with guys
who thought we'd get wasted
and they'd get lucky,
but somehow they always ended
up the ones under the table.
Hmm.
You haven't drunk with me.
Is that a challenge, Mick?
Line them up.
Didn't know you played cards.
Like you, Mr. Snart,
I am an enigma. Raise.
Ah.
- Thank you, gentlemen.
- SNART: I'm impressed.
My father was what some might
call a "degenerate gambler."
Others would say "criminal."
When I was old enough, he'd pull
me in on some of his schemes.
I picked up a thing or two
at a few of the card tables he frequented.
Then I took a different path.
"Like father, like son" isn't
always inevitable, Mr. Snart.
- I had a full boat.
- As did I.
Full of kings,
which beats your pair of queens.
- Don't I look busy to you?
- (STAMMERS) I'm sorry. I...
You spill another drop of
that whiskey, and you will be.
Just because you're losing,
doesn't mean you have to
pick on the waitstaff.
Mind your own business, Grandpa.
Unhand the lady.
Now, now, boys. Let's just take it easy.
Oh, when my friend here
is being reasonable,
we know we have a problem.
I'm not the one with the problem, you are.
- (GUNSHOT)
- (PEOPLE GASPING)
(BODY THUDS)
You killed him.
You're welcome.
Clearly, the deceased
was a friend of yours,
- but my friend here--
- Your friend drew first,
got put down, it was a clean shot.
Do we look like we care about clean?
He has a point.
(GROANING)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (MAN SCREAMING)
- (PIANO KEYS SMASHING)
- (GRUNTING)
(GUNSHOT)
MAN: All right!
Play time is over.
Anybody's got a problem
with that, they answer to me.
Thank you, Mister...
Hex. Jonah Hex.
You're not from around here, are you?
No. Uh, my friends and I
are from out of town.
Way out of town.
JONAH: All right.
Why don't you folks tell me
where you're really from?
RAY: I'm not sure that's
any of your business, sir.
Let me rephrase that.
Tell me when y'all are from.
You seven stick out
like a dog in a manger.
Like you said, we're not from around here.
You think you are the first time travelers
I've ever come across?
Uh, yes.
Where is he? I got some words
that need saying.
Where's who?
Rip Hunter.
(TAPPING)
What is it about you people
that whenever we go to a new timeline,
you feel the need to pick up
strays?
Nice.
I didn't get to see it last time around.
Last time?
A long story which we will not be telling.
My coat suits you good.
- What are you doing here, Jonah?
- I was collecting on a bounty,
wetting my whistle,
when your friends here
got in a lot of trouble.
We might've gotten into
a barroom brawl, back in town.
Well, that was entirely predictable.
One of them poured lead into
a member of the Stillwater gang.
- Mr. Rory.
- Snart, actually.
Ah, that was going to be my next guess.
This guy tried to kill Grey.
Snart saved him.
And brought this town a whole
lot of hell in the bargain.
Those boys you were trading
hands with in the saloon?
They're all members
of the Stillwater gang.
Why can't a gang
ever be a bunch of good guys?
Jeb Stillwater and his friends
have been raiding this town
for the past three months.
Stealing, robbing, killing.
Well, he'll have to go through us.
No, he won't.
No doubt, your little ruckus
has already placed the timeline at risk,
to say nothing for potentially
alerting the Hunters
to our presence here.
Sounds like someone's planning
on busting out of town again.
- Leaving already?
- No. No.
Look, this town is being terrorized
by the Stillwater gang.
And I aim to do something about it.
RORY: You "aim to"?
You getting all native on us, Haircut?
Look, we signed on to this mission--
To stop Vandal Savage.
To be heroes.
And saving a town from
a marauding gang of criminals,
that is what heroes do.
(CHUCKLES) Quite a posse of saints
you're riding along with nowadays.
Hey, bridge is that way.
Yeah, I'm not going to the bridge. I'm...
Where am I going, Gideon?
GIDEON: The valley you described is
consistent with Albano Gulch.
- Yeah, there.
- Okay, wait. Why?
(SIGHS)
Back at the saloon, I ran into a woman
and she caused me to have
more memory flashes,
so I think I might've known her
in one of my past lives.
And if so, she might be able
to help me find Carter.
Wait, so you're just gonna run
out there and try and find her?
Actually, I was planning on flying.
You want a partner in crime?
Okay, fine.
But you're definitely not carrying me.
How do you propose we get there?
(CLEARS THROAT)
Howdy. I'm Ray--
John Wayne.
What do you want, Mr. Wayne?
Well, I reckon you could use
another hand with the Stillwater gang.
You boys have any experience
with law enforcement?
Well, I have a fair bit of
experience fighting crime.
Congratulations, then.
- You're making me your deputy?
- Nope.
Just made you the new sheriff.
Excuse me, what?
Stillwater gang's been shooting
up this town for months now.
It's only by the grace of the good Lord
that I'm not pushing up daisies myself.
And I am done with pushing my luck.
But you're the sheriff.
Congratulations.
By the way,
you might find a warrant or two
out for me around these parts.
You know, we have stuff back
on the ship that can fix your...
- You know...
- Fix what?
Nope, nothing. Never mind.
(PIANO MUSIC PLAYING)
- What can I get you?
- Information.
Some friends of mine
are looking for Jeb Stillwater.
Are they the same friends
that shot Billy Conlon
and beat on the Stillwater posse?
I can guarantee you, he'll find you.
That being said, we'd very much
like to find him first.
Got any more of them greenbacks?
Let me go find a map.
(SNIFFLES)
Excuse me, ma'am? Are you all right?
I'm fine. I just want to be alone.
I understand. I'm new to these parts,
but I didn't think it was customary
for a lady to drink alone.
Tonic water. It's for my son.
I just needed a moment to myself.
Is everything all right?
I should be getting back to my boy.
If there's something wrong with him,
perhaps I can be of assistance.
I happen to be a scientist.
That's kind, but I'm afraid
there's nothing you can do.
My boy is going to die.
What's wrong with him?
(DOOR OPENS)
He has the consumption, they say.
Tuberculosis.
He's been like this, on and off,
for about a year now.
He always wanted to see the American West.
Our doctor thought a constitutional
might do him some good.
It hasn't, clearly.
You know there are medicines that--
The doctor here says he has a day,
maybe two, if he's lucky.
Does he look lucky to you, Mister...
I don't know your name.
It's Martin.
- Hello, young man.
- We call him Bertie.
Bertie.
Your mother tells me
you wanted to come out West.
Can't imagine you've seen much of it yet.
I want to ride a stagecoach.
Well, in that case,
I encourage you to get better.
- (WEAKLY) My mom, she's not sure I will.
- (SIGHS)
Well, then you must prove
your mother wrong.
So you can ride that stagecoach.
- (MEN SHOUTING)
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (MEN CLAMORING)
One of mine is dead.
And this here town's gonna pay.
Now, who the hell are you supposed to be?
John Wayne. Salvation's new sheriff.
And this here town is under my protection.
Well, you being new and all,
you don't know about
the arrangement that we got.
See, me and my boys, we ride into town,
we take whatever we want.
In exchange for what?
Not killing nobody.
Well, that sounds reasonable and all,
but arrangement's over.
Arrangement's over, boys.
(MEN SNICKERING)
They teach you numbers
where it is you're from?
'Cause the way I see it,
there's only one of you
- and a whole mess of us.
- (METAL CLANGING)
(HORSES WHINNYING)
You get out of town
and you don't come back.
Or the next bullet goes in your eye.
I got sharpshooters all around.
You really wanna test me?
Let's ride, boys.
(MEN URGING HORSES)
(CROWD CHEERING)
Nice, Haircut.
(LAUGHS) Dude, that was badass!
Let's not oversell it.
Well, running a bad guy out of town
has always been on my bucket list!
"Bucket list"?
A list of things one hopes
to accomplish before they die.
Well, you better hope it's
a real short list, stringbean.
We can handle the Stillwater gang.
Well, you're all just tearing up
the 1870s, aren't you?
Stillwater and his gang's
like a hornet's nest,
and your friends here keep poking at it.
They saved the town
from being raided, man.
Today. But what about tomorrow?
Or the day after that?
For a bunch of time travelers,
you don't seem to understand
the future much.
The day will come when you all leave.
And Salvation will end up like Calvert.
- What's a Calvert?
- A closed matter.
A word, Mr. Hex?
I believe you've all done enough
for one day.
Well, now I definitely want
to know what a Calvert is.
Then it's a good thing we have
access to a supercomputer.
Gideon?
GIDEON: Calvert was a town
in Oklahoma circa 1868.
"Was"?
(EAGLE SCREECHING)
There's something weird
going on with your face.
What?
You're smiling.
I didn't know you could do that.
- Well, don't tell anyone my secret.
- (LAUGHS)
It's just all of this...
It's so pure. So simple.
I'd say I miss simple,
but I guess you have
to experience something first
to miss it.
I know what you mean.
I've been having more
and more memory flashes lately,
and I'm not entirely sure why.
Well, if this woman was a friend
of yours in a past life,
hopefully, she'll have
another piece for your puzzle.
(THUNDER CLAPPING)
I feel like I'm being drawn to this place.
- Which way?
- There.
(URGING HORSE)
You know, stealing's against the law.
And the sheriff of these here parts--
How did you know I was
appropriating this medicine?
GIDEON: That was my fault, Professor.
Et tu, Gideon?
I suppose this is going to
earn me a lecture
on the perils of upsetting the timeline
by introducing futuristic
medicine to the 19th century.
Well, it seems you've already
given it to yourself.
Except this isn't futuristic medicine.
I've had Gideon fabricate
simple streptomycin for me.
Excuse me.
Which won't be used in medical
treatments for another 70 years.
This is about a boy in town
who's dying of an easily curable disease.
Just as you couldn't turn your back
on Jeb Stillwater and his gang,
I can't turn mine
on this boy and his mother.
Except Dr. Palmer is using
19th century technology
to deal with Stillwater, whereas you--
Just spare me the lecture, Captain Hunter.
You of all people.
This isn't about the mission, Martin.
Do you not recall what happened
when Dr. Palmer left
a bit of his suit back in 1975
and nearly destroyed Central City?
That was an accident.
I'm not talking about our mission
or Dr. Palmer's technological gaffe.
Calvert.
That town clearly holds
some emotional resonance for you
judging from the looks you've
been exchanging with Mr. Hex.
How do you know it's a town?
Gideon?
RAY: Calvert, Oklahoma.
What happened to you there, Rip?
And why is it so important to you?
Because the past is prologue.
It's not uncommon for a criminal
posse such as Mr. Stillwater's
to sack and pillage towns
which they find "uncooperative."
So, Stillwater's done this before?
In the case of Calvert,
it was Quentin Turnbull's doing.
But it was my fault.
I'd come to Calvert on a mission
from the Time Masters.
This was years before
my son, Jonas, was born.
Jonas. Did you name your son after Hex?
After my mission was completed,
I felt unable to leave.
I'd grown so attached to this era,
a victim of the same time drift
you experienced in 1958.
But, obviously, you left at some point.
Left? I had to tear myself away
from the time period.
For fear that I would never see
my then future wife, Miranda,
ever again.
Turnbull attacked Calvert
the very next day.
So, you can understand why I must act.
No, Martin, I don't.
As I said before,
this is advanced medicine,
unsuitable to the period,
to say nothing of what this boy's survival
might do to the timeline.
Be that as it may,
I refuse to live with the regret
I see on your face right now.
The information Mr. Stein got
from the barkeep paid out.
I know where
the Stillwater gang is holed up.
All right. Let's ride. Up high.
JONAH: You coming, Rip?
That's what I thought.
(BEEPING)
(DOOR SLIDES SHUT)
I wonder why she lives alone,
all the way out here.
Because I value my privacy.
Wait, wait, wait. Don't you remember me?
From the saloon back in Salvation.
I remember you,
you wigged-out little girl.
If I'd wanted to talk to you then,
I would've talked to you then.
I ain't fixing to talk to you now.
Now get off of my land!
Listen, we're not trying
to start any trouble.
Do you want that pretty little
mouth of yours filled with lead?
Your friend has a colorful personality.
I ain't got friends. I keep to myself.
She's right.
She wasn't my friend.
I was her.
WOMAN: We sat for that picture
at the county fair, 1830.
He looked like such a gentleman.
- What was his name?
- Hannibal.
Hannibal Hawkes.
And what happened?
Was it Savage?
What is this? It looks familiar.
That was ours in our first life.
I remember.
We crossed with Savage in Jefferson City.
He had it with him.
We escaped with it and our lives.
Do you still have it?
We lost it to bandits about a year later.
We heard that the Pinkertons
were after the same bandits,
but we just--
Hey, what is it?
Objects present at the moment
of my... Our first death,
can be used to kill Savage.
So if I can get my hands
on that bracelet, then--
You're gonna try to kill Savage
with a bracelet?
- You need to stop.
- Stop what?
Fighting our destiny.
Ain't destiny what brought you here?
What part of destiny is she fighting?
All of it.
We get reborn, we find Hannibal,
Carter, then Savage finds us,
and then we die. That's the way it is.
That's the way it's always gonna be.
I don't believe that.
Well, I have a few more years on you.
You can't break the cycle.
That's why I live out here. Alone.
For the rest of your life?
Well, I guess I had to figure
that out the hard way.
I was still a young woman
when Savage left me a widow.
Instead of waiting for him
to find me and kill me,
so that I could love
my Hannibal in the next life,
I tried to find love in this one.
Talk about a curse.
What happened?
He was a good man.
But he wasn't a soulmate.
It was like fate was trying to
break us apart.
Eventually, fate broke both our hearts.
So, I made a promise to myself
that I wasn't going to do that
to a person again.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- No, I'm who's sorry.
To have to be the one to let you know
that you're never gonna be able
to love anyone else. Ever.
How much do you know
about our previous lives?
I reckon not a lot
because you didn't recognize me.
So let me tell you
that we did love other men.
Loved them real and pure.
But it never ended well. Not ever.
Tragedy or heartbreak,
that's how it always ends
if the man's not Carter.
RORY: We could've used Sara
on this roundup.
JONAH: A lady? You crazy?
Just remember we're here to
arrest Stillwater, not kill him.
He's always this much
of a stick in the mud?
Yes.
Oh!
It's a miracle.
It's not a miracle, I can assure you.
- Uh, Mrs. Neal--
- Sarah.
Sarah.
When the illness is gone,
I need you to promise me
that you'd take what's left
of the medicine and burn it,
vials and all.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
Yes, I shall do it.
Sarah...
I wish you well.
Thank you.
I really must be going.
(HORSES NEIGHING)
Oh, damn.
(GUNSHOTS)
These boys got some stones.
(GROWLS)
(GUN COCKS)
(GUNSHOT)
RAY: Jeb Stillwater, you are under arrest.
You have the right to remain silent.
You have the right to an attorney.
There won't be Miranda rights
for another 100 years.
JONAH: Fall back! Fall back!
Jax!
(GUNS CLICKING)
We gotta go!
Not without Jax!
We got Stillwater. Means we got leverage.
Live to fight another day
or die tonight. Your choice. Hya!
Where is Stillwater?
He's knocked out cold in the MedBay.
Well, this is a simple matter.
We trade Stillwater for
Jefferson as Mr. Hex suggested.
It's not that simple.
If we release Stillwater,
we're back to square one.
And the town is still in danger.
So is the kid.
And we'll figure out a way to get him back
without releasing Stillwater.
JONAH: I got a notion.
Set up a quick draw.
You win, you get your guy back.
You lose, you set Stillwater free.
- And by "lose," you mean--
- Get shot and killed.
Oh, great, pistols at high noon.
Finally, someone's talking sense.
There has to be another way. A better way.
JONAH: Sure.
Go after Stillwater with
all your gear from the future.
I don't know how that'll sit
with your captain, though.
Mmm. Let's assume it's a bad idea.
So, who's standing in the
middle of Main Street?
I'll do it.
Raymond, now is not the time to
indulge your cowboy fantasies.
No one else is stepping forward.
Plus, I'm a decent shot.
At least I was with an air rifle.
I can't believe you're encouraging this.
No, it's the only way.
Dr. Palmer is going to get himself killed.
I think you forfeited your right
to an opinion
when you refused to leave
the ship since we've been here.
I had good reason.
Because of Calvert?
Yes, but not in the way you think.
Leaving Calvert, leaving this era,
is one of the hardest things
I've ever had to do.
And why is that, Captain?
A Time Master is trained to do
his work without interference.
Which means not helping people
or being a hero.
But as you've seen, Dr. Palmer,
this era offers
many opportunities for heroism.
I found it
enticing.
And you still managed to leave.
Something's been bugging me
all these years.
If you'd known what Turnbull
was gonna do to Calvert,
would you have left?
That's the thing, Jonah.
I did know.
(GROANS)
- I deserved that.
- You deserve a lot worse.
You knew and you still left?
Of course I knew. I was a Time Master.
And therein lay the problem.
Like Raymond, like Martin,
I felt the pull of heroism,
of this era's penchant for
being rife with opportunities
to make a difference.
That's one of the things
that called to me,
and that is why I had to leave.
Because had I stayed,
I could no longer
have remained a Time Master.
But I'm no longer a Time Master.
Which is why I'll face Stillwater.
Wait.
- I said that I would do it--
- Get yourself shot and killed?
It's appreciated.
But I'd rather you stayed alive.
Send word to Stillwater's posse.
I believe high noon
is in less than three hours.
You want to talk about it?
Not really.
(BEEPING)
You don't have to listen to her, you know.
Is this you not talking about it?
No, this is me ignoring you saying
you don't wanna talk about it.
Look, I get it.
Things may have gone very wrong
for Old-West-you and whoever
she loved who wasn't Carter.
But?
But Old-West-you didn't know Ray Palmer.
She didn't love Ray Palmer.
You do.
And you have to live your life.
She already lived hers.
You think Hunter can pull this off?
Reasonably.
If not, I got dibs on
that newfangled revolver of his.
You sure about this?
Well, if anything, it feels good
to be out here again,
in this era.
Well, don't get too attached.
That is what I keep telling myself.
I'll be drawing for Sheriff Palmer.
How do me and my boys know
you're gonna keep your word?
Sheriff Palmer's a straight shooter.
Then he should be the one in the street.
(GUN COCKING)
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
Jackson, are you all right?
Yeah. Did you just shoot somebody for me?
Yes. You're welcome.
I don't think we're done here yet.
(CROWD PANICKING)
- Oh, no.
- (COCKS GUN)
They found us.
(CROWD SCREAMING)
Ah! Friends! Welcome!
I think you'll find this
slightly more effective
than your current sidearm.
Yes, I will be wanting that back
by the way.
And you'll be needing this.
What about revealing our
future tech to the locals?
It doesn't seem to bother them. Shall we?
- What about our guns?
- Sorry. Grabbed what I could.
That's what's up! You all better
stay the hell away from us!
PROFESSOR STEIN: Calm down, Jefferson.
- Traitor.
- Not possible.
I was never on your side.
I was on my side.
(GROANING)
You'll never win.
Wake up, pal. We already did.
Fool. The Time Masters
have initiated Omega Protocol.
The Pilgrim is coming for you, Chronos.
Your deaths are just a matter of time.
(THUDS)
Yeah, yeah.
Well, that was easy.
- You're not staying.
- Are you?
Me? No. You know I can't.
But this town still needs a sheriff.
Well, I'm not the law-and-order type.
Nor the staying-in-one-place type, either.
Well, we have that much
in common at least.
At least.
Be well, Jonah.
Nice thing about my world, for you,
it ain't going anywhere.
Perhaps we will see each other
again, my friend.
Yeah, I reckon that'd be okay.
Interesting fella.
Indeed.
This town's seen a lot of "interesting."
Suppose you got one of those doohickeys
that erases people's memories
or something?
No.
But skepticism and disbelief
are a far more effective tool.
Ah. So if anybody here talks,
no one will believe them.
Would you, Mr. Snart?
I'm not going to pretend
to understand what I saw.
I'd prefer that you didn't
tell anyone about it, either.
That goes for you too, young Master Neal.
My last name's Wells.
- Excuse me?
- His father's surname.
Herbert George Wells.
You're H.G. Wells.
"H.G."? I like that.
Astonishing.
KENDRA: God, it feels so good
to be in normal clothes again.
The people here need to invent
fabric softener, ASAP.
Is that all?
It's just that you seemed a little off
ever since you came back
from your walkabout.
- Ray, I told you.
- Something.
But I don't think it's the whole truth.
I thought that we decided
to be honest with each other.
And I am.
I am being honest with you, Ray.
Look, I met a woman
and I learned some things.
I told you, about killing Savage.
And the rest...
The rest is what she thought.
Not what I think.
I don't have to listen to her.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Well, I think they're waiting
for us on the bridge.
We should go.
PROFESSOR STEIN: So, how are you feeling?
Given your concerns
about becoming addicted
to this era once again.
The last time I left, Martin,
I did to be with those closest to me.
I'm doing the same again.
- So where to now?
- Or more specifically, when?
Is there another Fragmentation
we can hide out in?
Yeah, unfortunately,
matters are quite not so simple.
(SCOFFS) How did I know you were
gonna say something like that?
- Rip's buddies.
- And yours.
The Time Masters have issued
Omega Protocols on all of us.
Well, that sounds pretty terrible.
RORY: The worst kind of order
they can issue.
They've sent the Pilgrim after us.
Who's the Pilgrim?
The Pilgrim is the Time Masters'
most deadly assassin.
And she will stop at nothing
until each and every one of you are dead.
Ooh, scary. Pretty sure
we can handle ourselves.
Indeed.
Which is why she won't be going after
the present-day versions of you.
She's hunting our younger selves.
And she won't stop
until each and every one of us
has been erased from the timeline.
(GUN FIRES)
English - SDH