How will we be remembered?
Will it be
for saving the world twice?
No, we're the team who broke time.
That's right, history
has been torn to shreds,
which means it's up to us
to put it back together again
piece by piece,
fixing these so- called anachronisms
before we get torn to shreds.
So please, don't call us heroes.
We're legends.
Zari Tomaz?
Previously on Legends of Tomorrow...
Come with us if you want to live.
That's enough, Zari.
You're not going anywhere without us.
My brother had powers
because he wielded this.
He fought against A.R.G.U.S.'
injustices, so he was hunted.
- We all were.
- Come with us.
What would you rather do,
hide from A.R.G.U.S.
your whole life or time travel?
- Lily.
- I'm pregnant.
Congratulations.
Hello?
What's your name?
Mine's Ray Palmer.
52-19. I repeat, we have a 52-19.
Subject on the move.
Lock down all exits.
Code Red.
Engaging lockdown protocols.
He went this way.
Got him.
He's headed for the lab.
Can't let you go in there, Raymond.
You're not gonna hurt me.
I'm, I'm just a kid.
And if you want
to make it to adulthood,
you'll start seeing
the reality of the situation.
So why don't you calm down
and we'll have ourselves a nice chat?
There you go.
Now come with us.
What makes a hero?
Is it powers?
Strength? Bravery?
No.
A hero is forged
by his or her relationships.
Our bonds of brotherhood
or sisterhood.
That is why I'm taking you all
through the ten-step
team-building process
I perfected at Palmer Tech.
Step one, part one: icebreakers.
Dude, we've been stuck on a ship
that has one bathroom.
I think we know each other
well enough.
And your timing couldn't be worse,
given that we're being chased
by a water-wielding assassin
and the Time Bureau.
We need to grow as a team.
First step is two truths and a lie.
- It's gonna be fun.
- Lie.
I haven't started yet. Look...
I know you guys probably think
this is lame...
Truth.
But we have a new crew member,
and it is important
for Zari to bond with us,
not only as team members
but as individuals.
Yeah, well, I'm no hero,
and I'm not a member of any team.
Besides, I've already
have you all figured out.
The old guy wants to be anywhere
but on this ship.
These two have some
will-they-won't-they thing going on.
Rory's been drunk since breakfast.
Jax is wondering if I'm single.
And your ship's still mad at me
for doing a teeny hack
on her subsystems.
Now, what's this about one bathroom?
Oy vey.
- Guys, guys.
- You're right, Haircut,
this is gonna be fun.
Let's just skip to step two:
trust falls.
Now, to demonstrate,
Mick, who hated me when we first met,
will fall trustingly into my arms.
All right, you promised me
good coin for doing this.
And you said you weren't
gonna say that out loud.
Well, just lean back and let go
'cause I'm not going anywhere, buddy.
What the hell?
Gideon, what happened to Ray?
According to public record,
Mr. Palmer died in 1988.
Wait, Ray's dead?
He better be.
How could Ray be dead?
He was just right here.
Yeah, well, he owes me money.
Gideon, you said Ray died in 1988.
Mr. Palmer went missing
on October 31st, 1988.
They recovered the body
two days later.
He was found in the woods,
dead, only eight years old.
If Ray disappeared on Halloween,
then we'll just go back to before
whatever happens, happens.
Gideon, get us to October 30th, 1988.
Wait. Are we time traveling?
You better buckle up.
Arriving in 1988.
I should have said there are some
really strange side effects.
Buddy! Hey, you're alive.
Man.
Oh, wow. I love you, man.
Me too.
And always ready for a bro-hug.
I'm in the paper.
- And I'm dead?
- Not yet.
We're in 1988, the day
before you disappeared.
Okay.
Well, I guess the fact
that I'm still here
means temporal permanence
hasn't set in.
Which means
we can still save my life,
and enjoy 1988 while we're at it.
Trust Ray to find
the bright side of dying.
Are you sure this is right?
That sweater's totally awesome.
- How do I look?
- Honestly?
Like you're being strangled
by a Muppet.
Can't believe people
used to wear this stuff.
Hey, speak for yourself.
I look good in any era.
I can't wait
to show you guys my home.
First we have to go to Pizza Master,
best slice in town.
Then we have to go to Video Village.
I can't tell you how much
of my allowance I spent there.
So you're always this positive,
even when you're dead?
How can you pretend
like everything's okay?
I'm not pretending. I believe it.
I found that
if I can trust in myself,
I can believe everything's okay,
and it usually is.
It's called positive thinking.
Give it a shot.
Is he for real?
School's almost out.
- You ready, kids?
- Yeah, let's motor.
This is amazing!
Blue skies, smiling kids,
an actual white picket fence.
Well, I think it's actually
a trellis, but yeah, same thing.
Wow, there I am.
Thanks for the pop quiz,
Mrs. Garvin.
It really reinforced
some fundamentals.
Yeah, that's definitely you.
Okay, now, whoever's
targeting me could be anywhere,
so keep a lookout
for anything unusual.
Guys, here I come.
I mean little me, he's coming at you.
Catch up with me
on Main Street, and...
keep me alive.
Got eyes on Ray to make a move.
Well, it looks like
you're taking a detour.
Did you frequent the Ivy Town
Newsstand as a boy?
Yeah, I must be picking up
the new issue
of "Scientific American."
I was more of a "National Geographic"
boy myself.
Once a geek, always a geek.
Well, whoever's after me
could be there, so...
Yeah, we'll stick on him.
Okay, I got somebody
checking out magazines
and one shopkeeper.
I could knock this place off
with a water pistol.
Okay, new mission:
keep me away from Mick.
I don't want today to be the day
I descend into a life of crime.
Well, Haircut...
looks like it's too late.
Wait, what does that mean?
You're by the candy bars.
Well, get me away from there.
- That stuff's poison.
- Yeah, that's not all.
Wait, what does that mean?
- You're shoplifting.
- Wait.
- What?
- Damn, Haircut.
You had balls.
I've never stolen a thing in my life.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, you have now.
I'm proud of you.
Little you's on the move.
Well, stop him.
Me. Stop both of us.
I'm no rat.
Ready at the home front.
See, now this?
This is a time machine.
I got eyes on little Ray.
- We got hostile incoming.
- What is it?
Assassin? Time Bureau?
Almost as bad.
Bullies.
Hey, Palmer, let's play.
No, it's just Gus and Ty.
We were friends.
Very funny, guys.
Do you want me to rough them up?
Nah, nah, nah, it's...
They were just kidding.
Give that back. Come on.
- Give that back!
- Here.
Beginning to think maybe
they weren't kidding.
This is boring. Let's go, Ty.
I can't believe he actually
thinks we're friends.
Bye, guys!
I guess kids are mean
in any time period.
'Cause love is blind
We circled the neighborhood,
checked the yard.
- It seems normal.
- Scary normal.
Maybe young Ray died of boredom.
No, something's up.
Something's wrong.
Look, maybe it was the candy.
Maybe I overdosed
on high-fructose corn syrup
and food coloring.
Or maybe your killer aborted
when we showed up.
Let's get back to the ship
and check the historical record.
Give me a minute.
Dinner time.
Got you gummy bears,
licorice, Nougat Nummies.
Wait till we go trick-or-treating
tomorrow.
There's a whole lot more
where that came from.
I'm talking to someone in my room.
Knew you were hungry.
Coast is clear, Gumball.
You can come on out.
Guys.
I think I know what kills me.
It's a Dominator.
So aliens are real.
Yep, and those ones
are called Dominators.
They're nasty too.
Capable of telepathy,
advanced technology,
and, the fun one, tearing
people limb from limb.
- Great.
- The last time we faced them,
they almost wiped out meta-humans
and made us fight each other.
And worse, fight together.
And now little me kidnapped one
and is treating it like a house pet,
which would be cool
if it wasn't deadly.
Maybe the baby Dominator
hasn't developed all
of its abilities yet.
The infant of the species
has the strength of the adult
with none of its discretion.
It can also mind-control
subjects at will.
How can you not remember
befriending an alien?
Because I didn't.
It never happened to me.
The Dominator is an anachronism.
- It's time-displaced.
- Right.
So we have to get the baby Dominator
out of Ray's bedroom
and back to where it belongs.
And how are we supposed to do that?
Well, it should be easy.
All we have to do
is sneak into my house
tomorrow when my mom's at work
and I'm at school
and kidnap the Dominator.
I even know where the spare key is.
Like stealing candy from a baby.
But not as fun.
Yo. Where were you, man?
- You missed the team meeting.
- Oh, you finished already?
I was just on my way,
but I can ask Gideon to debrief me.
Psychic connection,
so I know you're hiding something.
I have no idea
what you're referring to.
Zari was right.
You don't actually want to be
on the Waverider, do you?
Don't be ridiculous.
I am as committed to this mission
as I've ever been.
What's going on?
Grey's keeping some sort of secret.
You want to know what's going on?
Well, do you know
what's going on with him?
I have my suspicions, yeah,
and I have my ways
of extracting information.
Home, sweet home.
- Wait.
- What? What is it?
No shoes on the carpet.
I guess I can probably
let go of that now.
- Yeah.
Oh, man, never thought
I'd be here again.
My brother Sydney and I
used to fight over this thing.
He always wanted
to play "Tecmo Bowl,"
and all I wanted to do
was play "Legend of Zelda."
Yeah, the only video games we had
were military training simulations,
but yeah, that sounds hard for you.
Our record player.
- Hey, who's Billy "Jo-el"?
- What?
"Piano Man"? "River of Dreams"?
Really? Wow.
You really did live in a dystopia.
No time to waltz
down memory lane, Ray.
Find the Dominator
and get out of there
before anyone sees you all grown up.
Dude, I didn't know
you were a Billy Joel fan.
What's your favorite album?
Everyone says "The Stranger,"
but for my money, "Nylon Curtain,"
his Beatles tribute album,
is super ambitious.
Let us know
when you're heading out.
We're ready for retrieval.
I never thought
I'd be back in my room.
Guys, we're in my room.
It's in the closet.
Okay, no sudden movements.
Leave it to young you
to see the best in that thing.
Though you were pretty lonely.
What? I wasn't lonely.
I was just choosing
to focus on my studies.
This is probably just
my scientific curiosity
getting the better of me...
- Great.
- Again.
Popcorn's ready.
Aren't you supposed to be in school?
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah, this is a problem.
No. Yesterday I'm shoplifting.
Today I'm truant.
This thing is turning me into Rory.
Young you is on the way.
Hey, no, get off me!
No, no, no, no, no, I am not a toy!
Stop that.
Toys are our friends.
I don't remember you.
Come on, this is my favorite.
It's 1.30 already. It's morning.
Yes.
And what a lovely morning.
Good morning
We've talked the whole night through
- Is that music?
- Yeah, "Singing in the Rain,"
only the best musical ever.
Not as good as "Fiddler on the Roof."
It's great to stay up late
I love that show.
Good morning to you
What?
We got a new problem.
Do you anyone who owns
a green station wagon
with fake wood paneling?
What's my mom doing home?
Dude, you never mentioned
your mom was hot.
Why would I ever mention that?
To you and you and you and you
Good morning, good morning
We've gabbed the whole night through
Good morning, good morning to you
Nothing could be grander
Than to be in Louisiana
In the morning
Raymond Caswell Palmer!
You have to hide.
Where are you, Raymond?
Why did I get a call saying
that you didn't show up
to school today?
- Mom.
- I'm sorry, Mom.
I was sick.
Sick. Sick.
No kidding, of course you were sick.
Sick from eating all this candy.
You can forget
about trick-or-treating tonight.
Guys, the Dominator's getting angry.
Somebody needs to distract my mom.
Fine, I'll take one for the team.
Raymond, this is the second time
this month
that I've had to leave work for you.
First you're starting a fire
in the science lab,
and then, what, now you're sitting
at home skipping school?
School is boring.
I already know all the answers.
Too bad, you're going back,
so grab your stuff.
Let's go. Come on.
What was that?
Yeah, now would be great, guys.
What now?
Is there a cougar on the premises?
Excuse me?
Animal control.
One of the neighbors said
that they heard some strange noises
coming from your home.
So that's what he's been up to.
Yeah, we just got done
wrestling a bear
and saving, like, a busload of kids.
They were super cute.
We just need to come in
and take a look around.
Sure, come on in.
- Whatever you need.
- Thanks.
Whatever.
It's my son.
He's always sneaking off
into the woods
and bringing back strays.
Don't worry, we have seen it all.
Yeah.
I just Ray would make
normal friends, you know?
I mean, he would rather spend
his time with his animals
and movies or his weird inventions.
Sometimes I worry
that he just gets,
lost in his own head.
Hey, I hope kid you
didn't hear all that.
She always said
she liked my inventions.
- Captain Lance.
- What's up?
I am detecting the approach
of another timeship.
What if the assassin
followed us here?
We need to plead for clemency
with the Time Bureau
and ask for help.
Whosever here could be tracking us.
Stay off the comms.
I'm gonna check it out.
You keep watch here.
I'll be watching very, very closely.
They know about you.
We need to go.
No one cares about me anyway.
Oh, you need a friend.
Oh, no.
Come on.
Oh, no, I've got a play date.
Zari, stay with me.
I don't want to spook the Dominator
or traumatize my younger self.
I should have stayed in 2042.
Ray, hold on.
How do you know my name?
It's a long, mostly irritating story.
The only thing that matters is,
I'm here to save your life.
No, you want Gumball.
Well, you can't have him.
And I thought grown-up Ray
was annoying.
Listen to me, kid.
You don't want to be alone
with that thing.
You don't know him. We're friends.
Your friend is gonna kill you.
If I don't do it first.
What's going on?
This about Grey?
You said the professor's been
acting all squirrelly
about where he's been.
- Squirrelly?
- Yeah.
When you're on the run,
someone usually cracks.
Burns to crew to save themselves.
Burns the crew how?
Cutting a deal with the Time Bureau.
You think Grey is ratting us out
to the Time Bureau?
The old man wants off the boat,
thinks we're in too deep.
Yeah, but he wouldn't do that.
Really?
Then who's been boosting
the jumpship while we sleep?
- Gideon.
- I believe Mr. Rory
is alluding to the fact that someone
has erased the jumpship's travel log.
Someone's been sneaking off the ship
and snitching to the Time Bureau.
And if there's one thing
I hate more than pigs...
it's a rat.
How far could he have gone?
He's just a little kid.
Well, maybe if you hadn't stayed
to flirt with Ray's mother.
First of all, I didn't flirt
with Ray's mother.
I merely charmed her.
I can't help that I'm charming.
Wait, wait, wait, are you jealous?
Nathaniel, I just think
we should keep it simple.
Friends.
Like we were before
all of this happened.
I mean, that was still fun, right?
Right, right,
if we just had a timeship,
we could go back to where
we never even lived together.
- Nate, don't.
- With a Swedish bed
we never quite assembled.
I believe it was called
a Double Dorff.
- Just erased it and...
- Nate.
I'm getting something this way.
The mobile team
is setting up a lab now.
We need to find the Dominator
before it finds us.
- What about the kid?
- He comes with us.
We can't have this getting out.
Looks like a false alarm.
No sign of the Time Bureau here.
Gideon says the professor's
been spending
a lot of time down here.
The last time I was down here,
this place was just a storage room.
Looks like the professor's
been busy behind our backs.
So what? He's a professor, man.
That's what professors do.
They invent stuff.
- Stuff like...
- Like what?
Like this.
Best bet is,
this is some
sort of radio transmitter
that communicates through time.
With the Time Bureau?
I can't believe it.
Grey really is a traitor.
Kid, I know you're in there.
Oh, good, you found us.
You shall not pass.
There's no time for make-believe.
You are in actual danger.
Step down, you knave.
Zari, think like a kid.
You just have to play along.
I'm...
I'm here from a neighboring kingdom
to speak to Sir Galahad.
And?
- Sir Gumball.
- And...
Sir Gumball.
Yeah, good, that's good. Keep going.
It's an honor, my lieges.
Got it. I repeat,
- subject has been located.
- You lied to me.
No, I didn't. There he is! Get him!
- You're coming with us.
- Leave me alone!
Leave us alone.
No!
Careful. The Dominator's
sedation is wearing off.
Don't worry, this little
fella's not going anywhere.
Doesn't need to go anywhere.
Using its telepathic powers,
even a juvenile
could control us at its will,
force us to set it free
or do each other in.
I've seen it before.
This will suppress
its neural impulses,
neutralizing its powers.
As well as preventing it from
communicating with its mother,
the queen.
We have the girl in a storage room,
and the boy's in questioning now.
Get him to tell us
everything he knows
where he found the creature
and how long he's had it.
- Then what do we do with him?
- Make it so he can't tell
anybody else.
You mean...
This queen, if the baby
can control our minds,
what is she capable of doing?
Mental projection,
supplanting thoughts and sensations
into its victim's mind.
Also known to protect
their young at any cost.
You know what I'm looking for.
A breath mint?
Dermatologist recommendation?
Reese's Pieces?
Oh, right, your kid.
You're looking for your kid.
And if you let me go, I'll help you.
Your species cannot be trusted.
Look, I want to help you.
I do. You can't find him without me.
Agreed.
Going somewhere, Professor?
I don't have time to explain.
I'm taking the jumpship
whether you like it or not.
Yo, Mick, come on, man.
I just souped this baby up.
Jefferson, please, I need you
to help me get out of 1988.
Help you?
After you've been lying to me?
You've been sneaking out on us.
You erased the jump logs.
You're working with the Time Bureau.
What? Never.
What's in your back pocket,
Professor?
It's a trans-temporal communicator.
So you can talk to your
little Time Bureau friends.
No. So I can talk to my...
Hey, Dad.
My daughter.
Oh, and all of you guys.
- Hey, Lily.
- Dad?
I think it's time.
We're heading to the hospital now,
and you're gonna be here, right?
How could I miss the birth
of my first grandchild?
Good 'cause... This baby's coming.
Okay, I will see you there. Bye, Dad.
I took the jumpship back to 2017
so I could give Lily
the other communicator.
And you wiped the jump logs why?
Because I wanted you to know
that I was committed to you
and to the team.
I made the decision to stay
and I needed you to know
that I meant it.
Clearly, my subterfuge has...
robbed me of the chance to be
at the birth of my grandchild.
No.
We can take the Waverider.
What about the rest of the team?
- I'm sure they'll manage.
- You're serious?
Grey, it's your first grandkid.
Why would you think
I'd want you to miss that?
Come on, man, let's go.
What's going on? Where's kid Ray?
They're interrogating me. Him.
Code Red.
Engaging lockdown protocols.
Let's go.
So why don't you calm down
and we'll have ourselves
a nice little chat?
There you go.
Come with us.
You're real.
Go, go, go!
We got to move.
They won't stay down long.
We can't leave without Gumball.
Look, that thing is not your friend.
It may be cute and cuddly now,
but sooner or later,
it's gonna turn on you.
Gumball wouldn't do that.
We can save him, I know it.
Look, Raymond.
I get that you're lonely
and that you're just trying to cope.
But, buddy, you can't live
in a fantasy world forever.
- Ray.
- Look, trust me.
I understand that it hurts to learn
that the world isn't as perfect
as you want it to be.
But sooner or later...
you have to start facing reality.
Otherwise you're gonna end up
getting yourself killed.
Hey.
Listen to us.
We're gonna save your friend
and make it out of here together.
All right?
Because that's what brave knights do.
Right, Sir Galahad?
Let's do it.
Where are you guys?
Not sure exactly.
Looks like they turned the rec center
into some kind of government
research facility.
We're on our way to save
the baby Dominator.
- What?
- It's a long story.
Well, that story's about
to get a lot more interesting
because his mom just landed
and she's looking for him.
Wait, the Dominator has a Mominator?
And it gets worse.
I think she might have read my mind.
- Wait, what did she see?
- Well, she's looking
for her baby.
The last time I saw him was...
At my house.
My mom's home.
If the queen finds her...
Don't worry,
we won't let that happen.
I'll keep watch for the queen.
- You check on Ray's mom.
- Okay.
How do I look? I'm kidding.
Animal control. Again.
Back to check out my crawl space?
Your who?
So what's your excuse this time?
Family of possums?
Come to wrestle a bear?
How did you make a family
of possums sound so sexy?
Well, you found
your animal right here.
But good luck controlling her.
Who's there?
Mrs. Palmer?
Please help! Help!
But if you're here, then...
It's a...
Wow, you are very powerful.
You have no idea.
Trick-or-treat!
Ray's mom, it's an honor
just to be nominated...
We both know it's too late
to stop this.
Well, maybe if we just
get to know each other...
Get away from him, you bitch.
I knew it, you're jealous.
No, she's messing with your mind.
She's making you see things.
That...
Nate, that is not Ray's mother.
Don't be ridiculous.
Of course it's Ray's mom.
Who else would it be? Oh, my God.
I kissed a Dominator.
And I liked it.
What's the matter?
Don't you think I'm pretty?
Hey, over here.
Super ambitious album.
Sara, we found the queen.
Awesome costume.
I'm almost back to the ship.
I'll fly to you,
and we'll try
to lure her onto the brig.
Oh, crap.
"Oh, crap" what?
All right, on to plan B.
Let's say somebody stole
the Waverider.
What if we give the queen
what she wants
and just hope she goes in peace?
You mean the baby? I'm already on it.
Gumball.
Don't move.
Step away.
You have no idea what
that thing is capable of.
We're taking it with us.
No one needs to get hurt.
Can't let you do that.
I don't think you want to do that.
You should really lower your weapons.
I... I can't.
He's controlling them.
Ray, turn it back on.
- No.
- No? What?
- What do you mean no?
- It'll hurt him.
He'll hurt all of us.
He wouldn't do that.
I can't believe I was this stubborn.
Look, if you don't listen
to me, we're all going to die.
Good morning
We've talked the whole night through
Good morning, good morning
To you
Good morning
Sunbeams will soon shine through
Good morning, good morning to you
- Good morning
It's great to stay up late
Good morning, good morning
- To you
- So we should go, right?
Yeah, yeah.
I told you he wouldn't hurt anyone.
You're right.
I should have trusted you.
I'm sorry for the tough love.
Good morning, good morning to you
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Left the movie show
The future wasn't bright
But came the dawn, the show goes on
And I don't want to say good night
Man, you guys are really good.
- Ray.
- Yeah, but they were just...
- Good morning
- Yep.
Good morning
Quick, I'm sure those agents
are already coming to their senses.
- Hey, we can use those.
- Those aren't ours.
We can't steal.
I knew you were a good kid.
But let's just make
an exception, just this once.
Guys, we've got the baby.
And we got the queen.
And she's trying to kill us.
Let's hope everyone gets here
at the same time,
or else we're gonna have
one angry alien mama.
We're gonna make it.
Are you sure it's okay
we borrowed the Waverider?
I'm sure they'll be fine.
We're never gonna make it.
They went this way!
God, I hope this works.
Hey, Gumball.
Mominator incoming!
I'll take her. This one's personal.
She put me in a cocoon.
Whoa, it's like "E.T."
- What's "E.T."?
- "What's 'E.T.'?"
Go ahead.
You have to go now.
You need your mom.
But we'll still be friends.
I'll be all right.
I have people here
to take care of me.
And I wouldn't have found them
without you.
Go on. Go on, little buddy.
Go to your mama.
See you later, Gumball.
I'm not crying.
I just have alien goo in my eye.
Yeah, me too.
Now I'm gonna go
brush my teeth forever.
Wait. Why?
I'm so glad
I could be here
to welcome you to this world.
I'm sure it's overwhelming,
and I'm sorry to say...
it doesn't really ever go away.
But this place...
it's also full...
of wonders.
Wonders
that I'm discovering even now.
Hey.
I'm sorry, man. I...
You almost missed this because of me,
because I didn't trust you, and...
No, I should have been...
I should have been honest
with you from the beginning.
You're as much a part of this family
as Lily and Clarissa and now
this little guy, Ronnie.
It's perfect that you're here
with us right now.
Mr. Rory, on the other hand,
is inexplicable.
I thought we should celebrate.
One for you.
- One for you.
- Thank you.
- And one for you.
- Man, dude, come on, man.
Not the baby.
Cute.
- What happened?
- Possums.
It's mating season.
They got all in your vents. So...
we got rid of them.
So you're saying one
of Ray's strays didn't do this?
Your son?
No, no, no. And...
don't worry, I'm sure
he'll grow out of that eventually.
You know, and...
I think you're doing
a really good job with him.
Yeah, so could we go now, please?
Yep.
I can't believe you made out
with my mom.
Look, man, it was the '80s.
Did the right thing, you know.
Letting him go.
He was my only real friend.
We were supposed to watch
the movie together.
You know,
I felt alone for a long time.
So long that I just figured
that's how things were gonna be.
It turns out there were people
out there for me that
I didn't even know I wanted.
You'll find your people too.
I promise.
You just have to keep believing
that things will be okay
even when it's hard.
Will you watch the movie with me?
Yeah, my ride's here,
but maybe next time.
Besides, shouldn't you be out
trick-or-treating?
Me and Gumball
were gonna go together.
Besides, I can't eat
all that candy anyway.
Hey, look at Palmer.
What are you supposed to be?
I'm the Atom.
That's, like,
the coolest superhero ever.
The Atom?
That's a stupid name.
Actually, I think it's pretty clever.
Cool costume.
I can't believe you guys
talked me into wearing this.
How do you fight in these things?
Who are you guys?
We're his friends.
These guys are your friends?
Cool.
Hand the candy over.
And your allowance.
You know, in my time,
the FDA outlawed all this.
Guess they got my letters.
Hey, do your missions
always go this poorly?
No, no.
There was this one time where we...
No, actually, yes, they do.
Yeah, can't wait for the next one.
Which means we should probably
get to know each other.
So...
two truths and a lie.
Seriously?
Are we team-building right now?
Number one.
Back home,
my friends used to call me Z.
Number two, I got a copy
of "Zelda" on the black market
and never beat that final boss.
- Ganon.
- And number three,
I love musicals.
Z...
we're watching "Singing in the Rain."
I'll go get the popcorn.
Hey, movie night. Want to join us?
Man, I got some work to do, and...
Actually, I want to ask you
something.
Yeah, shoot.
It's just...
Seeing Stein
with his grandkid earlier, I...
I mean, we're his family,
but this isn't his home.
- Not anymore.
- Yeah. But...
you two are inseparable.
Like, literally.
That's what I need your help with.
I want to break up Firestorm.