Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
I have to keep you safe. Go!
You've had Mona in
custody this whole time?
You have the Kaupe too?
Sara, you need to bring in that fugitive
before someone gets hurt.
Step away from the creature, miss.
You murdered him.
Today I asked you for one thing.
- Ava, don't do this.
- Just go.
So I'll head to the Bureau
and do some digging?
Hank is torturing prisoners off site.
Keep digging. I want to know everything.
What do you mean you
couldn't capture the asset?
Blame it on your son's
time-traveling pals, sir.
Let me just say this,
and I want to say this
for the television news.
The people have a right to know
whether or not their
president is a crook.
Well, I am a crook.
Oh, actually felt good
to get that off my chest.
What other secrets have
I been holding back?
Ah, yes, despite the constant
reassurances of my wife,
I know that I'm certainly
only an adequate lover.
Mr. President!
The President won't be taking
any more questions at this time.
That is more about
Tricky Dick than I ever needed to know
And it's more than the
public needed to know.
In the days following
the news conference,
Nixon found himself unable to tell a lie
resulting in global chaos.
Nixon's blathering fouled up
ongoing peace talks
and trade agreements.
Without the release of
"All the President's Men",
Robert Redford's career floundered.
What? No Redford?
No Sundance, no indie
film, no artful nudity.
We have to fix this!
The only thing nastier
than a politician lying is when
he says how he really feels.
Now, there's no way he'd tell the truth
without a magical assist.
I hope the Watergate has vacancies,
because we need to make sure that
Nixon still cheats the press.
Uh, Captain's orders and
all, but do you think
it's really the best time
to be back on mission?
Yeah, I mean, it might
do well to take a beat.
I appreciate your
concern, but I'll be fine.
Just because Ava and
I had a disagreement
doesn't mean that I can't do my job.
I was actually talking
about the fact that
we're on the outs with the Time Bureau.
Yeah, and I was talking about Mona.
I mean, Hank's gonna be
after us since her boyfriend
offed that agent and, well,
we can't just stash her here forever.
Right, well, it has been eventful
but things are gonna blow
over with the Bureau.
We'll find a safe place for Mona.
And in the meantime,
I feel like we should be
doing what we do best.
- Am I right?
- Right.
Save Redford and independent film.
That's the spirit.
- Done it for worse reasons.
- Why not?
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Director Sharpe.
You look terrible. What happened?
Joke acknowledged,
Nathaniel, but tighten up.
Director Sharpe is
taking a leave of absence
to get her priorities straight.
I'll be acting as
Director of the Bureau.
Wait, so, um, you're gonna be
in charge from now on? That's...
- Great.
- It's great.
Looking forward to working
with you, Director Heywood.
Glad to have you on board, Agent Tomaz.
Though my first job is a sensitive one.
I need to catch the Legends.
This is the last time they will
thumb their nose at authority
and get away with it.
I know they're your friends,
so, if you want to sit this one out...
No, no, Dad. You know what?
- We have your back.
- Agreed.
I stand by the Time
Bureau and by my man.
- Thank you, babe.
- Glad to hear it.
We'll pinpoint the
location of the Waverider
and pay it a visit.
We'll meet in the situation room, 0900.
Yes, sir. Copy that.
We need to expose what Hank's up to
before he drops a hammer on the Legends.
Did... did you just call me "babe"?
Well, yeah, I was riffing.
I was trying to keep this thing afloat.
Anyways, now that
we are stuck with Hank,
we can't go through his phone ourselves.
With Ava gone, there's
no one here left to trust.
Well, there's one person we can trust.
Gary, we need to talk.
Is this about what happened
between Sara and Ava?
Wait, you're working at the Bureau?
Yes, and...
I need you to do something for me.
And you're my boss,
which is great, you know,
I'm happy for you. No
one deserves it more.
Damn it, Gary. Focus.
Hank is causing total chaos here.
Did you notice him using
Director Sharpe's mug, too?
You know, I was gonna say something.
It goes much deeper than that.
Mona was right.
Hank is running some secret project.
And now that he's in
charge of the Bureau,
he's trying to shut down the Legends.
Nate and I cloned his phone.
We're gonna keep him busy.
You need to go through his activity,
find out what he's been up to, so we can
end his time at the Bureau.
Use this to stay in touch
without being monitored, okay?
I've always wanted to
untangle a conspiracy.
I'll need a bulletin board, index cards.
I already have yarn. I've
been getting into crochet.
- Yeah, me too.
- We should start a club.
We'll talk.
Okay.
Konane, no!
Grr.
Kid.
You okay in there?
Sorry, I, uh, never used a
future tech toilet before.
- So many buttons.
- Mm.
Give it time. You'll
learn to live with it.
Oh, uh, don't touch the red button.
Oh, uh, Captain, I
wanted to talk to you.
Good. I need to talk to you, too.
So as far as the Bureau's
concerned, you're a fugitive.
I need you to stay on the ship
and not draw any attention.
It's not just that. Um,
when we were in Mexico...
No, when we were in Mexico,
a man got murdered by Konane
because you said we could trust him.
No, Konane didn't...
He didn't mean to.
Look, Mona, whatever
it is, it's in the past.
Now it's on to the next
problem. That's how this works.
Mick, Nixon's supposed to give
his "I'm not a crook" speech tomorrow.
We need him back to
his lying self by then.
You and John stay on the
ship, look after Mona,
make sure she doesn't
get into any trouble.
Make sure she doesn't
touch that red button.
I'm telling you, I'm not crazy.
In fact, I've never
felt better in my life.
That's the truth.
Here that? The truth.
Something is very wrong
with the President.
And he's supposed to be at
Disney's contemporary hotel
to address the entire American
press corps tomorrow.
We'll, uh, we'll take care of it.
- I'll update the VP.
- All right, sir.
We'll, uh, start off
with a little sedative.
Ugh.
Don't know why you lot
are relying on my powers.
They're still all mucked up.
Look, it'll be fine.
We'll get him to the
ship, fix what's wrong,
and we'll be right back.
Now, let's see your Nixon impression.
Nice.
We got the cargo.
We're on our way.
Well, let's figure out
what loosed his tongue
and get the hell out of here, shall we?
Listen, you guys can't be here.
- The Bureau's onto you.
- Ah, good.
- Time for a pig roast.
- No one's roasting anyone.
And it's not just the Bureau.
It's my dad and he's got backup.
- Go.
- No, not again.
Guys, we're working on
stopping Hank for good.
In the meantime, you need to
find the team and stay ahead of him.
On it.
What's going on?
Nate's old man commandeered the ship.
There they are!
All units, converge on my position.
Okay, take the stairs.
Get Nixon.
Ignis-sa.
Ow!
We have eyes on the Legends
and they have the President!
They've gone too far, again!
Siri... what, uh, Alexa...
Gideon! Fire up the engine.
Legends must have bricked the ship.
Oh, they think of everything.
Nicely done.
I want our men watching every time jump,
listening to every comm.
How are we going to make
distance with five of us
and a kidnapped Nixon?
There. There's our getaway.
That's a bit on the nose, no?
We left subtlety back in Mexico.
Gotta go.
♪ Come on and take a free ride ♪
The Legends are in the wind, Director.
- Damn it!
- They must have stolen
a vehicle and hit the road.
You know what?
I've never needed a Waverider before
and I don't need one now.
You give me a dragnet.
I want agents at every
rest stop, diner, store
along the highway.
Move.
And you, set up a police scanner.
If the Legends so much
as forget to signal,
we'll hear about it.
They'll slip up eventually.
That's probably accurate.
Okay.
Captain, you should know that
me and tight spaces might not mix.
Do you think any of us
want to be stuck in the RV?
Punch buggy. No punch backs.
Mona, the team's back
is up against the wall.
And right now, you are
a part of this team.
And if you want it to stay that way,
then you need to help,
not create more problems.
- Okay.
- Great.
Bob is struck with
appendicitis on an
all-new "The Waltons".
For all you lonely
hearts on the road today
here's a tune just for you.
You know, I've never been in
a car that's a room before.
Patricia.
No, I'm not Patricia, Dick.
Ooh. Camera.
Not to bother you, but
we've lost the ship,
drugged the President, and
I'm stuck in the back with her.
- Now what are we gonna do?
- We are going to Disney World.
Yawn. Haven't we been tortured enough?
I mean, we are going to fix Nixon
in time to get him to
Florida to lie his ass off.
We are not gonna let anything stop us
from what we set out to do.
Mick, watch our tail.
John, see if you can figure
out what's wrong with Nixon.
And Mona, find us something to wear.
Charlie...
We forgot Charlie!
Oh, "We'll be right back", they said.
Yeah, bloody right.
Mr. President?
- Oh, no, no, no. Okay.
- Mr. President?
Uh, quick, quick, quick, Charlie.
Mr. President, are you okay in there?
Just checking in, Mr. President.
You check in again,
you'll be lucky to be
guarding a shopping mall.
Um, okay, make your next left.
Okay.
No, your next right.
Hey, guys?
Looks like Nixon over there
is finally winning the War on Drugs.
Good God, I've been
kidnapped by hippies.
What is it you want?
Money? Power? I'll do anything.
Look, we're... We're here to help you.
Let's talk about money.
You know, right now we're your best shot
at getting back to your right self.
Oh, let's have a look.
Now, I have my suspicions
as to what's got at ya.
Yep, okay.
Vi veri universum vivus vici.
What the hell are you babbling about?
Oh!
- It's a roach.
- I've been bugged.
This is an agent of Ma'at,
the Goddess of truth in
the Egyptian pantheon.
You see, the creature,
it feeds off lies.
And whoever it eats at has
nothing but truth left to tell.
No wonder it found its way to Nixon.
You must have been a feast.
No, no, no... oh.
Sorry.
Put him in the closet.
Ugh.
- Come on, Dicky.
- Yeah.
Let's put Dick in a box.
Okay.
Um, Captain? Can we talk?
A lot's been going on and...
And a truth roach, well,
that's gonna be a wrinkle.
Look, Mona, I have a really
big responsibility for you.
- I need you to watch the roach.
- Me? But, um...
Your job was to take
care of creatures, right?
Who better than you?
Hey, little guy. Bet you're hungry.
Hank Heywood.
Renewed his Bestflix subscription...
December 16th... Hank Heywood...
November 27th... Hank Heywood...
So that means...
Oh, my God, how did this happen?
I am way out of my league.
What is it, Jerry?
- No, it's... it's Gary.
- Hm.
I notice you're reading "Body
of Proof" by Rebecca Silver.
- Is that a conspiracy thriller?
- Book club's at capacity.
Uh, no, no, that's not it. It's, um...
I need your help
uncovering a conspiracy.
Why would I help you?
Because you might be in trouble.
Hank has his agents
taking fugitives out
of their cells at night,
and I don't want you to be next.
So I thought if I release
you for the night,
maybe you could help me?
Hey, you okay?
It's not easy being trapped somewhere
where no one will listen to you, huh?
Hey, can you hear me?
You probably need air.
Oh. Oh, no, no, no, no.
What's going on?
Uh, oh, I just dropped it but it's okay.
It got it...
What... what's wrong with the brakes?
Can't slow down! Can't slow down!
Wasn't... Your foot, Ray.
Got it.
Who called the cops?
Cops?
I've never been pulled over before.
- What do I do?
- You just pull over.
Okay.
Just be cool. You got this.
Good afternoon...
Good afternoon, officer.
By the looks of your driving,
you're having a fine afternoon.
Ah.
What is it? Drinking? Drugs?
No, sir, no, sir, no,
sir, we're just, uh...
just driving and having a little
steering wheel problems.
Tell me some more about
this steering wheel trouble.
Oh, well, it's a real doozy.
So I'm here with my family
and we're on our way
to North Carolina to see the
largest chest of drawers.
- Ray.
- Uh, uh, so the steering wheel
was a little loose and
so I turned to my wife,
Claire, and, uh, I said...
My friends and I here
are time travelers.
We've kidnapped Nixon,
and we're headed to Disney World.
Like I thought.
You're high as a Good Year blimp.
I'm calling this in.
Get this out of me.
Vi veri universum vivus vici.
Ugh.
How'd it even...
Mona!
I'm at exit 244.
I've got an RV full of hopheads
who claim they're from the future.
See? Come on, son.
Let's go grab our guys
the old-fashioned way.
- Mm-hmm.
- Wait, I...
I tuned this to a
frequency Hank can't read.
And I think I know a
way to contact the team.
It's a little old-school
but it should work.
I'll be in touch.
I can't have a ticket on my record.
I can't have a ticket on my record!
Yeah, well, nabbing
Nixon's gonna give you
more than a bloody ticket, mate.
Gun it! I'm bored.
He's right. Gun it.
But then we'll become fugitives.
We're already fugitives!
Go!
Hey! Get... you come back here!
Officer, we heard your
report from up high.
Where are the offenders?
Uh, I was fixing to call it in.
You let them get away?
You're gonna have to
find another way home
because that's my car now.
There's a new sheriff in town.
Let's ride.
Nice moves, Palmer.
They're gaining.
Yeah, and I don't think
that's the cops on us, mate.
Whoa, hey! This car has no
airbags or traction control.
Exactly. Nothing but pure V8 power.
Whoa, okay.
We gotta lose Hank.
You got something for this, John?
I might, but I'll need you to get us
off the road quick, squire.
Absconditus Domus.
Where the hell did they go?
Nothing to see here.
What was with the radio?
The heat's heavy on the highway tonight
and that's no weather report.
Lucky for you, you're not alone,
because you got DJ Z to guide
you past those bad vibes.
DJ Z? That sounds like Zari.
Right now, the beat on
the street is to lay low.
But while you park it, here's
a hit to keep you safe.
All right, you heard her. We
should keep a low profile.
If we leave by night, we
should be able to make it.
In the meantime, no drawing attention
and no altering the timeline.
Well, we best keep that
bug bottled then, aye?
The only way to keep it contained is for
everyone to stay completely honest.
What the hell is going on here?
Checkers.
Maybe it's best if we
all just don't talk.
Now we just enter a command
line to a mirror site
and we can get into his email.
This email is linked
to a private server.
Must be where he's got his dirt.
We need a password.
Uh, or, we can reset it.
I forget my passwords all the time.
Those memory flashers
have a lot of side effects.
Password reset question.
Uh, we'll need some
personal info from Hank.
What's the word? Uh, sorry Gary.
- What's the word?
- I need some scoop on Hank.
Stand by, Gary.
Hey, Nate, we need to know the name of
your dad's childhood pet.
And whatever you do,
keep your dad off the FM.
I'm on it, Z.
Huh. That's a pretty cool trick.
You, uh, drink a lot of
Cokes when you were a kid?
Yeah.
My mom used to give me a
quarter for the corner store,
let me pick out whatever I wanted.
With her raising me
on her own, a quarter
was more than I even knew.
You don't really talk
about your childhood much.
Like, I'm not sure I
know where you were born.
Hackensack, in New Jersey.
Like the Billy Joel song.
We should turn on the radio.
1973, great year for music.
Actually, why don't
we... Why don't we talk?
You know, get to know each other.
You're right, Nathaniel.
You could call me Nate.
Did you have a dog?
A lab.
Yeah, named him Silver.
- After the...
- Lone Ranger's horse. Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
You used to show me old episodes.
Well, at least I taught you something.
Huh?
You know, my mom used
to take me on road trips,
stop for ice cream.
Without Dad around, she
really had to play both roles.
She didn't know how to be a father,
but she did her best.
Guess I could say the same for myself.
Um.
It's nice we get to make up
for some lost time, hmm?
But, uh, we should get back to the ship,
see if Zari's back online.
Actually, um,
why don't we forget the Legends
for a minute and go get some ice cream?
Fine idea, Nathaniel.
Nate.
Hey, Gary? The answer is Silver.
Silver. I'm in!
Hackers do say that in real life.
What is this?
Property deed in Hank's name from 1912?
What's this shipment for
dwarf star alloy from 1837?
He's using time travel
for personal gain?
That is against Bureau creed.
I have a copy in my wallet.
Shh-shh. Someone's coming.
Who was that?
Are you okay?
You have to take this to
Zari and stop digging.
I'll go back to my cell.
And, Gary, be careful.
I got an alert that someone
recovered your password
from the Time Bureau
and they're accessing your accounts.
But who would...
How would they even...
Thanks.
It won't happen again.
You know, I was just
thinking that even though
we've had some setbacks,
that this road trip
has really been a great
bonding experience.
I think you're an idiot.
Well, look, we've
dealt with a lot lately,
and I think this is a very
needed chance for us to sit
and really talk about how we feel.
Well, I'm glad you're happy.
No, wait, I mean...
I don't give a damn if you're happy.
And I certainly don't trust you
lot in helping me face Neron
no matter how many "go
team" pep talks you give.
Well, you can't keep me down!
Actually, ever since I met you,
I sometimes lie awake at night
staring into the dark thinking
I am it, and it is me.
Also, I don't think Han shot first.
- I'm gonna go sit up front.
- Also I used the strategy guide
to beat the Water Temple
in "Legend of Zelda".
Also, I really like gluten.
Well, I think it's a cool look,
but the whole loosened
tie is a little try hard.
Yeah, well, you know, it's not like
I went and loosened it myself.
Yeah, well, at least I
don't go make up my own
silly superhero names like
"Atom" and "Heat Wave".
Like I care what you think.
I want to grow my hair
out and look like Fabio.
Yeah, that... I think
that would be good.
So honestly, even as
much as I trust Sara,
this has been one disaster after another
and I really think that this
time we are totally screwed.
Captain, we're okay, right?
I mean, we just have
to focus on the mission.
Yeah, Mona. We're gonna be fine.
Ah!
Of course we're not fine,
Mona. Nothing is fine.
And I am definitely not fine.
Ava and I didn't just
get into an argument.
She asked me to leave.
And she hasn't answered
any of my calls since.
And she was my one chance,
my one chance, Mona,
at something real.
And now I don't have a ship.
I don't have a girlfriend.
And I am the Captain of an RV
and it is all your fault!
Well, I won't be your problem anymore.
♪ Baby she's gone she's gone all right ♪
Mona!
Mona, wait!
Mona, come back!
♪ What went wrong ♪
Look, I meant everything I said
but if you stay here in
1973, you'll never survive!
John, get this thing out of me.
Vi veri universum vivus vici.
Ugh.
All right. You guys,
get Nixon to Florida.
If you leave now,
there'll be time to spare.
What about you?
Mona's out there alone
and we don't leave our people behind
no matter how much they
bug the crap out of us.
I'd say no pun intended,
but that would be a lie.
Hey, mate. Hold that.
What? What, where are you going?
Oh, I just need to
stretch my legs, squire.
You all right, Dad?
You didn't finish your ice cream.
Put on your seat belt.
What's the hurry?
The Legends' RV was spotted
just outside Richmond.
My men are setting up a blockade.
They won't get away this time.
That's great. That's great!
Whoo!
You know, this is what I dreamed about
when I joined the Bureau.
Stealing a cop car?
You and me working together.
Uh, yeah. Oh.
Ooh, you know what?
Ooh, dad, that ice cream
is not agreeing with me.
Can you, uh... can you pull over?
Z? Z, can you hear me?
Nate, is that you?
Listen, I need you to warn the team.
Hank's got a blockade on the
highway north of Richmond.
They got to find another route.
- You got it?
- Roger. Over and out.
There you go, hon.
All right, what do you want?
- Whatever's fast and cheap.
- No, no, please no.
Can I get six Daphne House
burgers and a round of sodas?
Coming up.
Sara, hold up. Hey!
How do you even know
where she went, aye?
Bike treads went this way. We
passed a diner a while back.
- She's probably headed there.
- Hm.
Go ahead.
I know you've been dying
to say I told you so,
so just do it.
Uh, it's quite the opposite, actually.
It's... I wanted to see
how you're holding up.
Honestly I'm freaking out.
With the Kaupe dead and Mona in the wind
and then there's Ava and...
What happened?
I... I went to go talk to her and...
And I thought everything
was going to be fine
'cause it's always fine
and it was bad, John.
Look, I just... I don't know
how to convince everybody
that everything's okay
when I'm not okay.
Well, you know, if we were in
each other's shoes right now
then you'd be giving me
some rubbish speech about
how you don't have to
shoulder the burden myself
when I have friends around
me to help me carry it.
Not that I believe you for a second,
but that doesn't mean it's not true.
Thanks, even if you're just
lying to make me feel better.
Oh, I definitely am.
Hope it worked, though.
You all right there?
Uh, yeah. I'm... I'm great.
- Let's grab some tunes.
- Oh, no, no.
Hey.
I just got a white hot tip.
The voice sounds familiar.
I don't recognize her... or
him. I... I don't hear gender.
There's a smoky checkpoint
outside Richmond.
If you want to make it to
your final destination,
do yourself a favor and take
route 301 all the way home, bandit.
Sounds like we're taking a detour.
Dad, dad, dad, dad!
Are you insane? You
could have got us killed!
Ha! You're still here, ain't you?
Yeah, but we're going the wrong way.
Nope, we're right on target.
All units, Legends are
headed down route 301.
Reroute all units to converge
on their location now.
Come on, I'm not gonna
miss a chance to get back
at the Legends for Mexico.
They're gonna get what they deserve
for trying to protect that wolf bastard.
- His name was Konane.
- What?
Wait, I remember you.
You're the one Director Heywood fired.
You're the reason that mutt got out
of the containment
facility in the first place.
I said, his name was
Konane.
There's Mona's bike. Where is she?
Where is everybody?
Yeah, I know this kind of quiet
and it never means anything good.
Everybody out!
- Mona.
- I'll do it.
I'll shoot!
The Kaupe must have scratched her.
Oh, she tried to tell me,
and I didn't listen.
Mona, put him down!
Come on, love, this isn't you.
Stop the RV!
Step out of the vehicle!
What are we gonna do? We
can't drive through them.
- Kill 'em. Kill 'em all.
- What? No.
- Yes.
- No!
- Yes!
- No.
- Yes.
- N...
Oh, Nate's here.
I'm sure we can talk this all out.
Do you want to do the honors, Son?
Damn right, Dad. All right!
Don't worry, buddy.
I'll get you out of this.
Mr. Heywood, if we could
just talk about this,
I'm sure we can explain and show you
how this is just one
big misunderstanding.
How's that for a
misunderstanding, you pig?
By the power vested to me by
the United States government,
I hereby arrest both of you
on five charges of treason,
two of conspiracy...
Uh, sir?
Mr. President? Are you all right?
No!
These two men and their
co-conspirators kidnapped me.
They've besmirched my good name
and I've done nothing to deserve it.
Uh-oh.
Well, actually, there is
nothing good about my name.
If you were born with
the name Dick Millhouse,
you'd grow up to be a bastard, too.
- Ha-ha.
- What the hell?
Listen to me, Mona.
No one else needs to get hurt.
Funis Captis.
I am sorry about that, love.
Bloody hell.
Mona, can you hear me?
Come on, I know you're in there.
It's me. It's Sara.
I told you, Sara, I remember everything.
You pretended to be a friend!
- I looked up to you!
- Mona.
It was all lies.
Mr. President, what is going on?
I don't know, but I'm
supposed to be in Florida,
lying to the press.
He ingested a truth bug.
See, these blunders are the exact reason
why we should lock up the Legends.
Oh!
Nathaniel, are you all right?
No, I'm not.
I've been keeping secrets from you.
You think I don't know that?
But it's more than your
secret Pentagon side project.
It's always been like this, Dad.
The... the lying
and the hiding of the feelings.
Now that I'm getting to be
honest, I just want to tell you
that I love you, but you
just make it so damn hard.
Look, son, you don't understand.
And I like working with you at
the Time Bureau side by side.
I've never felt closer to you.
But now I'm having, like, a hard time
even looking in your face.
Just tell me why. Why
are you doing all this?
Why are you pretending that
we are on the same side?
I can't.
But everything I've
done has been for you.
And the fact that it's hurting
you, Nate, it's killing me.
But I want to make this right.
Okay.
You let the Legends walk.
That, or you lock me up, too.
Because if you don't trust them,
then you and I are not on the same side.
Stand down. The Legends are free to go.
From now on, we work together.
No more lies.
Watch yourself, love. She's
not in her right mind.
Oh, that's the problem. She is.
Mona, look, please stop.
I should have never
blamed you for everything.
Look, Ava, the ship, Konane,
none of it was your fault.
And I am so sorry that I told
you to ignore your feelings.
It was because I thought...
Look, I thought that if I
could forget the way that
I was feeling, then maybe
it wouldn't hurt so bad.
Look, Mona. I was wrong.
I was so wrong.
And you don't have
to bury your feelings.
You can let them out.
And if you ever need
a shoulder to lean on,
I will be there.
You promise?
I promise.
- Are you guys okay?
- Yes, no, I don't know.
First time in my adult life
I told my dad I love him.
Years of therapy couldn't
even get me to do that.
Hey, speaking of, I love you so big.
I love you so big.
- I love you so big.
- Aww.
Look, I don't always
agree with you, but, uh,
if Nathaniel trusts you, then so do I.
You're free to fly if you can
get that ship of yours working.
Someone ask for lift?
Ship was never broken was it?
Nope, it was Zari the whole time.
- Is she even your girlfriend?
- Nope, but I'm open to it.
Fat chance.
Come on your poor bastard.
Let's delouse you and get that
truth bug contained for good, yeah?
And Nixon here has an
important speech to deliver.
Let's get you back to Orlando.
You know, the truth
really does set you free.
After spending a few
days with all of you,
I know that I can be
a better leader, and even
more so, a better man.
Ah. History needs you crooked, Dick.
Who are you?
I really think I'm
gonna miss this thing.
Yeah, if I had to be
stuck on a road trip
at least it was with you guys.
You know, maybe that's what family is.
The people you don't
mind being annoyed by.
So you don't mind being annoyed by me?
Are you saying I can stay?
We could always use
another shoulder to lean on.
Besides, you're not the
first magical creature
that we've taken in.
We forgot Charlie!
Uh, Nate, hold up.
Gary surprisingly got
to the bottom of things.
It's not good.
Your dad's embezzling funds
for some black site
operation in Baltimore.
But he's not just taking the fugitives;
he's testing on them.
- But why?
- I don't know.
But I've seen this
before with A.R.G.U.S.
This is what they were doing to metas
to turn them into super soldiers.
You okay?
Yeah.
Now I know who my father really is.
Hank says he's doing this for me,
but I want nothing to do with it or him.
Hey, I... I'm sorry.
Um, yeah.
You called.
A little late for a meeting.
This better be good.
When you came to me, uh,
I agreed to this plan,
because I saw the potential
in your vision and I still do.
Don't tell me you're
having second thoughts.
I mean no disrespect.
Um, I value the work that we've done,
and I understand why it
needs to remain top secret.
But I have a new partner now.
My son.
And I can't let anything
come between us.
What are you saying, Henry?
I'm saying that I don't
need you anymore.
If that's the case,
I don't need you anymore either.
No!
You have to let me out of here.
You gotta let me out of here!
Gary!
Anybody!
No, no, no!
No, no!
Someone help me!
No. No, no, no, no.
- No, no, no, no.
- Dad?
Nate.
What did you do?
Nate. Listen, listen to me.
Right there!
I'm sorry.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --