Time travel is real,
and all of history is
vulnerable to attack,
which is why we must
travel through time
to stop the spread of these
so-called time Aberrations
and to erase their damage to history.
We are a team of outcasts and misfits,
so please don't call us heroes.
We're Legends.
Previously on “Legends of tomorrow”...
- Thank you, Mister...
- Hex.
Jonah Hex.
Temporal Aberrations cause these things
called timequakes.
If there was a way of
locating their epicenters,
maybe we'll be able to
fix the Aberrations
before they happen.
Whoa, there, wanderer.
Don't see many folks around here.
Been a while since this old mine
turned up anything worth taking.
Then I guess I'll be on my way.
And let you be on yours.
Oh, ain't you heard?
I'm the one that does the lettin'
around here.
- Or do you need a reminder?
- Wait.
I know things about these mines.
Things I can't tell you if I'm shot.
Oh, you'll tell me.
Or I'll shoot you, otherwise.
Now lower that iron and start talking.
The ore in there?
It's rare.
And powerful.
More powerful than gold.
And how would you be
the one to know that?
I can show you.
With your permission.
Found it using this.
There's enough in that
mine for the both of us.
We're the only ones who know.
We can be like partners.
Give it here.
Nice doing business with you, partner.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
What's with bad guys and ancient amulets?
Any idea why Darhk wants this?
All I know is, it's never a good idea
when your nemesis starts accessorizing.
And he's teamed up with a Speedster.
- What's a Speedster?
- Someone with super speed.
That's how Darhk escaped.
The energy of the Speed
Force grants the Speedster
Chronokinesis, temporal manipulation.
English, Professor.
It means that his running real fast,
lets him time travel.
I'll be in my room.
Martin, I need you to
gather everything you can
on Speedsters.
And Nate's right...
This amulet looks a lot like
the one we recovered off the Nazis.
There's got to be a connection.
Let me guess, I'm on library duty.
We're dealing with a Speedster here.
How long we gonna keep this
secret from them, Grey?
Come on, future Barry's message.
Yes, I know what you're
talking about, Jefferson.
And we have been through this.
Barry implored us not to share any info...
You okay?
I'm fine, it's just... Just a headache.
You would tell me if something
was up, right?
'Cause if we start keeping
things from each other...
I just need to rest.
Saving history can be
extremely wearing on the body.
I'm thinking this amulet dates back
to Late Antiquity and is
Judeo-Christian in origin.
Great.
Is... is that great?
Well, I can't find a
reference of it anywhere.
Like, none.
Historically speaking,
this doesn't exist.
Well, this is right in front of us,
so I'd say it does exist.
And we know that Damien
Darhk and the Speedster
are willing to kill for it.
Sounds like you got
some more homework to do.
What?
I-I just thought, becoming a superhero,
I would spend less time in
the library than my old job.
That's all.
Well, research skills are
a kind of superpower.
And you can turn to steel.
So you got two.
Saved by the Aberration.
Oh, what's the Trouble Alert say?
Look, I told you, don't call it that.
The timequake's epicenter is
Liberty, Colorado, 1874.
Hah! Back to the Wild West.
You guys were in the Old West?
- Yeah, town made me a Sheriff.
- That's cool.
All right, well, I will go
tell Jax and Stein.
Who wants to tell Rory?
- Not it.
What?
Okay. I'll do it.
I don't know how to use 'em,
but I'm wearing spurs.
I remember my first
time in the Wild West.
I drove a real-life
desperado out of town.
- That's cool.
- And that was my hat.
- Thanks.
- Mm-hmm.
Hmm.
- That's cool.
- What's this?
Oh, uh, that's nothing.
Don't open that...
You don't have to open...
You opened it.
Did you draw your own superhero costume?
No.
Absolutely not. Yeah, I did.
And I only did, because when I steel up,
my clothes stretch out
and they fit all weird.
And besides, don't I deserve a suit?
I mean, am I just the research guy here?
Look, I-I know what it's
like to be a rookie.
Just, uh, follow my lead,
and you'll be fine out there.
Oh, I know a few things
about the Old West.
Like, for instance, nobody says, "howdy."
- Uh-huh.
- And, uh...
you know how to ride a horse, right?
Yeah, I can figure it out.
- This loaded?
- Yes.
It is? Oh.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Guys, I think my, uh, horse is broken!
Where's the Professor?
Uh, he's feeling a little off.
More whiskey for me.
- Yee-haw!
- Whoo-whoo-whoo!
Sounds like a commotion of some kind.
Hold back, let's get a better look.
Yee-ha!
Yeah-hoo!
Look at him up there, boy!
Ah, it's a hanging.
Is that Hex?
You know that man?
We got to help him.
Well, we got to take his crew out first.
- They look armed.
- Don't worry, guys.
- I got this!
- What?
Well, well, well, you
look a lot less mean
with that noose around your
neck, don't you, Hex?
You think this is finished?
Lookin' pretty finished to me.
Don't you think, boys?
Ah!
You son of a bitch!
You might want to slow down there.
Because these here parts
ain't big enough for the...
five of us.
- And who the hell are you?
- What he said.
On second thought, I don't give a damn!
Hold still, Hex.
Nice shot.
Now you get on that horse
and you ride till you feel like
you can't ride any further, then...
you ride some more.
Now go on, get! Go on!
Whoo!
Hyah! Whoo!
Hyah!
Woo-ah!
Face.
What?
Nothing.
Oh, hell.
They're back.
Saved by a filly. Ain'Aithat
the damnedest?
A simple “thank you” would suffice.
How'd you know I needed saving?
Because we got an alert that
history was being changed,
and the coordinates led
us to your hanging.
Well, I guess it's nice to
know that I matter.
Leaving already?
I didn't get to shoot anyone.
I need a drink.
Where's Rip?
He's MIA.
Damn.
How the hell did you
miscreants manage to not
get yourselves killed without him?
Miss Lance has been serving as Captain.
But she's a lady.
You are a lady, right?
You know I could take your life
just as easily as I saved it.
Oh, fiery.
Whoever breaks her's in for a wild ride.
Too bad this filly's into other fillies.
You don't say.
So how did you end up in the noose?
Well, I was collecting the bounty
on a pissant by the name
of Quentin Turnbull.
- As in “Turnbull Country”?
- Never heard of it.
That's because it's
not supposed to exist.
This book has changed since
the last time I saw it.
- Check this out... Gideon.
- Right away.
That's a map of the
United States from 1876.
All right, who is Turnbull?
Two-bit, yellow-bellied cattle rustler.
Who controls all of the land
west of the Rocky Mountains.
Looks like we found our Aberration.
Am I supposed to have the faintest idea
what the hell this means?
It's means that we need to stop Turnbull
from taking over the West.
Looks like you got yourself
a posse, partner.
Where is everybody?
Ever since Turnbull set up shop
'bout six months ago,
everyone's been run out of town
or made to work in the mine.
Mine? What kind of mine?
- Gold?
- Hell if I know.
Nobody's been mining for
gold through these parts
for half a century.
Listen to me, "these parts"...
I sound like I'm a cowboy.
Well, he's pulling something
out of the ground
that's making him rich...
Turnbull also owns the saloon.
The hotel, the laundry...
and the whorehouse.
The answer's no, Mick.
Turnbull's got an office
above the saloon.
It's also got about a dozen men
making sure nobody gets close to him.
I think I know how we can.
Mick.
Why don't you mosey on in there?
- Have yourself a good time.
- If you insist.
I'm not sure I understand your plan.
You just set a match to a powder keg.
And if Turnbull doesn't
want his saloon to burn down,
then he's gonna have to come out
of his office and deal with it.
Better yet, get your boy to
get in a fight with Turnbull
and bring him out here on the street.
Amaya, your job is to make sure Rory
keeps his pistol in his pants
until he's outside the saloon.
Clearly, I drew the short straw.
So what you want us to do?
Reckon I can post up
nearby with a long gun.
- Are you chewing tobacco?
- Mm, Tootsie Roll.
Get rid of your hats and your guns.
What? I thought we were supposed to be
some badass cowboys?
You guys want to know how Turnbull
went from being a cattle rustler
to running his own country?
I'm gonna need you to infiltrate
his base of operations.
As what?
Y'all are tax collectors?
We're here to go over your books
and make sure everything's in order.
And we're in a bit of a hurry, so, uh...
Yes, we're on the next
train back to Washington D.C.
Well, there ain't no train to Washington.
Pass won't be open till spring.
He means mule train.
- Mm-hmm.
This guy.
How'd I go from desperado to accountant?
At least Mick's having fun.
Stuck here doing research
while everyone else
is out drinking.
It's like high school all over again.
A shot.
Make it two.
You're with him?
Unfortunately.
Guys, I think I found something.
According to this ledger,
Turnbull's stockpiling some kind of ore
in a nearby mining camp.
And you are?
I work for Mr. Turnbull.
Who are you?
My friends and I are with
the Internal Revenue Ser...
Ah, Mr. Turnbull don't like no taxmen.
Well, nobody likes paying taxes,
but they are an essential part
of the Federal Government...
Mr. Turnbull don't like the
Federal Government, neither.
Is that why he's trying
to start his own country?
Oh, now see, why'd you have to
go and say something like that?
Now I got to pump some lead into you
so you don't go blabbing
to the wrong person.
Hey, hey, would you shoot an unarmed man?
I think that's a yes.
So what's your history with Turnbull?
Come again?
Well, you said that you
had dealings over the years.
I can tell a vendetta when I see one.
I'm kind of an expert
when it comes to revenge.
This is what it's like
working with a woman?
You just sit around and
talk about your feelings?
Well, if your "feelings"
are what almost got you hung,
then, yeah, I'd say they're
worth talking about.
Not in my century.
Now that we've got outlaw outfits,
it's time to find out what
Turnbull's stockpiling
at his mining camp.
Or we could do the responsible
thing and head back to the ship
with the rest of the team.
You're joking, right?
Time to cowboy up.
Oh!
Another blackjack.
Must be my lucky day.
- You're cheating.
- I'm winning.
Sweetheart, that's for you.
I'll see you around.
Piano man.
Play something else.
I've had more fun at a funeral.
Bartender!
And who might you be?
- Name's Turnbull.
- Never heard of him.
That's my name on the
sign in front of the saloon.
Or can't you read?
So it's your money I'm winning?
Well, that's interesting.
I'd say your luck has run out, partner.
You just gonna stand
there and make threats?
Or you gonna back it up?
Amaya, what's going on in there?
You wanted Rory to start a fight.
I'd say your plan's working.
Man, these clothes smell like ass.
People didn't wash in
the Wild, Wild West?
Well, we're criminals, remember?
It's important to smell the part.
Game faces, boys.
We got company.
I don't recognize you three.
That's probably
'cause of our new bandanas.
This one off his rocker?
You could blow his brains out,
only he doesn't got any.
Nice work.
Gideon, let's run the
neural imaging scan again.
There must be something you missed.
The odds that I
misdiagnosed your condition
are infinitesimally thin.
The algorithm programmed into my
medical diagnostic systems...
Please just do it.
As you wish, Professor.
Biometric scan reveals
all brain functions
are within normal parameters.
Physiologically, there's
nothing wrong with you.
Are you implying that my
symptoms are psychosomatic?
Because...
Please...
I need you to run the test again.
Oh, my God.
What is it?
It's dwarf star.
One of the rarest minerals in the universe.
How does this help
Turnbull take over the West?
I used dwarf star to power the ATOM suit.
The piece I had was the
size of your little finger.
There's enough potential energy here
to power the entire Wild West.
Or blow it up.
Question is, how does Turnbull
even know what it is?
Bet ya this has something to do with it.
It's some sort of tracker,
definitely not from the 1800s.
Probably stole it from the time pirate.
We got to get this out of here.
Yeah.
Oh, I should've mentioned,
it's also the densest
material in the universe.
Let's get the rest of the team.
Amaya, it's been forever,
what the hell is going on in there?
Your plan's caught something of a snag.
Explain.
Well, it's hard to...
but Mr. Rory and Mr. Turnbull...
Like each other.
What?
What happened to Rory starting a fight?
I think it's more likely
that him and Turnbull
get matching tattoos.
Then they told me to put my
hands up and my pants fell down.
Because of all the loot I was carrying!
You see, that's what them damn fools
in government back in
Washington don't understand,
that men like you and me,
we wasn't meant to live in cages.
Hell, that's why our forbearers
busted away from England
to begin with, so we could be free!
And that's what "Turnbull
Country" is all about.
It's about keeping the Wild West wild.
I'll drink to that.
Will you have some of that?
Are you gonna sit around
while those two bend elbows?
What are you doing?
I'm gonna collect my bounty,
whether you like it or not.
Stick to the plan, Jonah.
Your guy on the inside
ain't sticking to no plan,
why the hell should I?
Sara? What do you want me to do?
Brace yourself.
Turnbull!
Well, if it ain't the great
Jonah Hex, himself.
Whoo, you got quite a pair
to walk into my establishment like this.
You're like a cockroach.
Hard to kill.
I'm taking you in.
Alive or dead.
Your choice.
I choose...
dead!
Actually, Jonah...
I'm glad you decided to
pay me this little visit.
You see, I've been working
on a little something.
It seems that ore that I discovered...
Well, it's got special qualities.
Let's party!
Come on!
Why do you guys get to have all the fun?
We just got back from Turnbull's mine.
The reason for the Aberration?
He's digging up dwarf star.
Get back to the ship.
That's right, run,
you yellow-bellied cowards!
Finally! Some excitement.
Mick, no!
And here I thought you
and me was gonna be friends!
I don't have friends.
- Ugh!
- Nate?
- Nate? Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I'm the Man of Steel, remember?
Oh, my gosh.
Gideon, prepare to run diagnostics.
What's to run? I've been shot!
The bullet has lodged
itself between several
of Dr. Haywood's internal organs.
How's that possible? He's made of steel.
Because it wasn't a normal bullet.
It was dwarf star.
I estimate his chance of survival at 51%.
Ugh, would it kill you to say
"better than average," Gideon?
We had a plan.
You went off book,
now you're gonna cut the crap,
and tell me what the hell is going on
between you and Turnbull.
I don't answer to you, Miss Lance.
It's Captain Lance.
And if you did answer to me,
Nate wouldn't have gotten shot.
Now, I know you don't like
taking orders from a woman...
but you're gonna like getting
your ass kicked by one
even less.
I've been after Turnbull
for eight years now.
I almost got him twice.
He wants to see me pushing up daisies
just as bad as I want
to see him do the same.
Because why?
Little town in Oklahoma.
Goes by the name of Calvert.
Turnbull and his men were harassing it.
And they hired me to fight back.
Calvert, that's the town
that Rip left in the lurch.
My little rebellion
made other towns think
they didn't need to pay
protection money to
Turnbull and his gang.
So one night...
Turnbull gathered every man,
woman, and child in Calvert.
Locked us in the church.
Set it on fire.
Somehow, I escaped.
The good Lord saw fit to
leave me with a souvenir.
Oh, what the hell am
I telling a woman this for?
You'd never understand.
Wrong.
Like I said, vendetta's kind of my thing.
I've got a Turnbull.
And he's still out there.
Well, here you are with a timeship.
Been there, tried that.
Killing Darhk would
create ripples in history
that I can't control.
But there are things that I can control.
I can help you capture Turnbull.
Even though I screwed up?
Been there, too.
I'm starting to think that screwing up
is just an essential part of surviving.
So how's your headache?
Oh, it's fine.
Nothing a little aspirin couldn't help.
Funny, that's not what Gideon told me.
What's going on?
And don't lie, because you
know I can always tell.
All right, while you were away,
I...
I had a vision.
A vision? Like a hallucination?
It's possible it could merely be
a side effect from multiple time jumps.
- Ah!
- Whoa, Grey!
Grey!
Grey?
That is not a reaction to time travel.
What did you just see?
A woman.
Someone I've never met,
but her face, it keeps...
flashing in my mind.
It's like...
I'm having memories of a stranger,
but she's not... Not really a stranger.
But I...
I haven't the slightest notion why.
Trying to work out your frustration?
Something like that.
What happened out there today?
You lost control.
Says you.
That man back in town,
the drinker, the gambler,
the animal that wants
to watch the whole world burn...
that's the real me.
I happen to know a thing
or two about animals.
They're not vicious by nature.
Unless they're attacked.
If you're trying to tell me to...
to tell you some sob
story about how horrible
and painful my life is, forget it.
I'm no victim.
Sara's told me all the things
that you've done for this team.
And you don't sound like an animal
who just wants to watch the world burn.
They like to pretend
I'm part of the team,
that they have me on a leash.
No.
Hmm.
Now...
if you'll excuse me.
Some superhero.
Maybe I am better suited for the library.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
You had no idea that
Turnbull laced the bullets
with dwarf star, or that you
were even vulnerable to it.
When I was a kid,
there was this bully, Shane Blocklin.
And one day, I decided,
"I'm gonna stand up to old Shane".
Long story short, he breaks
my nose in two places.
But from that point on, I was, uh...
I was different.
I was afraid.
And then I meet you guys,
and I get these superpowers.
And I said to myself,
"Nate, you don't have
to feel afraid again".
Well, maybe now you know how I felt
after you destroyed my ATOM suit.
When we were out
fighting with the Shogun,
without my suit, I was afraid.
Well, you hid it well.
That's because I realized that
weakness, or not being invulnerable,
is what makes me a hero.
There's no bravery without fear.
That was a really good
inspirational speech.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Well, I have a few other
aphorisms in my back pocket.
Like, uh...
"courage is the mastery of fear,
not the absence of fear."
"Strength is..."
You know what, buddy?
You nailed it.
Sorry, got a little carried
away with my train of...
That's it.
I think I know how Turnbull's
gonna make his own country.
When I saw how much dwarf
star ore he had in that mine,
I started to wonder, how could he transport
such a heavy shipment?
- He'd have to use...
- The railroad.
The railroad.
Okay, get to the part where we care, Ray.
I think he's gonna use the railroad
and the dwarf star to...
wait for it.
I don't want to wait for it.
Close Summit Pass.
- Oh, my God, Ray's right.
- Thank you.
Summit Pass connects
East/West via railroad.
Not if Turnbull uses this...
- the magic...
- Dwarf star?
Yeah, to blow the thing up.
Well, if he destroys the pass,
there's no way of transporting
soldiers and supplies
from the East coast.
The U.S. Army is effectively
locked out of the West.
So it's simple... We just stop Turnbull
from blowing up the pass.
Yeah, simple.
You don't have a suit,
you just had invasive surgery,
Stein's out of commission.
We'll think of something.
"Courage is the mastery of fear,
not the absence of it".
Yeah, what about Turnbull?
If that train goes boom...
he's not gonna be on it.
I overheard one of his people saying
Turnbull just called for
a meeting at his mine.
You, Jax, and Ray, stop the train.
The rest of us, we'll deal with Turnbull.
You sure about this?
Of course.
This isn't my first rodeo.
I wanted to say that.
There's our train.
Loaded with enough dwarf star
to punch a hole in a mountain
and cut off the pass to the East.
How do we stop a moving locomotive?
We don't.
I do.
I think.
Yah!
- So what do you think?
- I think I liked him.
That's three of them for every one of us.
Hex and I will draw their attention
while you two go make
sure Turnbull can't pull
anymore dwarf star out of the ground.
We'll need about five minutes
to plant enough dynamite
to seal the mine.
It's about time we got
to light something up.
Just light the fuse and run,
don't stick around for the fireworks.
Yeah, yeah.
All right, I've got a plan to
get us close to Turnbull.
Are you ready to follow
my orders this time?
- Aye, aye, Captain.
- Good, now put these on.
Hmm.
Quentin Turnbull!
Who's asking?
I heard you're looking for someone.
Jonah Hex!
Well, hell, looks like I'm
gonna have to kill you
for the third time.
I'm impressed, boy.
Jonah, Jonah, Jonah.
Back in the belly of the whale.
A lily-livered whale who
killed women and children.
Whoa, no, that was before.
I've changed.
I got purpose now.
Matter of fact, why don't
I show you what I'm working on
so you know why you died?
You come along too, boy.
Anyone who can bring in Hex
always got a place on my crew.
Nate, what are you doing, man?
Hold on!
- Keep your distance!
- What're you gonna do?
I'm gonna cut 'em off at the pass.
I've always wanted to say that.
You can't get in front of a moving train!
You said it yourself...
there is no bravery without fear!
Which is good, because I
am scared as hell right now.
Yah!
Colt Single Action Army.
"The gun that won the West."
Some folks like to call
it "the peacemaker."
Only, I don't much care for peace.
Yeah, thanks to what
I pulled out of this mine,
I got my own weapon now.
Something that's gonna tip the scales.
Win the West back for
the folks it belongs to.
The outlaws!
Hyah!
- Okay. I'm in position.
- And out of your mind!
You couldn't even stop a
bullet made with that stuff.
That train is loaded
with dwarf star, man!
You guys aren't helping.
You got a whole minute
to get out of here.
You mean we have a minute.
That's what I meant.
Should we tell them about the minute?
- No.
- Good.
I was hoping you were gonna say that.
- Who's next?
- Mick, we got to go!
Mick, now!
Put the animal away.
Okay.
Oh, yeah, those bullets ain't nothing.
Wait till you see what I got now.
Now get on in there!
You ain't no man!
You burned down Calvert!
You murdered all those people!
For what?
For power?
Oh, get it over with!
Alive or dead?
Alive!
You lucky son of a bitch.
I got this. I got this.
I got this.
I got this, I got this,
I got this, I got this.
Did you see that? Did you see that?
Tell me you saw that.
Yo, that was badass, dude.
Totally badass.
- You all right?
- No.
But I stopped a train.
- I think he's good.
- Whoo!
I stopped a train!
That's a mighty fine
job you did back there.
Captain.
I'll drink to that.
So now that you have your man,
what're you gonna do with him?
Turnbull?
If I had my way, he'd be in
for a long, painful demise.
I'd let him bleed out from the gut.
But I'm gonna turn him
over to the authorities.
So you don't have to worry
about your "Aberration."
Only territory Turnbull's
gonna be claiming is a cold,
dark prison cell.
Then our work here is done.
You do a mighty fine job bearing a burden
few men could deal with.
Good thing I'm a woman then.
Yes, ma'am.
I best get Turnbull.
Collect my bounty.
Now, you try to stay out of trouble.
Not likely.
Wouldn't imagine so.
It really is beautiful.
It's no wonder that human beings
have worshipped fire for millennia.
Fire gives us life, but also
has the power to destroy
everything in its path.
Your point?
Or are you gonna keep
talking in metaphors?
Yeah, I know what a metaphor is.
But don't tell them.
You were right.
The animal who wants to
watch the world burn...
that is who you are.
But it's not all that you are.
Your point?
Don't deny the animal.
But don't let it control you either.
I can help you.
Believe me, I know a thing or two
about controlling wild beasts.
Oh, there you are.
So I've been thinking
about your memory flashes.
"Manopause" moments,
or whatever it is you want to call 'em.
I got a theory.
What if when you interacted with
your younger self in 1987, you...
Inadvertently changed my past
so... so that my memories from my new life
are supplanting the
memories from my old life,
thus creating temporal dissonance.
Yeah, that's exactly what I was thinking.
Oh, it's a brilliant theory,
which I happen to share with you,
but it doesn't explain...
Who the mystery lady is.
Or...
that I'm fairly certain I love her.
Man, Clarissa is gonna kill
you when you get home.
Assuming there even is
a Clarissa to go home to.
Huh.
Hey, heard you were looking for me.
Oh, yeah, uh, I just wanted to thank you
for saving all that dwarf star ore.
I have enough to power 20 ATOM suits now.
That's cool, man, so we all get one?
Uh, actually, there's something
I've been working on
before I start building a new exo-suit.
It's, uh, not exactly what
was in your drawing.
I made a few improvements.
Shut the front door.
Yeah. I figure you earned it.
Steel.
Cool name.
Hey, are you guys done bro-ing out?
- I mean...
- Uh, well, not really, but...
- We can.
- Good.
Because our friends back in 2016,
they need our help.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --