- In 2166, an immortal tyrant
named vandal savage
Conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
And stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan
is opposed by the body
I'd sworn my allegiance to,
the time masters.
In the future, my friends
may not be heroes,
But if we succeed,
They will be remembered
as legends.
- Previously
on "legends of tomorrow"...
- Sorry we're late.
- Aren't you even
a little bit happy
To be back on the ship?
- I was happy with that life
we built together.
- You think I was hunting you
and your friends
Because the time masters
made me?
They barely had to ask.
Since I failed
to bring you in,
The time masters want
to bring me in.
They're called the hunters,
and they'll stop at nothing
Till every single one of us is
erased from the face of history.
- Do you have any suggestions?
- Run.
[ship engines roar]
- Aah! It's been quite a while
since I time-jumped
Far enough to experience
side effects.
Fond memories.
- I can't feel my face.
- Fine feel I.
- Linguistic dysplasia,
that should pass shortly.
- Better it now.
- Am I the only one who can't
feel their face?
- I can't feel my--
I better not say.
- Mr. Rory appears unaffected.
- What's going on?
We time-jump?
- Yeah, we time-jumped.
But "where to?"
is the better question.
- The town of salvation,
the dakota territory, 1871.
- I can't believe it--
the old west.
- This isn't going to work.
- It'll buy us time.
We can hide out here
while the hunters search
The other fragmentations.
- What if they decide
to check this place first?
- You know, feel free to loop us
in whenever it's convenient.
- As you've seen, time doesn't
operate as is generally thought.
It wants to happen.
It takes time to harden.
The--the timeline is unclear
on occasion,
Constantly in flux.
- Hence the difficulty
in locating savage
Throughout history.
- Indeed. And one of the other
interesting notions
Of time travel is the existence
of fragmentations.
- Temporal blind spots,
Specific places and times
the time masters can't see.
- The town of salvation
and its surrounding environs
Are located within one
of these fragmentations.
- So, basically,
we're hiding out in the old west
And hoping your boogeymen
don't find us here.
- The hunters
are not boogeymen.
And you better hope
they don't find us.
- Well, at least not until
I get a chance
To "punch a few doggies"
or "bust a bronco" or two.
Not that I condone
animal cruelty.
It's just that I watched a lot
of westerns as a kid.
- Alas, you'll have to enjoy
the old west from in here,
I'm afraid.
- Oh, come on.
What's the harm
in us just taking a look around?
- With this group?
Clearly, you haven't been
paying attention.
- Ugh, if I'm in the old west
and I don't get to look around,
I'm going to kick myself.
- I could help with that.
- I'll keep an eye on them.
Don't worry.
I'll be a good boy.
[lasers squeal]
- [chuckles]
I look just like wyatt earp.
- Now, the fabricator
can make clothing,
But you're also going to need
era-appropriate protection.
This era can get
a little, uh, rough.
- Oh, six shooters?
- Actually, most guns
Of that time period
had hammer blocks,
Thus reducing the number
of shots to five.
- Now, this should go
without saying,
But considering this group,
I am going to say it--
Only use these weapons
In the case
of extreme emergencies.
- You make it sound
like you're not coming with.
- From your duster and revolver,
I'd imagined you
As much an old west aficionado
as dr. Palmer.
- Indeed I am. But my time
is best spent back here
On the ship, plotting our next
move against vandal savage.
Besides, as mr. Rory says,
it's only a matter of time
Before the hunters
find us here.
- Don't worry. We're not
going to put down roots.
- Yeah, we'll stay
out of trouble.
- Mm, how I hope and pray
that to be true.
[dramatic western music]
♪ ♪
- Yahoo!
[indistinct chatter]
[saloon piano music]
- Remember, we're just here
to get the lay of the land.
No trouble.
- Sure that'll happen.
- I need a drink.
- Wow. It's a real
old-timey saloon.
- Oh, I beg your pardon.
- Not at all, ma'am.
♪ ♪
- That tastes like gasoline.
- Pretty much.
Hit me again.
- Oh, I'm so sorry.
- It's no bother.
- Time doesn't pass normally
in the vanishing point.
It's been years since I've seen
the bottom of a glass.
- Years?
How long were you...
- Chronos?
Never counted.
Doesn't matter.
Turns out it was
just another gig anyway.
- Doesn't seem like it.
You're different now.
- Better or worse?
- Don't know yet.
- You can handle your liquor.
I like that.
- I've been on more than a few
dates with guys who thought
We'd get wasted
and they'd get lucky,
But somehow they always ended up
the ones under the table.
- Mm.
You haven't drunk with me.
- Is that
a challenge, mick?
- Line them up.
- Didn't know
you played cards.
- Like you, mr. Snart,
I am an enigma.
Raise.
Aha.
Thank you, gentlemen.
- I'm impressed.
- My father was
what some might call
A degenerate gambler,
others would say criminal.
When I was old enough, he'd pull
me in on some of his schemes.
I picked up a thing or two
At a few of the card tables
he frequented.
Then I took
A different path.
Like father, like son isn't
always inevitable, mr. Snart.
- I had a full boat.
- As did I.
Full of kings,
which beats your pair of queens.
- Don't I look busy to you?
- I'm sorry.
I--
- You spill another drop of that
whiskey, and you will be.
- Just because you're losing
Doesn't mean you have
to pick on the waitstaff.
- Mind your
own business, grandpa.
- Unhand the lady.
- Now, now, boys,
let's just take it easy.
- Oh, when my friend here
is being reasonable,
We know we have a problem.
- I'm not the one
with the problem.
You are.
[gunshot,
patrons gasp, scream]
[body thumps]
- You killed him.
- You're welcome.
- Clearly, the deceased
was a friend of yours,
But my friend here--
- Your friend drew first,
Got put down.
It was a clean shot.
- Do we look like we care
about clean?
- He has a point.
[upbeat saloon music]
♪ ♪
[glass shattering]
[music stops]
[gunshot]
- All right!
Playtime's over.
Anybody's got a problem
with that,
They answer to me.
- Thank you,
Mister...
- Hex.
Jonah hex.
You're not from around here,
are you?
- No.
My friends and I are, uh...
From out of town.
- Way out of town.
All right.
Why don't you folks tell me
where you're really from?
- I'm not sure that's
any of your business, sir.
- Let me rephrase that.
Tell me when y'all from.
You seven stick out
like a dog in a manger.
- Like he said,
we're not from around here.
- You think you're
the first time travelers
I've ever come across?
- Uh, yes.
- Where is he?
I got some words
that need saying.
- Where is who?
- Rip hunter.
[tapping]
- What is it about you people
That whenever we go
to a new timeline,
You feel the need
to pick up...
Strays?
- Nice.
I didn't get to see it
last time around.
- Last time?
- A long story,
which we will not be telling.
- My coat suits you good.
- What are you
doing here, jonah?
- Collecting on a bounty,
Wetting my whistle,
When your friends here
got in a lot of trouble.
- We might've gotten into
a barroom brawl back in town.
- Well, that was
entirely predictable.
- One of them poured lead into a
member of the stillwater gang.
- Mr. Rory.
- Snart, actually.
- Oh, that was
gonna be my next guess.
- This guy tried
to kill grey.
Snart saved him.
- And brought this town a whole
lot of hell in the bargain.
Those boys you were trading
hands with in the saloon--
They're all members
of the stillwater gang.
- Why can't a gang ever be
a bunch of good guys?
- Jeb stillwater
and his friends
Been raiding this town
for the past three months.
Stealing, robbing, killing.
- Well, he'll have to go
through us.
- No, he won't.
No doubt your--
your little ruckus
Has already placed
the timeline at risk,
To say nothing of potentially
alerting the hunters
To our presence here.
- Sounds like someone's planning
on busting out of town again.
- Leaving already?
- No. No.
Look, this town
is being terrorized
By the stillwater gang.
And I aim to do something
about it.
- You "aim to"?
You getting all native on us,
haircut?
- Look, we signed on
to this mission--
- To stop vandal savage.
- To be heroes.
And saving a town from
a marauding gang of criminals--
That is what heroes do.
- [chuckles]
Quite a posse of saints
You're riding along
with nowadays.
- Hey.
Bridge is, uh, that way.
- Yeah, I'm not going
to the bridge. I'm, uh...
Where am I going, gideon?
- The valley you described
Is consistent
with albano gulch.
- Yeah, there.
- Okay, wait. Why?
- [sighs] back at the saloon,
I ran into a woman,
And she caused me to have
more memory flashes, so...
I think I might have known her
in one of my past lives.
And if so, she might be able
to help me find carter.
- Wait. So you're just
gonna run out there
And try and find her?
- Actually, I was planning
on flying.
- You want
a partner in crime?
- Okay, fine.
- But you're definitely
not carrying me.
- How do you propose
we get there?
[western music]
♪
- [clears throat]
Howdy.
I'm ray--
john wayne.
- What do you want,
mr. Wayne?
- Well, I, uh--
I reckon you could use
Another hand
with the stillwater gang.
- You boys have any experience
with law enforcement?
- Well, I have a fair bit
of experience fighting crime.
- Congratulations, then.
♪ ♪
- You're making me
your deputy?
- Nope. Just made you
the new sheriff.
- Excuse me. What?
- Stillwater gang
Has been shooting up this town
for months now.
It's only by the grace
of the good lord
That I'm not
pushing up daisies myself.
And I am done
with pushing my luck.
- But you're the...
Sheriff.
- Congratulations.
By the way,
You might find a warrant
or two out for me
Around these parts.
- You know, we have stuff
back on the ship
That can fix your...
You know...
- Fix what?
- Yep. Nothing.
Never mind.
[hooves clomping]
[saloon music]
♪
- What can I get you?
- Information.
Some friends of mine
are looking for jeb stillwater.
- If they're the same friends
that shot billy conlon
And beat on
the stillwater posse,
I can guarantee you
he'll find you.
- That being said, we'd very
much like to find him first.
- You got any more
of them greenbacks?
Let me go find a map.
- [sniffling, sighs]
- Excuse me, ma'am.
Are you all right?
- I'm fine.
I just want to be alone.
- I understand.
I'm new to these parts.
I didn't think it was customary
for a lady to drink alone.
- Tonic water.
It's for my son.
I just needed
a moment to myself.
- Is everything all right?
- I should be getting
back to my boy.
- If there's something
wrong with him,
Perhaps I can be
of assistance.
I happen to be a scientist.
- That's kind.
But I'm afraid
there's nothing you can do.
My boy is going to die.
- What's wrong with him?
- He has the consumption,
they say.
- Tuberculosis.
- He's been like this on and off
for about a year now.
He always wanted to see
the american west.
Our doctor thought
a constitutional
Might do him some good.
It hasn't, clearly.
- You know,
there are medicines that--
- The doctor here says
he has a day...
Maybe two, if he's lucky.
Does he look lucky to you,
mister...
I don't know your name.
- It's martin.
Hello, young man.
- We call him bertie.
- Bertie.
Your mother tells me
you wanted to come out west.
Can't imagine
you've seen much of it yet.
- I want to ride
a stagecoach.
- Well, in that case...
I encourage you
to get better.
- My mum--
she's not sure I will.
- [shudders]
- Well, then you must prove
your mother wrong...
So you can ride
that stagecoach.
[gunshots, shouting outside]
[gunshots]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- One of mine is dead.
And this here town's gonna pay.
♪
- Now, who the hell
are you supposed to be?
- John wayne...
Salvation's new sheriff.
And this here town
is under my protection.
- Well, you being new and all,
You don't know about
the arrangement that we got.
See, me and my boys,
we ride into town,
We take whatever we want.
- In exchange for what?
- Not killing nobody.
[light laughter]
- Well, that sounds
reasonable and all,
But arrangement's over.
- Arrangement's over, boys.
[light laughter]
They teach you numbers
where it is you're from?
'cause the way I see it,
There's only one of you
And a whole mess of us.
[gunshot, horse neighs]
- You get out of town,
and you don't come back,
Or the next bullet goes
in your eye.
I got sharpshooters
all around.
You really want to test me?
[dramatic music]
- Let's ride, boys.
♪
Hyah!
[men shouting]
[cheers and applause]
- Nice, haircut.
- [chuckles]
dude, that was badass.
- Let's not oversell it.
- Running a bad guy
out of town's always been
On my bucket list.
- "bucket list"?
- A list of things one hopes
to accomplish before they die.
- Well, you better hope it's
a real short list, string bean.
- We can handle
the stillwater gang.
- Well, you're all just tearing
up the 1870s, aren't you?
- Stillwater and his gang's
like a hornets' nest,
And your friends here keep
poking at it.
- They saved the town
from being raided, man.
- Today,
but what about tomorrow...
Or the day after that?
For a bunch of time travelers,
You don't seem to understand
the future much.
The day will come
when you'll all leave...
And salvation
will end up like calvert.
- What's a calvert?
- A closed matter.
A word, mr. Hex?
I believe you've all done
enough for one day.
- Well, now I definitely want
to know what a calvert is.
- Then it's a good thing
we have access
To a supercomputer.
Gideon?
- Calvert was a town
in oklahoma circa 1868.
- "was"?
[beeping]
[dramatic music]
♪
[bird screeches]
- You know, there's something
weird going on with your face.
- What?
- You're smiling.
- [chuckles]
- I didn't know
you could do that.
- Well, don't tell anyone
my secret.
- [laughs]
- It's just all of this--
It's so pure, so simple.
I'd say I miss simple,
But I guess you have
to experience something first
To miss it.
- I know what you mean.
I've been having more and more
memory flashes lately,
And I'm not
entirely sure why.
- Well, if this woman was a
friend of yours in a past life,
Hopefully she'll have
another piece for your puzzle.
- I feel like I'm being drawn
to this place.
- Which way?
- There.
[smacks lips]
- You know,
stealing's against the law.
I'm the sheriff
of these here parts.
- How did you know I was
appropriating this medicine?
- That was my fault,
professor.
- Et tu, gideon?
I suppose this is
going to earn me a lecture
On the perils
of upsetting the timeline
By introducing futuristic
medicine to the 19th century.
- Well, it seems you've
already given it to yourself.
- Except this isn't
futuristic medicine.
I've had gideon fabricate
simple streptomycin for me.
Excuse me.
- Which won't be used in medical
treatments for another 70 years.
- This is about a boy in town
Who's dying
of an easily curable disease.
Just as you couldn't turn
your back on jeb stillwater
And his gang, I can't turn mine
on this boy and his mother.
- Except dr. Palmer is using
19th-century technology
To deal with stillwater,
whereas you--
- Just spare me the lecture,
captain hunter.
You, of all people...
- This isn't
about the mission, martin!
Do you not recall happened
when dr. Palmer
Left a bit of his suit
back in 1975
And nearly destroyed
central city?
- That was an accident.
- I'm not talking
about our mission
Or dr. Palmer's
technological gaffe.
Calvert...
That town clearly holds some
emotional resonance for you,
Judging from the looks you've
been exchanging with mr. Hex.
- How do you know it's a town?
- Gideon?
- Calvert, oklahoma--
What happened
to you there, rip?
- And why is it
so important to you?
- Because the past
is prologue.
It's not uncommon
for criminal posses
Such as mr. Stillwater's
to sack and pillage towns
Which they find uncooperative.
- So stillwater's
done this before?
- In the case of calvert,
it was quentin turnbull's doing.
But it was my fault.
I'd come to calvert on a mission
from the time masters.
This was years
before my son jonas was born.
- Jonas...
Did you name your son
after hex?
- After my mission
was completed,
I felt unable to leave.
I'd grown so attached
to this era--
A victim of the same
time drift you experienced
In 1958.
- But obviously you left
at some point.
- Left? I had to
tear myself away
From the time period
For fear that I would never see
my then-future wife, miranda,
Ever again.
Turnbull attacked calvert
the very next day.
- So...
You can understand
why I must act.
- No, martin, I don't.
As I said before,
this is advanced medicine
Unsuitable to the period,
To say nothing
of what this boy's survival
Might do to the timeline.
- Be that as it may,
I refuse to live
with the regret
I see on your face right now.
- The information mr. Stein got
from the barkeep paid out.
I know where
the stillwater gang's holed up.
- All right.
Let's ride.
Up high.
- You coming, rip?
[dramatic music]
♪
That's what I thought.
[beeping]
[door whirs closed]
- I wonder why she lives alone
all the way out here.
- Because...
I value my privacy!
- Wait, wait, wait.
Don't you remember me...
From the saloon
back in salvation?
- I remembered you,
you wigged-out little girl.
If I'd wanted
to talk to you then,
I would have talked
to you then.
I ain't fixing
to talk to you now.
Now, get off of my land!
- Listen, we're not trying
to start any trouble.
- Do you want that pretty little
mouth of yours filled with lead?
- Your friend has
a colorful personality.
- I ain't got friends.
I keep to myself.
- She's right.
She wasn't my friend.
I was her.
- We sat for that picture
at the county fair, 1830.
He looked
like such a gentleman.
- What was his name?
- Hannibal.
Hannibal hawkes.
- And what happened?
- Was it savage?
- What is this?
It looks familiar.
- That was ours
in our first life.
[dramatic music]
♪
- I remember.
- We crossed with savage
in jefferson city.
He had it with him.
We escaped with it
and our lives.
- Do you still have it?
- We lost it to bandits
about a year later.
We heard that the pinkertons
were after the same bandits,
But we just...
- Hey.
What is it?
- Objects present
at the moment of my--
Our first death
Can be used to kill savage.
So, if I can get my hands
on that bracelet, then--
- You're going to try
to kill savage with a bracelet?
You need to stop.
- Stop what?
- Fighting our destiny.
Ain't destiny
what brought you here?
- What part of destiny
is she fighting?
- All of it.
We get reborn.
We find hannibal--carter--
Then savage finds us,
and then we die.
That's--that's
the way it is.
It's the way
it's always gonna be.
- I don't believe that.
- Well, I have
a few more years on you.
You can't break the cycle.
That's why I live
out here, alone.
- For the rest of your life?
- Well, I guess I had
to figure that out the hard way.
I was still a young woman
when savage left me a widow.
Instead of waiting for him
to find me and kill me
So that I could love my hannibal
in the next life,
I tried to find love
in this one.
Talk about a curse.
- What happened?
- He was a good man,
but he wasn't a soul mate.
It was like fate was trying
to break us apart.
Eventually,
fate broke both our hearts.
So I made a promise
to myself
That I wasn't gonna do that
to a person again.
- I'm--
I'm sorry to hear that.
- No, I'm who's sorry...
To have to be the one
to let you know
That you're never going to be
able to love anyone else, ever.
How much do you know
about our previous lives?
I reckon not a lot because
you didn't recognize me,
So let me tell you
that we did love other men--
Loved them real and pure,
But it never ended well,
not ever.
Tragedy or heartbreak...
That's how it always ends
if the man's not carter.
- We could've used sara
on this roundup.
- A lady? You crazy?
- Just remember,
we're here to arrest stillwater,
Not kill him.
- He always this much
of a stick in the mud?
- Yes.
- How?
It's a miracle.
- Oh, it's--it's not a miracle,
I can assure you.
Uh, m-mrs. Neal--
- Sarah.
- Sarah...
When the illness is gone,
I need you to promise me
that you'll take what's left
Of the medicine and burn it,
vials and all.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
Yes, I shall do it.
- Sarah...
I wish you well.
- Thank you.
- I really must be going.
[door opens, closes]
[horse neighs in the distance,
hooves clomping]
- Oh, damn.
[grunts]
[gunshots]
- These boys got some stones.
[gunshot]
- [snarls]
[rousing music]
♪ ♪
- Jeb stillwater,
you are under arrest.
You have the right
to remain silent.
to an attorney.
- There won't be miranda rights
for another 100 years.
- Fall back! Fall back!
- Jax!
[guns click]
- We got to go!
- Not without jax!
- Well, we got stillwater.
It means we got leverage.
Live to fight another day
or die tonight--
Your choice.
Hyah!
♪
- Where is stillwater?
- He's knocked out cold
in the med bay.
- Well, this is
a simple matter.
We trade stillwater for
jefferson as mr. Hex suggested.
- It's not that simple.
If we release stillwater,
we're back to square one
And the town
is still in danger.
- So is the kid.
- And we'll figure out a way
to get him back
Without releasing stillwater.
- I got a notion.
Set up a quick draw.
You win,
Get your guy back.
You lose,
You set stillwater free.
- And, by "lose,"
you mean...
- Get shot and killed.
- Oh, great.
Pistols at high noon.
- Finally,
someone's talking sense.
- There has to be another way,
a better way.
- Sure.
Go after stillwater with all
your gear from the future.
I don't know how that'll sit
with your captain, though.
- Mm, let's assume
it's a bad idea.
- So who's standing
in the middle of main street?
- I'll do it.
- Raymond, now is not the time
To indulge
your cowboy fantasies.
- No one else
is stepping forward.
Plus, I'm a decent shot...
At least I was
with an air rifle.
- I can't believe
you're encouraging this.
- You know it's the only way.
- Dr. Palmer's going to get
himself killed.
- I think you forfeited
your right to an opinion
When you refused to leave
the ship since we've been here.
- I had good reason.
- Because of calvert.
- Yes, but not in the way
you think.
Leaving calvert,
leaving this...Era
Is one of the hardest things
I've ever had to do.
- And why is that, captain?
- A time master is trained to do
his work without interference,
Which means not helping people
or being a hero.
But as you've seen, dr. Palmer,
this era offers
Many opportunities for heroism.
I found it...
Enticing.
- And you still managed
to leave.
Something's been bugging me
all these years.
If you'd have known what
turnbull was going to do
To calvert,
would you have left?
- That's the thing, jonah.
I did know.
[grunts]
[groans]
I deserve that.
- You deserve a lot worse.
You knew,
and you still left?
- Of course I knew.
I was a time master.
And therein lay the problem.
Like raymond, like martin,
I felt the pull of heroism,
of this era's penchant
For being rife
with opportunities
To make a difference.
That's one of the things
that called to me,
And that is why
I had to leave.
Because had I stayed...
I could no longer
have remained a time master.
But I'm no longer
a time master...
Which is why
I'll face stillwater.
- Wait. I said
that I would do it.
- And get yourself shot
and killed?
It's appreciated,
but I'd rather you stayed alive.
Send word to
stillwater's posse.
I believe high noon is
in less than three hours.
[dramatic music]
♪
- You want to talk about it?
- Not really.
- You don't have to listen
to her, you know?
- Is this you
not talking about it?
- No. This is me
ignoring you
Saying you don't want
to talk about it.
Look, I get it.
Things may have gone
very wrong for old west you
And whoever she loved
who wasn't carter.
- But?
- But old west you
didn't know ray palmer.
She didn't love ray palmer.
You do.
And you have
to live your life.
She already lived hers.
- You think hunter
can pull this off?
- Reasonably.
If not, I got dibs on that
newfangled revolver of his.
[dramatic music]
♪
- You sure about this?
- Well, if anything, it feels
good to be out here again,
In this era.
- Well, don't get
too attached.
- That is what
I keep telling myself.
I'll be drawing
for sheriff palmer.
- How do me and my boys know
you're going to keep your word?
- Sheriff palmer's
a straight shooter.
- Then he should be
the one in the street.
[tense music]
♪
[triumphant western music]
- Jefferson,
are you all right?
- Yeah.
Did you just shoot
somebody for me?
- Yeah.
You're welcome.
- I don't think
we're done here yet.
[people shouting]
- Oh, no.
[suspenseful music]
♪
They found us.
[lasers whirring]
[gunshot]
- Ah, friends!
Welcome.
- I think you'll find this
slightly more effective
Than your current sidearm.
Yes, I will be wanting
that back, by the way.
And you'll be needing this.
- What about revealing
our future tech to the locals?
- It doesn't seem
to bother them. Shall we?
[dramatic music]
♪
- What about our guns?
- Sorry.
Grabbed what I could.
- That's what's up!
Y'all better stay the hell
away from us!
- Calm down, jefferson.
- Traitor!
- Not possible.
I was never on your side.
I was on my side.
- You'll never win!
- Wake up, pal. We already did.
- Fool. The time masters
have initiated omega protocol.
The pilgrim's coming
for you, chronos.
Your deaths are
just a matter of time.
- Yeah, yeah.
Well, that was easy.
♪
- You're not staying.
- Are you?
- Me?
You know I can't.
But this town still
needs a sheriff.
- Well, I'm not
the law-and-order type...
Nor the staying-in-one-place
type either.
- Well, we have that much
in common at least.
- At least.
- Be well, jonah.
- Nice thing
about my world--
For you,
it ain't going anywhere.
- Ah, perhaps we will see
each other again, my friend.
- Yeah.
I reckon that'd be okay.
[clicks tongue]
- Interesting fella.
- Indeed.
- This town's seen
a lot of interesting.
Suppose you got
one of those doohickies
That erases people's memories
or something?
- No. But...
Skepticism and disbelief
are a far more effective tool.
- Ah. So, if anybody here talks,
no one will believe them.
- Would you, mr. Snart?
[indistinct chatter]
- I'm not going to pretend
to understand what I saw.
- I'd prefer that you didn't
tell anyone about it either.
That goes for you too,
young master neal.
- My last name's wells.
- Excuse me?
- His father's surname.
- Herbert george wells.
- You're h.G. Wells.
- H.G.--
I like that.
- Astonishing.
- God, it feels so good to be
in normal clothes again.
The people here need to invent
fabric softener asap.
- Is that all?
It's just that
you've seemed a little off
Ever since you came back
from your walkabout.
- Ray, I told you...
- Something, but I don't
think it's the whole truth.
I thought that we decided to be
honest with each other.
- And I am.
I am being honest
with you, ray.
Look, I met a woman,
and I learned some things.
I told you
about killing savage.
And the rest...
The rest is what she thought,
not what I think.
I don't have to
listen to her.
[sentimental music]
♪
I love you.
- I love you too.
I think they're waiting for us
on the bridge.
We should go.
- So how are you feeling,
given your concerns
About becoming addicted
to this era once again?
- [scoffs] the last time
I left, martin,
I did it to be
with those closest to me.
I'm doing the same again.
- So where to now?
- Or, more
specifically, when?
- Is there another fragmentation
we can hide out in?
- Unfortunately, matters are
not quite so simple.
- How'd I know you were gonna
say something like that?
- Rip's buddies.
- And yours.
- The time masters have issued
omega protocols on all of us.
- That sounds
pretty terrible.
- The worst kind of order
they can issue...
They've sent the pilgrim
after us.
- Who's the pilgrim?
- The pilgrim is
The time masters'
most deadly assassin,
And she will stop at nothing
Until each and
every one of you are dead.
- Ooh, scary.
Pretty sure
we can handle ourselves.
- Indeed...
Which is why
she won't be going after
The present-day versions
of you.
- She's hunting
our younger selves.
And she won't stop until each
and every one of us
Has been erased
from the timeline.
[dramatic music]
♪
[laser fires]
- Greg, move your head.