Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Astra's dead mother
was a powerful witch.
Why did you bring me back?
Natalie, is that really you?
Natalie brought you here
to help me save Astra.
What do you know
about the Loom of Fate?
Do you wanna know
what I'm hiding from?
- Yes, I do.
- That bloody Loom.
He still has ten years.
Can you make it zero?
Bye-bye, Johnny.
John.
John, can you hear me?
What happened?
He just collapsed.
Out of nowhere.
After coughing up a bucket of blood.
Come on, Johnny. Stay with us.
Gideon, we'll need to run a scan.
Right away, Dr. Palmer.
Oxygen mask, please.
The Loom. Where is it, Charlie?
Not now, John, all right?
You've got to rest.
- What loom?
- Astra's ghost mom.
She told... Oh, my God.
Hold me, hold me.
- Hold me.
- What the hell's going on?
As you can see
from his chest X-ray,
Mr. Constantine has a very
aggressive form of lung cancer.
I'm afraid it's terminal.
Well, there's no point
in quitting now.
There's nothing funny
about lung cancer, John.
Who's laughing?
If you lose your hair,
I'm shaving my head in solidarity.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on a minute.
No saucy AI is butchering me
and pumping me full of drugs...
I took the liberty
of administering a sedative.
Mr. Constantine needs to rest.
Gideon, prepare the Jumpship.
Clotho...
Where are you going?
You can't escape us.
Clotho...
You can't get away.
We see you.
No, no.
- Oh, mate!
- Charlie.
You're back.
How are you doing, B-easy?
Where you been?
I was just... I was just hanging
out at Constantine's.
How is he?
- Dying.
- What?
No, don't worry. You know John-o.
He's always got a trick up
his sleeve.
Bro, that donut you made me eat
had me hallucinating.
Starting today,
I'm on a juice cleanse.
Zari, this is my...
friend, Charlie.
Charlie, meet my sister.
Good fashion.
Team meeting on the bridge.
Does that mean me?
That means you, too, Zari.
Cool.
So, you coming?
I wouldn't miss it.
Oh, Charlie.
We could really use your
help right now.
With Sara in Star City and Rory
in a mood, we are short-staffed.
- What's Mick in a mood about?
- Ali. His girlfriend.
Ray, they only...
they only had sex once.
Well, when you know, you know.
You know?
Okay.
Listen, I know
we're all worried about John. Okay?
And we could just sit back
and wait for a miracle.
But, does Marie Kondo rest
just because she built an empire?
- No.
No, she tidies up.
And that is exactly
what we're gonna continue to do.
We are gonna tidy up the timeline,
yeah?
Gideon, show them
what we've been working on.
Each point represents
a potential Encore.
Which means, we can catch them
before they change history.
I call her...
The Prognosticator.
Okay.
Oh, anyway, there's a Category 5
in 1997, Hong Kong.
A mysterious gangster is moving in
on the Triad's territory.
Ray, I want you and Zari to QB.
Oh, you don't have to tell me
to Queen Bee.
It'll occur naturally.
You know what? Hong Kong traffic
is notoriously bad.
- So why
- Whoa!
don't we take my new scooter?
I call her...
Scoots McGoots.
- Dude!
- That's so awesome.
The scooter, you're all impressed by?
Oh, my God. I need one.
Wanna go for a ride?
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Away we go.
Okay, I'm next.
- Careful!
- Slow down.
All right, speed her up.
Nate. Nate?
Never been to Hong Kong before.
So, what's the plan?
I had Gideon cook up the same
sedative she dosed John with.
All we have to do is inject
the Encore
and bring him back to the ship
for nap time.
One problem.
We're just supposed
to hope the Encore shows up
looking for a cuppa?
This is no ordinary tea shop.
It's owned by the Triad.
Nate, how's the perimeter sweep?
No sign of a gangster from Hell yet.
So it looks like we've arrived
right as Great Britain
was getting ready to hand control
of Hong Kong back to China.
Oh, that's probably not pertinent
but keep up the research.
Gary! What are you doing here?
John's trying to leave the ship!
You have to stop him!
You should return
to the MedBay, Mr. Constantine.
John, what are you doing out
and about?
Oh, listen, big man.
Look, I know you're only
trying to help, all right?
But nobody gets Stage IV
lung cancer this fast.
Some sneaky git with a grudge against
me is bending the rules of magic.
Oh, who could hate you that much?
The list is long.
I'm taking the Jumpship
home to narrow it.
John, no. I cannot
let you leave this ship.
You are in need of medical
supervision.
You can't let me?
You forget who I am, old son.
Fine.
But I'm going with you.
Hallelujah!
That was intense.
The Encore's a no-show.
I say we split.
Thirteenth-century armor...
Fu Manchu mustache.
Guys.
I think I know who the Encore is.
It's Genghis freaking Khan.
How the hell did Genghis Khan
get to 1997
and learn how to ride a motorbike?
Genghis used horses
to revolutionize warfare.
A motorbike's the modern-day horse!
Looks like he's meeting
with the Triad.
What sort of man steals my drugs
and my nephew's ear
only to return them to me?
I have only one interest.
Conquest.
Surrender the Triad to me
and I will remake the globe.
And if I refuse?
We're not getting in that room.
We should abort.
Regroup on the ship.
What, and stay in Hong Kong longer?
Give me the syringe.
Let's finish this.
B, I'm gonna need a distraction.
It's too dangerous.
Any moment.
Charlie, stop. Don't do this!
Behrad!
We're the cops.
Freeze, jackass.
Great distraction, B.
No!
Genghis is leaving.
I'm going after him!
Charlie, wait!
Charlie?
- I'm out.
- Me, too.
Drop your guns!
Shoot him!
- Huh?
- Nice timing.
Scoots.
Shoot him!
- He's immortal.
- And I'm not!
You're lucky.
Maybe next time, not so lucky.
Gary, bring me the foxglove,
a serpent's tongue
and the hair of an albino.
John, need some water?
Bollocks.
No, mate.
Just do me a favor and pull up
the rug.
What are you planning?
A summoning spell.
I'm gonna throttle the bastard
that did this to me.
Are you really up for that?
No two-bit demon
is getting the better of me.
I'm John Constantine,
and I am devious to the core.
I added honey, just how you like it.
Good. Now, give it here.
Johnny.
Show your face.
The great John Constantine,
brought to his knees.
There are denizens of Heaven and Hell
who would kill to see this.
Surprise.
Astra, why?
You're bad for business, John.
The cancer was already in your lungs.
I just... sped it up.
Astra, this magic
is way beyond you, love.
Look, whoever helped you,
whatever you promised them
in exchange, trust me,
it's a trap.
I'll keep that in mind.
You know, I would have expected
your purgatory to be a little more...
gruesome.
You don't remember this place, then.
Your mother brought you here.
So that's your angle.
I knew you'd try something, John.
Astra, I can change
your mother's fate.
All right? She never dies.
You never go to Hell. Your dad, he...
He never drowns his sorrow in booze.
Your family can be whole again.
Tempting.
But everyone you try to help...
you hurt.
But this is different, all right?
I know someone who has a lead
on a very powerful artifact.
"I know someone."
John, listen to yourself.
It's pathetic.
No, what is pathetic is that someone
who is so content to rule Hell
because they're too scared
to make a go at a real life.
Look, this is what Natalie wanted,
love.
I just...
I need a little more time.
Time is something you're running
low on.
Oh, thank God.
No.
The man upstairs
had nothing to do with this.
It was Astra.
She owns the chip to my soul.
She's figured out a way
how to spin down the dial
on the time I have left.
Thanks, man.
John, I'm sorry.
Cheer up, lads.
This dog is still in the fight.
That went well.
My Queen Bee-ing, I mean.
You four almost got
yourselves killed.
- I had fun.
- "Fun"?
You got us stuck
in the middle of a shoot-out.
It's why I love Bruce Lee.
He never uses guns.
Keep your knickers on.
You have wind powers.
You could have
just stopped the bullets midair.
Stop bullets?
You're crazy.
Look, this is all my fault.
We should have been gathering Intel,
not doping the Encore. Gideon.
I'm currently tracking
Genghis Khan's whereabouts
via his license plate.
Great. 'Cause we need to figure out
how and why
Genghis just showed up
in 1997 Hong Kong.
Charlie, you up for
some undercover work?
Oh, I get it. Just
because I'm the shapeshifter,
I have to be the one
to infiltrate the criminal gang.
Sorry, pause.
Oh, you're a shapeshifter?
Yeah. I am, actually.
I can shift into anyone you like.
Anyone?
- Yeah, anyone.
- All right, come on.
Where's Mick? I'm gonna get a drink.
- I need a smoke.
- I...
I don't get it.
They used to be best buds.
Oh, there's only one explanation.
B and Charlie went to pound town.
Oh. Gross.
Wait, what?
Moan zone?
Smash city?
Ava.
They had sex?
All right, guys.
I'll see you in a bit.
- Charlie.
- Oh, here we go. Another lecture.
No, I just...
Be careful.
She won't talk.
Oh, the hero cop from the tea house.
Ava, are you there?
Yeah, Charlie. You find something?
Genghis kidnapped your cop friend.
What do we have here?
Only one child?
How unambitious.
Nevertheless...
give me what I desire
and I will spare his life.
John, Nora's here.
All right, I'm coming.
Okay, Pippa...
can you wish our friend John healthy,
like we discussed?
Yes, but I want something first.
Pippa's made a lot of progress
but we're still working
on a few challenges.
Hey!
The Master of the Dark Arts
needs your help!
Shut up, four eyes.
Now you listen to me,
you little squirt.
Now you're gonna make that damn wish
because if you don't and I die,
then I'm gonna come back and haunt
you every waking hour of your life.
Fairy Godmother, I wish your scary
British friend wasn't sick!
There you go. Easy.
Okay.
Oh, no matter.
I'll try something else.
I wish I was home!
Sorry.
Bye, Ray.
Bye, Nora.
So, when did
you and Charlie, you know...
It's that obvious?
After Heyworld.
Wow. That's nice.
- How was it? She shapeshift?
- That's what you want to talk about?
Hundred percent but we don't have to.
Look, Charlie's clearly
affecting you.
So come on, talk to me.
- It's stupid.
- What?
She left without saying goodbye.
Yeah, that sucks.
But if you were thousands of years
old, wouldn't you be over goodbyes?
The least she could've done
is texted.
How hard is it to send a ghost emoji?
Maybe it wasn't about you.
Dum-dum's got a good point.
B, chin up. You are a catch.
If there was a female version of you,
I would be all over her. Fact.
Like my sister?
Absolutely.
But the point is,
we don't know why Charlie
didn't say goodbye.
So just check your ego...
and ask her.
You're right.
- Thanks, Nate.
- My man.
Where's our prisoner?
Even with Prince Charles' motorcade
route, he'll be heavily guarded.
Wait. Prince Charles is the target?
He's here to hand Hong Kong
back to China.
What if the Khan wants Prince Charles
to give it to him instead?
An authoritarian power
wants to control Hong Kong.
It sounds familiar.
The worst part of my resurrection
was finding myself buried
in an impenetrable tomb.
It took me 700 years
to dig myself out.
The best part of my resurrection
was the sword I was buried with.
Genghis just killed a cop
with a Hell weapon.
Son of a bitch.
Okay, you got
what we needed, Charlie.
Get the hell out of there.
Yeung.
What is the status of my fleet?
Your fleet?
The one you are building
to conquer the globe.
Right.
Fleet's great.
In fact, I have to go
check on it right now.
Don't freak out. I can explain.
Never mind.
Clotho...
No matter what face you wear...
you can't hide from us.
No! Leave me alone!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
So? What's the verdict?
Can you heal me?
Well, then, screw you.
Come with me.
He didn't mean that.
Yeah, I did.
I wish you would let us
take you to the oncologist.
Raymond, how many times
do I have to tell you?
This is a disease caused by magic
and only magic can fix it.
"How to add years to your life"?
Oh, that should do it.
Although the ingredient list
is a little unusual.
We'll need a medieval knight.
I was once knighted
Sir Raymond of the Palms.
Great. Gary, grab a knife.
We're gonna perform a little
back-alley surgery on the big man.
Oh, what kind of surgery?
Well, first off, are you
uncircumcised?
- I... I...
- Well, I'll take that as a yes.
- Gary, the knife.
- No!
We tried Nora, we tried the Puca.
What if there isn't a cure?
Isn't there anyone you...
that you need to say goodbye to?
What about a bucket list?
Goodbyes are for saps
and bucket lists
are for mealy-mouthed cowards
who don't have the courage
to carpe the bloody diem.
I have a bucket list.
Thank you for proving my point,
Raymond.
Stop being so mean.
We're trying to help you.
- Help me?
- Yes.
Captain America
and the village idiot?
Well, I don't need your help.
I take care of myself. I always have.
What, you think
I'm gonna let Astra beat me?
I will fight and I will scheme
and I will make a deal
with the archangel himself.
You hear that, Gabriel, eh?
Come and get me.
Have I got an offer for you.
Looks like he's not coming.
I'll think of something. I always do.
Now piss off,
I've had enough of the pair of you.
Go on, piss off!
Hello.
Who the hell are you?
I am the last queen of France.
Right. Just when I thought this ship
couldn't get more barmy.
Looking for a Time Courier?
Why are you in such a hurry
to leave... again?
You know me.
Always looking for the next party.
Usually I would buy that...
but you just almost walked
into a truck.
Something has you spooked.
Is whatever's going on
the reason why you left?
- Here we go.
- Look, I'll admit it.
I liked you.
I was hurt when you left
and I've felt weird
ever since you returned.
Now, can you be honest with me?
Honestly...
you are starting to piss me off.
We had sex and it was mediocre.
Get over it.
Wow. Okay, I'm gonna ignore that.
If you don't want to talk, fine.
But we're about to go up
against Genghis Khan.
Don't leave now.
Just give me the Courier.
Bye, Charlie.
Mediocre is not bad.
Charlie's gone?
- How could you let her leave?
- I didn't.
It was her choice.
Okay. Hey, how about we focus
on Genghis Khan?
You're right.
We need to stop him from
attacking Prince Charles' motorcade.
But he is on his way to a ceremony
ending 156 years
of colonial rule, so...
Have you been researching history?
Oh, sorry. That's your thing, right?
- No. But...
- Okay.
Hey, okay. Moving on, right?
Turns out the person
Charlie impersonated is an engineer.
There's a shipment coming in tonight.
I'll bet you that's the fleet
Genghis uses for his attack.
What kind of fleet?
Whatever it is, it's the next step
of modern warfare.
I'll go to the docks,
I'll try to figure it out.
Okay.
Zari and I will monitor
the airspace above the motorcade
and you'll be on the street.
I know it's a lot of ground to cover.
If Charlie was here...
I get it. I'm on my own.
I can't believe you stooped
to trying to make a deal
with an angel.
Gabriel would have turned you
into his slave.
Well, at least I'd be alive.
There are worse fates than death.
Oi.
I will shove you where the sun
don't shine just to shut you up.
You'd probably enjoy that.
Hell of a way to spend
your last night's on Earth, though...
you arrogant bastard.
Especially when you could be
with two of the only friends
you have left.
Yeah. Nice one.
I... I just feel so helpless,
you know?
Me, too, Gary.
If he has to go, I just...
I want him to be at peace.
Well, that's not his style.
John's gonna go out the way he lived.
Like a bloody wanker, eh?
You know, it occurs to me
that I might owe you two
a bit of an apology.
We accept.
Okay.
Go on, sit down.
All right.
Okay, you're hurting me. Go on.
Sit down. Stop bloody fussing,
will you?
You know, I can't remember
the last time this room
was used as an actual kitchen.
Well, there's roast in the oven.
It'll be ready soon.
Did I ever tell you both
about the time I met
the ghost of Winston Churchill?
Behrad, what's your status?
It's complete gridlock.
No one's getting through
on the ground.
- The fleet must be in the air.
- Nate...
did you find the shipment?
Oh, no.
We're too late.
Whatever there was,
there was a lot of them.
Nate, get downtown and help Behrad.
Hold up.
I think they might have left
something.
What's that noise?
Oh, my God.
Scoots.
Khan!
Charge!
They're getting through the gridlock
on their scooters!
Heading straight
for Prince Charles' motorcade.
Stay down, Your Majesty!
Turn here!
I could really use some help!
Nate, tell me you're close, please.
I'd be lying.
B, it's your time. You got this.
Protect the Prince!
Get down! Take cover!
Look out!
Not again.
Look who it is.
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you,
Prince Charles.
It's not your fault.
But my friends call me Charlie.
Apprehend this imposter.
Show your true form or I end him.
Looks like your luck has run out,
shapeshifter.
Where is the Prince?
Sorry, Gengi.
He's somewhere you'll never find him.
Your shapeshifting friend
said you need to tell your team
that I'm here.
And I told her, I'm on my beer break.
Now, shut up, princess, and listen.
I've never met
one of your kind before.
You will be my 13th wife.
Come again, mate?
Your power will serve my reign well.
Join me, as I build a new empire
that will span the globe.
Look, I'm flattered.
But I've had power of immortals
and gods alike.
It blows.
My past is complicated.
And being in a relationship...
Trust me, that wouldn't end well
for either of us.
Wait.
Did you two sleep together
or something?
Oh. What a shame.
- Kill her!
- What?
No.
Come on.
Unless you lot want those bullets
firing back at you...
bugger off.
Run away! Run away!
I told you you could stop bullets!
Not how I wanted to find out.
Come here.
- Yeah, that was sick.
- I know.
Is that Genghis' toothpick?
Yeah, you want it?
Oh, no, it's disgusting.
You said you were gonna tell us
what's really going on with you.
Look, I'm just... I'm still trying
to find the words, all right?
Can you try to find them faster?
Fine.
I'm just gonna come out with it.
I am a Fate.
One of the three old Greek ladies?
That's offensive, but correct.
Which one are you?
Clotho, the spinner.
I'm super-confused,
but what do you spin?
Look, I don't spin anything anymore
but I used to spin people's futures.
On your loom.
Oh, lovely.
Even Gideon's joining in. Yes.
There was a loom, but I
destroyed it thousands of years ago.
No one should have
that kind of power.
I think people should just decide
their own destinies.
Why didn't you just tell us?
Look, I've been keeping this secret
for my entire bloody existence.
All right?
I've never told anyone.
Can we see your OG form?
Absolutely not.
Is it 'cause you're old?
It's because your eyes will explode,
all right?
And your ears, too,
if you could hear my original voice.
Why are you running?
My sisters are coming after me.
They have been
ever since I destroyed our loom.
Wait, you've been running
for thousands of years?
Yes. And I've always stayed
one step ahead.
I scattered the loom pieces
across the multi-verse
which took away my sisters' powers.
But, now that we're all in one
universe...
thanks to Sara
and her merry band of Paragons...
the Loom pieces are back
on one plane.
And now it's only a matter of time
until my sisters find me.
And when they do?
They'll kill me
and anyone that I'm with.
Which is why I left.
And it's why I'm out that door now
that we're done playing "Ask a Fate."
Stop running.
We got your back.
That is exactly what I'm afraid of.
My sisters are no joke.
Well, we're the Legends.
Yeah.
We can take out a couple old ladies.
What is with all these damn scooters?
They're a menace!
Oh. Hey, guys. What'd I miss?
Well, I lost my scooter at first.
But the good news is,
don't worry about it, I found it.
John, this wine is delicious.
And nutritious.
Well, there's no point
in saving the good stuff, eh?
I'm never gonna drink with you again.
Come on, mate. Stiff upper lip, eh?
I'm gonna miss you so much, you know?
Nothing can make me feel better!
Oh, bollocks, all right.
Look.
I didn't want you
to see my will until I died, but...
Raymond, if you'd do the honors.
Oh, sure.
You're giving this house to Gary?
Bloody hell. That was supposed
to make you happy, not insufferable.
I promise to take great care
of this place.
You know, I'll feed the Hell hounds,
I'll vacuum...
Why don't we talk about what you had
on your bucket list, eh, Ray?
- Really?
- Yeah.
Give me something meaningful, ey.
Well eventually...
I plan on asking Nora to marry me.
Can I be your flower boy?
Oh. That's very sweet, Gary.
Odd, but very sweet.
Why haven't you asked her yet,
big man?
I've been engaged twice before.
Both times didn't end as I had hoped.
You know, life, it is...
too short to dilly-dally, Raymond.
You can take that from a man
who has nothing but regrets.
So, if you love that witch...
you bloody well marry her, all right?
No, no, no, I'm all right.
I'm all right.
Now, how about a toast, ey?
Okay.
No, no.
Of all the ways
that I thought I'd go...
decapitated by a demon,
eviscerated by an elemental...
I wouldn't have picked
being at home with my mates.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
You know, I just wish
I had more time with you,
lovely idiots.
Well, you're not dead yet, John.
No, but I will be momentarily.
John Constantine...
he always goes out on his own terms.
John?
Couldn't wait to see me, John.
Sixty seconds and you're dead.
Poison does that.
It's the same poison
your mother used to kill herself.
You won't change my mind.
I'm not trying to.
I just want you to know that...
even though you gave up on her,...
your mom never gave up on you.
Are you going to Scarborough Fair
Parsley, sage, rosemary and thyme
- Stop.
- Remember me to one who lives there
For once she was a true love of mine
That was our song!
Aye, it was.
But she sang it to me first.
You can really bring her back?
Answer me!
I can fix everything.
I'm glad that hurt.
Tick-tock, John.
I can kill you anytime I want.
Oh, my God!
I can't take this anymore.
You're alive.
Astra, she reconsidered.
She reconsidered.
She reconsidered. She reconsidered.
She reconsidered!
I can't bloody believe it.
I'm back in the game!
Oh, bully. Bully, Bully, Bully!
I love you!
Bully, Bully, Bully, Bully, Bully!
Yes, I can't believe
she bloody reconsidered!
I feel like a new man.
I can't believe
I was gonna leave my house to you.
- What?
- Here, give me that will.
How did you get Astra
to change her mind?
By making a promise...
that I intend to keep.
Hail the Waverider.
I need to see a lady about a loom.