Previously on The Flash
and Legends of Tomorrow...
Thanks, man, we're good.
I'm leaving Central City.
Every hero has their own journey.
If yours is taking you on a new path,
you owe it to yourself to go.
I watched the men murder you.
Mother ran with Mari.
She abandoned me.
I'm sorry, Kuasa.
When Nora was possessed by Mallus,
he seemed scared of my totem.
You're one of the six.
Maybe these totems are the keys
to stopping him.
I only know about five totems.
Could there be more?
That woman
clearly has a crush on you.
I thought that maybe if you'd
like to come to the ship...
There's no time.
Director Hunter has escaped.
Wally West, I need your help.
This way, lads.
Fifteen men
on a dead man's chest
Yo-ho-ho and a bottle of rum
This be the spot. Get to diggin'.
Surely, ye don't mean for these men
to be knowin' where we
buried our treasure.
"Our treasure," my love?
Aye. Ours, and no one else's.
No, no. Don't concern yourself
over a few doubloons.
I didn't show these sorry sea dogs
the most valuable trinket
in me possession.
An emerald fit for a pirate queen.
How do I look?
Annie?
Edward!
Take it off!
I don't know what I'm looking at.
Looks like a hemorrhoid.
What? No. It's Mallus.
Demon horns?
Anyway, the hunt for the six totems
has begun.
There are only five tribes in Zambesi.
Each was gifted with a totem.
And I checked,
there's no record of a sixth.
Well, the good news is that we have
the Air and the Spirit Totems.
Kuasa has the Water Totem.
And since the final totem
is a complete mystery,
that leaves us looking for
Earth and Fire.
Now, the Fire Totem which is
currently smashed, BTW,
was last seen in Detroit Museum
in 2018.
Wait, how do you know that?
Because it is with
your granddaughter Mari's,
a.k.a. the other Vixen's, boyfriend,
Dr. Adam Macalester.
He's dedicated his life to the study
of the Zambesi totems.
Well, if Constantine is right,
and the only thing that Mallus fears
is the six,
then we need to get our hands
on the Fire Totem.
Ah.
Collect the set, win a prize.
We need to tell Sara
we gotta get to Detroit.
Nope. She's off to Star City.
She's been texting some guy.
They're going on a date.
How do you know?
What, are you looking at her phone?
I look at everyone's phone.
Helps pass the time.
Well, who's she going on a date with?
- Obviously it's Ava.
- Oh, that's hot.
What's hot?
Uh... The Fire Totem. Hot, hot.
Very hot and currently in Detroit.
So what do you say
we motor off to the Motor City?
Right now?
Um...
I might sit this one out
because I have to do
business back home.
I bet you do.
Hi.
Wow.
- You look...
- Weird.
I look weird, right?
I was gonna say beautiful, but...
Thank you. So do you. It's... Wow.
Do you wanna...
Right.
Madam?
You know what, I'll just have
whatever she's having, please.
- Vodka martini. Extra dirty. Stirred.
- Of course.
Stirred, not shaken?
Shaken's for lightweights who like
their booze watered-down.
And James Bond.
James Bond never had to fight off
a horde of Vikings
or help me escape a demon realm.
- True.
- Um...
How is work?
Work is... Ugh. This is awful.
You know what, I have an idea.
Let's just try to be normal
for one night.
No Legends, no Bureau.
What do you think?
- There you are.
- Thank you.
I feel like relationships
are complicated enough
without time travel
and supervillains, don't you?
Okay.
Then, here's to being two regular women
on a completely normal first date.
Completely normal.
Hey. You okay?
My granddaughter, the good one,
she's out there.
I wanna see her more than anything.
But you can't without
screwing up history.
Some days I wish I had never heard of
time travel.
Yeah.
Hmm. I like what you have done
with your hair.
Oh, really? I hate it.
- Good news.
- Bad news.
What's going on?
- I know where...
- Fire Totem's...
Ray-Ray, you go first.
We tried to steal the Fire Totem
from your granddaughter's boyfriend.
But someone beat us to it.
Damien Darhk.
You know, for a megalomaniac, he has
very lovely penmanship.
- I know, right?
- Yeah.
Oh, and by the way, don't worry,
Macalester's fine.
Can I talk now, please?
Yeah, you said you had good news.
I know where the Earth Totem is.
Or more precisely, when.
1717. Saint Lisette.
Saint Lisette. Sister ship of
La Concorde.
Get to the point, Pretty.
La Concorde was boarded by pirates
and later named
Queen Anne's Revenge.
It's Blackbeard the pirate's ship.
So Blackbeard has the Earth Totem.
Well, let's steal it.
No. Guys, hold on. Sara is on a date.
We should probably avoid
messing with history
while she's still on appetizers.
But think how happy she'd be
if we had the Earth Totem by dessert.
At this juncture,
the responsible thing to do
would be to consult Captain Lance.
Who would tell us we can't risk
the Darhks getting another Totem.
All those in favor
of setting a course to 1717?
Aye.
Arr.
Aye!
- Aye.
- Ah!
How are we supposed to find
Blackbeard in this rabble?
Well, we could ask a pirate nicely.
"Nicely"? Ray, pirates are terrified
of Blackbeard.
- They're not gonna just offer us...
- So you looking for Blackbeard?
How do I know youse not spies
for the Royal Navy?
Because we wanna join
Blackbeard's crew, you germ.
It's, uh, rather a lovely place
you've traveled to, Mr. West.
How did you find me?
By tracking the geo-location of
your MP3 player.
Your playlist consists of a rather
amazing number of repetitions
of George Michael's Careless Whisper.
Jesse loved that song.
I assume that your recent heartbreak
is the reason
for your spiritual quest?
However, with the fate
of the world at stake,
I'm afraid that you can no longer
sit idly by.
Uh, I'm sorry, my friend,
but my days of fafooming are over.
Right now, I'm living my life
one quarter-mile at a time.
Is that a Buddhist koan?
Dom Torreto. The Fast and The Furious.
Aren't you BFFs with the Legends?
I'm sure my boy Nate can help you out.
Uh, it seems that my days of Legending
are over.
Alas, you're quite secure
in your decision to slow things down.
I am.
Well, the last time I was this far east
was in the Opium War.
Be a shame to waste a trip.
Fancy a drink?
Another flagon of ale!
So this is where Blackbeard hangs out.
- Classy.
- Yep.
Line 'em up.
What's up?
Nothing.
I said, what's up?
Fine. You're an unbiased listener.
I want to change my granddaughter
Kuasa's past
and, well, improve her future.
So do it.
It's not that simple.
What if I inadvertently change
my other granddaughter's destiny?
So don't do it.
And then there's Nate.
I still have to go back to 1942
and marry someone else
so that Kuasa and Mari are even born.
We can never end up together.
I feel paralyzed.
Every step I take, it feels like
it could just have
disastrous consequences.
Take a look around.
You think these people give a damn
about consequences?
Take the night off.
A true pirate doesn't live for tomorrow,
they only live for the moment.
Thanks, Mick.
But I don't know the first thing
about acting like a pirate.
Well... I do.
It was just Laurel and I.
I was always the rebel,
and she was always the good one.
Why do you look like
you already know this, hmm?
What, did you google me?
No.
I may have read your file.
Back when you were a fugitive
from the Bureau,
and, look, I know that sounds stalker-y,
but in my defense,
I did not see this coming.
Well, what do you wanna know?
Okay. You always seem
so composed and cool,
but you can't be all cool all the time.
What's the most embarrassed
you've ever been?
That's an easy one.
First time I ever had a weapon
in my hand.
- Lian Yu?
- Nope.
Starling City Elementary.
I was Peter Pan in the school play.
I got up on stage for the first
scene and I just totally froze,
I couldn't remember any of my lines.
It was like my mind just went blank.
What did you do?
Well, I broke out into a tap dance
of course,
and then I ran off-stage crying.
You can dance?
Go ahead. You can check it.
I'm sure it's nothing. It's just...
- It's a voicemail. I'm just gonna...
- It's okay.
It wasn't my idea, but the team
has taken the Waverider
on a joyride to the Bahamas, 1717,
in a futile attempt to locate
the missing Earth Totem.
Just thought you should know.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, totally fine.
- Normal, in fact.
- Hmm.
The Captain wants to see you.
Oh, man, Sara's here?
Not that one, you dumbass.
I'm talking about the most fearsome
pirate queen to sail the seven seas.
The Dread Pirate Jiwe.
- She needs to loosen up.
- Yeah.
I heard she once cut out a man's tongue
for not obeying her orders.
Yeah, and she still carries it
to this day.
I never heard of no lady pirate.
That's because dead men tell no tales.
Aye.
They say she lost her ship to a kraken
and in retribution, she hunted
down the monster's wee bairn
and ate the gupper raw.
I heard she was spat back outta hell
by the devil himself.
Hmm. I hear she be more bold
and fearless than Captain Blackbeard.
Beggin' your pardon, Captain.
What was that ye said?
I have it under good authority
we be in the company
of the Dread Pirate Jiwe.
Why's everyone
staring at me?
Because one thing pirates love
more than treasure is a good story.
Blackbeard. He's heading this way.
- Hit me.
- What?
The mission is yours. Have fun
getting the Earth Totem back. Hit me.
Now, get out of my sight before
I really lose my temper.
So you're the Dread Pirate Jiwe, eh?
Welcome to Nassau.
Rory, Amaya, come in. Over.
Some sort of interference
with the communication system.
Guys, answer me. Over.
Hey, calm down. I'm sure they're okay.
My apologies,
but I'm experiencing
a Level 4 systems failure.
Wasn't me. Nothing to do with it.
I believe the fault lies
in our present coordinates.
You did park me in the middle
of the Bermuda Triangle.
Sailors call it "the Devil's Triangle."
No, the stories of ships disappearing
are grossly exaggerated.
Um...
You sure about that, Ray?
The scuttlebutt is you're wanting
to join me crew.
The Dread Pirate Jiwe works for no man.
What we seek is treasure.
As does every pirate
worth his or her salt.
You know, I believe that you have
this particular treasure
in your possession.
It's a necklace with
a very large emerald.
That description doesn't strike a chord.
Let me jog your memory.
A couple of pirates
after me own cold, black heart.
I'll tell you where the trinket is.
But at a price.
I'm here for the pirate
known as Blackbeard.
I expect you'll be wanting to see
me letter of marque?
A forgery, no doubt.
Your letter will win no favor with me.
I wouldn't so much as breathe
if I were you.
Good evening, Miss Jiwe.
They say the third time is a charm.
But this charm is the third.
No.
I must commend you, Lieutenant Maynard,
for leading us straight to Blackbeard
and his associates.
- You're most welcome, Admiral.
- "Admiral"?
I know, right? I look so handsome.
And I'll be made Commodore
once Blackbeard's severed head
swings from my ship's bowsprit.
You know, the last kingsman
who threatened me
ended up begging for his own life.
Gentlemen, please.
You may continue all threats
and counter-threats
as soon as I get what I need.
The emerald necklace.
Where is it?
That's Blackbeard you're talking to,
and he ain't gonna say...
I buried it on Grace Island.
Would you like me to draw you a map?
I can't promise to make it to scale,
but, um, I could do me damnedest.
You heard the man.
Let's have another drink.
Oh.
Appears to be empty.
Gimme some of that.
No, this, this is not for you.
Please. I drank Hemingway
and Van Gogh under the table.
Cisco gave this to me
before I left Central City.
The only way a speedster can get
drunk is off of this rocket fuel.
- Rocket fuel.
- Yeah.
Uh... Oh.
Mmm!
- Cisco's a ruddy genius.
- Yeah, he is.
So is Barry and Caitlin and Wells.
Wait, maybe that's why I never fit
on Team Flash.
And here I was, thinking you were
roaming the Chinese countryside
because your girlfriend
needed more space.
Look, I can do one better
than that, mate.
Both of my favorite protégés
conspired to have me put in prison.
- What happened?
- Well, I lied to Sara
in addition to accidentally aiding in
the resurrection of the man
who killed her sister.
And Ava is angry at me for sending
good agents to their deaths.
Whoa...
It sounds like you're a bit of a douche.
No offense.
No, none taken, I...
I intend to make it up to both of them,
but first I need the teensiest,
teensiest of favors.
Hey, Agent McNeil, just calling
to say congrats
on being named Agent of the Month.
The Bureau's lucky to have you.
I'm coming for you, McNeil.
Hello?
Who's there?
Not again.
This is way more fun than meditating.
I know.
Right, there is one item we must procure
from the Bureau storage closet
and one that is very near and dear
to my heart.
Oh.
We're screwed.
The ship's electrical systems
are experiencing
multiple unexplained malfunctions.
It's the Devil's Triangle.
Look, that's just a myth.
Whatever it is, we need to time jump
out of here.
What? And leave Mick and Amaya
stranded in pirate times?
It's a miracle we're still in the air.
Well, I'm sure they're having
a whale of a time with Blackbeard.
What's so funny about getting
your head chopped off?
Mmm. There are worse ends.
Like the one I brought on
that fool admiral.
That necklace is cursed.
I saw its dastardly work
with me own eyes.
Get your hands off me, you blaggards.
I'm so sorry, Mick.
If I really was the Dread Pirate Jiwe,
I never would have let Darhk
steal my totem.
The hell you apologizing for?
You're better than the story.
And a hell of a lot more fearsome
than some pirate queen,
with or without your totem.
This man, Edward Teach,
has been convicted of unlawful piracy
and plunder.
Therefore, it is my duty
as an instrument of the Crown to...
- Watch out!
- Aye!
You're in sore need of a sword, pirate.
Gideon, maybe you can help us
settle an argument.
What are the chances of survival
if we stay in the Bermuda Triangle?
Zero. There are multiple
cannonballs headed towards
our starboard bow as we speak.
Um, sorry, "cannonballs"?
I thought we were cloaked.
I tried to tell you coming here
was a bad idea.
Who the heck's firing at us?
I want that ship brought down.
Fire another volley!
Aye, sir!
You wouldn't kill an unarmed man.
You're showing him mercy?
Shut up! We just saved your hairy neck.
Try to keep up, boys.
Gideon, jump us out of here!
My heart is pounding,
my palms are sweaty
and I know that I only have
a few rounds left in my pocket.
So what did you do?
I grabbed a guy and used him
as a human shield.
And from that point on,
no one would ever play paintball
with me ever again.
Well, it sounds like
a hell of a 15th birthday party.
Mmm-hmm.
- You okay?
- I'm gonna run to the restroom.
Really quickly... I'm sorry.
We're gonna need the check.
Please tell me that the Waverider
did not just crash into Star City.
Star City? Is that where we are?
Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
Well, the good news is the cannonball
didn't hit the time core.
And Nate made a beautiful landing.
Yeah. Thanks, big guy.
So, Sara, how's the date going?
It's over.
Come here. Come here.
What the hell are you doing here?
Please don't be mad.
You weren't answering your phone.
This better be
a life-or-death emergency, Gary.
Worse. A speedster stole
my Time Courier.
And then pantsed me.
And then...
- Did you check if HQ is secure?
- Snug as a bug.
Except one item was reported
missing from storage.
A long, brown coat that
used to belong to, uh...
- Rip Hunter.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- You look great, by the way.
Shut up, Gary. Remember, we talked
about personal space.
- Yeah, okay.
- Come on.
Ouch.
Double ouch.
- You want me to box it up for you?
- No, Gary.
Okay, we need to find Rip.
He's got a Time Courier, which means
he could be anywhere, any time,
causing a whole mess of problems.
Time can never mend
The careless whisper
Of a good friend
To the heart and mind
Ignorance is blind
There's no comfort in the truth
Pain is all you'll find
I'm never gonna dance again
Guilty feet ain't got no rhythm
Though it's easy to pretend
I know you're not a fool
When I left, you were headed to Detroit.
Yeah, it's a... It's a really...
It's a really long story.
Mick and Amaya are marooned in 1717.
The Darhks have the Fire Totem
and Blackbeard has the Earth Totem.
That's... I thought it was gonna be
a longer story.
Thank God you're back. You look great.
The engine room's a disaster.
We're not going anywhere.
I don't know who looks more ridiculous,
you guys in your pirate britches
or me in this stupid dress.
Definitely them.
Hey, I know it looks like a mess,
but we really wanted you to have
a nice night out.
Yeah, if you really like that
mean Time Bureau lady,
you shouldn't give up on her.
Look, I'm not giving up on anything
other than maybe the idea
that I'll ever have a normal life.
Zari, get the ship back
in fighting shape
because until then,
Rory and Amaya are on their own.
All right, listen up.
We can't let the Darhks beat us to
Grace Island and to the Earth Totem,
so we're in need of a ship.
You want to sail
the Queen Anne's Revenge?
I told you that necklace is cursed.
What?
You're gonna let a curse stop you
from taking the gold?
Aye.
Why did you become a pirate
in the first place, eh?
- Well...
- To let an admiral get the best of you
or to claim your destiny
on the wide open sea?
I don't know what's waiting for us on
the other side of this journey,
but whatever it is,
it beats cowering in some alleyway
waiting for your black beard
to turn gray.
I swore I'd never go back
to that island.
And I'm a man of me word.
Fair winds, my hearties.
- Blackbeard's a coward.
- Look alive, men. Shoot on sight!
Come on, keep moving.
We don't need Blackbeard.
We just need his ship.
Ah, another drink?
Listen up!
The Dread Pirate Jiwe
is looking for a crew.
Your old captain, Blackbeard,
buried his treasure on Grace Island.
Ah.
So you've heard the rumors then,
that the treasure is cursed?
But while old Blackbeard is afraid
of his own shadow,
you men,
you vile and despicable men,
are willing to face Davy Jones himself
for a crack at gold and glory!
Who's willing to join me
as we take over Blackbeard's ship?
Mutiny!
Is that what this is, eh?
You'd rather follow
the Dread Pirate Jiwe
than your own captain?
Then I'm bloody joining you.
I'll dig up me chest
and share the spoils with ye men.
Hats off to the pirate queen!
- All hands on deck!
- Aye, sir!
Secure the backstays and hoist
the Jolly Roger high.
There's land ahead.
Sara!
Yeah. What now?
We have another anachronism in 1717.
The HMS Fortitude got into
a naval battle with Blackbeard's ship
off the coast of Grace Island.
So?
So that is a portrait of their Admiral.
Ugh. Damien Darhk.
I don't care if Zari has to duct-tape
the Waverider back together,
we have to get it in the air.
Well, I wouldn't advise
returning to the Bermuda Triangle.
It's "the Devil's Triangle,"
and Mick and Amaya are in danger.
Ava! Hey!
Don't "Hi, Ava" me.
You stood me up, jerk.
Awkward.
Blackbeard draws
one hell of a map.
Dig.
Oh! Blast!
I've left me compass on the ship.
It's a family heirloom...
Turn back and I'll kill you.
What aren't you telling us, eh?
Well, in me haste, I may have
left out some minuscule details
about the cursed necklace.
I gifted it to me love and queen,
the most devious,
dastardly woman I've ever
had the pleasure of meeting.
Apart from you, I mean.
But as soon as Annie put it on,
something dark and unholy overtook her.
Totems draw on the life force
of their bearer.
So if Anne was as wicked as you suggest,
the totem would have only amplified
her worst impulses.
It turned her into a monster.
How did you live to tell the tale?
Well, I did the only
decent thing any man would do.
I put a musket ball in her head and
buried her along with the treasure.
That cursed necklace won't let her
rest in peace.
Me Annie will rise again.
Stiffen your backbones, men.
I gotta hand it to you,
Miss Lance,
you take the phrase "Dine and dash"
to a whole new level.
Look, the Waverider fell out of
the sky. My team needed help.
Why does that
not surprise me?
Should we interrupt?
No.
But Ava gave me an idea.
Her Time Courier.
I'm coming with you. But first I have
to get the nanite pistol.
No, Ray! Don't!
Steady.
Well, hello, Annie.
It's good to see you're, uh...
You're looking so beautiful.
You know this was never gonna work out.
Really? Because I'm a mature person
who actually can communicate?
Oh, really? Such a communicator!
Like when you said
you were going to the bathroom?
- What are you talking about?
- You think I didn't see Gary?
Oh, my... Rip broke into
the Time Bureau.
I was coming back to the table
to tell you.
- You know what, this is pointless.
- Yeah, it is.
We should have never tried to be normal.
I'm not normal, all right?
I'm never gonna be normal. And I'm
not gonna be normal for anyone.
I don't want you to be normal.
- You don't?
- Hell no.
- What?
- The kiss was great. It's just...
We claim this ship and ye two women
as ours.
Come on.
Hey.
Let's do this.
Come on, ye namby-pamby.
They're only lassies.
Listen to me.
That totem can burden
even one born to wear it.
I know it must feel like a noose
around your neck.
Let me help you break free
of this curse.
Thank you for distracting her.
Unfortunately, now I have to kill you.
Surprisingly powerful.
Well, that was fun.
But playtime is over.
Hey, you guys!
- I want my totem back.
- Ah, you fool.
We don't need swords to kill you.
No!
Good shot, Haircut.
No! No!
Stay with me.
Stay with me, sweetheart. Come on.
You're gonna be okay. Stay with me.
Come on. Let's go.
Don't let her... Come on.
That was too easy.
You two bonny lasses be
the best fighters I've e'er seen.
How would you like to join me crew?
Ah.
The Waverider, eh?
She's a... An unusual ship.
But I can think of no more
appropriate vessel
for the Dread Pirate Jiwe.
Thanks for saving my life
and for stopping your bonny mates
from keelhaulin' me.
Well, thank you for leading me
to the accursed treasure.
And make sure you tell them
that Captain Jiwe spared you.
Absolutely, of course, I...
Fair winds, Captain Jiwe.
Amaya, I am, uh... I'm so sorry.
If I didn't push everybody to go
after the Earth Totem,
you wouldn't have lost yours.
It's all right, Nathaniel.
We'll fix this.
We'll get your totem back.
My birthright, it's always dictated
the path I choose.
It's like a compass
that just points the way.
It must be so difficult not to have it.
It's also freeing.
For the first time in my life,
I get to decide.
Amaya.
You know, I learned something
from hanging out with pirates.
They always focus on the problem
in front of them.
And what is that problem?
Do you yield, sir?
Aye, Captain.
Rum floats
were a very good idea.
It only seemed fair
since we missed dessert.
Ha.
What?
Sometimes we screw things up
for the better.
I will drink to that.
Cheers.
Ah. It's good.
Hey, look, I'm sorry
about bailing on you earlier.
I should have been honest with you
about what was going on with my team.
No. No, no, no.
I should have never put the kibosh
on talking shop.
- You're right, it's your fault.
- You... Oh, man.
Besides, I'd rather fight pirates
with you any day
than sit in some stupid restaurant.
Well, in that case,
I was thinking Genghis Khan
for our second date.
Done.
But only if I can call you "Peter Pan."
- Don't. Don't.
- Miss...
Okay.
So you got a room on this ship or...
Let's go find out.
Why do you look so chipper?
Oh, no, I had a terrible hangover.
It lasted three minutes.
Mmm. The benefits
of a speedster's metabolism.
Here, take these.
- Thank you.
- Mmm.
You know, last night was pretty fun.
- Yeah.
- It got a bit lonely here, I think.
Yeah, I've been a bit lonely too.
Hey, your girlfriend dumped you,
your team treat you like an outcast.
It's no wonder you're on walkabout,
but the world needs Wallace West
to step in from the cold.
And I know a place where outcasts
fit right in.
In fact, some might say
that they've become Legends.
- Care to join me?
- What?
Is Careless Whisper not the best
karaoke song of all time?
It is the way we sing it, mate.
Haircut, want a beer?
Everyone's off doing their own thing.
Just you and me.
Sure. I could use a beer.
Even if I am
your last choice of companion.
Oh, that. Just doing a bit
of light theorizing.
And then I had a breakthrough.
I'm going to develop a liquid for
the perfect dry-erase marker.
Strong viscosity, clean lines...
You're a terrible liar.
Yeah.
It's Nora.
The nanite pistol's gonna kill her.
Uh...
That's what it's supposed to do,
but now I feel...
- Like a badass.
- No.
Guilty.
What?
- You saved Amaya.
- I know.
Doesn't really make sense,
except that I met her as a kid.
Well, now, she's all grown up
and joined the demon side.
Yeah.
But you, you have changed
since I first met you.
And I hate to break it to you, Mick,
but you are a much better person.
And maybe Nora
could have become one too.
There was hope for her anyway
before I took it away.
Come on, sweetheart, you gotta fight.
Stay with me. Come on.
Look, I know I'm the last person
you wanna see.
What did you do to my daughter?
Nothing that can't be undone.
I have a cure.
You and your great big heart.
You just couldn't handle the guilt,
could you?
I've come for a trade.
Amaya's totem, and I will save Nora.
I honestly thought that would be harder.
My daughter is all that matters.
Come on.
Steady.
That's it.
Ray.
You remember me?
Yes.
Darling. Wait.
He may be of value.
Welcome back.