Grey's hit!
We gotta get him out of there.
Where's Barry when you need him?
Just tying up some loose ends.
He's almost at the breach hangar.
If we don't stop him, he's going
to blow up our only ticket home.
Not to mention us.
Some help with that, please.
No, no, no... No!
Grey, stay down.
Grey! No!
Grey!
Fall back. Fall back!
He did it.
He opened the breach.
Let's go.
Hey.
Barry, the breach is open.
Where are you?
We got to take him out now.
I have an idea.
Throw another lightning bolt.
We already tried that.
Just do it.
Now!
Barry, we need you to hurry up.
Stein's hurt.
All right, we're on the move.
He's alive,
but his condition is critical.
All right, Gideon will fix him.
No, it's too dangerous to move him.
Not if he's Firestorm.
Yeah.
Grey? Grey!
Grey!
Come on.
- Thanks for your help.
- We're not done helping yet.
Our enemies
are still on your Earth, Ollie.
Don't call me that.
Give it time, I'll get through
that crusty exterior.
No, you really won't.
I was talking to you.
- Oh, my God.
- Kara.
What are they doing?
This next sound,
metal through a bone,
is my favorite.
I think you should probably
close your eyes.
This will all be over in a minute.
What are you waiting for? Do it.
I'm trying.
I'm trying, but...
Mitts off, Mengele!
- Ray?
- Hi.
How are ya?
I got your SOS.
How was the wedding?
All right, don't worry.
The rest of the Legends are here.
We're busting everybody out.
Wait, we need
someone to lock the time vault.
I got it. You guys
get Kara out of here.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
Okay, I know I'm late to the party,
but why have Nazi doppelgangers
- taken over S.T.A.R. Labs?
- They are from Earth-X.
They hate everybody.
They want to steal Kara's heart.
And they have this giant robot.
Oh. I've actually
fought one of those before.
Little-known fact,
this suit doesn't just shrink...
Ray!
It embiggens.
Attention, all prisoners.
Great news. The cavalry has arrived.
About time.
I knew I could count on you, Pretty.
Did you bring beers?
Better yet, an army.
Who needs an army
when you've got Legends?
We have a problem.
I need you to wake up, Kara.
The general
is no longer safe, here.
I'm well aware.
Retreat to the troop carrier
and prepare for the invasion.
- Without you?
- I'm staying.
Supergirl is not leaving here alive.
Do not make it personal.
That is not a good idea...
Are you questioning
your Fuhrer's orders?
Of course not,
General.
Stay here. Stay safe.
And I'll be back for you
with her heart.
So, this is Earth-1? Cute.
We need to find Kara.
Then we need to split up.
I've got Supergirl.
I've got group B.
- You're late.
- Oh, don't mind him.
He's just pissy
because he came out of a steel box.
Actually, he's always like this.
What the hell?
How much further, Ray?
The Waverider's on the roof.
How do you two know each other again?
- We used to date.
That's awkward.
Careful.
Oliver got the girl.
I got a life adventure
on a time-traveling spaceship.
Step away from her.
There's no way.
My grandparents
didn't survive the Holocaust
so the world could be ruled by Nazis.
So, if you want Kara,
you got to go through me.
Even if you do,
you're not going to win.
Because we will not back down.
We will keep fighting.
So, get the hell off our Earth
while you still can.
As final words go,
those weren't bad.
Lower your weapon.
Or I'll kill her.
This guy is like the Terminator.
Why are you laughing?
I just love a good pop culture
reference in a moment of crisis.
Also, that!
Let's kick some ass!
You know,
her neck doesn't seem invulnerable.
So, I will say again,
lower your weapon!
- Don't listen to him. Just shoot.
- No! No.
I can save your wife's life.
There's only one way to save me.
We have friends at S. T.A.R. Labs.
There are ways to do this
without hurting Kara.
He's lying.
Do it for the fatherland.
Just kill her!
I thought that jerk
was supposed to be dead.
Hey.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay. You're safe.
- You're safe...
- I shouldn't have said what I said.
What if it was the last thing
we ever said to each other?
It doesn't matter. Nothing matters
except that I love you.
We don't need anything else.
I don't need to get married.
I just want to be with you.
Okay?
Gideon! Fix him!
His pressure is dropping.
We have to stanch the bleeding.
Right away, Dr. Snow.
Jax, relax.
The Professor is going to be fine.
He's a tough bastard.
Jax is hit!
I can't find an entry wound.
Look at their vitals, it must be
because of their connection.
What the hell does that mean?
Even though Jax isn't injured
their life functions
must still be linked somehow.
Well, how do we un-link them?
We can't.
Their connection is the only thing
keeping the Professor alive.
Are you okay?
I can't even begin
to answer that right now.
We should be on our honeymoon.
We should be on a beach
drinking mai tais out of coconuts.
Instead we're on this spaceship
looking for our friends'
evil doppelgangers.
We should have just eloped.
- Kara?
- Alex.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
- I can't believe they almost...
- I know. I know.
- I thought I lost you.
- Me too.
So much for
getting away from it all, huh?
I should have known better
than to think that a wedding
on another Earth is going to solve
- all of our problems.
- Yeah, but...
You know, fighting the evil versions
of ourselves does kind of put
those problems in perspective,
doesn't it?
Way to see the silver lining.
Hey there, friend.
No need to numb
your feelings with alcohol.
Ghost is back.
No. I'm not a ghost.
I'm Leo, Leo Snart from Earth-X.
It's okay, buddy.
I know you're hurting over Firestorm.
Get your hand off me.
What is wrong, partner? Talk to me.
You're not my partner.
You're a gangbanger.
I think you mean "doppelganger."
There was one of you
on my Earth, too.
Rest his soul.
Wait, I'm dead on Planet Nazi?
Let me guess, in a fire?
You just kept going back
into that burning police station.
Till the last officer
had been rescued.
I died
trying to save pigs?
I'm going to be sick.
How are you feeling, Jax?
Don't worry about me.
How's Grey?
I have him sedated.
Don't worry, Gideon and I are doing
everything we can to fix him.
Okay, good.
Still no improvement?
He's getting worse.
Marty or Jax?
Both.
Just can't believe
there's nothing Gideon can do.
Medically speaking, Professor Stein
shouldn't even be alive right now.
The only thing that kept him
from dying is...
Jax,
- bonding with him.
- Yeah.
Jax is basically functioning
as a human life-support machine,
able to keep
the Professor alive, but...
Only for so long.
Does Jax know?
That he's going to die, too?
I didn't know how to tell him.
It will be okay.
We've got a whole mess
of smart people on this ship.
Somebody is going
to figure out something.
Okay.
Oh, man.
I have just died
and went to geek heaven.
I told you we picked the right guy.
Picked the right guy to do what?
Hunt Nazis.
Meet our resident Earth-X expert,
The Ray.
But, you can use my real name,
Ray Terrill.
Your secret identity
is your first name
with a word "The" in front of it?
Yeah.
Why, what's your secret identity?
Mr. Terrific.
Really? It's a little boast-y,
don't you think?
That's just one of
my favorite wrestlers.
Still... You should change your name.
Can we talk about these Nazis?
They vanished, owing to the fact
that they have their own Waverider.
A Nazi Waverider?
Yeah. We had been tracking them
using the radiation signature
given off by Overgirl,
because of her...
Extreme exposure
to the solar radiation.
Are these readings right?
Yeah, of course they're right, why?
Because the trace radiation readings
on here are slowly approaching
the Chandrasekhar limit.
- Which means?
- Overgirl isn't just dying.
Yeah, if she doesn't
get Supergirl's heart,
she will create a supernova
that will destroy the entire Midwest.
Jefferson?
Jefferson.
I need to tell you something.
What? Talk fast.
Because unless you're sedated,
Gideon can't do her thing
to patch you back up.
Can't you see that
I'm dying?
What are you talking about, man?
I'm old, Jefferson.
And, even if I hadn't been shot,
no one lives forever.
Grey, I don't even want to hear
you talking like that, man.
As long as we're connected
I'm nothing more than an anchor
around your neck.
Which is why you must help me.
I don't understand.
Not Cisco's drug.
Gideon resynthesized the liquid.
She assures me it will free you
from my body's biology.
And it will free you of mine.
I'm the only thing
that's keeping you alive, man.
You're asking me to kill you, Grey!
I'm asking you to let me die
so that you may live.
Please, hand me the vial.
No.
I know you think
you're strong enough for both of us.
But, unless I do this,
we'll both die.
Then we'll both die. I don't...
No.
You have your whole life
ahead of you.
And now, it's time
for you to let me go.
But I'm not ready for you to go.
I'm not either.
But, when you think about it,
compared to the cosmos,
one's life is but a blink of an eye.
Really? You're going to lecture me
about astrophysics right now?
Grey, please, don't do this to me.
I can't do this.
You once told me
that I was like your father,
and I said
you were my son.
How could a father do anything less?
- Grey.
- Please.
Please.
Thank you, Jefferson.
Grey, no, don't.
Stay with me, please.
I'd prefer not to be alone.
Yeah.
Please,
tell Clarissa and Lily
that I love them.
I promise.
And thank you, Jefferson,
for the adventure of a lifetime.
I hope your life
is long and full of love.
Just as mine has been.
Grey.
No, no.
Jax?
He did it for me.
Where's Jax?
I'll get it, honey.
Jefferson!
I'm sorry.
Oh, my...
Oh, no!
How are you holding up?
I'll cry at the funeral.
Sara?
I'm fine.
We need to gather everyone.
Overgirl is going to go nuclear
and the Earth-Xers are going to use
their Waverider
to threaten Central City
and leverage us
into surrendering Kara.
How do you know that?
It's exactly what I would do.
I am sorry.
For what?
For being so weak.
I've managed to stabilize
her deterioration,
but without a transplant
she'll be dead within an hour.
Quiet!
Now, don't you listen to her.
There is more strength in you
than in this entire planet
of lesser humans combined.
Nice outfit.
Yeah, I didn't want to feel left out.
Where are we
with locating the other Waverider?
We've got a pretty good idea.
We've all heard
of the Chandrasekhar limit, I assume?
The data indicates it's still
in the vicinity of Central City.
Which also indicates that Overgirl
isn't long for this world.
Which means that this world
Failure is not an option.
Losing is not an option.
We are going to win.
And we are going to show these people
that this Earth belongs to us.
Great speech.
Sorry to interrupt, Mr. Queen.
But we're being hailed
by a fellow Timeship.
Put it on.
What do you want?
To offer a truce.
In exchange for what?
We will return to our Earth,
peacefully,
if you meet my one demand.
Supergirl comes with us.
Here's another difference
between you and me.
I don't abandon my friends.
All right. Everybody ready to go?
Never been more.
We can't bring Marty back,
but we can protect the city he loved,
and the family he left behind.
For the Professor.
Now, let's go kick some ass.
Let them run.
We'll turn this city
into a mausoleum.
Kill them all!
Yes, sir!
Excuse me, you can't just
go around roasting people.
- Why not?
- You ever heard of due process?
Rule of law?
No.
I could use a little help here.
I got you covered.
This is just like Star Raiders
on Atari, except it's real!
Cut the chatter, Red 2.
Fly the ship.
Launching torpedo one.
You don't have to say it out loud.
Okay guys, is it just me
or is this not working?
- It's not working.
You need to take down their shields.
Guys, this isn't working.
I think we need a bigger gun.
Way ahead of you.
General, we've got inbound.
Then fire countermeasures.
We can't.
It's hovering directly off our bow.
General, you care to step outside?
Waiting for some good news here.
I don't have any for you, man. The
only way to take out their shields
is to get someone
onboard that ship.
We're on our way.
We're on the bridge, Felicity.
But we don't know
what we're looking for.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm working on it.
Felicity's got it.
I'm sending you the source code
for their deflector shields.
Yeah, got it.
Manual override protocol.
If I am reading this correctly
all you need to do now is...
Hit the big blinking red button.
Got it. Shields are down.
- Think you can handle this bad boy?
- Walk in the park.
- Thanks.
- Where are you going?
Getting our friends off that ship.
On the count of ten,
hit them with everything we've got.
You got it.
Come on, Ramon.
Nailed it!
Go on. End it.
End it!
What's stopping you?
Oh, I forgot.
Barry Allen is above killing.
Isn't that right?
Get out of here.
I wonder what face I'll be wearing
next time we meet,
Flash.
Can't wait.
I'm detecting dangerously high
radiation levels.
Disembodied computer voice lady
is right.
Supergirl X is about to go supernova.
Supergirl? Your doppelganger
is about to have a meltdown.
What do I do?
You need to fly her up.
Up and away.
Now.
No!
I'm going to kill you!
How did you...
Figured it would take the Man
of Steel to catch the Girl of Steel.
That and, you know,
a tremendous amount of help.
Thank you, both.
This world owes you a lot.
Well, it's my world, too, so...
Punching out Nazis
is kind of our thing.
Well, if you ever need us
to do any punching over on Earth-X
- just let us know.
- Will do.
- Take care, Barry.
- Take care, Ray.
Barry, I need a hug.
Okay.
- Be good, Leo.
- Always.
I'm going to get ready. You got this?
Yeah.
All right, fellas.
- You ready to go home?
- Sure.
So, how does this thing work?
Oh. It's a very complex
two-part process.
One, I open a breach.
Two, you walk through it.
Cool.
Leo?
I think I'm going to stick around
here for a little while.
I...
I won't stay here forever.
I will come home to you.
Promise.
Okay.
- I love you.
Clarissa asked me to say
a few words.
But, as you all know,
it was Grey, Martin,
who was the wordy one.
But I got used to hearing his voice
inside my head.
And, even now, I can still hear him.
Because, even though he's gone,
he's still a part of me.
He's still a part of all of us.
He was the best man
right until the end.
The best teacher,
friend,
husband,
father.
Clarissa,
I'm so, so sorry.
I couldn't save him.
All he wanted was to come home
to you,
and you and Ronnie.
To his family.
Oh, Jefferson,
you were his family, too.
I just... I don't know how to do
any of this without him.
Well, then don't.
You said it yourself,
he's still part of you.
That's it, big guy, let it out.
Allergies.
Goodbye, my love.
Thank you for believing in me.
Tell Ronnie I miss him.
Thank you for bringing me
home to her.
So, you're going to another Earth
and I'm going to another time.
Yeah, that's kind of
how we roll, huh?
Totally normal.
- Should we...
It's a hug thing, okay.
Okay.
Thank you for putting things
in perspective for me.
Does that mean you are going
to take my advice on Maggie?
Yes, I'm going to trust my instincts.
I mean, there has got to be
somebody else out there for me.
- Right?
- For sure.
Just like there's somebody else
out there for you.
And for more than just a night.
It's funny. That was my takeaway too.
Boss.
The ship's ready.
Catch you on the other side.
You hit that?
Shut up.
Are you ready?
So, so ready.
Yeah.
Thank you, guys, for everything.
And thanks for inviting us
to your wedding.
And I'm sorry it didn't turn out
the way you wanted it to.
Well, at least it was memorable.
Yes.
We'll be back out for the do-over.
Iris and I talked about it...
And, yeah. We're just going to
get ourselves a justice of the peace,
and get it done. Quick and simple.
Fewer Nazis that way.
Well, take care, guys.
- Oh...
- Oh, that's good.
Yeah, bring it in.
All right.
- Let's go.
You guys are really not going to
have a wedding now,
after all that?
- Now she's pro-wedding.
- Hey!
Well, I mean,
we've already had the ceremony,
so all we need to do now
is exchange vows and rings.
Hey, can a mayor marry people?
I'm very flattered. But, I think,
that we would have to be within
the limits of Star City
for it to be official.
And we definitely
want it to be official.
Well, if you want it to be personal
I think we know a guy who's ordained.
It's a good thing
I didn't vomit, right?
- Yeah.
Are you okay?
A little warning next time?
Sorry.
What's up?
You got ordained to marry
your brother and Carly, right?
Yeah?
We were hoping that you
could give us the same treatment.
Wow, really?
- I'm honored.
- Yeah?
I am.
All right. Well, let's do it.
Okay, that's great.
I guess, that makes you
the best man, you the maid of honor?
- "Honored" is correct.
- All right. Let's get into position.
- All right.
- You're here.
- Here?
- Over there. Yeah.
- I see.
- That's great.
Did you guys write vows
or you just want the boilerplate?
Oh. Uh...
Yes, I...
Wrote mine.
I tried to write mine.
But then I realized
that I didn't need to.
My entire life has been marked
by two things.
First one is change.
From when I was a kid
to when I was an adult
things were always changing.
But, no matter
how different things became
or what new challenges I had to face,
I always had the other thing
that my life was marked by.
And that's you.
You've always been there
as a friend,
as a partner,
as the love of my life.
You're my home, Iris.
And that's one thing
that will never change.
That was really nice.
When I was nine years old
I wanted to be a ballerina,
remember?
Even though I was not
a very good dancer.
And, the day of the recital, I froze.
I couldn't move.
And I wanted to die.
And then I looked in the audience
and I saw you.
And you got up
and climbed on the stage
and you did
that whole routine with me.
We killed it.
I mean, we brought the house down.
And from that moment, I knew that
with you by my side
anything was possible.
The Flash may be the city's hero
but you, Barry Allen,
you are my hero.
And I am happy,
excited,
and honored
to be your wife.
Wonderful.
- Well, then I pronounce you both...
- Wait!
Wait. Wait, just one second.
If you guys don't mind...
I mean, if you don't mind.
Really, if you don't mind.
But, would you marry us, too?
Will you marry me?
I thought...
I mean, I thought
you didn't believe in marriage.
No, but I believe in you.
And, I believe that no matter
what life throws at us
our love can conquer it.
Married, unmarried, I love you.
And my greatest fear...
My greatest fear
in life is losing you.
- I...
- Yes.
Okay.
Yeah.
I do.
John, what do you say?
Are you kidding me, Oliver?
I'm the guy
for the past six years
who's been trying
to keep you two together.
It's only fitting that I marry you.
Okay.
Vows?
- No.
We can't do better than them.
Definitely not. We kind of
did those fake vows when we had
that fake wedding with that
psychopath serial killer archer lady.
I remember saying something
along the lines of...
You're the very best part of me.
Felicity, I'm a better human being
just because I've loved you.
Since we don't have any rings,
just yet,
I'll skip right to the part
where I say this.
Oliver Jonas Queen,
Felicity Megan Smoak,
Bartholomew Henry Allen...
Mmm-hmm.
...and Iris Ann West,
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
Please, kiss your brides.