[car sputtering]
All right, we gotta ditch Hoover's car.
APB's probably already out
on the Bullet Blondes.
That's fine. From here,
we'll just hop a train to New York.
Oh! Another train? Must we?
By my math, we should have
enough left for three tickets.
The other half can hang out
in John's portable phantom house.
I mean, it's technically
my portable phantom house.
But more importantly, does your math
account for Gary's
overly-generous tipping?
- He gave our last waitress 20 bucks.
- [Nate] No.
$20? That's over a quarter
of our entire budget, Gary.
$20 for a six-top seems fair to me.
Okay, so what's the damage?
Do we have enough to get to New York?
$35. That's enough for
one ticket and a few meals,
tipping like a normal person, in 1925.
All right, I call phantom house
'cause I am over trains.
But we still have to get across town
and on that train
without anyone recognizing us.
[Agent Sharpe hushing]
Well, then we stopped
at the right place.
[bell dings]
Oh...
I think yes.
Yes, it's very cute,
but we need to hide the blonde, babe.
- What about this?
- Yes.
Yes. It works.
No, no, no. We are in the 1920s.
That is not the look.
Okay, sir, can we see
all your wigs that are bobs?
Um... Hello? Potential customer here.
I asked you a question
which any good salesman
would take as an opportunity
to up-sell your finest wigs.
- Is he...
- Um... Hello?
Yeah. She asked you a question.
I'm sorry, miss.
I didn't realize she was with you.
These are the only bobs on display
since most of you ladies
chop and style your own.
Well, that's not happening.
Well, of course.
Not with those gorgeous locks.
Let me see what I can find in the back.
Racist dick.
I'm sorry. Let's just get these
disguises and get out of here, yeah?
Yeah. It's okay. Sorry.
[Nate] Uh... Is it just me or...
We probably should've ditched
Hoover's car before entering the city.
Yeah. Come on.
Hey, hey. Police found Hoover's car.
They're onto us.
We gotta get outta here.
I've got bobs in three different shades.
- Brunette, redhead...
- We'll take them both.
- Well, there's also blondes...
- [both] No blondes.
[Agent Sharpe] Okay,
how much for the two wigs?
Wait a minute.
- Are you two...
- Nope.
They're definitely not the...
Whatever you were gonna say.
[indistinct chatter]
- Guys, we gotta hustle.
- Okay. Here's what's gonna happen.
You're gonna help us
sneak out of here unnoticed
and we will buy these wigs
at double wholesale.
- Triple.
- That is robbery.
Look who's talking. Bullet Blondes.
They're crossing the street.
- You've gotta be...
- Aves.
Are you serious?
- Give him the money.
- [grunts in frustration]
[siren wailing]
[Agent Sharpe] Wig, wig, wig.
[Sara] Yeah, here you go.
- Put it on.
- Thank you.
Good. Good.
MAN: They're not very far.
Over here. Check the alleyways.
This is literally our only option.
Great. Then put the key in. We can
hang out here until the coast is clear.
- Hey.
You looking for the Sapphire String?
- Maybe.
- You got the password?
- Uh...
Swordfish.
- He meant salmon.
- Mackerel.
Are we doing this?
Are we really fishing
for a stupid password
so we can get out of this garbage alley?
Gang, we're screwed.
We have no money, no allies.
This time period sucks for anyone
who's not white, male and rich.
And only one of us, it's you,
is at least two of those things.
You said the password. Come on in.
- Wait. What was it?
- Password.
Ah! I see what he did there.
[Agent Sharpe]
The password is "password"?
[plays jazz music]
Welcome to my club. Name's Eddie.
Sorry it's a little quiet right now.
Running a little low on the drinks.
[Nate] We're at a speakeasy.
A very inclusive one, considering.
Considering what?
Well, the Mob had a tight grip on these
establishments and kept them segregated.
It looks like we've stumbled into one
that caters to everyone, which is rare.
I guess that's why
the password is "password."
- You play, brother?
- I noodle.
Come make us some pasta.
- What we got here? E flat?
- Yeah, brother.
- Classic.
- Yeah.
[train whistle blowing]
[groaning]
[grunts]
This is so degrading.
This is so exciting.
All right, we got through step one.
Sneak onto the train.
- Step two is the ride to Chicago.
- Steps? Who died and made you Ava?
We're going to New York
to prevent that from happening.
That reminds me. Don't talk
to anyone any more than we have to.
- We can't mess up the timeline.
- Okay, Captain Sharpe.
That's Spooner Cruz.
The most important thing
is to avoid any suspicion
for sneaking onto the train.
- [conductor] Tickets, please.
- Crap. Let's go.
Tickets? Hey. Hey.
I need to see your tickets.
Trying to sneak on my train
without a ticket?
What? No.
I just had it in my hands.
Maybe I dropped it while we were moving.
You're off at the next stop.
Stella, why are you bothering
this nice ticket man?
I apologize if these three
have given you any trouble.
These ladies are with you?
You're looking at the best pianist,
bassist, and clarinetist
you'll ever hear.
Just ask my boyfriend, Mr. Bottoni.
Of course, our train tickets
are all in our manager's pocket.
You're welcome to wake him
from his beauty rest.
But I have to warn you,
he has quite the temper.
[chuckles] You all enjoy your trip.
[exclaims excitedly]
I'm Maude and we're the Masqueradies.
Welcome to the band.
[theme music playing]
Any mention of an exploded Hoover?
According to this,
he's still alive and well
and ready to take on
the most notorious criminals,
Capone and the Bullet Blondes.
It's only a matter of time, babe.
He's after us.
So there's a new
and improved Hoover-Bot. Great.
- What else does the paper say?
- Oh! That we're bootleggers and robbers.
Worst of all, we're sisters.
- Sisters?
- Yeah.
We can't go on like this.
We can't rob another bank
because it'll cause too much attention.
- And we have no money.
- I know.
[Agent Sharpe whispering]
What are we gonna do?
Well, maybe it's time to give
our other enterprise a shot.
Wow!
- You make this yourself?
- Plenty more where that came from.
All we ask is access to your storage
room for the night and 25% of the bar.
- What do you want with my storage room?
- 20%. No questions.
- We got a deal.
- All right. Let's move some booze.
[man] The car was impounded an hour ago.
Your ears to the ground, boys.
Bullet Blondes are in Chicago
and are bound to make their move soon.
You really got us
out of a sticky situation back there.
It was plain as day
that you needed a hand.
Believe me, I've been there.
Gals help gals and make new pals.
That's how I see it.
If we don't look out
for one another, who will? Men?
Men don't look out.
They look at, if you know what I mean.
You're referring to the rampant
commodification of females by males
that is the societal norm
of this decade.
You talk funny.
I like it. My name's Suzie Spencer.
Suzanne Spencer.
Marries Colin Baker in 1928, has four
children, retires in Florida and dies...
That's enough talking, Gideon.
You're supposed to be resting
your voice, remember?
Oh.
Time to play the quiet game.
Oh, the game invented by parents to
quell their irritating children. Got it.
So, you're a jazz band
called the Masqueradies?
I know it's a silly moniker. We wear
fancy masks as part of our schtick.
Not that it made a lick of difference
on our East Coast tour.
We barely broke even.
You know how it is,
being musicians yourselves.
She's resting her voice?
Right. Yeah.
Gideon here is the lark of London.
Spoon... Esperanza is her vocal coach
and I am her manager.
A manager? Oh, my. They do things
differently in London, don't they?
Between us gals, I would kill
to have a woman managing our business.
[Suzie] Mmm-hmm.
Donny over there is
just an overpaid bodyguard really.
Is that so?
- Can I take a look at your contract?
- Sure. I have it right here.
[playing upbeat music]
Strange looking compact.
Oh, yeah. It's from California,
by way of China.
You know, business is
really picking up in here.
Yeah. It's 'cause the word got out
that we got the good stuff.
What can I get for you?
Whiskey on the rocks or straight up?
Oh. Neither. I don't drink.
- For health or faith?
- Faith.
Okay.
Soda water with lemon. On the house.
Thank you.
[toasting in foreign language]
Helps to know "cheers" in different
languages. I get all kinds in here.
Yeah.
- [Eddie] That your brother?
- [Zari] Yeah, it is.
I've actually never heard him
play like that before.
And you never will again.
Because what's going on
up there is a one-time special.
Oh, right.
Yeah. Those three guys
are feeling the vibe,
riffing off what the other guys
are bringing to the moment.
You can't recreate that.
Yeah, well, where I'm from, we have
a saying. Pics or it didn't happen.
A picture couldn't describe
the here and now. Here.
Now. It forces you to pay attention
or to just let it roll on
over you like a wave.
This is a catastrophe.
When did you sign this?
About three years ago,
when we first formed the band.
Okay, good. Hey, blubberbutt. Wake up.
You don't want to do this.
It says here that you're taking 60%,
criminal, mind you,
and yet you still don't have
these ladies
riding in first-class accommodation?
Are you lazy or stupid or both?
You're telling me how to do my job?
What's a colored girl like you
know anything about contracts?
Where I'm from, managers
and producers are a dime a dozen.
I learned from Phil Spector himself.
There's a clause here that says
these terms expire after 24 months.
This paperwork is defunct.
So I suggest that you
draw up a new contract
that will actually benefit your clients,
not exploit them.
You can't make me do anything.
True. I can't.
But she can.
- You're fired.
- What do you mean, fired?
You're out of a job, you low life.
So we'll be taking these.
[exclaims excitedly]
[speaks foreign language]
Would you look at that?
These for the first-class cabin.
Grab your gear, girls.
You just got upgraded.
[all cheering excitedly]
- [people chattering]
- [people cheering]
- [loud music playing]
- [indistinct]
[all applauding]
Where's my wife? I want to brag
to her about how I solved
all of our problems with some
good old-fashioned bootlegging.
She is taking a siesta in her mansion.
She said her wig was too itchy.
Probably synthetic.
[sighs]
I kind of wish we could stay longer.
Well, no can do, B.
Train for New York leaves at 8:00 a.m.
We gotta find this Gwyn Davies guy so he
can invent us some time travel and boom.
Here's the rest.
We got all we need. You keep it.
Thanks. Are you sure
you all can fit back there?
No questions.
Well, tonight was, um, eye opening.
You all are welcome back anytime.
And I know you mean that.
Good luck, Eddie.
[in sing-song voice] Eddie.
- Been a while.
- Evening, Mr. Bottoni.
When I rented you this place,
it was just a bunch of curtains
and a gramophone.
Now look at it.
Looks good. Almost classy.
Thank you.
Things sure do change.
For example, I told you you could
rent my little space for cheap
and I'd supply you with your liquor.
And what do I hear
but you got another source?
[clicks tongue]
[Eddie groaning]
Eddie? Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
Help. Help. We need help in here.
- Zari?
- He's hurt.
You're the Bullet Blondes?
Oh, no.
- Eddie, what happened to you?
- Yeah. Who did this to you?
You did.
- We can explain.
- I think I understand just fine.
You conned me. You put me
in the middle of a damn Mob war.
Now because of you,
I don't own this bar anymore.
- How's that work?
- My landlord, he's a mobster.
He found out I worked with you
and took the whole thing back.
Everything I had was in this bar and now
it's gone, 'cause of one night with you.
- Eddie...
- Just go.
The Mob will be here soon,
so you better not be.
You're just gonna
let him leave like that?
What are we supposed to do?
We can't take down
the entire Chicago Mob.
Our train leaves in a few hours.
A train we'd have no way
of affording if it weren't for his help.
He's the only one
who's opened his doors to us.
In fact, he's the only open-minded
person we've met on this entire trip.
- We have to fix this.
- Yeah, but how?
Money. Money. Money can fix anything.
If you hand me the reins for 24 hours,
I will help Eddie make enough money
to get back on his feet and then some.
It's just... We said small footprints
to the timeline.
Aves, we can't keep leaving
the timeline worse than we found it.
This place is one of the few safe spaces
that exists in this entire
crummy time period.
I'm not gonna be able to sleep knowing
we had a hand in destroying it. Are you?
- Let's do it.
- Thank you.
Zari's really wearing the pants
on this mission. I think I like it.
[shudders]
What could you possibly show me
that's gonna change anything?
Just patience, please.
[clears throat]
You know, it's locked. Can you
help me find a key? Maybe over there.
- A key? Just around?
- Mmm-hmm.
Mmm-hmm.
You know what? I found it.
[bell dings]
What is it with you people
and storage rooms?
It's a fair observation,
but just give it a chance, okay?
Okay, picture the main dance floor here.
A more exclusive lounge over here.
No smoking, of course,
but darker, sexier.
- And a bar over there.
- Whoa! Give me a second here.
Eddie, can I be real with you?
I know a thing or two
about throwing an excellent soirée,
and I'm going to throw you
the biggest fundraiser of the season.
Buddy, you are going to get
a Zari party. [clicks tongue]
[train whistling]
[conductor] All aboard.
- [man] Ms. Beaumont? Telegram for you.
- Thank you.
Hurry up, ladies.
My honey's got a new club and he wants
us to perform tonight. Ain't it great?
- You okay, hon?
- Yeah. Just feeling a bit queasy.
You know what'll help? A big plate
of eggs, bacon and hotcakes.
There'll be breakfast
at the new club, I'm sure.
We should probably be
on our way to New York.
Well, shucks. The train to the Big Apple
leaves once a day at 8:00 a.m.
- It's half past already.
- Damn it.
Don't fret. You can just come with me.
- No, we don't impose.
- That sounds perfect.
Well, there's nothing else to do other
than wait around at the station, right?
Well, aces. Follow me.
[groans]
My stomach telling me
something's off with these guys.
Your stomach is telling you
to get some free food.
Okay, Zari, things are coming
right along. That is good.
[sighs] I need better than good.
I need epic. I need a gimmick. A hook.
I need a show.
B, Eddie.
Okay? I need you guys to get out there
and spread the word.
I have the one thing
that's going to set this party off.
For one night, and one night only,
the Bullet Blondes are going to put on
the greatest show
this town has ever seen.
Wait. We're gonna do what?
So you're saying we can get
the word out with just one guy?
More than sure.
If you want a secret kept,
you make sure Ricky's the last to know.
Eddie, heard about the club.
You doing all right?
Peaches, Ricky.
Say, can you keep a secret?
[indistinct]
The Bullet Blondes.
Really. The password is...
- Rutabaga.
- [man 1] Rutabaga.
- [woman 1] Rutabaga.
- [man 2] Rutabaga.
- [man 3] Rutabaga.
- [woman 2] Rutabaga.
Ain't this Eddie's place?
Rehearsal in five, ladies.
Now let's see about
getting you some breakfast.
Maude.
Hi, baby cakes. We're home.
Nice new spot you got here.
Can't wait to get a wiggle on.
What's this I hear about
you firing Donny?
Donny was not a very good manager, baby.
See here.
Miss Astra here helped me draw up
new terms for a proper manager.
Give me that.
Garbage. This is what happens
when you do things without me.
I knew that whole tour was a bad idea.
Your manager is whoever I say it is.
Understood?
Yes, I understand.
New band member? Put her up front.
Give the audience something to look at.
Tonight is a big night, baby.
Mr. Williams from RCA will be here,
so get those getaway sticks to rehearsal
so you can sing open his checkbook
and get us a record deal.
Maude, wait.
- Hey. What was that?
- What do you mean, hon?
In front of your boyfriend?
You just disappeared.
I know he can be
a little rough sometimes,
but he's just got his preferences.
- You know how it is.
- No. Tell me.
He found me when I was
nothing but a string bean
with a undisciplined set of pipes.
I'm thankful. I really am.
You heard. Even RCA is coming
to see little old me.
When he says, "Sing," I ask "What song?"
But what happens when
you don't feel like singing?
You just don't get it.
Ross loves me. And I owe him everything.
Ross.
Ross Bottoni.
[singing]
Lately I've been wrung around
Tossed and turned about
Could this be the end?
Maude's boyfriend, I know him.
Ross Bottoni. I met him in Hell.
He talked about my "getaway sticks"
so I covered him in his worst fear,
1,000 tiny spiders.
That man is a monster.
We have to help her.
Astra, if we try to rescue every woman
in a bad relationship
from here to New York,
we'll never get a mile out of Chicago.
Maude chose this.
This is her life. She said so.
Nobody chooses this.
They find themselves in too deep
and they have to grab on to whatever
they can to keep from drowning.
That is not a choice.
That is survival, Spooner.
- You know, maybe she'll be okay.
- Gideon, what happens to Maude?
Is this a test?
I'm meant to be playing the quiet game.
Forget the quiet game. Will she be okay?
The body of Maude Beaumont will be found
floating in the Chicago River
December 18th, 1925.
Her death is ruled as a homicide,
but no charges are formally brought.
Are you pretending
[Spooner] Astra...
I don't care
if this is how it's supposed to happen.
I'm gonna save Maude and
there is nothing you can do to stop me.
Gary, I need you to make sure
the silks are secure.
We can't have it falling down
during the big show.
- Yeah?
- Absolutely, Zari.
And can I just say I think
you're doing a fantastic job
leading us on this mission?
I know.
- It's pathological with you, isn't it?
- What are you talking about?
- You have a crush on Zari.
- What? No.
Gary, you know what's happening here.
It's not a real crush.
Zari's triggering your attraction
to powerful people.
Think about it. Kayla, Ava, John...
[shushes] She might hear you.
You get off being bossed around,
you little sicko.
You're just figuring this out now?
Gary, don't you want to be with someone
who respects you for the alien you are?
No, not really.
[exhales] Worried about you, Gare.
I'm worried about you too, but I don't
go around shaming your pathology, do I?
My pathology? What pathology?
Well, that you find yourself in these
relationships that can't go anywhere,
so you don't have to put yourself
in the vulnerable position
of really giving yourself
to another person
because you have the excuse of timelines
or Totems holding you back.
What?
Okay, gang. The Blondes
have been rehearsing like crazy.
The mood is set and the whiskey
is literally all you can drink.
Are we ready to party?
I'm ready to party all night long,
because I'm in a relationship.
You do need to define
what that means, though.
Define whatever you need to define,
but I need you to do it as doormen
with good vibes.
- Yes, ma'am.
Hey, remember. Good vibes.
- No. Great vibes.
- Yeah. Great vibes.
[electric crackling]
I can fix that. I think.
[Sara] Hey, Zari,
do we have to do this in heels?
Yes.
Is everything good?
Eddie, everything is perfect.
It's a Zari party.
[instrumental music playing]
Hi. Ross Bottoni.
You're here to hear my gal, Maude.
She's got the best pipes
in the business.
Come this way.
We got a table for you in the front.
- Maude, you have to leave.
- Leave it be, will you?
I can't believe I'm the first broad
you ever met with a grumpy guy.
Besides, I'm not gonna hit the road
right before the greatest show
of my life.
If you stay, he will kill you.
Save the drama for the stage, honey.
It ain't gonna work on me.
Look, you know it's true.
You feel it in your gut
every time you think of him.
It twists your insides
every time he speaks.
You want to vomit
every time he touches you.
You're terrified, and you should be.
[Astra] There's a better life for you
out there, Maude. Trust me. I know.
This is crazy.
What about the performance?
He's gonna know the second
the curtain rises that something's up.
And the girls,
he's gonna take it out on them.
Maude, we'll take care of Ross.
Just go. Please, before it's too late.
Oh! Thank you.
You know, I always said gals
help gals and make new pals.
You gals are
some of the best I ever met.
[sighs]
[door closes]
- Thank you.
- For what? She knew you were right.
And I guess I knew you were right, too.
[announcer speaking]
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I announce to you
the lovely and mysterious Masqueradies?
[music starts playing]
Okay. Maybe I can put a glamor on you
and then you can look like Maude,
which means you can sing. And then...
I don't know the words
to this corny song.
Why can't you do it?
Wait.
[both] Where's Gideon?
[music continues]
[singing]
Lately I've been wrung around
Tossed and turned about
Could this be the end?
Sounds like she knows the words.
To my genuine surprise
I've met the gaze of those blue eyes
Doll face, are you pretend?
She's my future favorite
My love
No denying it
So very dizzy for this dame
Take me down the boulevard
Then around this crazy world of ours
Please don't say it's all a game
[upbeat music playing]
Zari, what's with the face?
Look around. Everyone's here.
I just... I know I'm missing something.
[sighs] What am I forgetting?
Me. Me. I'm forgetting me.
I should have been in hair and makeup.
I haven't even done an outfit change.
Who cares?
Look what's happening tonight
is a one-time special.
Be in the moment. Here. Now.
Let's dance before
some blondes steal the show.
[chuckles] Okay.
Rutabaga.
[announcer speaking]
Ladies and gentlemen,
the silver shooting sinners themselves,
the Bullet Blondes.
[upbeat music playing]
[bell dings]
- Rutabaga.
- Mmm-hmm.
Last time you saw Zari,
how did you end things?
We're still together.
We didn't break up.
How's that working out?
What is the plan?
Oh, my God. We love each other, Gary.
- You're not answering my question.
- [bell dings]
It's not the... Not now, Gary.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
[grunting]
[all cheering]
You can't put it off forever, Nate.
You need to discuss
what it means to be all in.
Otherwise you'll always
have one foot out the door.
- Or Totem.
- Shut up, Gary.
[gunshot]
[singing] We've been forced to hide away
our hearts until a better day
Now we are breaking down the door
Stand clear
Bear-cats coming through
My dear, I'm so in love with you
Hotsy totsy dancer on the floor
She's my future favorite
My love
No denying it
So very dizzy for this dame
Take me down the boulevard
Then around this crazy world of ours
Please don't say it's all a game
[both whooping]
Wait. Where's Hoover?
Time flies, so savor it
Let's toast and raise ourselves a glass
Cheers to all the memories
Facing danger, solving mysteries
In the present, future and the past
Sweetheart, our love is made to
Sweetheart, our love is made to last
[crowd gasps]
- [whooping]
- [glass breaks]
We're not sisters.
[all cheering]
Yo, that was incredible, Gideon.
Way to put those pipes to use.
My voice was well rested.
Way to croon, sweet cakes.
Come out front
so the nice man can meet you.
What's the big idea?
Where the hell is Maude?
Far away from here by now.
Who the hell are you
and what happened to my girl?
I'm Astra Logue, you idiot.
And Maude is gone.
You'll never see her again.
You think you're clever, huh?
She'll come crawling back.
You know, where I grew up,
we had this knack of finding out
what people were most afraid of
in the entire world.
And you think
you're so tough and strong,
but I know the truth.
What you're really afraid of...
Spiders, wasn't it?
Yeah, right.
Really?
You're not afraid
of an infinite amount
of tiny little spiders
all over your body?
Crawling under your skin, scurrying into
your nose, ears, your mouth...
You've seen what
my friend and I can do, Ross.
So if you ever go after Maude,
if you even think about her...
Spiders everywhere.
Forever.
- Gals help gals, you jerk.
- [whimpers] No.
Hey, ladies, we're gonna try to make it
to the end of the Blondes' set.
- Do you want to come?
- What are you talking about?
Didn't you hear?
The Bullet Blondes are putting on
a performance right now at Chapeaux's.
We're gonna try to catch
the rest of the party.
Legends. Vámonos.
You're right about me and Zari.
We are a bit stuck.
But I've been okay with it,
because I'm afraid of what comes next.
Well, it sounds like you and Z
need to have the talk.
And the Gare Bear,
he's here to talk after the talk.
Thank you, Gary.
It's enough for a small place,
but that's all I need.
And I don't know
how I'll ever repay you.
You just keep your doors open
for all of Chicago's misfits
and we will call it even.
No, no, no.
[both chuckle]
[panting]
- Guys?
- Check the doors.
They were here.
[sighs]
[train whistle honking]
[whispers] Don't worry, Legends.
We're on our way to the Big Apple.
So, I mean, technically speaking, using
you two as bait to lure Hoover-Bot here
was an inadvertently
brilliant stroke of genius on my part.
Well, you still got a couple hours left
of calling the shots, so...
I do appreciate the trust, Captain,
but when it comes to robots,
you're talking to the wrong Zari.
Oh, um...
While I'm gone, will you guys keep
an eye out for my cell phone?
It's MIA. Bye.
Oh... What's up, guys?
Huh... What did I miss?
[theme music playing]