- In 2166, an immortal tyrant
Named vandal savage
conquered the world
And murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
And stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately,
my plan is opposed by the body
I'd sworn my allegiance to,
the time masters.
In the future, my friends
may not be heroes,
But if we succeed, they
will be remembered as legends.
[exciting music]
- Previously on
"legends of tomorrow"...
- Boys, ship's all yours.
- Mick!
[gun blasts, thud]
- What are you gonna do,
snart?
- My husband and I get along
just fine on our own.
- We're still waiting
on sara
And the two lovebirds
to get back.
Seems they've taken
quite a shine to 1958.
[grunting,
swords clashing]
- Sara swore her allegiance
to the league of assassins.
It's time for her
to return home.
- My friend thea calls it
a bloodlust.
- Argh!
[both grunting, crashing]
- Sara, stop!
- I'm a monster.
[gun blasting]
- not this guy again.
- Captain, chronos has breached
the starboard hatch.
- How is that possible?
- Clearly received some new toys
from his time master friend
Since our last encounter.
- 1958's swell and all,
But I miss the internet...
And cell phones.
- Gideon! Seal the bulkheads
from here--
[guns blasting]
- Grey, come on!
Let's do this!
- If we merge
on the waverider,
It could destroy
the entire ship!
- Um, are you not
paying attention
To what chronos is doing?
- Fall back!
Get to the jumpship!
[tense music]
- Hey, come on!
- You sure it was a good idea
Leaving the terminator
on the bridge?
- Gideon has
lockdown protocols which--
- Have been overridden,
captain.
Chronos is utilizing superior
time master technology.
I cannot countermand
his orders.
- Uh...
What are they doing?
Hey!
- Hey!
♪
Where did they go?
- Better question:
Why did they leave us?
[suspenseful music]
- He's timejumping the ship.
- The ladies will
be left in 1958.
- What about ray?
- Like I said.
- Let's go!
We have to stop him!
[both panting]
- Argh!
Oh!
Gideon, open the doors
on my mark.
Get to the jumpship
and escape.
- We are not
abandoning you.
- No, you are obeying a direct
order from your captain.
♪
Now, gideon.
[yells]
[guns blasting]
♪
- I don't know if the jumpship
will even fly
From the temporal zone.
[indistinct yelling,
gunfire]
- It doesn't matter.
We're not leaving our team.
- What happened to:
"we could destroy
the whole ship"?
- A preferable alternative
to losing our friends.
Don't you agree?
- Yeah.
[explosion]
- We could've just opened
the door, jefferson.
- Sorry, I got a little
carried...
Away.
♪
- Oh, hey, hey, hey.
- Oh, god.
Where's chronos?
- He absconded with mr. Snart
on the jumpship.
I'm sorry, captain.
- Why would chronos
take snart?
- Gideon, can you
track them?
- We have a more
pressing matter.
- Strap yourselves in.
[dramatic music]
- What's going on?
- Chronos has sabotaged
the navigation system.
Unless we can find a way
to alter the course,
We'll be trapped
in the temporal zone
For all time.
- Gideon--
- I cannot override
chronos' commands.
[machinery powering down]
- What did you do?
- Rebooted gideon.
Until she's fully operational,
We're free-falling through time.
♪
[all groaning]
[groaning, yelling]
♪
- We just have to stay calm.
Wherever they timejumped--
whenever--
They'll come back
to this exact same moment.
[mysterious music]
♪
- They're not coming back.
Let's go.
- Look, as a former
eagle scout
With over 100 merit badges--
No big deal--
The first rule of getting lost
is stay the same place.
That way, you can be found.
- And as a former member
of the league of assassins,
The first rule when
you've been attacked
Is to keep moving.
- I sort of think league wisdom
trumps the eagle scouts here.
Plus, savage is still out there.
- Guys, the rest of the team
Would not leave us
marooned in 1958.
- Except for,
that's exactly what they did.
You said it yourself--
you have a time machine,
And you're never late.
They're not coming back.
[solemn music]
♪
One good thing about 1958:
No car alarms.
- I didn't think they had cars
in nanda parbat.
- Dated a lot of delinquents
as a teenager.
[engine turns over]
- And now we're
the delinquents.
If we leave harmony falls,
How's the rest of the team
gonna find us?
- We don't know
if they're looking for us.
But we know savage is.
We can't take him.
That means we can't stay here.
- Let's go.
♪
[classic rock and roll music]
- Oh, what did you do
to our apartment?
- I'm creating a time beacon--
A transponder which matches
The waverider's
quantum signature,
Basically creating
a radio wave firewall
That only our team can see.
- It's cute that
you think either of us
Understood a word of that.
But I hope it works.
- In the meantime,
Maybe we should invest
in some real beds.
- ♪ how you make me scream
because ♪
♪ you are no longer my queen
♪
- Congratulations.
You are a doctor.
- You know, I thought about
going to medical school once.
- Here you go.
$10,000 salary.
- That's it?
I made more as a barista.
- Well, it's 1958.
You're lucky to make that
as a woman.
- Touché.
Your turn.
- [sighs]
I miss netflix.
[beeping]
- aha!
The time beacon radio
is officially complete.
- Well, great.
- Okay, here we go.
Come on.
Here we go.
Hope there's a spot
on that game
That says
"return to the waverider,"
Because that's what's
about to happen.
Here we go.
[whirring]
[electricity crackling]
I just have to fix
a few of the kinks.
The next version will be
much less explosive.
- Next version?
I thought you said you were
gonna say something to him.
- Say what?
- That your beacon--
it's a waste of time.
They're not coming back, ray.
And it's not because
the waverider is broken,
Or they're lost,
or they can't find us,
Or whatever.
It's because they're dead.
And the sooner that
you accept that,
The sooner you can move on--
The sooner we can all move on.
- So what?
We're just supposed to give up?
- On being rescued, yeah.
- Sara, what are you doing?
- I can't stay here.
I need to find
somewhere I belong.
- Sara, wait.
You can't go.
- Savage is still out there.
Don't draw undue attention
on yourselves.
- Sara.
- Look, you two
have each other.
Most people,
In any time period,
Aren't that lucky.
Take care.
- [scoffs]
Which gives us
mesoscopic polymer
And biomolecular simulations.
Yes, mr. Gates?
- If that's true,
And you can soften matter,
Then doesn't that mean
You could theoretically
miniaturize an atom?
- In theory, yes.
But trust me,
You don't want
to try it at home.
And definitely not for at least
another, mm, 40 years.
Uh, aren't you supposed
to be at home?
I thought you said
your son was sick.
- Yes, william.
My in-laws are at my house,
So if you don't mind,
I'd rather be in here.
[laughter]
- Your son is bill gates?
- Bill?
That has a nice ring to it.
- Midterms are next week.
Go ahead and pick up
an exam book on your way out.
Class dismissed.
♪
Happy second anniversary.
- Happy anniversary.
I thought we said no gifts.
- I know.
Just open it.
- Your time beacon?
- I thought we could
destroy it together.
- You don't have to do that.
- I want to.
You know, I never thought
that I could build a life
With anybody but anna.
But, um, that's exactly
what we've done,
In the most unlikely time
and place imaginable.
And I know it may
sound strange,
But I'm...
Glad that we were
stranded here.
- Me too.
- I have one more
surprise for you.
- Ray.
[time beacon beeping]
The beacon.
It's picking up a signal!
[exciting music]
♪
- Shiby-washo,
sara-so-so.
- You are suffering
from linguistic disorientation.
It's a side effect
of such a severe time jump.
- I can't hear anything.
- It'll pass.
- What?
- Gideon, status update?
- I am detecting a time beacon
signaling the waverider.
But then again, this is 1960.
- 1960?
- The temporal
navigation system
Was compromised
and did its best
To return us as close
as possible to 1958.
- Salypso changa.
[time beacon beeping]
♪
- Sorry we're late.
[ship powering up]
[dramatic music]
♪
- Two years.
You left us stranded in 1958.
- That was never
my intention.
- [sighs]
can't we rev the ship back up,
Go back to 1958,
and pick that us up?
- You know very well
that we can't.
- Travel back to events
we participated in
Without time folding
in on itself.
- Raymond.
- Good to see you.
Glad you're back.
- Martin.
[chuckles]
- It's just--
I have 50 midterms
to grade next week--
By hand--
And I've just come to terms
With living in
the technological dark ages.
I have students
who count on me.
Kendra and I have friends
and a life...
- Ray.
- [sighs]
- This is what we've
been waiting for.
Remember the mission.
We can finally
be ourselves again.
Look, I'm sorry.
This is all...
Very intense.
It's been two years
for us.
We thought you guys
were dead.
- That very well
might have been the case.
- Chronos attacked us.
He sabotaged the ship
and took snart.
- We need to recover
ms. Lance as well.
Where is she?
- Uh, no idea.
People go their separate ways,
lose track of each other.
- Gideon, search the timeline
For any reference
of a sara lance,
Or a blonde vigilante,
circa 1960.
- Right away, captain.
- Why did chronos take snart?
Couldn't he have
taken you all in?
- You sound dubious.
- If chronos was gonna settle
for taking one person,
You'd think it would be you.
He took snart for a reason.
[ominous music]
♪
- Uh, hello?
- A ufo sighting
in hub city in 1960
Has created a time anomaly.
It looks like
your friends survived.
- And what would they
be doing in 1960?
- That is out of the question,
mr. Palmer.
- What are we talking about?
- You changed.
- Yeah, I couldn't wait
to get back in jeans.
So what's going on?
- I have to go back
to our apartment.
- Why?
- Because when we were
unexpectedly picked up
By a time ship, I was not
carrying the atom suit.
And not for nothing,
but we spent
The last two years together
in that apartment.
Is there anything you want me
to pick up for you?
Your favorite coffee mug?
Our lucky water vase?
- Lucky water vase?
- Yeah, it's a long
but endearing story.
Nothing?
Don't you care about anything
that we left behind?
- Yes, but I don't
think that I need
To go back to the apartment
to get any of our old junk.
- Old junk?
We lived there this morning.
- We certainly can't leave
raymond's exo-suit back in 1960.
I'll accompany you back
to your apartment.
We'll recover the future tech
And any lucky ceramics.
- Ray--
- I'll get those
blouses you like.
- Well, I hope that sara takes
to being back on the team
Better than ray seems
to be taking it.
- Depends, I suppose,
on where exactly she ended up.
[tense percussive music]
[swords clashing]
- [speaking arabic]
Ta-er al-sahfer.
I can see that the herbs
and meditation are working.
Your thirst to kill
no longer clouds your judgment.
Proceed.
Stand up.
I've enjoyed
watching you train.
I have never seen a pupil
advance so quickly.
- I've had time
to learn who I am,
And what it is
I'm meant to do.
- We will watch this one
closely, talia.
There is much you can
learn from her.
♪
- So, uh...
What's so special
about me?
I mean, aside from
my sparkling personality.
Back on the waverider,
You could've taken
your boy, rip.
But you took me instead.
Why?
Hey, if you're gonna
kill me,
You could at least tell me
what's going on.
- You should have
figured it out by now.
[ominous music]
♪
After all,
I am supposed to be
the dumb one.
- How?
I think I deserve
to know
What the hell
is going on here!
- You deserve nothing.
- Says the man who sold us out
to the pirates.
When I dropped you off
in that forest,
I meant to kill you.
That was the plan.
- You should've stuck
with the plan
And done me a favor.
- I wish there were
some other way, mick.
- You haven't got the guts.
You want to kill me,
kill me.
Only one of us is walking
out of here alive.
- You're right.
[gun blasting]
- I knew you lacked the guts.
[blows land]
- I am sorry, mick.
I may not have trusted you
on the ship with the team,
But I always, always
was coming back for you.
- Seems like one of us
lost track of time.
- Well, how long did you--
- By the time they found me,
I'd nearly lost my mind.
I was so weak,
I was strangling rats
to survive.
- When who found you?
- The time masters.
They took me to a place
called the vanishing point.
Time doesn't exist there
the way it does on earth.
I've spent lifetimes
being restored by them,
Training by them,
fighting by them...
Being reborn.
- And, uh, when exactly
did your new friends
Give you the, uh, lobotomy?
- You think I was hunting
you and your friends
Because the time masters
made me?
They barely had to ask.
- Hey, uh, can we
talk for a sec?
- Just--with everything
that's going on,
I don't know that
this is the best time.
- You say that like there's
gonna be a better time.
- Okay.
- Look, we spent every night
the last two years together,
Playing board games,
eating,
Deciding who was
gonna cook
And who was going
to wash dishes,
Falling asleep to
"the ed sullivan show."
But the second you
saw the waverider,
It was like those two years
never happened.
- Look, we were both
trying to adapt
To an impossible situation.
But you are not
a college professor,
And I'm definitely
not a librarian.
So honestly,
I'm just excited
To be able to be myself again.
I mean, aren't you even
a little bit happy
To be back on the ship?
- I was happy with the life
we built together,
What I thought would
be our future.
And this just all feels like
moving backwards.
- Moving backwards.
What if sara didn't move
forwards with her life--
She moved backwards?
- She said she wanted to go
to a place where she belonged.
What's the one place in 1958
she already called home?
- The league of assassins.
- There is one source
that we could check
To test your theory.
Gideon, bring up
the shadow record.
- Shadow record?
- The list of every member
of the league of assassins
Since the invention
of writing in 3200 b.C.
- Fascinating,
except these sheets of papyrus
Are entirely blank.
- No, no, no.
The league uses invisible ink.
I did my graduate thesis
at the academy on their history.
Gideon.
- Sara said that ra's al ghul
Had lived nearly a century
before she met him.
- Thanks to the lazarus pit.
It's basically
a life-extending jacuzzi,
Located in a place that's
the opposite of life-extending.
- You should count
yourself lucky, dr. Palmer.
Only a handful of outsiders
Have been inside
the league's fortress
And lived to tell the tale.
- You are correct, captain.
There is a mention
of a ta-er al-sahfer.
- That's sara's
league of assassins name.
According to the shadow record,
she joined the league in 1958.
- Incredible--
sara became a member
Of the secret organization
That trained her
to be an assassin
50 years prior
to when she initially joined.
- Sara needs our help.
By all accounts, ra's al ghul
Is a very controlling,
very homicidal fanatic.
Gideon, chart a course
for nanda parbat.
[exciting music]
♪
- Look, if you're gonna kill me,
just do it already.
- I'm not gonna kill you.
I'm gonna to take a trip
back to central city
And visit your baby sister.
The beautiful thing
about time travel
Is I get to kill her
more than once.
I can kill lisa
in front of you,
Go back in time,
Kill her
in front of you again
And again
and again.
- Sir, several anomalies
in the timeline
Suggest that the waverider has
touched down in nanda parbat.
- Chart a course.
I used to think the most
beautiful thing
On earth was fire.
Now I know
It's vengeance.
[ominous music]
♪
- Perhaps jefferson
and I should--
- Extricating sara
from the likes
Of the league
requires stealth.
So no firestorm
for the two of you.
And you're out of practice,
So no atom suit
unless absolutely necessary.
- Look out!
- [yelling]
[blows landing]
- Thanks.
- Well done, jefferson.
- You guard the exit
while I find sara.
We will be in
and out of here faster
Than you can say
"ra's al ghul."
Shh.
[foreboding music]
♪
Sara.
It's me.
- Rip?
- I'm here
to bring you back.
I'm so sorry
that it's taken me so long.
- Who else is here?
- The entire team.
Well, except for mr. Snart.
I'll explain everything
back on the--
[grunts]
[exciting music]
- [speaking arabic]
[ominous music]
♪
- Something's wrong.
They should have
been back by now.
- Well, I think this counts
as absolutely necessary.
I've got my exo-suit
shrunk down,
And I can miniaturize
and do some tiny sneaking.
- It's been two years
since you've used that suit.
And that's after
you scavenged it
For parts
for your time beacon.
You don't even know
if it works.
- Is now really the time
for your little marital spat?
- We're not married.
- Can we just
keep it down, please?
[dramatic music]
♪
- Sara?
- Found her.
- [speaking arabic]
- Oh--hey.
Hey.
- [speaking arabic]
- Sara, what the hell?
- You shouldn't
have come here.
- Yeah, I'm starting
to get that.
- We came here
to rescue you.
- I don't need to be rescued.
I've found peace here.
- Peace with
the league of assassins?
That must be the first time that
sentence has ever been uttered.
- Oh, I can't believe
I'm back here.
- If this is retribution
of some kind
For stranding you in 1958--
- It is the will
of ra's al ghul.
Trespassers
are to be executed.
- We just need a little
more time to get through to her.
- Do time masters
have a different understanding
Of the word "executed"?
- No, no, no.
It's called "time drift."
When one spends too long
in an alien timeline,
One loses ties
with one's former self,
Former identity.
- Oh, my god.
- What?
- I didn't
understand it before,
But my powers--
they went dormant.
- What are you talking about?
- My wings.
You must have noticed
that I haven't been able
To "hawk out"
in almost two years.
- I just thought
that you didn't want to.
Why didn't you tell me?
- Because it was so hard
For you to give up hope
that the team would return.
When you finally did,
you started to be happy again,
And I couldn't bear telling you
that I wasn't.
- That ain't good.
- I had no idea.
- Look, ray,
I loved being with you.
I wasn't just
losing my powers.
I was losing my memories
of my past lives.
I was starting to lose myself.
- I'm sorry.
I--
But, look,
you didn't have to protect me.
I could have handled
the truth.
- It couldn't have been so easy
for raymond, either,
Having to give up
being the atom.
- I'm sorry, can we
have a private moment?
- I think we all wish
you would've had
This moment in private.
[chains clinking]
- Don't you think
that we were meant
For something greater
than being stuck in 1960,
Eating fondue
with the neighbors?
- Yeah, we were meant to be
tortured and executed in
Nanda "I can't believe
I'm back here" parbat.
- If we die,
At least it would be
in pursuit of a greater purpose.
- That's it.
- What's it?
- Ra's al ghul's purpose in life
is to see that the league
Continues with all of its
ancient traditions intact--
- Including
murdering intruders?
- I will appeal
to ra's al ghul's respect
For the league's traditions,
Invoking one of them
right now.
- Well, what kind
of traditions, man?
- Guards!
Guards!
- [sighs]
- Would you mind loosening
these up a little bit
Before you leave?
Just out of curiosity,
What do you think your new
masters are gonna do with you
Once you've delivered
the team up to them?
I don't expect
there's a pension plan
For old bounty hunters.
Once they get what
they want from you,
They're gonna toss you aside.
- Like you tossed me aside?
- You and I both made choices
that led us to this moment.
What matters, mick,
is your next move.
And I'm willing to bet
That some little piece
of the old you
Is in that armor somewhere.
- No.
You're wrong.
- Mr. Hunter.
- Captain,
as point of fact.
- Right.
Well, I do hope your request
for an audience
Is not an attempt to justify
your trespass here.
- Most certainly not.
But it would be remiss of me
if I didn't use this opportunity
To reiterate that sara
Is very important to me--
To all of us.
- And as she is to me.
And as you can all see,
she has chosen to remain here.
- Yes, well,
if that is her wish,
We will indeed honor it.
- Well, thank you.
But your deaths will make
that concession irrelevant.
- Well, according to my
understanding of league law,
The whole death thing
can be avoided,
Should we prevail at trial.
- Yeah, I don't think these guys
are the "people's court" type.
- I demand a trial by combat.
- And how is a man such as you
so well-versed
On our traditions?
- Do we have an accord?
- May victory be yours.
- I was under the impression
that I would be fighting you.
- Then it would seem your
understanding of our laws
Requires some refinement.
You see,
I may choose
any champion I wish,
As may you.
[suspenseful music]
♪
- I'll do it.
- You haven't had very much
experience in swordsmanship,
Mr. Palmer.
I nominate ms. Saunders.
- What? No.
Didn't you hear?
She can't even hawk--
- I accept.
- Kendra, you can't--
- I've got this.
[tense music]
♪
[chain clinking]
[metal clattering]
♪
[metal clangs]
- You have to put a stop
to this.
- Sara taught kendra to
control her warrior side.
I believe that kendra can
remind sara of her humanity.
- Before or after
sara kills her?
- Sara.
Ta-er al-sahfer.
Whatever your name is now.
I know you don't
want to kill me.
[swords clanging]
[both grunting]
- Argh!
- Want is irrelevant.
I serve ra's al ghul.
[tense music]
♪
- [screaming]
[swords clanging,
both grunting]
♪
- Remember that move?
You taught it to me.
- Your teacher was excellent.
[intense music]
♪
- Sara, no!
- Argh!
♪
- [yelps,
groans]
Sara.
You're not a murderer
or an assassin.
- [speaking arabic]
- No!
- You're the white canary.
[intense music swells]
♪
- [exhales]
- [panting]
[booming]
I know that sound.
[gun blasting]
- Chronos.
[tense music]
[gun blasting]
- [speaking arabic]
[exciting music]
♪
- You can't face him;
you can't defeat him.
- [speaking arabic]
♪
[men grunting, blows landing]
[gun blasts]
[swords clashing,
grunting]
♪
[bullets pinging]
[guns blasting]
You brought him here.
It's only right you kill him.
♪
[fire rushing]
- It's a long story, pal.
♪
- Ray!
[ice shatters]
- [screaming]
[guns blasting]
[blows landing, grunting]
[swords clanging]
[dramatic music]
♪
[heavy blows landing]
- You son of a bitch.
- Don't do it.
Don't kill him.
- Snart?
- Sorry, don't kill chronos?
- He's not chronos.
Show them.
♪
- My god.
- There is no god.
[grunting]
- I imagine you have
some questions
About what you witnessed.
- When the lady you call
sara lance first arrived here,
Her skills were unmatched.
It was as if she had completed
the training before.
I suppose that's because
you're both from the future.
- When I came
to your doorstep,
For the second time
in my life,
I thought that I could
find a home here,
That this is where
I really belong.
- But your soul is divided
By your ability to kill
And your desire to show mercy.
And there is no place
for one so conflicted
Within the league.
Ta-er al-sahfer,
I release you.
You can reclaim
your previous name
And your past life.
- Thank you.
[solemn music]
♪
In October 2008,
Please see that your daughter
is off the coast
Of an island in
the north china sea--
Lian yu.
- Why would I send talia
on such a journey?
- Not talia.
Your daughter
yet to be born.
I'm pretty sure
you'll call her nyssa.
♪
- You think this is all over?
I will kill every single
one of you.
I will watch you all burn!
You--
You should have killed me
when you had the--
[panel beeps]
- You owe us
an explanation.
- Yes, it's quite remarkable
Mr. Rory is working
For the time masters,
considering you killed him.
- If you think back, I never
actually said I killed him.
- No, you just let us think
that you did.
- I didn't have to try
too hard, did I?
Well, maybe I should have.
And at least he wouldn't have
would up a chew toy
For the time masters.
- But if you did, we wouldn't
have this opportunity.
- An opportunity?
To do what?
- To reform mr. Rory.
- He killed aldus.
- Under the influence
of the time masters.
- Chronos killed aldus.
Mr. Rory was fighting
on our side that day.
- I know what it's like to be
trained by an organization
For one purpose, to kill,
And the kind of loyalty
that it can inspire.
I need to know that
we can reach rory.
For my own sake.
- The time masters
took one of our own
And turned him against us.
I say we undo their handiwork.
- Rory saved my life
back in the gulag.
He's more than just a criminal
and an arsonist.
- He's a member of our team.
- He's a lost cause.
- Oh, I wouldn't be
so sure about that.
You will see that miracles
abound on this old timeship.
Gideon, start
the regeneration process.
- What you mean regeneration?
- I took genetic samples
from each of you
At the start of our voyage
for this exact eventuality.
- Why am I only hearing
about this now?
- Because none of you
had lost a limb yet.
[exciting music]
- Ow.
♪
- [laughs]
[door opening]
- So were you gonna tell me?
- Sorry, tell you what?
- That you were moving
into your room without me?
- Oh, um,
I just assumed that
you wanted some space.
You made it pretty clear that
you were over our old life.
- Look...
Just because I wasn't satisfied
with the circumstances
Doesn't mean I didn't
fall in love with you.
[tender music]
♪
- It's just, I--
I don't want to lose you.
- And I don't want to lose you.
For the first time
In probably centuries,
I actually got to decide
who I want to fall in love with,
Instead of having it decided
for me.
So it doesn't matter where
Or when we are.
You're the person
I want to be with.
- Wow.
That was--
was that, like, rehearsed?
Because that was really good.
- So...
What do you want?
♪
[both giggling]
- I believe we're ready
to leave 1960.
- And go where?
I mean, when?
- 2147.
Mere decades before vandal
savage conquered the world.
- I thought you had no idea
where he was.
- You said savage
had been lost to history.
- Not world-changing history.
Records of the period
are scarce,
But I've always known
That vandal savage
can be located in 2147.
- So why haven't you
told us this sooner?
- Because that period of history
is fraught with more peril
Than I was willing to risk.
We have no choice
But to stop vandal savage
in 2147...
Or to die trying.
- Well, I've died before.
- So have I.
- Gideon, plot a course
for kasnia conglomerate...
♪
The year 2147.
[exciting music]
♪
- Greg, move your head.