[narrator] Last season on
Legends Of Tomorrow...
We have the six totems, but
you can't fight what you can't see.
What if the only way to kill Mallus
is to let him out?
[growls]
[Zari] Guys, we did it.
- [Nora] My father's time stone.
- He died to give you a second chance.
Don't waste it.
[Constantine]
Whose brilliant idea was it
to let an ancient demon
out of his bloody cage?
Well, you opened a door, love.
And Mallus wasn't
the only thing that got out.
- [dramatic music plays]
- [unicorn whinnies]
[reporter] The newest musical sensation
to cross the Atlantic,
a group of young men from Liverpool
who call themselves "the Beatles,"
have just arrived at JFK.
The Beatles, that's "B-E-A-T" because
that's the way they keep the beat.
Hey, Z. If you had to sleep with one,
which one would it be?
- How can you even tell them apart?
- [crowd cheering]
Well, Paul is the cute one,
George is the quiet one, and Ringo...
Never met an Englishman I haven't
wanted to punch in the face.
Relax, Mick. If it wasn't
for the British Invasion,
there'd be no Rolling Stones.
No Led Zep.
No Black Sabbath.
- Black Sabbath.
- Yep.
Well, we need to protect
these mop-heads
from whatever's screwing up history.
That's right, Mick.
So, Gideon sent us
on a wild goose chase.
This event in history is playing out
exactly as it should.
[all screaming]
The British are coming!
Interesting fact. The real
Paul Revere didn't actually say...
Oh, my God. It's Paul Revere!
I got this.
Who are you people?
Where am I?
Why are all those women... [grunts]
And now for the midnight ride
of Ray Revere.
[whistles] Sorry,
Nate Revere to the rescue.
Now ring the alarm back in 1775.
I got a country to save, suckers!
See you back on the ship, Nate.
[Nate] The British are coming!
The British are coming!
[whoops]
Geez. Who died?
Oh, come on. We just met the Beatles
and saved Fourth of July.
No, it's cool. It's just all
becoming, I don't know, old hat.
Yeah, we did spend all of last year
returning displaced people
to their proper place in history.
Four years doing the same old crap.
I'm beginning to think
Wally had the right idea.
He's taking time off, clearing
his head, traveling the world...
Speaking of the same old crap,
isn't that what he did last year?
Look. All I know is, Constantine
promised us new mysterious monsters.
So, where are they all hiding?
I'm confused. We are all happy that
there was only one dragon, right?
We don't wanna be fighting
werewolves in the Alamo.
Eh...
Well, it would be good
for our ratings.
What ratings?
Oh, you don't know? The Time Bureau
rates all their employees.
But don't worry, we have
a few dedicated fans.
Yeah, Gary doesn't count.
Who gives a damn about
Time Pig ratings?
I want dragons.
What is wrong with you guys?
Don't you get it?
Constantine was wrong.
Our crazy plan
to let Mallus out worked.
Finally, we're not screw-ups
forced to clean up our own mess.
For once in our lives,
we are actual heroes.
[Gideon] Captain, I'm receiving
a communique from Director Sharpe.
Ooh!
- Ow.
- Put her on, Gideon.
Captain Lance.
I would like you and your team
to report to the Time Bureau
immediately.
Copy that.
Gideon, set a course for Star City.
I'm not talking
about our field office, Miss Lance.
I meant our Time Bureau
headquarters in D.C.
Over and out.
Damn it!
Who told Ava about the dragon?
You sure that you can't tell us
what all this is about?
Oh, I'd love to but the boss lady
will kill me.
Mick.
- Talk
- I can't. Director Sharpe's...
Whatever Ava threatened is nothing
compared to
what I'm about to do to you.
You told her about the dragon head,
didn't you, Gary?
What? No!
- Did Constantine get you to squeal?
- I wish.
We looked.
There are no more monsters.
This isn't what you think.
[exhales] Then what the hell is it?
[all] Surprise!
[cheering and applause]
On behalf of the Time Bureau,
I would like to recognize
Captain Lance and her crew
for fixing the final anachronism.
Congratulations.
[clicks]
- What does that even mean?
- Well, it means that... [clears throat]
Paul Revere was the final crack
in the timeline.
You, my friends, fixed history.
The same history we broke?
Just take the win.
I don't want your stinking medal.
- There's an open bar.
- Where?
Sorry, Sara. I know
you don't like surprises but...
I like this one.
Now, I was thinking maybe you could
give me a tour
of the headquarters, Director Sharpe.
[music playing]
Gee, I really wonder how she managed
to escape from the Time Bureau.
Yeah.
I mean... I mean, if I had to...
If I had to guess, I'd probably say
that someone must have given Nora
her dead father's time stone.
Furthermore, that someone
must've done it
in hopes that she would
turn over a new leaf in life.
Sounds like that someone forgot
about Nora's serious lack of ethics.
Around, you know, murder, for one.
But that someone
must've had a really big heart
to give her a second chance.
You're a good guy, Ray Palmer.
[Sara giggling]
- Okay, I gotta go.
- Oh, no...
Yes, I gotta get back to the ship.
The Legends aren't used
to being on furlough.
Come on, they will be fine
for one night.
Besides, I was hoping
that you and your team
would be spending more time here
in 2018.
But mostly, you know, you.
With me.
In this apartment.
Ava Sharpe.
Are you trying to make
a kept woman out of me?
[gasps] What? No. I wouldn't dare.
I'm just saying that, you know,
since you fixed all the anachronisms,
maybe you wouldn't mind being kept.
Just part of the time.
It'd be fun to come home to you.
[sighs]
I'm sorry. Oh. That was just stupid.
You just got back into town,
and here I am hitching
the old U-Haul
to the back of the Subaru.
- It was stupid.
- No, no. Hey.
It wasn't that... I'm...
I'm just thinking and...
I'm ready to take the next step.
I am ready to be
a partially kept woman.
Yes!
[giggles] Come here.
Mmm. Mmm.
Okay. So why don't you rustle us up
another bottle of champagne
and let's make this thing official?
- That I can do.
- Yeah?
[cork pops]
Hello, John.
You know, tonight really isn't
the night for celebration, Sara.
The darkness, it's rising.
What are you doing?
And what does that even mean?
Mallus wasn't the only prisoner
to escape when you decided
to pull back the veil
between our worlds.
And yet for the past five months,
the timeline has been quiet.
If you wanted to come and see me,
all you had to do was ask.
Five months is a blink of an eye
for an immortal monster.
Look, this is your bloody mess,
Sara,
so stop playing tiddlywinks
with the missus and get ready
for the fight that's coming.
What if this is who I am now?
Really?
[whistles] This is who you are.
Fuzzy throws
and fluffy pink slippers.
I like my pink fluffy slippers.
- Huh. Yeah.
- Okay, reunion's over. Time to go.
[chanting incantation]
What am I looking at?
The knuckle bones
of a martyred saint, obviously.
They act as a divining rod
able to detect the presence of beings
not belonging to our world.
My team spent the last five months
scouring the timeline
for another one of
your mystical creatures.
You wanna know what we found?
Nothing.
[Agent Sharpe] What the hell
are you doing here?
[bones clatter]
Is everything all right?
- Yeah, everything is great.
- I was just telling Sara about...
About an exorcism that he has to do
tomorrow in Georgetown.
It's really nothing you want to hear
before bedtime.
Come back again soon now, John.
Don't be shy about that doorbell.
[Constantine]
I'll be seeing you around, Sharpie.
- [door closes]
- [sighs]
Should I be worried
about your ex-lover
breaking into my apartment or...
Well, I thought that this was
our apartment.
You are smooth.
Don't forget the bubbly.
[rattling]
[sighs] Bollocks.
[Nate] Mick, what are you
still doing here?
Machine's still spinning
and I'm still standing.
You know what?
Hook me up with one of those.
Now that we've fixed
our last anachronism,
it's only a matter of time before
the Bureau puts us out to pasture.
Which blows because being a Legend
was the only thing I was good at.
Well, speak for yourself.
I was a great criminal.
At least we got these cool medals.
Actually, the medal has to remain
top secret because no one can know
about time-travel. So I'll just take
these back now for safe-keeping.
What do you say you and I find
some real action?
Mick, I'm 100% down.
Ooh. I'll come with.
[grunting]
I could've just called us an Uber.
You ready to steal something, Pretty?
- Um... [blows raspberry]
- [engine starting]
Yeah, I could do some light theft.
What is this? Spring break?
I'm talking about a felony.
- Now get in.
- You know what, Mick?
If we're gonna rob a house,
we really should make sure
there's stuff in there
worth stealing.
And I think I know
just the neighborhood.
- [taps car]
- [tires screeching]
Mick! Wait, wait, wait!
You are so aggressive.
Why don't you look for a spare key?
Good spotting, Pretty.
Yeah, I'm a real criminal mastermind.
- [snaps fingers]
- Bingo.
[gun cocking]
Yes, I'd like to report a robbery.
You'll do nothing of the sort!
Oh, Nate! It is so good to see you!
What the hell is going on here?
Um, Mick, these are my parents.
I am Dorothy Heywood.
You can call me "Dot."
- Hi.
- And, uh, this is my dad.
- Hank.
- Henry Heywood.
And I believe one of my great
grandmother's silver candlesticks
has found its way into your coat.
Oh, you have exquisite taste
in silver, Mr...
Rory. Mick Rory.
Of the Central City Rorys.
We didn't mean to scare you, Mom.
I thought you'd be up at Martha's
Vineyard this time of year.
Oh, we were.
But your father just took
a very exciting job at the Pentagon.
- We'll get going. Right, Mick?
- [Hank] Good idea.
[Dorothy] Don't be ridiculous.
Mr. Rory, do you like sandwiches?
You bet your ass I do, ma'am.
Wonderful. Then I'm gonna fix
you boys a little midnight snack.
You, too, Henry.
You're one of the boys.
Gary, wake up.
[glass clatters]
I got a hunch there might be
a monster loose in history.
Like the dragon you made me
not tell Director Sharpe about?
Exactly.
Uh...
No, the timeline's only showing
a few burps.
This is the only significant one.
What if there's a creature
that no one's noticed yet?
The only way people wouldn't notice
a monster is if it was hiding.
[Sara] Or if they were on drugs.
I'm gonna go check it out.
- Ooh, I'll come with.
- Nope.
But if you're going back to 1969,
you're gonna need...
Your Time Courier.
[sighs]
[Zari] Going somewhere, Raymond?
And don't give me any of that
"routine maintenance on the Jumpship"
crap.
Yeah, no, I wouldn't do that.
I had Gideon monitor the Time Bureau.
Someone over there pulled up
unusual activity at Woodstock, 1969.
You think it's Nora.
And if the Time Bureau
finds her first,
she's gonna tell them you're the one
who helped her escape.
Ray, I'm not gonna let you
get on that Jumpship.
- [stammers]
- Not without me.
[sighs] Oh, good.
I was not looking forward to dealing
with those hippies on my own.
What's a hippie?
[rock music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
- Give peace a chance.
- Oh!
Together, we can end
the war in Vietnam.
[chuckles] Hey!
Yeah, this place is groovy.
So, tell me.
Why would Nora time stone
to the least evil event in history?
Well, who knows? Maybe she's
turning over a new non-evil leaf.
- Inspired by yours truly.
- Right.
- All right.
- What is that?
Oh. It's my old trusty
Eagle Scout compass.
I thought we could
locate the epicenter
of the temporal disturbance
the old-fashioned way.
- That sounds like a blast, Ray.
- Yeah.
197, 198, 199...
[sighs] Sorry, Ray.
It looks like Nora's in the wind.
What is that?
[Zari] Uh, what is that?
Ray...
It's beautiful.
It's like some
sort of magical pixie goo.
No, not that. That!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Why? Who would wanna kill
hippies at Woodstock?
Literally ripping
people's hearts out.
[Zari] Now that's the Nora I remember.
You certainly can eat
a lot of sandwiches, Mr. Rory.
Where did you get those big muscles?
Prison.
[chuckles]
What a hoot. Isn't he a hoot, Henry?
[laughing]
He's a real barrel of laughs.
Excuse me.
So you just drop in on us
in the middle of the night
after barely a phone call
for the past two years?
I know, Dad. I'm sorry.
I've just been busy.
- Busy doing what?
- History stuff.
You know, the same stuff
you never took seriously.
Maybe that's because
deductive historical reconstruction
isn't an actual profession!
I'm sorry.
Should I have your mother
just grab her checkbook now,
or would you prefer your friend here
swipe it out of her purse
on the way out?
I'm easy either way.
- I don't want your money, Dad.
- Then why are you here?
- Honestly, I don't know.
- You don't... [scoffs]
We had a name for people like you
back in my day.
Oh, here comes the big rant
about hippies. Go ahead.
To tell the truth, I have nothing
but pity for those people.
Yeah, since when?
Since they were slaughtered
like lambs back in '69.
Look, I'm not saying the Woodstock
massacre was their fault,
but it wasn't not their fault either.
[clears throat]
Mom, thanks for the sandwiches!
There's something wrong with history.
Not Nora. Hi. [clears throat]
Not Nora. Not Nora.
Definitely not Nora.
Ray, I really don't need to hear
your inner dialogue.
Sorry. [stammering]
I'm nervous and upset.
I mean, how could she be
so heartless?
Pun not intended.
Well, her father did give her over
to a demon-loving cult, so...
- Nora Darhk is here?
- Sara?
Hey, what are you doing at Woodstock?
Probably the same thing as you are.
Looking for whatever's
messing with history.
Huh.
I think I just saw Joan Baez
talking to Carlos Santana.
- Woodstock...
- ...turns into a massacre.
- Nate, you're here, too?
- Yeah, buddy.
Hey.
[both grunt]
Okay. What is going on?
Woodstock is no longer remembered
as three days of peace and love,
but instead, the end of
the hippie movement.
Reports from survivors
are sketchy at best,
but what they all could agree upon
was there was a series
of grisly murders
that ultimately led to a deadly
stampede where 400,000 kids
tried to escape the festival at once.
Yeah, Ray and I just saw a body
in the woods with a gaping hole
in his chest.
- We think that Nora did it.
- Well, that's a relief.
- It is?
- Yeah, it means we're in the clear.
Look, it's not our fault
the Time Bureau let Nora escape.
[man] Guys, come check this out.
Don't panic. I left Mick alone here.
He's itching to punch a hippie.
Ah... That's not good.
Is that what I think it is?
[Nate] Twilight Sparkle come to life...
[neighing]
Are you a brony?
Dude, we're brony-bros.
Mick, join the herd.
Outta my way.
Hey, what are you doing?
Well, it's not a dragon
but it'll have to do.
No, Mick, hold on.
It's not like it's hurting anyone.
[whinnying]
[all gasping in awe]
We didn't screw things up
for the better this year.
We screwed things up
for the more magical.
[all exclaiming]
It's beautiful.
[neighing]
Oh, my God!
[Nate exclaiming]
What?
[people screaming]
Oh, my God. Is it...
Yup, it's eating her heart.
I'm gonna be sick.
[retching]
- Mick!
- Shoot it!
Damn horse is fireproof.
[all groaning]
[Mick groaning]
I hate glitter.
- Seriously?
- Where'd it go?
Okay, we can fix this
before the Time Bureau
even has to know about it.
Oh, really? Can we?
Look, Ava still thinks of me
as the woman
who saved the world last year and...
I don't want her to know there's
a whole new problem with history.
Yeah. That we basically created.
You go find the unicorn,
and I'll go find Constantine.
Yeah. Every time.
[knocking on door]
[Constantine] I'll be right back.
Somebody can't read the bloody signs.
Do you not know
there's a "do not disturb" sign
on the bloody door?
Sara.
Yeah, uh...
I can't talk right now, love.
I've got a threesome
that's about to pop off in here
with some contortionists.
You were right.
Ah.
What was that now?
[sighs] You were right!
There's a magical creature
at Woodstock.
Now let's go.
You know, for someone with
a time-traveling machine,
you seem to be in an awful hurry.
John, the unicorn has already
gored two hippies.
Oh.
- A unicorn?
- Yeah.
Well, all right. I'm in.
But first, I need to know,
was any of your team
musked by the beast?
If that's what you're calling
its sparkle sauce,
then yeah. Why?
Oh, they're in for one hell of a ride.
[groans in disgust]
Man, I wish my dad could see us now
hunting a bloodthirsty creature
through Woodstock.
What's the beef between you
and your old man anyway?
- He hit you?
- No.
- Burn you?
- Nope.
He dress up like a clown
and scare the hell out of you?
What the hell, Mick? No.
He was emotionally unavailable
to me when I was growing up.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
To the whole world,
my dad was this great
larger-than-life guy, but to me,
he was just cold.
[Mick] Boo-hoo!
- Hank?
- [Mick's voice] What?
I'm not your dad.
Oh.
So you're ashamed of me?
Pa, I'm sorry I didn't follow
in your footsteps and enlist.
But for your information,
I had a medal pinned to my chest.
Only you don't have
the clearance to see it.
- What's happening?
- What?
Axl?
[squeaking]
[Nate] I'm getting something off
my chest. And you know what, Hank?
It feels pretty good.
I just wish, for once,
you would tell me you're proud of me,
no matter what I do with my life.
You know what I'd say?
[squeaks] I love you.
I love you, too.
- Really?
- I thought you were dead.
I thought you were dead
on the inside.
[Nate chuckles]
Ray. Ray, my hand is glowing.
[gasps]
Can you see it?
No, it looks like your hand.
No, no, you gotta
open your eyes, man.
[gasps]
It's all around us.
What is?
Love.
Oh.
Those hippies had the right idea.
Woodstock is beautiful.
- What's wrong, Ray?
- What?
[gasps]
You were hoping to see Nora here.
- You like her, Ray Ray.
- No.
No, I do not like Nora.
Uh-huh. Because you love her.
No. No. The only reason
I ever wanna see Nora Darhk again
is so that I can take
the time stone back
and I can lock her up
in the Time Bureau.
Oh, my God. She's here!
[chiming]
You know,
a unicorn is no bloody joke.
You might wanna get your
ol' girlfriend on the blower.
[chuckles] You didn't tell
Director Sharpe
that you let all the monsters out
to play, did ya?
Ava and I are in a great place
right now. Better than great.
In fact, she asked me to move in
with her and I said yes.
So, why rock the boat
unless it's absolutely necessary?
Because when the boat
eventually tips,
- you'll both bloody drown.
- Nice.
I'm just trying to
look after you, love.
You and I are similar.
We're both survivors but our survival
comes at a terrible cost.
Look...
You can take it from a man
who's caused nothing but misery
to everyone he's ever loved.
Trust me...
End it with Ava before it's too late.
You ever think that you cause misery
not because of some romantic
"I was born to walk alone" crap,
but because you're an ass
who doesn't know how to trust people?
You know, I trust,
the people around me get hurt,
killed, or far, far worse.
You think that I'm not scared?
That I don't know grief?
I'm not willing to turn my back
on life,
because that is exactly
what you're doing, John.
Our friends and family,
they don't make us weaker.
They make us stronger.
You know what you need?
You need to be a part of a team.
[chuckles softly]
You were saying...
This is King Solomon's
original grimoire.
The oldest magical textbook
in existence.
Now, if there is a spell to quell
our equine friend,
it'll be in here.
Well, not to pressure you,
but the entire fate of the sexual
revolution is in the balance here.
It is my favorite revolution.
John, welcome aboard.
Hey, Ray, big man.
Glad to see you're all back
from the land of milk and honey.
I'm still a little fuzzy on
how exactly we were...
Roofied by a horse.
That beast sprays a powerful
mind-altering hallucinogen
to disarm its prey. Ah!
"How to expel a magical creature
from the mortal realm."
Now, the ingredients from this spell
aren't so easy to come by.
Don't suppose any of you lot
have the saliva for
a nine-fingered man, now, do ya?
You could chop off one of my pinkies.
No, Ray. Don't be the giving tree.
Now, as every Dead Head knows,
Jerry Garcia was missing most
of his middle finger
on his right hand
from a wood-chopping accident.
Cool, so how do we get his saliva?
[psychedelic rock music playing]
Jerry! My man.
Can I get a hit of that?
This doobie will make you fly.
Cool.
- Spin move!
- Hey!
Not cool.
We need the protection stone
of a powerful shaman.
[grunts]
Watch it.
Brother.
And the lock of a doomed woman.
[panting]
Janis, this is quite an honor.
Little robot man.
Hi. My mom is a huge fan.
Your mom?
[laughing]
And for our final ingredient...
[Constantine inhales deeply]
...a quis virginem.
What?
A virgin.
[Ray] A virgin? At Woodstock?
Ha! Good luck with that.
This is
the least celibate place in history.
Are you serious?
[Zari] Yeah, apparently,
virgins are like catnip to unicorns.
And we need one to volunteer.
Rory, do you see any virgins
where you're at?
No.
Now, come to think of it...
I do know one virgin.
No. Not a chance.
This feels wrong.
Don't worry. We'll be watching from
a short distance and you'll be fine.
What am I supposed to do
with the pomegranate?
Oh, the unicorns, they can't get
enough of them, mate.
Yeah, that and human hearts.
So the pomegranate is the bait?
Yeah, we wouldn't put
an interim member of our team
in jeopardy, right, guys?
I'm an interim Legend?
Well, then... [chuckles]
Uh, one more question.
Are you sure that I'm a virgin?
- 'Cause that thing we did...
- Positive, mate.
Yoo-hoo!
Mr. Unicorn!
Come get this nice
juicy red pomegranate.
Admit it. This is fun.
Working with a team.
Well, if our Gary gets eaten alive,
it only goes to prove my point.
People who care about us die.
- What was that?
- Oh, nothing, mate.
You're golden. Carry on, yeah.
Hold it up a bit. More.
That's the money.
[unicorn whinnying]
[chiming]
Come on, pretty pony.
Come on. Come on.
Enjoy your snack.
[heart beating]
Oh, no. That's not
pomegranate juice, is it?
Guys!
John, whatever you're gonna do,
do it now!
All right. Here goes.
[roars]
I don't wanna die a virgin!
[roaring]
[shrieking]
Seriously, you're meditating
right now?
John! Hurry!
[chanting incantation]
[growling]
[neighing]
Come on, John.
[Constantine chanting]
[screaming]
Oh!
[chanting]
Help! Help!
[screaming]
Help me!
[grunts]
[neighing]
[all panting]
[screaming]
Gary, you okay?
Just a scratch.
Where did the unicorn go?
Ah! Sent the bastard
straight to hell, didn't I?
Yep, folks.
That is some
Grade A magic right there.
Maybe the Bureau will up our ratings.
People do love the supernatural.
Gary, you're like, really bleeding.
[yelps]
The unicorn bit my nipple off!
Oh. Hey, maybe Gideon can
make you a new one.
Oh, forget it, mate. Come on,
it's a badge of honor.
You see, my soul's heading
straight to hell,
but your nipple,
it just got there first, that's all.
It's like we're two birds
of the same dark feather.
Yeah, that's right, mate.
Come on.
Let's grab a beer, all right?
Now, about this whole
virgin situation...
[clears throat]
Nathaniel?
I assumed you would have left
town by now.
Yeah, I decided to stay
a couple of extra days.
Yeah, let me guess.
You got fired from whatever
online college
you conned into hiring you.
Sweet burn, Hank, but, um,
[clears throat] I was just
wondering if you wanted
to have a beer with me.
We don't do that.
Maybe we should start.
Wow, you're looking a little
glum there, buddy.
Just thinking about all the musicians
who died after Woodstock.
Janis Joplin overdosed in 1970.
Sad and alone.
That's terrible but this is
obviously about Nora.
When I gave her the time stone,
our hands touched.
And I felt a spark.
Ray, Nora is...
Nora is like a unicorn.
Beautiful and dangerous.
She's going to eat you alive.
I guess she and I are doomed.
There's something I wanna show you.
Come on.
Okay.
I don't understand.
What are we doing here?
That's my mom.
And that's me.
[inaudible]
We lived in D.C. in 2018
before my brother was born.
It would be so easy, Ray.
To just walk over there
and tell her to get her family
and go to Canada
before everything changes.
[voice breaking] Before this country
that she worked so hard
to become a citizen of betrays her.
You'd be changing your future.
You'd never meet us,
never become a Legend.
Think of all the people you saved.
Yeah, I know. I know.
There's no loophole where I can save
my family and not screw up history,
but that doesn't mean
I don't feel guilty
every day that I have the power
to change everything and...
I do nothing.
I'm so sorry, Z.
Look at her, Ray.
How could anyone be afraid of her?
[door opens]
Hello.
Smells good in here.
Oh, yeah.
I, uh, burned the first chicken piccata,
but I think I got the second one
just right.
Are those our medals?
I wanted to remind you of
all the good you did last year.
Yeah, we, um...
We weren't that good.
Would you stop being so hard
on yourself, Sara? I'm proud of you.
[sighs]
When we freed Mallus,
we accidentally released
magical monsters into the world.
And I didn't wanna tell you
because I love the idea of us
living together
and I didn't wanna risk that
or you thinking that
maybe I wasn't such a screw-up.
- I know.
- You do?
Mmm-hmm.
Gary was very proud
about losing a nipple.
- But you cooked dinner.
- Yeah.
[chuckles]
Because I love you, you goober,
and nothing is gonna change that.
Even after I went behind your back
to work with Constantine
to send a unicorn to hell?
Okay, yeah, I wasn't so crazy
about that part.
Let's not talk about Constantine.
I'm crazy about you. Come here.
Stop being neurotic.
I don't think that you're a screw-up.
I think that you are
a damn fine captain,
faced with some extraordinary
circumstances.
God, I love you.
And I got a question.
- Do we, you and I...
- Mmm-hmm.
...think that maybe right now
is not the best time
for me to move in?
You know that I want to.
Nothing would make me happier.
It's just...
I feel like I need to be out there
with my team.
I understand.
But can you promise me
that our relationship
will continue to evolve?
Please, I want this.
You and me. For real.
So do I.
We're gonna figure it out.
[knocking on door]
[chanting]
[door opens]
No.
I haven't even asked you
anything yet.
It's not even magic, love.
It's deduction.
You need me to join the Legends
despite knowing that
needing me always causes
somebody trouble.
What is up with you?
Something must've happened
in the last five months.
You're more miserable than usual.
[chuckles] Look...
[clears throat]
You and I are friends.
And I like friends.
Friends are useful, but roommates...
See, Sara, I would rather bloody
top myself than move in with you lot.
See you around, John.
[door opens]
[door closes]
Ah, so long, Sara.
[singing] One pill makes you larger
And another makes you small
And the pill that
Mother gives you
Don't do anything at all
Ah!
Go ask Alice when she's ten feet tall
[electricity crackling]
[growling]
All right, then. Who are ya?
Come on. Who wants some?
'Cause I'm a nasty piece of work.
[growling]
[grunts]
[groaning]
Get your bloody paws off me!
[screaming]
[groans]
[breathes heavily]
Oh...
Oh, bollocks.
[theme music playing]