Time travel is real,
and so are its consequences.
When a terrible time paradox
put all of history in peril,
an elite team was formed.
Theirjob? To protect history
and repair these
so-called anachronisms.
Unfortunately, this is
not that elite team.
And yet, this team of misfits
and outcasts is determined
to fix the history
which they have broken.
Not because they are heroes,
but because they are legends.
Previously
on Legends Of Tomorrow...
Seeing Stein
with his grandkid earlier...
You two are inseparable.
Literally.
I want to break up Firestorm.
The totem's strength grows
when the threats that you must face
become more powerful.
But you cannot face
this new threat alone.
That amulet... It's a totem.
We're bound together, somehow.
Cut the crap
and tell me what we're facing here.
That information is need-to-know.
The only thing you need to know,
your ridiculous team
could never handle it.
They're the reason Mallus is a threat.
And there just might come a day
when we need the Legends
to do what they do best.
You best stop following me, guv.
That is a most impressive scream.
In another era, you could have
a career alongside Vincent Price.
Rigor mortis hasn't set in.
He's been dead less than four hours.
Extreme pallor in the face
and fingernails suggests
rapid blood loss,
yet not a drop to be seen.
Killed off-site, his body dumped here
far from the illustrious streets
of his upbringing. A handkerchief
with his college crest.
A graduation gift, no doubt.
What do you make of that?
Improbably, it appears that
our killer is a vampire.
You sure you want to do this?
Break up Firestorm?
I'm sure Grey wants off this ship
and I'm sure that can't happen
if we're still bonded
to each other, so...
Yeah, but your bond isn't
just physical.
You guys have been psychically bonded
for over three years.
Yeah, and it's been no picnic,
let me tell you.
Last time I got laid, afterwards,
Grey said to me,
"Well done, Jefferson." I mean...
Could've done without knowing that.
Does Grey, I mean, Marty know that
you want to break up with him?
No clue, but if he did,
he'd say it was too dangerous.
Well, if you're really determined
to do this,
severing your psychic connection
could give us some much-needed
mental space to figure out
how to untie the nuclear knot.
- Well, let's do it.
- Okay.
Here goes.
Oh! I forgot that there might
be a couple side effects.
What side effects?
Um, just like, you know,
facial swelling,
maybe a little gastrointestinal upset.
Oh, and short-term memory loss.
- How do you feel?
- Uh...
Normal, except
I'm not craving grapefruit.
Okay.
Ray, it's 9:00 a.m.
and I'm not craving grapefruit.
Mmm. Delightful.
Let me get this straight. This ship
can make any kind of food
you can imagine, and you three
picked grapefruit,
a bran muffin and oatmeal.
After you try everything,
you go back to the basics.
I lived my whole life
eating rations and bland food.
From now on, I eat like a queen.
I'm glad you left 2042.
Actually, I wanted to talk to
you guys about going back to 2042.
Or better yet, 2041.
I was thinking, why is my family dead
when I'm on a time machine?
Unfortunately, that's not
how this works.
I thought you could change the past.
We can correct the past
and the future, but...
- We don't change it.
- Why not?
Because doing so could cause unforeseen,
possibly even disastrous consequences.
It's a temporal butterfly effect,
if you will.
Try not doing something
that would save your brother's life.
Does a sister count?
Wassup, shipmates!
I got exciting news to share.
Team meeting in 10 minutes.
And, Mick, I have beer.
One lousy beer for breakfast.
It's breakfast?
Yeah. What time
did you go to bed last night, buddy?
I didn't. Drank a lot of coffee.
Can you tell?
Nate, why are we staring at
an anachronism map?
Because, Cap'n, I did
a deep dive on the data,
and the anachronisms we created
at first glance seem scattershot,
random, but since history
is cause and effect,
I decided to do a little experiment.
I folded the linear timeline onto
itself, following the mathematics
of the golden ratio. Follow me.
Damn it, Gideon, that was your cue.
My apologies, Dr. Heywood.
Ah. See, the anachronisms
form a pattern.
I should have guessed.
Though time may be broken,
like all matter in the known universe,
it still possesses
a mathematical harmony.
Not exactly. What about those two?
Those two are outliers.
First one is Seattle, 2042.
When the assassin tried to kill me.
Right, while cool, not the part where,
you know, you almost got killed,
it's not as cool as the other one.
London, 1895. How do I say this?
There's a vampire.
Half dozen men snatched off
the streets...
Only to have their bodies dumped
three days later
- completely drained of blood.
- Vampires.
Waited my whole life to kill one.
Do you just carry that around
all the time?
My whole life.
There's no such thing as vampires.
Increased immigration
at the fin de siècle
and the fear that good Englishwomen
would lose their virtue
to foreign predators is responsible
for these ludicrous stories.
I say we go see what's so interesting
about this anachronism.
Victorian London. Opium dens
and low-cut corsets.
Arthur Conan Doyle
and the rolling fog.
Syphilis, whores and vampires.
That's a strong smell of garlic.
It's tied around my neck.
Yeah, you're a regular Van Helsing.
That's from Dracula.
I'm reading it.
Don't tell me the end.
Another vampire victim found
dead in the street.
Oi! Give me that.
Whoa. Vampires, what the hell
is he talking about?
The blood-sucking creatures
that we're here hunting.
Oh, no.
Short-term memory loss,
one of the side effects of the serum.
Shh. Come on.
- Who are you lot?
- Oi. Scotland Yard.
We're here to see about
these so-called vampire attacks.
And we're with the NYPD.
Nothing like a bit of cooperation
- from across the pond, right?
- Uh-huh.
This one of the victims?
Unlucky devil.
Whoa! Mick!
You don't want him
coming back to life, do you?
What's going on here?
Scotland Yard has already
visited twice,
and if the NYPD is issuing
ladies warrant cards,
then I'm the bloody Queen.
All right, who brought their phone?
Wasn't me. Even though
I do love that song.
It's not a phone. It's a 2016
Palmer Tech 7G smart watch.
Hand it over.
I don't know what you're on about.
You want some of this?
Who does that watch belong to?
No? All right. Mick, stake him.
All right, all right.
A vicar was walking down the street,
as calm as can be,
when a dead man fell from the sky.
It wasn't no normal corpse neither.
No identification, strange clothes
and that there watch.
Which you stole.
He wasn't gonna miss it.
I will, though. That is
the finest timepiece I've ever seen.
It did sell better in England.
So where's our John Doe now?
Uh, I buried him in Stone's Hollow,
and the next day, the first vampire
victim was snatched from the street.
'Cause that corpse you buried
was a vampire from the future,
- you idiot.
- All right, time to go.
Who are you lot?
Tonight, we're grave diggers.
All right, we're looking for one
unmarked grave among hundreds.
I say we split up,
check them row by row.
Or we can start with the one
that's already dug up.
Yes. Ah!
The vampire must have dug himself out
before nightfall.
Damn it, that anachronistic corpse
was our only lead.
Wait, did you hear that?
Kill it, kill it.
- Rip.
- Rip?
- Welcome to London.
- Listen, Englishman.
Those time pigs try to take me,
I'll burn 'em alive.
The Time Bureau are not actually
aware of my current whereabouts,
and as surprising as this may sound,
I need the Legends' help.
Ms. Jiwe, I was surprised to hear
that you'd rejoined the team.
It's surprising me too.
I trust we're not under arrest?
- Far from it.
- Rip?
Rip, where the hell
did you come from?
- Where did he come from?
- Where do any of us come from?
You know, what are the odds of that one
lonely sperm
meeting with that one special egg?
You know, us science types are always
still wrestling with the big questions.
We've answered those questions,
Dr. Palmer.
Mmm-hmm.
I need Jackson's help with this.
There's some GPS data on here,
and, um, it might be able to tell us
where our dead man walking came from,
and, uh, where he's going. Or her.
So, yep.
Oh, man, the short-term memory loss
is worse than I anticipated.
Marty's definitely gonna notice.
It's okay, uh, I got this.
I'll just write myself a note,
like, "Rip's back."
- Excuse me, what's going on?
- Nothing, man.
You're acting awfully strange.
- It's... Temporal dysplasia.
- Temporal dysplasia.
You know how that is.
Mmm-hmm.
- Lily.
- Dad.
- Is everything all right?
- Ronnie won't sleep.
Your lullabies
are the only thing that work.
All right. Excuse me, priorities.
All right, little guy, it's time
for you to go to sleep.
Hush, little Ronnie
Don't say a word
Come on, man.
All right, we'll continue
with the plan.
But not until we figure out
whose watch this is,
which could be difficult.
Digital Digest gave
my software encryption
a five-padlock rating.
Sorry, I didn't mean to interrupt.
I didn't realize that you were praying.
Mecca's that way. I was just
looking for my earring.
I wanted to talk to you about before.
I know that it's tough.
That I'm not allowed to save
my family? Yeah, it's real tough.
You should take comfort that your
brother wanted you to have that totem.
You reclaimed it.
It's your birthright.
- It's your family...
- Stop talking about my family
when you're telling me
I can't save them.
What the hell was that?
This is the reason I asked you
to stay aboard the ship.
The reason that
I haven't returned home.
- We're connected.
- What for?
I don't know. I was hoping that
we could find that answer together.
Not to be overly sentimental, but, uh...
I've missed this place.
We'd love to reminisce with you
but your Time Bureau is on our tail.
Makes us slow to help you out.
I'll get down to it then.
When I permitted the Legends
to keep the Waverider...
Nobody permits us to do anything.
I had an ulterior motive.
Why does that not surprise me?
For the last five years,
I've been chasing a phantom.
A name whispered across time
and in every language.
Mallus.
A phantom mollusk, an evil shellfish?
"Mallus."
An evil so ancient and powerful that the
Time Masters dared not speak his name.
Now, I believe that
he is recruiting allies
from throughout time to his cause.
Now, anachronisms are the result
of your breaking time.
Her idea.
But these outliers, they are most
certainly the work of Mallus.
Now, the Time Bureau is a bureaucracy
and lacks the imagination
to understand this particular threat,
and Director Bennett
objects to my crusade.
Hmm.
I'm alone out here.
So, what I'm hearing is, your hot
new girlfriend dumped you,
and now
you're crawling back to your ex.
And I am no one's side piece.
You know, I think they're
on to something here.
Look, sweetie.
We would love to take you back,
but we don't know
how we could trust you again.
Would circumstances be any different
if I were to call off
my hot new girlfriend's
pursuit of you?
Mmm...
Deal.
All right, what's your plan?
Right, this outlier, the vampire
is most likely the objective of Mallus.
Catch the vampire.
Catch Mallus.
Sounds like we're gonna need
vampire bait.
Me?
Is it 'cause I'm handsome?
Pretty.
Pretty handsome.
Overcrowding and poverty made
Whitechapel a breeding ground
for criminal activity, culminating
in the Ripper's murders right around,
well, now.
Isn't history fascinating?
It certainly is.
Trusting the Englishman
was a damn mistake.
You know we're all on comms,
don't you, Mr. Rory?
I don't give a rat's ass.
No sign of any vampires.
I wish this was like
a Kristen Stewart type.
All broody and sparkly.
Vampires don't sparkle.
You know, Mick, you
and the vampire have a lot in common.
You both like to sleep in
and, you know,
kill people.
Stein? What are you doing out here?
Looking for you, dear boy.
Nate. Nate?
We seem to have lost Dr. Heywood.
- Nate, answer me.
- Look.
- He's got Dr. Heywood.
- Let's cut him off.
Well, that was invigorating.
- Did you find Pretty?
- No, we lost him.
We found potatoes.
Never fear.
The game's afoot.
"Methought I heard a voice cry,
'Sleep no more.'"
Professor Stein?
No, Shakespeare actually.
And it's "Sir Stein" to you.
It's not every actor who is knighted.
Oh, God, this can't be happening.
Thanks to your life blood, my master
will finally make his return.
But there's much to be done
in the meantime.
Oh.
Yeah, well, that wasn't creepy.
- Sara?
- Nate.
- Where are you?
- I don't know.
But I just had a chat
with Professor Stein's
weird lookalike evil cousin.
Great-great-grandfather,
to be exact.
The famous stage actor,
Sir Henry Stein.
Astonishing.
The chances of us running into
one of my ancestors
are astronomical.
Family lore recalls him as being
an eccentric.
But then what can one expect
from an actor?
He's also an occult weirdo
who kidnapped me to feed his master.
Excellent! The vampire
will lead us to Mallus.
Stay where you are, Dr. Heywood.
Yeah, that's not gonna be a problem.
Whatever they roofied me with
fritzed out my powers.
- Can you describe where you are?
- Uh, I think...
An operating room? All I know
is there's a spooky-ass
red moon painting on the wall.
- What's that?
- It's some of my research on Mallus.
"Beware the blood-red moon
when the door
"that separates death from life
will be opened."
It's the first line of an oath taken
by the Order of the Shrouded Compass,
an infamous secret society
of London's aristocracy
obsessed with the occult.
That sounds like the perfect place
for an out-of-time vampire
to take refuge.
The Order also believe in the magical
properties associated with...
A total lunar eclipse.
Which is set to occur right here
in London tonight.
If I wasn't vampire hunting, I'd rob
these rich bastards blind.
Hunting a tiger for sport,
it's just perverse.
Can't believe we're in a time where
women can't vote and the Internet's
not a thing.
Savages.
Anyone doesn't have a reflection,
they're getting a stake.
Ladies and gentlemen, if I could have
your attention please?
Truly uncanny.
It's that 'stache that's astonishing.
I know you're not here
for idle chit-chat
and aperitifs.
So please allow me to introduce
the star of the evening.
A famed mystic who has come
all the way from America
to communicate with the dead.
Madame Eleanor.
Can't believe people
are buying this garbage.
I sense...
Someone in the room who longs
to speak to a departed loved one.
Come, sit at my table
if you have no fear.
Since we can't hack the watch
for its GPS data,
we're gonna have to solve this one
the old-fashioned way.
With fingerprints.
Okay, we got
the coroner's fingerprints.
And the second one is mine, obviously,
and the third one is unidentifiable,
and the fourth one is Oliver Queen.
Oliver's a time-traveling vampire
from the future?
We gotta call Team Arrow,
figure out what the heck's going on.
Return of the Mack
Pump up the world
Watch my flow
Return of the Mack
You know...
About time.
I'm as excited as you are.
But we all must wait for
the blood-red moon
before the ceremony may begin.
Oh!
Gross.
If you need me,
I'll be right over here.
Sara. I could really use
a rescue right now.
We're working on it.
Do you remember our mission
from the Greyhill building?
Like it was yesterday.
Excuse me.
Could you tell me where
the powder room is?
Oh, I've missed this.
Everyone, please, join hands.
There is a doubter among us.
I too was a skeptic once.
Before the spirits spoke to me.
But now...
I am their conduit.
Kahar.
Do you remember the night
they came for us?
How fast you ran.
You abandoned me, Khaahar.
You let them kill me
so you could live.
- No...
- You are scared now.
Just as you were scared
of A.R.G.U.S. then.
So much fear.
You were my big sister.
You should have protected me.
- Please...
- Stop this at once.
You heard the lady.
Sara, our cover is blown.
We need to leave.
Wait, the vampire, that was you?
A two-pronged needle
by my own invention
is hardly vampiric.
Then who's the stiff?
Nate, are you okay?
Does it look like I'm okay?
Instead of a sexy vampire,
I get stuck with this weirdo.
He's all yours.
The Order has plans for our
time-displaced corpse.
That's why they're kidnapping men
and draining their blood.
It's for their ceremony.
Shall we find out who it is?
Whoa! Guys, I am digging the digs.
I mean, I have some serious
lab envy over here.
Yeah? Well, check this out.
Whoa. Okay, well, I've analyzed
that unidentified print
and got back 100,000
possible variations
on a complete friction ridge.
Okay, so do we have a match?
Unfortunately. I hope you guys
have a bar on that ship,
because you're gonna need a drink.
The watch belongs to...
Damien Darhk.
Darhk must be integral
to Mallus' plan.
We can't leave Damien Darhk's
body to be resurrected.
Darhk may be a madman
but he's not the madman
we're presently after.
Guys, we have definitely
overstayed our welcome.
Fall back.
The hell is going on?
We're not killing vampires anymore?
Captain Lance, need I remind you
we are no longer just fixing
ordinary anachronisms here.
Mallus is the only game that matters.
No, it's your game. We have to stop
Damien Darhk from coming back to life.
And we will.
But from all indications, Mallus
is coming here to recruit Darhk.
If we destroy Darhk's body,
we destroy any chance
of apprehending Mallus
at the resurrection ceremony.
If Sara says kill Darhk,
or re-kill Darhk,
or prop him up in a convertible
like Weekend at Bernie's,
that's what we do, because
she's the captain.
I know that you all want
to destroy Darhk once and for all.
You're just gonna have to be patient.
I'd like to speak to you in private.
Good luck in there.
I'm not letting Damien Darhk
come back to life.
- Full stop.
- You've lost perspective.
You're letting personal prejudice
cloud your judgment.
If I had, I wouldn't have put
Damien Darhk back into the timeline
and erased his memory so that
he could kill my sister again.
Look, Sara...
I understand how perilous it would be
for Mr. Darhk to return.
Do you?
Because I am the only one
in this room that's been resurrected
and it wasn't an improvement.
You're right.
You've got to understand, Sara,
that I've been chasing Mallus
for so long
that perhaps it is I
who's lost perspective.
Never gonna learn
how to knock, are you?
I'm concerned about you.
I know that you think that
woman channeled your brother.
His name was Behrad.
The night A.R.G.U.S. came for us,
I ran.
I knew he was staying to fight,
but I was scared.
I left my brother there to die.
You happy?
Now you know my secret.
- Sorry.
- Yeah, I don't want this anymore.
Whatever's going on with it,
or with us,
I don't care.
That totem is your only remaining
connection to him.
It's not a connection,
it's a reminder.
That I should have been the one
who died.
You know...
It's kind of weird not being able
to sense Stein's emotions.
Don't tell me you're missing
your psychic connection?
Oh, come on, of course not.
- Well, maybe a little, but...
- Aha!
I've uncovered your ruse.
- You've been using my lab.
- Your lab?
To impede our psychic connection.
It's the very foundation
of Firestorm.
Actually, that's the foundation
It's the formulae for building
a thermocore.
No, playing hangman.
"Q."
Grey, don't take this out on Ray.
He was just helping me figure out
a way we could...
Break up Firestorm.
So that you could go home
and I could stay on the ship.
Oh, I see.
So, are you cool with this?
Why wouldn't I be? After all,
you've only been here tinkering,
in secret, with how to split up
a walking, talking,
living nuclear reactor.
- Of course I'm "cool with it."
- Okay.
After everything we've been through,
how could you attempt something
of this magnitude behind my back?
Grey, it's not like...
Oh, it seems we both share
a craving for solitude.
- Is everyone aboard the ship?
- As far as I'm aware.
Is there something I can do for you?
In fact there is. Could you please
tell Captain Lance that...
I'm sorry.
- What are you doing?
- Gideon.
Initiate Gentleman's Dreadnought.
Command code recognized.
Are you sure, Director Hunter?
She left me no choice.
- Seven, six...
- Gideon.
Five, four, three, two...
- It's Mr. Hunter.
- What's he done?
- All the exits are locked.
- And I can't override the command.
- Damn it, Rip.
- Told you we should never
have trusted the Englishman.
Where's Zari?
Come in.
I was hoping we might meet again.
You channeled my brother earlier.
I need to talk to him again.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I cannot merely summon the dead
at whim.
Please, I need to tell him
that I'm sorry,
and I have a way to bring him back.
I can save him this time.
I could try.
I would need a memento,
something that belonged to him
that I could focus my energy on.
Would this work?
So much power.
And you give it away so easily.
A mistake you're unlikely to repeat.
Hmm?
Madame Eleanor,
the blood-red moon beckons.
Restrain her.
I must prepare for the ceremony.
Damn, Gideon, how many secret commands
did Rip program you with?
I believe this was
the last of them, Captain.
Well, I'm captain now
and I order you to override Rip's orders
and ready the ship for take-off.
Right away, Captain Lance.
Director Hunter's command allows you
to fly the Waverider,
just not let any of you off of it.
Well, it's a start.
Plot a course for
the Shrouded Compass.
Damn right, Capitaine.
And bring the ship's
weapon system online.
Needless to say, it's highly likely
that Mr. Hunter is in that building.
And I'm willing to bet
that so is Zari.
You want an omelet,
you gotta crack a few eggs.
When you welcomed me to the Order
you were seeking proof.
Evidence that life does not have
to end with death.
But the power that courses through
my veins is not mine own.
It is a gift from Mallus.
Stop this abomination!
Everybody down, now!
Your so-called master, where is he?
Mallus is everywhere and nowhere,
refracted in every moment of time.
He is dead, he is risen.
And he will come again.
Right, that's very cryptic,
but I demand to speak to him.
Oh.
Oh, very well.
Director Hunter.
Pleasure to meet you.
Oh, I'm not here to speak
to your puppet.
I think it's about time
you and I met face-to-face.
You could not look upon
my true form and live.
While you are hopelessly mortal,
I am a god.
You're too late.
It's good to be back.
Who stole my watch?
Our coordinates say we're right
above the Order.
Prepare the shock missiles.
- Three pages left.
- What are you doing?
Zari's in there.
I need you to target the cargo bay.
- Our cargo bay?
- Shouldn't we have a team vote first?
If anybody has a better idea
how to get the ship open,
now's the time.
Trust me, Jax, fire.
Shock missiles away, Captain.
Oh. This is gonna suck so bad.
Uh, Grey, if we're gonna die,
I don't want us to go out mad
at each other, so...
I can't remember what for,
but I'm sorry.
You were just thinking of me.
Actually, I should be thanking you.
- Aw. Who wants to hold hands?
- Ray, it's not friggin' Toy Story 3.
Everyone, shut up.
I got one page left.
Any last words, Rip?
Yes, I remember you.
I remember everything.
Remember us?
Oh, goodie, more Legends.
Here to kill me, I assume.
This time it'll stick.
That's my totem.
Let's go.
Till we meet again.
- Mmm. Not bad. A little tart.
- If you can believe it,
Clarissa prefers to eat her grapefruit...
With salt. Yeah, I remember.
How?
I got Ray to restore
our psychic connection.
I can feel how much you're missing
your family.
Ever since baby Ronnie
was born, it's only gotten worse.
It's like there's a hole in my chest.
I'm so sorry.
I never expected the birth
of my grandson
would make being away
that much more painful,
and I certainly never
wanted you to share this burden.
But with this new Mallus threat,
and the return of Damien Darhk,
the team needs Firestorm
more than ever.
Yeah, and the team can get Firestorm.
And you can go home.
If we can stabilize the matrix
into my body.
T.S. Eliot once said, "Only those
who risk going too far can possibly
"find out how far one can go."
So, when do we start?
As soon as I, uh, fix that giant hole
in the cargo bay.
- Well, good luck with that.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Knock, knock.
Still not knocking.
You wanna sit?
Sure. Thanks.
This is gonna sound weird, but...
When my amulet came back to me,
I felt Behrad's presence,
like, almost like he was with me.
That doesn't sound weird at all.
First A.R.G.U.S.,
then that Water Witch
and now some formerly dead guy
all wanna kill me.
My ancestor told me that
the totem strength grows
when the threats we face
become more powerful.
Fantastic.
I think what she meant is that...
You and I are gonna become
great friends,
and we'll defeat whatever
evil comes, together.
I like that.
We need to talk.
By now you know me better
than to expect an apology.
Agents are dead because of you.
They understood the risks
of their profession.
But we learned so much
from the events of last night.
- Next time...
- There won't be a next time, Rip.
You show up out of nowhere,
practically begging for our help,
and then you betray us.
You've gone rogue from every
organization that you've ever been
a part of.
'Cause you don't trust anyone.
I don't know how I could've
ever trusted you.
Sara, I need you with me now
more than ever.
Do you remember when you told me
you had nothing left to teach me?
I guess you had one final lesson.
How to be a cold son of a bitch.
Director Bennett.
Director Hunter.
You've called in your last chit.
I should never have sanctioned
last night's mission.
But the mission proved
that Mallus is real.
Explain it to the tribunal.
In the meantime, you are being
detained and suspended
from active duty.
You can't detain me.
I created the Bureau!
Then you of all people should know
that no one is exempt from its rules.
Agent Sharpe.
Thank you for notifying us
of Director Hunter's whereabouts.
Now the Legends
are free to fly the skies?
Affirmative.
The Time Bureau has bigger things
to worry about than a bunch of idiots.
Mallus is getting stronger,
Captain Lance.
Last night was only the beginning.
There is a war coming,
and history needs you to be ready.
You and the rest of the Legends.