In 2166, an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan is opposed
by the body I'd sworn my allegiance
to the Time Masters.
In the future, my friends
may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered as legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
We're in the Temporal Zone.
I don't understand.
No one should be able to...
A scan of the vessel
suggests that it is
the bounty hunter, Kronos.
A crash landing...
in both place and time.
Gideon, camouflage the ship.
This doesn't look like
the type of place
we want to linger out in the open.
That looks a lot like
a Palmer Tech building,
but why does it have
a Smoak logo on it?
Wait, this is Star City.
I thought you said
the timeline was safe.
Yes, Star City was intact in 2016.
This... this is 2046.
Don't move!
- Thank God.
- I said don't move.
It's me.
It's Sara.
Hey, Oliver, look.
I know it's been a long time.
But don't you remember
that Rip Hunter
recruited us to become legends?
I never heard of any Legends.
Get back!
This guy a friend of yours?
I don't like him.
What are you doing?
It's called shooting back.
Can't be the Green Arrow.
That's not Oliver Queen.
Sure dresses like him.
Shoots arrows like him.
Well, whoever he is,
I don't plan on sticking around
to shish kebabbed by this dude.
Kid's right.
Let's stay behind and kill him.
We need you in charge of the ship.
All right, Rip. Tell us the truth.
You've all seen how
the timeline is malleable...
in flux until it is set.
Well, this future is not set.
Remember when I told you
it was dangerous
for any of you to know too much
about your own futures?
Well, the events that you dread
could very well come to be
due to your actions to prevent them.
You know what I think?
I think you think too much.
Believe me when I tell you
that the best thing
for yourselves and for this mission
is to make the repairs
to the Waverider here in 2046
then head back to your own time
and make that none of this
ever comes to be.
Looks like the whole
propulsion system's jacked.
How do you even know
what we're looking at here?
Doesn't matter if it takes you
down the road or through time.
An engine's still an engine.
How long will it take you
to make repairs?
I'm not too sure,
but it would go a lot faster
if I had some help.
Maybe Kendra
could lend me a hand?
Enlist whoever is free to help,
I have this to contend with.
This is the Neuromorphic Interface
for Gideon's logic
and navigation matrix.
Without it, Gideon cannot function.
Well, that explains how we got
stranded here in the future.
Palmer Tech was working on
a self-learning, Neuromorphic Cortex.
They surely would have gone
to prototype by 2046.
We are going to need that prototype.
Palmer Tech is now
Smoak Technologies,
but I'm sure I can still get us in.
As I said, we must keep
you and Ms. Lance
separate from your future homes.
In any case, there's a reason
why I recruited individuals
adept at misappropriating
others' property.
It's not money. It's not jewels.
It's not a valuable artifact.
You're just lucky I'll steal
anything right about now.
As I suspected.
We'll get your gizmo.
You just get
this bucket flying again.
- I'm coming with.
- No, no you are not.
You're too emotionally
connected to the city.
- We've been over this.
- I'm over you.
You got us on a mission
to change the timeline for yourself.
And you won't even let us
look at our futures?
Now, I know this city
better than anyone else,
and you're gonna need me out there.
So, either I'm coming with,
or we can find out
if the Time Masters
are as good at teaching
people to fight
as the League of Assassins.
So the rest of the team's
on a field trip to Palmer Tech,
now Smoak Technologies.
Palmer Tech sounds better, right?
Be honest.
Honestly, they sound about the same.
Even assuming our compatriots return
with a Neuromorphic prototype,
we'll still need to prepare Gideon
for the new device.
And the engines could
definitely use some loving.
Actually, I could use
an extra pair of hands.
Well, Raymond, why don't
you and Ms. Saunders
continue repairing Gideon,
and I'll assist Jefferson
with the engines?
This is just a potential future.
It doesn't matter
if we kill anyone here, right?
Well, to avoid the risk of a paradox,
it's probably best to refrain
from killing anyone.
I'm not gonna promise anything.
My sister's apartment
used to be over here.
I seem to remember something
about your father
being a police captain.
- Your point?
- Did one hell of a job.
My father and everyone else
would never have let this happen...
unless they were all dead.
You really are pretty good at this.
Yeah, I was a shipyard welder
in 1944.
No way.
A real life Rosie the Riveter?
Is there anything you can't manage
to put a positive spin on?
No, I got it, the DMV.
So you do have a dark side.
You making fun of me?
Little bit.
Doesn't mean I don't find
your unwavering optimism...
enjoyable.
I find watching you weld enjoyable.
Dr. Palmer,
in case you weren't aware,
you are on an open channel,
and we can hear
everything you're saying.
Is it too much to ask for some
professionalism around here, and...
why am I getting so upset?
One moment, please.
I'm not upset. You're upset.
No, I'm not.
My elevated blood pressure
confirms that you are.
I'm just...
I'm just getting annoyed
that those two
are talking instead of working.
I mean...
- You like her.
- Dude, you're being crazy.
You do remember that we share
a psychic connection.
I can sense what you're feeling.
If that were true,
then you would shut up.
Hey, it's no day at the beach
for me, either.
Believe me.
Well, it doesn't matter,
'cause I don't stand
a chance with her anyway.
Now, why would you say that?
Because right now, my competition
is a billionaire genius
who built his own super-suit
and some other dude she's known
for 4,000 years
who she is destined to be with.
If I may offer one word of advice...
I really wish you wouldn't.
That word would be "confidence."
You met my younger self.
I was quite the ladies' man.
Put yourself out there.
Good things will happen.
Palmer Tech's
just two blocks up this way.
Or at least it used to be.
Take cover in there!
It's like World War III out there.
It's beautiful.
We need to find another route.
Ms. Lance, don't.
Sara!
Damn it!
You two... don't move.
We'll be right back.
Right.
We're not gonna sit here, right?
Imagine all the looting
we can do in this chaos.
Why don't we stretch our legs
at that bank we passed
three blocks back?
Drop your weapons,
and hand over your wallets.
Wait, are you actually
trying to mug us?
What is this, amateur hour?
If you don't do what my man says,
we're gonna crush you
into the pavement
like a couple of ants.
Really?
What do you say we teach
these fellas a lesson?
Yeah.
That's what you get
when you don't follow directions.
Interesting.
Hold this.
Second thoughts...
Where did you get that?
eBay.
Now, your boss
will not be needing this.
Well, this has been fun,
but I think it's time to leave.
Leave?
Why would we leave?
Come on, sweetheart.
Don't move.
You...
you are persistent.
I saw you get shot point-blank.
It's high-density Kevlar, now...
who the hell are you?
- Who are you?
- I'm the Green Arrow.
Oliver Queen is the Green Arrow.
No, he's not.
Oliver Queen is dead.
How did Oliver die?
I don't know. No one does.
No one's seen him since...
Well, since the Uprising.
Uprising?
Is just what people called it when
Well, when all this happened.
15 years ago, he brought
an army with him.
- Who brought an army?
- I did.
No, it's not possible.
How did you get off Lian Yu?
Say something, damn it!
Ms. Lance?
Who is this?
Somebody very dangerous.
Then now is not the right
time for me to say it
but please, remind me later
to tell you that I told you so.
How are you still alive, Slade?
Slade.
That's a name I haven't heard
in a long time.
How do you know my father?
He called you Ms. Lance.
Any relation to the late
Captain Lance?
If so, you must have heard
stories about my father.
I knew your father.
He was insane.
Seems to run in the family.
I'm going to enjoy killing you...
or we will.
Okay, bad idea.
Come on.
All right.
Grey and I have got
the mains back online.
Great.
Ray's working on something
called the quantum manifold.
But I can't seem
to get this to cooperate.
Let me give it a try.
Hey, you actually seem
to know what you're doing here.
Oh, yeah, machines
are kind of my thing.
Plus, I've been looking
at the instruction manual
in my downtime, so...
Most people can't follow
the instructions to build
their new bookcase,
and here you are working
on a spaceship.
A time- traveling spaceship
from the future, no less.
Well, when you put it like that,
I am kind of amazing.
And humble.
Hey, if you ever
have any bookcases
need putting together...
I'll know who to call.
So, Raymond,
you were working with Kendra earlier.
I couldn't help but notice
there might've been a little...
spark.
Really?
Oh, yes.
It was quite apparent
and if I'm not mistaken,
I've noticed her throwing
one or two glances your way.
Wow, that's... that's surprising.
- Is it?
- Well, yeah.
I don't know, I hadn't really
considered her in that way.
Why are you bringing this up?
Jeez, I feel like
I'm back in high school.
I honestly wouldn't know.
I skipped 10th grade.
And 11th.
I haven't really spent
that much time with Kendra.
You know, other than time
that we shared with her
and her reincarnated soulmate,
or people trying to kill us.
All the more reason to avoid
personal attachments.
This ship may be large,
but our group is small.
Yeah.
Preaching to the choir, Professor.
We're onboard the Waverider
to save the world...
not hook up.
Yes, quite right.
Hey, you, I'm terrible with names.
- I'm gonna call you Fonzie.
- Yeah!
- I'm gonna call you Kenickie.
Anyone else here need a name?
Your highness, can I get
a moment of your time, please?
Sure.
Isn't the future great?
We really should be
getting back to Rip and Sara.
- Why?
- 'Cause I'm not looking
to put down roots here.
Why not? It's everything
we've ever wanted.
I got a gang that does
everything I tell them to.
I got a fur coat.
I got a chalice.
Speaking of.
- What about stopping Savage?
- What about it?
You're the one who said we're in this
for the score, remember?
We could live like kings here.
No cops, no heroes...
just some fool in a green hoodie.
It's Christmas every day.
My sweet.
Slade had a son?
Look, Oliver tried.
He tried to raise an army
to fight Deathstroke, but...
everyone just wanted to evacuate.
How can you save a city
that doesn't want to be saved?
A moment. Sara, I know
what you must be thinking,
but none of what has transpired here
is your fault,
nor do you have the means
to change it,
but Vandal Savage's future
is preventable.
I implore you,
please stay focused on our mission.
We're very grateful
for your assistance,
but we really must be moving along
- to Smoak Technologies.
- What for?
That place has been
cleared out for years,
but a lot of Felicity Smoak's
projects got relocated.
Where?
Come on.
You didn't say that Felicity's
equipment would be here.
Well, where else would
you think it'd be?
Mr. Queen's base of operations
appears to have seen better days.
Yeah, well...
the place got attacked
after Grant Wilson
outed Queen as the Green Arrow.
Let's just find what we're looking
for and get out of here.
Whoever's there, get out.
I said get out!
Whoever you are, get out.
Oliver?
Hello, Sara.
Long time, no see.
Is that...
Oliver Queen.
Everyone thinks that you're dead.
They're not wrong.
Put the arrow down, John.
You're embarrassing yourself.
- John?
- John Diggle Junior.
My dad is dead
because I couldn't save him.
I don't deserve his name.
I'm Connor Hawke.
So you won't take his name,
but it's all right to parade around
in someone else's outfit?
Well, someone has to,
because last time
that I checked, you were dead.
Everyone thought you were dead.
I've been trying to hold
this city by myself
because I thought you were gone.
What happened to you?
To Laurel, to my dad...
- Felicity...
- They're gone.
- All of them.
- What do you mean?
- Ollie...
- Gone.
What do you want me to say, Sara?
30 years ago, you and Ray
hopped on a spaceship,
- and you never came back.
- We will.
I don't want to say that...
things would have ended differently
if you and Ray had been here, but...
But if we were,
it could've made the difference.
You thought I was dead.
What are you doing here?
We were looking
for a Neuromorphic Prototype
that Felicity Smoak was working on.
Felicity left
after everything that happened.
Everything her company
was working on
is being kept in a warehouse
at Adams and O'Neil.
- Entry code is 4-5-8-7.
- Thank you, Mr.
You found your way in...
find your way out.
I got to admit,
that wasn't bad advice, Grey.
So things went well
with Ms. Saunders?
Oh, yeah.
Well, I have more good news.
I was able to very subtly confirm
that Raymond
has no romantic inclinations
towards your crush object.
Okay, well, once we've
sorted out my love life,
we need to update your vocabulary.
Can't wait.
I'm gonna go check on Kendra.
- Hey... confidence.
- Yeah.
Hey.
I got the initial dampeners
back online.
Once the rest
of the team returns with
the Neuromorphic Prototype,
- Gideon will be good to go.
- Excellent.
Sooner we get out of here,
the better.
- And thank you, by the way.
- Whatever for?
Well, till you mentioned it,
I hadn't really thought
about Kendra in that way,
because, you know, she and Carter
were destined to be together
in this lifetime,
but it's all changed
and you know, she's quirky
and funny and beautiful
- and a pretty good welder.
- So... you know,
what about all those things
we were talking about?
The mission and so forth?
Oh, well,
we're all adults here, right?
Getting to know each other
a little bit better,
it's not gonna stop us
from saving the world.
Oh, boy.
Who invited them?
Word on the street is Deathstroke
is pissed about something.
Deathstroke...
what kind of name's that?
Party's over.
Everyone hit the streets.
Hit everybody on them.
I want Green Arrow dead by morning.
Listen, pal, this is my gang.
The only orders
they take are from me.
Might be your gang, but it's my city.
Green Arrow is running
with a female assassin in white
and a Brit in a brown coat.
Kill them all.
Heard the man. Let's go.
Looks like your new minions
are about to go on
a citywide manhunt
- for Rip and Sara.
- So what?
They're gonna kill our friends.
Since when did they
become our friends?
You tell me.
You and Raymond seemed
to get pretty tight back in Russia.
I've never been tight with anyone.
Mick, it's time to go.
- You're not the boss of me.
- Actually, I am.
Okay, let's both take a deep breath.
And we'll make ourselves a deal.
You help me get to Rip and Sara.
Once they're safe,
we can have this conversation.
Fair?
Thank you for agreeing
to accompany us, Mr. Diggle.
It's Connor.
It's not like I needed
to stick around Oliver Queen
for anything.
- Did you know?
- Know what?
That this is what
would happen in my city?
Oliver said that the only reason
that things got so bad
is because Ray and I
weren't there to help.
I suspected that might be the case,
but that's actually a good thing.
Now, once our mission is complete
and you and Dr. Palmer are
returned to Star City in 2016,
you will both be present
to stop Grant Wilson's Uprising.
This future
is only a potential timeline.
So this...
this version of Star City...
this doesn't have to happen?
Correct.
The future is always in flux.
Hopefully,
this will never come to pass.
This world isn't real.
Let's split up.
We'll cover more ground.
Hello, beautiful.
There's too many of them!
Gentlemen, your timing is exemplary.
Where's Connor?
He's been taken.
These are Grant Wilson's men.
The guy with the half face
and the body armor
has a real mad-on
for the kid in the hoodie.
Can I have a word?
- Rip...
- I know what you're going to say.
- We have to get him back.
- Yes, that.
You're forgetting this future
is only a potential timeline.
Yeah, where Grant Wilson
kills Connor.
Wilson's not going to murder Connor,
because once you're returned to 2016,
there won't be a Wilson or a Connor,
at least not as we know them
both right now.
Now that we rescued them,
let's have that chat.
You want to stay here.
Thought I made that pretty clear.
What I'm less clear
on is why you don't.
A city of thieves and criminals
Sounds like a lot of competition.
Then we wipe them out.
What I did to that other guy,
we do the same thing
to this Grant Wilson
and anyone else stupid enough
to get in our way.
Take a look around, Snart.
We're living the dream.
Yeah. Speaking of which...
Sleep tight, buddy.
What happened to him?
Difference of opinion.
Right.
We need to get this and Mr. Rory
back to the Waverider.
Oh, Jefferson, perfect timing.
I'm in need of your
mechanical acumen.
Okay, let's do it.
- What?
- What did you do?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You did something.
What did you do?
Nothing, nothing.
You know, this psychic
connection thing,
it goes both ways
and the moment that I walked in here,
I started feeling
really anxious and guilty.
You feel guilty, so what did you do?
In my defense, I was only
acting in your best interests.
What did you do?
It's possible
in my attempt to discern
whether Dr. Palmer had competing
feelings for Ms. Saunders...
Oh, you didn't...
I may have inadvertently
prompted him
to think of her in ways in which...
he hadn't.
- Grey!
- I'm sorry.
My intentions were honorable.
Oh, it's cool.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
I mean, nothing's really changed
apart from the fact
that now I got competition
I didn't have before,
but I should still
have confidence in myself.
Right?
Right.
Oh, they're back.
Where's Mr. Rory?
Sleeping it off.
We have the Neuromorphic Prototype.
Any luck with the ship's engines?
Yeah, it's all good.
Is there something wrong, Ms. Lance?
Well, all my friends and family
are dead,
except for Oliver Queen,
who happens to be dead inside
and missing his left arm.
Sara, I have told you...
That this is just a potential future
and that it's all gonna go back
when we return to 2016...
if we return.
But what if we don't?
We all know Carter's
not coming back.
It's not like we have
the safest line of work.
I think if Sara wants
to stay and help
that then we should.
I mean, that's what we signed up
for to be heroes.
I agree with Jefferson.
Yes, of course you both do,
because neither of you
understand the pitfalls
of changing the timeline.
Meddling with the future
is arguably more dangerous
than changing the past,
because it is still in flux.
Your wife and son's death
are in the future.
- You want us to change that.
- Don't play that card with me.
So what?
Are you only willing
to risk the timeline
if it's your own family?
I am not just trying
to save my family
and I'm not just trying
to save one city,
but the entire world!
I'm not being selfish, Sara.
Go to hell.
Most likely.
If you want to go
and save Mr. Hawke,
then be my guest.
I'll keep the ship here for one hour,
then we're leaving.
With you on board or without.
Hello, Mick.
You son of a bitch.
Just calm down.
You lied to me!
Wouldn't be the first time.
Remember the Del Ray
Currency Exchange?
The Blackhawk Armored Car job?
If I hadn't lied to you
on those scores,
we'd both be in prison or dead.
I'm the brains. You're the muscle.
That's how it's always been.
And on occasion,
I've had to call some audible.
You have a habit of getting
in your own way, Mick.
You're right.
You've lied to me about jobs before,
but then again, you lied to me
about this being a job.
It's not about the score
anymore for you.
You'd rather save the world
than be my partner.
A real team player.
'Cause that's what it's
gonna take to defeat Savage.
Then what? More money?
More power?
A life of leisure and sin?
Don't you get it, Mick?
If we take out Savage,
this immortal monster,
can't you see what that gets us?
No, tell me.
We'd be the two baddest
sons of bitches of all time.
I don't want a ticker tape parade.
You know what I want from this world.
Yes...
to see it burn.
You lay a hand on me again,
you'll burn too.
Oliver.
Oliver!
Thought I told you to go.
Grant Wilson has Connor.
They're gonna kill him.
He knew what he was signing up for
and you there's nothing
I can do to help him.
That's not the Oliver Queen
that I know.
Maybe I'm not that person anymore.
Look at me, Sara.
I'm literally half
the man I used to be.
Then that's the half this city needs.
He's got too many men, Ollie.
I can't do this by myself.
What about your friends?
I'm on my own...
unless I'm not.
Come on, Sara.
I never got the chance to ask Connor
why he wears the hood,
but I know why.
It's because this city
will always need a Green Arrow.
Is the ship ready for departure?
No, Ms. Lance is not yet onboard.
I gave her an hour.
- Hardly enough time for...
- And she's been 90 minutes.
How much longer
are we supposed to wait?
It doesn't matter
that this is a potential future.
It doesn't matter that this
may never come to pass...
may never be real.
For Sara, this is very real.
I know, which is why I gave her
an extra 30 minutes.
Gideon, what's our status?
The Waverider is operational,
Captain,
but I can't guarantee for how long.
- Explain.
- We are cloaked,
but positioned dangerously close
to where the city's criminal
element is gathering
to witness the execution
of Connor Hawke.
The longer we wait,
the greater the risk
of detection and further damage
to the ship.
Do you really want to risk
being marooned in this version
of 2046 forever?
Certainly more than I
want to maroon Sara here.
She's our friend. Our teammate.
What's the point of stopping Savage
if we only become as immoral
as he is in the process?
You should be honored.
This is hallowed ground.
I took Oliver Queen's arm
in this very spot.
Well, then let me go,
and we'll see
which one of us is tougher
me or Queen.
I already know the answer to that.
Ready the prisoner.
Sir.
We saw her trying to
sneak past the perimeter.
Sloppy.
The League of Assassins
would be embarrassed.
What was your strategy here?
You really think you could
just turn up tonight...
kill me?
No.
It was just my job to distract you.
You're not Green Arrow.
You're just a punk
in a Halloween costume.
Funny, I was gonna say
the same thing about you.
You want to fight the Green Arrow?
I'm right here.
How do you convinced Rip to stay?
Actually, sending in
the cavalry was his idea.
Where's Mr. Queen?
Connor!
Cowards, all!
Oliver?
It's good to see you again, Ray.
Kendra.
Thanks for the assist.
So who's that?
His name is Grant Wilson.
Once upon a time, his father, Slade,
tried to ruin my life.
That's not a nice family.
That's good shooting, John.
It's Connor.
Either way,
it's Green Arrow.
We have a lot of work to do.
Grant Wilson did a good job
of keeping the criminal element
in the city together.
Now, there will be plenty of people
to fill the vacuum.
I feel like I should stay.
Before Ray left,
he told me why Rip
brought all of you together.
It's important, Sara.
I just hate the idea
of leaving you here to fix it alone.
I'm not alone.
Just... just be careful, all right?
Well, you should know
better than most
I rarely ever am.
You watch his back.
Copy that.
Let's get to work.
All right, confidence.
Confidence. Okay.
So, I think Rip might have
some of that vodka left
in his cabinet.
And?
And...
maybe we could get a drink?
Are you asking me out?
Yes? No.
I think so.
Is that okay?
Yeah, that... that's totally okay,
except that three months ago,
I was a completely normal person
and now I'm a hawk goddess
traveling through time,
trying to avoid being killed
by an immortal psychopath
who murdered the man
I was destined to be with.
So...
I'm sorry, Ray. I...
I think my life's complicated enough
without throwing whatever
this is into the mix.
Yeah, totally understand.
If I was a reincarnated
Egyptian priestess,
I'd probably feel the same way.
I'm gonna go check
on Professor Stein.
Yup.
All good here.
Absolutely no problems.
Everything okay here?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, fine. You?
Oh, yeah, good. Good. It's good.
How much of that did you hear?
Oh, enough.
I'm sorry.
Sorry too.
Wait, you knew that I...
Yeah.
Yeah. You're not that subtle.
She would've picked me, by the way.
Keep telling yourself that.
She would've.
I'm just working on determining
our next destination.
I've considered your
suggesting of hell,
but I think I'll give it
a miss for the time being.
I just wanted to say thank you
for sending the team to back me up.
As it turns out, you were right.
That must've been hard to say.
Of late I've discovered that
I still have a lot to learn, I admit.
Including the fact that every future
is worth fighting for.
That said...
this mission is going to continue
to present us with difficult choices,
and I need to know that
you are a member of this team.
I guess so.
All right, Gideon,
let's see if these repairs
that Martin, Ray, and Jax made
are up to scratch.
As far as I can tell, Ms. Saunders
did most of the work,
while the two gentlemen
- competed for...
- Just get us out of here.
Please, Gideon.
I'm gonna miss this place.
Yeah, they really seemed
like your kind of people.
I don't know
who my people are anymore.
So where to next, Captain?
Well, the beauty
of this mission is that
the real question
is not where, but when.
In which case,
I suggest that we next hit
Savage when he least expects it.