Previously on Legends Of Tomorrow
and Arrow...
Kuasa is my granddaughter.
Darhk and his daughter
are just too powerful.
They have magic
that we don't understand.
John Constantine.
What? You never seen magic before?
The last time we met,
I saved your soul.
Now there's a demon out there,
possessing a little girl.
He knows your name.
Sara Lance.
Who's there?
I am Mallus.
Sir?
Visiting hours are over.
You never saw me,
and, uh, everything is perfectly normal.
Perfectly normal.
Emily.
Hey, sweetheart.
It's me again.
It's John.
I didn't think you'd find me
after they locked me up in here.
His voice, it's so loud.
He says I can't fight him.
Well, let's prove
the nasty git wrong, shall we?
Come on, let's get you up.
All right, love,
this, uh, might sting a bit.
Go back to the place
from whence thou come.
I cast thee out!
You cannot save
this one, Constantine.
You've already failed her
just as you failed Astra.
This vessel is mine.
Even now, her soul
slips into the dark
to be joined by another.
A friend of yours,
Sara Lance.
Sara.
How do you know Sara?
Tell me.
Tell me!
Sir!
I don't know how you got in here,
but I've contacted the authorities
and will press charges.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right, love.
I can explain.
Don't get your pearls in a twist.
If you'll just look
at this here coin.
I will do nothing of the...
Sara Lance.
What the bloody hell
have you gotten yourself into?
We'll get to your demon,
but how did you even find me?
A simple matter.
I tuned a dowsing dagger
to your specific energy.
I followed it from there.
And I thought time travel was weird.
Well, you are not wrong
about that, love.
Blimey!
Ooh, this is one hell of a jam jar
you got here.
I thought we gave the Englishman
to the time pigs.
That was Rip.
This is John Constantine.
Skinny Brit in a trench coat,
same thing.
Oh, doubtful, mate.
You see, I'm an accomplished warlock,
an expert of the occult
and a master of exorcism.
I'm also a Taurus
for those of you taking notes.
The Anansi Totem.
That belongs to...
Her granddaughter.
Same totem, different Vixen.
She's from 1942.
You were saying
about the warlock thing.
Accomplished warlock, mate.
Well, I am charmed to know another
who bears the family name.
It's an honor.
So, what's your story then, handsome?
I'm from another Earth,
and I'm spoken for.
Yeah, his girlfriend's a guy.
Anyway, this is too much for me.
I'm going to watch TV.
I've nearly finished assembling
our new nanite pistol.
Soon, it's going to be,
"Look out, Darhks."
One blast of this baby,
and Damien's going to wish
he'd never come back from the dead.
Well, that is,
once the code's finished.
It's not a race, Ray.
No, of course not,
we're all winners here.
Just, you know, some winners
are faster than other winners.
This code will replicate
the combustive effects
of a heat and cold gun
crossing streams, using nanotech,
the only thing
that's made him flinch so far.
You really want to rush me?
No, no, no.
Besides, the last explosion
in this lab
caused a Freaky Friday Firestorm.
I miss them, too.
I broke into the loony bin
to perform an exorcism.
And while I was at it,
that demon called your name.
Said you'd soon
be slipping into the dark.
And I figured if Emily's demon
has you on a first-name basis,
you might know something
that can help me save you both.
I don't need saving.
And I am done fighting demons.
You think this has something to do
with the demon we're fighting?
I was speaking
of them metaphorically,
but, yes, I did recently visit
the spirit world. It's a long story,
but it's probably
how the demon knows my name,
and the demon's name is Mallus.
Mallus.
Smashing.
Very handy, demon names.
Just what I need
to cast this Mallus wanker out.
Now, I don't know what you
and your, uh,
dishy lot have gotten
yourselves into,
but I suggest you leave
it to the experts.
So, nice one for the tip,
I've got a girl to save.
Oh, not so fast.
You said it yourself,
this is not just any demon,
and we've been fighting it
before you even knew its name.
And if this girl's
connected to Mallus,
she might be able
to help us destroy him.
You want to tag along
for an exorcism.
Yup.
That's out of the bloody question, love.
Well, we gave you its name,
so you owe us.
Well, I gave you your soul,
so you owe me indefinitely.
Hmm, all the more reason
for me to help you.
Nice.
If we're lucky,
Mallus hasn't cemented
his control over the girl yet.
Well, if you're looking for luck,
you're on the wrong Timeship.
How's about a light, then?
Ask Mick,
if you want your face burned off.
I'm doomed either way.
We're receiving a transmission
from the Time Bureau.
It's Agent Sharpe.
Or should I call her Ava?
Just put her on, Gideon.
Ava, hi.
Any progress with Rip?
Not yet.
I just wanted to let you know
that I'm still waiting
to meet with Director Bennett.
Unfortunately, no one here believes
that Rip was right
about Mallus being real.
I've even been barred from visiting
him while he is incarcerated.
It's a whole mess of red tape.
Well, if anyone can
get through it, it's you.
Thanks. I could use
a little encouragement.
Well, I think what we could both use
is a glass of wine.
Yeah.
Uh, well, I'd better go.
So I will let you know
how things progress. Bye.
Aw.
What?
First, I apologize for interrupting.
Second, that woman
clearly has a crush on you.
Just don't.
Come, come, Captain.
She called you
for absolutely no reason.
It was just an excuse to talk to you.
Mmm-hmm.
Gideon, play back
that last bit please.
Gideon, don't.
Yeah.
Head down, eyes up,
cheeks flushed.
Classic courtship signals.
Even if it was, and it is not,
we're completely different people.
I don't know.
You're both strong women.
You're both obsessed
with repairing time.
You're both super hot.
Gay, not blind.
Look, Ava's the kind of girl that
you take home to your parents,
and I am the kind
you take to an exorcism.
All right, we've landed.
Where did they move her?
Can't find anyone named Emily
in the admissions record.
Guys, be careful.
You're in an asylum with a demon.
It's a twofer of terror.
Give her an additional
four milligrams of thiopental,
and prep her for another session.
That's her.
Oh, there she is.
Thank you. I can take it from here.
I mean, her from here.
I'm sorry. Who are you?
I'm Doctor...
Yeah, I'm not doing this.
Nice one, love.
I'll make sure no one else
gets in our way.
Find a place for her,
and we'll rendezvous.
All right.
Now, where to perform an exorcism?
There's a vacant room
in the east wing, room 237.
237. Allons-y, Alonso.
It's Kuasa. I'll hold her off.
Go.
I don't want to fight you.
I just want to talk.
There is no time for talk.
I must protect the moment
she became his.
Emily.
Emily, I need you to speak to me.
That's not my name.
Uh, guys,
that girl you're trying to save
is Nora friggin' Darhk.
This is Damien Darhk's daughter?
How's that even possible?
They changed her name.
Looks like after Darhk
was killed by the Green Arrow,
Nora was placed
in Child Protective Services.
Demons prey on
the most vulnerable of souls.
This one, she lost her name,
her family.
Okay, so if we exorcise Mallus,
we could stop the family business
before it takes off?
We need her alert for an exorcism.
Nora, Nora, love.
Oh, they've got her knocked out cold.
You guys go hit up the pharmacy,
see if you can find some adrenaline.
Screw it.
I'm going to help Amaya.
You get the drugs.
Nate, take it.
- How do I use it?
- You pull the trigger.
Leo, we really need...
Yes, drugs, pronto. On it.
Nice one.
Oh, and, uh, see if you can
find me a light, yeah?
Got it.
What?
Huh. That is a sensitive trigger.
Nate, don't.
What did you do to her?
She was going to kill you, Amaya.
Let's get your granddaughter
back on the ship
before she thaws out.
I got the adrenaline,
and what is this?
It's the Triangle of Solomon
with some elder runes
and Enochian script.
It's a trap of my own design.
Mallus will have no chance
of breaking free.
Now, I've got to warn you both,
things are about to get
a little bit wonky in here.
Anything with an electrical current,
you might want to turn it off.
Guys, we're going dark.
Good luck.
Give her a nudge, love.
Who are you? Where am I?
It's okay.
All right? You're safe.
Now, you told John here
that you heard voices in your head.
Can you tell us
what they were saying?
"Six.
- "Six."
It's the number of the beast.
Now, step aside, Lance.
It's okay.
I summon the demon Mallus.
I order you to come forth.
Step into the light.
- Nora...
- No, no.
That's not Nora.
I've been expecting you, Sara Lance.
Soon, you will gaze
upon my true face.
Soon you will inhabit my world.
Mallus, you tosspot.
I see you.
No, John.
Your tricks won't work on me.
Bloody hell!
Any ideas?
That was all my ideas.
She's preparing an incantation.
Maybe we should stop her.
Emily?
Emily, are you all right?
They were trying to help me,
but now he has them.
So where are we exactly?
Well, I think the question is "When?"
January 16th, 1969.
She sent us back in time.
Wait, is that Nora's doctor?
Apparently, her taste
in jewelry never changed.
Yeah, this is all a bit weird.
Could we get your team
to come pick us up?
We can't communicate across time
without special equipment.
You mean we're stuck here.
Well, we wouldn't want
to stand out now, would we?
Bollocks!
Look.
They still have the same paintings
on the walls.
That's how we send our message.
The picture of the Blessed Virgin
that fell off the wall
when Nora was possessed
would still be hanging now in 1969.
If we write the message
on the back of the painting,
then the Legends
will find it in 2017.
Sure, as long as no one redecorates
for the next 50 years.
Fingers crossed.
Mick, have you heard from Sara
or the rest of the team?
They're not answering on comms.
Well, that explains the peace and quiet.
It's fine. She's my granddaughter.
Yeah, well, tell that to your arm.
You two, take it outside.
It's week 16 of the division titles.
You know we're on a Timeship, right?
Hey, Gideon, who won the...
No!
I haven't watched a live game
of football in three years.
I do not want to know the score.
Sara, it's Ray. Do you copy?
Z, would you please tell her
talking to Kuasa is a bad idea?
- No.
- Thank you.
I refuse to accept
that my granddaughter is pure evil.
Fine, she's 89% evil.
Guys, I think Sara is in trouble.
Quiet!
Haircut, take the new girl.
Find Blondie, Fake Snart,
and Trenchcoat.
Amaya, the MedBay. Pretty, the library.
Water Bitch stays in the freezer.
You know, Mick, you're really showing
some management potential.
Get out.
You ready?
Bet you wish you'd finished
coding the gun we've been working on.
If you don't shut up about that gun,
that demon's going to be
the least of your...
Whoa!
Nate, we haven't found Sara
or the rest of the team,
but we did find a strange symbol.
What's it look like?
Well, it's like a circle
with a line above the circle,
and then there's like a "U" shape
coming off of the circle.
A duck?
Welcome back to the 21st century,
you Luddites.
Incoming message from Ms. Tomaz.
- What's it mean?
- It's an ancient runic symbol
used by practitioners
of the dark arts
for temporal manipulation.
Oh, no.
Guys, I think Sara and co.
Got sucked into the timeline.
Gideon and I are
going to do some research
to figure out where they're
going to get spit out.
Or we can just ask her.
She is the one who cast the spell.
Hey, uh, don't touch the meatloaf.
You'll regret it, trust me.
This isn't my first time
in a place like this.
You know, I had this roommate once
who, um, thought I was her pet cat.
She would hide tuna fish
in my bed every night.
I don't know what was worse,
the smell or the fact that she
insisted on calling me "Slinky."
Friends of ours
came to see you last night.
They tried to help you.
- Where did you send them?
- I don't know.
It was the demon.
He took over.
And they won't be able
to stop him the next time.
And they'll lock me up
somewhere else,
put me on their drugs.
No. No, they won't.
We're going to get you out of here.
We can't take her out of here.
We're dealing with a...
D-E-M-O-N.
I'm not five.
I know how to spell "demon."
Places like this just make people
crazier and more vulnerable.
Isn't it best we keep an eye on her?
We can't take her on the ship.
No, not the ship, we need somewhere
sunny and boring.
Oh, that's your jam, right?
That... It is my jam.
We need to
give this girl a chance.
Who knows? Maybe she won't
grow up to hate us.
Clear.
Sara.
You're getting closer, Sara.
Are you all right, love?
I'm fine. Come on.
We're almost at room 237.
They can't reach you.
Only I can.
Sara.
- Nora?
- Help me, Sara.
Nora?
Is that you?
Please, help.
Captain Lance!
What is it? There's nothing there.
It's Mallus.
Well, I told you there'd
be repercussions
to going to the dark side.
It leaves a trace.
And now that he's sniffed you out,
he'll want to use you, too.
You can't let him break you.
- We've got to get out of here.
- All right.
Go.
The painting.
I'll put a message behind it.
I'll see to her
and come and find you.
- All right.
- You've got to help me.
- He's coming for me.
- All right, come on.
What do you think you're doing?
"Legends, we got dropped through time
from 2017
"and are now trapped in the past.
"The day is January 16th, 1969.
"Come quick."
So you are a time traveler?
Would you believe
I'm also from an alternate Earth?
Of course you are.
Take him to the operating room.
Hey, come here.
Stay with me. Stay with me.
- What's happening?
- It's Mallus' trickery.
Fear, anger. He's using
your darkest emotions
to prime you for possession.
He wants you to be afraid.
I need you to fight him, Sara.
Feels like the mother of
all hangovers, don't it?
Yeah.
A shot of pickle juice and a gin
and tonic will sort that right out.
I thought this was all over.
The bloodlust, the fight for my soul,
all the crap that I've had to endure.
Well, there's always
more crap to endure.
Take it from one who's
damned his own soul to hell.
There was a...
A girl in Newcastle.
Astra.
I failed her.
Some might say
you should forgive yourself.
Well, if I could,
then perhaps I wouldn't have the need
to save the likes of poor Nora.
What about you?
Have you forgiven yourself
for your sins?
I don't deserve forgiveness.
What is that?
It's a little reminder that
you are a survivor.
Strong enough to keep even
the most powerful demons at bay.
A laundry room
in a mental asylum in 1969
might not be the worst place
to be stuck.
Are we really this damaged?
I certainly hope so.
You must find the girl.
She needs your protection.
Are you okay?
What do you care, N ana Baa?
It's strange to be called "Grandmother."
If I've learned one thing,
it's that time travel
can be maddening.
I can imagine.
If you have the power
to change history,
and you choose to do nothing.
I choose to protect people
from those who would prey upon them.
And what about your own people?
If you really cared about them,
you'd take this ship
back to Zambezi, 1992.
I can't interfere with our fate.
Then you are a coward.
Yet you were a wonderful grandmother.
I adored you, Nana Baa.
I wanted to be just like you.
Then one night, the men came.
Please, I can't know this.
I watched the men murder you.
Then they burned our village
to the ground.
Mother ran with Mari.
She abandoned me.
No.
She thought you were dead.
I was alone
in a country ravaged by war.
I'm sorry, Kuasa.
I learned to embrace the pain,
using it to strike bargains
with powerful beings.
Like Damien Darhk?
What has he promised you?
Something you've refused.
A chance to protect our village.
A chance to save your life.
Chance to go anywhere,
and she chooses a coffee shop?
She just wants to feel normal.
Hey, you okay?
Hmm. Feels good to be in real clothes.
Yeah, tell me about it.
So, what are you going to order?
Oh, um...
Hot chocolate
with whipped cream and caramel sauce.
Uh, we just got her off her meds.
We really want to get her
hooked on sugar?
You know what?
I think I'll have a donut, too.
Nora, would you
find us a seat please?
Thank you.
We've really got to come up
with a plan
besides taking Mallus
to a coffee franchise.
Anything's better than
that insane asylum.
No, no, no.
No, you are making a serious mistake.
I'm not insane, I promise.
You don't know what you're doing.
I've performed thousands
of trans-orbital lobotomies.
After we've finished,
your disease will be cured.
Who are you?
We're also from the future,
and spoiler alert, you don't age well.
They found the note.
And we need to find
another way out of here.
Okay, the symbol that Nora drew
was a time travel spell, right?
So why don't we just cast
the same spell and get out of here?
Yeah, she was channeling
the power of Mallus
when she cast that spell.
Not even I have that kind of juice.
I do. You said that Mallus can use me
the way that he does Nora,
so you summon Mallus into me.
I draw the rune same as her,
and we get to go home.
And what about
when the demon is inside you, eh?
You said I was strong enough
to hold Mallus off.
Yeah, well,
I was trying to seduce you.
Oh, please, I was seducing you.
I hope no one
was trying to seduce anyone
while I was about to be lobotomized.
You know,
this is why I like to work alone.
Okay, it's a musical.
Oh, this is an easy one.
No, no, not this again.
Ray, please don't sing.
Please, please.
Oh, what a beautiful mornin'
Oh, what a beautiful day
I've got a beautiful feelin'
Everything's goin' my way
That's okay, but I can't...
You guys know
this is a state, too, right?
Yeah.
Come on, my turn.
What? What is it?
Mayor Queen is facing trial
for multiple murders,
including that of Damien Darhk
two years ago.
- We should go.
- Yeah.
Hey, let's get out of here,
all right?
There's no place you can take me.
No place he won't find me.
- Hey.
- Nora.
Nora, we know you're still in there.
Hey, Nora, listen to us.
The girl is empty.
Long before you arrived,
she was mine!
You have to fight him, Nora.
She feels nothing.
She is nothing.
Hey, that's enough.
Everyone, get out.
Let her go.
Your fight's not with her.
It's with us.
There will be no fight.
We need backup. Nora's possessed.
Come on. Push back.
We're trying, but we need help.
Where's the defense?
That's what we're asking you for.
Oh, tie game. Third and... Goal.
- Here.
- Thanks.
Have you seen Amaya?
She's talking
to her granddaughter-sicle.
Wait, what?
You let her go in there?
Starting goal.
Damn it, Mick.
What do you mean,
you spoke to one of our ancestors?
She came to me in a vision
and told me to protect
the new totem-bearer.
I assumed she was talking about Zari.
But now...
I think she meant you.
You want to help me?
You're family.
Get away from her.
Put the gun down, Nathaniel.
Once you're under, don't let
the demon coax you in any further.
You must out-will Mallus
and draw the temporal rune.
Are you sure you want
to do this, love?
You want to stay here forever?
The ash of a slain phoenix
will hold Mallus
within his parameter.
And we'll hasten his wake-up call
by combining extract of hawkweed
with the saliva of a damned man,
which I'm sorry to say, love,
you'll have to ingest.
Let's summon this demon already.
All right.
Let him go.
It's working.
Somebody out there?
What's going on?
Why did she stop?
Come on, Sara.
Finish it.
Nora?
He's possessing you, too.
I don't like what I'm doing up there.
I don't want to hurt them.
Hurt who?
Listen to me. You are not Mallus.
You are not a demon.
You are Nora Darhk.
You think you can fool me?
You're one of the six.
I'm what?
Nora!
Look at me. It's not your fault.
But now you get to make a choice.
You don't have to give in
to the darkness. You can fight it.
Nora, I know.
Because I fight it every day.
Can you do that, Nora?
Can you help me fight?
Hey, it's okay.
It's okay. It's over.
Anytime today would be good, love.
Come on!
- Are we leaving? We're leaving now?
- Grab her arm!
Are we back?
She bloody did it.
No, no, no.
No, no, don't do this to me.
Sara? Come on, Sara, come back to me.
Prove me wrong.
Oh, no.
You...
You should really
see your face right now.
Get up.
Kuasa, don't.
If you're going to kill me,
pull the trigger.
At least you'll have done something
to change my fate.
He can help me save you
so that I can go home.
Let him go.
You need him, too.
Don't disappoint me,
Nana Baa.
I...
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to...
Nora, look, we know that wasn't you.
You have to know that.
You have to believe that, too.
Hey, we're going to find you a home.
Somewhere where people
understand you.
Look no further.
I heard you guys were in town,
so I just had to stop by.
Daddy?
Hi, honey.
Nora, don't.
You're alive.
I missed you so much, Daddy.
Everyone's been so mean,
and every place I've gone
has been terrible,
but they kept me safe.
Your friends lied to you.
They're afraid of what you are.
You see, Mallus is no demon.
He's your savior.
Do you remember how he made you feel?
The power.
One day, you'll use that power
to bring me back to you.
You just have to accept him.
Nora, look, I know it's hard,
but don't listen to him.
Look, you still have a chance...
Come to me.
That's right, my darling.
Come to Daddy.
Now, we're going to have to part
for a little while,
but I know someone
who's going to give you a home,
a place where they
understand your power.
But...
The Order and I will help you
work with Mallus
so that you can bring
your father back for good.
Come on.
I know.
Family reunions can really suck.
God!
How many times
do I have to tell you? I'm fine.
Well, somehow you managed to channel
a demon of the highest order,
and you didn't succumb.
Sara's strong.
She's the strongest person I know.
Hey, when Nora
was possessed by Mallus,
he seemed scared of my totem.
He said that I was "one of the six."
And that bastard doesn't fear much.
If your totem gave him the frights,
maybe these trinkets are the keys
to stopping him.
So much
for our anti-magic nanite gun.
I only know about five totems.
There's my spirit, your air,
Kuasa's water, and then there's earth
and there's fire.
But could there be more?
I'll do some digging.
I have numerous contacts
I can draw on.
Well, this has been, uh, weird.
Even for me.
Well, I'll be on my way, then.
Hey, before you go, I, um...
I just wanted to say thank you.
For helping me with Mallus, that is.
Oh.
Of course. Uh...
Helping you with Mallus
was, uh, good for me, too.
If you ever need me to help you
with Mallus again,
just give us a call.
I'll be right there.
Although there are
lots of people out there
with very weird demons,
and they all need my help.
Mmm. I understand.
Good.
And thanks for the shag, too.
That was great.
Oh, Ray, big man, do us a favor.
Uh...
Give us a hand
with the cargo door, will you?
It's actually
a pretty intuitive design mechanism.
Basic open-close functionality.
I know how to open
the damn door, mate.
Now, what's this
about an anti-magic gun?
Oh, I was going to put it in storage.
Don't.
You keep it nearby.
You said so yourself,
the key to stopping Mallus
are the totems.
That could be.
But in the meantime, you may need
a more accessible solution
for a more familiar target.
Sara may not know it,
but the demon's power,
it lives inside of her.
If, or more like
when, she succumbs to it,
you're going to need that gun.
As always,
this is a non-smoking aircraft.
Don't worry, Gideon, sweetheart.
I'll see you around, squire.
That guy's cool.
The highlight so far,
there was the interception...
Hello, friend.
Would you mind, uh, turning that off
for a second?
Off.
Okay. Um...
Just wanted to say I'm grateful.
Grateful I was allowed to tag along
with you and the Legends. It was...
It was an experience
and, uh, an education.
Likewise.
I'm proud to know you and...
This is hard.
This is me saying goodbye.
Take care of yourself, Mick.
You, too.
You know he's still
watching TV, right?
I wasn't watching...
Just a little bit.
On that note, Captain Lance,
I'm going home.
I'm going to ask Ray to marry me.
- Ray?
- My Ray, not your Ray.
Wow, that is a bold move.
It is.
Just feels like it's time
to sign up for a...
A different kind of adventure?
A different kind of adventure.
Exactly.
Snart.
I mean, Leo.
See you around.
I'll see you around.
Gideon, can you get me
a line on Ava, please?
Yes, Captain.
Would you like some privacy as well?
Cheeky bot.
Captain Lance,
I was just about to call you.
Really? I mean... Cool.
'Cause, uh, I just wanted
to compare notes.
And I thought that maybe
if you'd like to come to the ship...
There's no time.
I finally got through
the Bureau's red tape,
and it seems Director Hunter
has escaped.
What?
Well, where is he?
We have no idea.