- In 2166, an immortal tyrant
named vandal savage
Conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
And stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately,
my plan is opposed
By the body I'd sworn
my allegiance to:
The time masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
But if we succeed,
They will be
remembered as legends.
- Previously, on
"legends of tomorrow"...
- The time masters
discourage marriage,
But I fell in love
and we had a child, jonas.
- Maybe we could get a drink?
- Are you asking me out?
- Yes. Is that okay?
- I think my life's
complicated enough
Without throwing
whatever this is into the mix.
- This is star city.
- Yes, star city, 2046.
- It's everything
we've ever wanted.
We could live like kings here.
[grunting]
You son of a bitch.
You lay a hand on me again,
you'll burn too.
- Go ahead, jonas.
He's listening.
- Hi, daddy. We miss you.
- And love you.
- Anything else
you want to say?
- Come home soon, daddy.
- [laughing]
Hi, rip.
Not sure if you got
our last message.
I told jonas that you got
caught up with work,
But I really thought
you'd be home by now.
London is--
Things have changed.
It's hard to tell
what's going on
With so many soldiers
and rumors.
I just want to know
you're all right.
Wherever you are,
Whenever you are,
I love you, rip.
Go ahead, jonas.
He's listening.
- Hi, daddy. We miss you.
- And love you.
- I'm sorry
to interrupt, captain.
- No, uh, not at all.
Just, uh, catching up on work.
- What is all this?
- Just trying
to connect the dots,
Find the optimal time
to strike at savage.
- And?
- And the trail's gone cold.
In order to preserve
the element of surprise,
I wager the best
course of action
Is to travel
further back in time,
But nothing here indicates
where to find him.
- Perhaps I
can help you look.
- I've been looking!
I apologize.
It's just the stakes
are so high.
I vowed to save my family,
but I'm failing them.
Perhaps I'm not
the time master they need.
- You must be.
You're the only one they have.
Can't gideon help us?
- No.
When a timeship returns
to the vanishing point
After a mission,
its cpu is updated
From the temporal database,
Which, given my rogue status,
We are unable to do.
- So, what you're saying is
Gideon requires
a software update.
Which explains why you've been
holed up in here
For the past week.
- Has it really been a week?
- Mm-hmm.
And some of our teammates
are getting just a tad antsy.
- [screaming]
[grunts]
I'm done.
- Don't mind him.
He's still sore
about having to leave 2046.
- I'm sore because
I was recruited
For my unique ability
to light things on fire.
And now, I'm locked
in the one place
Where I can't light things
on fire:
A spaceship.
- Where do you think
you're going?
- Why?
You gonna clock me in the head
if I don't listen again?
- Everything okay with you two?
- Yeah, peachy.
- Captain,
I've just intercepted
A deep space transmission.
It's a distress signal
from the acheron.
She's the--
- flagship of the time fleet.
Yes, I know that.
Thank you, gideon.
- Systemic malfunction.
I'm stranded, unable to jump.
Controls unresponsive.
This is captain eve baxter
Of the timeship acheron,
Requesting critical rescue.
- And we care about
this chick why?
- We don't,
but the acheron's computer
Will contain the current intel
on savage's whereabouts.
Gideon, set a course
For the acheron's position
in deep space.
- Yes, captain.
- Deep space?
I had no idea we had the ability
To explore the unknown realms
of the galaxy.
Astonishing.
- No.
What's astonishing
is that we're acting
As roadside assistance
for the people who's chasing us.
- Doesn't it seem suspicious,
This distress call just
happened to reach us?
- How do we know
it's not a trap?
- We don't, but
what we do know
Is that savage's trail
has run cold.
And unless gideon
can upload the data
From the acheron's computer--
- I'm in.
- You are?
- The sooner we end savage,
the sooner
I get back to where I belong.
- Prison?
- Any prison on earth's
better than this one, professor.
- Gideon.
- Yes, sir.
- Engines to full throttle.
- Of course, captain.
[exciting music]
♪
- Professor stein,
mr. Jackson,
Would you care to join
the boarding party?
- A chance for an
extra-vehicular
Docking maneuver?
What could be more exciting?
- I could think of a few things.
- Let's get this thing started.
- Hey, you think
there's something
Worth stealing on that ship?
- I'm just looking
for a change of scenery.
If that's okay with you, boss.
- Dr. Palmer.
I leave the ship
in your hands while we're gone.
And I leave him in yours.
♪
- I'm having
the strangest sensation.
It's like I'm
ten years old again.
- You do a lot of space travel
as a kid, professor?
- Only in my dreams,
after I read
My first issue of
"rick starr: Space ranger."
- Space ranger stein?
Yeah, I don't see it.
- I wanted
to travel through space,
Surviving only by
my wits and laser guns.
I even built a rocket
out of cardboard boxes.
- What stopped you?
- Nasa has rather strict
guidelines regarding
Nearsightedness.
- And smoking weed.
- Gideon, have you been able
to link up
To the acheron's computer?
- It appears
a self-destruct code
Has disabled the ship's
temporal navigation system.
- Well, what does that mean?
- It's possibly the result
of a malfunction.
Just in case, martin,
I'm going to ask you
To remain behind here
on the jump ship.
- You're telling us
if something goes wrong,
Egghead's in charge?
- Break out the emergency gear.
Space ranger has a job to do.
- Rip? Rip, I need an update.
- How about this update?
They've boarded the ship!
We've been overrun!
- Excellent.
- Perhaps you're not
taking this seriously, miranda.
- Gary?
- Yes, captain?
- Be a dear and open the
portside bulkhead, would you?
- Look,
I enjoy a suicide mission
As much as the next person--
- you heard me, gary.
- Yes, ma'am.
- What's the plan here?
- Rip, you might want to grab
hold of something.
- Yes, I am!
It's called a gun!
- Something else.
Do it, please.
Now, gary.
[screaming]
- Gamma-delta hatch opened.
Explosive decompression
has evacuated the time pirates.
- Seal hatch, engage time drive,
and punch it.
- Well done,
lieutenant coburn.
- Well done?
She nearly got us killed.
The simulation equivalent,
at least.
- She demonstrated
unconventional thinking
Against overwhelming numbers.
You could learn a thing
or two from her,
Lieutenant hunter.
[romantic music]
♪
- Declan was right.
Teach me more.
- [laughs]
- [clears throat]
[both gasp]
- Sir, I can explain.
- Don't bother, lieutenant.
Save it for
your disciplinary hearing.
- Hey, hey, hey.
We can figure this out.
We'll get through this together.
- That's just it.
We can't be together.
We knew from the start.
Relationships
are strictly forbidden.
- There has to be
a way to fix this.
- I'm sorry.
I need some time to think.
[somber music]
♪
[dramatic music]
- Stay close and stay alert.
- To quote
every "star wars" ever made,
"I've got
a bad feeling about this."
[clangs]
[grunting]
♪
- Valiant effort.
Let the man go.
- Or else what?
- Do as the man says.
- [screams]
- Who the hell are these guys?
- These, mr. Jackson,
Are time pirates.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Captain john valor.
- Oh.
What happened to captain baxter?
- She was on her way
back to the vanishing point
To imprison us
when we made our escape.
But before we could
take control of the acheron--
- She destroyed her time drive
in accordance with protocol.
- The same protocol that said
Another time master
would come to her rescue.
- Do I look
like a time master to you?
- You look like
the kind of man who'd
Throw his grandmother
out of an airlock.
- Nor am I a time master,
So you might as well just
let us go.
- [laughing]
Correct me if I'm wrong.
You're rip friggin' hunter.
I thought you'd be taller.
- You never said
you were famous.
- Infamous.
There was a time when he had
men like me
Running scared
all along the timeline.
- Unless you let
us return to our ship,
A man named vandal savage
will destroy the entire world.
Time masters and pirates alike.
For once, we're fighting
on the same side.
- That little slogan
should come with its own shovel.
Prepare a boarding party!
- Yes, sir.
- If I were you, I'd reconsider
your plan, mr. Valor.
- Really?
- I gave my crew instructions
to shoot any boarding vessel,
Along with the ship
launching it.
- With the great
rip hunter on board?
I highly doubt it.
- You don't know my crew.
They're iron-willed
and battle-hardened.
The most formidable warriors
to navigate time and space.
- Captain's log.
Stardate 837.9.
We're awaiting word
from the away team
Aboard the acheron.
- I hate
to break it to you,
But you're no captain kirk.
You're picard.
- But picard was cautious,
Pontificating, sort of sexless.
- Well, tell that to vash.
And for the record, picard was
way hotter than kirk.
- Ooh, mick had it wrong.
This ship isn't a prison.
It's a torture chamber.
- Well, I don't think
mick's problem is with the ship.
- You think it's with me.
- You did knock him out
and force him to leave
2046 star city, which is like
disneyland for felons.
- He'll get over it.
Mick runs hot.
He always has.
Once he calms down, everything
will be back to normal.
- Yeah, I bet that one sounded
more convincing in your head.
[computer beeping]
- I'd like to speak to
acting captain raymond palmer.
- Ooh. Acting captain.
I like the sound of that.
I'm captain palmer.
Who are you?
- I'm the man
holding your crew hostage.
- Captain palmer,
I've informed mr. Valor
Of the fiery retribution
you'll rain down upon him
If we are not released
immediately.
- Mm.
- [grunts, gasps]
- I'm gonna
make this real simple.
You surrender your ship,
and I'll drop you off unharmed
At a place and time
of your choosing.
You've got 10 seconds to decide.
- Or else what?
If you want the waverider
for yourself,
There's no way
you'll fire on us.
- Perhaps, but right now,
I've got my sights set
on your captain's head.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay.
Just give me a chance
to negotiate.
- Ten...Nine...
- Maybe he's bluffing.
- Eight...
- Doesn't feel like it.
- Seven...
- You don't know palmer,
And how he survived
the "imperiex" onslaught.
[alarm blares]
- Uh, gideon?
- Captain hunter programmed me
To execute certain protocols
In response
to specific keywords.
- What does that mean
in english?
- Strap yourselves in.
We are on the move
and preparing to fire.
♪
- Great scott!
We're under attack!
Gideon, who's firing at us?
- Captain's orders.
- Palmer, you idiot!
- No, captain hunter's.
Attacking the pirates
who've taken the rest
Of the boarding party hostage.
- Pirates?
- What are you doing, gideon?
- Just a warning shot to let
them know we mean business.
- My partner's on that ship.
- D--dr. Palmer?
Captain hunter?
Is anyone there?
It's up to you now, martin.
- Gilbert!
- Yes, sir.
- Set a pursuit course
and prepare to return fire.
♪
- If you destroy the waverider,
None of us are getting
back home.
- Don't worry.
I'm only targeting
Your ship's life
support systems.
- Now, if I were the weapons
targeting system
On the acheron...
Where would I be?
- There's a hull breach
in the aft portion of the ship,
And the pirates have taken out
the telemetry controls.
- Gideon, switch to manual.
- What are you doing?
- If this is anything
like a video game,
Flying a space ship.
- Where are you guys going?
- To deal with the hole
in the ship.
- Make sure picard here
doesn't get us all killed.
- Actually,
I'm more like sulu right now.
Or han solo!
♪
- Target their thrusters
and fire.
[machinery whining,
powers down]
I said fire!
- Sir, the weapons systems
have been taken offline.
Manually.
- Who else is on my ship?
- Oh, a good captain
keeps his best weapons hidden
From his enemies, mr. Valor.
- Find the saboteur!
Bring him to me, dead or alive.
I guess we'll just have
to follow your friends
Till they're out of air.
Shouldn't take too long,
given the size
Of the hole in the hull.
[hissing]
- Here.
[electricity whines]
- Hail the crew
of the waverider.
Rip, tell your crew
to let us board,
And I will happily save them.
But either way,
we are taking the waverider.
- Take the damn deal, rip.
- A captain never
surrenders his ship.
Besides, you'll never
catch captain palmer.
He once outran
kanjar ro himself.
- Who's kanjar ro?
- Engaging protocol
now, captain.
- Awesome.
- I wasn't talking to you.
♪
- What the hell
happened to 'em?
- We were following
a holographic projection
Which allowed the waverider
to slip away.
- Giving secret commands
to your crew.
Very clever, captain.
- Mm-hmm.
- Throw them in the brig!
We'll find your friends' bodies.
Eventually.
- How long
can you keep that up for?
- Not long.
I'm gonna run out of charge.
- Be advised, the breach
is only partially contained.
- Guess we know
the bulkhead doors are working.
- Too bad we're on
the wrong side of them.
[alarm blaring]
- Uh oh.
- Thanks for stopping by.
- We're gonna get you
out of here.
Just hang tight.
- Is there another option?
- Don't mean
to rush you, raymond,
But it's getting cold in here.
Normally I
wouldn't complain, but--
- Can't you just open
the doors, gideon?
- The bulkhead is designed
to remain shut
Until the breach is sealed.
- Well, that's not happening
from in here.
- How much time
do we have until--
- We're dead?
- Ah!
Ah...
Captain baxter.
I'm rip hunter.
I'm here to rescue you.
- I doubt it.
You walked straight into a trap.
- I will admit
that we've encountered
Some...Unforeseen obstacles.
- Right.
- But, we're gonna get you
out of here in a second.
Mr. Jackson, will you please see
what we can do
About disabling
this force field?
- You don't think
I've tried that?
But by all means,
if you think this kid
Will have better luck.
- Whoa, who you callin' kid?
- I'm sorry.
I meant criminal.
- Actually, that's me.
- All of you.
If we ever do get out of here,
The first thing I'll do
is take you
To the vanishing point
to await trial
Before the time council.
The great rip hunter,
But look at you now.
- Yes, look at me now.
Helping you break out
of a pirate's brig
Aboard your own timeship.
- I don't want help from a man
who broke his oath,
Stole a timeship, and decided
to change history
For his own selfish reasons.
Doesn't make any sense to me.
- No, I don't expect it would.
- Rip hunter.
Miranda coburn.
Those aren't
your real names, are they?
- No, sir.
- And why is that?
- Because if our enemies knew
our true identities,
Our ancestors and descendants
across the timeline
Could be potential targets.
- As well as
anyone else you might love.
Which is why...
- Personal attachments
are expressly forbidden
By the council of time masters.
- And grounds for immediate
discharge from service.
Do either of you deny
that you were conducting
An illicit affair in violation
of this council's rules?
In that case,
I motion that we adjourn
this disciplinary hearing
For one hour to afford you
The opportunity
to consider your response.
Though I sincerely doubt
there's any answer
You can provide that will
prevent this tribunal
From discharging you
both from the time masters.
- I suppose this feels like
a day at the beach for you?
- If I had to pick
a way to die,
Freezing wouldn't be the worst.
What's it like?
Dying?
I imagine you've got
a unique perspective.
- You know, it's funny.
I mean, you'd expect
it to be terrifying,
Just panic and fear.
- What'd you feel?
- I guess lonely.
Yeah.
Like everybody I loved
was a million miles away.
I mean, I don't like you, but at
least I'm not dying alone.
- Closest I ever came to dying
was, uh...
The day I met mick.
- Why does that not surprise me?
- It wasn't like that.
It was my first day in juvie.
I was 14, and the smallest kid
in there by far.
Some of the older kids
wanted to make sure I knew it.
So they jumped me.
I fought back,
but one of them had a shiv
And I figured that was it
Until mick stepped in.
And they didn't mess
with me after that.
He's been standing up for me
ever since.
- Let's just hope he's
standing up for rip and jax now.
- Who else is gonna
take on those pirates?
[dramatic music]
♪
- Hey!
[grunting]
- ah!
♪
- That'll teach you to mess
with a nuclear physicist.
♪
- You ready?
- Given I never designed
the atom suit for outer space,
I'm not exactly sure
how to answer that question.
While I'm gone, you're captain.
- Thank you.
But I think we both know
I'm in charge either way.
- [chuckles]
- Good luck.
- Gideon, open the hatch.
- [sighs]
- sorry, captain.
I can't jerry-rig the door open.
- Don't worry, kid.
It's not your fault.
It's his.
- In case
you've forgotten, mr. Rory,
You volunteered to be
part of this boarding party.
- I volunteered to get
away from my partner,
Who hasn't been
acting like my partner
Ever since you fed his head
with fairy tales
About saving the world.
- Your partner has a mind
of his own,
Mr. Rory, which is more
than I can say of you.
- Are you saying
that I'm dumb, captain?
- Let's pretend,
just for a moment,
That you're the captain,
Stuck in the brig
while the rest of your crew
Slowly perish
on their damaged ship.
Now, what would you do
to get yourself
Out of that predicament?
Oh, no brilliant ideas?
Really?
Why am I not in
the least bit surprised?
- Shut your mouth, now!
- Okay, let's all just
take a deep breath.
- Or what?
You'll punch me in the face,
Or burn me alive,
or employ
Some other barbaric form
of violence?
- That's why you recruited me,
isn't it?
To hit, hurt, and burn?
- No, I recruited you
because you and your partner
Were a package deal.
- What?
- I'm sorry, mr. Rory.
But a serial arsonist
was never part of my plan
To stop savage, much less one
with the iq of meat.
I didn't mean to be so blunt.
If I could just have
a moment of quiet,
Then perhaps I can think
of a way
Of getting us off
this pirate ship.
- I think
I just beat you to it.
Can anyone hear me?
- What the hell
do you think you're doing?
- Me and the pirates
are gonna have a little parlay.
- Do not do this, rory.
- Too late.
- What do you want?
- I want to speak
to captain valor.
- About what?
- About a timeship.
- I am warning you.
- Shut up!
I may have the iq of meat,
But I know how to cut a deal.
[dramatic music]
♪
- [screams]
[eerie music]
♪
- [grunts]
- I'm listening.
- You want the waverider.
I want to go home.
- Where is home
for a man like you?
- 2016, central city.
- Of all the places
in time, you want to go there?
- That's right.
To the exact moment hunter
recruited me and my partner
On this suicidal mission
of his,
But, this time,
I'm gonna tell him
where to shove it.
- Let me get this straight.
I let you go,
You'll deliver the waverider.
- Yes.
Do we have an accord?
- You think your friends
will believe
You were able to escape?
Not unless I do this.
[grunting]
- How's it going out there?
- Good.
By which I mean
utterly terrifying.
I'll have the breach sealed
in two more minutes.
- Okay. How's your oxygen level?
- Uh, I think
the technical term is lousy.
- Just two more minutes.
You got this.
- Nothing quite like dying
to make you think
About all the mistakes,
all the wrong choices.
- Is this leonard snart
coming to god
In his final moments?
- Hardly.
- [shivers]
- Just wishing I could take
a few things back.
I should've left mick
in future star city.
- Why didn't you?
- Without me to keep
him in check,
Mick can be a scary guy.
- Agreed.
Hate to break it to you, but
Even if we make it
out of here alive,
You're still gonna have
a problem on your hands.
And I've seen enough to know
That mick's in a dark place.
He's not coming back.
- Man, I can't believe
rory sold us out.
No, actually I can.
But still, man.
- What choice did he have?
The crew left on the waverider
are most probably dead by now,
And god knows what happened
to professor stein.
It's no wonder that mr. Rory
Chose to save his own skin.
And what I can I do about it?
I'm stick in a pirate's brig
and I've lost both my ship
And the loyalty of my crew.
- You're one
to talk about loyalty.
- Oh, but I am, captain baxter,
And not because
I pledged an oath
To serve as a time master,
But a long time ago,
I made
A far more important oath.
When you call me a failure,
captain baxter, you're right.
'cause I failed
both my wife and my son.
For betraying the time council
I have absolutely no regrets.
But failing to save my family?
That is something for which
I will never forgive myself.
[somber music]
♪
- Time master declan?
I thought the tribunal
was re-convening.
- It's been cancelled.
Lieutenant coburn assumed full
responsibility for the affair.
The other time masters
were moved by her argument.
- They've dismissed the charges?
- Once lieutenant coburn
resigned.
- Why would she do that?
- It seems she believes in you.
Now you must prove
to yourself and all of us
That you are indeed the man
she believes you to be.
[electricity powers down]
[dramatic music]
[adventurous music]
I thought we were done for.
- Take heart, dear captain.
This battle is far from over.
Now, who would care
to join me
In a daring escape?
- Space ranger.
- Indeed.
[alarm beeping quickly]
[dramatic music]
- Ray, don't go
nodding off on me.
- No, I wasn't.
[exhales sharply]
I was just resting my eyes
for a second.
- You've got
to stay with me, ray.
Just stay focused on my voice,
and keep talking.
- About what?
- Anything.
Like, um,
What was your first pet's name?
- [chuckles] slinky.
- Is that a cat?
- Burmese python.
Yeah, I'm allergic to cats
and dogs.
Pretty much anything
without scales.
- Okay, then,
enough about pets.
Um, what's your
favorite color?
- Don't have one.
- Who doesn't have
a favorite color?
- It's kind of
like having a favorite beatle.
- No, everyone
has a favorite beatle.
- Not me.
Wouldn't be fair
to the other three.
- Okay, fine,
enough about pets,
And colors, and beatles.
- It's a good thing
we never went for that drink.
This space date
is going terribly.
[alarm beeping rapidly]
♪
- Ray?
Are you still with me, ray?
Ray? Are you there?
- I'm sorry.
It's all I have left.
[triumphant music]
- Ray, are you there?
- It seems that mr. Palmer
patched the hole in the hull,
Allowing mr. Snart
and ms. Lance
To escape the engine room.
- Okay, as soon as he's on
board, I need you
To close the cargo bay
and seal the airlock, gideon.
Ray.
Ray! Hey, stay with me.
- I'm afraid mr. Palmer
has gone into cardiac arrest.
- Please, I can't lose you too!
Ray, I need you! Please!
- His chances of survival
are less than 3,720 to 1.
- Ray!
Ray, come on. You're strong.
Please, ray. Come back to me.
Ray!
[grunting]
- [gasps]
Could you please stop
punching me in the chest?
Why do they always make it seem
like it's a good thing
To do in the movies?
- I thought you were dead.
- I think I was, there,
for a second.
Thank you.
- You kids need a moment?
- You okay?
- Mr. Palmer nearly died.
- Welcome to the club.
Gideon, what's happening
on the acheron?
- Funny you should ask.
I just received a message
from mr. Rory.
It seems he escaped capture
And is now returning
to the waverider.
- Told you.
Those pirates picked
the wrong guy to mess with.
- Since when does rory even know
how to fly the jump ship?
- How did he even find us?
- Actually, I did the flying.
He received quite a beating
At the hands of the pirates.
That's him now.
[suspenseful music]
♪
- You okay, mick?
- Boys!
Ship's all yours!
♪
- You son of a bitch.
- What are you doing, mick?
- I'm getting us home.
Are you in?
[electricity whines]
- Yeah.
Time to choose a side,
I guess.
Chosen.
- Bastard!
Get them!
I'll get the time drive.
- Is the acheron's jump ship
still operational?
- Yes.
- All right, go to it
And get off the acheron.
I some unfinished business
with mr. Valor.
- I'm not leaving my ship.
- And we're
not leaving you behind.
- So what's the plan, captain?
- Valor and his men
substantially outnumber us.
We're not going to be
able to defeat them
By conventional means.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Mr. Rory is making his way
to the engine room
To access the time drive.
- I'll handle it.
♪
- [grunting]
- What's going on?
- You're losing.
- Gilbert?
- The time pirates are indeed
Ten seconds behind you,
and closing.
- That doesn't
give us much time.
- You think
rip's plan will work?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
- Step away from it, mick.
- I'll tell you what, blondie.
Walk away and I won't kill you.
- You know I can't do that.
- I like you, sara.
You got a lot of guts.
That's why I'm only
gonna kill you a little bit!
[both grunting]
[exciting music]
♪
[all grunting]
- Mick!
- Captain hunter?
We're in position.
Captain hunter?
- Yes, yes!
I'm a little bit busy right now!
- Be that as it may,
we've run out of time.
Captain, the plan.
♪
We're waiting
for your signal.
♪
- Gilbert?
- Yes, sir?
- I need you
to listen to me very,
Very carefully.
[alarm blares]
[screaming]
- Rip! We're good!
- [panting]
- bulkhead door closed.
Explosive decompression
has evacuated the time pirates.
- Thank you, gilbert.
Please hail the waverider.
Waverider,
this is captain hunter.
We've regained
control of the acheron.
What's your status?
- What are you gonna do,
snart?
- I suppose
it wouldn't be very fair
If I arrested you
after you reclaimed my ship
And apprehended
john valor for me.
- Happy to help out
a fellow time master.
Even though I don't
deserve that title.
- I was wrong.
You've proven that today.
You're still one hell
of a time master.
Which is why I'm
giving you this.
- What's that?
- Gilbert?
- Using the vanishing point's
most current timeline data,
I calculate a 99.8% probability
That you will find
vandal savage
In harmony falls, oregon,
in March of 1958.
- Thank you, captain baxter.
- I still don't understand
why you're doing all this.
- Before all this started,
I don't think
I would've, either.
- We protect history,
safeguard time itself.
There is no higher calling.
- It's called love.
- Rip. Rip.
Rip!
Look at me, rip.
- [sighs]
- Please don't be mad at me.
- Oh, no, I'm not mad at you!
I--I was going to resign.
- I know
and I couldn't let you.
This has always been
your dream.
- Yes, but you are
so much better at this than me.
I--I can't understand
why you would--
Why you'd give all that up.
- It's funny, because you're
the one who made me realize
That I could never
be a time master.
I found something with you,
Something wonderful.
I found love.
That thing that the time masters
Always taught us to hide from,
But they were wrong, rip.
Love's no threat.
It's beautiful,
and powerful,
And once you know it,
Love changes everything.
Like it changed me
And that's why I have to resign,
Because I could never
belong to something
That turns its back
on the truth.
- Suddenly my chosen
profession seems
So terribly unimportant.
- No.
The world needs
the time masters
And the time masters,
most assuredly,
Need rip hunter.
- [groans]
- my only wish is that one day,
When you're off traveling
space and time,
You'll realize what I have,
and understand
Why I'm doing what I'm doing.
I hope you think of me
when that day comes.
- I will...
Because I'll be with you.
[soft romantic music]
♪
- Hey.
I was just looking for you.
How are you feeling?
- Good. Yeah.
Turns out I bounce back
pretty quickly from hypothermia.
In fact, I managed to remember
some of the things
You said to me
when I was almost dead.
You were wrong, b-t-w.
You don't need me.
You don't need anybody.
I mean,
you're pretty amazing
And I'm lucky
to be your friend,
Be on this mission
together with--
♪
That's...Surprising.
Okay.
I'll say it.
Why don't we just
drop him off back in 2016?
- Because my sister
lives in 2016.
And your sister,
and your wife.
- So what exactly
are we talking about here?
Leaving rory in the brig
until we take down savage?
- No, no, no, no,
the brig is unsuitable
For long-term incarceration.
- Leaving him free run
of the ship is not an option.
- I'll handle it.
- By handling it,
you mean murder?
- I said I'll handle it.
[ominous music]
♪
- [grunts]
[groaning]
- [sighs]
- I told you that'll be
the last time you hit me.
- You were right.
- That the plan?
Take me out
in the middle of nowhere,
Where no one can find the body?
- I wish there were
some other way, mick,
But you're dangerous.
A liability to the team.
- Team?
You and I were a team!
What happened to you?
- People change.
- You think you're
some kind of hero,
But deep down
you're still the same
Punk kid I saved in juvie.
You haven't got the guts.
You want to kill me?
Kill me.
Only one of us is walking
out of here alive.
- You're right.