Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Pairs to being two regular women
on a completely normal first date.
Wally West, I am trying to save
the universe, care to join me?
When Nora was possessed by Mallus,
he seemed scared of my totem.
You're one of the six.
The hunt for the six totems
has begun.
Good evening, Miss Jiwe.
No.
Darling.
Wait.
He may be of value.
You know what getting I think
I have some more
where amazing french toast.
You must have worked up
an appetite last night.
Sara, can we take the Waverider
to when Mount St. Helens erupted?
I've always wanted...
Psych, that would not be
a cool thing to do.
This is, a very important
time vehicle.
We... we would never use it
for recreational
or dangerous purposes.
Hey, Ava.
You look great
in what you were wearing yesterday.
- Right.
- I'm going to...
I'm going to stop talking now, yeah.
Hey, Zari.
This is weird.
Why are there so many dirty dishes?
Ray loves doing dirty dishes.
Oh, yeah.
I also don't hear him spewing
the neurological benefits
of putting butter in his coffee.
Gideon, where's Ray?
I don't know.
But we are being hailed
by the Time Bureau.
Put them on.
Hello, Legends and Agent Sharpe.
What is it, Gary?
This was just delivered to us.
There was a, a Palmer Tech
phone hidden inside
with a message recorded on it.
Hey, guys, if you're finding this,
it's me, Ray, obviously.
You've probably guessed by now,
that I have been abducted
by the Darhks.
Hey, when we see him, do we tell him
we didn't even notice he was gone?
Yeah, definitely not.
The Darhks said
that they'd let go of me
when they were done with me.
He is asking me if I want to see
a Grateful Dead concert,
which is really kind of weird.
But look, you'll probably
try to come after me and find me.
If you do,
he said that he'll kill me,
so, you know,
please don't do that.
Okay, bye.
Okay, I have done as you asked,
so no more torture today, right?
I really don't think you understand
how this whole torture thing works.
Work.
Work, work, come on.
Why won't this stupid thing work?
That stupid thing has been
in my family for generations.
It should've been mine.
Well, it's mine now.
Besides, Mallus wishes
for only his most devoted followers
to wield totems
and you already have one.
Now, why can't I access its powers?
Because power is all it is to you.
Until you find a selfless reason
to wield it,
my grandmother's bond to the totem,
even at a distance,
will remain stronger than yours.
What about this Fire Totem
I stole in Detroit?
- Afraid of a broken trinket?
- That thing killed me once.
Even in pieces,
it's still to be feared.
Totems are eternal.
They can never be destroyed.
So they can be fixed?
Oh, so I can get a necklace myself?
It would take a truly brilliant mind
to figure out how.
You guys hungry?
I could really go for some eggs,
poached, runny.
Oh, my coffee with grass-fed butter
and MCT oil.
Are you sure
we should be looking for Ray
after he told us not to?
- What the hell are you doing here?
- Ditto.
I thought you said
they'd be psyched to see us.
Look, I know
what you're both thinking,
but if you'd just let me explain.
If you're here to apologize
for burgling the Bureau
and... and, and humiliating Gary...
Well, we actually did that
for a good reason,
- because we have to stop "Mollusk".
- Yeah.
- Mallus.
And, yes, we know all about him.
Sara basically met him.
And you're here,
because the Time Bureau
has finally come to its senses, or...
- Ava and I are...
- Working together, independently.
Right, Wally, it's good to see you.
I remember you from Barry
and Iris's wedding.
Yeah, wasn't that so fun?
It was such a beautiful ceremony.
The hors d'oeuvres were, like, meh.
- And then, the Nazi invasion.
- The what?
All right, you guys still haven't
told us why you're on the ship.
Atoning...
I hope.
I should never have kept
you both in the dark.
The deaths of those agents
and the return of Damien Darhk
will haunt me
for the rest of my days.
But surely, you understand
the gravity now of what we're facing.
- Hey.
- Nate, my brother.
What are you doing here?
- Hey, man.
- Oh, man.
What the hell are you doing here?
Any sign of Ray?
Oh, no, just another
Grateful Dead end.
- I for sure got a contact-high.
- Yeah.
And I managed to swipe
Jerry Garcia's glasses.
Once a thief, always a thief.
No, we... we allow light
to moderate theft on this ship.
We like to call them souvenirs.
It's okay, it's okay.
No, no, no.
No, not gonna do it.
You and I both realize
that your idiot friends
are gonna search
every Dead show in history
before they realize
that I don't even like jam bands.
Be that as it may,
I will not fix the Fire Totem.
Sorry.
You're gonna have to kill me.
- Suit yourself.
- No, no, no.
Hold on a second, sweetie.
I think I'm gonna give
this suit to Genghis Khan.
Imagine what history would be like
if the Mongols
had a dwarf star-powered
rocket man.
The Legends will just find
the anachronism and fix it.
Good point, way to go, Ray.
Maybe I will just murder
a young Sandy Palmer
picking her sons up
from Ivy Springs Day Care, 1982.
I'll need a lab.
UPSWIPZ HQ 2018
Hi, Alan.
- Sorry, Alan.
- What the hell, Ray? You quit.
There's no take-backs in Upswipz.
Oh, you're the up-and-down guy.
Me, I prefer side to side.
Our focus groups found
up and down was more intuitive.
Okay, wait, wait.
You know, he might be right.
We think it shifts the paradigm.
Oh, you have your lab.
Now, get to work, nerd.
We are still not any closer
to finding Ray.
Nate, I need you hitting those books.
Look for any sign of him.
Gideon, scan the anachronism map.
Something pops up, you let us know.
- Rory...
- Crush a six-pack.
You do what you do.
I'll head back to the Bureau,
put our resources on it, too.
I have an idea.
- It's a little experimental.
- I'm listening.
Well, we know that Ray
is with the Darhks
and so is my totem.
If I meditate with Zari
using her totem to anchor me,
I think I can reach out
to the Ancestral Plane.
- If we find my totem, then...
- Then you find Ray.
Meditation?
I've actually been doing
a lot of that
and I think I could help you.
Perfect, make it happen.
Sweetie, you think it's too early
for me to, you know,
get back out there?
I mean, how long should
I mourn your mother?
It's been 23 years on my end, Dad.
I say go for it.
Thank you.
Trouble is, I haven't had
a single match yet.
I think the thing is broken.
If I may...
You might have more luck
if you talk about your hobbies.
I just said that I enjoy
destroying the world
to remake it in my image.
Oh, I like trying new restaurants.
Also, your profile says
you're 199 years old.
Yeah, it, it wouldn't go any higher.
Can you fix that?
Well, everyone lies
about their age, brah.
- Can you please stop fooling around?
- Nora-doll.
What's the point of living
if you can't have a bit of fun?
Well, I'm not enjoying myself.
- I'm annoyed.
- Hi, Annoyed.
I'm Dad.
Right? That's good.
Fine.
No.
Okay, I have analyzed the shards.
We'd have to go back
to the Big Bang
in order to get enough energy
to reignite the Fire Totem.
That or invent cold fusion.
- And since that's not possible...
- Yes, it is.
Cold fusion was invented in 1962
by a German physicist
named Bernhard Vogal.
Yeah, no.
- See, I'm kind of a science dork.
- Kind of?
And if someone had invented
cold fusion, let alone in 1962,
I think I'd have heard of it.
Actually there's a very good reason
why you haven't.
The reason you've never heard
of Bernhard Vogal
is because the most ruthless
and efficient assassin
the world has ever known
made sure that no one ever did.
Me.
Killing Vogal
was one of my greatest hits.
Someone developed an energy source
that could have replaced fossil fuels
and essentially save the world?
While putting the oil industry
out of business.
Some very powerful people
with some very deep pockets
wouldn't stand for it,
so they hired me.
He was waiting for transfer,
holed up in an East Berlin
safe house,
somewhat of a misnomer in this case
when your old man got involved.
And you buried the secret
to cold fusion?
And the man who created it.
Yeah, I know, that was implied.
Well I guess I'm off to East Berlin
to stop myself from killing Vogal.
Should be fun.
You watch the prisoner
and I'll bring you back
some chocolate.
Oh, who am I kidding?
I'm probably gonna get a hat
for myself, too.
No, I'm going.
To 1962 Berlin?
Too dangerous.
If your younger self sees you,
it could change the course
of your entire life.
All right, obviously,
you haven't been listening.
We're talking about going back
against me in my prime.
You don't stand a chance, Nora-doll.
We're partners,
I can do this mission.
Or you could just
call the whole thing off.
This is obviously causing
a lot of family tension.
- Shut up.
All right, tell me your plan.
We return to 1962
and convince Dr. Vogal
that we're American agents
there to help him.
Then we jump straight back
to this moment.
Oh, I'm sorry.
We? Are you taking him?
Dr. Vogal needs to trust us fast,
which means he needs a peer.
Someone who speaks nerd.
You better come right back,
you two, do you understand me?
And use protection.
- I think he's warming to me.
- Just go, God.
EAST BERLIN 1962
Just follow my lead
and we'll be out of here
before my dad even shows up.
My God, what's he doing...
Be quiet and listen.
Your life depends on it.
Are you decent?
We're the CIA,
here to take you back to America.
No, West Berlin.
As I told your British friends,
I, I will not speak a word
about cold fusion
until I am reunited with my family.
Touching, but not our mission.
We'll get you back to your family,
but first, you have to come
with us, it's not safe here.
Wait, I, I have to get something
from the other room.
- A doll for my daughter.
- No, no, no.
No, there's no time.
There's an assassin
on his way here right now
and trust me, he's not very nice.
I will not leave here
without that doll.
Can I hurt him yet?
Hurt me?
Wait, you are not CIA.
Help, intru...
Release him.
Stand back.
Oh, crap.
What happened to your magic fingers?
That virus you shot me with
must be affecting my powers.
We got to get out of here
before more guards come,
or worse, your dad.
Dr. Vogal.
Hey, we're here to save you.
Hey, who are you?
Hey.
Hello.
No.
See?
Who needs magic?
- Hold
- Stand down.
Run.
Okay, I believe you.
Get me out of here.
Time-jump us out of here.
Oh, crap, there goes our exit.
Well, back to basics.
So I just eat this Lyoga root
and it's, boom, vision quest?
No.
That much would kill you.
This tea has plenty to take you
to the world between worlds.
We'll use your totem to anchor us
while we look for any signs of mine
and, hopefully, Ray along with it.
The incense will calm you
and I'm just gonna ease you
into the altered state
through some guided meditation.
- Thank you for helping us.
- Yeah.
So, how do you know Nathaniel?
I was kind of like his
wingman back in Central City.
Just helped him
get over a broken heart, actually,
because this basic bitch
just dumped him on his birthday.
Can you believe that?
Yeah, because I was actually
that basic bitch.
Great vibe, Wally.
- I think we can take it from here.
- Yeah, yeah, okay, I'm gonna go.
Okay.
No worries.
That's a classic
first-attempt blunder.
Happens to the Legends all the time,
sometimes twice on the same mission.
All we need to do is regroup
and come up with plan B.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Plan B.
Tell us the formula for cold fusion,
or I'll break your fingers.
No.
The formula can die with me.
Oh, I'm not gonna kill you.
- You'll just wish I had.
- Nora, just put it down.
- Torture is not the answer.
- Yeah, but it's fun either way.
Do your worst.
I've already faced
the most terrible pain
that a man can endure.
The prospect that
he will never again see
the ones he holds most dear.
The doll, it's your daughters?
I only had enough money
for papers for my wife and daughter.
So when they left,
Greta wanted me to keep it...
with the promise that I would
bring it back to her soon.
So...
Torture me all you want, Fraulein.
I swear, I will never give up
my secret until I am with my family.
This was supposed to be simple,
in and out.
Now, we're stuck here in this dump.
Damn it.
My father still thinks
I'm a little kid.
Now, he's gonna lord it over me
that he's stronger than me,
that we're not equals and that if...
that I failed.
It's not all bad.
We have extended Dr. Vogal's life
past its normal expiration date.
- What?
- So, all we have to do is
just get him across the border
and then he'll talk, right?
Of course.
Why didn't I think of that?
We'll just mosey across
the most heavily guarded
border in all of history.
Yeah.
- Is that sarcasm?
- No.
No, that's not sarcasm.
Yes, it's sarcasm.
Look, it's not gonna work.
- Without magic, it's impossible.
- Nothing's impossible.
We thought cold fusion
was impossible.
So you don't have magic.
Young Darhk is no match
for our brains and determination.
And you know what?
It's high time you showed your dad
what's really inside you.
Besides a demon.
Dr. Vogal, where does one go
to acquire forged papers?
Looks like our master forger's
changed occupations.
This was the address I was given.
Perhaps we should come back
during the day.
You really think we'll live
to see morning
with you-know-who on our tail?
Wait.
Don't judge a storefront by its hats.
Let's get to work.
First, the documents
must be flawless.
Then, we need the right
set of wheels.
Only diplomatic vehicles are the ones
to be waved across the checkpoint.
Guten abend.
You look like a yummy
morsel, Fraulein.
How much for a little taste?
How about your car?
And last but not least,
the most important
part of any time-travel mission,
disguises.
Legends never go
anywhere without them.
Thank you so much, and again,
sorry for ruining your night.
They should've been back
an hour ago.
Was I not clear when I said,
"Come right back, no dawdling?"
I think I was crystal clear
on that point.
You know, maybe you're right.
Maybe she is testing me,
pushing her curfew
to see how I react.
Am I being paranoid?
Maybe you're right.
Maybe I'm not being paranoid enough.
Maybe she needs me
to be more involved.
I mean, for her,
I've been gone for 20 years.
Oh, think of everything
that I've missed.
Life was so much simpler
before fatherhood.
So much anxiety.
You know, you're right, Alan.
I need to take action,
not wallow in doubt.
I'm going after them.
Thanks, pal.
Great chat.
Don't worry, Nora.
Daddy's coming.
Remember our story.
Yeah.
Now is probably
not the right time to mention
that I'm a...
that I'm a terrible liar.
Try and imagine my surprise.
Papers?
What were you doing in East Berlin?
We... we were at the opera.
For the whole night?
Opera was a... a very long show.
Big show, good show.
We have the best shows.
Very long, very big, but very good...
Is there some problem?
I just find it odd you're returning
at this hour of the morning.
We made a proper night of it.
I must run this by my supervisor.
(Foreign Language)
You stay back, stay back.
Do you know who my husband is?
You know what?
Do bring your supervisor over.
I want him to know just how idiotic
his underlings are.
- Excuse me, sir.
- Of course, I... I see it now.
I'm sorry, mein Herr.
I, I did not recognize you in that...
hat.
You, on the other hand,
are a fantastic liar.
Oh, no. It's my dad.
Yeah, hit man Darhk's gonna kill us.
Not that dad. That dad.
Oh, he's definitely gonna kill me.
I was supposed
to have you home by now.
What the hell are you doing here?
Saving you, Nora-doll.
And is that any way
to speak to your father?
Safety first. Strap in, kids.
Floor it.
I could've handled myself back there.
I didn't need your help.
For the love of Mallus,
would you stop
with the hat thing already?
Oh, hi.
Is all of this just a game to you?
Because I feel like I'm the only one
taking any of this seriously.
Well, since my Time Stone
still works,
we're gonna do things my way.
We're gonna bring
the good doctor back to 2018
and torture him until he talks.
Torture isn't the answer.
Says who?
He knows his secret is the only way
he'll ever see his daughter again,
because unlike some fathers,
he values his family
more than himself.
I just saved your life back there.
What...
Honey bunny, listen...
Look at me, don't you know
that I've only ever had
your best interests at heart?
Was it in my best interest or yours
when you pushed a scared little girl
into the arms of a demon?
- Yeah, to bring us back together.
- To bring you back to life.
What has gotten into you?
I send you off on one lousy mission
by yourself, and suddenly the...
Oh, of course.
I should have known Ray Palmer
would be a good influence on you.
Perhaps I should give you
two some privacy.
You know what?
I thought I raised my father
from the dead,
but instead I see
I just got a selfish man-child.
"Man-child"?
Why don't you run along
to your little hellscape
and boo-hoo to Mallus?
Because now, that you're
a demon's mouthpiece,
it's obvious you don't need me.
Nora, I...
- Nora.
- Leave me alone, Dad.
No, that's good.
Just... just keep talking.
So, Ray's nowhere to be found
and things are getting worse
at the Bureau.
Bennett is so stubborn,
he's refusing any meetings
with Rip that don't involve shackles.
I'm so sorry. Here I am babbling
about Bureau politics,
and your friend is in trouble.
How are you holding up?
Mutilating photos of your nemesis.
Got it.
Well, at least our nonverbal
communication skills
are off to a good start.
Everything that we're doing
to find Ray,
it's turning up empty.
Hey, you're gonna get Ray back,
I promise.
Can we have a little bit more
of some nonverbal communication?
I... I, I thought you said
this place was beautiful.
Yeah, it was.
Something's wrong.
You shouldn't be
walking around alone.
Stop treating...
You.
Expecting someone else?
You know, the last time I saw Nora,
she was still Daddy's little girl.
And before you know it...
20 years passes just like that.
And, sure, we're traveling
through time together,
plotting the end of the world, but...
I'm left wondering,
where is that little girl
and how do I get her back?
Look, I'm not keeping you alive
for my health.
Speak.
See...
If you really care that much
about Nora,
then maybe you shouldn't let her be
a conduit for a primordial evil.
I admit, this isn't the life
that I wanted for her, but...
world domination was supposed
to be my gift to her,
not her career path.
Then maybe
you should tell her how you feel.
She's under a lot of pressure,
you know.
- And it's all to impress you.
- Me?
I am so proud of Nora.
Obviously she knows that.
She only knows
what you say to her, Damien.
Can I call you Damien?
- Yeah?
- I have the girl.
Nora?
If you hurt her, I swear...
Meet me on the rooftop
of the Schneider Cement building.
An even exchange.
Her life for the scientist.
I am gonna kick my ass.
What is it? Is it Nora?
- Is she okay?
- She's alive.
His life for hers.
He wants to meet in one hour.
I should've just listened.
This is all my fault.
- If I lose her...
- Look, it seems like
- you're having trouble with a knot.
- I am.
Okay, well, you're probably slipping
the slack through the half-hitch.
- How do you know that?
- Because I'm an Eagle Scout.
Trust me.
Look, I, I fought you lots of times.
Together, we can save Nora.
Just give me back my suit.
Oh, sure,
and after we save my daughter,
maybe we can go shoot some hoops
and grab a brewski.
Now, that's a good knot.
One therapy session
does not make us friends.
You are still gonna die
when I'm done with you.
You...
There's no reason
why we can't collaborate.
We'll take the doctor for a few days
and give him back
when we're done with him.
You don't want to talk
about your plan even a little bit?
Oh, the plan is simple.
I'm going to kill you.
Hey, you know, I think we should go.
No, not yet.
It's like I can feel
my totem everywhere in here,
but it feels different.
You're still here.
What happened to this place?
The longer your totem
is in the possession of darkness,
the more it is corrupted.
I am fighting it,
but I cannot resist forever.
I'll get my totem back, I promise.
You must get Kuasa back as well.
She needs you.
And soon you will need her.
What for?
The first totem bearers
imprisoned a great evil
- and if he breaks free...
- You mean Mallus?
Do not say his name here.
He cannot enter your world,
but this is the world between worlds.
Time does not exist here
and time is his cage.
And the further time is broken,
the closer the demon
comes to break him free.
This is why Darhk and his allies
are creating anachronisms.
And if you do not stop them,
all of time is at risk.
Nora.
- If you hurt her, I...
- I want to see the scientist.
Now, give me back my daughter,
you cocky little bastard.
Nora!
No!
I got you. I won't let you fall.
This is why I'll never have kids.
They make you weak.
Dad!
Magic.
I should look into that.
I got you.
Activate suit.
Voice authentication denied.
Okay. Suit, fire Atom Blaster.
Dr. Palmer, voice authenticated.
Okay, reduce Atom Blaster
power by 99 percent.
Target...
45 degrees to the left,
10 degrees down.
Make it 10.1 degrees.
And...
Fire?
Nora.
Dad...
You have to let me go.
No. I won't.
If you don't, you'll die.
No.
I can't lose you, not again.
I'll be okay.
I love you.
Why won't you die?
Because I have something
to live for.
The totem, it's turned.
She has claimed its power.
Okay, we need to get out of here.
No. You must leave, my children.
Run.
Looks like you still got it, old man.
Who you calling old man?
I look good for 257.
I've always wanted to do that.
Nice one, honey.
Got them.
Dr. Vogal, you okay?
A Roboter man?
No, no, it's me.
Look, we got to get you out of here.
I can't make it.
It's too late for me.
Here, take this.
No. No, you're gonna get it back
to Greta yourself.
The doll was never hers.
Everything you need to know
about cold fusion...
it's all in there.
I'm not gonna leave you here.
Your family needs you
and the planet
needs your brilliant mind.
Okay.
No.
Well, I wasn't gonna let him
ruin my perfect record.
Excuse me.
Where do you think you're going
with that doll, Ray?
I promised Vogal
I'd get this back to his daughter.
If I've learned one thing
from all of this,
it's that you're a terrible liar.
Give me the doll.
Sorry, Nora.
I can't do that.
Come on, you and I both know
you're not gonna shoot me.
You're right.
What was that?
It's a time quake.
Gideon, what's the source?
An Aberration has occurred in 1962.
It appears that someone has blasted
a hole in the Berlin Wall.
- Ray.
- Which appears to be the straw
that broke the camel's back.
I'm guessing that's bad.
Yeah, those are tears
in the fabric of time itself.
Gideon, plot a course
for East Berlin, 1962.
All right, kid, you're up.
Let's see how fast you really are.
Okay, you're gonna want to hold on.
Oh, see you.
Speedsters?
I hate speedsters.
Almost as much as I hate that guy.
- Look who I bumped into.
- Hey.
- Buddy.
Ray, thank God you're back.
Yeah, dishes need cleaning.
And I can't wait to get them done.
Rip, nice to see...
Wait, is it nice to see Rip?
Yeah. Yeah.
- Oh, okay.
- I hope that your abduction
afforded you some insights
into our opponent's designs.
Yes, they needed me to reignite
the Fire Totem, using this.
Another doll.
How wonderful.
Well, no, actually it's...
- Oh, she...
- The secret to cold fusion,
which is pretty epic.
Now, all we're missing
is the Fire Totem.
Oh, you mean this?
Yeah.
How do you get this?
Well, I saw it
in Damien Darhk's pocket
and I thought, "Yo, that
would make a sick souvenir."
- What?
- Well, great.
I can get to work putting
this back together right now.
Then it'll be three against two.
And with yours,
it'll be four to one.
Good to see you.
- Good to see you.
- Yeah, welcome back.
We found out that my totem
has been corrupted
when we were on our vision quest.
But we did find out
why the Darhks are so psyched
about anachronisms.
The more the timeline's corrupted,
the weaker the prison
holding Mallus becomes.
If they continue destroying history,
the demon will be freed.
You should inform the Time Bureau.
Immediately.
Gideon, patch us
through to Director Bennett, please.
Make it fast, Agent Sharpe,
because I've got to stop
Alexander Hamilton
from seeing Hamilton the musical.
How's it possible that everyone
got tickets to that but me?
Director Bennett,
we have some developments
in the Mallus investigation
that you need to be aware of.
Such as your arresting
Director Hunter?
I, haven't arrested him
- exactly yet.
- Look, we got bigger problems
right now, than punishing Rip
for what happened to those agents.
I doubt those deceased agents
would agree with you, Miss Lance.
Now, you place Hunter
in handcuffs this instant,
or you're all going to...
- Oh, my God.
- It's Grodd, actually.
Ava, I'm so sorry.
He was a good man, I think.
Yes, most unfortunate.
I believe that this tragedy makes you
the highest-ranking official
at the Bureau.
May I return to work...
Director Sharpe?
Yes.
Thank you for searching
all of history
to save me from
a demented supervillain.
Two demented supervillains.
Are you forgetting the apple
of Damien Darhk's eye?
She's had a tough life.
She may come off all mean
and witchy but,
underneath all that,
she's a real person.
Wait.
Do you have the hots for Nora Darhk?
What? No.
No. No?
Look, I'm not blind. She's hot.
But she's also bonkers, which is...
kind of hot.
I just think that...
You know,
maybe there's hope for her.
You would, you big softie.
But you're a delicate flower,
Raymond Palmer.
Take care of that heart of yours.
Wally.
Hey.
I just wanted to say,
good job out there.
Are you sticking around?
No, I, I might join Rip
at the Time Bureau instead.
Right. Yeah, I mean, I get that.
If you want to go hang out
with a bunch of stiffs
instead of the cool kids, but, yeah.
Well, I'm kind of getting,
like, a weird vibe here.
Like, I feel like Mick and Zari
both hate me already
and the others are probably
not that far behind, so...
So, what?
I mean, when Nate first arrived,
he threw Ray into the Temporal Zone.
Amaya beat everybody up.
Zari tricked us
into pulling off a heist.
And Mick, well, he's betrayed us
at least 10 times.
I mean, we're kind of like
the all-stars
of bad first impressions, so...
I think you'd fit in great.
Wally, there you are.
Ready to leave?
I'm actually gonna stay.
I was hoping you would.
Well, I wish we could stay longer,
but my boss
was just murdered by a gorilla,
not to mention the mess
in Berlin that needs fixing.
Well, call me.
Until next time, Captain Lance.
Until next time, Agent Hunter.
Director Sharpe.
So...
you and Miss Lance.
I, I think
there's something real there.
Yep, she's, she's special.
And so are you.
Gideon, delete file 354-Z.
Sara can never find out
the truth about Ava.
Yes, Director Hunter.
I thought you were getting
a breath of fresh air.
Well, I felt like an apology
was in order.
I lost the Fire Totem
and I know how much
it meant to you
and to the big guy, Mallus.
But I also remember something
that used to bring a smile
to your face.
Hot chocolate
with whipped cream
and caramel sauce.
Oh, wow. I haven't had
one of these since...
Since I came and told you
to join the Order.
Since I sent you
into the arms of a demon.
I'm glad you did.
- It brought us back together.
- No.
I never should've doubted
your strength.
Look, I know you feel
a lot of pressure
to be like your old man,
but I just want you to know that...
I'm proud of you,
no matter what.
Oh, I think there's something
in my eye there.
I think I saw some Brandy back there
for our hot chocolate.
Let me go get some.
Everything okay, Nora-doll?
I'm fine, Daddy.