RIP: In 2166,
an immortal tyrant named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan is opposed
by the body I had sworn my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered as legends.
RIP: Previously, on
Legends of Tomorrow...
We're in the Temporal Zone,
I don't understand.
No one should be able to--
GIDEON: A scan of the vessel suggests
that it is the bounty hunter Chronos.
We're crash landing.
In both place and time.
RIP: Gideon, camouflage the ship.
This doesn't look like
the type of place
we want to linger out in the open.
That looks a lot
like a Palmer Tech building,
but why does it have a Smoak logo on it?
Wait, this is Star City.
I thought you said the timeline was safe.
Yes, Star City was intact in 2016.
This... This is 2046.
Don't move.
- Thank God.
- I said, don't move.
It's me. It's Sara.
Hey, Oliver, look.
I know it's been a long time,
but don't you remember that Rip Hunter
recruited us to become Legends?
I never heard of any Legends.
RIP: Get back!
This guy a friend of yours?
I don't like him.
- What are you doing?
- It's called shooting back.
This can't be the Green Arrow.
(GRUNTING)
That's not Oliver Queen.
Sure dresses like him.
Shoots arrows like him.
Well, whoever he is,
I don't plan on sticking around
to get shish-kebabed by this dude.
Kid's right.
Let's stay behind and kill him.
We need to return to the ship!
All right, Rip,
tell us the truth.
You've all seen how
the timeline is malleable,
in flux until it is set.
Well, this future is not set.
Remember when I told you it was dangerous
for any of you to know too much
about your own futures?
Well, the events that you dread
could very well come to be
due to your actions to prevent them.
You know what I think?
I think you think too much.
Believe me when I tell you
that the best thing for
yourselves and for this mission
is to make the repairs
to the Waverider here in 2046,
then head back to your own time
and make sure that
none of this ever comes to be.
It looks like the whole
propulsion system is jacked.
How do you even know
what we're looking at here?
Doesn't matter if it takes you
down the road or through time,
an engine's still an engine.
How long will it take you
to make repairs?
I'm not too sure, but it would go
a lot faster if I had some help.
Maybe Kendra could lend me a hand?
Enlist whoever is free to help.
I have this to contend with.
This is the neuromorphic interface
for Gideon's logic and navigation matrix.
Without it, Gideon cannot function.
Well, that explains how we got
stranded here in the future.
Palmer Tech was working on
a self-learning neuromorphic cortex.
They surely would've
gone to prototype by 2046.
We are gonna need that prototype.
Oh, Palmer Tech is now
Smoak Technologies,
but I'm sure I can still get us in.
As I said, we must keep you and Ms. Lance
separate from your future homes.
In any case,
there's a reason
why I recruited individuals
adept at misappropriating
others' property.
It's not money, it's not jewels,
it's not a valuable artifact.
You're just lucky I'd steal
anything right about now.
- As I suspected.
- We'll get your gizmo.
You just get this bucket flying again.
- I'm coming with.
- No. No, you are not.
You're too emotionally
connected to this city.
- We've been over this--
- I'm over you.
You've got us on a mission
to change the timeline for yourself,
and you won't even let us
look at our futures?
Now, I know this city
better than anyone else
and you're going to need me out there.
So, either I'm coming with,
or we can find out if the Time Masters
are as good at teaching people to fight
as the League of Assassins.
- (BEEPS)
- (DOOR OPENS)
So, the rest of the team's on
a field trip to Palmer Tech,
now Smoak Technologies.
Palmer Tech sounds better,
right? Be honest.
Honestly, they sound about the same.
Even assuming our compatriots return
with a neuromorphic prototype,
we'll still need to prepare
Gideon for the new device.
And the engines could
definitely use some loving.
Actually, I could use
an extra pair of hands.
Oh, Raymond, why don't you
and Ms. Saunders
continue repairing Gideon?
And I'll assist Jefferson
with the engines.
(SIGHS)
RORY: If this is just
a potential future,
it doesn't matter
if we kill anyone here, right?
Well, to avoid the risk of a paradox,
it's probably best
to refrain from killing anyone.
I'm not gonna promise anything.
My sister's apartment
used to be over here.
I seem to remember
something about your father
being a police captain?
Your point?
He did one hell of a job.
My father, and everyone else,
would never have let this happen.
Unless they were all dead.
(CHUCKLES)
You really are pretty good at this.
Yeah, I was a shipyard welder in 1944.
- No way! A real-life Rosie the Riveter?
- (LAUGHS)
KENDRA: (OVER RADIO) Is there anything
you can't manage
to put a positive spin on?
RAY: (OVER RADIO) Uh...
- I've got it! DMV.
- (KENDRA LAUGHING)
So you do have a dark side.
Are you making fun of me?
A little bit.
Doesn't mean I don't find your
unwavering optimism enjoyable.
- I find watching you weld enjoyable.
- (KENDRA LAUGHS)
Dr. Palmer, in case you weren't aware,
you are on an open channel
and we can hear everything you're saying.
Is it too much to ask for some
professionalism around here?
Why am I getting so upset?
PROFESSOR STEIN: One moment, please.
(BEEPS)
I'm not upset. You're upset.
No, I'm not.
My elevated blood pressure
confirms that you are.
I'm just... (SIGHS)
I'm just getting annoyed
that those two are talking
instead of working. I mean...
- You like her.
- Dude, you're being crazy.
You do remember that we
share a psychic connection.
I can sense what you're feeling--
If that were true, then you would shut up.
Hey, it's no day at the beach
for me, either. Believe me.
It doesn't matter 'cause I don't
stand a chance with her anyway.
Now, why would you say that?
Because right now, my competition is
a billionaire genius
who built his own super-suit
and some other dude
she's known for 4,000 years
who she's destined to be with.
If I may offer one word of advice--
I really wish you wouldn't.
That word would be "confidence."
You've met my younger self.
I was quite the ladies' man.
Put yourself out there.
Good things will happen.
Palmer Tech's just two blocks up this way.
At least it used to be.
- (YELLING)
- Take cover in there!
(GUNSHOTS)
It's like World War III out there.
It's beautiful!
- We need to find another route.
- (GUNSHOTS)
(GRUNTING)
(RORY LAUGHING)
Ms. Lance, don't.
Sara! Damn it!
You two, don't move. We'll be right back.
Right.
We're not gonna sit here, right?
Imagine all the looting
we can do in this chaos.
Or we stretch our legs at that bank
we passed three blocks back.
Drop your weapons,
and hand over your wallets.
Wait, are you actually trying to mug us?
What is this, amateur hour?
If you don't do what my man says,
we're gonna crush you into the
pavement like a couple of ants.
Really?
What do you say
we teach these fellas a lesson?
Yeah.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(LAUGHS)
(GRUNTS)
That's what you get when
you don't follow directions.
Interesting. Hold this.
(GRUNTING)
On second thought...
(GANG MEMBERS EXCLAIMING)
Where'd ya get that?
eBay.
Now, your boss will not be needing this.
Well, this has been fun,
but I think it's time to leave.
"Leave"?
Why would we leave?
(LAUGHS)
Come on, sweetheart.
(ENGINES REVVING)
(GANG MEMBERS WHOOPING)
Don't move.
You.
You are persistent.
I saw you get shot point-blank.
It's high-density Kevlar.
Now, who the hell are you?
- Who are you?
- I'm the Green Arrow.
Oliver Queen is the Green Arrow.
No, he's not. Oliver Queen is dead.
How did Oliver die?
I don't know. No one does.
No one's seen him since...
Well, since the Uprising.
Uprising?
It's just what people called it when...
Well, when all this happened.
15 years ago, he brought an army with him.
Who brought an army?
MAN: I did.
No. It's not possible.
How did you get off Lian Yu?
Say something, damn it!
Ms. Lance? Who is this?
Somebody very dangerous.
Then now is not the right time
for me to say it,
but please remind me later
to tell you that I told you so.
How are you still alive, Slade?
Slade.
(LAUGHING)
That's a name
I haven't heard in a long time.
How do you know my father?
He called you Ms. Lance.
Any relation to the late Captain Lance?
If so, you must have heard
stories about my father.
I knew your father.
He was insane.
Seems to run in the family.
I'm going to enjoy killing you.
Or we will!
(GREEN ARROW GASPS)
Okay, bad idea.
(GRUNTING) Come on!
All right.
Grey and I have got
the mains back online.
Great. Uh, Ray's working on something
called the quantum manifold. Eh...
I can't seem to get this to cooperate.
Let me give it a try.
(BEEPS)
Hey, you actually seem to know
what you're doing here.
Well, yeah, machines are kinda my thing.
Plus, I've been looking
at the instruction manual
in my downtime, so...
(CHUCKLES) Most people can't
follow the instructions
to build their new bookcase,
- and here you are working on a spaceship.
- (CHUCKLES)
A time-traveling spaceship
from the future, no less.
Well, when you put it like that,
I am kinda amazing.
- And humble.
- (LAUGHS)
Hey. If you ever have any bookcases
that need putting together...
I'll know who to call.
So, Raymond.
When you were working
with Kendra earlier,
I couldn't help but notice there
might have been a little spark.
Really?
Oh, yes.
(CHUCKLING) It was quite apparent.
And if I'm not mistaken,
I've noticed her throwing
one or two glances your way.
- Huh.
- Mmm-hmm.
- That's surprising.
- Is it?
Well, yeah.
I don't know. I hadn't really
considered her in that way.
Why are you bringing this up? (SCOFFS)
Geez, I feel like
I'm back in high school.
I honestly wouldn't know.
I skipped tenth grade.
And eleventh.
I haven't really spent
that much time with Kendra.
Other than time that we shared with her
and her reincarnated soulmate,
or people trying to kill us.
All the more reason
to avoid personal attachments.
The ship may be large,
but our group is small.
Hmm.
Yeah. Preaching to the choir, Professor.
We're aboard the Waverider
to save the world, not hook up.
Yes. Quite right.
- (ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING)
- (WHISTLING, HOOTING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey, you!
I'm terrible with names.
I'm gonna call you Fonzie.
- MAN 1: Yeah!
- And call you Kenickie.
- ALL: Yeah!
- Anyone else here need a name?
Your Highness, can I get
a moment of your time, please?
Sure.
(GRUNTS)
Isn't the future great?
We really should be
getting back to Rip and Sara.
Why?
Because I'm not looking to
put down roots here.
Why not? It's everything
we've ever wanted.
I've got a gang that does
everything I tell 'em to.
I've got a fur coat.
I've got a chalice.
Speaking of...
What about stopping Savage?
What about it? You were the one who said
we're in this for the score, remember?
We could live like kings here.
No cops, no heroes.
Just some fool in a green hoodie.
It's Christmas every day.
Ah. My sweets.
(SIGHS) Slade had a son?
Look, Oliver tried.
He tried to raise an army
to fight Deathstroke, but...
Look, everyone just wanted to evacuate.
How can you save a city
that doesn't want to be saved?
A moment.
Sara, I know what you must be thinking,
but none of what has
transpired here is your fault.
Nor do you have the means to change it.
But Vandal Savage's future is preventable.
I implore you, please,
stay focused on our mission.
We're very grateful for your assistance,
but we really must be moving
along to Smoak Technologies.
What for? That place
has been cleared out for years.
But a lot of Felicity Smoak's
projects got relocated.
Where?
Come on.
You didn't say that Felicity's
equipment would be here.
Well, where else did you think it'd be?
(RIP WHISTLES)
Mr. Queen's base of operations
appears to have seen better days.
GREEN ARROW: Yeah, well...
The place got attacked
after Grant Wilson
outed Queen as the Green Arrow.
Let's just find what we're
looking for and get out of here.
MAN: Whoever's there, get out!
I said, get out!
(GUN COCKS)
Whoever you are, get out.
Oliver?
Hello, Sara.
Long time no see.
- Is that...
- GREEN ARROW: Oliver Queen.
Everyone thinks that you're dead.
They're not wrong.
Put the arrow down, John.
You're embarrassing yourself.
- John?
- John Diggle, Jr.
My dad is dead
because I couldn't save him.
I don't deserve his name.
I'm Connor Hawke.
So, you won't take his name,
but it's all right to parade
around in someone else's outfit?
Well, someone has to.
Because the last time that
I checked, you were dead.
Everyone thought you were dead.
I've been trying to
hold this city by myself
because I thought you were gone.
What happened to you?
To Laurel, to my dad, Felicity--
They're gone. All of them.
What do you mean?
- Ollie--
- They're gone.
What do you want me to say, Sara?
30 years ago, you and Ray
hopped on a spaceship
and you never came back.
We will.
I don't want to say that
things would have ended differently
if you and Ray had been here, but...
But if we were,
it could've made the difference.
If you thought I was dead,
what are you doing here?
We were looking
for a neuromorphic prototype
that Felicity Smoak was working on.
Felicity left after everything
that happened.
Everything her company was working on
is being kept in a warehouse
at Adams and O'Neil.
The entry code is 4-5-8-7.
- Thank you, Mr. Queen--
- You found your way in.
Find your way out.
I gotta admit,
that wasn't bad advice, Grey.
So, things went well with Ms. Saunders?
Oh, yeah.
Well, I have more good news.
I was able to very subtly confirm
that Raymond has no romantic inclinations
towards your crush object.
Okay, well, once we've
sorted out my love life,
we need to update your vocabulary.
- Can't wait.
- (CHUCKLES)
I'm gonna go check on Kendra.
- Hey, confidence.
- Yeah.
I got the inertial dampeners back online.
Once the rest of the team returns
with the neuromorphic prototype,
Gideon will be good to go.
Excellent. The sooner
we get out of here, the better.
And thank you, by the way.
Whatever for?
Well, until you mentioned it,
I hadn't really thought
about Kendra in that way.
Because, you know,
she and Carter were destined
to be together in this lifetime.
But it's all changed.
And, you know, she's quirky,
and funny, and beautiful,
and a pretty good welder.
So, you know,
what about all those things
we were talking about?
- The mission and so forth.
- Oh...
We're all adults here, right?
Getting to know each other
a little bit better,
it's not gonna stop us
from saving the world.
Oh, boy.
- (ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING)
- (INDISTINCT CHATTER)
- (CLATTERING)
- (GLASSES SHATTER)
Who invited them?
Word on the street is
Deathstroke is pissed about something.
Deathstroke?
What kind of name is that?
Party's over.
Everyone hit the streets,
hit everybody on them.
I want Green Arrow dead by morning.
Listen, pal. This is my gang.
The only orders they take are from me.
Hmm. Might be your gang,
but it's my city.
Green Arrow is running
with a female assassin in white
and a Brit in a brown coat.
Kill 'em all.
(SCOFFS)
You heard the man. Let's go!
Looks like your new minions
are about to go on a citywide
manhunt for Rip and Sara.
- So what?
- They're gonna kill our friends.
Since when did they become our friends?
You tell me.
You and Raymond seemed to get
pretty tight back in Russia.
I've never been tight with anyone!
Mick, it's time to go.
- You're not the boss of me!
- Actually, I am.
Okay, let's both take a deep breath.
(INHALING)
And we'll make ourselves a deal.
You help me get to Rip and Sara.
Once they're safe,
we can have this conversation.
Fair?
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
Thank you for agreeing
to accompany us, Mr. Diggle.
It's Connor.
It's not like I needed to stick around
Oliver Queen for anything.
- Did you know?
- Know what?
That this is what would happen
to my city.
Oliver said that the only reason
that things got so bad
was because Ray and I
weren't there to help.
Well, I suspected that might be the case,
but that's actually a good thing, hmm.
Once our mission is complete,
and you and Dr. Palmer are
returned to Star City in 2016,
you will both be present
to stop Grant Wilson's Uprising.
This future is only a potential timeline.
So this version of Star City,
this doesn't have to happen?
Correct. The future is always in flux.
Hopefully, this will never come to pass.
This world isn't real.
Let's split up and cover more ground.
Hello, beautiful.
(GRUNTING)
There's too many of them!
(ENGINE REVVING)
Gentlemen, your timing is exemplary.
(GRUNTING)
Where's Connor?
He's been taken.
These are Grant Wilson's men.
Mmm. The guy with the half-face
and the body armor
has a real mad-on
for the kid in the hoodie.
Can I have a word?
- Rip--
- I know what you're going to say.
- We have to get him back.
- Yes, that.
But you're forgetting
this future is only a potential timeline.
Yeah, where Grant Wilson kills Connor.
Wilson's not going to murder Connor
because once you're returned to 2016,
there won't be a Wilson or a Connor.
At least not
as we know them both right now.
Now that we rescued them,
let's have that chat.
You want to stay here.
I thought I made that pretty clear.
What I'm less clear on is why you don't.
A city of thieves and criminals.
Sounds like a lot of competition.
Then we wipe 'em out.
What I did to that other guy,
we do the same thing
to this Grant Wilson,
and anyone else stupid enough
to get in our way.
Take a look around, Snart.
We're living the dream.
Yeah. Speaking of which...
(GRUNTS)
Sleep tight, buddy.
What happened to him?
Difference of opinion.
Right.
We need to get this, and
Mr. Rory, back to the Waverider.
Oh, Jefferson, perfect timing.
I'm in need of your mechanical acumen.
Okay, let's do it.
- What?
- What did you do?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You did something. What did you do?
Nothing. Nothing.
You know, this psychic connection thing,
it goes both ways.
And the moment that I walked in here,
I started feeling
really anxious and guilty.
You feel guilty. So, what did you do?
In my defense, I was only acting
in your best interests--
What did you do?
It's possible, in my attempt to discern
whether Dr. Palmer had competing
feelings for Ms. Saunders--
Oh, you didn't.
I may have inadvertently prompted him
to think of her in ways
in which he hadn't.
- Grey!
- I'm sorry.
My intentions were honorable.
(SIGHS)
Ah, it's cool.
- Is it?
- Yeah.
I mean, nothing's really changed.
Apart from the fact that
now I've got competition
I didn't have before.
But I should still have
confidence in myself, right?
Right.
Well, they're back. Where is Mr. Rory?
Sleeping it off.
We have the neuromorphic prototype.
Any luck with the ship's engines?
Yeah, it's all good.
Is there something wrong, Ms. Lance?
Well, all my friends and family are dead.
Except for Oliver Queen
who happens to be dead inside
and missing his left arm.
Sara, I have told you--
That this is just a potential future.
And that it's all gonna go back
when we return to 2016.
If we return.
But what if we don't?
We all know Carter's not coming back.
It's not like we have
the safest line of work.
I think, if Sara wants to
stay and help, then we should.
I mean, that's what
we signed up for, to be heroes.
I agree with Jefferson.
Yes, of course you both do,
because neither of you
understand the pitfalls
of changing the timeline.
Meddling with the future
is arguably more dangerous
than changing the past
because it is still in flux.
Your wife and son's death
are in the future.
You want us to change that.
Do not play that card with me.
So what?
Are you only willing to risk the timeline
if it's your own family?
I am not just trying to save my family.
And I'm not just trying to save
one city, but the entire world.
I'm not the one being selfish, Sara.
Go to hell.
Most likely.
If you want to go and save
Mr. Hawke, then be my guest.
I'll keep the ship here for
one hour. Then we're leaving.
With you on board or without.
Hello, Mick.
You son of a bitch!
Just calm down.
You lied to me!
Wouldn't be the first time.
Remember the Del Rey currency exchange?
The Blackhawk armored car job?
If I hadn't lied to you on those scores,
we'd both be in prison or dead.
I'm the brains. You're the muscle.
That's how it's always been.
And, on occasion,
I've had to call some audibles.
You have a habit of
getting in your own way, Mick.
Hmm. You're right.
You've lied to me about jobs before.
But then again, you lied to me
about this being a job.
It's not about the score anymore for you.
You'd rather save the world
than be my partner.
A real team player.
'Cause that's what it's gonna
take to defeat Savage.
Then what? More money? More power?
A life of leisure and sin?
Don't you get it, Mick?
We take out Savage,
this immortal monster,
can't you see what that gets us?
No. Tell me.
We'd be the two baddest
sons of bitches of all time!
I don't want a ticker-tape parade.
You know what I want from this world.
Yes.
To see it burn.
You lay a hand on me again,
you'll burn, too.
Oliver.
I thought I told you to go.
Grant Wilson has Connor.
They're gonna kill him.
He knew what he was signing up for.
And you know there's
nothing I can do to help him.
That's not the Oliver Queen that I know.
Maybe I'm not that person anymore.
Look at me, Sara. I'm literally
half the man I used to be.
Then that's the half this city needs.
He's got too many men, Ollie.
I can't do this by myself.
What about your friends?
I'm on my own.
Unless I'm not.
Come on, Sara.
I never got the chance to ask
Connor why he wears the hood.
But I know why.
It's because this city
will always need a Green Arrow.
Is the ship ready for departure?
No, Ms. Lance is not yet on board.
I gave her an hour.
- Hardly enough time for--
- And she's been 90 minutes.
How much longer are we supposed to wait?
It doesn't matter
that this is a potential future.
It doesn't matter that
this may never come to pass.
It may never be real.
For Sara, this is very real.
I know, which is why
I gave her an extra 30 minutes.
Gideon, what's our status?
GIDEON: The Waverider
is operational, Captain,
but I can't guarantee for how long.
- Explain?
- We are cloaked,
but positioned dangerously close
to where the city's criminal element
is gathering to witness
the execution of Connor Hawke.
The longer we wait, the greater
the risk of detection
and further damage to the ship.
Do you really want to risk being marooned
in this version of 2046 forever?
Certainly more than I want
to maroon Sara here.
She's our friend,
our teammate.
What's the point of stopping Savage
if we only become as immoral
as he is in the process?
- (CHEERING AND SHOUTING)
- (GRUNTING)
You should be honored.
This is hallowed ground.
I took Oliver Queen's arm
in this very spot!
(CROWD CHEERING)
Well, then let me go,
and we'll see which one of us is tougher,
me or Queen.
I already know the answer to that.
- (GRUNTS)
- Ready the prisoner.
MAN 1: Sir?
We saw her trying
to sneak past the perimeter.
DEATHSTROKE: Sloppy.
The League of Assassins
would be embarrassed.
What was your strategy here?
Did you really think
you could just turn up tonight
and kill me?
(CROWD LAUGHING)
No.
It was just my job to distract you.
(WHIRRING)
(GRUNTING)
DEATHSTROKE: You're not Green Arrow.
You're just a punk in a Halloween costume.
Funny, I was gonna say
the same thing about you.
(GRUNTING)
You want to fight the Green Arrow?
I'm right here.
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
How'd you convince Rip to stay?
Actually, sending in the cavalry
was his idea.
(GRUNTING)
Where's Mr. Queen?
Connor!
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
Cowards, all!
Oliver?
It's good to see you again, Ray.
Kendra, thanks for the assist.
So, who's that?
GREEN ARROW: His name is Grant Wilson.
Once upon a time, his father
Slade tried to ruin my life.
That is not a nice family.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
That's good shooting, John.
It's Connor.
Either way, it's Green Arrow.
We have a lot of work to do.
Grant Wilson did a good job
of keeping the criminal element
in the city together.
Now there will be plenty
of people to fill the vacuum.
I feel like I should stay.
Before Ray left, he told me why
Rip brought all of you together.
It's important, Sara.
I just hate the idea of leaving
you here to fix it alone.
I'm not alone.
Just be careful, all right?
Well, you should know better than most,
I rarely ever am.
(SIGHS)
You watch his back.
Copy that.
Let's get to work.
(EXHALES SHARPLY) All right.
Confidence. Confidence. Okay.
RAY: So, uh, I think Rip might have
some of that vodka left in his cabinet.
KENDRA: And?
And...
Maybe we could get a drink.
Are you asking me out?
Yes. No...
I think so.
Is that okay?
Yeah, that's totally okay.
Except that,
three months ago
I was a completely normal person
and now I'm a Hawk goddess,
traveling through time,
trying to avoid being killed
by an immortal psychopath
who murdered the man
I was destined to be with.
So (CHUCKLES)...
I'm sorry, Ray,
I think my life's complicated
enough without throwing
whatever this is into the mix.
Yeah. I totally understand.
If I was a reincarnated
Egyptian priestess,
I'd probably feel the same way.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I'm gonna go check on Professor Stein.
Mmm-hmm, yep. All good here.
Absolutely no problems.
- Everything okay here?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, fine.
- You?
- Oh, yeah, good. Good.
That's good.
Uh...
How much of that did you hear?
Oh, enough. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too. (CHUCKLES)
- You knew? Uh...
- Yeah...
- Yeah.
- You're not that subtle.
(SIGHS)
She would've picked me, by the way.
(CHUCKLING) Keep telling yourself that.
(BOTH LAUGH)
RAY: She would've.
I'm just working on determining
our next destination.
I've considered your suggestion of hell.
But I think I'll give it a miss
for the time being.
I just wanted to say thank you
- for sending the team to back me up.
- Mmm.
As it turns out, you were right.
That must've been hard to say.
Of late I've discovered
that I still have a lot to learn,
- I admit.
- (PEN CLICKS)
Including the fact that every
future is worth fighting for.
That said,
this mission is going to continue
to present us with difficult choices
and I need to know that you are
a member of this team.
I guess so.
All right, Gideon,
let's see if these repairs
that Martin, Ray and Jax made
are up to scratch.
GIDEON: As far as I can tell,
Ms. Saunders did most of the work,
while the two gentlemen competed for her--
Just get us out of here please, Gideon.
RORY: I'm gonna miss this place.
Yeah, they really seemed like
your kind of people.
I don't know who my people are anymore.
PROFESSOR STEIN:
So, where to next, Captain?
Well, the beauty of this mission is that
the real question is not where,
but when.
In which case, I suggest
that we next hit Savage
when he least expects it.
(WAVERIDER ENGINE REVVING)
English - SDH