Previously on
Legends of Tomorrow...
Good job out there.
- Are you sticking around?
- Wally. Ready to leave?
I'm actually gonna stay.
The hunt for the six Totems
has begun.
No!
We'll fix this.
We'll get your Totem back.
Nora was possessed by Mallus.
He seemed scared of my Totem.
You're one of the six.
The good news is we already
have the Air, Earth and Fire.
Kuasa has the Water Totem.
Which leaves us with the final Totem,
which is still a complete mystery.
Good point.
"Way to go, Ray."
Hello, sir.
Um, I've been saving up for a while,
and I think it's time...
I'm here to buy a guitar.
I know it ain't much,
but what do you think I can get
with what I got?
I'm sure we can find you something.
You know, a boy picking his
first guitar is a sacred moment.
In fact, some say
the instrument chooses you.
- I'll take that one.
- Oh.
You don't want that guitar.
What happened to the instrument
choosing me, sir?
I was just, uh, building a moment.
Besides, you can't afford it.
Well, I'll get the money.
I'll come back.
Look, I gotta tell you the truth.
Before that guitar
found its way here,
it belonged to a one Robert Johnson.
- The Robert Johnson?
- Uh-huh.
Legend said he sold his soul to
the devil to play as good as he did.
Legend also says that guitar
is cursed because of it.
I ain't afraid of no guitar, sir.
You gotta let me try it at least.
It must be messing
with the power lines outside.
With a sound like that,
how could it be cursed?
You know what? The guitar's yours.
You just take it away from here.
Thank you, sir. Much, much obliged.
An instrument as good as this,
I promise, one day, you'll be hearing
my name on that radio.
Hey.
What is your name, son?
Presley, sir, Elvis Presley.
...which brings us to the kitchen.
We divvy up cleaning duties
by Ray's chore wheel,
which uses a complex system
I pretend to not understand
till he eventually does
my chores for me.
"Wipe down the food fabricator."
Bet you thought time travel would be
seeing Woodstock, saving Shakespeare,
and having ethical debates,
while standing over baby Hitler.
Trust me,
it takes time to get used to life...
Cool. So, what's next?
It's gonna take time for me to
get used to life with a speedster.
This is my room.
Guess you and me are bunkmates
while we help move you
into Stein's quarters.
You just moved yourself in,
didn't you?
I figured, why bother anyone else?
I was gonna
invite you to be my player two,
but you're officially
not my problem anymore.
Wait, who beat all my high scores?
Oh, you see, the thing with Miss Pac-Man
is you gotta just ignore the fruit.
All the points come
from digging out the ghost.
Yeah, I know that, but nobody
could beat these scores without...
Without lightning-fast fingers.
You better not have messed
with Guitar Hero.
What's Trombone Hero?
Hold on, Axl, sammie's coming.
Just gotta find the damn mayo.
Come on, Mick.
What did I say about
having him in the kitchen?
- Not to.
- Yes.
Would you toss me
the walnuts, please?
Thank you.
I'm gonna need some brain food
if I'm gonna fix the Fire Totem.
You know, Nora thought
using cold fusion
to reboot it was a crazy idea, but...
Don't care!
Where's the mayo?
The new kid.
Uh, I saw him speed-moving in
to Marty's old quarters.
Too much change on this damn ship.
That's what I love about old Axl.
Doesn't change.
"Josh Groban"?
Who the hell is Josh Groban?
Who the hell
changed the name of my rat?
All right, kids,
it's anachronism o'clock.
- What you got?
- How about this one?
It's a category two
during the Belle E' poque in Paris.
Sounds romantic.
Hmm. Or this category three,
which is the launch
of the Spirit of St. Louis...
I always wanted to join the Mile
High Club. It's when two people...
Hey, really cute that you guys
are crazy in love,
but date night
is going to have to wait.
If these anachronisms
are loosening Mallus' cage,
we need to double down.
Mmm-hmm.
What happened to your hair?
What are you talking about? What?
What? What is it?
What happened to my trademark
volume and sheen?
Who changed my rat's name?
Yo. Who switched my game?
Gideon?
A scan of the timeline reveals
a change in Memphis, Tennessee, 1954.
Says here,
Memphis became a ghost town
after a mysterious bout of
mass hysteria in July 1954.
That's what caused the changes.
Memphis is the birthplace
of rock 'n' roll.
If rock never makes it
out of Memphis,
then none of these things exist.
Your pet rat's namesake.
Electric guitar.
- Your hair gel.
- It's not hair gel, Wally.
It's Royal Crown pomade,
it's the same product used by...
- Elvis Presley.
- She knows what I'm talking about.
No, dodo, look.
"While the population
fled in hysterics,
"one person was left standing
in the aftermath.
"A local teen named Elvis Presley."
Don't tell me
they messed with the King.
Whatever he saw, drove him crazy.
He was taken to the
Boulevard State hospital.
Treated for insanity.
If Memphis is abandoned in '54,
then rock doesn't hit the mainstream,
which means there's no
Howlin' Rain, no Little Richard.
The Elvis sandwich.
Peanut butter, banana,
fried in greasy bacon fat.
The man was a visionary.
But if it didn't show up
on the anachronism map, then...
Darhks.
The only people evil enough
to wanna kill rock 'n' roll.
Oh. And I bet you,
that sick bastard likes ska.
All right. Let's go check this out.
We need to find Elvis
before panic sets in.
Elvis Presley's uncle preached
to the Church of Zion every Sunday.
The boy never missed a service.
You heard the lady.
What?
Why are you staring at me?
Well, you know, waiting for you
to do the thing you do.
What thing?
You usually send us into
the field with a little more pizzazz.
All right, Legends.
Put on your Sunday best
because we are going to church.
That's pretty good.
Amen.
Oh, this is uncomfortable, and I'm not
just talking about the dress.
Yeah, I guess these people didn't get
the whole "Love thy neighbor" talk.
- Shh.
- Shush yourself, lady.
Have you heard your singing voice?
Just keep Mick away
from the collection tray
and the communion wafers.
It's not bread!
There is a sickness
coming over this town.
I see it
in the schoolyard,
as I pass in the morning.
And to my horror,
I see it in this very church
on Sundays.
It infects the mind.
It drives people crazy.
Maybe the righteous Reverend
is on to something.
They call it "rock 'n' roll."
I call it "the Devil's music!"
Never mind. He has no idea
what he's talking about.
Now, I would like
to invite my nephew,
Elvis, to play for us,
and encourage you all to attend our
first annual Heavenly Night of Hymns.
Elvis.
Remember what we talked about, son.
Keep it godly.
Yes, ma'am.
Can you believe this?
The first show
we see together is Elvis live.
You're not the only one
who's excited.
This one's called...
Onward, Christian Soldiers.
Okay.
So, this is rock 'n' roll?
I mean, it's no Benny Goodman, but...
No, we did not come all this way to
listen to Elvis play grandma songs.
That's it, Elvis.
Put a little sauce on it.
Yeah, swivel.
Satan's got a hold of her!
What the hell's going on?
My Totem,
it's reacting to something.
Be gone, Satan!
Well, I think she's talking to us.
Behold,
what you have seen
with your very eyes,
witnessed in this house of God!
That is the act of Satan!
The Elvis sandwich.
I guess Elvis is
the King of rock 'n' roll.
One hip shake and Z loses it.
Yeah, tell me about it, sister.
I didn't lose control
because of Elvis' hips.
Yeah, me neither.
My Totem was glowing,
and so was Elvis' guitar.
- But that means that Elvis is...
- Yep.
Elvis is a Totem bearer.
So, Elvis is the bearer
of the long-lost sixth Totem.
Consider me all shook up.
- So, he has to join the team, right?
- No.
I mean, we can't defeat Mallus
unless we have a full set.
We could get Gideon
to fabricate him a spangling jumpsuit
and he'll fit right in.
What Totem would choose
a guitar-toting choirboy
- as its bearer?
- Isn't it obvious?
It's Elvis we're talking about.
It's gotta be...
Sandwich Totem.
I was gonna say "Music."
Just imagine what the Music Totem
would do for my upper register.
I can finally give
local theater a shot.
That is after we use it
to destroy Mallus.
So, we're gonna vanquish a time demon
with our killer harmonies.
It's gonna go great.
Every Totem is growing stronger
in response to Mallus' threat.
What if the preacher was right,
and Elvis' music
literally drives Memphis insane?
Then we have to get it
before that happens.
I got it. Elvis' guitar Totem.
So I'm not the only one
who finds that annoying, right?
- So annoying.
- Yeah.
Okay, come on.
We're good to go, right?
Are we? 'Cause Elvis hasn't recorded
his first single yet.
And without that guitar,
he may never record,
which means
rock 'n' roll history is...
Josh Groban.
What if we have Gideon
fabricate a ringer guitar
and drop it off to the future King?
Great idea. I call a mission.
Amaya, come with me. I will teach you
what rock 'n' roll's all about.
Till then, everyone,
shake, rattle and roll.
Beale Street was the heart
of the music scene
in Memphis in the 1950s.
Brothels, churches, juke joints.
All next to each other,
all black-owned.
This, this was
the spirit of rock 'n' roll.
There he is.
- It was right here.
- Hey, kid.
I don't think you wanna keep this
lyin' around.
Something tells me it's special.
You have no idea.
There's no way I'd ever be able
to thank you for this.
If you wanna write a song about me
there are several words that rhyme
with "Nate."
Just knock 'em dead.
I can't wait for you
to see Elvis live.
It's going to change your life.
You really believe that my life
can be changed by one song?
Of course. Music is so much more
than just a song.
Music is about identity.
It's hearing a track
for the first time,
and you think to yourself,
"Wow, this is who I am."
I don't care how long it takes.
We're gonna find your music,
whether be it rock 'n' roll or,
God forbid, ska.
Debuting tonight, y'all,
give it up for Elvis Presley!
I guess it's time
to have my life changed.
Yep.
How you folks doing tonight?
Ow!
If it's all right with y'all,
I'mma play a little song for my mama.
Now, you...
Wait. Don't go.
Why? You all wanna make fun
of my playin' like everybody else?
No, actually, we're, uh...
We're music managers.
And we think you're very talented.
So, uh, what happened up there?
This doggone guitar ain't working
how it's supposed to.
Y'all gonna think I'm crazy, but...
My guitar, it's more
than just a guitar.
Now that it ain't
working right, I just...
You don't feel like yourself anymore?
Yes, ma'am.
And I'll tell you why,
usually when I play...
I got my twin brother, Jesse,
up there to back me up.
You have a twin brother?
Yeah, he ain't with us no more.
Passed when he was a baby.
But this guitar of mine,
used to connect me to him.
- Told you, you'd think I'm crazy.
- No. Not at all.
I've always believed that objects
can connect us to our ancestors.
Yeah, I guess we call it
a "spirit life."
But on stage...
On stage, just now, for the
first time, Jesse wasn't with me.
I mean, he's gone all of a sudden.
I just don't know where he is.
Whoa. That was weird.
Yeah, you feel that?
It's freezing.
I am detecting an
EMF reading of six milligauss
that is disturbing the ship's
electrical service.
- EM... What?
- Electromagnetic field.
It's a scientific term
that's been wrapped up
in a bunch of paranormal nonsense.
Paranormal, as in...
Ghosts.
Whoever you are,
just put the guitar down.
Doesn't look like
he's taking requests.
Maybe the preacher was right
about rock 'n' roll.
You know what never hurt anyone?
A nice show tune.
I got it!
Okay, Axl, time to break the seal.
- Axl, come back!
- What the hell is going on?
Guitar hit me in the head.
Oh, that explains nothing.
I got ya.
- The guitar, it's haunted!
- We know.
But by who?
That's what's so strange
about my brother.
I ain't never met Jesse,
but somehow,
I've missed him all my life.
Until you bought your first guitar.
Man at the store said it was cursed.
He's only half-right,
it's also a blessing, too.
I don't know if my brother's
out there, somewhere without me.
I can't imagine he's too happy.
Excuse me.
Guys, Elvis' guitar is haunted.
- We know.
Yeah, and I'm guessing it's gonna do
whatever it takes
to get back to Elvis.
Good guess!
- Where is Axl?
- About that ghost...
It's Elvis' dead twin, Jesse.
Jesse, stop!
We know your brother.
I know this all sounds like hogwash.
Magical guitars, the ghosts
of gone family members.
But I can't play without them.
I got a session to record
at Sun Studios tomorrow.
I saved up to buy it.
It's your first recording session?
You're gonna keep that appointment.
- And we're gonna get you Jesse back.
- You will?
We will?
All right, so I talked to Constantine
about our Totem.
He compared it with his notes,
and this...
Is what he found.
Death Totem, badass.
Yeah, and whoever wields it
has domain over the dead.
Which is why we need to keep this
Totem with us and safe at all times.
Elvis needs his Totem back.
You have no idea
what we are dealing with.
"The Death Totem.
"The most volatile of all
of the Totems.
"Lost for eons, along with
the sixth tribe of Zambesi."
Maybe they suffered the same fate
that's about to befall Memphis.
- You don't understand.
- No.
You don't understand.
We are talking about a Death Totem,
and it could turn this
whole place into a ghost town.
Elvis has a session at Sun Studios.
That's where he cuts his first demo.
That's how he gets discovered, okay?
We do not have the time
for Elvis to get his groove back.
- Jesse has to be there.
- Nathaniel.
I understand
how important this is to you,
but we can't give Elvis a Totem
just to save his music.
It's not about the music, okay?
Rock has inspired
many historic milestones,
protests, revolutions.
Me losing my virginity.
Elvis doesn't need a Totem forever.
Just one song that changes the world.
Please.
Fine.
You take it to him,
you let him record with it,
and you stay with it at all times.
At all times!
All right, son. Are you ready
to lay this down on wax, or what?
I've been waiting all my life, sir.
Now, that's rock 'n' roll.
What do you think?
It's okay.
I just don't see
how it's worth risking
the most volatile of Totems for.
Wow. I thought that was gonna be
our music moment.
"Our music moment"?
One of those times
where the right song comes on,
and ties everything together
so perfectly, that it becomes...
It becomes a story.
We already have plenty of stories.
We saved the world together,
we saw dinosaurs.
There was that time
that I discovered Netflix
and we watched every episode
of Friends in one week.
All stunning accomplishments, yes.
But the music moment is different.
You'll see.
How was that?
Whoo, boy! Now, that's a record.
We gotta get this straight down
to WHBQ.
You're gonna be on the radio.
- Whoo, boy!
- Yeah.
Uncle Lucius.
What are you doing here?
Well, well, well.
You missed choir practice.
Then, I hear, 'cause you're down
at Sun Studios.
Well, no kin of mine
is gonna record the Devil's music.
Not after what we saw in church.
I got talent. My manager says so.
You got my nephew into this?
Yeah.
- Hey, that ain't yours to take.
- Give me that.
I knew you'd put up a fight!
Sheriff!
Get him out of here.
Let's see if a night
in the jailhouse
rocks some sense into you.
That record's gotta make it
on the radio tonight.
- Get him out of here, too.
- You're making a huge mistake.
Get behind me, Satan.
White Stripes, great album.
At least it was.
Your mama's been too easy
on you, boy.
Look at the sort
you got mixed up with.
These are the types that go on down
to Beale Street
and dance the hoochie koo
like heathens.
You keep on preaching hate.
I'm only trying
to bring folks together.
As the Lord destroyed the wicked,
I must do the same with this record.
I'll make an example of you
at the Heavenly Nights of Hymns.
That ought to teach them
young folks a lesson.
Reverend, you don't know
what you're messing with.
- The music your nephew made...
- Has turned Memphis
into Sodom and Gomorrah.
I will not allow it
to be the ruination
of that boy's soul, too.
Don't worry,
we'll get you out of here.
All I ever wanted to do
was make my mama proud.
Now, she ain't never gonna hear
my song on the radio.
At least I still got you, Jesse.
Guys, we have a bit of a setback.
- We're listening, what's up?
- Uh, long story, funny ending,
Amaya, Elvis and I
were thrown in the slammer.
So, just steel up and break out.
Yeah, I know I can, but I'm afraid
my work here isn't done.
- What do you need?
- I need you to go back to the church,
get the record from the Reverend,
and bring it to WHBQ
and make sure it debuts tonight.
On it.
Despite everything you've seen,
I really think my powers
could come in handy right now,
because I could just go
grab that record, and then...
Okay, if this were a Central City
bank robbery,
sure, you could just speed in,
save the day,
the mayor would give you
a key to the city.
That actually happened, you know.
Barry and I...
History is different.
You can't be a chainsaw,
you need to be a scalpel.
You need to get in there,
talk to people.
Find out what they really need.
Now, let's go talk to the preacher
like human beings.
Okay, Axl,
I know how to draw you out.
With a nice little snack.
Mick? Mick, don't panic.
You just forgot to chew again.
Axl.
Is this one of your
stupid science experiments?
- Looks like Josh Groban...
- "Axl!"
...had something even more lethal
than your Elvis sandwich.
I'm sorry, buddy.
Look, the life expectancy of a rat
is one and half to two
and a half years, so, you know,
the little guy really beat the odds.
And you know what?
We can pick you up another one
in the next time period we stop in.
Because what's one more change
on this ship?
Jailhouse
Jailhouse party
Getting warmer.
There's gotta be a song
in here somewhere, Jesse.
Okay, songwriting time-out.
Listen, um...
There's no easy way to say this,
but when we get out of here,
you're gonna have to give us
that guitar.
It has power,
and it can be dangerous.
No. I mean,
I can't play without Jesse.
I mean, before he came along,
sure there were songs,
but there wasn't ever any music.
Look, even after he's gone,
you're gonna have the music.
I mean, that's why you play, right?
The real reason music matters,
is because it keeps things alive
long after they're gone.
Any idea why Ray needs us?
No clue.
Whatever this is, I don't like it.
Wait. What is that?
We are gathered here
in remembrance
of our dear friend, Axl.
Right. I'm out of here.
- I'm with him.
- Wait, you need this.
We all need this.
Fine, but when I mourn, I drink.
Fair enough.
Charles Dickens once wrote,
"Life is made
of ever so many partings
"welded together."
Axl is once such parting.
And while we may lose some,
they're never really gone,
and they certainly can't be replaced.
They'll live on in the memories
we shared with them,
and the lessons they taught us.
And it's because of that,
that we can embrace the change.
I still remember
the first time I met Axl.
It was in the vents.
I was tiny Atom, he was a big rat.
And he tried to eat me.
I knew we'd laugh
about it one day together.
Sara, I believe it's customary
for the captain
to share a few words.
- Oh, no. You're doing a great job.
- Thank you.
Well, then, please join me
in a chorus of Sweet Child of Mine.
Mmm-mmm.
All right, I'll say something.
Mmm.
Axl was a friend.
Our friend.
Some might say he was the best of us.
Can we have a word?
And not the good word,
we just wanna talk.
What could you possibly
wanna talk about?
We need to talk about your nephew
and his record.
You can't destroy it.
People need to hear it.
That includes you.
How do you all know
what I need to hear?
I might actually know
what you are going through.
You see, my dad,
he came into my life pretty late.
We couldn't always
figure each other out.
We didn't always know how to fit
into each other's lives,
until I knew that I just had to go
and set out on my own.
Truly sorry to hear that, son.
I think you might be afraid
that you're losing your nephew.
But if you both could just try
to understand each other,
you might actually find something new
between you two.
You might even find something
really special.
Now, I know someone
that would love to play that record
if you're ready to give it a chance.
And a lot of young souls
would be moved
by your nephew's voice.
Hmm.
Mysterious ways indeed.
Okay, so, we walked real far,
and it took a long time,
and then we got thrown around...
History is at stake.
You better run fast.
Hoo-wee. Daddy-O Dewey here
with a new record
literally burning my fingers,
by a young local boy
name of Elvis Presley.
Remember where you heard it first.
How on Earth?
My nephew is on the radio.
My nephew is on the radio!
Well, I'll be...
The kid kept his promise.
So I'm gone
Yeah, I'm gone
I'm gone, gone mama
It would seem that Ms. Tomaz
and Mr. West have succeeded.
I'm gone, gone mama
To Axl.
For Axl.
I'm going to get me
a big pink Cadillac
Been ages since I've seen
so much life in this place.
Maybe you ain't so ungodly
as I thought.
You know, you and I
might have different names for God,
but I'm guessing
we have a lot in common, too.
- What took you so long?
- Seriously?
Hey, um, what does dancing
look like in the future?
- Oh, um... Pretty much the same.
- Hmm.
Oh, no.
Great. Well, we'd love
to stick around for hymn night,
but we should head back to...
On second thought,
how about those hymns?
That music, it's summoned the dead.
This time,
he actually might be right.
Don't tell me you're converting.
Elvis recorded that song
with the Death Totem.
It must have given his music
the power to literally raise spirits.
You're kidding.
This must've been what drives
everyone out of Memphis.
Right, ghosts can go
through anything.
It's kind of their thing.
Okay, Mick, time to send him off.
What?
Axl lives.
You just had to throw
a rodent funeral, didn't you?
Where's it going?
Remember, the real points come
from taking out the ghosts.
Let's make Miss Pac-Man proud.
How's that for a high score?
Impressive, but I think it's
gonna be game-over soon.
At least you got to hear yourself
on the radio.
Don't go quoting this to my uncle but
I sound pretty damn good, don't I?
Hey, what's going on out there?
The whole town's been
overrun by ghosts!
- Well, let us out!
- Let me in!
- The Death Totem.
- Death Totem.
Well, I'll be...
It worked.
You can command spirits.
Well, if you can raise them,
maybe you can also lead them away.
Lead them where?
How about back where they came from?
The cemetery
outside your uncle's church.
You were right.
His music really does have power.
Could have stood being wrong
on this one.
Well, we need to get
past them somehow.
Don't be scared.
The dead don't want nothing
but to be acknowledged.
I mean, is there anything
this guy can't do?
I knew I should have smashed
that record when I had the chance.
Now your song has gone
and let the Devil into my church.
This ain't the Devil's doing.
And you're right,
music has a power.
Brings life to the lifeless,
soothes the souls of the restless,
but it ain't just rock 'n' roll,
either.
And I would like to prove it.
Put an end to all this
while I'm at it?
Now,
get on up there, boy.
Now, I know y'all can hear me.
Come on in.
All are welcome here.
Amazing grace
How sweet the sound
That saved
A wretch like me
Should we take 'em out?
No, it's okay.
I think I understand what they need.
I once was lost, but now am found
T'was blind
But now I see
T'was grace
That taught
My heart to fear
I actually know this one.
Care to dance?
Axl.
I'm sorry,
your corpse is starting to stink.
I didn't think you'd mind.
I, uh, saved you a sammie.
Axl, what's wrong?
I think it's time, brother.
I've got a feeling this goodbye
ain't gonna be forever.
Thank you, Jesse.
Thank you very much.
I think we just found our moment.
Better make yourself comfortable.
Something tells me you'll be spending
a lot more time in here,
especially after that show
you just put on.
Yeah, something came over me,
I guess.
I was up there,
looking at those ghosts,
I realized, one day, this is all
gonna be over for all of us.
Might as well get the most
out of life that we can.
You know what?
I think you just discovered
the spirit of rock 'n' roll.
And I think that this...
Is probably gonna be safer with you.
That was fun and all, but...
I don't soon want
to be raising the dead again.
Promise me you'll keep playing
even without your brother.
Oh, Jesse ain't really gone.
The things he taught me,
the love that we had,
is gonna live on with my music.
Can I ask you a question?
You ain't really
a music manager, are you?
Busted.
Well, something tells me,
you're gonna be just fine.
Even without this.
Thanks to you.
I think I'm just about ready.
Go get 'em.
All right, gentlemen,
how are y'all doing?
I say we start it off
with some little bit of fast tempo.
Okay, fellas,
get your fingers going.
You're ready, Captain?
Hello, gorgeous.
- Look at that volume.
- Don't touch it.
- I think you...
- I'm serious, don't.
Well, well, well.
Look who got his swagger back.
Hey, just because
I saved rock 'n' roll
and reinstated the King
to his proper throne...
Doesn't give you an excuse
to hog our one bathroom.
- Some of us need to get...
- Celebrate the fact that
we beat the Darhks
to the Death Totem.
Although I don't imagine
our acquisition
will stay off the radar for long.
Well, think of it like this.
We're four Totems up
in the fourth quarter.
Time's running out for those idiots.
Yep, even though
they still have mine.
There will be time to send them back
to whatever hell they came from
once we get your Totem back.
Yeah, and in the meantime,
we need to make sure
we keep that Death Totem on lock.
Box.
Lockboxes.
I got it covered.
I made encrypted lockboxes
for each one of the Totems.
Well, good.
The Death Totem's powers
are not to be taken lightly.
Perhaps you need
some assistance, Ms. Jiwe.
Just give me a moment,
Gideon, please.
I've sabotaged Axis tanks.
I am sure I can figure out
a stupid playlist.
Hey, Gideon said you wanna see me?
I wanted to say thank you.
Oh, you know...
Check you out.
You got a playlist going.
As soon as I'm done uploading
all The Smiths' music,
we'll do a deep dive
into the Morrissey solo stuff...
Actually, I thought it was time
for me to teach you
about my music.
Okay.
Like some big band stuff?
I think I'm at a point where
I can appreciate a trumpet solo.
No, this is the music of Zambesi.
Gideon helped me locate
some supposedly lost tracks.
You like it?
Oh...
I love it!
So good.
Now you know
how I feel about rock 'n' roll.
What's that?
I said you're almost
at the good part.
You mean this isn't the good part?
I love you, Nathaniel.
What?
I said, there's a lot more
where that came from.
It's a good thing we got time.