RIP: In 2166,
an immortal tyrant
named Vandal Savage
conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
and stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately,
my plan is opposed
by the body I had sworn
my allegiance to,
the Time Masters.
In the future,
my friends may not be heroes,
but if we succeed,
they will be remembered
as legends.
SARA: Previously,
on Legends of Tomorrow...
The Time Masters
discourage marriage.
RIP: But I fell in love.
And we had a child.
Jonas.
Maybe we could get a drink.
Are you asking me out?
Yes. Is that okay?
I think my life's
complicated enough
without throwing
whatever this is into the mix.
This is Star City.
RIP: Yes, Star City 2046.
RORY: It's everything
we've ever wanted.
We could live like kings here.
(GRUNTS)
RORY: You son of a bitch!
You lay a hand on me again,
you'll burn, too.
MIRANDA: Go ahead, Jonas. He's listening.
Hi, Daddy. We miss you.
And love you.
Anything else you want to say?
Come home soon, Daddy.
(MIRANDA CHUCKLES)
Hi, Rip. I'm not sure
if you got our last message.
I told Jonas that you
got caught up with work,
but I really thought
you'd be home by now.
London is...
Things have changed.
It's hard to tell
what's going on
with so many soldiers,
and rumors.
I just want to know
you're all right.
Wherever you are,
whenever you are,
I love you, Rip.
Go ahead, Jonas. He's listening.
Hi, Daddy. We miss you.
MIRANDA: And love you.
JONAS: And love you.
I'm sorry to interrupt, Captain.
Uh, not at all.
Just catching up on work.
- What is all this?
- Trying to connect the dots.
Find the optimal time
to strike at Savage.
And?
And the trail's gone cold.
In order to preserve
the element of surprise,
I wager
the best course of action
is to travel
further back in time.
But nothing here indicates
where to find him.
Perhaps I can help you look?
I've been looking!
I apologize.
It's just,
the stakes are so high.
I vowed to save my family,
but I am failing them.
(SCOFFS) Perhaps I'm not
the Time Master they need.
You must be.
You're the only one they have.
Can't Gideon help us?
No. When a Timeship returns
to the Vanishing Point
after a mission,
its CPU is updated
from the Temporal Database,
which, given my rogue status,
we are unable to do.
So, what you're saying is,
Gideon requires
a software update?
Which explains why you've been
holed up in here
for the past week.
Has it really been a week?
Mmm-hmm.
And some of our teammates
are getting just a tad antsy.
(GRUNTS)
I'm done.
Don't mind him. He's still sore
about having to leave 2046.
I'm sore because I was recruited
for my unique ability
to light things on fire.
And now,
I'm locked in the one place
where I can't
light things on fire,
a spaceship.
Where do you think you're going?
Why? You gonna clock me
in the head
if I don't listen again?
Everything okay with you two?
Yeah. Peachy.
GIDEON: Captain, I've just intercepted
a deep-space transmission.
It's a distress signal
from the Acheron.
She's the flagship
of the Time Fleet.
Yes, I know that.
Thank you, Gideon.
Systemic malfunction.
I'm stranded.
Unable to jump.
Controls unresponsive.
This is Captain Eve Baxter,
of the Timeship Acheron,
requesting critical rescue.
And we care
about this chick, why?
We don't.
But the Acheron's computer
will contain the current intel
on Savage's whereabouts.
Gideon, set a course
for the Acheron's position
in deep space.
GIDEON: Yes, Captain.
Deep space?
I had no idea we had the ability
to explore the unknown realms
of the galaxy. Astonishing!
No, what's astonishing is that
we're acting
as roadside assistance
for the people who's chasing us.
Doesn't it seem suspicious
this distress call
just happened to reach us?
- How do we know it's not a trap?
- We don't.
But what we do know is that
Savage's trail has run cold,
and unless Gideon
can upload the data
- from the Acheron's computer--
- I'm in.
You are?
The sooner we end Savage,
the sooner I get back
to where I belong.
Prison?
Any prison on Earth's
better than this one, professor.
- Gideon!
- GIDEON: Yes, sir.
- Engines to full throttle.
- Of course, Captain.
(ENGINE POWERING UP)
Professor Stein, Mr. Jackson,
would you care
to join the boarding party?
A chance for an extra-vehicular
docking maneuver.
- What could be more exciting?
- I can think of a few things.
Let's get this thing started.
Hey, you think there's something
worth stealing on that ship?
I'm just looking
for a change of scenery.
If that's okay with you, boss.
Dr. Palmer, I leave the ship
in your hands while we're gone.
And I leave him in yours.
I'm having
the strangest sensation,
it's like I'm 10 years old
again.
You do a lot of space travel
as a kid, professor?
PROFESSOR STEIN: Only in my dreams.
After I read my first issue
of Rick Starr: Space Ranger.
Space Ranger Stein?
Yeah, I don't see it.
I wanted to travel
through space,
surviving only by my wits
and laser guns.
(CHUCKLING SOFTLY) I even built a rocket
out of cardboard boxes.
What stopped you?
NASA has
rather strict guidelines
regarding nearsightedness.
And smoking weed.
RIP: Gideon, have you been able
to link up
to the Acheron's computer?
GIDEON: It appears a self-destruct code
has disabled the ship's
temporal navigation system.
Whoa. What does that mean?
It's possibly
the result of a malfunction.
But just in case, Martin,
I'm going to ask you to remain
behind here on the Jumpship.
You're telling us,
if something goes wrong,
the egghead's in-charge?
Break out the emergency gear.
Space Ranger has a job to do.
MIRANDA: Rip, I need an update.
How about this update?
- They've boarded the ship!
- (FIRING)
- We've been overrun!
- Excellent.
Perhaps you're not
taking this seriously, Miranda.
- Gary?
- GARY: Yes, Captain?
Be a dear and open the
port-side bulkhead, would you?
Look, I enjoy a suicide mission
as much as the next person.
- You heard me, Gary.
- GARY: Yes, ma'am.
- (GRUNTS)
- What's the plan here?
Rip, you might want to
grab hold of something.
Yes, I am. It's called a gun.
Something else. Do it, please.
Now, Gary.
(SCREAMING)
GARY: Gamma-delta hatch opened.
Explosive decompression
has evacuated the time pirates.
Seal hatch, engage time drive,
and punch it.
(AIR HISSING)
Well done, Lieutenant Coburn.
"Well done"?
She nearly got us killed.
The simulation equivalent,
at least.
TIME MASTER DECLAN:
She demonstrated unconventional thinking
against overwhelming numbers.
You could learn a thing or two
from her, Lieutenant Hunter.
Uh... (SIGHS)
Ah, Declan was right. Teach me more.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
(COUNCIL MEMBER CLEARS THROAT)
(GASPS)
Sir, I can explain.
Don't bother, lieutenant.
Save it for
your disciplinary hearing.
Hey, hey, hey.
We can figure this out.
We'll get through this together.
That's just it.
We can't be together.
We knew from the start
relationships
are strictly forbidden.
There has to be
a way to fix this.
I'm sorry.
I need some time to think.
Stay close and stay alert.
To quote every Star Wars
ever made,
"I've got a bad feeling
about this."
(GRUNTING)
Valiant effort.
Let the man go.
Or else, what?
MAN: Do as the man says.
(GRUNTING)
Who the hell are these guys?
These, Mr. Jackson,
are time pirates.
Captain Jon Valor.
Oh, what happened to Captain Baxter?
She was on her way back
to the Vanishing Point
to imprison us,
when we made our escape.
But before we could
take control of the Acheron--
She destroyed her time drive
in accordance with protocol.
The same protocol that said
another Time Master
would come to her rescue.
Do I look like
a Time Master to you?
You look like the kind of man
who'd throw his grandmother
out an airlock.
Nor am I a Time Master,
so you might as well
just let us go.
(LAUGHING)
Correct me if I'm wrong.
You're Rip friggin' Hunter.
I thought you'd be taller.
- You never said you were famous.
- VALOR: Infamous.
There was a time
when you had men like me
running scared
all along the timeline.
Unless you let us
return to our ship,
a man named Vandal Savage
will destroy the entire world,
Time Masters and pirates alike.
For once, we are fighting
on the same side.
That little slogan
- should come with its own shovel.
- (MAN LAUGHING)
- Prepare a boarding party.
- MAN: Yes, sir.
If I were you, I'd reconsider
your plan, Mr. Valor.
Really?
I gave my crew instructions
to shoot any boarding vessel
along with the ship
launching it.
With the great Rip Hunter
on-board?
I highly doubt it.
You don't know my crew.
They are iron-willed
and battle-hardened.
The most formidable warriors
to navigate time and space.
Captain's log. Stardate 837.9.
We're awaiting word
from the away team
aboard the Acheron.
I hate to break it to you,
but you're not Captain Kirk.
You're Picard.
But Picard was cautious,
pontificating, sort of sexless.
Tell that to Vash.
And for the record,
Picard was way hotter than Kirk.
(SIGHS) Mick had it wrong.
This ship isn't a prison,
it's a torture chamber.
I don't think Mick's problem
is with the ship.
You think it's with me?
You did knock him out
and force him to leave
2046 Star City,
which is like
Disneyland for felons.
He'll get over it.
Mick runs hot. He always has.
Once he calms down,
everything'll be back to normal.
Yeah, I bet that one sounded
more convincing in your head.
(BEEPING)
I'd like to speak to
Acting Captain Raymond Palmer.
Ooh, "Acting Captain."
I like the sound of that.
I'm Captain Palmer. Who are you?
I'm the man
holding your crew hostage.
Captain Palmer,
I've informed Mr. Valor
of the fiery retribution
you will rain down upon him
if we are
not released immediately.
Hmm.
(GRUNTS)
I'm gonna make this real simple.
You surrender your ship,
and I'll drop you off unharmed
at a place and time
of your choosing.
You've got 10 seconds to decide.
Or else what?
If you want
the Waverider for yourself,
there's no way
you'll fire on us.
Perhaps, but right now,
I've got my sights set
on your captain's head.
Wait, wait, wait. Okay, just
give me a chance to negotiate--
Ten, nine--
Maybe he's bluffing.
- ...eight, seven.
- Doesn't feel like it.
You don't know Palmer.
And how he survived
the Imperiex onslaught.
(ALARM BLARING)
Uh, Gideon?
GIDEON: Captain Hunter programed me
to execute certain protocols
in response
to specific keywords.
What does that mean in English?
Strap yourselves in.
We are on the move
and preparing to fire.
(GRUNTS)
Great Scott! We're under attack.
Gideon, who's firing at us?
- GIDEON: Captain's orders.
- Palmer, you idiot!
No. Captain Hunter.
Attacking the pirates
who've taken
the rest of
the boarding party hostage.
Pirates?
What are you doing, Gideon?
GIDEON: Just a warning shot to
let them know we mean business.
My partner's on that ship.
- Dr. Palmer?
- (RADIO STATIC)
Captain Hunter? Is anyone there?
It's up to you now, Martin.
- Gilbert!
- GILBERT: Yes, sir.
Set a pursuit course
and prepare to return fire.
If you destroy the Waverider,
none of us
are getting back home.
Don't worry.
I'm only targeting your
ship's life-support systems.
Now, if I were the weapons
targeting system on the Acheron,
where would I be?
(FIRING)
GIDEON: There's a hull breach
in the aft portion of the ship,
and the pirates have taken out
the telemetry controls.
Gideon, switch to manual.
What are you doing?
If this is anything
like a videogame,
I'm flying a spaceship.
Where are you guys going?
To deal
with the hole in the ship.
Make sure Picard here
doesn't get us all killed.
Actually, I'm more like
Sulu right now.
Or Han Solo!
Target their thrusters and fire.
- I said fire!
- (WEAPONS SYSTEM POWERING DOWN)
Sir, the weapon systems
have been taken offline.
Manually.
Who else is on my ship?
A good captain
keeps his best weapons
hidden from his enemies,
Mr. Valor.
Find the saboteur,
bring him to me, dead or alive.
I guess we'll just have to
follow your friends
till they're out of air.
Shouldn't take too long
given the size
of the hole in the hull.
Here.
Hail the crew of the Waverider.
Rip, tell your crew
to let us board,
and I will happily save them.
But either way,
we are taking the Waverider.
Take the damn deal, Rip.
A captain
never surrenders his ship.
Besides, you'll never catch
Captain Palmer.
He once outran
Kanjar Ro himself!
Who's Kanjar Ro?
- GIDEON: Engaging protocol now, Captain.
- Awesome.
I wasn't talking to you.
What the hell happened to them?
We were following
a holographic projection,
which allowed
the Waverider to slip away.
Giving secret commands
to your crew.
- Very clever, Captain.
- Um...
Throw them in the brig.
We'll find your friends'
bodies, eventually.
How long can you
keep that up for?
Not long.
I'm gonna run out of charge.
GIDEON: Be advised. The breach
is only partially contained.
Guess we know
the bulkhead doors are working.
Too bad we're
on the wrong side of them.
(ALARM BLARING)
Uh-oh.
Thanks for stopping by.
We're gonna get you out of here.
Just hang tight.
Is there another option?
Don't mean to rush you, Raymond,
but it's getting cold in here.
Normally,
I wouldn't complain, but...
Can't you just
open the doors, Gideon?
GIDEON: The bulkhead is designed
to remain shut
until the breach is sealed.
Well, that's not happening
from in here.
How much time do we have until--
We're dead?
(GRUNTS)
Captain Baxter, I'm Rip Hunter.
I'm here to rescue you.
I doubt it.
You walked straight into a trap.
I will admit
that we've encountered
some unforeseen obstacles.
Right.
RIP: But we're gonna get you
out of here in a second.
Mr. Jackson, will you please see
what we can do about
disabling this force field.
You don't think I've tried that?
But by all means, if you think
this kid
will have better luck...
Whoa! Who you calling kid?
I'm sorry. I meant criminal.
- Actually, that's me.
- All of you.
If we ever do get out of here,
the first thing I'll do
is take you
to the Vanishing Point
to await trial
before the Time Council.
The great Rip Hunter.
But look at you now.
Yes, look at me now.
Helping you break out
of a pirates' brig
aboard your own Timeship.
I don't want help from a man
who broke his oath,
stole a Timeship,
and decided to change history
for his own selfish reasons.
Doesn't make any sense to me.
No, I don't expect it would.
Rip Hunter.
Miranda Coburn.
Those aren't your real names,
are they?
No, sir.
And why is that?
Because if our enemies
knew our true identities,
our ancestors and descendants
across the timeline
could be potential targets.
As well as anyone else
you might love.
Which is why...
Personal attachments
are expressly forbidden
by the Council of Time Masters.
And grounds for immediate
discharge from service.
Do either of you deny
that you were conducting
an illicit affair
in violation
of this Council's rules?
In that case,
I motion that we adjourn
this disciplinary hearing
for one hour
to afford you the opportunity
to consider your response.
Though I sincerely doubt there
is any answer you can provide
that will prevent this tribunal
from discharging you both
from the Time Masters.
SARA: I suppose this feels like
a day at the beach for you.
If I had to pick a way to die,
freezing wouldn't be the worst.
What's it like, dying?
I imagine you've got
a unique perspective.
It's funny.
You'd expect it
to be terrifying,
just panic and fear.
What did you feel?
I guess, lonely.
Yeah.
Like everybody I loved
was a million miles away.
I mean, I don't like you,
but at least
I'm not dying alone.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Closest I ever came to dying
was the day I met Mick.
- Why does that not surprise me?
- It wasn't like that.
It was my first day in juvie.
I was 14, and the smallest kid
in there by far.
Some of the older kids
wanted to make sure I knew it.
So, they jumped me.
I fought back,
but one of them had a shiv.
I figured that was it.
Until Mick stepped in.
And they didn't mess
with me after that.
He's been standing up
for me ever since.
Let's just hope he's standing up
for Rip and Jax now.
Who else is gonna
take on those pirates?
GUARD: Hey!
(GRUNTING)
That'll teach you to mess
with a nuclear physicist.
Are you ready?
Given I never designed
the Atom suit for outer space,
I'm not exactly sure
how to answer that question.
While I'm gone, you're captain.
Thank you.
But I think we both know
I'm in charge either way.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Good luck.
Gideon, open the hatch.
- (BEEPS)
- (SIGHS)
Sorry, Captain.
I can't jerry-rig the door open.
Don't worry, kid,
it's not your fault. It's his.
In case you've forgotten,
Mr. Rory,
you volunteered to be part
of this boarding party.
I volunteered to get away
from my partner.
Who hasn't been
acting like my partner
ever since you fed his head
with fairy tales
about saving the world.
Your partner has
a mind of his own, Mr. Rory.
Which is more than
I can say of you.
Are you saying
that I'm dumb, Captain?
Let's pretend, just for a moment
that you're the captain,
stuck in the brig,
while the rest of your crew
slowly perish
on their damaged ship.
Now, what would you do
to get yourself
out of that predicament?
Oh, no brilliant ideas? Really?
Why am I not
in the least bit surprised?
Shut your mouth. Now!
Okay. Let's all
just take a deep breath.
Or what? You'll punch me
in the face, or burn me alive,
or employ some other
barbaric form of violence?
That's why you recruited me,
isn't it?
To hit, hurt, and burn?
No. I recruited you
because you and your partner
were a package deal.
What?
I'm sorry, Mr. Rory,
but a serial arsonist
was never part of my plan
to stop Savage.
Much less
one with the IQ of meat.
I didn't mean to be so blunt.
If I can just have
a moment of quiet,
then perhaps
I can think of a way
of getting us
off this pirate ship.
I think I just beat you to it.
Can anyone hear me?
What the hell
do you think you're doing?
Me and the pirates
are gonna have a little parley.
- Do not do this, Rory.
- Too late.
What do you want?
I wanna speak to Captain Valor.
- About what?
- About a Timeship.
I am warning you.
Shut up!
I may have the IQ of meat,
but I know how to cut a deal.
(GRUNTS)
I'm listening.
You want the Waverider,
I want to go home.
And where is home
for a man like you?
2016 Central City.
Of all the places and time,
you want to go there?
That's right.
To the exact moment Hunter
recruited me and my partner
on this suicidal mission of his.
But this time, I'm gonna
tell him where to shove it.
VALOR: Let me get this straight.
I let you go,
you'll deliver the Waverider?
Yes. Do we have an accord?
You think your friends will believe
you were able to escape?
Not unless I do this!
- KENDRA: How's it going out there?
- ATOM: Good.
By which I mean
utterly terrifying.
I'll have the breach sealed
in two more minutes.
Okay. How's your oxygen level?
(SIGHS)
I think the technical term
is "lousy."
Just two more minutes.
You got this.
SNART: Nothing quite like dying
to make you think about
all the mistakes,
all the wrong choices.
Is this Leonard Snart
coming to God
in his final moments?
Hardly.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Just wishing I could
take a few things back.
I should've left Mick
in future Star City.
Why didn't you?
Without me to keep him in check,
Mick can be a scary guy.
Agreed.
Hate to break it to you,
but even if we make it
out of here alive,
you're still gonna have
a problem on your hands.
I've seen enough to know that
Mick's in a dark place.
He's not coming back.
Man, I can't believe
Rory sold us out.
No, actually, I can.
But still, man.
What choice did he have?
The crew left on the Waverider
are most probably dead by now,
and God knows what happened
to Professor Stein.
It's no wonder that Mr. Rory
tried to save his own skin.
And what can I do about it?
I'm stuck in a pirates' brig
and I've lost both my ship
and the loyalty of my crew.
You're one to talk
about loyalty.
But I am, Captain Baxter,
and not because
I pledged an oath
to serve as a Time Master.
But a long time ago, I made
a far more important oath.
(SCOFFS)
When you call me a failure,
Captain Baxter, you're right.
Because I've failed
both my wife and my son.
For betraying the Time Council,
I have absolutely no regrets.
But failing to save my family...
That is something for which
I will never forgive myself.
Time Master Declan?
I thought the tribunal
was reconvening.
It's been canceled.
Lieutenant Coburn assumed
full responsibility
for the affair,
and the other Time Masters
were moved by her argument.
They've dismissed the charges?
Once Lieutenant Coburn resigned.
Why would she do that?
It seems she believes in you.
Now you must prove to yourself,
and all of us,
that you are indeed
the man she believes you to be.
(FORCE FIELD POWERS DOWN)
I thought we were done for.
Take heart, dear captain.
This battle is far from over.
Now, who would care to join me
in a daring escape?
Space Ranger.
Indeed.
(CRACKLING)
(BEEPING)
- KENDRA: Ray, don't go nodding off on me.
- (GASPS)
Uh, I wasn't. I was just
resting my eyes for a second.
- You gotta stay with me, Ray.
- (EXHALES)
Just stay focused on my voice,
and keep talking.
About what?
Anything.
Like, um, what was
your first pet's name?
(CHUCKLES) Slinky.
- Is that a cat?
- Burmese python.
Yeah, I'm allergic to cats.
And dogs. Pretty much
anything without scales.
Okay, then. Enough about pets.
Um...
- What's your favorite color?
- Don't have one.
Who doesn't
have a favorite color?
It's kind of like
having a favorite Beatle.
No. Everyone has
a favorite Beatle.
Uh, not me. Wouldn't be fair
to the other three.
Okay. Fine. Enough about pets
and colors and the Beatles.
It's a good thing
we never went for that drink.
This space date
is going terribly.
(BEEPING RAPIDLY)
Ray?
Are you still with me, Ray?
Ray, are you there? Ray?
I'm sorry.
That's all I have left.
Ray, are you there?
GIDEON: It seems that Mr. Palmer
patched the hole in the hull,
allowing Mr. Snart and Ms. Lance
to escape the engine room.
Okay, as soon as he's on board,
I need you
to close the cargo bay
and seal the airlock, Gideon.
Ray.
Ray, hey, stay with me!
GIDEON: I'm afraid Mr. Palmer
has gone into cardiac arrest.
Please, I can't lose you too.
Ray, I need you, please!
His chances of survival
are less than 3,720 to one.
Ray!
(GRUNTS)
Ray, come on. You're strong.
Please, come back to me.
Ray! (GRUNTING)
Ray!
(GASPS)
Could you please stop
punching me in the chest?
Why do they always
make it seem like
that's a good thing to do,
in the movies?
I thought you were dead.
I think I was there
for a second.
Thank you.
SNART: You kids need a moment?
Are you okay?
GIDEON: Mr. Palmer nearly died.
SNART: Welcome to the club.
Gideon, what's happening
on the Acheron?
Funny you should ask.
I just received a message
from Mr. Rory.
It seems he escaped capture
and is now returning
to the Waverider.
Told you.
Those pirates picked
the wrong guy to mess with.
Since when does Rory even know
how to fly the Jumpship?
How did he even find us?
GIDEON: Actually, I did the flying.
He received quite a beating
at the hands of the pirates.
That's him now.
SNART: You okay, Mick?
Boys!
The ship's all yours.
You son of a bitch.
What're you doing, Mick?
Getting us home. Are you in?
Yeah.
Time to choose a side, I guess.
Chosen.
(GRUNTS)
Bastard!
Get them!
I'll get the time drive.
Is the Acheron's Jumpship
still operational?
- Yes.
- Go to it, get off the Acheron.
I have some unfinished business
with Mr. Valor.
I'm not leaving my ship.
And we're
not leaving you behind.
So, what's the plan, Captain?
Valor and his men
substantially outnumber us.
We're not gonna be able
to defeat them
by conventional means.
GIDEON: Mr. Rory is making his way
to the engine room
to access the time drive.
I'll handle it.
(GRUNTS)
(FIRING)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
What's going on? (GRUNTS)
You're losing.
Gilbert?
GILBERT: The time pirates are, indeed,
10 seconds behind you.
And closing.
- That doesn't give us much time.
- You think Rip's plan will work?
Yeah, that's what I thought.
SARA: Step away from it, Mick.
I'll tell you what, blondie.
Walk away and I won't kill you.
You know I can't do that.
I like you, Sara.
You've got a lot of guts.
That's why I'm only gonna
kill you a little bit.
(GRUNTING)
(SARA GRUNTS)
SNART: Mick!
(GRUNTS)
PROFESSOR STEIN: Captain Hunter,
we're in position.
- Captain?
- Yes, yes!
I'm a little bit busy right now.
Be that as it may,
we've run out of time.
Captain, the plan.
(STRUGGLING)
We're waiting for your signal.
(GRUNTING)
- Gilbert.
- GILBERT: Yes, sir.
I need you to listen to me
very, very carefully.
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (SCREAMS)
Rip, we're good.
(GASPING)
GILBERT: Bulkhead door closed.
Explosive decompression
has evacuated the time pirates.
Thank you, Gilbert.
Please hail the Waverider.
RIP: Waverider,
this is Captain Hunter.
We've regained control
of the Acheron.
What's your status?
What are you gonna do, Snart?
I suppose
it wouldn't be very fair,
if I arrested you
after you reclaimed my ship
and apprehended
Jon Valor for me.
Happy to help out
a fellow Time Master.
Even though
I don't deserve that title.
I was wrong.
You've proven that today.
You're still
one hell of a Time Master.
Which is why
I'm giving you this.
- What's that?
- Gilbert?
GILBERT: Using the Vanishing Point's
most current timeline data,
I calculate a 99. 8% probability
that you will find Vandal Savage
in Harmony Falls, Oregon,
in March of 1958.
Thank you, Captain Baxter.
I still don't understand
why you're doing all this.
(SIGHS) Before all this started,
I don't think
I would have either.
We protect history,
safe guard time itself.
There is no higher calling.
It's called love.
MIRANDA: Rip.
Rip. Rip.
Look at me, Rip!
(SIGHS)
- Please, don't be mad at me.
- Oh, I'm not mad at you.
- I was going to resign.
- I know.
And I couldn't let you.
This has always been your dream.
Yes, but you are so much better
at this than me.
I can't understand why
you would give all that up.
It's funny, because you're
the one who made me realize
that I could never be
a Time Master.
I found something with you,
something wonderful.
I found love.
That thing that the Time Masters
always taught us to hide from.
But they were wrong, Rip.
Love is no threat.
It's beautiful and powerful,
and once you know it,
love changes everything.
Like it changed me.
And that's why I have to resign
because I could
never belong to something
that turns its back
on that truth.
Suddenly my chosen profession
seems so terribly unimportant.
No, the world needs
the Time Masters,
and the Time Masters
most assuredly need Rip Hunter.
(SCOFFS)
My only wish is that one day,
when you're off
traveling space and time,
you'll realize what I have
and understand why I'm doing
what I'm doing.
I hope you think of me
when that day comes.
I will.
Because I'll be with you.
Hey. I was just looking
for you right now.
How are you feeling?
Good. Yeah.
Turns out I bounce back
pretty quickly from hypothermia.
In fact, I managed to remember
some of the things
you said to me
when I was almost dead.
You were wrong, BTW.
You don't need me.
You don't need anybody.
You're pretty amazing,
and I'm lucky to be your friend,
be on this mission
together with--
That's surprising.
Okay, I'll say it.
Why don't we just drop him off
back in 2016?
Because my sister lives in 2016,
and your sister and your wife.
So, what exactly
are we talking about here?
Leaving Rory in the brig
until we take down Savage?
Oh, no, no, no.
The brig is unsuitable
for long-term incarcerations.
Giving him a free run
of the ship is not an option.
I'll handle it.
By "handling it,"
you mean murder.
I said I'll handle it.
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(SIGHS)
I told you that'll be
the last time you hit me.
(GUN POWERS UP)
You were right.
That's the plan?
Take me out
in the middle of nowhere,
where no one can find the body?
I wish there was
some other way, Mick,
but you're dangerous.
A liability to the team.
Team?
You and I were a team.
What happened to you?
People change.
You think
you're some kind of hero,
but deep down, you're still the
same punk kid I saved in juvie.
You haven't got the guts.
You wanna kill me?
Kill me.
Only one of us
is walking outta here alive.
You're right.
English - SDH