Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
We can't change history.
That happens, the Darhks
will be able to free their demon.
Do not let him take you away from me.
We can save Nora and stop Mallus
from being freed.
- Together.
- We have the six totems.
What if the only way to kill Mallus
is to let him out?
We are here to help you create
the anachronism,
so we can release Mallus,
and then we can kill him.
- I'll find you...
- Go!
No.
Nora.
Mallus is taller than I thought.
My name is "Malice," you fools.
What?
I knew it.
- Sounds way cooler.
- Hand over the totems,
or I will lay waste to your world.
You want the totems?
Come and get them.
Amaya!
All right, everyone fall back.
Rip, we're going to need a evac.
We're in over our heads here.
If my read of the situation
is correct,
what you need is a miracle.
I'm going to buy you some time.
- Wally, create a distraction.
- Got it.
I'm starting to think letting Mallus
out of his cage was a bad idea.
The Waverider's Time Drive
is highly unstable.
- Removing it...
- May very well be the only way
to hold our adversary at bay.
I believe I know
what you're planning.
It is extremely reckless
with a low likelihood of success.
Well, then, it seems like
I've finally learned to think
like a Legend.
- The odds of survival are 0.0...
- I know.
I will miss you, Gideon, truly.
No more than I'll miss you, Rip.
Guys, I can't hold him off
much longer.
I'm going to get her to the med bay.
Wally, I need you back
on the ship now.
So, you're saying you don't fit in?
You're an outcast, a misfit.
That's assumed.
Sounds to me like you're a Legend.
Together you are the best crew
the best team,
a captain could ever hope for.
Love changes everything.
Daddy?
Gideon, get me eyes on Rip.
I have a visual, Captain.
What the hell is he doing?
Rip disengaged the time drive,
making it unstable.
When it reaches critical mass,
it will consume Mallus.
And Rip.
- Gideon, time-jump us out of here.
- But she can't.
Rip has our time drive.
Yes, but there is another one.
On the Jumpship.
Wally?
Gideon, put me through to Rip.
Rip?
I'm a little busy at the moment,
Sara.
Look, you didn't tell us
that you were buying us time
with your life.
Listen carefully.
This gambit will not kill Mallus.
It will only delay him long enough
for you to make an escape.
There has to be another way.
No, there isn't.
It's all right, Sara.
I should very much like to see
my wife and son again.
I will miss you, Captain Lance...
you and the rest of the Legends.
My one hope is that you all
live up to that name.
Captain Lance, the time drive
is reaching critical mass.
Can we jump?
Miss Tomaz has finished
making repairs.
We have 15 seconds.
Good bye.
Good bye, Captain.
Gideon, get us out of here.
Ironic, isn't it?
A time demon who's run out of time.
You don't drink.
Yeah, well, we lost Rip.
Okay, somebody's got to say it,
so I'm going to say it.
This is all our fault.
Apparently I'm not going to say it,
but, yeah, we let Mallus out.
Well, whose stupid idea
was it to fight him
with some magic necklaces?
It wasn't the totems that failed.
It was us.
Yeah, we might want
to rethink that whole,
"We screw up things
for the better," motto.
Okay, so, what's the plan, Captain?
All I know is that Rip gave his life
so that we could take the totems
somewhere that Mallus
can't find them.
So, that's what we're going to do.
And where is that?
The Old West.
Salvation, North Dakota.
It's basically a temporal blind spot.
Wait a sec, we just unleashed
an ancient time demon
who's about to lay waste
to all of history,
and our plan is to hide?
Yes, it is.
Gideon, plot a course.
Well, I hope you're here
to make good on your promise
and kill me, which would work
out for both of us.
It'd be a real win-win.
Mercy killing's not my style.
Even if it was,
you don't deserve my mercy.
You deserve to live out
the rest of your days
knowing that you destroyed
your own daughter.
What are you doing here?
It's my lab.
Don't do anything stupid.
Captain, we've arrived
in the Wild West.
Thank you, Gideon.
Have everyone meet me
in the fabrication room.
Ray, nothing stupid.
Is she right?
Are you really planning
something stupid?
Maybe.
Probably. Most likely.
But it could fix this whole thing
and get Nora back.
Salvation 1874
Salvation Town Hall
Salvation
Yo, this is tight.
I know everyone's dead.
I know time is broken.
But can we just take a second
to acknowledge this?
You know, as much as I enjoy
this getup
and I actually really do...
Mallus is still out there.
And we'll deal with him, but first,
we need to get our heads on straight.
- How long is that going to take?
- Depends.
- On what?
- How strong the whiskey is.
All right, I think it's working.
I am on the edges of a plan.
Great. Let's hear it.
So, we know that the six totems
are the only thing
that can stop Mallus.
They weren't much use
to us last time.
"Us" being the key word.
You and Amaya were born
to wield the totems,
- and the rest of us are just...
- Losers.
That's why Rip picked us,
Snart, the Professor,
those stupid hawk
flying-chicken people.
We're all expendable.
Not that any of these
unwashed hayseeds
look like righteous totem bearers.
Who you calling a hayseed?
Jonah Hex.
You know this guy?
Me and these ruffians go way back.
Wally, Zari, this is Jonah Hex.
Nice hat.
Thank you, ma'am.
Obviously joking.
So, who died and made you sheriff?
That'd be the old sheriff.
Well, now it's my job
to keep the peace around here.
So, you can't be causing any trouble.
We are not here to cause trouble.
We are here to avoid it.
This the trouble you aiming to avoid?
Not exactly.
- Looks like Phallus...
- Mallus.
Mallus has brought back
our old buddies.
I thought Mallus wasn't supposed
to be able to find us here.
Fools.
Mallus sees all, knows all.
Then why did he bring back
you jerks to do his business?
Because he's probably still
recovering from that beat-down
- Rip gave him.
- Oh, now, do not confuse
Mallus' clemency with weakness,
my hearties.
- Mallus will spare your lives.
- It's actually "Malice."
- It's actually Mallus.
- Nope, "Malice."
- Mallus!
- Guys, it doesn't matter.
If you surrender the six totems.
Yeah, sorry, we only brought two,
and mine's kind
of a family heirloom, so...
Then we have no choice
but to march our army on your town
and kill every fool
who has given you shelter.
You leave my town out of this.
You have been warned.
We'll be back to collect the totems.
Shall we say high noon tomorrow?
Tootles.
Well, so much for hiding out.
Guys, if you can hear me,
I need you to put
the Waverider on lockdown.
You know, I'm only doing this
because of my daughter.
Well, if this works, we can save her.
Going somewhere, Raymond?
No, no, of course not.
Zari rerouted the time drive, so...
Yeah, Gideon just said someone
re-rerouted it. What are you doing?
Well, Sara wanted the ship
on lockdown, so...
So you decide to load
Damien Darhk onto the Jumpship?
- Hey, Nate.
- Don't wave.
Have you lost your complete mind?
- I know this looks bad.
- Yeah.
But there's a completely
rational explanation.
I'm listening.
Me too.
- Sorry.
- Oh, my nose!
Ray, what are you doing?
You know, not that
I couldn't watch Pompadour
get punched out all day,
but you could have just told
him where we're going.
- Ray open the door.
- Where are we going?
To right before Mallus
took over Nora.
And I can't tell anybody
because we're not supposed
to travel to events
in which we've participated in.
I will punch through this door!
- And no one on your team trusts me.
- Damn it, Ray!
That goes without saying.
Did you hear me over comms?
Ray punched me in the face
with his giant banana hands
and took off with Damien Darhk.
What are you doing?
Lyoga root?
Do you really think
this is the best time
to go on a psychedelic vision quest?
Who am I kidding?
It's never a bad time to go.
You can't come with me, Nathaniel.
I'm going all the way back
to the beginning
to meet with my ancestors...
the original totem bearers.
Why?
Sara thinks we're not cut out
to wield the totems.
But I believe the reason
we didn't defeat Mallus
the first time is because
we didn't know how.
So, you want to talk
to the original bearers
so they can teach you
the totem user manual.
- I am definitely coming with you.
- No.
It was my decision
to save my village.
I shattered history
and allowed the demon to escape.
It's up to me to find a way
to stop him.
Amaya.
Amaya, look at me.
We decided to save the village.
Now, if you're going to go
on some crazy drug trip,
you better believe
I'm coming with you.
No, Nathaniel...
You're only supposed to take
a sip of that.
Really?
I'll see you on the other side.
Nate.
Nate, open your eyes.
Totem bearers.
What are they doing?
Oh, snap! They got lasers!
Nathaniel?
Wake up.
They beat him
with the Care Bear Stare!
No.
They stopped Mallus together.
That is the only way to defeat him.
Together. Together.
Database access passthru
alternative delivery
What gives, Gideon?
You have a visitor.
Begging your pardons, ma'am.
Captain Lance thought
that you might need a hand.
Yeah, I think she was just
trying to get rid of you.
What in tarnation is that?
It's a computer program I designed
to act as a temporal beacon.
Like a smoke signal.
Sara wants us to find
new totem bearers,
but we're a little short on allies.
Well, the Legends,
they may be an unorthodox lot,
but they got a knack
for making friends.
Like you?
I don't take a shine to most folks.
Me neither.
Well, you send out a smoke signal...
I'll bet you a greenback
you get a response.
I'll take that bet.
Sheriff.
You can call me Jonah.
Ma'am.
Hello, this is Nathaniel Heywood
speaking,
and we have a code 113.
Repeat, code 113.
If the code is 113,
it's off to the bridge
for you and me.
You memorized Ray's song?
He sings it often enough.
Nathaniel and I shared
a cup of Lyoga root tea
to access the memories
of the original totem bearers.
Oh, you are still high.
Now, the reason the totems
haven't been working for us
is not because we're unworthy.
It's because we've been using
them wrong.
The totems were not designed
to be used individually.
- Individually... individually.
- Shut up.
Their elemental powers combine
to create a perfect being of light
to fight Mallus with.
- Like Voltron.
- Like Voltron?
Defender of the Universe.
Right, well, weren't all
of the original totem bearers
actually from Zambesi?
But you all wield them now.
I mean, do you think
that was an accident?
Yes, I do.
Mick...
the chances of you running
into your father in Vietnam
are next to zero,
and yet you did,
and you came out
a better man for it.
Zari, do you remember the way
your totem called to mine
the moment you put it on?
It wanted you to stay with us.
So, maybe it wasn't a coincidence
that I joined the team.
No.
That was just another one
of the Englishman's crazy ideas.
Sara.
Please. We have to try.
- Fine.
- Sick. Yes.
Because, no coincidences.
All right, Amaya. It's your show.
How do we create this
magical light being?
All right, everyone, over here.
Make a circle.
Mick, your fire is going to provide
our champion with its spark.
Zari, use your air to give it breath.
Wally, use water to flow life's
blood through its veins.
- Nate.
- I will use the Earth totem
to give Voltron flesh.
- You got to stop calling it that.
- I will never stop calling it that.
I'm going to use my spirit
to provide it with a soul.
But without the final totem,
our champion will be incomplete.
No, it's not happening.
Without the death totem,
the other five totems
can only imprison Mallus.
We need death to kill him
once and for all.
Don't worry.
If you turn into a witch wench,
I'll kill you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
All right.
Let's do it.
We're good.
Okay, hold hands.
- Come on.
- Clear your minds...
and focus on your breath.
Imagine a perfect warrior
of justice, mercy, and light.
Why does
Pretty have such girly hands?
Damn, this Lyoga root is strong.
Concentrate, Nate.
Think about
"Voltron, Defender of the Universe."
I kind of pictured myself
wielding something cool,
like a lightning totem.
Am I crazy, or is Jonah Hex hot?
Eh, you could do worse than Hex.
- Wait, you can hear me?
- We can all hear each other.
Even what I said
about Pretty's girly hands?
- Yes.
- Okay, please.
We need to clear our minds.
It's working.
Are we making a baby?
Guys, we have to focus.
You telling us to focus
is making it harder to focus.
All right, look, this is why
we're not worthy of the totems.
- Seriously, are we making a baby?
- Everyone, just shut up!
Kraken baby.
Is it supposed to be gooey?
Mick!
What? I'm just putting this slop
out of its misery.
Voltron.
Right, we need to try again.
No, what we need to do
is find some people
that are worthy of using
these totems.
If that's not an entrance line,
I don't know what is.
I got your message. We all did.
You guys just can't seem
to keep yourselves out of trouble,
can you?
Zambesi 1992
Whoa, sounds like I'm really
giving you the business in there.
- Yeah, still hurts.
- Sorry.
Okay, so here's the plan.
We have to knock Nora out.
Gently, because I know
she's still your daughter.
And we probably have to keep
her unconscious
until we figure out a way
to de-demonize her.
We better move quickly.
I can't believe you were ever
this young, Nana Baa.
I can't believe you came to my aid.
If you only knew the odds
against that happening.
Odds?
I've been given a chance
to fight alongside the woman
who saved Zambesi.
What was I supposed to say? No?
Am I still high,
or is the water witch a pal,
Helen of Troy a warrior princess,
and Jax is wearing a wedding ring?
I believe you owe me a greenback.
Not to look a gift horse
in the mouth,
but I was hoping
for some real soldiers.
I'm Helen. Nice to meet you.
Huh. Nice to meet you, little lady.
Well, it's really good
seeing you again, Jax.
I just wish it was under
better circumstances.
Hey, listen, I'm just glad
that we got Zari's beacon in time.
I mean, going up
against three armies,
you all are going to need
all the help you can get.
Hey, what happened to Ray?
You do not want to know.
Come on, do it now.
Before it's too late. Go!
Oh, man, you really
shouldn't hit your daughter.
You stole my Nanite gun?
But that'll kill her.
Sorry, honey.
Nora...
Nora.
Dad. Why?
Because I love you
and I couldn't watch you
become a monster...
like me.
You fool.
You thought destroying this vessel
would thwart my return?
I'll gladly take you instead.
I was counting on that.
Good bye, Nora.
- Go, go.
- No.
Get her out of here.
- Go.
- No!
Dad!
Is it weird that I keep
expecting your granddaughter
to use that thing
to try to drown me again?
This Kuasa never suffered in the war.
She never worked for the Darhks.
She's a good person
who's led a good life.
And she and Mari share the totem.
It worked.
I can't believe it.
I can.
You told us the universe
was guiding us,
prepping us for this fight.
You listened to your heart,
and it drove you to do
a really good slash
super messy thing.
Since when did you have time
to have a baby?
You've only been gone
a couple of months.
Well, I mean,
that's how it is for you guys.
But for me, it's been five years.
Here, look.
Her name's Martina.
And her and her mom
are the light of my life, man.
Well, mazel tov.
- Okay.
- Cheers.
Yeah.
Okay. Stay with me, Nora.
- Okay, you're safe. It's okay.
- No, my dad. My dad.
He traded places with you
as Mallus's vessel...
to save you.
How could you let him do that?
- Why didn't you stop him?
- It's okay.
No, no! Dad!
Just point and shoot.
Damn, girl.
Damn. Where'd you learn
to shoot like that?
I learned to fight on Themyscira,
but the Legends were the ones
that inspired me.
You gave me the gift of a new life.
It is an honor to be here
to help you save yours.
Thank you, but we need to be
teaching you to use the totems,
and I'm pretty sure you didn't
learn that on Themyscira.
That's not why we're here, Sara.
We're here to help you,
not replace you.
Look, we've already tried twice,
and we failed miserably.
You still don't see it, do you, Sara?
You guys made Kuasa
and Helen's life better.
And that is just the tip
of the iceberg.
We are all here
to support the Legends.
And what, you're going to stand there
and tell me that
you aren't the exact people
to wield the totems
against Mallus now?
Good speech.
Thank you.
And it's a good point.
By the way,
I wanted to ask you, just,
did you mean what you said
the last time we saw each other?
When I told you to run?
No. Before that.
Oh, you mean,
when I told you, I loved you?
Yeah.
What do you think?
I...
think that...
Howdy, partners!
What did I miss?
Where's Darhk?
Wrong Darhk, wrong Darhk!
No, no, look, look,
she's, she's been de-Mallused.
She's no longer a demon.
So, so we don't have
to fight Mallus anymore?
Not exactly.
And what about Damien Darhk?
Long story short,
he sacrificed himself for Nora,
and now he's Mallus's vessel.
So, what's new in the Old West?
Well, Caesar, Blackbeard,
and Leif Erikson's crazy sister
are demon pawns.
They gave us an ultimatum
to hand over the totems.
Well, how long do we have?
All right.
We're facing an army of Romans,
Vikings, and pirates.
But you know what today is?
Today's the day that we prove
that Rip did not sacrifice
his life in vain.
And today is the day
that we prove that we are not losers.
that we earn the name Legends.
- Yeah.
All right, all right.
Now, how do we sneak out the back?
Nice of you to bring your fan club.
So...
about that ultimatum.
There is honor in surrender,
Captain Lance.
Our new god may grant you mercy.
Yes, be a good girl
and hand us over your magic baubles.
I changed my mind. New terms.
Get out of town or get hurt.
Attack!
Can you believe
this is my first time on a horse?
Haven't you ever learned
never to turn your back
on your enemies?
Caesar.
That's a Roman nose.
I should have known
it was just a tall tale.
You're not the Dread Pirate Jiwe.
No, her name is Amaya Jiwe
of the Great Tribe of Zambesi.
Tootles.
Dynamite? You sure about this?
No, but it's too late
for second guessing.
Do it now.
So, we should probably get
back to fighting.
Right.
Well, next round's on me.
Not to be a buzzkill,
but this doesn't look good.
It's Mallus.
Go. Make good your preparations.
The rest of us shall buy you time.
All right, you heard the lady.
Well, hopefully
this goes better than last time.
All right, we have to believe
in the totems,
that they've chosen each of us.
Well, if this really
is the end of the world,
then I choose
to surround myself with you guys.
Come on.
- Whoa. You feel that?
- It's working.
All right, now,
imagine a powerful light
of pure goodness.
Something's forming.
Can I peak? I'm gonna peak.
- Oh, God.
- Oh, God?
- What "Oh, God"?
- Everyone focus.
Wait, is somebody thinking of...
I'm sorry, you said think
of something pure,
- and I thought...
- No, you didn't.
Again, I said I'm sorry.
Yeah, I can't stop
thinking about him, either.
Guys, whenever you got...
What the Sam Hill is going on?
I think this is part of Sara's plan.
I lo... lo... love you.
The Blue God, he has returned.
That is your captain's plan?
Where in the hell are Sara
and the others?
- That is Sara and the others.
- What?
Beebo hungry.
Man, have I missed you guys.
Like the gods of Olympus
made manifest.
Oh, hey, I know you're not
gonna take that, Beebo.
- Nana baa...
- Come on, guys. You got this.
Beebo can't breathe.
Don't you dare give up on me, Lance.
Beebo.
Yeah. Come on, that's it.
Kick his ass.
Not even the six can stop me now.
Beebo want cuddle.
No!
Guys. Guys.
Are you all right?
Guys, we did it.
Our totems united to create
a single furry love child.
Worst orgy ever.
Dad.
I'm sorry, Nora.
He died a good man.
Damnation. Now I just have seen
about everything.
So wait. Wha... That's it?
You... you destroyed the demon?
I'm just glad the ancestors
aren't here to see this.
Yeah, but Rip would be proud.
Yes.
We did it, Mick.
Get off of me.
The totems came together
when the world needed them most.
Now it's time for them
to find new bearers.
I trust you'll keep them safe
until they do, Nana.
Are you sure you don't want
the power to move earth,
call on the dead?
No, I'm good with just steel.
And I prefer being a speedster
over a water wizard.
Too old for jewelry.
Nana baa.
Unhand me, you fiend.
You shall pay dearly for this.
He saved us.
Beebo is our one true god.
The bonny ones always
be the craziest.
Well, I guess we'd better get
to mind wiping Mallus's three amigos.
Guys, you think this was crazy?
Try having a kid.
Oh, no, thank you.
I bet you're damn good at it.
I'll be seeing you, Miss Lance.
Oh, you can count on it, Miss Sharpe.
Come on.
No.
Well, seeing as though
this is the last time
we'll see one another...
Something to remember me by.
Oh, your dirty hat.
That's... that's weird.
But sweet.
Hey, stop. I need to...
I need to talk to her
for, like, two seconds.
Alone, please.
I lied.
It'll be more like 20 seconds.
So, I found something on the ship
that was your dad's,
and I thought maybe you'd want
something to remember him by.
As I spend the rest
of my life rotting
in a Time Bureau prison?
This is my father's time stone.
He died to give you a second chance.
Don't waste it.
Are you glad I picked you up
in Zambesi six months ago?
I think the words you used were,
"Just one more mission."
It's better than the line
they used on me.
"Come with us if you want to live."
I almost die every week on the ship.
- But you found a home.
- I did.
And as much fun as this has been,
it's time for me to go home.
Come on, you can't leave me
and Sara and...
Thanks. My pleasure.
You guys are my family.
Always will be.
But I have another family
waiting for me
in the years to come.
And they need me more.
Well, you always have a home
on the Waverider.
I'm gonna miss you guys.
Is that Jonah Hex's hat?
- Shut up.
- Is there...
- I can't.
- Did they is this...
- Stop, please.
- I'll miss that.
Zambesi 1942
Yeah, I guess this place is all right
if you like untouched nature
and beautiful views.
I do love it here.
But there are a lot of things
I'm gonna miss,
like cheese puffs and sports bras.
And you, Nathaniel.
You aren't gonna miss
any of those things...
because you're not
gonna remember them.
I don't want to forget...
Because if I do,
I would have lost the only part
of you that I'm allowed to keep.
Good bye, Amaya.
Don't turn around. Don't turn around.
Don't turn around.
Aruba 2018
Good call, Mick.
When I said Aruba,
I meant me, not all of you.
Still, nothing helps
a broken heart like a good tan.
Should have invited Ava.
Oh, we've got plans.
And until then, she's busy fixing
all those pesky anachronisms
we left behind.
Well, that's the thing
about defeating
an ancient time demon
everything else seems boring.
I'm good with boring.
Hey, idiot. Get out of here.
This is a private beach.
Fancy meeting you lot out here.
Constantine?
Did you really think I was him?
It's me.
Gary, Ray obviously
has been day drinking.
- The wig's too much, right?
- No, it's very presidential.
Gary, what do you want?
He's been with me, love.
Oh, I need a word with you sorry lot.
Now...
whose brilliant idea was it
to let an ancient demon
out of his bloody cage?
Sara's.
Well, you opened a door, love.
And Mallus wasn't the only thing
that got out.