Previously
on Legends Of Tomorrow...
Thank you for notifying us
of Director Hunter's whereabouts.
Now the Legends
are free to fly the skies?
The Time Bureau
has bigger things to worry about
than a bunch of idiots.
Mallus is getting stronger,
Captain Lance.
There is a war coming,
and history needs you to be ready.
- Do I know you?
- No. No.
I'm Marty.
So, you're Leonard Snart's
doppelganger?
No, I'm Leonard Snart,
but you can call me Leo.
I'm asking you
to let me die
so that you may live.
This is the last store in town
with the Beebo dolls, Clarissa.
I promise I am not leaving
without one for Lily.
Professor Stein. Merry Christmas.
And a happy Hanukkah to you, Chuck.
Every kid needs a Beebo doll, right?
So it would seem.
I got one. I can't believe I got one!
I don't suppose you can tell me
how many Beebos you have back there.
Plenty. Don't worry about it.
That was our last one.
Actually, we just ran out of them.
- But you just said...
- I'm sorry, folks.
We are expecting
a new shipment in February.
February?
Five-year-olds
don't wait until February.
Wait!
There's one more Beebo right there!
Move!
Think, Marty.
Distance of about six meters,
allowing for air resistance.
Breathe in, hold...
- Eureka. I've got it!
- Beebo loves you.
Get him!
Barbarians!
Great Scott!
Barbarians?
Gideon said that you
wanted to see me.
Come in.
Have a seat.
You comfortable?
I know the Legends lost a friend.
I've been there.
I want to help you guys
through the grieving period.
Oh, that's very sweet of you.
I want to give you the chance
to get anything off your chest.
Anything at all.
What would you like to say...
To Professor Martin Stein?
I think that everyone
copes in their own ways.
It's clear the Legends
are ill-equipped to cope at all.
This way?
This is wrong.
Well, actually, there is one question
I never got to ask Marty.
Great.
When I reduce
the Waverider's coefficient
of sinusoidal depleneration,
it seems to inversely hyper-celerate.
Let's hear it again.
What would you like
to say to me, Nathaniel?
Still, a little too nasally.
Remember, you speak very precisely.
This is therapy.
Not acting class.
Nice. That's the right level
of frustration.
Very Stein.
Now just do it with the puppet.
My goodness, you're really
working out some rage issues
with Professor Stein.
No, I just hate puppets.
All right, I am
putting the puppet away.
I get it now.
It wasn't the best tactic.
Look, Jax,
I think that you, even more so
than the others,
must be in pain about this.
He died so I could live.
End of story.
It wasn't your fault.
I should never have given him
that Firestorm cure.
I should've been strong enough
for both of us...
Mmm.
No. We're not doing this.
What was that?
An anachronism caused
a disturbance in a temporal zone
which created a Timequake.
And this is where Marty
would've said, "Fascinating."
All right, everybody,
I know you're sad,
so this is what we're gonna do.
I want you to take
all of your feelings about Martin
and put it in a box, and then I
want you to close the box.
And then you're gonna lock the box.
Well, that sounds healthy.
Maybe not, but we got a job to do.
Gideon, the anachronism, please.
A "Level 12"?
"Level 10" didn't do itjustice.
Leif Erikson's Vikings set up
a colony in the New World
around 1000 AD.
Little known fact, the Vikings
"discovered" the Americas 492 years
before Columbus, but due to
Erikson's adoption of Christianity,
the Vikings decided
to pack up their bags and head home.
Sorry, Gideon, you were saying?
In this version of history,
the Vikings stayed and conquered
all of North America
or as it's called now, New Valhalla.
- Cool hat.
- How many beers is that?
It's not even noon yet.
You have a problem, Mickey.
I don't have a problem.
Now shut up.
All right. Let's go.
I don't think the Legends
are ready for the field.
Listen, Leo, kicking ass
is how we heal.
I don't like it, sister.
This land is bountiful,
but its people,
these Skraelings...
They're skilled warriors.
We should not challenge them.
It's time to return home
to Greenland.
Brother, this continent is vast.
Who knows how far west it goes
and what riches it has to plunder?
It is our destiny to conquer
all of New Valhalla.
That's Leif Erikson
and his sister Freydis.
Now, this moment
has huge historical significance.
It determines whether or not
the Vikings leave North America
which for me is very exciting...
You okay, man?
Yeah, yeah. I'm fine.
Let's just stay on mission.
Okay.
The Christian monks
say that endless war
means our people
will never know peace.
It is what the Blue God
has demanded, brother.
The anachronism isn't a weapon.
Uh, guys, we're dealing
with some kind of Blue God.
Found him.
Is that Martin?
Martin's the anachronism.
They use his genius
to conquer the New World.
Hey, it's supposed to be
a stealth mission.
Damn it!
Jax, get back into position. Now.
Jefferson, what are you doing here?
I haven't seen you since...
1987.
Uh, don't worry, Martin.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Wait! No, no, no, no!
- Hey, you all right?
- Most certainly not!
Look out!
I haven't had a bath or a change
of clothes for over a week.
I could've died.
- Was it something I said?
- No, nothing. It's fine.
We just gotta get out of here
before the rest of the clan comes.
No, no, no. Wait, wait.
- We have to go back.
- Go back for what?
- My Beebo.
- What the hell is a Beebo?
As in "cuddle me" Beebo?
It's a Hanukkah gift for Lily.
We're not going back
for some damn toy!
You don't understand!
That damn toy
is gonna change history!
The four-eyed man has escaped.
No matter.
We still have our god.
Beebo hungry.
And our God hungers for battle!
- Yeah!
Beebo! Beebo!
Beebo! Beebo! Beebo!
All right, let me get this straight.
So the Vikings think
that Beebo is a god.
Beebo as in,
"Wow, wow, Beebo love you!"
As preposterous as it sounds,
that obnoxious toy
is the only reason I survived.
The Vikings who found me in the woods
were about to kill me
when Beebo spoke.
It was like a spell
was cast over the barbarians.
Here. This should warm you up.
- Earl Grey?
- With a little bit of brandy.
Oh. My favorite. Thank you, Jefferson.
It does make sense.
Norse mythology is filled
with creatures like Beebo.
Trolls, gnomes, tomtens...
Okay, sure.
But thinking he's a god who wants
them to conquer the New World?
You see, at first,
the Vikings thought
that only I could make Beebo talk.
But, it soon became clear
that my translations
were not what Leif's sister
wanted to hear.
Freydis usurped my position
and twisted Beebo's words
for her own agenda.
All right, sounds like
we gotta go get that Beebo,
and send the Vikings packing.
Zari, can you take young Stein
to get cleaned up?
Come on.
I could help him, it's just,
I've got nothing else...
- It's okay. Zari's got it.
- Hmm.
Mart... Marty. Martin.
You're looking young and lively.
- Good to see you.
- You too, Raymond.
One question. Where's me?
- Uh...
- At peace.
With your family
for the holidays.
Oh, I almost forgot!
Happy Hanukkah.
I'll drink to that.
It's disgusting.
What's wrong with this beer?
Man, can you believe Sara?
She doesn't trust me
around young Stein.
So you're saying you weren't planning
on warning Martin about him dying?
Okay, fine. But, come on, man.
Grey dies, and then all of a sudden
his younger self
gets displaced in time?
Yeah, I know. It's crazy that we
keep bumping into ourselves.
Yeah.
I mean, Ray and the baby Dominator
and Sir Stein and his killer 'stache?
Mick's dad. I mean,
this can't just be a coincidence.
What if this is fate's way
of saying we should step up?
That we can actually improve things.
Martin made his choice, Jax.
We should be honoring his sacrifice,
not trying to undo it.
Yeah, but it's Grey.
I mean, how can we not tell him?
Because what if
knowing about his death
makes young Marty choose
not to create the Firestorm matrix?
Or meet you,
or step foot on the ship?
He never would've wanted you to risk
the present to save him in the past.
And how exactly do you know
what he would've wanted, Ray?
You weren't psychically
connected to him for three years.
Gideon! The beer
tastes like sewage water!
Was that a question, Mr. Rory?
Don't get smart, lady.
I adjusted the fabrication settings.
The Waverider is now a dry ship.
No alcohol allowed.
You son of a...
You said your drinking
wasn't a problem.
If you can go
a couple of days without booze,
you've proven your point.
"A couple of days"? Forty-two hours?
Forty eight.
So I checked the lunar calendar,
and today is Yuletide.
Oh. Like Christmas?
Well, before Christians rebranded it,
wreaths, trees, elves were all
Norse traditions first.
And tonight, Leif is throwing
a huge Yuletide feast.
Which is the perfect cover for us.
Oh. We could dress up as Norse gods
and order them
to head back to Greenland,
or face our wrath!
- Worst idea you've ever had.
- That's a terrible idea.
Mmm-hmm.
Incoming transmission
from Agent Sharpe.
Put her on.
Agent Sharpe,
it's been a while, thankfully.
- Captain Lance.
- Let me guess.
You saw that there's
a Level 12 anachronism
and you're calling to lecture me
on everything that we're doing wrong.
No.
- Okay, yes.
- Hmm.
But, I also heard about Martin Stein
and I'm calling
to express my condolences.
Well, thank you.
But, my team and I,
we have it under control.
I hope so, because the Legends fixing
a Level 12 under normal circumstances
would be a Beebo Day miracle.
Did you just say "Beebo Day"?
December 25th, Beebo Day?
When families exchange gifts
and sing silly songs
and discover that they can
no longer live under the same roof?
Beebo Day is part
of the anachronism, isn't it?
- Yeah.
Never felt right.
This anachronism
is cementing fast.
And to be honest, my team is still
pretty raw from losing Stein.
We could use an outside perspective.
- Are you asking for my help?
- No.
Okay, yes.
All right.
What's the plan?
You ready to see
the Legends in action?
The goal is to do this peacefully,
without action.
There's a first time
for everything, I guess.
Hail, Leif, son of Erik.
I, Nathaniel Henryson.
Hail, Nathaniel, son of Henry.
A Yuletide surprise.
You sure this is wise, brother?
We know nothing
about these people.
We brought booze.
Tell me of your clan.
You certainly are
an odd collection.
We're from all over, but we
stick together the best we can.
Although recently,
we lost a brother.
Ah. That can be difficult.
I've lost far too many men
and women in my own clan.
It has made you soft, brother.
Let's not fight
in front of our guest, sister.
As far as strategy goes,
this would not be my first pick.
Why not?
They welcomed us in,
we get Beebo and we get out.
The Bureau has rules
about fraternizing with the locals.
And these costumes are ridiculous.
Nah, you look good.
- Give me that.
- No, no, no, no.
"No booze" means no booze, Mickey.
Stop calling me that.
You have 35 hours left.
Can you handle it?
Are you ready to admit
that you have a problem?
You're the problem.
Ah! There you are, you little bastard.
Beebo thirsty.
You dare to steal from our god?
He's not gonna drink it.
Our gods do not
tolerate such insolence.
Beebo will decide your fate.
Anyone have eyes on Beebo?
Short, blue, looking for cuddles?
Yeah. We're working on it.
Here we go.
By Odin's spear, you bested us!
Beautiful. And they can
hold their mead.
Tell us, which of these clansmen
are your husbands,
and we'll kill them.
Oh. I'm not really the husband kind.
Perfect. Me neither!
All right. You guys said if we won,
you'd take us to see your Blue God.
Two out of three!
Fellow warriors.
Our guest has been
stealing mead from the Blue God!
And now, our god
will render judgment.
Beebo! Beebo! Beebo!
Beebo! Beebo!
How judge you, Beebo?
Beebo hungry.
Our God demands justice!
To the pyre!
Yeah!
Nate and Amaya,
you're on Beebo.
Everyone else, let's make sure Rory
doesn't get burned alive.
Freydis, it's Yuletide.
Let's not ruin it.
More wood. So bright Odin
can see it from Valhalla.
Is it weird
that I find her hot?
Weird, but then again,
not surprising.
Leo, can you
take care of the fire?
Copy that, Captain Lance.
I thought you said this was
an undercover operation.
Well, blowing your cover
is half the fun.
Into the flames!
Now.
It's a sign!
Beebo does not want
our clansman to be burned!
The Blue God has shown mercy.
I love you.
I accidentally squeezed him.
He's so damn huggable.
Unhand him or die!
I'm leaving myself wide open
and you can't land a single punch.
Yeah, I'm just warming up.
Let's up the stakes, then.
Loser takes the other's chores
for a month.
Deal.
I know what you're
trying to do, by the way.
What's that?
You're trying to distract me?
I'm also trying to beat you.
The distraction working?
I still want to warn Grey.
So do it.
I would've warned my brother
if I had the chance.
Yeah, but, Sara...
Just 'cause she's the captain
doesn't mean you have
to do everything she says.
Yeah, no, I know. But...
Ah. Jefferson. There you are.
Ah! Game over!
- Oh! Come on.
- I'm scary good at this.
You're just okay.
Forgive the interruption,
but I would very much
like to return
to my Clarissa and Lily.
With or without
that wretched Beebo.
Yeah, sure. I'll take you
in the Jumpship.
Yo!
This is your chance.
Find some loophole like I did
with Helen of Troy.
You could save your friend's life.
- Nathaniel!
- Beebo likes to play.
Nate, Nate! I'm open!
Whee!
I hate puppets.
Beebo want cuddle.
I know how much you
wanted to believe, sister.
But Beebo's a false god.
Full of false promises.
We are Vikings.
This is our land to conquer.
It's time to go home.
And abandon this colony.
It seems the old gods
have abandoned us.
Well, looks like the Legends
have saved Odin Day.
Odin Day?
Well, you mean Christmas.
Doesn't ring a bell.
Oh, I thought we fixed
the anachronism.
My name is Odin.
Ruler of Asgard.
Damien Darhk.
You know this guy.
And his daughter.
See? I told you the Norse god
costumes would work.
Bow to the king of the true Gods.
He has left Valhalla
to lead you into battle.
Together, we will
conquer the New World.
Mick, no. We're outmatched.
Let's go.
Kneel before Odin, brother.
That was unexpected.
I mean, not the Darhks showing up.
They seem to enjoy altering history.
- You retreating.
- Well, Vikings are one thing.
If we're gonna
tangle with the Darhks,
we've got to get
our heads on straight.
I, for one, am glad
you're treading cautiously.
We've arrived safely
in the temporal zone.
But I'm afraid the anachronism...
Let me guess, it's worse.
Thank you, Gideon.
Another Timequake.
We are not letting America go Viking.
Ava, can you call
the Time Bureau for backup?
Wait, wait.
Are we really that desperate?
- Yeah.
The last time we faced Nora Darhk,
she put Sara in a coma.
Right.
- I'll speak to Director Bennett.
- Thank you.
Wow. That's quite the getup.
Where's Martin and Jax?
Uh, they're on their way
back to Central City.
Gotta get Martin home
for the holidays.
You've been awfully quiet, Jefferson.
Uh, my bad.
I've just had some things on my mind.
It's good to be home.
I can't wait
to see Clarissa and Lily.
Listen.
This is going
to sound crazy, okay?
But, you need to open this letter
on November 28th, 2017.
I've seen Back to the Future,
Jefferson.
That mockery of time travel
that Clarissa adores.
I don't suppose this letter
has anything to do with my future.
This letter
could save your life.
Then I categorically
refuse to take it.
You know the dangers
of trying to improve history.
No, no. This is your future.
And your past.
Give me a little credit.
I know the team was lying
when they said
I was visiting family
for the holidays.
Then take the damn letter
and stop being so stubborn.
Think about your family.
This letter is a loophole.
Nothing changes
until November 28th, 2017.
Please.
Okay, Jefferson.
Thank you.
Hello, friend.
Looking for booze?
I'm not your friend.
You almost died back there
and I know you're
craving a drink.
That's why it's
so important to resist!
You have to stop numbing yourself
to fear and pain.
That's when
the true transformation begins!
Mickey!
You're right.
You're right. I apologize.
That was his name.
Your Earth-X Doppelganger
was my best friend.
We grew up together
in the resistance, and when he died,
I was devastated.
Seeing you made me realize
I was a long way
from acceptance.
I didn't come on board
just to help you process your loss,
I came so I could process mine.
Was that guttural sound
your response?
To what?
My heartfelt confession.
I don't care. I wasn't listening.
Well, the Mick Rory I knew did care.
And he did listen.
He was the kindest,
most selfless person I've ever met.
A far cry from the crude alcoholic
oafish waste of space before me.
I'm a disappointment?
The Leonard Snart that I knew
was a cold, ruthless criminal
who didn't say "Boo"
about my drinking
because he knew I could
get the job done.
I don't like you.
You don't fit in.
Why don't you go back
to that Nazi hellhole you call home?
If that's how you feel,
then I'll leave
as soon as we return from Vinland.
- Good.
- Good!
Are we clear, Agent Sharpe?
Crystal, sir.
Please tell me you have good news.
I'm afraid Director Bennett
doesn't believe this mission
is the best use
of our resources.
So, what, the Time Bureau
is just gonna let the Darhks
run around and change history?
The Time Bureau
is in disarray.
Ever since Rip
was sentenced to prison...
Wait. Rip is in prison?
He was hardly convincing
at the tribunal,
raving about Mallus,
completely unapologetic.
And in his absence, Damien Darhk
has recruited even more allies.
Gideon, can you pull up what
Director Bennett showed me, please?
Grodd survived Vietnam.
Darhk secured him
a means of time travel.
Of course.
Darhk and his daughter
are just too powerful.
They have magic
that we don't understand.
We've lost scores of agents
trying to fight them.
So what? What does that mean?
That you're just gonna throw
in the towel?
We can't afford
to lose anyone else.
And I can?
No...
Do you have any idea
how hard this has been on us?
I really am sorry, Sara.
Director Bennett has ordered me
to return to the Time Bureau, so...
Screw his orders.
I need you here.
Look, I know Darhk
is personal for you.
And you're the last person
to back out of a fight,
but you asked me
to give you an outside perspective.
If you're concerned about the safety
of your team, leave Vinland.
This is not a fight
the Legends can win.
Hey. You rang?
Yes. Heard you took young Stein
back to 1992.
- Yep.
- How did it go?
He's just glad to be home.
Okay. Here's the deal.
Backup is not coming.
The Time Bureau thinks
the Darhks can't be defeated.
And they're probably right.
Leo asked us
to talk about our feelings.
Well, my feeling is that history
needs us to stop the Darhks,
but after losing Stein,
I can't lose anyone else.
I need you guys to take
the Waverider and leave.
Not without you.
You can't face Darhk alone.
I have a plan.
I'm here to speak to Odin.
Let her pass.
My father will enjoy killing you.
You've come alone.
I'm here to make you an offer.
Oh, this ought to be good.
Oh.
Leave now
and I'll let you live.
No.
Hold up.
Your plan sucks.
Pretty's right.
Well, I can't do nothing.
Yeah, but you can
come up with a better plan
that like, doesn't get you killed.
Okay, Z, what's your big plan?
Well, first of all, you don't
enter the longhouse by yourself.
My father will enjoy killing you.
You've come alone.
Not exactly.
And then Darhk will
have some sort of quip.
Something evil.
But not too mustache-twirly.
What, are you gonna huff and puff
until you blow my house in?
What's the matter?
Performance anxiety?
So far this works, but it
doesn't solve our Nora problem.
And what about the rest
of the Vikings?
Odin is under attack!
Defend him if you
want to see Valhalla!
You're gonna need backup.
Listen, Sara.
Just don't let Grey's death
teach us the wrong lessons.
Either we do this together
or not at all.
Gideon, plot a course to Vinland.
What, are you gonna huff and puff
until you blow my house in?
What's the matter?
Performance anxiety?
Odin is under attack!
Defend him
if you want to see Valhalla.
It is I, Beebo,
risen from the grave.
Like Christ himself.
Yes. Jesus is the one true God.
But it doesn't mean science
or evolution isn't real.
Anyway, you need
to return to Greenland,
hmm, which will soon be melting,
thanks to global warming.
Which is also real.
Like a little fire?
How about a little ice?
Nora.
They killed the Valkyrie!
Nora!
Not this time.
Sara Lance.
Who's there?
Who are you?
What is this place?
I am Mallus.
Soon I will be free.
And your world
will know unendurable pain.
- You came back.
- It's like you said.
You needed me.
Well, your timing is impeccable.
It's a Christmas miracle.
Yes.
There is nothing
physically ailing you, Captain Lance.
Told you, I'm fine.
You also told me
you visited an alternate dimension.
Well, it wasn't my first time.
Sara.
Tell me exactly
what you saw in there.
I don't know, okay?
It wasn't about what I saw,
it was about what I felt.
It was an absence of feeling,
no warmth, no love.
Just a void.
And the only thing
filling the void was...
Mallus.
It seems Rip was right
to be obsessed with him.
I need to tell the Bureau.
Aren't you afraid of getting
in trouble for disobeying orders?
It was worth it.
I'll see you again.
Gideon, how's the old timeline?
Records show
that history has been restored.
New Valhalla
is North America again.
And the only war Beebo has incited
is in shopping malls
across the nation.
Sounds like our work here is done.
Gideon, you're sure there are
no other changes to the timeline?
If you're referring
to Professor Stein,
he still died in 2017.
I'm sorry, Jax.
I just don't understand.
The loophole, it should've worked.
That letter told him exactly how to
protect himself on the day he died.
What happened?
He must not have read it.
Oh! Hey, Lily.
A little birdy told me you
wanted one of these guys.
- Beebo! I love him.
- Happy Hanukkah.
Clarissa, you remember Jefferson?
You haven't aged a day.
Neither have you.
Can I get you some Earl Grey?
Uh, yeah, sure.
Come on.
I think I know
why you're here. Come in.
The letter, you never read it.
That's because I already burned it.
What?
I was tempted, to be sure.
I thought a lot about that date.
November 28th, 2017?
I'll be 67 then.
I'll have had adventures.
Watched my daughter grow up.
And I'll have made a friend
who is willing to risk far,
far too much for me.
I'm trying to save you.
You need to let me go.
We both know
you shouldn't be here.
I may have a life
ahead of me, but to you,
I'm a ghost.
No, to me...
I'm not gonna cheat death, Jefferson.
None of us live forever.
And yet I clearly live
a wonderful life with many chapters.
And if I had one wish, it wouldn't
be for me to prolong my life,
it would be for you
to live yours
and to have
all the happiness you deserve.
Okay.
Goodbye, Grey.
Goodbye, Jefferson.
Did you try to change his fate?
It didn't work, so, uh...
I'm sorry, Jax.
Me too.
If I stay on this ship,
I'll never be able to move on.
What do you mean?
You want to leave?
You can't leave, Jax.
No, you're not leaving.
You're a part of this team.
And I always will be.
But, right now,
this is something I gotta do.
I need a different kind of adventure.
Is this what you really want?
Yeah.
I would order you to stay,
but I know you'd just disobey me
and follow your heart
like you always do.
Hey.
Can you do me a favor?
Don't tell the others
until I'm gone.
I don't do goodbyes.
It's not my thing.
Yeah, yeah.
Totally. I get it.
Okay.
- Surprise!
You didn't really think we were
just gonna let you sneak out
of here without saying goodbye.
Yeah, you can't
celebrate the holidays
without the whole family.
Happy Yuletide!
Well, I think we made
an impressive team out there.
It reminded me of old times.
Hmm.
Mmm.
As you can taste,
I reprogrammed Gideon.
I should not have
tried to change you.
I'm sorry, Mick.
To the ones we lost.
Or left behind.
- Speech!
Speech, speech, speech!
Okay, all right.
Uh...
When Grey first dragged me
onboard this ship,
I thought it was the last place
that I wanted to be.
I mean, you were all
a bunch of screw-ups,
B-list superheroes,
washed-up bank robbers.
- No offense.
- It's true.
But, the thing is,
when you get a bunch of broken pieces
and you put them
all together the right way,
they make something new.
And suddenly, they don't
feel so broken anymore.
And I'm pretty sure
that's what a family is.
So, uh...
I don't know what happens next,
but I know I'll always
have a family here.
With you guys.
- That's right.
- You're right, little brother.
Always.
Cheers.
Well, it's been an honor, Captain.
Come here.
Hey.
I'm sure it's only
gonna be a matter of time
before some Aztecs with jetpacks
invade Central City, so...
Then the honor's been all mine.
It's been a long time, love.
John?
Now, let's see.
The last time we met,
I saved your soul.
Now there's something
you can do for me.
Look, I'd love to help,
but your timing is terrible.
But this won't take long, you see.
There's a demon out there.
It's possessing a little girl.
That demon,
he knows your name.
Beebo loves you.