Previously on "Legends of Tomorrow"...
I couldn't send Neron into hell
without sending Dez down with him.
I killed the man I loved, and for what?
John, you have to stop this.
If Desmond isn't dragged to hell
and you don't join the Legends,
the effects could be cataclysmic.
History be bloody damned.
I really care about you.
This thing between us, it isn't real.
It never was.
- Uh...
- What's that?
I think John just broke time.
Oy, see, check this out.
I got my powers back.
Zari.
Constantine did it.
He changed the timeline
back in New Orleans.
He saved old Dez.
Unfortunately, I have no
idea why you're a cat, Z.
Oh, quit your whinging.
I know it's a pretty raw deal for you.
Especially 'cause...
Well, who knows what
they put in cat food.
On the plus side you are cute as hell.
Z, it has been an experience.
Now, I'm gonna set the autopilot
to take you back to the "Waverider,"
but first we're gonna drop
me off somewhere fabulous.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Hope y'all are thirsty for champagne.
Because I'm feeling a little bubbly.
Whoo!
Hello, Red.
Ms. Monroe. How's
lady luck treating you?
Ooh. Ooh.
Red, it's me. Charlie.
- Shapeshifter.
- Cheers to Saint Patrick.
What are you doing here?
I haven't seen you since
we escaped from that prison.
Yeah. Hey listen, mate.
You got to stop doing
your leprechaun magic
so out in the open like this, all right?
I do this all the time.
These humans, they
don't notice anything.
Watch.
Lucky 11. Winner!
Quit doing that.
But I'm just having a little fun.
What's got you so worried?
The Magic Police?
They're called the
Legends and I'm just trying
to stay off their radar
for a little while.
Sounds to me like you're scared.
What, of them?
No, no, no, they're not dangerous.
They're just annoying
little boy scouts, you know?
Reach for the sky, you filthy animals.
Pretty please.
He asked nicely.
Greetings, gentlemen.
Ah, the leprechaun.
You fellas play?
Ahh... no.
Oh, my God. Why did you do that?
Marilyn Monroe.
I am killing it at
historical figure bingo.
All right, everyone, calm down.
We just saved your butts
from a very dangerous magical creature.
Who are you guys?
Hi, Nate Heywood. Monster hunter.
Just wanted you ladies to
know you're in good hands.
Man, Garima is gonna flip
when she hears we met Marilyn Monroe.
Do you think a murderous alien queen
that sprang to life from Mick's
fantasies is into Marilyn?
Yes.
Hmm.
What is up with these guys?
Gideon, any messages while we were gone?
You missed calls from Barry Allen,
Oliver Queen, and Kara Zor-El.
Sounds like the annual crossover.
Yeah, that's gonna be a hard pass.
Did I tell you Oliver owes me money?
I bet this year they'll swap costumes.
Oh, Zari. Well, I'm glad to see
that you made it back to the ship okay.
Okay, I hear you.
You're still mad at me.
Listen, I really need your help.
All right, yeah, I can
see that being a cat
is your main concern right now,
but I still don't know why you're a cat.
Ms. Tomaz was turned into a cat
during the team's encounter
with a Fairy Godmother.
Whoa, Gideon, your
latest upgrade, smoking.
Thank you, Miss Jiwe.
Amaya Jiwe, yup, that's me.
And may I say your
new upgrade and accent
are also smoking.
- Oh, yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
You know, I'm just trying something out.
Yeah, okay, one last question.
Why are the Legends
homicidal wankers now?
If you're referring to the
Custodians of the Chronology,
their policy towards magical creatures
has been shoot on sight
since their disastrous
encounter at Woodstock.
Right. Thanks, Gideon.
Must be fallout from
Constantine altering the timeline.
Right, this zero tolerance
bollocks ends now.
Hey, people!
I have an announcement to make.
Please, gather around.
Come listen.
So I know our shoot-first,
ask-questions-never policy
has lead to some
interesting decorations,
but it's time to change.
From now on we are going to
capture the magical creatures
and bring them to the Bureau
like we are supposed to.
Why are you looking at me weird?
Well, just seems like a shame
to change our policy now.
Considering we're so close
to capturing our white whale.
That's a "Moby Dick" reference.
And what is your white whale?
The only creature we
haven't been able to capture
because it's quite elusive.
Maybe because it has the
ability to change shape.
Shapeshifter!
How dare you step on this ship
and pretend to be our dead captain.
What?
Wait, Sara's dead?
Yeah, that's why we
know you're not Sara.
Is that why you guys are like this?
Like what?
Hunting down magical
creatures like it's a...
Yes!
Damn it, Garima.
I called dibs on killing
shapeshifter last week.
You know what? He did.
You remember when we were roasting
that little baby Gryphon,
which was delicious, by the way,
but you guys got into an argument
about who actually killed
it, so then Ray got upset
and he was like, "Hey, I
wanna kill the shapeshifter."
Oh, it heals itself
and turns into Amaya.
This is not good.
- Kill her again!
- I get to kill her this time.
After her!
Zari.
Oh, bollocks.
- Go, go!
- Come on, Ray!
Check the library!
Make sure she doesn't steal anything!
They've become maniacs.
Okay, this is bad.
What, Constantine?
Yes, this is his fault.
He needs to help us fix
this, but where is he?
Nice work, Zari cat.
I can't very well walk
around here looking like this.
Oh, hush, it's still me
despite the insane grin on my face.
I don't remember there
being a memorial here.
Sara Lance struck down by unicorn.
Bollocks.
Gary, you're late.
Uh, sorry, Mr. Heywood,
my cat-sitter quit on me, so...
This place is going to
hell in a hand basket.
Yeah, it's my bad, sir.
Look, the Custodians of the Chronology
just destroyed a freaking leprechaun.
All right, you know
what? If you see them,
tell them they're getting
a scream-down from me.
Oh, one more thing, Mr. Heywood.
Have you seen John Constantine around?
Is that a joke?
He's been in confinement for months.
You put him there.
- Idiots.
- Right.
This isn't the when
when I'm supposed to be.
Johnny... Johnny...
No, the truth is not the truth!
All right, this is not the when
when I'm supposed to be.
You should go.
So what's real, Johnny?
Reality is fractured, but the pieces,
they speak to each other like light
between broken mirrors.
John Constantine.
Confined for becoming
dangerously unstable
after suspected time crimes.
Are you real?
Do you exist? Because it's
really hard to tell these days.
Yup, bloke's gone cuckoo.
Ha.
I sense a familiar face.
Who is that?
Z? Z, Is that you?
Why the transmogrification?
Let's get this sorted out.
Yeah, all right, I'm sorry,
but this is the only way
that you will know your true self.
Oh, finally.
Hairball.
Because of you dicks, I
have been a cat for so long.
Do you know where this tongue has been?
Places.
I wasn't sure that
reversal was gonna work
because I've been feeling a little,
you know, insane lately.
Yeah, well, you only
have yourself to blame.
Wait, what?
You created a time wave
when you changed your past with Desmond.
Because you're the epicenter,
your experience of this
timeline and that one
both exist in your brain.
Just give me a break here.
All right, what you're trying
to say is that I broke time?
Yes, back in New Orleans.
Sure, you don't have to live
with the guilt of damning Desmond,
but you also never joined the Legends.
Without John's help with
the unicorn at Woodstock,
Sara died, which made
the Legends into killers.
Well, there's only one way to fix this.
We go to back to
Woodstock and we save Sara.
- Yeah.
- No!
Guys, you're not listening to me.
You have to go to New Orleans
and set history back on track.
Whoa, whoa, Z.
You're suggesting a total
reset of the timeline.
What we need is a surgical strike.
Now, if we save Sara,
then the Custodians of
the Chronology never exist.
I keep my powers, Dez is de-demoned,
Bob's your uncle.
I'm sorry, guys.
I have to stop you before you
before you make this any worse.
Ow!
All right, then.
I'm sorry, love.
Until you can learn
to stay out of my way,
then you...
...are a cat.
In the mood for a prison break?
Oh, yes I am.
Is the coast clear?
How much of that did you hear?
Uh... nothing at all.
Nothing about breaking
out or hacking history.
Please don't turn me into a cat.
Well, I didn't turn her into cat.
I returned her to being a cat,
which is considerably
easier, believe me.
But if you gotta, maybe
a Calico and real fluffy.
Okay, I'm ready. Do it.
- What are we gonna do with her?
- I have no idea.
You don't have to do
anything. I wanna help.
You do?
The Custodians of the
Chronology must be stopped.
They turned my Kaupe friend into a rug.
So if you're trying to defeat them,
I want in.
Oy, watch the bumps, yeah?
- Oy!
- Shh, someone might hear you.
Red Alert, the "Waverider" is landing.
- Red Alert.
- Oh, man, the Custodians are here.
Could things get any worse?
Wait, stop right there.
Are you me?
Yes.
From the future.
Do I ever find love, or
at least my sunglasses?
They might be in my other pants.
Yes, Gary, all that and more.
It's the Custodians!
But right now, I need you
to delay the Custodians.
Okay. Oh, but be careful.
There's been reports of a
shapeshifter on the loose.
Yeah, I know that already.
Because I'm you from the future, dummy.
Secure the prisoners.
Lockdown protocols have
been activated. Hurry!
Okay.
Come on.
We gotta find a place to hide.
Knock, knock, anybody home?
Come on, hurry up! Let
me out of this thing.
Oh, God.
Where are we?
This is Ava's office,
but she's gone.
Gone, gone?
I'm right here, you idiots.
Dad, we tracked a shapeshifter here,
so we're gonna need you to stand down
and let us our job and bag it for you.
Your job, son, is to bring the creatures
back to the Bureau alive.
Not leave their insides
strewn through history.
It's called payback for
what they did to Sara,
and don't get in our way.
Sharpie? What happened to you?
I'm allowed to grieve in my own way.
Why the hell are you out of your cell?
Well, plans change, luv.
Are you sure you're
okay, Director Sharpe?
I'm fine!
I'm just taking some time
to get my head together
after Sara was unicorned.
I'm really sorry about that.
Things are not as they seem.
- Amaya?
- No.
Well, it's a long story, but time is...
Well, broken.
What are you talking about?
Well, you see, you're
living in a timeline
that doesn't exist, and
we are from a timeline
where your hair is still blonde.
Okay, I don't have time
for this timey-wimey crap.
No, no, this is the truth.
Now, listen. The
Custodians of the Chronology
are actually the Legends of Tomorrow
and they're the good guys, mostly.
Yeah, and the kicker is
Sara is supposed to be alive.
Did you say Sara's alive?
Yeah.
I knew it!
I knew something was wrong.
I mean, I like the Indigo Girls,
but they should not be a way of life.
Then let's help them set things right.
What do you guys need from me?
Well, well, well, look who's
helping our magical fugitive.
Take position.
We were looking for you.
Got eyes on suspects.
Thought you might want to have some fun.
I got 12 gauges of fun right here.
That's it.
I'm placing you all under arrest.
Shut your mouth, pops.
Go!
Take cover!
Get 'em out of here!
I'll cover you. Go save Sara.
Did they really all
just kill each other?
Don't think about it.
And we'll go back in
time and we'll fix things.
We have to.
Target ahead.
Arming the weapons now.
Is that what I think it is?
Twilight Sparkle come to life.
We didn't screw things up
for the better this year.
We screwed things up
for the more magical.
- Yes!
- Nice shot!
Who the hell's in the jump ship?
Who cares? Mission accomplished.
And you guys thought
we needed Constantine.
Yeah, we saved Sara's life.
Now that should fix everything.
The Custodians should be
back to being the Legends,
and Zari should no longer be a cat.
All right, this might
be a crossed wired thing
in my brain, but that is still
a cat sitting there, isn't it?
Killing the unicorn
didn't solve the problem.
No, Zari, we're not
going back to New Orleans.
We need to find out what's
wrong with this timeline
and fix it.
All right, we go back to the Bureau,
figure out our next step.
Charlie, come on. Talk to me, luv.
What's happening? Is everything normal?
No.
In fact, things are
pretty far from normal.
No reason to panic. We still got this.
Right, we'll find out how the
boys died in this timeline,
then we'll go back and save them,
and hopefully when they return
they won't be magical
creature murderers.
Right, sounds so simple.
Hey, watch it.
Out of the way, suckers.
Make way for S.O.S.
What the hell is S.O.S.?
Good morning, Sirens.
Good morning, Hank.
Well, I hope you're
ready to go to work today
because we have one hell
of a case on our hands.
If anyone knows what
happened to the guys,
it'll be them. Hang tight on the ship.
Looks like I'm joining the S.O.S.
All right, ladies. Weapons check.
Way ahead of you, babe.
My pistol's hot and ready.
Hey, girls. Save some fun for me.
Amaya, what are you doing here?
We thought you went back to 1942.
I did, but then I heard
about your monster problem,
and, well, I couldn't stay away.
It's perfect timing.
We are up to our peaches
with magical creatures
and about to kick some ass.
I'm in.
Johnny, just be honest with me.
This thing between us, it isn't real.
It never was. It doesn't exist.
Get it together, John.
Come on. Get your head together.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
I know what you're thinking.
You want me to put things
back the way they were,
but that's not gonna bloody happen.
No, I'm not all right to be honest.
So what kind of fun costumes
are we gonna need for this mission?
We don't do costumes anymore.
Yeah, we stopped so we
could streamline missions.
Yeah, why get all dressed
up if we're just wasting
these magical creatures straight away.
I mean, please tell me you don't keep
a trophy room of their skulls.
What do we look like? Barbarians?
- No, we just toss them.
- You what?
Yeah, ever since that
Fairy Godmother killed
Nate, Ray, and Rory we just waste
any magical creature
that comes in our path.
No questions asked.
Well, they can't all be bad.
We haven't met a good one.
Hey, how is Zambesi?
Hmm? Who?
Zambesi. Where you're from.
It's great.
Yeah, it's, like, chill.
Super chill.
If I do what you ask,
I'd be sending Desmond to hell.
Yeah, I know, maybe I
deserve this insanity.
Oh, you're all soft.
Oy, wake up, losers.
I know how to fix it.
Right, we got to take care of
the Fairy Godmother in Salem.
Fire up the ship. I'm
heading up there now.
Cor blimey.
No more tea and crumpets
for this dodgy doppelganger.
Hard Drive here knew you
weren't really Amaya all along.
I'm equipped to detect
shapeshifter pheromones.
How fortunate our white
whale swam right into our net.
What is with you guys and white whales?
Oh, you really think
you three can take me?
Oh, I can take you alone.
Damn it. Get back here!
Oh, hey. How were the
Sirens in Space-Time?
Well, they're not the Custodians.
They may actually be worse.
Now, let's go save the lads.
The three of you have been so
rude with your nasty attitude.
♪ It will be ever so sublime ♪
♪ To slowly choke you up with vines ♪
Whatever you're gonna do, Charlie,
you better make it fast.
I got this.
♪ A peach or a cherry ♪
♪ Any good thing to make us so merry ♪
Prudence.
Fairy Godmother, are you finished?
That was fast.
Yes, and I was thinking,
if I'm to be your Fairy Godmother,
you must start behaving
like a proper young lady.
How do you mean?
Oh, nothing dreadful
or out of the ordinary.
Just chores, daily baths,
church service each morning,
and you must start eating broccoli.
But I don't want all that.
Well, until our bond is severed,
I'm afraid that's the way it must be.
Now, eat the broccoli.
Fairy Godmother, I relinquish you.
That's cool.
♪ I alone may become satiated ♪
♪ When you're all asphyxiated ♪
My bond with Prudence has been severed.
Oh, fiddlesticks.
You know, I hate to jinx us,
but I really think we
nailed it this time.
I just hope you guys are right.
What's wrong? What are you looking at?
There something on my nose?
Bollocks.
- Anything yet?
- Don't rush me, luv.
Who knows what surprises
wait for us in here.
Looks like there's
reptilians in the Renaissance.
Sounds like a team meeting.
I'll just pop in and say hello, shall I?
So put on your period-appropriate boots
because we are going lizard stomping.
Oh, hey, everybody, look.
It's our good friend, John Constantine.
Yay.
What the...
♪ Flying through history ♪
♪ Solving some mysteries ♪
♪ We give bad guys the boot ♪
♪ In super hero suits ♪
♪ We'll win our victory ♪
♪ By stopping witchery ♪
♪ So they've got magic ♪
♪ Well we've got heart and fabric ♪
♪ Puppets of Tomorrow ♪
♪ Puppets of Tomorrow today ♪
Welcome to "DC's Puppets of Tomorrow."
"Fraggle Rock" is going on here?
Well, today we learned about
the importance of cooperating.
And about the number three.
And about a famous man
from history named Napoleon.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
I think I need a drink.
Ooh, we can help.
♪ When you're thirsty for a drink ♪
♪ And you just can't reach a sink ♪
♪ You gotta ask for a help ♪
No, stop. All right, please, please.
No more singing.
Just tell me, why are you puppets?
Because Rory called us a
bunch of Time Bureau puppets.
Yeah, and then he ran off
with his new partner in crime.
So did you figure out how
I turned into a damn puppet?
Yeah, it's worse than I thought.
After we managed to separate
the Fairy Godmother from Prudence,
she somehow glommed onto Rory.
You can probably figure out the rest.
Well, we're just gonna have
to keep fixing what's broken
- until we get it right.
- Yeah.
Damn it.
Nope.
Hmm.
No plaques.
No plaques. No plaques.
We did it. I'm shocked to bits.
Everyone's alive, Zari's human again,
and I still have my powers.
Ah, that's smashing news, luv.
Yeah. I mean, sure,
it's got a few cracks,
but fixed the timeline.
- See that, Zari.
- John, are you okay?
Yeah, yeah, it's... Never better.
John. John.
What happened?
Passed out, mate.
He didn't just pass out.
His brain can't handle
this wad of bandages
you call a timeline.
I can take the pain, luv.
What if you can't?
What if you die, John?
What happens to all the people
who need you alive and Constantine-y?
Yeah, well, you can leave
that to the real heroes,
all right, because
I'm done giving a damn.
Oh, I see.
This is isn't about
saving Desmond anymore.
It's an excuse for you
to give up on yourself.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, just
leave him alone, will you?
You think because there's no
plaques the world is fixed?
I promise you, it's just
as messed up out there
as it is in John's brain.
I know you don't want
to send Desmond to hell,
but that doesn't have to
be the end of the story.
You of all people can find a
way to keep fighting for him.
Go to New Orleans and set things right.
Don't listen to her.
Come on, John. It's you and me.
We can make this timeline work.
No, Charlie.
We've tried over, and over, and over
to get what we wanted
and it hasn't worked.
Zari's right.
There's still hope for Desmond,
and maybe there's still
hope for your powers too.
Hope?
My powers aren't some magic trick.
They're who I am.
I'm not gonna just sit around
and hope that they come back.
I'll fight for them.
This ain't over.
Not by a long shot.
Ava, I wasn't expecting to see you here.
Yeah, the Bureau got an emergency alert
about a magical presence
in New Orleans, 2018.
I thought maybe we could
check it out together.
Let's get to work.
Cool.
Jeez.
I didn't live this specific
moment, but I remember it.
It's all part of jumbled, bloody memory.
By the way, only about
10% of what you're saying
makes any sense, but
by all means continue.
Right, so the earliest me
just left for the market.
The other one is upstairs
breaking up with Dez right now,
and when Dez leaves upset, I stop him.
Put things back to normal.
All right, good luck.
Blimey, that's a lot of ammo.
- Blimey?
- Huh?
Oh, I meant wow.
All right, boys, orders
are shoot to kill.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Shouldn't we discuss
what kind of creature
we're dealing with here?
We can't just go in guns a-blazing.
What if whatever's causing
this is just a little misguided?
It's a magical fugitive.
We kill those.
You two head out. Stay on the comms.
I killed the man I loved, and for what?
To buy New Orleans a little more time?
Neron needs souls...
Okay, right, I think... I think that
something should be landing
right here any second now.
I work alone.
Got it.
All right, Gideon,
what are we looking at?
I've located multiple
targets on the ground
each one with a substantial
magical signature.
Do we have a visual yet?
Coming up now.
Wait, that's John Constantine,
and there's more than one of him.
Looks like our shapeshifter
has a shapeshifter friend.
Wait a second, how do you know that
that's not really Constantine out there?
Because it's John Constantine.
He doesn't time travel.
Believe me. I tried to recruit him.
Okay, so why don't we
capture all three of them
so we can find out if any
of them are the real John?
What is wrong with
you? You feeling okay?
I'm fine. I'm just a firm
believer in taking precautions.
Precautions. Good one.
Ray, Rory, what's your status?
All right, we're in position,
with our sights on the shapeshifter.
When do we get to shoot?
All right, on my mark, open fire.
Sara, don't.
Damn it, Ava, why not?
'Cause I'm the shapeshifter.
Guys, stand down, we have
a code blue on the ship.
What the hell's a code blue?
Just don't shoot yet.
There's something going on in your life.
Just be honest with me.
Yeah, do you know what?
This thing between us?
It isn't real. It never was.
It doesn't exist.
You should go.
Yeah, you're right. I should.
But this, this was real, Johnny.
Hey, you... you dropped this.
My phone.
How did you get down here?
You were just upstairs.
Yeah, never mind about that right now.
I have something really
important to tell you.
You know what? I think you've said
quite enough today already...
No, no, Dez, please.
Give me a minute, all right?
So you're the shapeshifter.
Why do you look like Amaya?
It is complicated, but
this is how you know me.
What's happened to the
Legends to make you like this?
What do you mean?
You guys are so intent on
killing magical creatures.
Can't you see that this is wrong?
Not really.
Look, now I know this sounds crazy,
but the me that you were
just speaking to upstairs
is my past.
So you break up with me out of the blue,
act like a total ass, and suddenly
that's in the past, just like that?
Listen, literally, that
is me from ages ago,
but the person who's standing
in front of you right now
is a little bit older and
he's a little bit wiser.
Sure. Still playing games, clearly.
Look.
I thought this was real.
Yeah, it is real, Dez, and that's why
I moved heaven and earth
so that I could save you
from a lifetime and eternity of anguish,
anguish that I caused.
Look...
I guess what I'm trying to say is
I'm sorry you ever even met me.
Don't be sorry.
Only a fool would fall in
love in John Constantine
and not expect it to be rocky.
I knew the risks
and I took 'em anyway for you.
I'm still pissed at you.
Why can't we just go back
to the ways things were?
That's exactly what I was thinking.
What is that?
Know one thing, Desmond.
I'm not quitting on you.
Sara, crazy-looking Constantine
just memory-flashed a civilian.
Can we shoot him yet?
Wait for my signal.
I'm dealing with a
situation on the ship.
Constantine might be...
Sara? Sara?
Hold on a second, Ray.
Where did you get that?
Look, I don't know who you are,
or why you are on my ship,
but you're never leaving.
Oh, hello, handsome.
What are you doing standing
in the middle of the street?
I was...
You... you went to the market.
I did.
Next thing I know I was
standing in the street.
I don't know.
Wait, Sara, please.
Just tell me why
you're so intent on
killing magical creatures.
Because that's how we stay alive.
Stop doing that!
- Don't you remember London?
- No.
When you and I first met
and I helped you see the
truth about magical creatures.
And how did you do that?
By being me?
By showing you that I'm
not here to hurt humans.
That not all monsters
need to be put down.
That's cute, but never happened.
What...
How can you not remember?
Bollocks.
Because of Constantine,
you and I never met
and you never changed.
I'm the missing ingredient
in every one of these botched timelines.
I'm sorry,
but all I see is a threat
that needs to be taken out.
Ray, fire when ready.
- You got eggs.
- I got the eggs.
I got the bread. Got everything we need.
Soufflé?
Soufflé, but first things first, eh.
You need to be a part of the team.
Your shapeshifting days
are over, sweetheart.
- No!
- I know who's coming for you.
But choosing a life of magic,
it never leads to a happy ending.
That's the thing about time travel,
there's always a way.
I'm sorry, Dez.
John, you okay?
Yeah, well,
my mind is no longer split in two,
but can't say the same
about my heart though.
You?
Well, lost my powers.
Back to being mortal.
Sorry, guys. It had to be done.
Well, let's go on and
find the Legends, shall we?
Yeah, see if all this was worth it.
Yeah.
Well, everything seems
pretty normal so far.
This isn't over, you dingalings.
You better watch your knees, Sara Lance.
Oh, no, is everyone a puppet again?
What?
- What are you talking about?
- I'll kill you all!
I got an anti-magic isolation chamber
with your name on it, Mike the Spike.
Ah, the usual insanity that
passes for normal around here.
What is this?
Why are you being so weird?
Well, I...
I do have a little bit of a
tale to tell, to be honest.
You fancy a drink?
Hmm, one of those stories.
Let's go.
Hey, Zari, I wanted
to say that I'm sorry.
For what? For stuffing me into a bag
or almost destroying all of history?
Well, yeah, that too, but
what I'm really sorry about
is that we got off on the wrong foot.
You're a shapeshifter.
Your whole deal is tricking people.
Yeah, but now I'm being honest with you.
You know, I could have been anyone
when I got my powers back.
Do you know why I kept
coming back to this form?
Because Amaya is very hot?
It's because this is the form I was
when I joined the Legends.
Now, I have been a part of many crews,
and you guys...
Well, you're not rubbish.
Listen, destroying
history for personal gain,
it's happened to almost everyone here.
Rite of passage.
So you think I'm hot then?
I made snicker doodles with your recipe.
Not bad.
Hmm.
I'm reading your novel.
I'm on the last chapter.
Your females characters
are shallow, libidinous,
and so much fun to read.
Hmm. Thanks.
Yeah, good job, um, Rebecca Silver?
Nom de plume.
Got it.
So let me get this straight.
They're making love on
the surface of the sun?
It's a metaphor.
Got it.
And the worst part?
It didn't even make a bloody difference.
I was a fool thinking I
could outrun this fight
flying around with you lot.
Yeah, we tend to fly
directly into fights.
But we do it together,
and we have your back.
Well, as long as you know
what you're getting yourself into
because a demon like Neron,
he doesn't just want to win.
He wants to win in the
cruelest possible way.
Yeah?
The Kaupe escaped?
Here's what I want you to do.
Track him down and
recapture him, or else.
Um, there's been a setback,
but we'll make it right.
Oh, you'd better.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --