Previously on
Legends Of Tomorrow...
It's a dragon egg.
You're possessed.
Ray's gone.
I've taken over his body.
If Neron wanted John dead,
he would have killed him on the spot.
I need you
to open up a doorway to Hell.
It's to bring someone here
from the other side.
Tabitha.
I'm sorry, it wasn't me.
It was my nipple.
Save me.
As you wish.
I'm not leaving Mona behind.
Do you really think that
everyone in Hell deserves to be there?
This is your opportunity
to make things right.
I'm gonna save Ray.
Honey, time to go!
Come on, honey.
Let's go, we're gonna be late.
Zari, you better not
be eating the halva.
No, Mommy.
Zari jaan.
Dessert is not for after breakfast.
What?
It's only a kick.
Behrad must be anxious to meet you.
Now go put your shoes on
so I can take you to school.
Violent people
are pouring into our country.
Illegal immigrants, terrorists,
meta-humans.
Politicians promise to keep you safe,
but they've been hiding the truth.
There's a dangerous new threat
already within our borders.
Hi, I'm Ray Palmer.
Yes, that Ray Palmer,
former CEO of Palmer Tech.
And I'm here to warn you
that creatures once thought only
in legends and fairy tales are real.
Yes, folks,
monsters are real
and they walk amongst us.
And they will stop at nothing
until they destroy humankind.
Interested in learning more?
Then join me at PalmerX 2019
where "The power is
in the palm-er of your hands."
I don't care Neron's wearing
my best friend's face,
- I want to punch him.
- Get in line.
Ogres are big softies.
That one wouldn't even hurt a fly.
Neron's been a step ahead of us
for too long.
We need to play offense.
- Agreed.
- I'm sorry, what are we agreeing to?
It's time for us to fight back.
We're retaking the Bureau.
Gideon, pull up the blueprints
of the Bureau
and start fabricating an arsenal.
Right away, Captain.
Look, Gary has bonded
with the Fairy Godmother
and while he might be an idiot,
she is not to be underestimated.
Mick, Nate, you think
you can handle Tabitha?
Granny is dead.
Good. Ava and I will handle Neron.
Yeah. I want a crack at him.
It's my Bureau
he's running his operation from.
Not to be a buzzkill,
but even John and Nora
couldn't out-magic Neron.
- I just felt a kick.
- Oh, I wanna feel...
Right now the smart play
would be just to bide our time.
Wait for John-o to return
with Ray's soul.
Shockingly, I agree with Charlie.
I love you little Wicksty...
- Oh, I felt it.
- I told you just...
Okay. Can you guys stop being
dragon baby-crazy right now?
Look, this commercial is proof
that Neron is up to something big.
And we need to stop him
before it's too late.
Captain, I have an incoming
communication from Nora Darhk.
Put her on.
Sara?
Talk to me. What's your status?
I'm tired of skulking around air ducts.
I'm going after Mona.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
We're gearing up for an assault.
Hold your position.
Hey.
Too late.
- Wait. Where's Gary?
- In Ava's office.
Getting real comfortable.
Mmm.
Oh, Fairy Godmother?
Yes, my pet.
I want to dig deeper on my next wish.
Excellent idea.
What do you have in mind?
Well...
We've already redecorated my office.
I now have three nipples,
because a spare never hurts. And...
Perhaps you could make a wish
regarding the Legends.
You want me to wish something for them?
I'm talking about revenge.
Oh.
They lied to you, Gary.
Promised you could be an Interim Legend.
One wish, and you can send them
all to Hell with John Constantine.
Speaking of John,
you think he's all right?
That warlock sent thousands of demons
to rot in the pits.
I think he's well and truly
screwed, dearie.
Does this mean we're straight?
I got a more important
collection to make.
Who is that guy?
That, my friend, is John Constantine.
In the flesh.
Congratulations, Mona.
I have selected you
for a very special assignment.
That's okay, Ne-Ray.
Can I call you that?
I'm okay here.
You see, before Nate's father
decided he wanted to be PT Barnum,
we were working together.
Training monsters to do our bidding.
Actually, I worked extensively
with your dear friend, Konane.
I mean,
your dead friend Konane.
I found Mona.
Hurry.
Copy that.
This seems like overkill.
The Legends never included me
in their pizza parties.
Or asked me to play
Dungeons & Dragons.
Make them suffer, Gary.
I can make them do whatever you want.
I just wanted to be part of the team.
Soon as Ava opens the portal,
we go in firing.
Time to burn some freaks.
I wish...
Opening a portal in three, two, one...
Welcome to book club.
Why, you little...
I'd be careful how you speak
to my charge.
Gary, why are you doing this?
Because I would like to discuss
The Collector.
Forget the book, Gary.
You helped a demon
take control of the Bureau.
What happened to the Bureau Creed?
Oh, I could ask the same about you.
Article 27. Hmm?
"A supervisor must never
show favoritism."
You started a book club
with another employee.
Gary.
Mona is being tortured right now.
Neron said he's trying
to protect humans from monsters.
You saw Mona gnaw off my nip!
She did you a favor.
Okay. Um...
Maybe we should just reschedule
until after we've read the book.
Oh, Fairy Godmother...
Oh, no.
Wait.
That book was terrible.
Oh, my head.
That's the spirit.
Sara, Ava. Come in.
Where are you guys?
Hey, Nate, can't talk right now.
Are you talking to Nate on comms?
Tell him I say hi.
Gary says hi.
And we're at book club.
Move on to Plan B.
What's Plan B?
I only listen for my name.
I assume it's like Plan A
but, you know, with less people.
Well, without the captain and the clone,
the Bureau's a suicide mission.
Mick's right.
We need to sneak into PalmerX.
Do some recon,
find out what Neron's up to.
Now that sounds like a Plan Z.
Hey, baby.
Hey.
You looking for a good time, handsome?
I'm always looking
for a good time, love.
But, uh, regrettably,
my time here is limited.
Maybe you can help me.
I'm looking for a broker
in the soul trade,
he goes by the name of Masher.
I might know something.
Well, this here is holy water.
Now, you can use this
to burn the skin off
any demon tosser who messes with you.
Uh-uh-uh-uh.
Masher likes to hang out at
the strip club after trading's done...
John.
How do you know my name?
Oh, I know who you are.
Half of demonkind
is searching for John Constantine.
- The holy water?
- Oh, this?
No, this is just whiskey, love.
Sure, our protagonist
was keeping people hostage,
but that's only because
he never received love as a child.
They don't want you
in their book club, Gary.
Doesn't that make you angry?
Make a wish and they will pay.
You're right.
They don't want
to spend time with Gary Green,
the lowly Time Bureau agent.
But they would love
to spend time with Gary Green,
Captain of the Waverider!
Welcome aboard, Captain Green.
Thanks.
I have no quarrel with you, dear.
You didn't send me to Hell
like John Constantine and the Legends.
Yes, I was in Hell for 327 years.
And what was my crime?
I sprinkled a little magic over Salem,
trying to help a girl
whose mother was accused of witchcraft.
Okay.
Well, you're out now, why help Neron?
Neron rescued me in Hell,
and what can I say,
true love bloomed.
I know what you're thinking,
he's so much older than me.
Sometimes you have to look past age.
You know, in another life,
I think you and I
could have been friends.
- Toodles.
- Wait, what...
Ray.
Without all of the idiotic tendencies.
Make a move on me and Mona dies.
Ray is good and strong.
He can fight his way back from Hell.
Who do you think
is having a worse time in Hell?
Ray or your father?
Turns out Daddy Dearest isn't so tough.
I hear Damien Darhk is going
stark raving mad in the pits.
Why am I here?
Well, you and John tried to kill me.
Nearly did.
If the doofus in the skin-suit
I'm wearing hadn't have interrupted,
I'd have been obliterated.
I spent many nights just dreaming
about how I was going to get my revenge.
And then it came to me.
What better punishment
than making you sit front row
to all of the fear and rage
I'm about to unleash on the earth.
All while in the body
of the man you love.
Now...
Smile for the cameras.
Are monsters real?
What's tonight all about?
All of your questions
will be answered soon.
- Oh. Excuse me.
- What's wrong with you?
Well, you know, a room full of people
fearful of magical creatures,
just makes me a little fearful,
all right?
The worst part is,
Ray loves tech events.
Good evening, DC,
and welcome to PalmerX 2019.
Now, you're all probably wondering,
what in the heck is Ray Palmer
doing back in the public eye?
Well, folks,
for the past two years,
I have been hunting magical creatures.
Hang with me here.
I've created an exosuit
capable of combating
the most ferocious of their kind.
What a douche.
But I can't do it alone.
I need your help.
I need you to help me
find these creatures.
Creatures that may be hiding
right here, amongst us.
Now, everyone,
take out your smartphones.
Better be Palmer Tech.
I've created a small, simple app
that will change the world.
And I want you all
to download it right now.
The app is called EYES.
Now, on EYES,
you will be able to share real-time,
lifesaving monster sightings.
Share them.
And I will be there to save you.
Remember,
the power is in
the palm-er of your hands.
You really expect us
to believe monsters exist?
I thought you were
going to offer us proof.
Thank you, Cindy.
You're absolutely right.
Here is your proof.
Now,
this may look like a helpless hipster
who should be working at a bookstore.
But believe me,
she's something
altogether more dangerous.
- Masher.
- John.
Yeah, all right. Keep your hair on.
No need to tell the whole bloody club.
Oh, buddy, now I know
you're out of your mind.
What are you doing in Hell?
I'm here to save a friend,
his soul belongs to Neron.
Cheers, love. He's paying.
Nobody gets into Neron's soul vault
without his say-so.
Except the triumvirate.
And I have a plan to deal with them.
But first, there's a hunch
I need to confirm.
What's Neron trading at?
He's steady.
But I'll let you in on a little secret,
his stock is about to rise.
I'm talking a massive
soul collection on Earth.
You know what that means?
Neron is finally making his play
for the throne of Hell.
Oh, cheers, Masher, I can use that.
Be careful, John,
not every demon you sent to Hell
is as forgiving as I am.
Yeah. Don't I know it.
You're dead, demon hunter.
I was gonna be a demon proctologist
but the pay wasn't as good.
Hold him.
Oh!
Oh, Calibraxis.
You're looking good, mate.
You grow your beard?
John Constantine.
I'm really going to enjoy
watching you breathe your last.
I invoke a parley.
I demand to speak to the triumvirate.
I'm a demon, not a pirate, John.
I thought you understood the rules.
Well, you little maggot...
As long as I'm alive,
then the triumvirate can pass me around
like a little sparrow amongst the cats.
But as soon I die, you dim-witted dick,
then my soul belongs to Neron.
And then the triumvirate lose out
on all the tasty little bits
of torture that they have
got planned for me.
So you have got two choices.
You can either kill me
and royally piss off
the old bags that run this place.
Or take me to speak
with the triumvirate.
I'm detecting a fugitive alert...
Stop it.
At the Inquisition, Captain Green.
Oh. I don't do torture.
He could have fooled me.
Hey. Play nice.
We have to distract Gary
while the B team is plan B-ing.
Would a fairy at the
Great British Bake Off suit your fancy?
Shall we, uh...
Keep calm and pastry on?
I'll plot a course, Captain.
Get it?
Keep calm and pastry on?
- Good one, Cap. Good one.
- Hilarious.
Thanks, guys. Thanks. Yeah.
Take a good long look at her.
Mona Wu.
You saw her on the street,
you wouldn't think twice.
Come on, Mona.
Don't give him what he wants.
But she has a strange
and violent condition,
brought about when she fell in love
with a repulsive creature.
I feel like a bridge scene
should have more people.
Oh. No, we love
three-people bridge scenes.
Yeah, otherwise we'd just end up
standing around all day.
Oh, that's why Mick's always grumpy.
Come on, Mona,
I promised these fine people a show.
Let's not keep them waiting.
Shift now.
Or end up dead like Konane.
Folks, proof
of the world's very first werewolf!
That's what we're missing.
The boys!
- No.
- Yeah.
Fairy Godmother.
- Z.
- Nate.
She made him disappear!
Well, well, well.
What do we have here?
More magic in the audience?
She's one of them.
He's right.
I am.
She's a witch.
Witch. Witch.
Witch. Witch. Witch.
Witch. Witch. Witch. Witch. Witch.
Don't worry, folks.
The witch won't get far, not as long as
everyone downloads the EYES app.
Share your sightings.
We'll find the witch.
It's only a matter of time.
Sara? You guys okay?
Yeah, we're fine.
As long as we keep placating Gary.
I guess Charlie and Z are our last hope.
Great, we're toast!
Welcome to Hell.
Good evening, this is
your captain speaking.
- Just...
- What?
We'll be cruising at a high altitude
on our way to save
a bake-off in Britain.
Whoo!
- Yeah!
- Yeah.
Gary, is that the Kid Steel costume?
Uh-huh.
You likey?
Why would anyone wish to be a sidekick?
Close your legs.
Oh, he's such an idiot.
What?
Nothing.
They're just teasing you.
- Oh.
- You're my Gare-Bear.
We're gonna have so much fun.
Okay.
Hashtag-Eyes-app is trending on Twitter
below Kanye's surprise album
and a cat getting a bath.
Mmm. How many downloads?
Only 2,000, Mr. Palmer.
The news cycle is so fast these days,
it's hard to cut through all the noise.
But a monster attack on the capital
will dominate the headlines for weeks.
And then what?
More people will download some app?
That's your big plan?
Why, yes it is.
Ah.
My love.
Would you please
escort our guest to a cell?
Let's go, dearie.
Neron didn't say which
containment cell to put you in.
Why are you helping me?
Because you're a fellow witch.
And I think we can help each other.
Mona.
How do you feel?
I've been better.
Remember, I'm just
a "Fairy Godmother" away.
Trust me, we'll be safe here.
Where are we?
My childhood home.
I thought you grew up
in a dystopian city, Z.
You had a pool?
In a couple years, A.R.G.U.S. will use
people's growing fear of meta-humans
to seize control.
Of course, it didn't help
that we were Muslim.
We were forced to move
to a ghetto district in 2021.
Humans are so easy to manipulate.
I mean, you just show them
a scary ogre or a dangerous meta,
and they just go barmy.
I haven't even been able
to get into this EYES app yet
because the terms of service
are so long.
No one bothers reading those.
It's a demon app.
I'm gonna read the fine print.
Can't believe it's just us left.
I mean, you and I both knew
from the start
that it was madness to storm the Bureau.
Oh, my God.
What?
Z?
In New Orleans,
John said Neron needed
more souls to take over Hell.
Here it says
What, you're saying that anyone who
downloads the app is going to Hell?
Yeah.
Oh, that is mental.
This little fairy was causing quite
the fray around the souffle.
I think I know just
the place for you, madam.
I can't take it anymore.
I'm gonna kill him.
Hey, Z, Charlie.
Please tell me you have something.
Well, we figured out Neron's app
is a way to collect souls.
- That's crazy.
- Yeah.
It gets crazier. To drum up fear
and increase downloads of his app,
we think he may be planning
a monster attack.
Okay. We'll, we'll stall Gary.
But you gotta get every single one of
those monsters out of the Time Bureau.
I was afraid you were going to say that.
Who you talking to, Sara?
What?
Gary. Baby, Bobby, bubelah...
There's a whole big world of problems.
You know, Neron
and your Fairy Godmother,
they're not really your friends.
But do you know who your friends are?
These guys.
Huh?
Are you trying to schmooze me?
Feels good, right?
Uh, actually, it feels a little false.
Gary.
You are our friend.
I mean, would we lie
to an Interim Legend?
Ah, you see, that's just it,
because I'm not an Interim Legend.
You just promised me that
to use me as bait.
You know what, Gary.
It's a little hard to feel sorry for you
when you're holding us all hostage.
You're not getting it.
This whole time Tabitha's been
trying to use me to hurt you.
All I wished was for us to hang out.
I was trying to protect you.
I get it. I'm not cool.
But I don't deserve
to be treated like a joke.
So now...
Now, the joke's on you.
What's he doing?
Oh, Fairy Godmother!
Yes, my pet?
Mick thinks he's a tough guy.
But I think he's a big baby.
And Nate,
who's never been bullied
a day in his life.
Welcome to my high school years.
And Sara and Ava,
the cool girl and the class president.
You know what I want you to do for me?
Dance.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Faster.
Gary, stop it.
Charlie, I get that you're scared,
but the team is counting on us.
I'm not scared.
It's just breaking the monsters out
of the prison is a multiple person job.
You can be multiple people.
Look, Z. Yeah, I can for a second.
And you what? It takes its toll.
I could end up back in prison
or even worse, dead.
When A.R.G.U.S. came for my family,
my brother, Behrad, told me to run.
And I did.
I've never forgiven myself.
You won't either.
We can't change my family's future,
but we can save their present.
Zari jaan, make sure you take
your shoes off before you go in.
I know.
Charlie?
If I die, I'm gonna
come back and haunt you.
I would love a ghost friend.
Come on.
Cool.
Greetings, Satan.
First of the fallen.
It's been a long time, John.
Belial.
We've been looking forward
to hearing the bunk you're peddling.
And Beelzebub.
Not as popular, but you were
always my personal favorite.
This is a waste of our time.
I take it you've noticed
a certain demon's stock
has been on the rise?
Neron's been doing very well
for himself.
Neron is trying to take control of Hell.
And let me assure you,
his method for collecting souls,
it won't be
to sign on the dotted line in blood.
He's, uh, young,
by your standards at least.
And let's just say,
he means to disrupt the system.
If we interfere with Neron,
we'll look weak.
Well, that's precisely
where I come in, Bubby.
And what do you want in exchange?
Not your own soul, I hope.
I'm here for the soul of Raymond Palmer.
You let us two leave Hell,
and I pledge to you
that I will dedicate
all of my crafty and wicked ways
to thwarting Neron
and securing your reign.
Are you really here for Raymond Palmer?
We thought there was another.
A young girl whose life you destroyed.
Astra.
Yeah, well, you know,
I didn't want to be too greedy.
But yeah, I'll take them both.
Both of them?
That is greedy.
But if you were to choose...
Well, then that's a different matter.
John!
Help me.
John. You're here.
You gotta get me back to Earth.
Please, John, they're hurting me.
Make up your mind, John.
This offer won't last.
John?
Astra.
It's following me. Make it go away.
Come here. I've got you.
You can't have her!
You can't save her.
John, get me out of here!
I'm sorry.
I choose...
Astra Logue.
Stick to the plan, Charlie.
You mean the plan where I need to
rely on my shoddy shapeshifting
to portal creatures
one by one out of their cells
and onto the Waverider,
where Gary may or may not
wish them to kingdom come.
Yup, that plan.
This isn't you, Gary.
Why are you being so cruel?
Please.
Stop. You're killing them.
I don't do mime, dearie.
Just stop. Everything.
As you wish.
Mona. Hey, wake up.
Hey, Nora.
Hey.
You're still here?
Book club forever.
Oh, Fairy Godmother!
Uh...
I have to pop off for a second, Gary.
I thought we were
gonna play Settlers of Catan later.
Don't be silly.
We're not friends.
Oh.
I'm so sorry, Gary.
I took you for granted.
I never, ever should have
let you do my dry cleaning
or work overtime without pay.
I mean, that's illegal, anyway.
I'm so sorry.
I still want to kill you.
Gary, when Rip
first recruited the Legends,
he picked the people
that were insignificant to history.
The original losers.
You don't have to be cool
to be a Legend.
And maybe we forgot that
somewhere along the way.
But you're one of us.
Now, come on, Gary.
Ray and Constantine are both
stuck in Hell and you can help them.
Just use your Fairy Godmother
powers for good.
Save her.
Sadly, my hands are tied.
But if you become
Mona's Fairy Godmother,
she could wish to be healed.
How do I do that?
If another witch takes the wand...
You'll take my curse,
but with it, all of my power.
Nora...
Nora. No.
No.
It worked.
Quick, Mona, make a wish.
Well...
Uh, Fairy God Nora.
I wish to be safe on the Waverider.
Oh!
How I've missed me.
Sadly for you,
when you took on
the wand's power and responsibility,
you also took on its charge.
- Gary?
- I'm afraid so.
Fairy Godmothers are prisoners.
Their magic is dependent on
whiny humans and their petty demands.
You lied!
Obviously.
Toodles.
Excuse me.
- Marilyn Monroe?
- Well, yes.
I seem to have gotten a little lost.
Can you help me get back home?
Of course, ma'am.
Let me just program in the year.
Ah. Yeah. Uh...
Thanks.
Oh, my love, my love.
Still no luck with Nora?
No.
Well, she'll take your curse soon.
After all, you are very convincing.
Well, I better head back.
Evil deeds to do, and all that.
Well, that was bloody close.
I'm at the first cell.
Anytime now, Z.
Okay. Just give me one second.
The public doesn't always know
what's best for them.
So, tonight, we'll release the Minotaur,
and scare them
into accepting our protection.
It is done, mon amour.
How do I look?
You were just...
No, the shapeshifter.
Can someone sound the alarm?
Charlie, Tabitha and Neron
are on to you.
Yeah, I figured.
You need to get out now.
Open all the doors.
Turn off the force fields.
I'm not leaving.
Are you waiting for an invitation?
It's a bloody jailbreak!
I mean, there are pros to trusting
your apologies are sincere, and cons.
Maybe I'll make a list.
Gary, Gary, just...
Go with your heart.
Oh, Fairy Godmother?
- Nora.
- Oh.
Go find John and help him
rescue Ray from Hell.
Oh, fiddlesticks.
- Wait!
- Wait, Gary!
Gary, you dick.
Come on, you lot. Get a move on.
You don't have to tell me twice.
Faster, Sassy!
You all right, little one?
Oi, Ogre, catch.
- Charlie, you're out of time.
- Z. Get out of here.
See you on the other side.
I'm going after Mona.
Mona.
Come on, love.
Let's get you out of here.
Oh, I hate shapeshifters.
Break her neck.
Patience, mon amour.
Get Mona.
No.
Looks like things ain't going so well
for you, Neron.
You wanted a monster to attack DC.
Now, you have every single monster.
In one.
You promised you'd take me to see Astra.
Patience, John.
I made a pledge to you,
and I expect you
to keep your end of the bargain.
What the hell are you playing at?
John.
John, is it really you?
Yes.
Yes, Astra, love. It's me.
It's me. It's Johnny.
Thank God.
God?
You know better than to thank him.
Astra?
John is here to take you back to Earth.
You're welcome to go.
Yeah. It's all right, love. It's me.
No.
Wait.
Hold on.
What do you mean "no"?
Looks like the deal is null and void.
Neron is a thorn in our side, John.
But torturing you
is too much fun.
John?
It's following me.
Make it go away.
Please.
John. Get me out of here.
Astra, love.
This isn't you.
No. Of course it is.
Or would you rather
I stayed that terrified little girl,
crying and waiting
for you to come and rescue me?
I would have been waiting a long time.
I'm so, so sorry, love.
But this place, it's twisted you.
If anything,
it's made me more like you.
Right, John?
You're not like me.
You're not.
You chose wrong.
You should have saved your friend.
Hey! Watch it.
Back off, freak.
It's like a demented Noah's Ark.
What about Charlie?
It's my fault. I'm the one that
convinced her to risk everything.
Hey. Don't go down that road.
- We'll do what we always do.
- Yeah?
Forming stupid Beebos?
Hey. Where you going?
Well, after everything,
I just figured you wouldn't
wanna have me around anymore.
It's all hands on deck, Gary.
Yeah. We're gonna need
all our friends to defeat Neron.
Aye, aye.
You all right?
Not really.
I'm glad you and Wicksty are okay.
What happened?
Oh, my God.
Hi.
My name is Zari.