Uh...
Uh, you need some
help with that, Mick?
Maybe you should just,
you know, take it easy.
I'm pregnant, not paralyzed.
Yeah. Okay. Well, do your thing.
Are you sure
this is the right spot?
- I'm just following the beeps.
- Then why are we going in circles?
Maybe the tracker's busted.
Moment of truth.
And that is not right.
Oh, what's up, squire? What's wrong?
Why you crying?
- They're soggy in the middle.
- Maybe I can help.
Fiery flames. Burning blazes.
Infernal conflagrations.
Dude.
Sorry about that, Behrad. Guess I just
don't know my own strength lately.
Let me make it up to you.
Cannabis edible, euphoria incredible,
brain matter bendable!
No. Please don't fire a spell
at my brain.
Poof!
Yeah, good point.
You're feeling mighty magical
this morning. Almost overcharged.
I feel astounding.
Where's Zari?
I want to share this with her.
Sorry, my friend.
My sis swapped places with Flannel Zari
who's currently on a date with Nate.
And you just missed the pod squad too.
So, Nate is with the Zari
that lives in a Totem.
That seems very problematic.
Where's he taking her?
Watch the Beatles perform live?
Maybe the fabled pleasure domes
of Kublai Khan.
Great outdoors.
Nothing beats Mother Nature.
Yeah, I feel like we've seen
all the nature.
Yeah.
In all seriousness,
I am very glad to be here with you.
We're almost there.
Look, I know you only have 24 hours
before you have to go back
into the Totem.
Right. 24 hours.
So I just want to spend
some time together,
you know, with no distractions.
- Yes, I would like that too.
- Hello, neighbors.
Looks like campsite's double-booked.
That's okay. We love company.
- I'm Jeff. This is Jamie.
- Rock 'n' roll.
Yeah.
Yeah. We kinda got it all,
as you can see.
Who wants dogs?
Oh, uh...
You know what, Jeff?
We're gonna go off on our own. Thanks.
A-ha!
Oh!
Last pod in the timeline
and it's a total dud.
Wait. There's something inside.
- Nothing's happening.
- Here. Could be dangerous.
Ah, it's one of those,
uh, puzzle things.
You gotta solve it to open it.
- Hey, I'm not done yet.
- Give me that.
No, I can do it.
Hey, babe, I think, uh, we're,
gonna be a while.
Take all the time, babe.
There's seriously no rush.
- Oh! No.
- What?
It's bad luck to see you in
your wedding dress before the big day.
It's not bad luck.
I'm not marrying you, Gary.
And besides, this isn't the one.
It makes me feel,
I don't know, not right.
Stop whatever you are doing.
No, no, no. Okay?
- I have a job for you. Yeah?
- Anything.
You're gonna help me
find the perfect wedding dress.
Oh!
- Give it to me.
- Give this...
- Let go.
- I got it.
Guys, can we please just
get it together?
Give me the damn...
Where the hell are we?
One minute we're in a gross junkyard,
the next we're in a gross bowling alley.
- Spooner, are you getting something?
- This place... Major alien vibes.
- I don't see any aliens.
- I got a bad feeling about this.
The sooner we get out of here,
the better.
Whoa. Where is everything?
I have a feeling
we're not in Kansas anymore.
- So we've been abducted by aliens.
- Again.
Ava? B? Can you guys hear us?
Courier isn't working either.
Wherever we are, we're stuck.
Okay, well, if these guys are aliens,
maybe we can bum a ride home.
Yeah, sure. Go for it.
I'm gonna see if this guy
knows anything.
Thanks for catching me.
But I think I'd rather you let me die
than spend another minute here.
I'm taking a leak.
Hi, um, sir...
The name's Buddy. What's your shoe size?
I'm not here to bowl, but I was hoping
you could tell me
how the hell I got here.
I would wager you opened an invitation.
- No, I didn't get an invitation.
- Shiny. Irresistible.
Drags your ass
across the universe instantly.
Okay, yeah, maybe I did.
Damn it. The Puzzle Box.
How do we get back to Earth?
Earth? But you just got here.
And I'm so happy you did.
Because I bet you're incredible bowlers.
Why's that?
Bowling was invented
by Earthlings after all.
Everyone else here just looks human.
- Why don't I show you around? Come on.
- Okay.
Coming down to the wire, folks.
Sorry to bother you,
but my friends and I are stranded and
we're looking for a ride back to Earth.
Earth, huh?
Yeah, sure, we'll give you a ride.
But you and your friends
have got to beat us in a game first.
- We're kind of on a tight schedule.
- Oh, come on. What's one game?
Unless, of course,
you're afraid of losing.
I can roll with anyone.
Then how about
we spice things up a little
and play a game of Cosmic Bowling?
Is that with the neon balls
and the black lights?
Yeah, that ain't really my thing.
All I'm saying is if you want
to get a ride out of here,
you got to roll against us.
All right then. Game on.
I was hoping you'd say that.
Cute trick. But it's what you do
on the lanes that counts.
Once we're through putting
these red shirts out of their misery,
you're next.
The guidebook said we should be able
to see the Northern Lights,
but... I can't see a single star.
Huh! Maybe it's too cloudy.
Listen, I know this is super on brand,
but I'm feeling kind of hungry.
Hungry, you say? Hmm.
Well, I happen to have
made your favorite
Persian delicacy, abgoosht.
- What?
- Yep.
And for dessert, the very exotic donuts.
It's very sweet.
No.
- This must be Spooner's bag.
- Oh, that makes sense.
- The only food in here are MRE rations.
- Maybe they're super delicious.
Want to try it?
Rock and roll!
- Is that what I think it is?
- Yep.
Rock and roll!
What's the point of unplugging
if all your camping gear has a cord?
Meanwhile, we're out here
trying to squeeze in one date
before I turn into a Totem pumpkin,
and they're over there
with all the carefree time in the world.
- I'm jealous of those two idiots.
- Me too. It's insane.
That's it. That's it.
We're getting another campsite.
- Yeah, that's good.
- Gideon? Gideon.
Oh.
- My Time Courier's going nuts.
- Yeah.
Something's wrong. Something's wrong.
It's funny.
It even smells like a bowling alley.
Yep. I included everything you'd find
in a bowling center on Earth.
That's how much I love bowling,
the greatest sport in the universe.
I'm sorry. You created this place?
Does that mean you were the one
who sent out the invitations?
I had nothing to do
with those cursed invitations.
That's the work of the Pin Killers.
The guys in the purple shirts.
They came here and ruined
my little bowling paradise.
I need you to beat them.
They're the top dogs now,
and you only get one game
to try to knock them off.
So don't challenge them
until your team is ready.
Guess what. I found us a ride home.
All we got to do is just beat those
aliens in those ugly purple shirts.
We got next.
Hey, will you hand me that?
Mmm. Just need to adjust the frequency.
The sun is missing.
It's night everywhere on Earth.
Massive unexplained chasms appeared
in Mexico, Canada and Alaska.
- We're in Alaska.
- Who did this? Aliens? Demons?
Did God give up on us?
Either way, it's the end of the world.
We're all gonna die.
Alaska, Canada.
- They're gone. They're just gone.
- Nate...
I think the world is ending.
We need to get out of here.
This is one of the top five worst dates
I've ever been on.
We're all gonna die. We're gonna die.
We're all gonna die.
Jamie and I can go anywhere in the world
and I can still blaze us
a Neapolitan pizza at 800 degrees.
- Supes quick. Ha-ha!
- That's so fantastic, Jeff.
Yeah, the char on this
is something else.
- Hmm... Hmm.
- Hmm?
Say, Jeff... Sorry. Bro.
Can I borrow your truck supes quick
so we can go into town
and pick up some stuff?
Uh...
- Sure. What are neighbors for?
- There's a bro.
Hey, why don't we all go?
- No.
- Rock and roll.
- No, no, no.
- Yeah.
Nate, you're riding shotgun.
Boys in the front.
Oh, my God.
Battery's dead.
I don't know, Jeff.
Maybe all your devices drained it.
Well, good luck, guys.
Where are you going?
- We're heading into town.
- Great. We'll come with.
Maybe we can find some folks
to jump the truck battery.
Rock and roll.
Looks like we're hiking.
All right. Enough of this
ding dong dallying waiting around.
I say we get out there
and we find Sara and her gang.
I'm sure they could use
a magical assist.
Come to think of it,
we haven't heard from them in a while.
Gideon, let's go visit Sara.
Kansas City, 2021.
Calculating, calculating.
That is impossible at this time.
Come on. You're Gideon.
Everything's possible.
I'm sorry.
I'm having trouble locking onto Earth.
Never seen that before.
I came looking
for my summer wedding inspo binder,
but did Gideon just say
we can't get back to Earth?
- Yeah.
- This is bad.
Ava cannot be marooned
in the Temporal Zone away from Sara.
- This could be triggering.
- Calm down. Just breathe.
Keep Ava occupied.
We'll figure something out. Right, John?
Oh! Most assuredly.
All right, team. We are stranded
on the edge of the universe
and the only way out is
to beat the Pin Killers.
- Question.
- Yes.
- I don't bowl.
- I don't either, but how hard can it be?
Pretty sure you just pick it on up
and then we just roll it on down.
Nice, Sara.
Well...
What can I say? Guess I'm a natural.
Mick, let's see what you got.
All right.
Right. It's gonna be good.
It's gonna be great.
Go. Just... Right on.
Whatever feels natural.
Nice and smooth. Okay.
Wrong lane, but, hey,
you got some pins, right?
If you lose the gloves,
you'll drop more pins.
- Watch and learn.
- Here you go. Oh. Okay.
Ah, we got a standard house oil pattern.
A bit chilly,
so the lanes will be slick.
We got a dip in the 16th board.
- Yeah.
- What the hell was that?
I learned the art of bowling when
I was 13. Kept me out of trouble.
The footwork concentrates my mojo.
You keep that mojo concentrated.
Nice moves.
All right, Astra. Lace them up.
Let's go.
I am not putting my feet
in those fungus-filled shoes
or my fingers
in those fungus-filled holes.
All right. Then you can cheer us on
from that fungus-filled chair.
- You're just gonna let her skip?
- Whatever she wants.
I'm getting a good feeling
about this one.
It is amazing.
This is the one. I'm sure of it.
Okay. Well,
I can't show Sara, obviously,
but I can tell her that it's done.
Gideon.
Actually...
Uh... You're fine with the shoulders?
Um... The shoulders?
Yeah. What's wrong with them?
Nothing at all. It's your wedding.
As long as you're fine with it.
Gary, spit it out.
They're a little plain.
They lack pizzazz.
- Pizzazz?
- Mmm-hmm.
Oh, yeah. Now that I look at them,
they do seem really boring.
Well, I mean, they're not that bad.
Gary, what am I gonna do?
I can't get married in plain shoulders.
Gideon?
We're gonna need some alterations.
So you're saying we're stuck?
Every time I plot
an exit vector, it fails to reach Earth.
My safety protocols do not allow us
to attempt a doomed jump. So, yes.
Right. Like John Henry, I will prevail
where the machine could not.
- How?
- I will compel the ship to Earth.
Whoa! Sounds big, even for you.
Well, I am feeling invigorated, squire.
I need you to bring me
the four elemental aspects of our world.
Earth, Fire, Air and Water. All right?
Got it. Hey.
Maybe your powers are growing stronger
since you drank
from the Fountain of Imperium.
Oh, yeah, the Fountain.
That's right. Good.
Well, uh, hop to it, Skippy.
Final frame.
Red Shirts, game over.
- Oh! Another one bites the dust.
- Pin Killers can't be stopped.
And now you're mine.
- You don't have to do this, Mike.
- You won. Isn't that enough?
Well, here's the thing.
I do it for the trophies.
- You're a bastard, Mike.
- Yeah, well...
They have a lot of balls.
That whole team
just vaporized into thin air.
Yeah. And I'm guessing that's what's
gonna happen to us if we lose too.
I hope you're warmed up.
Because Mike the Strike
says it's game time.
I can't tell you how many trucks
I've had to abandon,
and in some of the most scenic places
on Earth.
- So you and Jeff are big campers, huh?
- Rock and roll.
Right. Of course. Rock and roll.
I get the vibe that you and Nate
are doing the long-distance thing.
Uh, I didn't know we gave off that vibe,
but, yeah, we are.
- And you two can handle the distance?
- Yeah, Jamie, we can handle distance.
Well, if you can stand to be apart,
doesn't that just kind of prove
you don't need to be together?
- What? No.
- I'm sorry if I touched a nerve.
It's just that's
what all the magazines say.
You didn't touch a nerve.
It's fine. I'm fine.
Nate and I are fine.
Our relationship is fine.
Our vibe is very fine.
Everything is fine. Yeah.
- Everything all right back there?
- Fine.
Rock and roll.
All right, everyone. We've got
ourselves a game of Cosmic Bowling.
The Pin Killers versus the Legends.
Ten frames. Ten pins.
And 60 feet of wood.
May your rolls be true.
- All right, Buddy.
- You've got this, Murph.
- That's my Murph. Murph the Curve.
- All right, baby.
Yeah.
Clare the Spare
always picks up the spare. Always.
Lose the gloves, Mick.
Have respect for the game.
Quiet.
Yes, yes.
That's it, that's it. Just keep doing
your thing. You're doing your thing.
- What did I tell you, Mick?
- Shut up.
If we don't get those two to play nice,
we may never get out of here.
I think you've almost nailed it.
I'm thinking lace.
- Perfect.
- Yeah?
Yes, the lace. It brings out
your skin tone. Bigger with the veil.
Um...
Aw!
- Okay, so we're good.
- Nope.
- What?
- You need something floral.
- We're done.
- I love it. What about a bustle?
All right. I got them all.
Oh, excellent.
We make a good team, Smokey.
John, when you started dating my sister,
I was worried you'd be a bad influence.
I mean, most people you date
end up dead or worse.
But I can see how much
you've changed, for the better.
You're a good man, John Constantine.
Well, I am glad to hear it, mate.
Now, shall we begin?
Earth.
Water.
Fire.
Air.
You okay?
It's gorgeous. Very on-trend.
What the hell was that?
- Gary?
- It's nothing to worry about.
- I'm sure you'll see Sara again.
- What? What happened to her?
It's more what happened to us.
What the hell is going on?
Well, we were stuck in the Temporal Zone
because Gideon couldn't find Earth.
And now, well, we're not in the Temporal
Zone at least. Trippy dress, Ava.
That's not what I was going for, Behrad.
Why did no one tell me
we were stuck? Gary?
I was trying to distract you
so you wouldn't be upset.
Okay, so where the hell are we?
I cast a spell to bring us to Earth.
It's here somewhere.
Wait, wait, wait.
There is something out there.
We're at a floating
bowling alley in space.
Thank you, everyone here, for making
my day about a floating bowling alley.
You dumdums stay here.
Hi. Hello? Hi.
- Ava?
- Sara, you're here.
What's with the bowling shirt?
I'll tell you about the bowling shirt
if you tell me about this wedding dress.
Wedding...
Oh, my God.
I forgot that I was wearing it.
I was so mad at Gary
because he didn't tell me...
- Babe, you look gorgeous.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Why won't these fricking doors open?
Could we get a little help here, please?
League champs took control
of those doors.
No one enters without an invitation.
What is that sweet man talking about?
Uh, when we tracked down that last pod,
we found this device
and it zapped us here.
And now the only way for us
to leave is for us to beat
this team of alien bowlers
who are surprisingly good.
How did you find us?
Gideon couldn't find Earth,
so Constantine cast a spell
to bring the Waverider to Earth
and it brought us here.
What? So you're saying that Earth
is in this bowling alley?
I guess.
Who would be a cruel enough jerk
to hide the Earth in this bowling alley?
Oh! You've got to be kidding me.
Hey, look at that.
Light. See that, Zari? Daylight.
Maybe everything will be fine.
Yeah. Maybe everything will be fine.
Or maybe we're doomed.
Wait. What?
What the hell is that?
Earthquake.
- Everyone okay?
- What the hell is going on?
What was that thing?
What?
Whoa!
Where is everything?
- Hey?
- It's the end of the world.
Jamie, I can't die without
you knowing the truth.
I got a secret vasectomy,
and that's why you never get pregnant.
No!
- Are you frigging kidding me?
- Baby.
Not rock and roll, Jeff.
Not rock and roll at all.
If we have kids, we won't be
able to afford our stuff, right?
Wait. Wait. Where are you going?
Into town.
To find someone whose truck works.
Wait.
That's rough.
Hey, am I a bad person
if I found that very enjoyable?
- No, no, no. They're terrible people.
- Okay, good.
Totally off topic, but does that cloud
look like Mick to you?
You know, from here, you can tell
how fragile and beautiful it really is.
Coming through.
Hey, take it easy!
So you're literally bowling
with planet Earth?
That's why it's called Cosmic Bowling.
You go mano-a-mano
for the survival of your species
and if you lose, you and your
entire home planet get banished
to our trophy shelf for eternity.
Wow! That's godlike power.
I'm not a god.
I'm just an average Joe who loves
to bowl, and destroy countless worlds.
Yes, Mike.
Buddy, if this is your place, why don't
you just kick them out of here?
Can't. Rules say they can stay
as long as they're champs.
Now they've taken root and taken over.
It's your fault we're playing
this dumb game.
Place is full of bad energy now.
At least I was being proactive
and trying to get us out of here.
Be less proactive.
They made the game so
competitive, no one wants to play here.
- This team is falling apart.
- Hey, yo. Come on, Legends.
What are you waiting for? You got
a game to lose. Let's get going.
They turned my bowling alley
into a bullying alley.
Game on.
Damn it.
- You're not listening to anything I say.
- I am listening.
I'm just choosing to ignore you.
Bowling's stupid.
Bowling is not stupid, you ignorant lug.
You can't control the ball
if your fingers aren't in the hole. See?
You son of a...
Oh, my God. I think I jammed it.
- Son of a...
- That's gotta hurt.
Time-out. We're at time-out.
- Let's take a walk. Come on.
- Pathetic.
I'll get you some ice
and we'll do something.
Okay, let's get ice.
We'll get some ice. All right.
- Why did we come back here?
- We need a plan.
Okay. Plan. I'll Steel up.
You use your wind power.
Shoot me like a bullet...
- No. We need a plan for us.
- Us, us?
Yeah. You know, I was thinking about it
and I just want to give us a chance
to end things amicably.
What? The world is ending and you
want to have a relationship talk now?
Just trying to be mature and...
And... And pragmatic.
Look, Zari, I know we're gonna have
to spend time apart,
like, a lot, so the timeline
doesn't collapse,
but the time
we do spend together will be worth it.
I don't know. Will it?
Get your strike.
See, I feel like
we're on this doomed path
and just blindly
walking towards a cliff.
All right, look. Obviously, I can see
dating a woman from another timeline
that's stuck in another dimension
might end bad.
Does that mean we shouldn't do it?
No. Because the alternative
is way worse.
Zari, I cannot stand being away
from you. It actually hurts my heart.
That is... what I needed to hear.
Mm. Mm-mm...
But, um, listen. If we're gonna
save this relationship,
we need to go save the world first.
Yeah, okay.
Rock and roll.
I just...
I need to clear my head.
Why the long face?
Well, Buddy, team's falling apart
and every human being alive
is about to be annihilated.
Shame.
The way I see it,
bowling is all about bending your elbows
with friends and wetting your beaks.
Best bowling happens
when you're not thinking at all.
Can't beat bad energy with bad energy.
You're right.
I've been going about this all wrong.
Buddy, can you do me a favor?
Nachos and fries.
Breakfast of champions.
And a Cherry Coke for the lady.
Thank you, Buddy.
Whoa! The game isn't done yet.
The scoreboard looming over our head
is stressing us out.
Besides, it doesn't matter if we
win or lose if we're not a team first.
You do realize that the Earth gets
destroyed if we lose, right?
Well, okay, yes,
the outcome does matter,
but we're not gonna win
by tearing each other apart.
I mean, guys, we're not even losing
to the Pin Killers right now.
We're losing to ourselves.
And what we do from this moment on
decides the fate of our planet.
So I'm asking you,
are we losers or are we Legends?
Huh? Do I have a Legend?
Do I have a Legend?
There we go. That's that team spirit.
Cheers.
Here.
- There.
- Thanks.
I suppose that's one good reason
to keep your gloves on.
There's others.
My past is not for everyone to see.
So, Astra, we're gonna need you to roll.
I've never bowled before. Not even once.
Come on. Don't you want to de-ball
that Jersey Shore wannabe?
Hmm?
Welcome to the team.
Hey, I might know how you can bowl
and not have to take your gloves off.
Rory. Rory. Rory.
Ah, here he goes.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- Come on, Astra.
- Come on.
Slide that in.
That's all right. That's okay.
Told you this was a bad idea.
That's a great warmup. This is the one.
Breathe. Breathe.
- We'll take it. Whoo!
- Let's take it. Yes, Astra.
No spare there, Clare.
Ah, our bowling party...
...is definitely putting a cramp
in their style.
- Gary, what are their chances?
- At this point?
We're gonna need a miracle.
We still don't really know
what's coming from the sky.
- A middle finger.
- What?
There's a dial here set to three,
but it goes all the way up to...
Well, Spooner just drew
a middle finger.
- Right. Okay, let's go for that.
- Middle finger it is.
You got this.
- Come on, Mike. Yeah.
- Come on, Mike.
Let's give it the middle finger.
What the hell was that?
- Poor Mikey. Mike, aw.
- You missed it.
Wow! That is a lot of backdraft.
Wouldn't it have been dumb
if broke up for nothing?
My Time Courier's working.
Go!
Oh! Looks like you guys
had a fun day. Rad.
Oh, there's a whole bowling thing
going on. Sort of high stakes.
Okay.
- How we doing?
- It's the last shot and Astra's up.
- Sara, are you there?
- Yeah, I'm here.
Uh...
If Gary's calculations are correct,
you guys can actually win this thing.
But Astra needs to roll a strike.
Of course the stakes couldn't be
any higher my first time bowling.
Look, it's gonna be all right.
We need to change tactics.
It's a very classic style.
All you got to do
is get right in the middle.
Nice deep bend, and roll it on through.
I left Hell to bowl granny-style?
What's become of my life?
Hey, you got this, all right?
You have the whole team behind you.
Here goes nothing.
Go!
Go, go, go.
Astra!
Let's get out of here. Come on.
Hmm. You forgetting something?
How about a rematch?
Not a chance.
Let's put you back where you belong.
How about that?
I control the alley once again
thanks to you,
and I say it's open for everyone.
- Yeah!
- Babe, you did it.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- We're out of here.
- Rude.
Buddy, one last favor. Another round
of nachos for my friends?
- You bet.
- You're the best.
Aren't you curious?
I sense in you powers
both mighty and abundant.
Do you now?
Well, you have a keen eye,
bowling alley denizen. A keen eye.
Powers that will be the death of you.
- I'm sorry I called bowling stupid.
- Bowling means a lot to me.
The old man who fostered me brought
me to league night every week.
Helped me feel like
I belonged to something.
Well, you belong with us now.
I know it's bad luck for you to see me
in a wedding dress.
Babe, you looked amazing.
You look amazing in whatever you wear,
but I love you too much
to let you get married in that thing.
It's great seeing folks have a good time
in the bowling alley again.
How about a team photo?
Oh! Come on, come on, come on.
Okay. All right. Come on.
Say cheese.