- In 2166, an immortal tyrant
named vandal savage
Conquered the world
and murdered my wife and child.
I have assembled an elite team
to hunt him throughout time
And stop his rise to power.
Unfortunately, my plan
is opposed by the body
I'd sworn my allegiance to,
the time masters.
In the future, my friends
may not be heroes,
But if we succeed,
They will be remembered
as legends.
- Previously on
"legends of tomorrow"...
- His name is chronos.
He works for the council
of time masters.
Chronos was clearly sent
to bring me in.
- The lazarus pit
brought me back,
But it left me
with this need to kill.
- Sara! Sara, don't!
- I'm dangerous.
- Up until two months ago,
I was a barista,
Not some damn
winged demigoddess.
- Be the person,
the woman,
The warrior
you were meant to be.
[airplane engine roaring]
[exciting music]
- [breathes heavily]
That wasn't so bad, was it?
- Walk in the park.
So where are we now?
- Washington, d.C.
The year is 1986.
- We've landed at the height
of the cold war
In a world poised
for nuclear annihilation.
- We've traveled here
because I have a new lead
On vandal savage's location.
- Yes.
Gideon managed to intercept
this telefax concerning
Savage's last known whereabouts.
- Tele-what?
- It's like an email...
On paper.
- Wow,
that's totally useless.
- Dude,
this whole thing's crossed out.
- Yeah, redacted
by the u.S. Government,
Which is why we are here
to steal the original file
On savage back from those
who are tracking him.
- Uh, that's the...
- Now, now...
Don't worry.
We are cloaked.
- You want us to break in
to the pentagon?
Sounds awesome.
- It sounds crazy.
- What's the plan?
- Oh, the fabricator
will fashion you
The necessary
pentagon credentials.
- Ooh, and don't forget
our g-man disguises.
I always wanted
to be a spy.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
- Now, the file we're after is
kept in a secure records room.
In order to gain access,
we're going to need to, uh,
Borrow a magnetic key card.
- Because this is so much easier
than just shrinking down
And stealing it.
- Let me show you
how it's done...
Old school.
[shoes squeak]
- [gasps]
- You okay, ma'am?
- I wasn't watching
where I was going.
Thank you.
- Just doing my job.
♪ ♪
- That's a nifty
little trick.
Really?
We're trying to save the world
and you're lifting wallets?
- It's called multitasking.
[upbeat string music]
♪ ♪
[cardreader beeps]
- The records room
has closed-circuit cameras.
We need a diversion.
- Someone call my name?
Yeah! Whoo-hoo!
[cheers and applause]
[crowd cheering]
[all shouting]
- Double or nothing
says I put this punk
On the pinewood.
- Yeah, I'll take a piece
of that action.
[cheers and whistling]
- We got the file.
- Okay, now
for the tricky part.
All personnel
are subject to search
Upon exiting
the pentagon.
Firestorm will divert the power
long enough for you to exit.
- Ready when you are.
[electricity sparking]
All clear.
♪ ♪
- What did you do, jefferson?
I warned you about
the electromagnetic pulse.
Now you've touched
a neutral wire,
Causing the power
to pass through us.
- You mean,
"pass through me."
- If you knew anything about
alternating current power--
- Gray?
- Yes, jefferson?
- Shut up.
[static crackles]
[explosion]
[distant alarm wailing]
The alarm!
- This is a restricted exit.
- Sorry, we must have
gotten lost.
- I'm going to need to see
your key card, ma'am.
[distant alarm wailing]
We have a code seven violation.
[grunting, blows landing]
- We have a slight problem.
[cheering,
alarm buzzing]
- It's been fun, fellas.
Back!
- Where is that smoke
coming from?
- Ah!
- We've got the file.
What the hell does kendra
think she's doing?
[alarm buzzing]
- Good question.
[man screaming]
- All right, wonderful,
we've got a demigoddess
Who's gone
completely berserk.
Abort.
I repeat, abort.
Get back to ship
right now.
- Roger that.
- I meant,
"use the door,"
But while you're at it,
can you help return
Our winged avenger
to her cage?
- Instead of dwelling
on what went wrong,
Let's focus on the positive.
- What are you talking about?
It was awesome.
- In the same way that
tsunamis, earthquakes,
And other natural disasters
are "awesome."
- We got the file on savage.
- Despite the hiccup
with the alarm?
- Oh, so it's my fault now?
You know, maybe if you
weren't always yammering away
In my head,
I could actually focus.
- You have access to 60 years
of knowledge and experience.
Why not just take advantage
of that?
- Because it's my body on
the line out there, not yours.
- Hey,
it's not your fault.
Everything would have been fine
if big bird over here
Hadn't freaked out.
- Excuse me?
- Enough.
There is plenty of blame
to go around.
Now, fortunately, gideon was
able to generate a low-end emp,
Which erased all the pentagon's
magnetic media.
- Like security footage?
- Look, you're just lucky
that the department of defense
Likes to keep incidents
like this under wraps.
Gideon, any luck
with our purloined secret file?
Please say yes.
- Yes, captain.
According to the pentagon,
savage has defected
To the soviet union.
- So the most powerful evil
the world has ever known
Has just gone red
at the height of the cold war.
- And now he's gonna help them
cook up something
That kills the future.
- Gideon,
set a course...
For the soviet union.
[airplane engine roaring]
- Captain, we've just crossed
into soviet airspace.
- Don't worry, jefferson,
we are moving far too fast
For anyone to track us.
- I'm afraid that's not true.
Someone is tracking us.
[airplane engine roars]
- I thought
this ship was cloaked.
- It is.
- Boba fett's back.
- Chronos must have
followed us
When we made the jump
from the '70s.
- Sir, we have a lock
on the waverider.
- Prepare to fire.
- He's closing fast.
Captain,
what would you like me to do?
- Slow down,
drop our cloak,
And make as much noise
as possible.
- Whoa, that's, like,
top three on the list of things
We definitely shouldn't do.
- Just trust me.
[airplane engine
powers down]
- We run out of gas
or something?
- Chronos is still
in pursuit.
Weapons systems tracking.
- Look, if this is your idea
of trying to lose him, then, m--
- Uh-huh.
The soviet air force
to the rescue.
Now, let's see how badly
chronos wants to follow us.
[suspenseful music]
- Wow, it's a mig-21.
No one's ever been this close
to one before.
- Are you quoting "top gun"?
- Maybe.
- I've got
heat-seeking missiles
Closing at a distance
of less than a mile.
- Which is why I need you
to cut the engines.
- Whoa, wait,
don't we need those to land?
- I said,
"cut them," gideon.
- Missiles are now targeting
something else.
- Chronos.
[alarm buzzing]
[explosion]
- I suggest you all
strap yourselves in.
It's going to be a bit
of a bumpy landing.
- Initiating
emergency landing protocol.
- How's it going, gideon?
- There's not much more
I can do.
Elevation is 5,000.
4,000. 3,000.
- When I said, "bumpy,"
I meant, "prepare
for crash landing."
[airplane crashing]
- Good news, captain.
Despite our rough landing,
The ship is
still fully operational.
- Welcome to the u.S.S.R.,
gentlemen.
- If it were up to me,
they would revoke
Your pilot's license.
- "they" are
more than welcome to,
Considering I don't have one.
Did you get anything on savage
from the pentagon file?
- It appears our friend
has been quite busy
Since we last saw him.
- Svarog?
- God of fire
in slavic mythology;
A secret project
the soviets are working on.
Considering
savage's involvement,
Most likely some sort of weapon.
- Valentina vostok.
Graduated top
of her physics program
And then just dropped out
of academia.
- To help develop
savage's new weapon, no doubt.
- The cold war's up for grabs,
And miss vostok
is the linchpin.
- I say we put two
in the back of her head
And call it a day.
- We have no idea
who this woman is
Or what her effect may be
on history.
She may be the next madame curie
for all we know.
- She's working for savage.
That's all we need to know.
- She probably has no idea
who's backing her research.
Just let me approach her
as a scientist,
And we'll see what she knows
about savage's weapons program.
- It's 1986,
you're american,
And you don't speak russian.
She'll have you pegged
as a spy in a second.
- Perhaps I can help
with that.
Ingestible translators.
They attach to your larynx
via neural interface.
Swallow them;
you can speak and understand
Any language spoken to you.
- How--how do you turn it on?
- Gideon?
Switch them into russian.
Go on.
Say something.
- [scoffs]
[speaking russian]
Wait, I'm still
speaking english.
[speaking russian]
I'm speaking russian now,
aren't I?
- Now you're annoying
in multiple languages.
- Gideon, switch him
back to english.
Now, according
to vostok's file,
She's a big fan
of the ballet.
She has box seats
at the bolshoi
And attends every performance.
- It seems
the final performance
Of "le roi candaule"
is today.
- Dr. Palmer,
you will engage vostok
At the ballet,
whilst you, mr. Snart...
You're going to be
his wingman.
- Oy.
- Better go bone up
on vostok's cv.
- I guess I'll bone up
on the ballet.
Gideon, bone me.
- We have a problem.
- Right, you're going to have to
be a little bit more specific.
- It's kendra.
She's completely unstable;
you saw her at the pentagon.
That psycho priestess chay-ara
took over
And clawed a guard's eyes out.
- Perhaps kendra just needs
a bit of time.
Remember, it was
her first time out in the field
Since carter's death.
- Well, carter's not going to be
the only dead body on our hands
If someone doesn't get her
under control.
- You know,
perhaps you're right,
And it just so happens
I have the perfect candidate
for the job.
- No.
No, I was not talking
about me.
- And yet, I can think of no one
better suited to the task.
- I'm not a fan of feelings.
If kendra needs someone
to talk through her grief with--
- Kendra needs someone
to help her
Get her warrior side
under control.
I imagine you,
above anyone else,
Know how to do that.
- This is a bad idea.
[upbeat instrumental music]
♪ ♪
- I got eyes on vostok.
She's headed straight for you,
lover boy.
- All right, gentlemen.
Everything's looking good
from my end.
Proceed.
- Ms. Vostok.
Simon huntsberger,
university of moscow
Physics department.
- I'm not interested
in talking to student.
If you want lecture,
come by office hours.
- I'm actually
a fellow scientist.
I read your paper
on applied physics
And nuclear fusion.
Perhaps, if you allow me
to take you to dinner,
We can discuss in detail.
♪ ♪
- Damn, that was cold,
Even by russian standards.
- Heads-up.
- What the hell is this?
- Warriors train every day.
- Sorry,
but I'm not in the mood.
- "sorry" is not gonna help
that guard that you defaced
At the pentagon.
- Two months ago,
I was a barista.
I had no idea
I had some psycho hawk goddess
Inside of me,
And then I meet carter,
and he convinces me
To let her out,
and now that he's gone...
I can't control it,
So thanks for the offer,
But I won't risk
letting that monster out again.
- That monster inside you
is not gonna go away.
You have to learn
how to control her.
- And how, exactly,
do you expect me to do that?
- Let's find out.
[metal clanging]
[beeping]
- Temporal anomaly detected.
- Chronos.
- The russian jet
damaged his ship.
- He's still alive?
- He went down just outside
moscow city limits.
- Mr. Rory,
How would you like
to accompany me
On a little mission?
- Will I get to
use my gun?
- A near-certain likelihood.
- Lead the way, captain.
- You struck out, raymond.
Maybe I should
take a crack at her.
- I think we may have
gotten off on the wrong foot.
I don't mean to bother you--
- too late.
- But, as an investor,
I'm in a position
To fund your research.
That is why
I wanted us to meet.
- Easy, raymond,
you're gonna spook her.
- I think it's important to know
who's funding your research,
Don't you think?
For instance...
Project svarog.
- Sorry,
is this man bothering you?
- Don't trouble yourself.
I'm not a damsel in distress.
- Good,
because I'm not a white knight.
[bells chime]
- Seems intermission
is over.
- You wouldn't want to miss
queen nisia dancing naked
With the nymphs.
- My favorite part
of the ballet,
But I've seen it
so many times.
Perhaps, you wouldn't mind
walking me home instead.
♪ ♪
[crickets chirping]
- I hate nature.
- Shh, shh, shh, shh.
- Thirty meters.
Chronos must be hiding out
in the trees.
- Is that any way
to treat an old friend?
- Time master druce,
How on earth
did you find me?
- You haven't exactly
been subtle.
- Can I waste this guy?
- Could you
give us a moment?
- You said I'd get
to use my gun.
Hmm.
- What a colorful team
you've assembled for yourself.
- I thought
that you were--
- Chronos?
He was killed in the crash,
I'm afraid.
I was sent to scuttle
his time ship,
Lest it be discovered
by the soviets.
- And you left
a temporal anomaly.
- To lure you
out of the cold, as it were.
You've turned your back
on the very institution
You were meant to serve.
Our job is to protect time,
Thereby protecting
all life.
- I am trying
to save the world
From complete destruction.
- You and your band
of rogues have run rampant
Throughout history.
This is why
we work alone, rip.
A team is a liability;
you've proven that.
They keep you from making
the tough choices.
- I am here
because the council refused
To make that tough choice.
- Well, they can sometimes
be slow to realize the obvious,
But I've been authorized
to offer you a deal.
End this foolish crusade;
return with me
To the vanishing point.
You'll be acquitted
of all charges, and in...
A few hundred years,
we may even be able to fix
The damage you've caused.
- And what about my team?
- They will be returned
to their own timelines unharmed,
Which is more than I can say
for carter hall.
You were one
of my brightest pupils
And by far my favorite.
Will you at least
consider my offer?
- I'll consult
with my comrades.
- Please do, rip,
And then meet me here
in an hour.
- And if I don't?
- Then you're
beyond my help.
- That's a pretty sweet deal
"time cop" offered you
back there.
- Well, I see we can add
"eavesdropping"
To your criminal resume.
- Maybe you should start
thinking more like a crook.
Your friend's planning on
killing you.
- Time master druce is one
of my most trusted friends;
Besides, if he wanted
to do me any harm,
Why didn't he do it just now
when he had the chance?
- Because he wants you to
bring the whole team with you,
And that's not gonna happen,
Because I'm taking a pass.
[both grunting,
metal clanging]
- Are we done here yet?
- If you want
to harness your power,
You need to learn
to control your fear.
- Yeah, well, you've
been training for half your life
To be some
cold-blooded assassin,
So I really don't think
you understand what it's like.
- Before you can control it,
You have to accept
that it's part of you.
- [grunts]
Ease up, will you?
- You've got to
channel your anger.
- Sara, stop.
- Push down your emotions.
Focus on your opponent.
- [grunts]
[high-pitched squeaking]
- Kendra?
- [shouts]
[both grunting]
- Sara!
Sara, I'm so sorry,
I'm so sorry--
[both grunting]
- Sara, what are you doing?
It's me!
[both gasping]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[accordion music]
- Are you sure
you don't want your coat back?
I can't believe
how you're not freezing.
- Oh, I love the cold.
- And ballet.
- So what is it about the ballet
that you love, valentina?
- The combination
of grace and strength,
Pushing the body
to its breaking point.
It's a thing of beauty.
My apartment.
You know,
this time of night,
It's colder
than a siberian winter.
- It sounds perfect.
- You know, I'm sure we could
heat it up.
- Sadly, I have business
elsewhere this evening.
- Well...
If this is good-bye...
♪ ♪
- You enjoy the show,
raymond?
- I think I've got frostbite
in some not-so-fun places
From waiting out here.
Did she tell you
what kind of weapon
Savage is building?
- Didn't come up.
Such a romantic evening;
I didn't want to spoil the mood.
- So other a steamy
good night kiss
And a possible case of
hypothermia,
We've got nothing.
- I wouldn't say that.
It's valentina's security badge
for a place called
Luskavic labs.
Whatever weapon she's building
for savage,
We'll find it there.
- I guess I should just be happy
you didn't swipe her wallet.
- So, uh, what happens?
You hand over the ship
and turn yourself in
To the time masters,
and the rest of us just--
- Will be returned
to your former lives
In January 2016.
It will be
as if you never left.
- Aside from the fact that
starling city might be part
Of the u.S.S.R.,
thanks to our efforts.
- All the more reason
to consider the offer.
The time council will do
everything within their power
To correct the mistakes
that we've made.
- But they still haven't
changed their mind
About stopping savage?
- Well,
according to them, he's part
Of the natural course
of history,
Terrible as that course may be.
Look, I'm not saying
that this offer
Is without its downsides.
If we abandon our plan now,
then I still lose
My wife and son.
- So why throw in the towel?
I thought you said this mission
was bigger than any one of us.
- Yes, but if you'll remember,
when I first recruited you,
I wasn't entirely forthright
about my motivations
Or about how dangerous
this mission would be.
- Carter hall knew the risks
before he signed on.
- Hmm.
Well, for the rest of you,
it's now time to decide
Whether the future
is worth fighting for.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[crickets chirping]
- I cannot tell you
How pleased I am
to see you, hunter.
- I finally came
to my senses.
You were right,
as always.
I've risked the lives
of my team;
I've endangered the very fabric
of time itself.
I only hope
you can forgive me.
- All will soon
be made right again.
- Hello, old friend.
- I'm so sorry
it had to turn out this way,
But the council cannot risk
keeping you alive.
- Such a shame.
I won't be able to tell mick
he was right.
- Mick?
- My colorful friend,
who was convinced
You were planning on
killing me.
- Your friends
seem to have abandoned you,
But no matter.
Chronos will track them down.
- Can't believe
you brought this stooge
To do your dirty work.
I never had you pegged
as a coward, druce.
- In that case,
I promise to stay here
To ensure that your punishment
is carried out properly.
I wouldn't want you
to die alone.
- Who says I'm alone?
[explosion]
[flamethrower fires]
- What a wuss.
[laser gun fires]
[explosion]
- This is not the time
to show off.
It's best if we attack
from a covered position.
- I'm through playing it safe.
This time,
we do things my way.
[screams]
[beeping]
[explosion]
- Run, punk! Run!
- Jefferson!
Where is he? Chronos' blast
forced us to separate--
I--I didn't see where
he landed.
- Jax!
Jefferson!
- All right, no need to shout;
I'm right here.
- There you are;
thank god you're okay.
Why didn't you answer
when I called you?
Did it not occur to you
that I'd be worried?
- Look, I just got a...
Little lost.
- We need to get him
to the med bay now.
- Oh, gentlemen,
I trust everything went
According to plan
at the bolshoi?
- Piece of cake.
Made contact with vostok
and swiped her badge.
- Thanks to me. Pretty boy
just froze his ass off.
- [breathes heavily]
- What happened to him?
- Chronos.
- Jax here was--
- almost got himself killed.
- And we need to get you
to the med bay.
- Ah, the med bay,
Where a morphine drip awaits me.
- Now just try
and take it slowly.
- Don't bother telling him
what to do;
He'll just do the opposite.
- Oh, yeah, it would be
my fault that I got hurt,
Because I didn't listen to you
in your infinite wisdom.
I am sorry, professor.
- Exactly.
It seems this...Partnership
of ours has become untenable.
- Partnership?
No, this is a dictatorship,
One in which you get
to call all the shots
And I get to take
all the shots.
- Do you think I like
seeing you hurt?
- Don't act like you actually
care about me, man.
I'm just a life-support system.
I didn't even want to come
on this stupid trip.
You kidnapped me.
- Oh, this old tune.
- Did you ever stop to think
that I actually had a life
Back in 2016?
- I almost forgot:
A promising career
As an auto mechanic.
- I had a mom,
A widow.
What happens to her
if something happens to me
In 1986?
Huh?
She's just gonna think
that I left her
Without even saying good-bye.
Man, do you have any idea
what that does to her?
- We've all made sacrifices.
But can't you see that
this mission, stopping savage,
Is bigger than any one of us?
- I am so sick
of you using that tone.
When are you gonna learn
you are not my father?
- I'm sorry you lost him
at such a tender age,
But if your father were here,
right now,
He'd be saying
what I'm saying.
Just grow up, jefferson.
The future of the world
is at stake,
And if you insist
on getting yourself killed,
As terrible as that might be
for your mother, or me,
Who, incidentally,
would also die,
I am more concerned
with the billions of people
Who will die
because of your...
Arrogant adolescent ego!
- Okay.
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
- Please don't--don't--
don't say it.
I was cruel
And unjustified, and I--
I said those things
Just for the sake
of hurting him.
- Why aren't you telling that
to jax?
- I had to hurt him, raymond;
it's the only way
I can get through to him.
I've tried everything else.
- Well, he's just a kid.
- So was ronald,
and look what happened to him.
- Your former half
of firestorm.
- Yes.
I can't--I--
I can't go through this again.
I can't lose another.
The reason I'm constantly
lecturing jefferson
Is because I'm the one
who brought him along,
And if something happens,
I'm the one who has
to go back to 2016
And tell his mother
that her little boy
Is never coming home,
And I would rather die
than do that.
- That looks sore.
What happened?
- Maybe you should ask
the lunatic
You put in charge
of training me.
- I...Actually, I was hoping
that the arrangement
Between you and sara
might be, uh...
Mutually beneficial.
- You mean you knew
about this bloodlust thing?
- It's the captain's job
to know everything on his ship.
Look, sara went through hell
when she was resurrected,
And I was hoping
that you'd be able to...
Coax out her human side
from the darkness
Of the lazarus pit.
- Why me?
- Well, after 4,000 years
of reincarnation,
Surely you know a thing or two
about rebirth.
- Heads up!
Let's go.
"a warrior trains
every day," remember?
- I'm not a warrior,
and I tried to kill you
The last time we did this,
remember?
- "tried"
being the operative word.
Look, you want to know
my theory?
- No.
- I think your problem
is the opposite of mine.
I need to learn to embrace
my inner hawk goddess,
But you--you need to learn
to embrace your human side.
- And what if that side of me
is gone?
What if she
doesn't exist anymore?
- Well, only one way
to find out.
- What, are you baiting me?
- No,
I'm training you.
Come on.
Are you scared?
[bars clink]
[airplane engine roaring]
- Here we are,
luskavic labs,
The secret facility
where vostok works.
- So what's the plan?
- Simple.
We use vostok's credentials
to enter the lab
And find out what she's building
on behalf of savage.
- Reconnaissance
in a laboratory.
Finally, my kind
of mission.
- No, no, no,
hang on a minute;
Jefferson's still recovering
from his injuries.
- This is hardly a job
for firestorm;
Let him rest.
[speaking russian]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- I'm dr. Gregor gavrilov
of the state council of science,
And I'm here
to inspect the facility.
I'm in
and heading to the basement.
♪ ♪
Here's hoping the key
that mr. Snart stole
Off valentina works.
[beeps, door clicks open]
Oh, my god.
I know what vostok
is working on.
She's trying
to build...Me.
- What do you mean?
- I mean, savage has spent
the last decade trying
To level the arms race
against our team.
Operation svarog.
Slavic god of fire,
of course.
He and vostok are building
A soviet firestorm.
[steam hissing]
- They've already
built a thermal core.
- Professor,
need I remind you,
This is
a reconnaissance mission.
- It's only a matter of time
before vostok figures out
How to stabilize
a soviet firestorm.
[machine whirring]
I'm not leaving
without it.
It's the key
to building others just like me.
- Yes, but perhaps you should
wait for the rest of the team.
They're on their way.
- Are you familiar
with ultra-high-energy
Cosmic rays, captain?
The radiation released
inside this chamber
Will kill anyone
other than me.
- Look, despite
your impermeability
To nuclear energy,
You're still
quite vulnerable to bullets.
- I just need someone
to take the core offline,
So I can remove it safely
and shield it.
- I'm all over it,
professor.
- We're all over it.
- Remember, dr. Palmer,
that shutting down the core
Incorrectly can lead
to the creation of--
- Strangeness, black holes,
and uncontrolled
Fusion reactions
that consume the universe?
See? I was listening
during class, professor.
[door creaking]
[pressure hissing]
[electricity crackles]
- How we doing,
boy scout?
- Uh, point of fact,
I completed all 21 merit badges,
Including nuclear science,
so I'm an eagle scout.
Uh-oh.
We got a problem.
Valentina's headed toward
the core containment unit.
The radiation
stein's about to unleash--
I--if she opens the door--
- We're here to stop savage
from building
A nuclear-powered superhero.
Saving some commie broad
ain't on the agenda.
- Even if the radiation
doesn't kill her, savage will,
The second he finds out
the lab's been sabotaged.
Look, we gotta get her out
of here.
- Well, who's gonna shut down
the core, raymond?
I skipped that merit badge.
- Raymond, why
is the thermal core
Still running
at full power?
- I'll handle the core.
You handle valentina.
- You're willing
to risk the mission
For a woman you barely know?
- Be helpful to others.
It's the scout motto.
- 30 seconds.
I'll get vostok,
you kill the power for stein,
And, raymond,
Promise me.
- Bad idea.
- What are you doing here?
- Believe me,
I've been asking myself
The same question.
- That night at the bolshoi.
It was you
who stole my keys.
- And your wallet,
but it was nothing personal.
- What the hell
is that man doing?
He has no idea
what the core is capable of.
- Relax.
He's the one
who invented it.
[radiation fizzles]
- I'm the first person
to have ever seen
Cosmic radiation
with his own eyes.
- You know, let's keep it
that way.
Snart, you better
keep valentina out
Of the core containment unit.
- You used me.
You work
for american government.
- I'm wanted
by the american government.
Does that count?
Look, I may be your white knight
just this once,
But that weapon
savage has you building?
He's creating
a nuclear-powered monster.
- I know.
It was sweet of you
to think of me
As a damsel in distress,
But...
I'm not the one
who needs rescuing.
- Don't flatter yourself,
sweetheart.
I'm not
the sentimental type.
- No,
but your partner,
The physicist
with the big brown eyes,
Is.
- Turn the core
back online.
You will turn it back on,
or I will put a bullet
In your friend's head.
- Don't you dare.
She's gonna shoot me
whether you do it or not.
- That may be true,
And you can take that gamble
if you like.
It's only his life
you wager.
- Almost there.
- I'm not joking, raymond.
Don't you dare
push that button.
- Raymond,
what's going on?
The core just went
back online.
- Sorry, professor,
I had to do it.
- You idiot.
- I--I can still remove it.
I just hope I can absorb
the excess power.
- No. Do you have any idea
the kind of energy that--
- Should have listened
to your friend.
- What the hell
are you doing, gray?
- Jefferson?
- You are not firestorm;
you're just a stubborn old man
Who's about to make
a really stupid decision.
- Wait, I--is this
what it's like
When I'm in your head?
I--I apologize, dear boy,
because it's rather distracting.
- Your body
cannot handle this alone.
- Appreciate your concern.
You were right.
I've risked your life
enough times.
Now, it's my turn.
- No!
[radiation sizzling]
- [breathing heavily]
- He's too weak.
He'll never get out of there
alone.
[gun cocks]
- Professor stein,
Your comrade here tells me
you know quite a bit
About this project
of mine.
Very good.
You and I
have much to discuss.
- [grunts]
- What are you waiting for?
You forget how
to use that thing?
- My employer, mr. Savage,
would very much like
To meet you
and the rest of your friends.
- Careful what you wish for.
- This where
the party's at?
[flames whooshing]
[gunshots]
- Aah!
- Mr. Snart,
can you hear me?
Do not let vostok leave
with that thermal core.
[gunshots]
- Get the hell out of here!
What are you waiting for?
Go, go!
[gunshots]
- Now might be a good time
to send in reinforcements.
Mick and stein just got pinched
by the russkies.
- You're gonna have to
get out of there right now.
- They're hanging us out to dry,
rip; I need backup.
- I'm afraid our only option
is retreat.
- What about my partner?
- Well, until we devise
our next move,
Mr. Rory will have to
fend for himself.
Remember the mission.
If the soviets get that
thermal core back,
Your partner will not be
the only one who dies.
[gunshots]
[explosion]
- You better kill me now.
If I ever get my hands on you,
I'm gonna get all "rocky iv"
on your ass.
I'm gonna remember that,
comrade.
- We must leave now, colonel.
- There's still
one more intruder,
And he has the thermal core.
- We don't need it now.
We have something far better.
- Ugh,
Thank god you managed
to grab it.
- Where was my backup,
captain?
Half the team is gone...
[laser powers up]
Because of you.
- Only if I'd have sent
the other half in to save them,
They'd be captured too,
and where would we be,
Hmm?
Savage would have both halves
of firestorm,
A dead kendra
on top of a dead carter,
Everything he wants.
It would be the end
to our little crusade,
And, most likely, the world.
So before you
pull that trigger,
Ask yourself:
What would you have done?
- That is
a pretty cold calculation, rip.
Almost criminal,
Except we criminals
have a code:
"you never leave
one of your own behind."
- We will get them back.
Now, if savage even hopes
to create a firestorm,
First, he's going to need
a new one of these.
- A thermal core?
- Let me get this straight.
You had kendra and I
training for the next mission,
When we should have been
out there helping them.
- We will help them,
and our next mission
Is to get our compatriots back
from vostok.
- Who is to say
they're not already dead?
- Vostok needs
the professor alive
In order to rebuild
the thermal core.
- And ray and rory?
- Savage will
keep them alive too.
- As leverage.
He'll torture them
if stein tries to hold out.
- Well, we'll have to pray
that he does.
If savage's goal is
to create his own firestorm,
Then stein himself is the key,
the missing piece of the puzzle.
And if vostok figures out
how to turn stein's powers
Against us, then...
I'm afraid the world
is beyond saving.
- Stein's a lot tougher
than he looks.
I mean, it will take a lot
to break him.
- That's the good news.
The bad news
Is that our compatriots
are being held
In an impenetrable
soviet gulag.
[door clangs shut]
- Get a good night's sleep.
You and dr. Vostok
have much work to do
In the morning.
- My companions
from the lab...
What did you do
with them?
- Don't worry.
They're alive.
Whether they remain that way
Is entirely up to you,
professor.
[dramatic horn music]
♪ ♪
[exciting music]
- Greg, move your head.