Time travel is real,
and so are its consequences.
When a terrible time paradox
put all of history in peril,
an elite team was formed.
Their job... to protect history
and repair these so-called
anachronisms.
Unfortunately,
this is not that elite team.
And yet, this team of misfits
and outcasts is determined
to fix the history
which they have broken.
Not because they are heroes,
but because they are legends.
Previously,
onLegends Of Tomorrow...
Seeing Stein with his grandkid
earlier...
You two are inseparable. Literally.
I want to break up Firestorm.
Your totem's strength grows
when the threats that you must
face become more powerful.
But you cannot face
this new threat alone.
That amulet is a totem.
We're bound together somehow.
Cut the crap and tell me
what we're facing here.
That information is need-to-know.
The only thing you need to know...
your ridiculous team
could never handle it.
They are the reason
Mallus is a threat.
And there might just come a day
when we need the Legends
to do what they do best.
You best stop following me, guv.
That is a most impressive scream.
In another era, you could have
a career alongside Vincent Price.
Rigor Mortis hasn't set in.
He's been dead less than four hours.
Extreme pallor in the face
and fingernails
suggest rapid blood loss,
yet not a drop to be seen.
Killed off-site,
his body dumped here,
far from the illustrious streets
of his upbringing.
A handkerchief with
his college crest...
a graduation gift, no doubt.
What do you make of that?
Improbably,
it appears that our killer is...
a vampire.
You sure you want to do this?
Break up Firestorm?
Well, I'm sure Grey wants
off the ship,
but I'm sure that can't happen
if we're still bonded to each other,
so...
Yeah, but your bond
isn't just physical.
You guys have been psychically
bonded for over three years.
Yeah, and it's been no picnic,
let me tell you.
Last time I got laid,
afterwards Grey said to me,
Well done, Jefferson.I mean...
Could have done without knowing that.
Does Grey...
I mean, Marty, know that
you want to break up with him?
No clue. But if he did,
he'd say it was too dangerous.
Well, if you're really
determined to do this,
severing your psychic connection
could give us some...
much needed mental space to figure
out how to untie the nuclear knot.
Well, let's do it.
Here goes.
Oh, I forgot.
There might be a couple side effects.
What side effects?
Just, like, you know,
facial swelling,
maybe a little
gastrointestinal upset...
oh, and short-term memory loss.
- How do you feel?
- Oh, normal.
Except, I'm not craving grapefruit.
Okay.
Ray, it's 9.00am,
and I'm not craving grapefruit!
- Delightful.
- Let me get this straight.
This ship can make any kind
of food you can imagine,
and you three picked grapefruit,
a bran muffin, and oatmeal.
After you try everything,
you go back to the basics.
I lived my whole life eating rations
and bland food.
From now on, I eat like a queen.
I'm glad you left 2042.
Actually, I wanted to talk to you
guys about going back to 2042.
Or better yet, 2041.
I was thinking, why is my family dead
when I'm on a time machine?
Unfortunately,
that's not how this works.
I thought you could change the past.
We can correct the past.
And the future, but...
- we don't change it.
- Why not?
Because doing so could
cause unforeseen,
possibly even disastrous
consequences.
It's a temporal butterfly effect,
if you will.
Try not doing something
that would save your brother's life.
Does a sister count?
What's up, shipmates?
I got exciting news to share.
Team meeting in ten minutes.
And, Mick, I have beer.
One lousy beer for breakfast.
- It's breakfast?
- Yeah.
What time did you go
to bed last night, buddy?
I didn't. Drank a lot of coffee.
Can you tell?
Nate, why are we staring
at an anachronism map?
Because, Captain,
I did a deep dive on the data.
And the anachronisms we created
at first glance seem scattershot...
random.
But since history is cause and effect
I decided to do a little experiment.
I folded a linear timeline
onto itself
following the mathematics
of the golden ratio.
Follow me.
Damn it, Gideon. That was your cue.
My apologies, Dr. Heywood.
Oh, see, the anachronisms
form a pattern.
Should have guessed.
Though time may be broken, like
all matter in the known universe,
it still possesses
a mathematical harmony.
Not exactly. Uh...
What about those two?
Those two are outliers.
The first one is Seattle, 2042.
- When the assassin tried to kill me.
- Right.
While cool... not the part where,
you know, you almost got killed.
It's not as cool as the other one.
London, 1895.
How do I say this? There's a vampire.
Half dozen men snatched
off the streets
only to have their bodies
dumped three days later
completely drained of blood.
Vampires.
Waited my whole life to kill one.
Do you just carry that around
all the time?
My whole life.
There's no such thing as vampires.
Increased immigration
at the fin de siècle
and the fear that good English
women would lose their virtue
to foreign predators is responsible
for these ludicrous stories.
I say we go see what's so interesting
about this anachronism.
Victorian London.
Opium dens and low-cut corsets.
Arthur Conan Doyle
and the rolling fog.
Syphilis, whores, and vampires.
There's a strong smell of garlic.
It's tied around my neck.
Yep, you're a regular Van Helsing.
That's from Dracula.
I'm reading it.
Don't tell me the end.
Another vampire victim
found dead in the street.
Oy, give me that.
Whoa, vampires?
What the hell is he talking about?
The blood-sucking creatures
that we're here hunting.
Oh, no. Short-term memory loss.
One of the side effects of the serum.
Come on.
- Who are you lot?
- Oy, Scotland Yard.
We're here to see about these
so-called vampire attacks.
And we're with the NYPD.
Nothing like a bit of cooperation
from across the pond, right?
- Right.
- This one of the victims?
Unlucky devil.
Whoa, whoa, Mick!
You don't want him coming back
to life, do you?
What's going on here?
Scotland Yard has
already visited twice,
and if the NYPD is issuing
ladies warrant cards,
then I'm the bloody Queen.
All right, who brought their phone?
Wasn't me, even though
I do love that song.
That's not a phone.
That's a 2016 Palmer Tech 7G
smart watch.
Hand it over.
I don't know what you're on about.
You want some of this?
Who does that watch belong to?
No? All right. Mick, stake him.
Oh, all right. All right.
A vicar was walking down the street
as calm as can be
when a dead man fell from the sky.
It wasn't no normal corpse, neither.
No identification, strange clothes,
and that there watch.
Which you stole.
He wasn't gonna miss it.
I will, though.
It is the finest timepiece
I've ever seen.
It did sell better in England.
So, where's our John Doe, now?
Well, I buried him in Stone's Hollow.
And the next day,
the first vampire victim
was snatched from the street.
Because that corpse you buried
was a vampire from the future,
you idiot.
All right, time to go.
Who are you lot?
Tonight, we're grave diggers.
All right, we're looking for one
unmarked grave among hundreds.
I say we split up.
Check them row by row.
Or we can start with the one
that's already dug up.
Yes.
Ah, the vampire must've dug himself
out before nightfall.
Damn it, that anachronistic
corpse was our only lead.
Wait, wait, did you hear that?
Kill it, kill it, kill it!
- Rip.
- Rip?
- Welcome to London.
- Listen, Englishman.
Those time pigs try to take me,
I'll burn them alive.
The Time Bureau are not actually
aware of my current whereabouts.
And as surprising
as this may sound...
I need the Legends' help.
Miss Jiwe. I was surprised to hear
that you'd rejoined the team.
It's surprising to me too.
I trust we're not under arrest?
Far from it.
Rip?
What... Rip, where the hell
did you come from?
Where'd he come from?
What... where... where do any
of us come from?
You know, what are the odds of that
one lonely sperm meeting with
that one special egg?
You know us science types are always
still wrestling with the big
questions.
We've answered those questions,
Dr. Palmer.
I need Jax's help... with this.
There's some GPS data on here,
and it might be able to tell us
where our dead man walking came from,
and where he's going. Or her.
So, yep.
Oh, man, the short-term memory
loss is worse than I anticipated.
Marty's definitely gonna notice.
It's okay. I got this.
I... I'll just write myself a note.
Like, Rip's back.
Excuse me, what's going on?
What? Nothing, man.
You're acting awfully strange.
- Oh, it's a... Temporal dysplasia.
- Temporal dysplasia.
You know... you know how that is.
- Lily.
- Dad.
Is everything all right?
Ronnie won't sleep.
Your lullabies are
the only thing that work.
All right. Excuse me. Priorities.
All right, little guy.
It's time for you to go to sleep.
Hush little Ronnie
Don't say a word
- Come on, man.
- All right.
We'll continue with the plan.
But not until we figure out
whose watch this is.
Which could be difficult.
Digital Digestgave my software
encryption a five padlock rating.
Sorry. I didn't mean to interrupt.
I... I didn't realize
that you were praying.
Mecca's that way.
I was just looking for my earring.
I wanted to talk to you about before.
I know that it's tough.
That I'm not allowed
to save my family?
Yeah, it's real tough.
You should take comfort
that your brother wanted you
to have that totem.
You reclaimed it.
It's your birthright.
It's your family's...
Hey, stop talking about my
family when you're telling me
I can't save them.
What the hell was that?
This is the reason I asked you
to stay aboard the ship.
The reason that I haven't
returned home.
We're connected.
What for?
I don't know.
I was hoping that we could find
that answer together.
Not to be...
overly sentimental, but...
I've missed this place.
We'd love to reminisce with you,
but your Time Bureau's on our tail.
Makes us slow to help you out.
I'll get down to it, then.
When I permitted the Legends to keep
the Waverider...
Nobody permits us to do anything.
I had an ulterior motive.
Why does that not surprise me?
For the last five years,
I've been chasing a phantom.
A name whispered across time
and in every language.
Mallus.
The Phantom Mollusk?
An evil shellfish?
"Mall-us."
An evil so ancient and powerful
that the Time Masters
dared not speak his name.
Now, I believe that
he is recruiting allies
from throughout time to his cause.
Now, anachronisms are the result
of your breaking time.
It was her idea.
But these outliers, they are most
certainly the work of Mallus.
Now, the Time Bureau is a bureaucracy
and lacks the imagination
to understand this particular threat.
And Director Bennett objects
to my crusade.
I'm alone out here.
So what I'm hearing is, your hot
new girlfriend dumped you,
and now you're crawling back
to your ex.
And I'm no one's side piece.
You know, I think
they're onto something here.
Look, sweetie.
We would love to take you back,
but we don't know
how we could trust you again.
Would circumstances
be any different
if I were to call off my hot
new girlfriend's pursuit of you?
Deal.
All right, what's your plan?
Right, this outlier... the...
the vampire is most likely
the objective of Mallus.
Catch the vampire, catch Mallus.
Sounds like we're gonna need
vampire bait.
Me?
Is it because I'm handsome?
Pretty.
Pretty handsome.
Overcrowding and poverty
made Whitechapel
a breeding ground
for criminal activity,
culminating in the Ripper's
murders right around...
well, now.
Isn't history fascinating?
It certainly is.
Trusting the Englishman
was a damn mistake.
You know we're all on comms,
don't you, Mr. Rory?
I don't give a rat's ass.
No sign of any vampires.
I wish this was like
a Kristen Stewart type,
all broody and sparkly.
Vampires don't sparkle.
You know, Mick, you and the vamp
have a lot in common.
You both like to sleep in,
and, you know...
kill people.
Stein? What are you doing out here?
Looking for you, dear boy.
Nate.
Nate?
We seem to have lost Dr. Heywood.
Nate, answer me.
Look.
He's got Dr. Heywood.
Let's cut him off.
Well, that was invigorating.
You find Pretty?
No, we lost him.
We found potatoes.
Never fear. The game's afoot.
Me thought I heard a voice cry,
Sleep no more!
Professor Stein?
No. Shakespeare, actually.
And it's Sir Stein to you.
It's not every actor who is knighted.
Oh, God. This can't be happening.
Thanks to your lifeblood,
my master will finally make
his return.
But there's much to be done
in the meantime.
Yeah, well, that wasn't creepy.
Sara?
Nate, where are you?
I don't know.
But I just had a chat with Professor
Stein's weird lookalike evil cousin.
Great-great grandfather,
to be exact.
The famous stage actor,
Sir Henry Stein.
Astonishing.
The... the chances of us running
into one of my ancestors are...
astronomical.
Family lore recalls him
as being an eccentric.
But then, what can one expect
from an actor?
He's also an occult weirdo
who kidnapped me to feed his master.
Excellent.
The vampire will lead us to Mallus.
Stay where you are, Dr. Heywood.
Yeah, that's not gonna be a problem.
Whatever they roofied me
with fritzed out my powers.
Can you describe where you are?
Uh, like a...
an operating room?
All I know is there's a spooky-ass
red moon painting on the wall.
- What's that?
- It's...
It's some of my research on Mallus.
Beware the blood-red moon,
when the door that separates
death from life will be opened.
It's the first line of an oath
taken by the Order
of the Shrouded Compass,
an infamous secret society
of London's aristocracy
obsessed with the occult.
That sounds like the perfect place
for an out-of-time vampire
to take refuge.
Yes, well, the Order also believe
in the magical properties
associated with...
a total lunar eclipse.
Which is set to occur right here
in London tonight.
If I wasn't vampire hunting,
I'd rob these rich bastards blind.
Hunting a tiger for sport is...
is just perverse.
I can't believe we're in a time
where women can't vote
and the Internet's not a thing.
Savages.
Anyone who doesn't have
a reflection,
they're getting a stake.
Ladies and gentlemen, if I could
have your attention, please.
Truly uncanny.
It's that 'stache that's astonishing.
I know you're not here
for idle chitchat and aperitifs.
So please allow me to introduce
the star of the evening,
a famed mystic who has come
all the way from America
to communicate with the dead.
Madame Eleanor.
Can't believe people
are buying this garbage.
I sense...
someone in the room who longs
to speak to a departed loved one.
Come.
Sit at my table, if you have no fear.
Since we can't hack the watch
for its GPS data,
we're gonna have to solve
this one the old-fashioned way.
With fingerprints.
Okay, we got the coroner's
fingerprints.
And the second one is mine,
obviously,
and the third one is unidentifiable,
and the fourth one is...
Oliver Queen?
Oliver's a time-traveling vampire
from the future?
We got to call Team Arrow,
figure out what the heck's going on.
Return of the Mack
Pump up the world
Watch my flow
Return of the Mack you know...
About time.
I'm as excited as you are.
But we all must wait
for the blood-red moon
before the ceremony may begin.
Oh, gross.
If you need me, I'll be, um...
I'll be right over here.
Sara, I could really use a rescue
right now.
We're working on it.
Do you remember our mission
from the Greyhill Building?
Like it was yesterday.
Oh, excuse me.
Could you tell me
where the powder room is?
Oh!
Oh, I've missed this.
Everyone, please join hands.
There is a doubter among us.
I, too, was a skeptic once,
before the spirits spoke to me.
But now I am their conduit.
Khaahar.
Do you remember the night
they came for us?
How fast you ran?
You abandoned me, Khaahar.
You let them kill me
so you could live.
No.
You are scared now.
Just as you were scared
of A.R.G.U.S. then.
So much fear.
You were my big sister.
You should have protected me.
- Please.
- Stop this at once.
You heard the lady.
Sara, our cover is blown.
We need to leave.
Wait, the vampire, that was you?
A two-pronged needle by my own
invention is hardly vampiric.
Then who's the stiff?
Nate, are you okay?
Does it look like I'm okay?
Instead of a sexy vampire,
I got stuck with this weirdo.
He's all yours.
The Order has plans
for our time-displaced corpse.
That's why they're kidnapping men
and draining their blood.
It's for their ceremony.
Shall we find out who it is?
Whoa, guys, I am digging the digs.
I mean, I have some serious lab
envy over here.
Yeah? Well, check this out.
Whoa, okay, wow.
Well, I've analyzed
that unidentified print
and got back 100,000
possible variations
on a complete friction ridge.
Okay, so, do we have a match?
Unfortunately. I hope you
guys have a bar on that ship,
because you're gonna need a drink.
The watch belongs to...
Damien Darhk.
Darhk must be integral
to Mallus' plan.
We can't leave Damien Darhk's
body to be resurrected.
Darhk may be a madman,
but he's not the madman
we're presently after.
Guys, we have definitely
overstayed our welcome.
Fall back.
The hell is going on?
We're not killing vampires anymore?
Captain Lance, need I remind you
we are no longer just fixing
ordinary anachronisms here.
Mallus is the only game that matters.
No, it's your game.
We have to stop Damien Darhk
from coming back to life.
And we will.
But from all indications,
Mallus is coming here
to recruit Darhk.
If we destroy Darhk's body,
we destroy any chance
of apprehending Mallus
at the resurrection ceremony.
If Sara says kill Darhk,
or re-kill Darhk,
or Prop him up in a convertible
like Weekend at Bernie's,
that's what we do,
because she's the captain.
I know that you all want to destroy
Darhk, once and for all.
You're just gonna have to be patient.
I'd like to speak to you in private.
Good luck in there.
I'm not letting Damien Darhk
come back to life.
Full stop.
You've lost perspective.
You're letting personal
prejudice cloud your judgment.
If I had, I wouldn't have put
Damien Darhk back into the timeline
and erased his memory,
so that he could kill my sister.
Again.
Look, Sara.
I understand how perilous it would be
for Mr. Darhk to return.
Do you?
Because I'm the only one in this
room that's been resurrected,
and it wasn't an improvement.
All right.
You're right.
You've got to understand, Sara,
that I... I've been chasing Mallus
for so long that...
perhaps,
it is I who's lost perspective.
Never gonna learn how to knock,
are you?
I'm concerned about you.
I know that you think that
woman channeled your brother.
His name was Behrad.
The night A.R.G.U.S. came for
us, I ran.
I knew he was staying to fight,
but I was scared.
I left my brother there to die.
You happy?
Now you know my secret.
- Sorry.
- You know, I don't...
I don't want this anymore.
Whatever's going on with it
or with us,
I... I... I don't care.
That totem is your only remaining
connection to him.
It's not a connection.
It's a reminder...
that I should have been
the one who died.
You know...
it's kind of weird not being able
to sense Stein's emotions.
Don't tell me you're missing
your psychic connection.
Oh, come on. Of course not.
- Well, maybe a little, but...
- Aha!
I've uncovered your ruse.
- You've been using my lab...
- Your lab?
To impede our psychic connection.
It's the very foundation
of Firestorm.
Actually, that's...
that's the foundation of Firestorm.
It... it's the formulae for building
a thermocore.
No, I was playing hangman.
Q!
Q...
Grey, don't take this out on Ray.
He was just helping me figure
out a way we could...
break up Firestorm.
So that you could go home,
and I could stay on the ship.
Oh, I see.
So are you cool with this?
Why wouldn't I be?
After all, you've only been...
been here tinkering in secret
with how to split up a walking,
talking, living nuclear reactor.
- Of course I'm cool with it.
- Okay.
After everything we've been through,
how could you attempt something
of this magnitude behind my back?
Grey, it's not like...
Oh, it seems we both share
a craving for solitude.
Is everyone aboard the ship?
As far as I'm aware.
Is there something I can do for you?
In fact, there is.
If you'd please tell
Captain Lance that...
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
Gideon, initiate
Gentleman's Dreadnought.
Command code recognized.
Are you sure, Director Hunter?
She left me no choice.
Seven, six, five...
- Gideon!
- Four, three, two...
- It's Mr. Hunter.
- One.
What's he done?
All the exits are locked.
And I can't override the command.
Damn it, Rip.
Told you we should never
have trusted the Englishman.
Where's Zari?
Come in.
I was hoping we might meet again.
You channeled my brother earlier.
I need to talk to him again.
Well, I'm sorry.
I cannot merely summon
the dead at whim.
Please, I need to tell him
that I'm sorry.
And I have a way to bring him back.
I can save him this time.
I could try.
I would need a memento,
something that belonged to him
that I could focus my energy on.
Would this work?
So much power.
And you give it away so easily.
A mistake you're unlikely to repeat.
Madame Eleanor.
The blood-red moon beckons.
Restrain her.
I must prepare for the ceremony.
Damn, Gideon, how many secret
commands did Rip program you with?
I believe this was the last
of them, Captain.
Well, I'm captain now,
and I order you
to override Rip's orders
and ready the ship for takeoff.
Right away, Captain Lance.
Director Hunter's command
allows you to fly the Waverider,
just not let any of you off of it.
Well, it's a start.
Plot a course
for the Shrouded Compass.
Damn right, Cap-i-tan.
And bring the ship's
weapon system online.
Needless to say, it's highly likely
that Mr. Hunter is in that building.
And I'm willing to bet that
so is Zari.
You want an omelet,
you got to crack a few eggs.
When you welcomed me
to the Order,
you were seeking proof.
Evidence that life does not
have to end with death.
But the power that courses
through my veins is not mine own.
It is a gift.
From Mallus.
Stop this abomination!
- Turn around! You, turn around!
- Everybody down, now!
Come on, right now!
Your so-called master, where is he?
Mallus is everywhere and nowhere,
refracted in every moment of time.
He is dead.
He is risen.
And he will come again.
Right, well, that's very cryptic.
But I demand to speak to him.
Oh. Well, very well.
Director Hunter.
A pleasure to meet you.
Oh, I'm not here to speak
to your puppet.
I think it's about time
you and I met face-to-face.
You cannot look upon
my true form and live.
While you are hopelessly mortal,
I am a God.
You're too late.
It's good to be back.
Who stole my watch?
Our coordinates say
we're right above the Order.
- Prepare the shock-missiles.
- Three pages left.
What are you doing? Zari's in there.
I need you to target the cargo bay.
What? Our cargo bay?
Shouldn't we have a team vote first?
If anybody has a better idea
how to get the ship open,
now's the time.
Trust me, Jax. Fire.
Shock-missiles away, Captain.
Oh, this is gonna suck so bad.
Grey, if we're gonna die,
I don't want us to go out
mad at each other.
So, I can't remember what for,
but I'm sorry.
You were just thinking of me.
Actually,
I... I should be thanking you.
Who wants to hold hands?
Ray, it's not freaking Toy Story 3.
Everyone shut up.
I got one page left.
Oh
Come on
Yeah
Well I tried to tell you so yes I did
But I guess you didn't know
As I said the story goes
Return of the Mack
Return of the Mack come on
Oh my God
You know that I'll be back here I am
Return of the Mack once again
Return of the Mack pump up the world
Return of the Mack watch my flow
Any last words, Rip?
Yes, I remember you.
I remember everything.
Remember us?
Oh, goodie. More Legends.
Here to kill me, I assume.
This time it'll stick.
That's my totem.
Let's go.
Till we meet again.
Not bad. A little tart.
If you can believe it,
Clarissa prefers to eat her
grapefruit...
With salt. Yeah, I remember.
How?
I got Ray to restore
our psychic connection.
I can feel how much
you're missing your family.
Ever since baby Ronnie was born,
it's only gotten worse.
It's like there's a hole in my chest.
I'm so sorry.
I never expected the birth
of my grandson
would make being away
that much more painful.
And I certainly never wanted you
to share this burden.
But with this new Mallus threat,
and the return of Damien Darhk,
the team needs Firestorm
more than ever.
Yeah, and the team can get Firestorm,
and you can go home,
if we can stabilize the Matrix
into my body.
T.S. Eliot once said,
Only those who risk going too far
can possibly find out
how far one can go.
So, when do we start?
As soon as I fix that giant hole
in the cargo bay.
- Well, good luck with that.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Knock, knock.
Still not knocking.
You want to sit?
Sure. Thanks.
This is gonna sound weird, but...
when my amulet came back to me,
I felt Behrad's presence.
Like, almost like he was with me.
That doesn't sound weird at all.
God, first A.R.G.U.S.,
then that Water Witch.
And now some formerly dead guy
all want to kill me.
My ancestor told me
that the totems' strength grows
when the threats we face
become more powerful.
Fantastic.
I think what she meant is that
you and I are gonna
become great friends.
And we'll defeat whatever evil comes,
together.
I like that.
We need to talk.
By now you know me better
than to expect an apology.
Agents are dead because of you.
They understood the risks
of their profession.
But we learned so much
from the events of last night.
- Next time...
- There won't be a next time, Rip.
You show up out of nowhere
practically begging for our help,
and then you betray us.
You've gone rogue
from every organization
that you've ever been a part of.
Because you don't trust anyone.
I don't know how I could have
ever trusted you.
Sara, I need you with me
now more than ever.
Do you remember when you told me
you had nothing left to teach me?
I guess you had one final lesson.
How to be a cold son of a bitch.
Director Bennett.
Director Hunter.
You've called in your last chit.
I should never have sanctioned
last night's mission.
But the mission proved
that Mallus is real.
Explain it to the tribunal.
In the meantime,
you are being detained
and suspended from active duty.
You can't detain me. I...
I created the Bureau.
Then you of all people should know
that no one is exempt from its rules.
Agent Sharpe.
Thank you for notifying us
of Director Hunter's whereabouts.
Now the Legends are free
to fly the skies?
Affirmative.
The Time Bureau has bigger things
to worry about
than a bunch of idiots.
Mallus is getting stronger,
Captain Lance.
Last night was only the beginning.
There is a war coming.
And history needs you to be ready.
You and the rest of the Legends.