And a side of fucking Rod Stewart's jizz.
Wait a minute. What are we drinking
water at a fucking bachelor party for, Phil?
You got to show my son your tits later.
Promise me. Promise me.
That's nice. Yeah, good.
This is great, sweetheart.
Really good.
Nice work. You're going deep on us, huh?
That's it.
What's this, sir?
That's just a little tip, you know,
if you give me a full package.
Okay. That's a $150 additional charge.
You're talking to the wrong guy.
That's a little out of my price range.
lt includes scalp treatment, reflexology.
How much is it to tickle my pickle?
To yank my crank?
To give me a ho-jo to go?
Sweetheart, l'm not asking
for a finger up the ass.
l just want you to just jerk it a little bit.
Donny, this isn't a brothel.
Then l'm completely confused
what the fuck we're doing here right now!
So, what, you're just going to
get a hand job in front of all of us?
l don't know. Am l?
l guess not!
You know, l have worked
very hard on this night, Don,
and you're being just plain rude.
-Phil, no! Phil!
-No, no. Don't do this.
Nice. That's nice.
That's good. That's good.
lt tickles.
Just fight through it, man. It's worth it.
lfyou stop, l swear l will kill you.
You know what,
if l don't see a tit in five minutes,
l'm going to strangle this motherfucker.
You should be ashamed of yourself
for fucking arranging this bullshit!
Well, l feel very relaxed,
and l think this was
a good use of a Groupon.
You fucked us, buddy!
Five more minutes till you
get to choose amongst four
artisanal house-blended
chocolates, gentlemen.
We can't let tonight end like this, boys.
We got to go out.
l'm telling you, l can't let my son have a...
My son of a gun best friend
have his bachelor party be this.
You fucking... You guys got your
face covered in leprechaun shit.
We should be getting whacked off,
all of us, as a fucking team!
Donny, l think
we've had enough excitement for one night.
Besides, it's not like you can throw
together a whole other party this late.
l could have six chicks making out
with each other on our laps in 10 minutes.
l could stay out a little later.
Bam!
We gonna get our dicks sucked.
There it is.
Unless, Mrs Ravensdale,
you want to whip them knockers out?
We'd love to see them.
All right, you know what?
You are an imbecilic,
immature, asinine, childish,
caveman-like, hairy-knuckled,
single-chromosomal,
obnoxious, uneducated, ignorant asshole
who l would like to fuck hard and long!
So, l'm going to go put a dent in that.
You guys get that green jizz off your face.
l'll be back in 20.
We're going out, boys!
Hey, this is the shit,
this place, l'm telling you.
The hottest chicks,
the best Denver omelettes.
-You have to eat one.
-All right.
-Donny!
-Yeah, this is who l was telling you about!
-What's up? Give me that.
-l'm so happy to see you.
-You look so fucking cute!
-l know, right?
And you brought a military man.
What's your name, soldier?
Chad Martin, private first class,
United States Marine Corps.
You think you can keep that dick
at attention for a couple hours?
That's an order!
Already on it.
Look at my man!
You guys, let me get in here
and introduce myself.
Hello. l'm Phil.
l'm married with four children,
and l have actually
only seen three vaginas in my entire life:
my wife's, my baby's
and my aunt's once by accident
on the back of a tandem bike.
Well, here's number four, baby!
l'm going to count that
as numbers four and five.
Champale would líke to dedícate thís
to Mr Todd Peterson.
-Yeah, baby. Yeah.
-Here you go.
Oh, hey.
Do you want any eggs?
No. l really have to watch what l eat.
No fatty foods. But thank you.
l'm Brie.
l'm Todd. Nice to meet you.
l know who you are, Han Solo.
No, you can't...
Don't worry, your secret's safe.
Who did that?
-Gerald, get in the car.
-l love you, Donny!
Yeah, l love you. Get in there.
Man, you got to give me the recipe, man.
Can't buy everything, Spirou!
Bro, but they use olive oil, not butter.
That's the big secret.
Okay, Chris, get him in there.
Be gentle, he's protecting our country.
All right, good night, guys!
Gerald, you're a sick man, buddy!
Whoa.
Hey, what... Where's everybody going?
l sent them home, guy.
l thought we could have a little
best manlgroom alone time.
But shouldn't l go with them?
'Cause Jamie's gonna get mad at me.
Easy, guy.
You're gonna have plenty of time
for her to be mad at you when you're married.
l got you a wedding gift,
and l want to give it to you alone, all right?
You got me a gift?
Of course l got you.
And l think you might dig it.
An earring.
Yeah, l know, but that's an earring
that your mom gave me,
and l thought maybe we could
keep it in the family, you know?
Just kind of keep it going,
generation to generation, actually.
Yeah, but l don't have a pierced ear, Donny.
Yeah.
No.
All right, fuck it, fuck it.
Do it, just do it.
lt's not gonna hurt, buddy.
You got a nice buzz going.
Yeah, l got it, l got it.
Hang on.
Yeah.
Liquor it up.
Fuck!
Come here. Come here.
Hang in there! Go ahead, just sit still, homie.
Yeah!
How we doing?
Oh, God.
That's it. That's the way to man up.
-That wasn't so bad.
-Let me see it.
Am l bleeding?
-l don't think so.
-No?
Does it look good?
You look like you could be playing
drums for Foreigner or some shit.
You look like a bad-ass.
-Really?
-Yeah.
'Cause it makes me feel kind of...
Dangerous.
There he is, man!
That's your personality,
like when you were seven years old,
me and Uncle Vanny used to
Iaugh our asses off from you.
Uncle Vanny, that's right.
What happened to that guy?
Dude, you know what it's time for?
To get you back together with the old gang.
Come on.
l just hope the guy will talk to me.
Phil!
Come on, you're gonna get arrested, buddy.
l shouldn't be doing this.
No, don't stop, don't stop.
All right, look.
l came here to tell you l'm sorry
about what happened
with me and your mother.
lt was an accident,
and it will never happen again.
That's all l've been waiting for
all these years, man, a simple apology.
lt's water under the bridge.
Don't sweat it. Holla.
Wait, are you Vanilla Ice?
Was Uncle Vanny Vanilla Ice this whole time?
Who did you think l was?
l don't know, a friend of my dad's
that wore a lot of parachute pants?
Anyway, you're looking great, little Han Solo.
Thank you.
-You lost some weight.
-ls this kid all right?
-You're not a little fat kid no more.
-No, no, no.
-Remember this one?
-No, no.
Yeah, we used to do this to you all the time.
-Remember, back in the day?
-Hey, nugget pocket.
-Nugget pockets.
-No, l'm not a nugget pocket.
-What's up, nugget pocket?
-No.
No, but seriously, Iceberg,
me and my boy got a little head start on you,
but you got any desire
to get wasted with us?
More than life itself.
ln fact, l might have
a little head start on you guys.
What?
-Yeah.
-lt's so illegal.
l don't want to do that in front of my kid.
Turn around for a minute. Just turn around.
Give me that fucking shit.
What?
Hey, let's get out of here.
l did not do that.
-Let's go have some fun.
-Hey!
Hey, where you think you're going,
Mr Vanilla Ice Cream?
l'm going out for the night, man.
Hell no, man! You know l don't know
how to fry no damn chicken nuggets!
lt's Todd Bridges.
Yeah, yeah, watch this.
What you talking 'bout, Willis?
You come back and say that to my face,
you fake white rapping motherfucker!
Todd, seriously, though, you look great.
How's Mr Drummond doing, huh?
Mister... Fuck you!
''Mr Drummond. Mister...''
Man, l... What you want?
Bowl of chili nuggets.
A what?
You know, that shit ain't on the menu, man!
Shit, it is. Damn it.
Fucking skate! Just fucking skate!
The Berger boys are here!
Come on, look out! Look out, now!
What the fuck?
Hey! Give me my hat back!
-Do it, do it!
-Give it back!
Hey, it's a fucking lovely night, ain't it?
Oh, my God!
You fucking assholes!
Go, go!
What the... Go!
Go, go, go!
What the fuck? Get out of here!
Holy shit!
You know, they seem like fun guys.
We're all gonna dive! Let's go!
What are you doing?
Oh, my God!
l didn't... l didn't spill my beer!
l fucking love it.
-Fuck!
-You fucking hard-ons!
''You fucking hard-ons.''
Fucking...
-What are you doing?
-No, no, no, no!
-You don't fucking do that, you fucking idiot!
-Yeah!
Look at this, fuck face. Look at this.
What the fuck?
Come on.
-You fucking guy. l say, take it.
-l can't.
-Just go, go, go, go, go.
-No, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait. Stop, stop, stop.
l changed my mind. l'm scared.
l don't want to do it.
-Oh, man.
-l can't do it.
You're rubbing your underwear.
What is that? Why are you doing that?
l suppose l'm the reason.
Yeah. Yeah. Remember in first grade
when you were supposed
to pick me up after school,
you left me waiting for five hours?
l had detention myself, guy.
What the fuck was l supposed to do?
-Yeah, well, l shit in my pants.
-All right.
-Then l had to walk all the way home alone.
With shit in my pants.
Dude, l promise you,
l'll never forget you again.
l swear to God.
Throw the fucking things away.
-Don't fuck with me.
-Throw them away.
Throw them away. Throw them away.
Get rid of the fucking underwear,
you don't need that.
You're better than that, guy.
Okay, fuck it. Okay, fuck it.
Squeeze it out and fucking... Yeah.
You're a good kid.
Come on, fucking hit this thing
and let's get it rocking.
-All right. All right?
-Here we go.
-Come on. Push, push. l got you.
-Okay.
-l'm not good at it.
-All right.
lt's balance, it's just balance.
You got this, kid. You're an athlete.
You got it. No, it's in you, buddy.
-Straight.
-l don't know how.
l got you. l ain't gonna let you fall.
-Don't let me go.
-l won't let you fall.
-Don't let go.
-All right, l'm still with you.
-Okay.
-l'm still with you.
Let's pick up some speed, though.
l'm with you, guy.
l'm with you. l'm with you.
-l'm not letting go.
-Don't let me go.
l'm not letting go. l'm with you, my boy.
-Wait...
-l'm with you, my boy!
-Yeah, that's all you!
-l'm doing it!
-Yeah! Yeah, yeah, baby!
Oh, my God!
Are you...
Kid, are you...
Are you all right, buddy?
Sorry.
-Dude, l'm trying to make love to my wife!
-What the fuck?
-No!
-Fucking naked people.
l'm gonna fucking kill you!
Oh, my God, they're chasing me!
What the fuck? Get off him!
Go!
-Oh, my God! Look out!
-Go!
Keep going, guy!
Donny!
-Yeah!
-You're the best.
-You are, Jay.
-Good luck!
l like your fucking hairdo!
Good luck with the taxi business!
-Love that guy.
-Classic. Classic.
Classic.
lt's a classic night.
No way! Party's not over!
Come on!
Dude, Uncle Vanny's fucked up.
l love you, son.
l do.
l've always loved you, all right?
Sorry to spring that on you like that.
lt's all right.
lt's cool, Donny. That's nice, thank you.
Hansie, Hansie.
Why don't you not call me
''Donny'' when no one's around.
You can call me ''Dad.''
Yeah, l know, l know.
lt's...
l don't know if l'm ready for that, Donny.
-You know?
-Yeah, yeah.
No prob.
Sorry.
Sorry if you fucking don't like me.
l probably would've fucked my teacher, too.
Yeah.
But...
So, what time are we gonna
go to the prison tomorrow?
Wait, you'll go to the prison?
Yeah, l'll go.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
That's... They cancelled that.
l talked to the warden, and he says
that your mother was just pulling our leg.
She's only got the chicken pox.
-What?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah, l know.
She said she was dying because
they give you better food
if you're wicked sick like that,
like Beefaroni or microwave pizza
or some shit, so...
That just made me hungry.
Well, check your pockets.
A treasure!
Come on, eat it.
-No, it's nasty.
-Come on, l'm telling you.
Fucking Todd Bridges
worked hard on that thing.
Yeah. You like that.
Pretty good.
Look at me, l'm a fountain!
Throw a penny in here!
Make a wish, motherfucker!
What the...
Grandma D, what's going on?
What are you doing here?
Well, you've had the fantasy,
so now it's time that you try the real thing.
No, no, no, l can't do that.
l'm sorry.
l appreciate the offer.
No, no, no, don't.
l can't. Don't you... l shouldn't.
Oh, God.
You got the old-timey bathing suit on.
Okay, l'm in.
l'm going to ride you like a Model T.
Yeah.
Jamie.
You're wearing your dress again.
You look beautiful.
l want you so bad.
Be nice to me.
Make me feel good.
All right, all right.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Oh, my God!
Help me!
What happened?
Are you okay?
Do l sound okay?
You puked all over my wedding dress!
Prepare to get fucked up, motherfuckers!
Sorry, l heard you scream.
l thought Jamie was getting murdered,
so l was gonna fucking
smack someone around.
-What happened?
-l don't know!
l just found my wedding dress
covered in barf!
And something else, something sticky.
lt's jizz.
You puked on my dress and then fucked it!
You're a madman.
No, no, no, no. No.
-Sweetheart, it wasn't my boy.
-You shut up.
Donny, just shut up!
Who wants a piece ofthis, huh?
-Who wants a piece?
-Whoa, no, no, no!
lt's okay, buddy.
Todd just fucked the dress.
lt's under control.
What is Vanilla Ice doing in our room?
He's my other best friend.
Yeah. And a wicked good rapper.
Give it up for him. Come on, now.
-Let's give it up.
-My boy.
l don't know what's going on here,
but l don't have time to deal with this, so...
Okay, this is what's gonna happen.
l'm gonna go take a shower.
l'm gonna go to Pilates.
You're gonna take that dress
to the dry cleaners!
And then we're gonna have
rehearsal dinner tonight,
and you're gonna be
the normal Todd from three days ago, right?
And you can start by taking out
that stupid Duran Duran earring!
l was thinking it's more Foreigner.
No? No, no,
Duran Duran's a good call, though.
Guess l'm gonna go
finish up with Grandma Delores.
-Yeah.
-ls that all right?
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
-Have fun, buddy. Have fun.
Not too much, though. Don't hurt her.
No, no. l get it right and keep it tight.
Okay.
Look, l need a couple hours to fix this.
Hey, we've all been in that situation,
and you'll be fine, kid.
l'll whip up some pancakes
for everyone else, all right?
-All right.
-l love it.
You jizzed on a mannequin.
Respect it.
But you were only 13.
She took advantage of you.
No, all right.
That's what the law says, Su-Jin,
but l don't know...
We were kind of like soul mates.
You know, there was...
There was a connection there.
l never had it with anyone else.
l'm getting a call. l'm sorry, guys.
Do not touch these plates. l'm cleaning them.
Okay, Su-Jin?
Go for Donny B.
Wassup!
Hey, big man. What's going on?
How'd it go with the lady?
You patch things up?
Yeah, pretty much. It was amazing.
The dry cleaner said they've
definitely seen that combo of fluid before.
You see? Yeah, those things
go together like gin and tonic.
Hey, lísten, whíle I got you,
l left you a little
best man gift on your dresser.
l think you'll get a kick out of it.
You did not. Oh, my God.
My whole body, like,
got a shocked feeling over that.
Buddy, no one gets me a gift.
-Where are you, anyways?
-l'm in the car.
l decided to go see Mom after all.
You did what?
Oh, my God. Dukes of Hazzard!
Hansie.
Donny, what are you doing here?
We got to get out of here now.
What? What are you talking about?
lt's your wedding weekend, dude.
You come here after the wedding.
You show your mother your new ring.
That would make her happy.
Wait, are you nervous to see her?
Hansie, can we just blow this place off
and have a beer, please? l'm begging you.
Look. Is that her?
Oh, my God.
There you are.
My little Hansie, you're all grown up.
Hi, Mom.
l didn't know if l'd ever see you again.
l know. l'm sorry l stopped visiting.
lt just got too hard.
No, l totally understand.
Wow.
You still have my eyes.
ls that the earring
that l gave you after the Loverboy concert?
Yes, it is, Miss McGarricle.
You know, l think about you every day.
Fuck, l love you so much, Miss McGarricle.
l never stopped.
l love you, too.
Do you remember...
Oh, God, here we go.
...all the nasty things
that l taught you, Donny?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Of course l do, Miss McGarricle.
Are you still my dirty boy?
Yeah, l'm the dirtiest boy
you'll ever know, Miss McGarricle.
Donny.
Oh, fuck, yeah.
l'm hard right now. l'm hard.
Okay. Yeah, l'm hating that, so...
But it is really good to see you, Mom. l...
lt's good to see you, too, baby.
Can you describe
what you're feeling right now, Han?
TV's Randall Morgan?
What are you doing here?
Must be quite emotional
for you to be face-to-face
with the woman
who molested your father, isn't it?
-What is going on right now?
-Who is this dude?
Listen, before you get mad at me...
This is why you came to see me?
For some reality TV ambush?
-No.
-How much they paying you, Donny?
Nothing, l swear to God. l'm not getting...
Fifty thousand dollars
to deliver you to this prison.
All right, it was 50 grand, but l'm not...
l'm not...
l'm not going to do it. l swear to God.
l'm not... l would never take his money.
Donny Berger, what have you done?
Hansie, dude, it's me.
lt's the guy from last night.
We had fun. Don't fuck it.
l'm telling you, this is...
This is something that can be fixed.
-You're unreal.
-Hansie.
What...
You go after him, Donny,
and you take care of our son.
-Hansie.
-Come on, he is pissed. Fuck!
-Take care of our baby, Donny!
-Hansie!
Hansie, please, let me explain to you...
l can't believe l let you
back into my life again.
Guy, guy, just come on. Listen to me.
l owe the IRS a lot of money.
-Of course you do.
-l know, l know. l'm a fuck-up.
But if l don't give them 43 G's by Tuesday,
l'm going to prison.
Wait, so you're telling me,
if l give you 43 grand,
you don't have to go to jail?
l will pay you back, l swear to God.
Would you loan me the money?
No! Fuck you!
-Get your shit out of my boss's house!
-Okay!
No! Don't do that.
That's my boy there.
No.
l think he just shit his pants.
Tell me you got that on camera.
You made me throw out my extra underwear!
l'm sorry. l didn't know
you were going to shit yourself again.
That was awesome.
Donny, couldn't have gone any better.
Loved it.
You know what l need from you, Todd,
is l need you
-to sign the release form right...
-Fuck you!
Get away from me!
Get those cameras off me!
l hate you, Dad.
Hansie!
l can't pay you a dime
unless l got a release form.
Fuck.
Did l get any shit on me?
Let me off here. Let me off.
Let me get off. l'll fucking run up.
Keep it running.
l got to pick my shit up.
You're so adorable.
No, l know, but l told you
not to call me on this line.
What if Todd picks up?
No, no, no, l want to.
No, Steve.
Todd doesn't know anything.
l don't care if he finds out after the wedding.
There's nothing he can do
about it then anyway.
You're so sweet.
Steve, huh?
Well, Steve Spirou, l'm going to fuck you up.
l'm going to fuck you up!
Well, l got some great news.
l've made my decision
on who my new partner is.
Phil!
Phil, l knew you could do it.
Look at Phil's face.
l'm just busting your balls, Phil.
No, l'd never pick you.
Oh, no.
lt's you, Todd. Partners.
Partner.
Oh, my gosh.
lt's going to be a lot more hours
and a lot more responsibility.
You know that, right?
And a lot more money!
-Somebody's going shopping!
-Yeah!
l thought he left.
Yeah, that's what you wish, Steve.
l need to talk to you, homeboy. Yeah.
Hey, Jamie.
Listen. Listen.
Dude, this is not about you and me, all right?
You're not marrying the right girl.
She is cheating on you.
You are unbelievable.
Can't you just let it go?
This is my last chance to be normal.
Are you determined to ruin my life?
-Honey, what's going on?
-Nothing.
Don't ''honey'' him,
you little snake in the grass.
l heard your phone call.
''Steve, why'd you call on this line?
''Todd could have picked up.''
That's right, sonny boy.
Your wife-to-be's fucking your boss.
Right there.
Fuck you, buddy.
You are an idiot!
ls that right, sweetheart?
-Yes, it is.
-Yeah, yeah. Why?
l was on the phone with Steve.
Steve Goldstein,
the Boston Herald wedding reporter.
Yeah, he's doing a piece on
the most beautiful places to get married,
and l didn't want Todd to know
because he doesn't like being in the paper.
So, l am sorry
that l wanted everyone in the world
to know l married the perfect guy.
Honey, do you think you can forgive me
for keeping such a big secret from you?
Okay, due to this newfound evidence,
the conclusion might be that l'm an asshole.
Bye.
Fine.
Have a good wedding.
l'll leave with pride.
l'm a good person.
Bye! l'll see you tomorrow!
Wow, what a stressful day, huh?
-Can't wait to get back to the beach house.
-Thank you.
-Bye.
-Just the two of us, you know?
No, honey.
l'm staying in the city tonight, remember?
-What? No.
-Yeah, the bride and groom,
they're supposed to sleep separate
night before the wedding.
So see you tomorrow, big guy.
l'm going to drop Jamie
at the Fairmont Copley.
Mom and Dad,
you guys got the hedgehog. Okay!
-Love you.
-Watch the door.
-Love you. Okay.
-Sleep well.
Wait, but don't they not have a car?
All right, Donny, go.
There's your chance. Go.
l ain't got no more chances, buddy.
The kid hates my guts.
Right? 'Cause you guys don't have a car.
l'm not talking about him, Donny.
-Wake up, man.
-What?
Jamie's the gatekeeper for your son.
-Yeah?
-Win her over, then she'll convince Han
to give you another chance. Boom!
How am l ever going to get her trust?
She freaking hates me.
Donny, you want to know
what all women love?
lce cream.
Hi. l'm Todd Peterson.
No, you're not. You're Donny Berger.
You fucked your teacher
in the seventh grade.
Hi. l'm Todd Peterson.
Hi, Mr Peterson. What can l do for you?
What room was my fiancée in again?
Let me check. 641.
You're a fucking stud.
Hey, when the legendary
Donny Berger comes in here
using a fake name, you go with it!
All right, l will.
641. 641.
All right, come on, sweetheart.
Oh, yeah!
What, did Todd come out here?
You're half the size of Todd,
but you use it so much better!
l guess not.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God.
Fucking shit!
Fucking shit.
Yeah. Okay.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Okay.
Yeah!
You do not deserve these treats.
Are you finished, sweetheart?
Oh, my God.
Your fiancé's at home, you know.
This really gets me upset.
You know why?
'Cause he's too good for you.
He is.
And you're sitting here gallivanting with...
l think l know who.
Don't l, Mr Steve Goldstein?
Wait. Are you...
What am l seeing?
No... It...
With each other?
Am l... This is...
ls he your stepbrother at least
or adopted or something?
No reply.
So it's real.
Oh, my God.
Donny, Donny, you don't...
You don't understand what's going on here.
l don't think Charlie Sheen
would understand what's going on here.
Look, l love Todd,
and we're going to get married,
and we're going to have a great life together.
And yes, l've had sex with Chad
from time to time.
lt's what good-looking people do.
They have sex with
other good-looking people.
You know? Just so happens that
this one particular good-looking person
is my little brother.
Okay.
lt's all making sense to me now.
l know that sounded bad, but, Donny,
this was going to be the last time.
l would never carry on
with a married woman.
l've got better morals than that, Donny.
Chad, adultery is bad,
but incest is fucked up!
Please don't let him tell Mommy
about our secret tickle time.
''Secret tickle time''?
You got a name for it?
And with a United States
military man, no less.
You are a disgrace to that uniform!
No, he's not a Marine.
He buys those uniforms on eBay
so Dad doesn't find out
he's a modern jazz dancer.
What?
That's possibly worse than the incest thing.
This is an abomination. l'm telling Todd.
-No, he won't believe you.
-Yeah, he will.
No, he bought that Steve Goldstein story.
Come on, you think he got
that partnership on his own?
With that ''beep boop beep'' shit?
No, l gave him a boost.
How many people have you fucked?
Well, maybe he'll believe this.
Nice. Save.
You two have fun together.
Sickies.
All right, how much?
l'm going to be a very rich woman.
l can write you a big fat cheque.
What's it going to take for this to go away?
Todd has to pop a Xanax
when he loses a contact lens.
What do you think he's going to do
when he finds out about this?
Todd's happy.
You really want to take that away?
Hey, buddy.
l got something to tell you, and...
l'm not expecting you to believe this, but...
l got the money.
That's great, Donny.
Your son came through for you, didn't he?
Yeah. His fiancée gave me $50,OOO
to keep quiet about her
having sex with her brother.
Yeah, l've been there.
We've all been there.
She said it was her last time, so...
Maybe thíngs wíll work out.
Then how come l feel like shit right now?
Yeah, it's kind of a moral thicket.
But the good news ís
you stay out of the slammer, ríght, Donny?
Donny?
''Go do something.''
l don't know, Mr Mitty.
l don't know if l can fucking handle it.
''Be a good person.''
Donny?
-No, no, don't hit me.
-No, no.
Just give me a moment, please, Todd.
Just a moment. Relax.
You know, after praying with the monsignor,
l realise that l committed the sin
of prideful anger in the church,
and l hope that you'll accept my apology
and allow me the honour
of being a part ofthis joyous day.
Well, what about Father Shakalu?
Stupid bird.
Come on, fly!
Well, he's cool.
Great. Sounds good.
By the way, Todd,
was it you that hit me in the head
with the bottle?
No.
Well, then, who, then?
lt was Chad.
lnteresting.
Two, three, four.
Fosse, and Fosse,
-and Fosse.
-lnteresting.
Yo! Donny Berger! All right!
l'd sign something for you, buddy,
but l got no time right now.
lce!
lce, you in there, buddy? l need you!
You still got the 5.O?
What does that mean? Is that a yes or no?
l don't understand the pose.
Yeah? Let's go, let's go!
Go, baby, go!
No!
Look at this fucking guy!
Man!
No, no, no, no, no! We're stuck! We're stuck!
To hell with the 5.O. Let's run for it, man.
-But we need great tunes!
-Come on, let's get them!
Right here, l got a Walkman.
-The Walkman!
-Yeah, baby.
Let's go!
-Damn it, man!
-Come on! Let's go!
Oh, my God!
Hey!
You forgot to pay!
So, Jamie, do you promise
to provide Todd here
with unending empathy,
encouragement and honesty,
till death do you part?
l do.
Hey, Donny. Come on!
What are you doing, guy?
You jumped?
There was a door right here!
Come on, we got to get there!
And you, Todd, do you promise to love,
honour and protect this special lady
for the rest of your life?
Don't answer that question!
Oh, shit.
We ran well over a mile.
l object to these two getting married.
No, we're past that part already.
What are my options, then?
How about leaving?
You shut the hell up, you satanic hose-bag!
Hey!
Gerald! l'm sorry it sounded so harsh,
but you'll understand
why l said that in a few minutes.
There ain't gonna be a few minutes,
-you goddamn son of a bitch!
-Calm down!
Calm down!
Let the boy talk.
l can't let you marry this chick.
l can't believe you're doing this.
Listen to me, buddy.
You don't love this girl.
l'm telling you. l had love, it's different.
lt's a different feeling.
Love is like...
lt just leads you to a special connection.
lt's full of, like, feelings of awesomeness.
And the feelings you...
That wrap around you.
lt's deep in your stomach.
lt's in your head.
It's in your fucking nut sack.
lt's in your dick when it gets hard.
There's still love at the tip.
And it fucking sprinkles out
like morning dew
shooting all over the grass.
Okay, l've had just about enough of this.
Phil, sit down before l tell your wife
what you did at the strip club.
Okay.
Son, l'm sorry, l just...
l can't let you marry this skank.
''Son?''
-Your son?
-Son?
What is he talking about?
Honey? You can tell me.
l'll forgive you.
That's what love's about, right? Forgiveness.
All right, fine.
Donny's not my best friend.
He's my father.
Oh, my...
My parents didn't die in an explosion.
l lied because l'm the product of
an inappropriate
teacher-student relationship.
Teacher-student relationship?
Do you know how gross that sounds?
You're disgusting!
Are you fucking kidding me right now?
She can still cancel that cheque, Donny!
Chad.
Cancel what cheque?
l don't...
She gave me 50 grand
to keep my mouth shut.
Fifty grand? Jamie.
Yeah, it was... l was gonna hold on to it,
you know, to get me out ofjail, but...
Yeah, yeah. That's what l think of that.
That's how much l hate this fucking whore.
Wait. Keep your mouth shut about what?
Todd, don't listen to him.
He's a liar and he's crazy!
Father McNally, please continue.
l promise to do
all that shit you mentioned
and so does Todd, right?
Wait, what is going on?
Tell him.
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't tell him, don't tell him.
You tell him or l'll tell everybody here.
It's up to you.
Come on.
Okay. Well, that's not that bad.
What? You didn't tell him,
you fucking lying piece of shit!
Get on it now or l'll fucking crush you!
No.
Jame, you can tell me.
l mean, how bad could it be?
What?
Okay, she told him.
You fuck your brother?
Oh, my God!
Fucking white people.
l'm not looking so bad now, am l, Dad?
l'm out of here.
Mom, she started all this.
l didn't want to. l'm still your little soldier, l...
-Fuck!
-Take that uniform off.
You're insulting us all.
No, no, no. Don't you see?
lt's gonna be even better now.
You're a mess, l'm a mess.
Come on. Doc Shakalu, get your ass up here!
l got to be part ofthis shit?
Todd?
Please.
Come on, baby. Come on, Todd, let's do this.
Yeah, yeah.
No! Let's not do this.
Okay?
And for the record,
my name's not Todd Peterson.
lt's Han Solo.
Named after the man who made
the Kessel Run in less than 12 parsecs.
And l am a Berger, like my father before me.
Also, l want to tell everyone here
that l've got a pretty huge
New Kids on the Block tattoo on my back.
The heads are warped,
but fuck you guys, it's funny.
lt is fucking hilarious.
And Steve?
Nothing personal, man, but l quit!
No, no. Come on, Todd, don't be like that.
We quit, too.
Fuck you!
Good call, Han Solo,
'cause your fiancée banged him, too.
What?
l didn't know
about the brother thing, though.
l am as sickened as you, believe me.
You know what? It's all right, Steve.
'Cause guess what?
Donny and Vanilla Ice fucked your mom!
Vanilla Ice banged Grandma?
That's fucking awesome!
Donny, look out!
Word to your mother, brotherfucker!
l'm sorry.
l know l'm not supposed to hit a chick,
but l got to tell you, it felt good.
l mean, l wouldn't do it again,
but with this psycho, you know,
it was warranted.
Donny! l'm gonna kill you!
At ease, bitch.
Dude! That's it! Nice!
Hang on, though. Hang on.
No, don't hurt me.
Even Steven.
Father, take off the collar.
That's right. You're not meant for this.
-Well...
-Yeah.
Nicely done.
All right, come on.
Let's get out of here, Dad.
Did you hear that? Did you hear that?
My son called me ''Dad!''
He called me ''Dad!''
That's right!
The Berger boys are back, bitches!
Wassup?
Wassup...
Shut up.
His boss and her brother?
lt sounds like a Rodney Dangerfield joke,
but it actually happened to my boy here!
Now we got to find Han Solo
one ofthem new girls.
One that don't care about
all that money he make.
-No, no.
-Yeah, like a girl version
-of Todd Bridges would be perfect.
-That's right!
Female version of me. That's right.
Well, you know, l actually might be
doing okay in that department, so...
What's that?
What the fuck... What the heck?
Todd and Brie, sitting in a tree.
l have balls down to my knee!
-What?
-He said it! Yeah!
-Donny!
-Yeah, buddy?
You're my best friend. l'm gonna miss you.
l know, l know.
But there's good news.
You know what,
Miss McGarricle gets out in three years,
so the timing's kind of perfect
for us to start our lives together.
Dad, let me just give you the money.
No. No. l'm not gonna do that.
lt's time for Donny Berger
to take responsibility for his screw-ups.
l made my bed, now l got to lie in it.
Donny! Donny! Are you watching?
Turn on the TV! Turn it on!
There he ís, the fat guy we've been
talkíng about all day, Tubby Tuke,
actually gaíníng on the Ethíopíans
here ín the fínal stretch.
ls this the fat guy l put the money on?
Twenty bucks at 8,OOO-to-1 .
-A hundred and sixty grand?
Come on, you fat shit, move it!
Go, Tubby! Go, Tubby!
Keep running! Keep running!
Pass those Ethiopians!
Pass them skinny fucking Ethiopians!
This defies every law of science,
but it's happening!
Get the fuck up!
He's up! He's up! He's up!
-That'll replenish him! That'll replenish him!
-No!
Lísten to the roar of that crowd.
Fat guy! Fat guy!
Can he possíbly wín ít?
He's gonna do it!
Tubby Tuke has won!
Tubby Tuke wíns! Tubby Tuke wíns!