[blows]
[alarm clock beeping]
[Benny gasps] Ugh...
Huh?
Ugh... [speaking Minionese]
[snores]
MINIONS: Happy birthday!
[barks]
[grunts] No, no, no!
[gasps]
[all cheering]
[speaking Minionese]
- [speaking Minionese]
- [snarls]
[grunting]
[groans] Huh?
[screaming]
Blegh!
[balloon squeaks, deflates]
[cheering continues]
[screams]
[Benny grunting]
Ouch!
- Huh?
- [chuckles]
La-la-la! [giggles]
[gasps]
Oh, no! [blowing]
[alarm clock beeping]
[gasps] Again?
[gasps]
[speaking Minionese]
Another birthday?
MINIONS: Happy birthday!
- [barks]
- Huh?
[speaking Minionese]
[stammering] No! No, no, no!
[grunts]
No, no, no, no! [gasps]
Blegh!
[balloon squeaks, deflates]
- [balloon Minion screaming]
- Whoa! [yelps]
[screams]
No, no!
[Benny grunting]
[screams]
[groans]
[alarm clock beeping]
[Benny yelps]
No! [quivering]
MINIONS: Happy birthday!
- [barks]
- [gasps, screams]
[snarls]
[screams] No!
[screams]
[alarm clock beeping]
- [grunts]
- [screaming]
[screams]
- [screams]
[grunts] Oh! [chuckles]
[screams]
Ow!
[speaks Minionese, grunts]
- [barks]
- [screams]
[alarm clock beeping]
[screams]
- [alarm clock beeping]
- [groans]
[screaming]
[sighs]
[speaking Minionese]
Huh?
Oh! [speaks Minionese]
[grunts] Okay.
- [Benny grunts]
- [Minions] Happy Bir...
[grunts]
[balloon squeaks, deflates]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[grunts]
[cheering]
[chuckles] La-la-la!
[blows]
Ha-ha-hallelujah!
Eh, Benny, eh?
[giggles]
- [alarm clock beeping]
- [Benny] No. No, no! [sobbing]
[grunting, groaning]
Oh? [stammering]
[laughs]
[speaking Minionese]
[all cheering]
["Walking on Sunshine" by
Katrina and the Waves playing]
- [grunting]
- Oh...
- [laughs]
- Oh, oh...
[8-bit music playing on TV]
Eh, eh? [speaks Minionese]
Eh... [exclaims]
- [Bob speaking Minionese]
- Aah!
Bob! [speaking Minionese]
- Ooh!
- [groans]
Aah! No!
[both grunting]
[laughing]
- [speaking Minionese]
- [growls]
[speaking Minionese]
[gasps] Aah! Oh, no!
Aah! [speaks Minionese] Oh.
Huh? [chortles]
Uh... [gasps]
Oh, oh... Le-le-le...
le poystick!
[chuckles]
[controller warbles]
- [grunts, mutters]
- Hey...
ANNOUNCER:
Player o...
- Uh...
- [short chuckle]
ANNOUNCER:
Player one.
- Ready.
- [exclaiming]
- [whimpers]
- [chuckles]
- [laughing]
- [8-bit music playing]
Aah! Oh!
No, no, no, no, no, no...
- Oh... Aah!
- [muffled shouting]
Whoa, ho-ho-ho.
Bingo!
[laughing]
[whimpering]
[groans]
[grunting]
- Hey.
- [laughs]
Ooh!
- [growls]
- [speaks Minionese]
- [barking]
- [muttering frantically]
Ay, hop.
[screams]
[yelps]
- Ow. Ow. Ow.
- [birds chirping]
[yells]
[triumphant music plays]
- Aah! Uh-oh.
- [groaning]
Bikini!
Bikini?
- Huh? [grunts]
- [Kevin muttering nervously]
You little...
Whoa-ho-ho!
- [Kevin gibbering nervously]
- [others grunting]
- [growls]
- Aah!
[muttering]
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
- MAN: Hey, what"s he doing?
- [Kevin exclaims]
MAN:
The flag!
[triumphant music plays]
Ah!
[gasps]
[growls]
No, no, no, no, no.
[shouting]
- MAN: Oh, we"re gonna get him!
- [screams]
[panting]
[shouts]
[laughs]
Eh?
Uh... uh, S-Stuart, no, no, no.
Eh...
[laughs]
[Kevin screams]
MAN:
Hey, he stole the doughnuts!
Get back here, you punk!
[Stuart chuckles]
[Kevin whimpering]
- [engine revs]
- [gasps]
- [engine idling]
- [indistinct conversation]
!¡Ay-ay-ay, caramba!
[sirens wailing]
- OFFICER: Come here.
- [Kevin shouting]
[screams]
Police! Put the doughnuts down!
Oh, thank you.
[screaming]
[gasps]
Voilà.
Wow.
Eh, eh, eh.
[puzzled grunt]
[growls]
[Kevin screaming]
[both scream]
Uh...
[chuckles]
Ke-Ke-Kevin.
ANNOUNCER:
Player two, ready.
Uh-oh.
[speaking Minionese]
[gasps, whimpers]
[screams]
No, no, no.
[gibbering frantically]
[groans]
Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow.
Ow!
[yelps]
[strains]
No, n-n-n-n-n-no.
- [grunts]
- [laughs]
Eh, eh...
[groaning]
[speaks Minionese]
[choppy yelling]
[laughs]
[exclaims]
[grunts]
[panting, munching]
[screams]
[warbles]
[laughter]
Yeah!
[cheering]
[laughter]