My name is Chris Renaud, and to my side
is Pierre Coffin, the foreign guy.
We are the directors of Despicable Me.
-Yeah, this was one of those things that...
-Hello! Hello!
Hey, look! Hey! Here are Tim and Bob.
They're coming to join us. Come on in, guys.
Hey, guys!
Pierre has this French thing
about kissing all the actors.
Yeah, well, it's cultural.
There's nothing wrong with that, right? No?
Hey, pull up a chair, guys.
There's only one left.
-Well, just share it.
-Thank you.
Come on, Bob, share the seat, will you?
So, guys, we wanted to
talk about your acting methods.
No, no, acting methods.
Listen, listen, acting methods! Methods!
Come on, Bob, leave him some room,
will you?
What did he say?
He said that the minions took a lot of
inspiration from Twinkies, Tylenol capsules,
-and tennis balls, which is weird.
-Sure.
Yeah, I don't think these guys have methods.
He's just saying
every yellow thing he knows.
That's true, he is.
He's just identifying things by color.
You don't understand me, right? You do?
I don't think he does.
I think he says he does, but he doesn't.
Okay.
One nice thing you can see here,
particularly this character and his son,
were some of the character designs
of Carter Goodrich
as realized by the modeling team in France,
and really sort of captured the quality
of his illustrations and his designs.
-Goodrich is the designer...
-American?
He's a character designer.
He obviously worked on
some of the Pixar films, notably Ratatouille,
and he brought his really distinct approach
to human characters to this film,
which we were very excited about.
Which kind of broke, actually,
with all the, I would say, regular CG style
-that there is out there.
-Yes.
And we tried, in every aspect of the design,
to just come up with some unique solutions.
So we've got a 3-D moment coming up here.
Which lasted one second
at the beginning of the movie.
Yes, but we liked it so much,
we kept adding time, actually,
‘cause it was so much fun
watching this kid enjoy his plane.
Oh, boy. There he goes.
-I love that joke.
-Yes.
This was one of our first big effect moments,
early effect moments,
with the deflating pyramid,
figuring out that,
and also the dust and sand that comes up,
So the effects team
was able to do a great job
with creating a believable effect there.
Try to protect their beloved landmarks.
-That's the French touch.
-We should probably mention,
this film was entirely animated
in France, in Paris, in fact,
so there's a lot
of little design sensibility animation
that is really very distinct and
unique to France and Paris, I would say.
And here's the new...
Well the main character of the movie.
Yes.
Here is Gru, and, you know,
we went through several designs
to land on this particular character,
sort of wanting somebody who was
appealing, but also looked like a villain.
And we landed on some
distinct characteristics, notably his scarf,
which we originally were talking about
dedicating an animator,
-remember, to just doing that scarf.
-Yeah.
But we were able to
work out a simpler solution,
so we could have the scarf
through most of the movie.
Poor kid.
So, obviously,
from a story point of view here,
we wanted to show
that Gru was the type of character
who was maybe not so nice to children,
and that was a clear way to establish it,
particularly as he moves through the movie
and his attitude changes.
It was actually interesting, also, finding all
the sorts of physicality this guy could have.
Our inspirations were
a John Cleese, Mr. Bean type of guy.
-Peter Sellers.
The things we talked about was just trying
to show that he had joy in his villainy,
like, just his laugh
when he shoots the freeze ray,
or drinking his coffee while his giant tank
pushes other cars off the road.
Always that he enjoyed being bad.
He sort of delighted in it.
There's his...
We were looking for
what Gru's house would look like,
and we took the idea of a standard suburb,
and then Gru's house
was kind of a similar shape,
but was really a black spot on the world.
He'd taken his house,
made it bigger, and painted it entirely black,
so that's kind of where we...
That car that Gru was driving
was one of our early designs
from Eric Guillon, the art director,
but also one
of our chief concept developers, visually,
and it really became
a touchstone image for us
and sort of defined Gru,
with his Cold War-era machinery.
This is some other things
that Eric had done...
There's Kyle. Get to that in a second.
With the interior of Gru's house,
it took us a while to land
what Gru's house would look like inside.
We wanted to have a lot of...
There's a lot of Charles Addams design cues.
The paintings on the wall, the disasters,
the suits of armor, the taxidermy.
Remember how the design
used to be very clogged?
-Yes.
-And it became almost... Not Zen-ish,
but gained in clarification,
Just because we couldn't find
the character in there anymore.
Yeah, and I think we ended up
putting things back in
to get the little bit of the clutter,
the neat bric-a-brac
that Gru has in his house.
So we did a journey with
a little too much stuff, not enough stuff,
and then we found a nice balance.
In terms of designs also, the girls were
actually interesting, in terms of process,
just because these girls
that you see in the movie today
weren't designed that way
at the beginning at all. They were...
I don't know if they were more realistic,
but they certainly were a design
that went into 3-D...
In CG, sorry, in a very bad way.
Either our translation of it or just their
design initially didn't work out so well,
-S0 we went back to the drawing board and...
-And we made them more stylized.
Some of our inspirations
were the Peanuts characters,
even the designs of some of The Simpsons
characters, how they're very graphic,
and we started thinking about those ideas
as we developed the girls,
and just making them more graphic
and more stylized.
So, here's Gru making his way.
We wanted that kind of Get Smart,
contraption-converting idea,
so here is where we first see his elevator
down to his underground lab,
where Dr Nefario works,
who we just met in the previous scene.
It feels a very complicated way
just to get down there.
It does! And we actually had all kinds
of problems making it work, remember?
It was, like, the door opens one way,
then it opens another way.
Couldn't he just take an elevator
down there?
Sliding down that pole there,
and then that's it.
In the end, it works out all right.
So here's a first glimpse of Gru's minions,
which started as typical-type henchmen
or stormtroopers,
and then we came upon the idea
of making them more like drones,
and that they're cloned little mole people
that are truly just innumerable.
There are so many of them.
I don't know if that's a word, "innumerable,"
but there's just a ton of them,
and they all look the same.
There's basically six different body shapes,
I think, in here, that we use throughout,
but it creates a faceless army of thousands.
I think we have three body shapes
and six different haircuts.
And eye configuration.
So, yeah, some have one eye,
some have two.
And so, yeah, here they're gathering,
and this is the scene where we get
the first glimpse at Gru's master plan
to steal the moon.
All right! Simmer down.
One of the things that we see also here,
this is one of the earlier scenes
we recorded with Steve Carell,
is really the accent that Steve developed
through the course of creating the film
and the character,
and in his own words, "Somewhere between
Bela Lugosi and Ricardo Montalban."
Sort of an accent
from everywhere and nowhere,
obviously with a European influence.
And this was one of the first scenes
where he started playing with the dialogue
and creating these Gru-isms.
Basically where he would turn a phrase,
a catchphrase,
and he would mix up the cadence
or sort of put an "S" on the end of a word
and would make it his own,
as he was going through the character.
I think it's very gutsy, too,
at least from the production side of things,
to take very famous actors
and not necessarily recognize their voices.
Even Jason Segel and...
-Yeah.
-Miss Hattie.
Kristen Wiig and Julie Andrews
really playing against type.
I mean, we tried to...
Clearly, when Steve set the bar here,
we talked to the other actors
about creating characters
versus just using their ordinary voice,
and everybody
was really enthusiastic about that,
and I think really created a unique character,
which was, I think, a lot of fun to animate,
but also to create a story around.
-Russell Brand as Dr Nefario.
-Yeah, he's great.
Could you check just a little bit...
I'm asking you the questions here.
Our mediator, Pierre Coffin.
No, it's really interesting, just because
I had preconceived ideas about...
Okay, a written script has these,
well, little gems of dialogues in there.
How much direction do you give actors?
Do they have liberty to go beyond the text
and try to find something else?
Do any of the changes they provide
influence a rewriting of some sort?
They do. I think it's usually within the script,
and it sort of depends on the scene.
We'll see Sleepy Kittens later,
which was a scene
that was beautifully written on the page,
and there's actually not much adlibbing
in there.
And then some scenes... I think this one,
in some ways, had more than others,
‘cause it was one of the early scenes,
and I think one of the first that we recorded,
but also one of the first
that we wrote and storyboarded,
or we didn't write, but Cinco and Ken wrote.
So the actor had an opportunity here
to contribute in a bigger way,
‘cause it was so early in the process.
I think this scene in particular
was where we landed some of those,
like I said, Gru-isms,
where he took the dialogue
and made it his own,
‘cause he was creating this character, really,
with this scene
as one of the main building blocks,
‘cause it's where the character
announces his plan and all that kind of stuff.
Once we had those recordings
and built the scene
as a radio play, practically,
the writers, Cinco and Ken,
were able to think about that
as they were creating successive pages
and scenes.
So, yeah, the voice that the actor
helped create off an early scene...
Yeah, you take it back,
and it influences
how the rest of the pages are written,
or how the ideas for the scenes come about.
It's actually cool,
because in animated movies,
-you get the gift of time, just a little bit...
-Yes.
...because there's so many processes,
like writing, storyboard, layout,
where you can actually massage
these little changes in, in terms of dialogue.
Yes. It's definitely an iterative process.
Things like that little joke that just went by
with the tape on the floor
was contributed by a storyboard artist.
And so, it's the kind of thing
where everybody, the writers,
the actors, the storyboard artists,
the producers, everyone sort of contributes,
and it's definitely like building a house
one LEGO brick at a time,
which I think is a big difference
from live action,
where before you shoot,
you really want
everything worked out beforehand.
We build it as we go, I'd say, a little bit.
I think we can do a little better than that.
Here's Miss Hattie.
This is Kristen Wiig, who sort of gave that...
Our idea was, on the surface,
a nice person that says terrible things.
So, she really took that and
had this nice little Southern lilt to her voice,
and, of course, would turn up the volume
when she had to yell at the girls.
And it's a gift for animators to have
these character changes happening so fast.
It's just so easy to see someone nice
play around with the idea that,
"She's nice," and then...
All of a sudden
you've got the voice helping you out
to make the physicality
of the animation come out
and bring out that other character.
And I think what we always try to look for
are contrasts,
and here's a great one with Gru's mom.
The contrast, frankly, is in the casting.
Julie Andrews playing
a terrible mother and woman
who is not supportive of her son in the least,
So that kind of creates a nice thing
in and of itself.
And certainly, Gru,
who's a powerful villain on the surface,
but he's got minions who are incompetent,
his chief scientist can't hear,
so those kind of contrasts
within the characters
are just always something we would try
to find, ‘cause it just lends itself to comedy.
Even in terms of sequences, actually.
In the previous sequence we saw
Gru being at the top of his game, basically,
and now he's gonna come
into the Bank of Evil,
where he's not gonna be
appearing so big at all.
Yeah, he's like every man
who has to state his case
before somebody more powerful than him.
This is a great visual pitched
by Pierre Coffin, who came up with this.
-Did I really? I can't remember.
-Yes. Yeah, I'm pretty sure you did.
Thank you.
But what's great about it is,
it says everything
about, probably, how a lot of people
feel about banks these days, yeah.
So, anyway.
I was surprised to see how
that Lehman Brothers joke actually worked.
-Yeah. Our timing weirdly was...
-Is it gonna work in two years?
-Yeah, yeah, I don't know.
-Lehman who?
So, this is a moment
where we really get a sense of Gru's...
What he went through as a child.
We felt that was
an important character thing to, again,
let the audience side with this bad guy,
is that we see why he chose a life of villainy.
And as usual, it's the fault of his parents.
But anyway. Then this is Vector,
who was played by Jason Segel,
who becomes Gru's main rival
through the film.
Sort of an up-and-coming villain.
Our first idea, or in the original story,
it was a hero Gru was up against.
It went through, I think,
a few different versions,
and then the idea came about
to make it a rival villain,
So it was more about the world of villainy,
which instantly made it
a bit more interesting, I think.
That was Sergio Pablos' initial concept,
right? The superhero thing?
I actually don't remember
the hero portion, whether that...
I think that was
in the original story pitch, yes.
Ever seen one before?
No, you haven't. I invented it.
Do you want a demonstration?
This story originally came
from Sergio Pablos, a Disney animator,
and the main elements of
a villain with these three little girls
that he needed to break into a fortress
were all present in that original pitch.
It's actually funny,
because when we see his initial pitch now,
we see all these milestone images
that are actually ending up in the movie.
-Like the tea party.
-Yeah. Yeah, I think the narrative stuff,
like the shrink ray and the moon plot,
and all that stuff, came later,
but the core story of this villain
taking care of these three little girls
was definitely present in that stuff,
and some of the specific ideas,
which we'll see later comedically.
Again, talking about contrast,
here's a guy who's a super-powerful villain
brought low by these girls
Just instantly lent itself
to drama and comedy.
This is the banker, played by Will Arnett,
who is going for a Larry Flynt...
He just is this quintessential heavy,
and his voice is really great for that.
I have to mention,
there was a moment when, in this scene,
the banker was smashing many more things
besides an apple,
doing too many things,
and so we pulled it back to just the apple.
It was a bizarre scene that was funny,
but the pacing just didn't work
with the overall film, which is...
Constantly, you have to make that choice,
what to remove,
because very often people,
storyboard artists, animators, writers,
contribute great ideas,
but it becomes about
the overall pacing of the film,
and you have to...
That's a big part of the process.
It's not about what to include,
but what to take out.
There goes one last piranha.
So anyway. So here is the sequence
where Gru and a couple of his minions
come to steal the shrink ray,
which they need for the moon plot.
This was also a very early scene done,
this particular moment,
‘cause none of our main characters
were in the scene.
And you can see more
of Gru's technology in this,
and how it contrasts
with Vector's technology.
The thought was,
Gru's things were
Cold War-era metal rivets, iron,
and Vector was gonna be more like an iPod,
white plastic with orange accents.
Do you remember how these guys
started to dance at one point?
-Yes.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah!
It was too long. Get it out.
So, here comes one of the minions.
We had to design a special...
I think, originally, the claw,
he was just hanging on it.
We had to design a little, special seat
for him to be on it.
Yeah.
I should mention quickly, I guess,
the voice of the minions
through most of the film is Pierre.
I do a little bit, and also...
We got it!
-I'm spacing out.
-Jemaine Clement.
Jemaine Clement, sorry, yes.
Sorry, I spaced out.
So, we did quite a bit of work
trying to figure it out.
We had some sound design done,
and then Pierre basically...
-I spoke French.
-Yeah.
And we pitched that,
and it sounds like minions. Easy as that.
No, it's true that at some point we were
discussing, should they make noises?
Should they have their own language?
Should their own language have little words
that we should recognize?
-And we settled for that idea.
-Yeah, we kind of go on the range.
We started thinking that they would be mute,
not speak at all,
and be completely pantomime characters,
but it limited us a bit too much.
And I think we also thought,
"Would we go for the obvious, high-pitched
voice or would we try something different?"
But the reality is, is that in our minds,
the high-pitched just is funny,
-So there's no getting around it.
-Classic, I would say, but it does work.
And it's weird how important they got
as the movie progressed, I guess.
Yes. Yeah, we quickly found as we...
And this is one of the early scenes where
we tried to incorporate them in, actually.
Originally, they weren't in the scene,
and we started looking for ways
to give them a bigger part of the movie.
That's weird. What is going...
This was some nice work,
working with the effects team
on what a shrink ray would look like
and what things shrinking would look like.
-What clouds would look like.
-Yeah, exactly. Clouds and missiles.
So, this was quite a big scene.
Weirdly enough, even though everything
changed in the core of that scene,
-the ending never changed.
-No.
There was always that one shot of him
Sitting on the little ship.
I hate that guy!
-Is that a phone? Is that your phone?
-It's not my phone.
I don't know where's... Mine's off.
-Hello?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, yeah. It's Tim.
-Tim?
Tim, what did we talk about?
What's the number-one rule
before we come in here?
-What's the number-one rule?
-We're never gonna finish this.
No. That is not the number-one rule.
I don't even know what you're talking about.
-He's not even hanging up.
-No, he's not, he's...
You're right, he's still just talking.
Tim, who are you talking to?
Who's so important
you've gotta talk to them right now?
Listen, you need to hang up right now.
He's still not...
Yeah, Bob, could you punch Tim
in the shoulder, please?
Okay.
-So, what were we saying?
-I don't know.
Yeah, yeah, it's gonna take me awhile
to get back my train of thought.
-Did you invite these guys?
-No, no.
-Who did? Is it Production?
-I think it was, yeah.
-I don't know.
-John Cohen? Chris Meledandri? Who?
Janet Healy? It can't be Janet Healy, right?
Yeah, they should be in the room with us.
Yeah, to control them, exactly.
We play with this a couple of times
in the movie, is Gru in disguise,
which was the thing we were talking about
from the Peter Sellers films,
you know,
particularly the Pink Panther movies,
where he was always in some kind
of crazy disguise, which made no sense,
So we made that
an element of this character,
which we use a couple of times.
With Vector, you know, we were
talking about having his technology be
almost impersonal,
like just the push of a button,
where Gru is more hand-to-hand combat,
you know?
He's out there, he's got
the night-vision goggles, he's trying...
-In broad daylight.
-In broad daylight, of course.
Where are the neighbors?
And I think another thing
we tried to do here in the beginning
is have a cartoon quality to the violence,
for lack of a better word,
because these are villains with guns
and missiles and weapons,
and so we felt that, to make it work,
we had to give it a Warner Bros. quality,
where it was obviously ineffective
and cartoonish.
This scene, this moment,
a perfect example of that.
It's such a cool beginning of the movie,
at least in the front part,
being very cartoony, because it sells...
It doesn't prepare for what's coming up next,
which is emotional and...
Right. And it lets us get away with things,
you know,
particularly when you're including guns
and things like that.
-And sharking Gru. How'd he survive that?
-Yeah, exactly!
-Tell the people how Gru survived that.
-You don't want to know.
Whoa! Cool.
So, here is really a pivotal story moment,
and that's why we made Vector's house
truly a living weapon,
with the idea that it was impenetrable,
and very clear, visually,
that there was no way to get inside
except, of course,
for these little girls selling cookies,
and so, this is where Gru hatches his plan
to use them as a Trojan horse.
So, this is the pivotal moment
of how their lives collide.
And again, this is another element
that we use a couple of times,
is his hallucinations, I guess,
for lack of a better word.
His visions of his life with the girls
and how he's gonna use them.
I'm going to need a dozen tiny robots
disguised as cookies!
What?
This is a phone call to Dr Nefario,
and this was an element
of Dr Nefario's character which,
it's funny, kind of went away and then we,
sort of, though, built it back slowly,
which was that he was hard of hearing.
But we got a lot of good stuff,
I think, out of that idea.
Dr. Gru.
There's another disguise.
It's cool to see...
Graphically, that side shot is great,
just because you see how awkward it is
for a big guy to sit on a little chair.
Yeah.
Always has that strong pause
that makes the image interesting.
So, Pierre, can you tell us anything
about the minions there,
-as far as the development of the language?
-I... I don't want to.
-I'm putting you on the spot.
-Yeah. No, no. Nothing...
I remember making all these sounds.
I didn't bring myself over to the studio yet,
and I was recording this
with my kids banging on my door,
asking me what I was doing.
On certain tracks
you can actually hear my son
asking me to come out.
Nobody will ever know, but the language...
You had the framework there
that you'd done with the storyboards,
and I just illustrated it,
giving it character, basically,
in terms of voicing, vocal performance,
and that's the secret, I guess,
to making it come to life.
I think the magic thing is to...
Whatever word you're saying,
you've gotta feel what the intent is,
and that's universal. Whatever.
You can say it by words,
but you can certainly say it the way...
By the way you're saying it, you totally
understand what the guys are saying.
And that was an early moment
for the minions,
where we discovered a personality thing
that we all thought worked,
which was that they're irresponsible.
They get lost. They're trying to help,
they're trying to do their duty,
and then they sort of veer off
into fighting each other,
and so, as we started putting
the pieces together of these characters,
that was one of the early ones
that we thought would really work well
and be funny.
Please tell Margo, Edith and Agnes
to come to the lobby.
So, just one of the things
with the girls is that,
in the early part of the film,
we were treating them all as the same.
Basically just little visions
of childhood innocent...
Sort of like Agnes, I suppose.
Three different Agneses.
But as we went along, we quickly discovered
that we needed
to make them individual, strong characters,
and so Agnes became
the young, innocent, cute one.
Edith was a bit of the rebel who acts out,
and then Margo was the...
I'll go with voice of reason.
She has the unenviable job of being
the one trying to talk sense into her sisters
and into Gru.
-But an important role, actually.
- Totally.
So that worked much better,
and that was obviously
what informed the design
and the voice casting.
You know, we went
with Miranda Cosgrove for Margo,
who's actually much older
than Margo is in reality,
but it's nice. It gives her voice some weight.
You know, she feels like the sensible one.
And then Elsie Fisher, who plays Agnes,
was just...
Just had this great, genuine quality
that is hard to match.
You know, she instantly... Her dad
would actually tickle her in the session,
and that's how we got
some of these great laughs
-that we recorded and used for her character.
-How did you do it when she cried?
That was... That was...
Listen, there's child labor laws.
I'm not gonna go into...
And then Dana Gaier, who played Edith,
Just had this great kind of...
We compared her to Peppermint Patty
in the Peanuts cartoons.
This nice, husky quality
that made her very distinctive.
She's very good, actually, just because...
The character of Edith
is really great just because...
Again, an animator's dream,
just because she has a boyish charm to her,
and everything is about
her physical movements,
and you gotta make that little effort
to understand what she's feeling,
and that's always fulfilling for an audience.
So, this moment was about
checking back in with Vector
and the rivalry,
and what he's up to with the shrink ray,
-as he plays with it in the bathroom.
-Is that your joke? The shrinking toilet?
Is it? I don't know, actually.
It might be from Cinco and Ken.
I think the toilet exploding, that was...
That was the...
That was the part that I was able to...
With the board artist, David Berthier,
I was able to work on.
Okay, bye.
So whenever we have a toilet explode
in a character's face, I'm all for that.
-It's always funny.
-Yeah, it is.
-You've seen that in the past, right?
-Yeah, that's right.
A lot of classic films.
Yeah, we've seen a lot of classic films
use the miniature toilet explosion.
So anyway,
this is the girls' first view of the house,
and then Gru's dead lawn.
You can see, particularly on the house,
the front of the house,
and in this hallway,
there's some beautiful texturing,
and really... All kinds of little paintings
and things that Gru has, you know?
That's a Jesse James "Wanted" poster.
There's headlines of his past deeds,
and all kinds of interesting things
in his house that you'll never see,
but the modeling, surfacing,
art direction teams
really did amazing work filling out his world.
When we got adopted by a bald guy,
I thought this'd be more like Annie.
There's a giant Venus flytrap which
we wanted to animate, but never could.
This is Kyle, who we saw earlier,
who is Gru's sort of dog.
We never really... He's not really a true dog.
We always figured
he was a genetic mutation,
much along the lines of the minions,
that Gru took a liking to and keeps as a pet,
even though he's a bit afraid of him.
-Do you remember when Kyle was Kragul?
-Yes, Kyle was Kragul,
and Gru had an Igor-like sidekick
named Kyle, who was human.
Very often in these films,
you get to the point
where you're like,
"We've got too many characters to service
"and to do justice to,"
So you have to make some decisions,
again, about what to put in
and what not to put in.
We really wanted always to focus on Gru
as a character and really make him
appealing as the centerpiece of this movie,
and as a result,
we gave the name "Kyle" to the dog
and got rid of the human sidekick.
And I think Nefario actually came up
a little bit as a result,
sort of filling that hole.
It was kind of weird, having a talking pet.
I remember scenes in it where...
-That's true.
-The dog talked for a time. Yes, we tried that.
Rule number one.
Russell Brand was a good sport.
He went from being a talking dog
to Dr Nefario.
He did a great job with Dr Nefario.
It was so great to have him take that role.
It was much better than the talking dog.
-Where did you get that?
-Found it.
Again, you can see in the kitchen,
there's all kinds of great things in there.
There's a brain in the water cooler,
there's a chainsaw hanging on the wall,
there's a flamethrower.
There was a scene at one point
of Gru cooking breakfast,
using all his implements of evil.
Yeah, that was supposed to be
the opening scene.
Yeah, that was an opening scene,
and so a lot of the items
that were created for that scene
are still in the kitchen.
So, there's some interesting things in there.
Okay, don't worry.
Everything's going to be fine.
And, of course, an espresso machine,
you can see back there.
Some ordinary things as well.
Yeah, that's right.
-That's Nefario's first screw-up, is it?
-l think it is, yes.
So this was a moment of, again,
establishing Nefario's inability
to hear the mission,
and he creates boogie robots
instead of cookie robots.
An understandable mistake.
So, we really went for the
Saturday Night Fever lighting scenario here,
‘cause that felt like the most fun.
Boogie!
Look at this. Watch me!
And the lab set is...
You know, what we tried to do
is create something that was simple,
but would feel
as If it was really cool and interesting,
So there's not a lot of detail in there,
but it still has a neat feel to it.
This is the girls heading out,
trying to figure out what's going on,
and they stumble upon Gru's elevator.
TV!
-She's never gonna reach it.
-Yeah.
This is one of those staging cheats,
where she's got no...
She's, like, one-foot high.
Which you do all the time, you know?
That's the fun thing about animation,
is we always have fo...
Pierre would say to me, “Let's cheat it,"
and so very often we did that,
Just to get things to work and play.
Come on!
I don't think he's a dentist.
And this, yeah, the door in the elevator
opens differently here
than it does when Gru first goes downstairs.
So this is my favorite scene in the movie,
which is a terrible thing to admit because
-it's completely surface...
-Well, I don't know if it's the scene...
I don't know if it's the scene
or just one shot.
Or the moment. The moment.
-/ love this one, too. You can...
-Yeah, that's true.
So this whole bit was... We wanted
to do something with Nefario as Q
in the Bond films,
and sort of show his ineptitude.
So, Bob, what can you tell us...
What do you remember about this moment,
when we were on the set?
Yeah, he says the worst they made him do
was the dart gun. I could see why.
But he says the smell was something
like burned cabbage, which is...
-Doesn't sound good.
-That didn't sound like cabbage.
So finally Nefario creates the cookie bot,
which is what Gru needs
to carry out his plan.
And, of course, it's interrupted by the girls.
So, this was a scene
that we worked on quite a bit.
We kept changing it, what was happening,
trying to make it feel like
the girls were really interrupting something,
and also that they were suspicious of Gru,
that they weren't just innocents
that weren't like,
"Hey, what's going on here with this guy?”
And Gru comes up with a lie
that he's a spy, which was nice.
It gave the girls...
They didn't seem like fools, I guess,
or just so innocent
that they wouldn't operate in our world.
You know what I mean?
So they felt like kids
that you could relate to a little bit.
Hey!
My unicorn!
That gun that Edith's holding,
we never could agree
which end was the end that shot, remember?
-I think we got it wrong in the end.
-Chris! Chris! Chris!
-What? What? What do you need, Bob?
-What does he want?
-What?
-He's gotta go to the bathroom.
-We're in the middle of recording.
-Bob. Bob, come on.
This is the... Okay.
The DVD people listening to this
commentary are gonna be super interested.
-You can't hold it for two...
-He's gone, he's gone.
Hey, close the door! Thank you!
-We're still recording in here.
-Thank you, Bob.
Please don't... Yeah.
-He flushed.
-Yeah, he flushed.
Great. Thanks a lot, Bob.
Feeling better? What? Yes? Okay.
Listen, just take your seat.
You two share the seat
and just keep it down
for the rest of this audio commentary, okay?
Okay, okay.
Tim just left the room also.
Monkey see, monkey...
Minion see, minion do.
Hey, you know what?
I think I'm gonna go, too.
You're not leaving me here with these two.
-Big moment.
-Yes, this was a big moment.
This was...
We'd started with the idea the minions...
I can't remember if they were going out
to get a toy originally or not,
but we called it "The Minion Mission,"
and it was quite a long bit at some point.
-They always went to a store first...
-Yeah.
...but then it was they foiled robbery,
won some money, bought a car.
We had this idea of having them...
That little trip to the corner shop
or whatever
was supposed to go like...
Carry them to the other side of the world.
-Yes.
-And then they were, maybe...
We were thinking of having them come back
and save the day.
In the third act,
or maybe they didn't come back,
and we picked up with them in the credits.
So, we played with this idea for awhile.
But basically what happened,
which very often happens,
is that the narrative of it just...
It was too much material
that was outside of the narrative drive,
which at this point in the movie
is Gru trying to get the moon
and his bonding with the girls,
so eventually we made it the moment
that you see, where they're in the store.
It was your cousin's idea.
What?
That's you.
-How come that got left in?
-I know, that's right.
That was one of the few minion voices
that's not Pierre.
So here's Gru putting the girls to bed
in these bomb beds,
which was, again, one of the early designs.
If you look on the shelves in this room,
there's all kinds
of early robotic minion prototypes,
little models of Gru's car and his plane.
There's a mobile of the planet Earth
and the moon that's in the ceiling,
which I'm not sure
you ever get a clear shot of, actually,
but there's all kinds of cool stuff
in this room that we filled it with.
I think there's some paintings,
like a Cézanne,
and all kinds of stuff
that he's stolen over the years.
So, it was a fun set to come up
with different ideas of what to put in there.
He's just kidding, Agnes.
So, anyway, Tim, can you tell me a little bit
about this moment? Do you remember this?
Pierre, I don't remember it that way.
Do you remember it that way?
I think he's...
I'm sorry to say, Tim, I think you're lying.
Yeah, yeah. What I remember is
you screaming at both of us,
and then you stormed off
to your trailer for two hours.
It's true. You know it's true.
I remember that idea
came super late in the day.
Yes, yes.
Keep that floating minion perpetual...
Perpetually floating through the film.
We had to figure a way to identify him,
so we had him hold that beaker,
and that's how we were like,
"Okay, well, we know.
"Hopefully the audience will recognize
that it's the guy from the lab scene.”
That's the one thing, when setting up jokes,
is thinking about when you set them up
and how to try to pay them off.
Like, was the timing right?
Especially an idea like that,
that's a couple of scenes previous,
So you hope that everybody remembers
where it came from.
Do you remember that scene?
-How long it used to be?
-Yes.
I think... What was the timing that we...
How much movie did we make?
Did we go over 20 minutes or something
of material?
I don't know
how much we went through to animation,
but we did it pretty quickly, actually.
I mean, things that you make a decision...
This was a scene where we had Gru sort of...
He was counting,
trying to get the girls back into the car.
Basically the idea of,
"Get in this car or I'm gonna count to three.”
And he sort of... We played it out,
and there was some fun material,
but the scene itself
didn't feel like it had much drive,
So we eventually came to
what you're about to see,
where his counting
cuts right to the dance class.
So, we basically removed
the whole middle portion there.
Which is really,
really super elegant, actually.
-Yes.
-It turned out beautifully, in terms of pacing.
And I think that's... Part of the trick is
that we try to figure out what...
How many beats do you need
to establish an idea,
or establish a relationship?
I think that's always the trick.
Does the relationship feel authentic?
Have you done enough?
You don't want to shortchange it.
Or are you doing too much?
And the moment's already there.
-Is this our favorite sequence?
-I think it's gotta be up there.
This is the whole point of the movie,
in some ways.
This is the reason he's gotten the girls,
this is the mission,
to steal the shrink ray back from Vector.
Yes, yes! I went to kindergarten.
I know how the alphabet works!
So I think we had this car, and then
we never really had an interior for it.
There were supposed to be missiles...
There were supposed to be missiles
that came out,
so it didn't really have an interior,
So we sort of came up with
one that looked like a camper.
Almost over. It's almost over.
Girls, welcome back to the fortress.
We even, obviously, came up with
a look for Gru's computer screens,
using purples and reds.
So that has a consistent feel as well.
Should probably mention Yarrow,
that helped Eric
-in designing all these things.
-Yes, yes.
...two caramel clumpies
and fifteen boxes of coco-nutties.
And Yarrow was great about
really making sure the design language
between characters and worlds
was consistent,
and really established a look
that really followed the rules.
-He did all these, actually.
-Yeah.
Yarrow is very hands-on. He's sort of...
Like, that display he actually created.
-Cookie OS.
-Yeah.
-...nine...
-Why are you wearing pajamas?
So, the shark took on its own life as well.
He started as...
I think there was, early, early on,
a scene in Gru's lab where...
‘Cause villains, of course,
always have sharks.
There was a rhino-shark hybrid,
or something like that,
and that went away quickly.
And then the storyboards
for the break-in scene
that occurred way back,
where the shark was just a total surprise,
showing up eating Gru.
And then what happened is, when we were
designing the interior of this room,
the idea came about of having the shark tank
be the floor to Vector's living room,
and so that kind of explained
how that shark showed up,
where originally it was a non...
It had nothing to do with anything,
which was a surprise comedy beat.
And so the shark started taking on
a real presence in the movie,
and in these scene,
we actually got to use that idea,
and that, I think, is what cemented it.
You'll see later,
when Gru is hanging above the shark,
and it becomes an important element.
This scene, originally, we had it with Gru
in a van outside, and the cookie bots,
he was just monitoring them,
and then the idea came about...
I talked with John Cohen,
one of the producers,
about Gru coming in, and John
pitched the idea of him getting locked in,
and I think that, that then
took the scene to a whole new place,
with Gru really an active participant,
which was kind of a consistent... There's a...
Kind of a crazy idea from Mark O'Hare,
one of our story artists.
Kept coming up with new uses for minions.
But we always tried to make the choice
of having Gru be an active participant
in the scenes,
like the break-in, originally, the heist,
whereas I think when we first started,
he was more imperious.
He would send people out
to do his dirty work.
Which was less funny, actually,
because right now we see him fail miserably,
or at least get put in situations
that lead to this type of physical stuff,
where he's gonna look ridiculous,
like, in about a few seconds.
Like here.
-And here, obviously.
-That's gotta hurt there.
So, here we see the shark coming into play.
Some of the things we talked about
with this scene were,
of course, Mission Impossible,
but also Spider-Man, when his blood
is dripping over the Green Goblin.
Those kind of tension moments, trying
to build that, but comedically, in this case.
Even though the shark
obviously can't reach him,
you play the idea that maybe it can,
Just to build some tension.
And the music here,
which originally we had the Jaws theme,
but we scored it with Heitor.
Our composer did an amazing job
of giving us something as good
as the Jaws theme for that moment.
Come on, girls, let's go!
This is interesting,
‘cause the world here looks like
it's the Pacific Coast Highway in California,
and the city where Gru lives
is sort of everywhere and nowhere.
Like, the city, in some ways,
has water towers on the buildings,
So it looks a little bit like Brooklyn
or an East Coast city,
and then here it feels like the West Coast,
I suppose, of the United States.
So we tried to keep it not very...
As unspecific as we could.
-Please?
We'll never ask for anything else,
ever again!
-Pretty please?
-Please?
There's another one of Gru's fantasies,
sending the...
That was, again,
another last-minute thing that we did.
Do you remember
when that whole Super Silly Fun Land
-was supposed to be a matte painting?
-Yes. I was just thinking that.
Particularly for the 3-D,
we wanted to do the roller coaster,
and so it quickly became apparent that
we were gonna have to
build it in some form or fashion,
so I think we built a rough outline
of the track, put a camera on it,
and then decided what pieces we needed
to build out more specifically
when we edited it together.
So anyway,
this scene was a lot of fun to construct
-because...
-3-D moment.
Yeah, and it's on a roller coaster.
Who doesn't love to ride a roller coaster?
Tim, what's wrong? Are you okay?
You getting motion sickness?
Why doesn't anyone tell us these things?
This is really disgusting.
It's not very interesting for a DVD extra.
I'll just tell our listening audience,
just be glad you're not here with us.
Can somebody get Tim a bag?
-What do we do with this?
-I don't know.
Bob, is there anything... You know?
Okay, why don't you come over here by us.
Don't want to get your shoes dirty.
Oh, man. You okay? Yeah?
Tim, why don't you lie down?
We'll come back to you in a little bit, okay?
How much for the fluffy unicorn?
And then this is Jack McBrayer,
who plays the Carnival Barker.
He's just perfect for it,
giving Gru a hard time.
We wanted this moment to be the first time,
in some ways, Gru bonds with these girls,
so we tried to make it a relatable situation,
where he feels injustice
when the girls get cheated, basically,
by this Carnival Barker.
Again!
-Wait!
-Come on. One more time!
Just one more.
I accidentally closed my eyes.
So, this gave us some experience
with animating crowds,
and getting a lot of people in there,
So you could really fill out
the whole carnival to make it feel alive.
Especially that shot.
It took us, literally, weeks,
and the end result is
that everything is out of focus.
Yeah.
You do all that work,
and then you put depth of field on it.
And then you get
a bunch of animators hitting you.
Yeah.
It feels natural, though. It's good.
That little tin spaceship?
You see how it's not knocked over?
Do you know what that means?
We tried, mostly at Pierre's behest,
to make the camera feel natural
with depth of field, lens flares.
Things that were a little tricky
to manage in 3-D, actually,
but certainly give it a less CG feel,
where you feel like
you're really with these characters.
We tried to create a different,
distinctive look for each of Gru's weapons.
The shrink ray, the freeze ray,
and this was the death ball ray, I don't know.
So when the effects department
came up with the idea
of it forming into a ball of plasma,
we were like, "That's cool,"
‘cause we hadn't seen it before.
So, we tried to create a real,
distinct language for each weapon.
Let's go. Let's try another game!
It's funny because that previous sequence,
if you really look carefully
at all the background characters,
-you've seen them somewhere.
-Yes.
Just because we tried to be witty
about reusing background characters,
but I'm pretty sure that,
for the experienced eye, you can notice.
-"I've seen that guy before."
-It was a great idea to have Gru's face paint.
We can't afford any distractions!
Delivering those lines with face paint.
Another scene that
the minions were incorporated into.
I figured that you would want to see this!
What?
So that little moment with Mr. Perkins there,
where he goes, "What?"
That was just a little thing we dropped in
that will pay off later,
when we see that Mr. Perkins is actually
working against Gru behind the scenes.
Setting up his role with his son.
-Did I just ruin that?
-I think so. It's a spoiler.
Well, hopefully you've watched the movie
already before listening to this.
Could you excuse me for just one second?
We gave him a solid gold laptop there.
Hey, can we order pizza?
Pizza? You just had lunch.
Not now, for dinner.
Dinner?
Again, this scene is about...
If you've ever worked at home
and you've had little kids around,
you know how hard it is
to get anything done,
So it seemed like... Doing a teleconference
seemed like a logical way
to have the girls get in the way
of Gru's work
in a very real way, that actually ends up
having consequences down the road.
If you look, in the upper corner there
of Mr. Perkins' desk is actually the photo,
you'll also see later, of him with Vector,
who's his son. Don't tell anyone.
What?
You don't seem terribly focused, Gru.
Believe me, I am...
Some of the art direction cues,
in Gru's apartment, especially...
Those wood floors are floors that...
The way the planks are laid out
is something you really find here in Paris.
Most of the floors in the United States
are usually just slats,
So it's interesting,
there's little things here and there.
I think the doorknob
on Miss Hattie's orphanage is in the middle.
So those little design cues... I know
I always say that, but I think that's neat.
Those little design cues
that are unique to France.
-You guys aren't normal.
-It's true.
-You'd have put carpet everywhere in there.
-I know, it's probably freezing in there.
Another interesting thing in that moment
is the way Gru drew himself here.
-He's bald.
-Yeah.
He knew exactly
how he was gonna turn out later.
These three moments
are something we played with a lot,
like Gru as an artist
going through different things.
He did a painting...
And we played with them
several different ways.
Then there was a moment where he was
getting photographed with an astronaut,
and his mom asked him
to get out of the picture.
So we really... It was trying to find a balance
between something that was funny,
but also made you feel for him.
It didn't feel too cruel.
So anyway,
I think we ended up in a good place.
It sort of reinforced his character,
and that he was obsessed
with getting to the moon.
I don't know
what that guy has with apples, but...
Feels like he only has them around
Just to squish them.
This was a fun set.
It was sort of the rec room for the minions,
and there's all kinds of things in there.
-Drinks and a pinball machine.
-Pinball.
-Ping-Pong game.
-Every video game system known to man.
An espresso machine,
a coffee machine, back there.
And originally we talked about
staging this scene in the lab,
where Gru originally gives the talk
about stealing the moon,
but we just felt it needed
to be more casual than that.
So, I think there's a little posting back there
of somebody looking for...
-The carpet is great.
-The carpet, yeah.
It looks like they can play soccer.
But it gave it a fun...
You catch the minions in their downtime.
Sorry, that's one of my favorites.
Drunk minion. Drunk on milk.
Yeah, not drunk at all.
As I suggest that all of you do, as well.
What is it?
This also was an animator's dream,
Just because of Carell's performance,
in terms of voicing.
How he played very optimistic,
but saying horrible stuff.
Followed by this very silent moment.
-The music is great, also, in that moment.
-Yeah, it's very...
Again, this is Heitor
creating the emotional swell here.
It was really nice.
And the themes were based on
some of the songs of Pharrell Williams,
which gave us a rich material
to create the tapestry of the score.
And the next scene, in fact, we're gonna
go into a song called Prettiest Girls,
which Pharrell wrote and recorded,
which is great and just defines the moment
as they're carrying off all kinds of stuff.
We keep saying that everything is great
in that movie.
Yeah, that's true. We should talk about...
You know what I didn't like?
That shot wasn't that good.
And the animation is kind of...
You know what? You're right.
It is getting a little boring here.
That is terrible! No.
Anyway, it's a nice song,
and it really carries the moment,
gives it the lift that it needs.
We went through different ideas
of what this montage should be about,
and we landed on it being a little bit
about Gru and Nefario's relationship,
where Gru... We really get the sense
that Gru is getting pulled away from his job,
and I've always liked to say that the movie,
at the end of the day,
is about the choice
that a lot of us have to make,
which is family versus career,
and that's kind of what this scene is about.
What did you choose?
Don't put me on the spot like that.
My wife's gonna listen to this. No.
In his Sunday best.
He looks like a girl!
Gru's mom there
is wearing the same shoes as Margo.
-We didn't have any money anymore.
-That's right.
-For budget reasons.
-We didn't have wardrobe.
Those marshmallows
should be much blacker,
but we decided to
go for having them look edible.
Here we can see the girls
starting to transform their surroundings,
like they paste pictures on the wall,
hang up a curtain,
Just trying to
make Gru's rather inhospitable home...
-Pink. Kyle...
-Make Kyle...
So, they're sort of becoming
the dominant force in changing his world.
This is the moment
where Gru is slacking on the job, so...
Some nice effects there
with the sliding pancake.
-Our character effects.
-What? Oh, my God!
Okay.
We had Vector...
It just sort of gave it a nice...
It reinforced the family element
of the movie, actually,
in that this is another side of parenting.
You have a spoiled brat as a kid.
The dad is giving his son everything,
and he still can't seem to make it work.
Financing his... So anyway, we just thought
that it was a nice way to reinforce...
Maybe a nice surprise,
but also reinforcing the family themes,
the dysfunctional family themes
of the movie.
-Hey, it is all about that, right?
-Yeah.
The girls don't have any parents,
they're searching for ones,
but those who have parents
actually have problems with them.
Yeah, that's right. What are we saying?
There's a squid on my face!
Don't worry.
Nice. The squid acting. A fully-rigged squid.
This is a scene that we called
"Sleepy Kittens," based on the book,
and it was really a beautifully written scene
by Cinco and Ken.
I remember first reading it, and it actually
made me laugh and touched me.
-I'm admitting that, sorry.
-You wuss.
But it is a great moment in the movie,
and nothing really happens, action-wise.
It's really just about
this guy reading to these girls,
and I think a lot of the movie
is about bad parenting,
which I think a lot of people watching it
can relate to. I know I can.
Making the bad choice or reading a book,
you're like, "Oh, God, this is terrible,"
but you... It becomes about
making the sacrifices for your kids,
and for Gru's case, his adopted kids.
He finally agrees to read this book,
which he wants nothing to do with.
What's actually cool about Gru
is that he speaks his mind.
-Yes. He says what we think.
-Yeah, exactly.
What we wouldn't say to our kids,
he's just says. "This is garbage."
So very early on,
even after we storyboarded it,
and as I said, nothing happens,
they just sit there through the scene,
we kind of knew, and particularly
when we got Carell's dialogue in here...
Or, I'm sorry, his recordings in here,
we felt we had something special,
and again, it really represents a turn
for Gru's character.
"Fine, but at least
you should brush your fur."
Now you brush the fur.
So, it's one of
those puppet books, obviously,
which I think is designed incorrectly,
‘cause his hand goes in the wrong side,
but anyway, it works.
Here you can get a clear...
From an art direction point of view,
you can get a clearer vision
of how the girls
have started transforming the room.
We changed the lighting
from being very cold to warmer,
helped along by that big blanket
that they've hung behind their beds,
and the soft lights,
and the bombs have been arranged
on the floor, so it's just much cozier,
versus the rather...
When they're on the rack on the wall,
very cold and very utilitarian in feel.
But again, they've transformed
the world around them to suit their needs.
And this is a turn in the character here.
"Good night kittens, close your eyes.
Sleep in peace..."
Again, an animator's dream,
Just to get carried away by the voice
and the performance
and the actual meaning of the scene.
We tried to play it not over the top,
So hopefully we've been subtle about it.
Just to make that turn work.
-Wait!
-What?
Yeah, some of the facial expressions of Gru
in this scene
are really some of the best in the movie.
Even the one I missed early on,
where he goes, "Okay."
It's just the way his eyes blink.
I think that's the key to great animation
that the team here has been able to hit,
is that, try to do something
that's unexpected, but also identifiable,
and that's kind of cool,
when you see life in these characters.
There's Gru's family tree,
which is a funny illustration.
You don't really see it that much,
but I think there's a werewolf in there,
and all kinds of things that have lead to Gru.
Of course the girls connect themselves to it.
All systems are go.
About that.
And Gru is reduced to picking up toys.
That's probably the biggest sequence shot
in the movie, right there.
I believe this is the last shot rendered,
actually. It was so big, it took forever
to get it out of the computers,
So we could put it in the movie.
This was also one of the...
I think one of the...
I don't know if it was the last set,
but it was definitely one of those things
where you had to, like,
"Where we gonna stage this?"
We created this quick hallway set
somewhere outside of the girls' room,
which we ended up using later again,
I believe,
when Gru steps out at the end of the movie.
-Yeah, with the minions.
-Yeah.
But these girls
are becoming a major distraction!
They need to go.
If you don't do something about it,
then I will.
Great job there on Nefario's hair.
We debated that a little bit,
‘cause the hair is so thin.
You know, "Would you ever see it?"
But it's just a funny thing.
What are they looking at? Hey, guys, guys,
listen. Wait. You're not helping.
-Guys. Please. Please.
-What's making them...
-l think it's... Well, it is funny. He's right.
-What?
-He's xeroxing, and he said...
-The "butt" thing?
Yeah. He said the word "butt,"
which is good.
I know this scene's funny, but...
-Butt?
-Butt!
Now I see what's so funny.
-They're photocopying their butts and...
-You guys.
You guys are right, this is funny,
but please, you gotta keep it down.
Miss Hattie, what are you doing here?
I'm here for the girls.
That was a callback to a joke
from the previous scene together,
with the Spanish dictionary.
And also,
I did purchase a Spanish dictionary.
One thing we always tried to think of, we
had to figure out set-dressing on our sets.
We'd always be shooting scenes and be like,
"There's no cars or anything,"
so we'd have to go back
Just to make the world lived in.
The funny thing with CG is that,
‘cause you have to create everything,
you always have to think about
what needs to go...
It's not like going to a city street.
You have to, like, "We've got the street,
but there's nothing on it."
To make it feel like it's a world
that is believable and lived in,
including seat belts,
which we added into this moment.
Thanks for everything.
-Which she puts on. Very quickly.
-Yes, she does. There we go.
The front of the house, we had some trouble.
We made the front of the house
before we had all the characters finished,
and we basically had to
create a second front of the house.
-Bigger.
-Bigger, so we could get this shot
with the window, ‘cause it was very stylized,
everything very high, tall and thin,
and so we had to create a...
-And actually, Gru didn't fit in that door.
-Gru did not fit in the door,
-So0 we had to cheat.
-He had to walk sideways,
which made it weird.
So, here's a nice... It's a twofold thing.
My daughter has one of these heads,
and they're always kind of creepy.
It's like this disembodied head,
So it seemed like a good opportunity
to do an homage to The Godfather.
-It's for you, Francis.
-Yeah.
There's the pink suit, which was another,
we felt, very strong image,
after the girls wash their tutus
with the space suit, and Gru comes out.
So it'd be a nice visual reminder of the girls
as we go through the third act,
in which the girls actually aren't present,
‘cause they've been taken back
to Miss Hatftie's.
We kept the shrunken minion
as an important part of the story.
We always thought he was funny.
The recital?
It's interesting how we didn't get lost
in all those arcs. The small minion, the...
Kyle, also, has a nice arc now.
-The floating minion.
-Yeah.
So, in order to reinforce the idea
that they had made the rocket
out of things they found,
a lot of the engines on the bottom,
there's a steam train, I think,
a locomotive, there's a steam ship,
there's parts of aeroplanes,
and the cockpit has a blender, a toaster...
Gosh. Everything we could find prop-wise,
we threw into that cockpit.
-There's a shower.
-Yeah, there's a showerhead,
to make it feel like it was just put together
with spare parts.
Here's McDade, Gru's neighbor,
played by Danny McBride,
and he's sort of the hapless neighbor
who's, like, just witnessing...
Powerless as all these things
are going on around him,
including dueling super-villains.
Finally got to use that squid launcher.
Oh, yeah!
Nice work, Doctor. All systems go.
There's the piranha gun again.
Completely ineffective.
Again.
This is where we started getting into
figuring out how to do our clouds,
which was a lot of work.
Oh, yeah! Once again, the mighty...
There's the floating minion.
This shot was added,
So we had to figure out
the progression of the rocket
through the sky,
So we had to go back and forth
a little bit on that
to make sure that shot made sense.
So that means
the minions don't breathe air, right?
Yeah, that's right.
They don't breathe air, they can glow.
We just would give them attributes
as we needed them.
That's what makes them
great animated characters.
Well, one cool thing about Gru in space is,
in 3-D, one of the coolest things
is just an object floating
in the middle of nothing,
and of course a character floating in space
gives you a real opportunity to do that.
So, inadvertently, this moon mission
gave us some neat 3-D opportunities,
‘cause after this happens,
Gru's just floating there with the moon,
and it's just the coolest thing
to have this thing
that's free from the frame
and just floating there.
It's really neat.
I've got it!
I've got the moon!
This is the moment you were talking about.
It is true that all the 3-D aspects
work better with slow-moving things
coming out at you
-or floating in...
-Like this ticket.
-Wow. Hey. Look at that timing.
-Yeah, no. It really works nicely.
It's a great way to get the most out of 3-D.
-There are moments like that.
-Plus, it's not aggressive, so...
Here we go.
Yeah, so we needed a way for Nefario
to witness that trouble's a-brewing,
and so we enlarged Kevin, or Stuart,
whoever that ended up being,
one of our minions,
as Gru rushes back to Earth.
He's still not here.
Why would he come? He gave us up.
But he pinky promised!
So again, it's a spin on the classic situation
of a dad trying to get home from work early.
This time he happens to be at work in orbit.
In order to see his kids' dance recital,
in this case.
Gru makes that choice up there
after he's got the moon, which he thought
was gonna fulfill the hole in his heart,
but turns out it doesn't.
So, Nefario tries to warn him,
and then you get a nice, old-man cart joke.
Okay, we had talked about
using that cart more, but we never...
One thing we always debated, too,
IS what is the role of the world in this?
Like, the moon shrinking.
Is there pandemonium, earthquakes, waves?
At the end of the day,
what we decided was to make it simple,
and that the moon, he takes the moon,
it's an object, and he goes,
and it becomes a very... It's really a story
of Gru and the girls, and so other things,
like there's a moment coming up
where you see this rocket fall,
and there's kids on a playground
and they laugh at it.
But moments of
the world at large witnessing all this,
we kind of kept that to a minimum,
because it becomes another story
that we probably didn't have time to tell.
And I'm not even sure we wanted to tell,
because the way this is now,
it's very focused.
You have all this grand imagery
of a rocket landing in the street
as a guy's trying to get home from work,
but we don't go into
what people around the rocket think.
-"Where are the cops?”
That's what we always kept saying.
"Where's the Army?”
So we just kind of went around those things,
and I think it was definitely the right choice.
Yeah. It would've overcomplicated the thing.
It's not really the story.
From a lighting perspective here,
we really tried to
go for that golden hour thing,
and all of the third act is done that way.
We're thinking of Maxfield Parrish
and some of the beautiful paintings he did
of the clouds in his work,
and the light breaking across them,
So we just wanted it to have
that feeling of the end of day.
Plus, it kind of helped us. We were
going back to the same location, so...
Yeah. It helps it feel different,
like it's something new.
Nice acting there,
as Gru gives pause for a second.
The animation team did a great job.
I think I'll hold on to them
a little while longer.
No!
Oh, yeah! Unpredictable!
So the idea here, we wanted to...
And I always think this is a cool moment
in movies, is sort of where the hero,
in this case Gru,
Just almost takes on superhuman powers,
and this was something
that Chris Meledandri had mentioned,
like becoming The Terminator,
and that can always be a satisfying moment,
and I think the music actually here
really reinforces it.
The funny thing I always think about
with this is, like, now all of a sudden
these missiles are dangerous.
I mean, earlier in the film
he was shot by a hundred of these
and it had no effect.
So that's kind of the fun of, tonally,
Just sort of shifting it,
making it feel like there's weight this time
in these weapons.
The idea always was... Originally, Gru was
just trying to break in to steal a shrink ray.
Now he's breaking in for his daughters,
or for love,
and so the meaning of it,
even though it's the same location,
the same weapons, is much different.
And, of course, the shark doesn't eat him
this time. He gets punched in the face.
We had briefly talked about Vector's house
becoming a walking robot,
which we thought
would've been kind of interesting, too,
but we went with the escape pod idea.
And then being able to use the pyramid
that Vector's got
So cleverly hidden back there
as Gru's method
of catching up with the ship
just to tie everything together.
Hang on, Gru.
You want to talk anything about
some of the staging challenges in this?
God, they were all over the place.
Yeah, it was very, very complicated.
Like, the next few shots you're gonna see,
that whole moon enlarging, girls escaping,
Gru trying to have the girls
Jump towards him,
and in the meantime, you have the moon
still rolling inside Vector's ship,
plus the fact that the girls have to jump
at a particular timing, was a nightmare.
One thing, too, is the ship originally,
Gru's ship here, which enlarged,
didn't have an opening at the top,
So we had to redesign it,
so we could actually pull off
what we needed to.
Did you see that?
-Vector! Help!
-Vector!
-Over here!
-Hey!
What are you girls doing back there?
And then, of course, the moon enlarging.
-We didn't talk about the Nefario Principle.
-We skipped the Nefario Principle!
Man, it's the important thing in the movie.
Obviously, the ship, everything,
the timing was a little off,
So we came up with the explanation
that the larger the mass
the less time it stays shrunk,
which, of course, makes no sense,
and Russell Brand was able to add,
"I call it the Nefario Principle,”
-which sort of made it work, in a weird way.
-What's nice about it is just the timing of it.
Like, instead of a very long explanation,
it's like, "I just came up with it now."
-Mr. Gru, up here!
-Mr. Gru!
I think this sequence
got edited numerous times.
Yes. We had to find the right balance
of, really, how much we needed,
because the moment is basically...
Once he attaches himself to the ship,
it's about him... There's two things.
There's the action you want to keep going,
but also the emotional moment
of him getting them,
particularly Margo, to trust him,
So balancing those two things...
Some shots we took out,
which I think helped a lot,
because if somebody's
about to jump to their death
and you're talking about your emotions,
it doesn't make any sense.
So you try to make that as quick
as possible, so you get both things to work.
So, obviously, this is...
-Would you jump? Really?
-It looks dangerous. It really does.
Remember the sawfish gun we had there
for a minute?
We couldn't get it to work,
so we were like, "Just use the piranha gun.”
It never worked, so let's just use that.
So we started with the tightrope thing,
and then it just felt unbelievable, so...
That's how we had it in the storyboards,
but then animation took it
and made it more buy-able,
and also I think it felt more dangerous,
‘cause it felt more real,
like what you'd have to do
to rescue somebody.
The minions just broke that.
The idea you're gonna see
came super late in the day also,
this minion chain.
And what was cool was, we'd had the idea
of, when Gru landed in the ship earlier
and waves at all the minions
and it's kind of a fun reveal,
and then this idea, as Pierre said, came later,
but it was a nice way to justify
why all those minions were in the ship.
-And they were actually useful in the end.
-Yeah.
This was another moment we had
to make the decision where less is more,
just in, like,
"How do we get that moon up there?”
So the idea was the ship
was pushing it along on its jet thrusters,
and then, of course, we see Vector with...
-Again, a nice effects thing where...
-Yeah, with the bubble.
The bubble helmet had a little life of its own.
But once again, law enforcement is baffled,
leaving everyone to wonder,
who is this mysterious hero?
This was another thing,
just trying to tie everything together.
The newscaster we see in the beginning,
and he says, "Who is this new hero?”
Instead of the new villain.
So the newscaster became
the viewpoint of the world,
in a very abbreviated form.
Here we see that Kyle became tamed.
Became Agnes' best friend.
Nothing scares animals and pets
like little kids.
So here, again,
this is the full progression of Gru,
where he now has made a book for the girls,
and tells them a story.
But, yes, it probably will be.
Here we go.
It's obviously the full journey
to him being a parent, and a good one.
-He's quite an artist.
-Yeah, he is.
"And turned his whole life upside down."
Some of the props, obviously,
have changed in here.
Our kids have done some drawings
that are hanging over there.
And obviously,
all their beds have their own character,
where Agnes' looks like a unicorn,
and Margo's looks like a princess.
And Edith's is slipping my mind right now,
but it's something.
I think it's... Yeah, it's just a brass bed.
So the bombs have been completely
converted into a very nice...
So again, this scene is the third
where the kids are going to bed,
and we see the full progression of
the characters coming together as a family.
And again, we tried being super subtle
in terms of animation.
On this shot, for example. Just to make
this one a little bit more surprising.
Just like the reactions of the girls.
Agnes looks up, Edith just smiles.
I love you.
And the lighting's got a nice warmth,
and that's...
‘Cause Margo was the most resistant,
and to have her give a hug
was a nice moment.
And minions again.
And the minions
asking for a kiss good night.
I think that's a great comic relief,
like, coming out of that scene.
You feel something,
even if you don't show it,
and then you see the minions telling you,
"You're allowed to laugh now."
-Yeah.
-That helps.
This is a great bit of Gru
getting visually scolded by his mom.
That was something the animation team did.
It was great.
So, what's cool about this,
that we were always debating
about dancing at the end of animated films.
But what we like about this is that,
this was actually
a great way to end this story,
because Gru never got to see their recital.
So the girls are presenting a recital
for Gru down in the lab,
and of course the minions and Gru's mom
and Nefario and everybody can participate.
So again, continuing along the idea
of Gru's transformation as a character,
‘cause now they haven't changed
Just his home,
they're also changing his workplace,
which happens.
So anyway, we wanted to use
some kind of song we felt was very iconic
to just get the characters dancing,
and so we chose the Bee Gees here.
That's gotta be because we're 40-ish.
-Yeah, yeah, maybe it's that, I guess, right?
-We could put Grease in there, too.
But Gru's probably 40-ish, too,
So it probably makes sense.
-Actually, he looks like us.
-Yeah.
No, actually, he looks like Chris Meledandri.
He looks more like me than you,
that's for sure.
So anyway,
then you just see Gru cutting loose.
And we went, again, for
that Saturday Night Fever lighting,
just to make it as fun as possible.
And also using that platform
that we see Gru,
when he's announcing his plan to steal
the moon in the early scenes of the movie.
We had another opportunity to use it here.
Nefario's got something going
with Gru's mom there.
That's a lot of minions
to animate right there.
There's Vector. He's okay.
I love that moment.
I love doing a non sequitur cut,
and then there's the floating minion.
And this image was always the image
we wanted as the last image of the film.
-It was nice we figured out a way...
-This one?
This one here.
...to make that work,
‘cause we had several different versions.
-Janet Healy.
-Our great producers, Chris and Janet.
Chris Meledandri put it all together.
I'm trying to say, have we mentioned
everybody and what they've done?
-I think now's the time.
-Here we go, yeah.
-What about this moment, Chris?
-Yeah, right.
-What about this moment?
-Yeah. Who did that?
So anyway, this was an idea
that started with Chris Meledandri
about trying to do something
that was very fun and unique for 3-D.
And so, it was really
at the end of the production,
so he came in with the idea of
the minions having a competition
of who could poke something deeper into...
Who could poke further into 3-D space.
So it starts with their hands, and then goes
to one standing on the end of a plunger,
and the little guy on the right is the referee
with his tape measure,
and so it's kind of an abstract idea,
but in 3-D it works.
So you people at home
watching it in 2-D DVD...
Hopefully 3-D TVs are out by now.
So anyway...
So yes, we created this little sequence
that was then punctuated by the credits.
And John actually really pushed the 3-D
on that little sequence.
Yeah, John Benson.
And again, 3-D tends to work best
when it's an object
coming from the deep distance
into the deep foreground slowly,
and this little sequence was really
Just designed to take advantage of that idea,
and also have a little bit of fun
with the minions.
That's an old Harpo Marx joke.
Should I admit that?
I guess I shouldn't. I don't know.
Anyway, so the minion there
obviously can't get them to stop.
We always wondered, in this shot,
where he's going.
He's heading off somewhere.
-Did we mention Bruno?
-No.
Did a great job. Robert.
He's sitting here with us,
-So we have to...
-Oh, God, yeah, Robert.
Great, great associate producer.
The classic, the cartoon canon. Here we go.
So we're trying to think of ways
to have this come to an end,
So the minion actually comes all the way out
through the audience, was the idea,
into the projection booth.
But when you think about it,
it doesn't make any sense, right?
-Because it's digital, right?
-Yes.
-It's digital...
-Don't tell anyone.
This is all gonna have to be edited out,
I think. "Leave us in.”
So then, it's a shadow-puppet thing
at the end there,
and then we have Gru come in,
and we end the movie the way we started it,
which is with Gru's
rather distinctive silhouette,
which we saw on the Despicable Me logo.
-Look at it.
-Look, what an ego on that guy!
I think I'm five times.
Hey, I negotiated six times.
I had them take one off. I couldn't take it.
-Where are you? I didn't see you, Chris.
-I know. I'm nowhere.
Yeah, that was great.
This is the whole French crew, actually,
that did the...
That was the story team.
What are you talking about?
Those are Americans up there, my friend.
No. Actually, there were some French...
We had the story people all over the world.
That was the one department that was...
We had them in Spain,
we had them in Canada,
Ohio, California, New Jersey.
And here comes the French team.
So basically the rest of the movie,
from layout up till the finish,
was all created in France.
There's a lot of names there
I can't pronounce.
Or I can't pronounce correctly, I should say.
Hopefully we're better at making movies
than at playing football.
Actually, the song here is
the one that was from Super Silly Fun Land.
It's Pharrell Williams,
and he'd originally talked about it
for the opening scene, but we used it...
It was perfect,
‘cause it was called Fun, Fun, Fun.
It was perfect for Super Silly Fun Land,
and we liked it so much,
we put it here in the end credits as well.
So anyway, did you guys feel at any point
that this movie was going to be a huge hit?
-He just said yes, right?
-Yeah.
I still have problems
understanding these guys.
Yeah, I know. It's like they have
their own language or something.
So, I guess that's it, right?
-Are we gonna stay...
-Till the bitter end?
What are you doing afterwards?
I think we're gonna have to
stay and do this over again.
That's right.
I know we're gonna listen back to this,
and it's not gonna be nearly as funny
as we think it is.
We're gonna wish
we had just kept our mouths shut.
The sound post, that was also done
over at Skywalker in the US.
-Great guys over there.
-Yeah.
Awesome.
I think what's super interesting
in terms of experience...
Like, when did we start doing this film?
Two years and a half, or two years...
-Yeah, yeah. 2008.
-2008. It took us two years.
Yeah, some of the sound work was great,
‘cause that's the cool thing
about an animated movie,
is that there really is the need
to create a world of sound
that's unique to the film.
And the guys at Skywalker,
particularly their experience with machines
and things like that,
really gave us some great stuff,
particularly for Gru and Vector
and all their technology.
-Should we say goodbye?
-We should say goodbye.
The logos are showing up. That's the end.
What was that?
Man, what was that?
Is that supposed to be a French word?
Thank you for listening.
-Goodbye, everyone.
-Yes.