Illuminat...
Ah not.
Gracia.
Késako?
Illumination!
The year was 1985,
and the number one show on TV was...
Evil Bratt!
The show starred
young Balthazar Bratt
as a child prodigy
and criminal mastermind
bent on world domination.
There he is! Get him!
I've been a bad boy!
Bratt was the biggest
child actor of the 1980s,
striking a chord with
audiences all over the world.
There he is! Get him!
But it all came to an end
in Season 3, when...
I've been a bad boy!
The young star experienced,
Boy?
An unexpected growth spurt.
The show was canceled.
Hollywood rejected him
and Bratt quickly plunged
into a downward spiral,
starting to actually believe he was
the character he played on TV.
What are you looking at?
Leading us all to wonder,
where is he now?
You know what, Clive?
Playing a villain on TV was fun,
but being one in real life,
is even better.
Heist music!
Here it comes.
What Clive?
What are you doing?
How is that heist music?
Sorry. My bad.
Mommy!
Stop or I'll...
Sir, the ship has been boarded
by some kind of monster!
Wait! That's not a monster.
That's a man wearing shoulder pads!
There's only one supervillain
whose fashion sense is quite that dated.
Balthazar Bratt.
Blast it! The Dumont
Diamond is on that ship.
I want every agent in the area
on the scene immediately!
We're already here.
Agents Grucy are closing fast.
Yes! Wait. What did you call us?
Grucy. You know, Gru and
Lucy mushed together. Try it.
I like it, but not a lot.
I don't like it.
Stop! On the ground!
Go, go, go, go!
Too late again, Gru!
He's getting away!
That's what he thinks.
Go! Go! Go...
Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go!
I don't think we can make it, Gru!
We can make it!
No, we can't!
Get ready!
Get ready for...
Hey. How you doing?
Are you ok?
Bellas.
You guys are so cute.
Go get him, Gru-Gru!
Hello, Gru.
How's your transition coming?
You know, from world's worst villain
to world's worst agent?
That's hilarious.
You should be on TV.
That's right. You were!
But then you got canceled!
What about that?
What? Girls!
Dance fight!
Alpha Team, the diamond is secure.
Come and pick up the package.
Copy that.
Alpha Team in approach.
Gru!
Did you actually think
I was unconscious?
It's called acting, hoser.
And clearly, I've still got it!
I've been a bad boy!
Freeze! Don't move!
Son of a Betamax!
Go, go! Get him!
He's getting away!
This isn't over, Gru.
You hear me? This is not over.
Yeah? Well, I still have the diamond.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday to...
Happy birthday, dear Dan.
Happy birthday to you.
Hey?
La Macumba?
Si.
Ta-da!
Ta-da la Macumba!
I can't believe,
Bratt got away again.
How is this possible? How?
And it's not just that he got away,
It is he's so smug about it.
I've been a bad boy!
Edna, hey!
Looking hot today.
Got... cats on you.
And it was so humiliating,
dangling there
in the bubble-gum Speedo.
And I didn't have time
to go to the gym this week,
and I had a big breakfast.
And was feeling a little bloated.
You know what?
He's not even worth talking about.
I don't even want to waste
another breath about the guy.
And another thing!
Next time I see Bratt,
I will moonwalk
all over his stupid face!
Thank you all for coming
at such short notice.
It is with great sadness
that I inform you that as of today,
I am retiring as head of the AVL.
No!
Your new leader is coming
directly from head office.
Effective immediately.
She is the very gifted,
very ambitious,
Miss Valerie da Vinci.
As I look out over all your faces,
I am flooded with so many memories.
Boy! This is a snooze fest!
Excuse me, this is my last...
Blah, blah, blah! We understand.
You're old, you're fat, you're done.
Let me breathe in.
Broke a little sweat, there.
First order of business.
Which one of you losers is Agent Gru?
That would be me.
Although, I don't know
if I'd say loser, per se.
Kind of is...
it's the girls!
Not a good time.
Hey!
Yes, sir!
Ma'am?
You're making me nervous.
How could you let Balthazar Bratt,
the AVL's most wanted villain,
just get away?
That is the opposite
of what we do here!
Ok, ok.
Yes, maybe he got away.
Again.
But he didn't get the diamond.
And I am this close to bringing him in.
This close.
Interesting.
You're fired!
What?
That's totally not fair.
Gru is a great agent!
You know what? If you fire him,
you're gonna have to fire me,
sister-sister.
And do you really wanna do that?
Do ya?
No, no, no!
Well, I guess she did.
Honey, you didn't have to do that.
I know how much you love your job.
Well, I love other things more.
You know, we're gonna
have to tell the girls.
Can you do it?
The whole mom thing
is still kind of new to me.
Sure.
Hello?
Aloha!
This is unexpected.
Well, you never got
to go on a honeymoon, so...
We made you dinner!
It's a luau!
We got pineapples
and coconuts and ukuleles!
The soup of the day.
Madame and Monsieur.
The gummy bears were my idea.
Looks too good to even eat.
Am I right?
But I made it for you.
Good soup!
I love the combination...
of gummy bears,
and meat.
I'm gonna hold it in my mouth.
Because it's so good,
I don't wanna swallow it.
So, how was work?
Did you take that guy down?
Did anything explode?
Well, actually,
today, Lucy and I,
were invited to not work,
at the AVL anymore.
No!
You got fired?
No! No, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes.
But don't worry.
I'm sure we'll get new jobs.
Real soon.
Even better ones.
What's better than being
super-cool secret agents?
I know! You could gamble online!
That's what Katie's dad does.
Ok. We will definitely look into that.
That's a good suggestion.
And let's not go over
to Katie's house anymore.
Guys! I don't think you heard me right.
No, no, no, no, no.
This does not mean that we are
going back to being villains.
Pignoo flacomico.
Ok, alright. I get it.
Look, I know it's been
a little tough lately.
Especially with Dr. Nefario,
accidentally freezing
himself in carbonite.
But our life of crime is over!
Mel!
Mel, you're with me on this, right?
Looka.
Bueno.
Pignoo.
Minions!
Po les Pignoo!
Pignoo! Pignoo! Pignoo! Pignoo!
Guys, listen to me!
Read my lips!
Lissa me lipo.
Pomodoro la comquit.
What? What?
What did I say?
It's not kumquit?
Ok.
Pomodoro la kumquat.
Didusay kumquat palano?
No les palano.
Don't take that tone with me!
We're not going back to villainy.
No villainy?
Yes! And I don't want
to hear another word about it.
Look, if you guys don't stop right now,
there will be consequences.
Wat, vazy molo!
Hey! Don't say anything
you're going to regret.
Noo les famos, les quittas!
Ciao Belo.
What? You quit?
You're serious? Come on!
Putchy?
Dave! Jerry!
Great news, guys.
You have been promoted.
You're in charge now.
Not bad.
Viva! Solo!
Yipee!
Rooba. Rooba. Rooba.
Jeesh!
Monsieur Pompeux!
To what do we owe the presence
of the world's foremost gem expert?
The chief of police sent me.
He was concerned that during
the recent heist attempt,
the Dumont Diamond was
replaced with a phony.
Olala!
You have been duped!
What? We have?
Yes.
By me!
But, what is...
Oh no! Help!
I've been a bad boy!
Or should I say...
Je suis un mauvais garçon!
I'm a bad boy!
Hey, Gru.
What you doing down here?
In the dark.
Alone.
Nothing. Just thinking.
You ok?
Yes. Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
It's just...
I don't know. I guess I just feel like
a failure.
Like I don't have a purpose anymore.
Hey, mister, you are not a failure.
If only I could have nailed Bratt.
So many times, I almost had him.
But now I'll never get the chance,
because I have been kicked to the curb.
Gru, you've got to let this go.
It's time to look forward.
Things will get better. I promise.
Colé Céré. Colé Céré.
Papilion lapavaka.
Papilion.
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
Colé Céré.
Young people?
Would you tell me
how to get to this address?
Cé la casa des Minions.
I'm looking for a Mr. Gru.
Gru pignoo to bad.
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Ciao!
To bad.
Idiots.
No! Kyle!
Stop! Kyle, let go!
No! No!
You've got to be kidding me!
Lucy, did you se...
He helps you if you have nightmares.
And he's really good to snuggle with.
No, no, no. Agnes! Agnes!
So take good care of him.
Thank you!
Agnes, what are you doing? You...
You sold your unicorn?
Well, I just wanted to help,
since you don't have a job.
I got two whole dollars for it.
Excuse me?
Sorry, buddy, the sale's over.
Yes, but this will only take a...
Hey!
Eyebrows, get off the lawn.
Yeah, but...
Hey, could you...
of course.
Now, as I was saying, I...
Goodbye!
Listen, Agnes, you don't need to worry.
We're going to be fine.
For real?
For real.
Now come on, let's pack this stuff up.
Seriously?
Buddy, you're not getting the hint.
Excuse me, Mr. Gru,
but I really must have a word with you.
How do you know my name?
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Fritz.
Good puppy.
And I am inquiring on behalf
of your twin brother, Dru.
He needs your help.
What? Twin brother?
Twin brother?
Tin bruther?
Ja.
He would like to fly you
to Freedonia to meet him.
Your father has recently
passed away,
and...
Ok, cuckoo.
I'm sorry, but my dad died,
when I was a baby,
and I don't have any brother.
You got the wrong guy.
Really?
Well, then,
how do you explain this?
Bellissimo!
Hello, Gru.
Hi, Mom.
It's important to keep active
in one's golden years.
There you are, you cutie, you.
These are my diving instructors.
Vincenzo und Paolo.
Ciao, boys.
So, what do you want?
Mom, do I have a twin brother?
How did you find out?
Who told you?
Wait, what? It's true?
You never told me I had a brother!
And you told me that Dad died of
disappointment when I was born.
Ja, ja...
That was the agreement.
Agreement?
What are you talking about?
Shortly after you and
your brother were born,
your father and I divorced.
We each took one son
to raise on our own
and promised never
to see each other again.
Obviously,
I got second pick.
I have a brother!
Hey, girls! How are things in Row B?
I put together some fun
activities for the trip!
Who is up for some gin rummy?
Yeah...
We're good.
Ok.
I'll just sit here and play solitaire.
I hope I win.
I wonder what Dru will be like.
Maybe we'll have the twin thing
when you can read
each other's minds, no?
How cool would that be?
Super cool!
Freedonia! Freedonia! Freedonia!
Hi, piggy, piggy!
Look at that house!
It's like a castle!
I can't wait to meet my brother!
What's with all the pigs?
This is the family business.
The largest pig farm in
the whole of Freedonia.
Ok, nice pig.
No! That's my private part!
This pig has issues!
Please, come in.
This is amazing!
It's like the Sistine Chapel!
But with pigs.
My brother!
Gru!
Dru!
Brother! I am hugging you!
I'm so happy!
After all of these years,
finally I'm meeting you!
Yup. Alright. Good.
Look at that.
You must be the beautiful wife.
Beautiful?
Stop it.
Sweet talker.
How is my brother finding a wife
like you when he is so bald?
I'm joking!
These must be my nieces!
You're Agnes!
You are small with big eyes.
And it makes me wanna
put you into my pocket.
You can't do that!
I'm too big.
Edith! I can tell that you are
a little mischievous.
We're gonna have to make
a little trouble later.
I already have!
Please!
Why are you doing that?
Fist bump for mischievous behavior!
And Margo.
You are so mature!
I'm guessing what you're 15?
15?
She's 12. She looks 12
and will always be 12.
So, Dru, this place is amazing!
I mean, you just walk through
the doors and you're like...
it's nice, I guess, sure.
I'm not really into things.
This is so cool!
Look at that!
My gosh! He's even got a helicopter!
This is the best!
Yes, the best!
Alright, let's go home now.
Home? Why?
I don't know. This guy with
the mansion and the cars
and all of the hair,
with the silky smooth, luxurious hair.
I feel worse than I did before I came.
But, he's your brother, Gru.
Give this a chance.
I was thinking, while Gru and I
catch up on some brother stuff,
you girls should go with Fritz.
He has a surprise for you!
Yay! Awesome!
I love surprises!
This is perfect!
Mother-daughter bonding time.
Let's do it!
Bye! You boys have fun!
Whoopi!
Now you can be as evil
as Balthazar Bratt
with the Evil Bratt action figure.
Featuring music-activated
breakdance mode.
Also featuring bubblegum-launching
shoulder pads!
And the all-new Mega Diamond Laser!
No more math!
I've been a bad boy!
The Mega Diamond Laser does not
actually incinerate books.
How could Hollywood cancel a show
that produced toys like this, Clive?
Evil Bratt was a masterpiece!
Does no one value true art anymore?
It's a disgrace and a travesty, sir.
Well, now that I've got the diamond,
it's payback time.
It's too bad Gru,
won't be around to try and stop me.
Wait! No, it's not.
I hate that dweeb!
And you, Hollywood!
This time, I'm canceling you
and all the losers who rejected me!
Piggy, piggy!
So, how are things going
for you career-wise?
Great! So, so great!
Crushing it.
Well, I've got something that I think
you will find very interesting.
Hold onto your face, brother.
Y-ah! Ya! Ya!
Y-ah!
Salami.
Hey, wonton ya Salami.
Si. Si.
Ya Salami.
Come on! Come on!
What is all this?
The pig farm was just a cover
for the real family business.
Hey.
It's Gru with boobs.
Now, feast your eyes on.
Dad's lair!
Ta-da!
Wait.
So, our dad was a villain?
No, no, no, not just a villain.
One of the greatest of all time!
He was known as the Bald Terror!
That's him?
Our dad?
He was so proud of you.
And what a great villain you were.
He was?
But me,
not so much.
To Dad,
I was just a failure.
He never thought I had
what it took to be a villain.
But now, you can help me
prove him wrong!
Brother,
teach me the art of villainy!
No.
No, no, no. I can't do that.
What? But it's our family tradition!
You can't say no to that!
Look, I'm sorry.
I left that life behind me. End of story.
Ok. I understand.
I wonder what this does.
Holy moley!
Dad's villain wheels!
Pretty slick?
Hey, you wanna take her out
for a spin, just for some fun?
Look out!
What a beautiful day!
Zero to 400 in three seconds.
Able to withstand a nuclear blast.
Armed to the teeth.
Ok, that's pretty nice.
And it's a hybrid. Look out!
Help me!
I am not enjoying this.
What is going on here?
Welcome to the annual
Freedonian Cheese Festival.
Go!
Look, look! Look at all the candies!
Lucy, can we get these? Please.
Ok, but only one each. I mean it.
Oh, man.
No, I don't.
Get as many as you want.
I don't care.
Yeah!
Awesome!
What?
Well, it's ok to tell them no,
sometimes too, you know?
Moms need to be tough.
Right, right. Tough. Good one.
I can totally do that.
You know, still figuring
out this mom thing.
Getting my sea legs, matey!
It's a unicorn!
Can we go in there?
Please, please, please, please!
Sure! Yeah!
You know, but first let's...
Look!
It's a traditional Freedonian dance.
How amazing does that look?
♪ Say, say, say cheese! ♪
Cheese! I love this.
The little girls go and get the
cheese from the little boys.
That's adorable!
Look at that poor little guy.
With his little boots.
Nobody picked him.
Margo, why don't you go up there?
No way!
Ok.
Wait a minute.
No!
Go take a bite of his cheese, young lady.
Right now!
What?
I'm being tougher, you know?
Like you said.
No! I meant be tougher on them.
Not me!
Come on, just do it.
What's the worst that could happen?
Fine.
Hey, there. I'm Margo.
Hello, Margo!
I am Niko.
Would you like some of my cheese?
♪ Say, say, say cheese! ♪
Yes! Thank you, Margo. Thank you!
Thank you!
Bam! I am a great mother!
Did you see that, girls?
I laid down the...
Oh no! Where are they?
Agnes? Edith?
Hello.
Look! A unicorn horn!
My little brain is going to explode!
Agnes, that's fake.
It's real, alright.
That horn came from the Crooked Forest.
The only place on earth,
where unicorns still live.
Laugh, laugh, all of you.
They all think I'm crazy.
But I'm telling you,
I saw one once.
With my own eye.
Wait, wait, wait.
You saw a for-real live unicorn?
What did it look like?
Did you pet it?
Did it smell like candy?
Was it fluffy?
It was so fluffy,
I thought I was gonna die.
Do you think maybe
I could find one, too?
They say if a maiden pure of heart
goes into the Crooked Forest,
the unicorn will come,
and be hers.
Forever.
Agnes!
Goal!
Excuse me.
Girls, don't worry. I'm here.
Are you ok?
Yeah, we're fine.
Are you?
Unicorns are really real!
And I'm gonna find one!
Sorry. Went a little mama bear on ya.
You know, I heard a scream and...
Yeah, ok, have a good one.
Wait for me here.
Stop that! You kicked me.
Hey! Hey! What are you doing?
Did you just steal candies? Yes!
That's a lot of effort for two lollipops.
No! The police!
What do we do? What do we do?
Come on! This is gonna be fun!
The police are gonna get us!
I'm freaking out!
Brakes!
Cops!
Stop Police!
They're back!
Alright!
Like this!
Man, that was crazy!
We were so close to getting busted.
Tell me about it.
I thought you were going
to pee your pants.
I did!
You did!
Mel, tofa.
Hey Mel.
Laba city, la papaya, noo la potato.
Hey, Mel la potato?
La pizza. Pala komay.
Noo les tofa. Pa payé.
Pizza! Pizza! Pizza!
Hey! What are you doing?
Intruders! Intruders!
Pizza! Pizza!
There they are! Stop!
Hey, you, don't move!
Halt!
Call for backup!
Komay. Komay.
Les pula la carbonara.
Oula.
Happy too les mocha.
Do it, do it.
No, No, no, no, no. No.
No, No, no, no.
♪ Pito Papa Milo Mila ♪
♪ Taka Tiki Poulé Tika ♪
♪ Cépa Lajoi Démi Toka ♪
♪ Lana Moulé Macaréna ♪
♪ Pao Lettus Pabo Pati Mélé ♪
♪ Cépa Maka Gusta Mami Lébel ♪
♪ Méla Moustache Ella Pika Mucha ♪
♪ Moka Coca Pila Caca ♪
♪ Fissa Bella La Massala ♪
♪ Papa Mama Loca Pipa ♪
♪ Pola Gusta La Rumbada ♪
♪ Chépa Koda Mila Toka ♪
♪ Bocca Pizza La Lasagna ♪
♪ Kika Lapo Maka Bomba ♪
♪ Bella Mira La Bologna ♪
♪ Pito Papa Milo Mila Taka Tiki Poulé Tika ♪
Get them!
Go! Go!
♪ Cépa Lajoi Démi Toka ♪
♪ Lana Moulé Macaréna ♪
♪ Moka Coca Pila Caca ♪
♪ Fissa Bella La Massala ♪
♪ Papa Mama Loca Pipa ♪
♪ Pola Gusta La Rumbada ♪
♪ Moka Coca Pila Caca ♪
♪ Fissa Bella La Massala ♪
♪ Papa Mama Loca Pipa ♪
♪ Pola Gusta La Rumbada ♪
♪ Chépa Koda Mila Toka ♪
♪ Bocca Pizza La Lasagna ♪
♪ Moka Coca Pila Caca ♪
♪ Fissa Bella La Massala ♪
♪ Papa Mama Loca Pipa ♪
♪ Pola Gusta La Rumbada ♪
Yeah!
Hey, you! Freeze! Don't move!
Hands in the air!
Face it, Gru. Villainy is in your blood.
You can't tell me you
don't miss the rush.
A little?
Maybe a little.
And now you've got
the chance to get back on top.
Get your mojo back.
Become Gru again.
How awesome would that be?
Please, come on.
Just one heist.
There's got to be something
out there, somewhere
that you still wanna steal.
There is something.
How about we steal
the largest diamond in the world?
Yes! I love it!
Thank you, brother!
Thank you from the bottoms
of my heart.
You know what?
We should do something to celebrate!
I've got the perfect idea.
Fritz, my good fellow, could you
get me another napkin, please?
Yes. Of course, Miss Edith.
Hey, where are Gru and Dru?
Here we are!
How's it going?
It's me! Gru.
And me, Dru.
I hug everybody whether
they like it or not.
Why are they pretending
to be each other?
What's for dinner?
I probably won't like it.
I'm so grumpy all the time.
Hey. I laugh a lot.
And I'm kind of an idiot!
I'm busting a gut!
Look at them! They had no idea!
Total burn.
Look, it's me, Gru!
And I'm Dru!
We switched places!
It's so nice to see you two
are getting along.
We're getting...
Along perfectly.
Wait. Did we... Just finish...
Each... Other's...
Sentences? Sentences?
That's delightful.
Not creepy at all.
And you're gonna stop now though, right?
Sorry, it's a twin thing.
So,
what did you guys do today?
Nothing.
Ok. What does it...
All done!
Pardon me!
Out of the way! Good night, everybody!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Put the brakes on.
What's the rush?
I need to get to bed so I can
wake up and find a unicorn!
Good night!
What was that about?
Agnes thinks she's gonna find a
real unicorn in the woods tomorrow.
She's totally freaking out.
I feel like someone's got
to tell her the truth.
Not it!
Don't worry. Parenting 101.
I got this.
And please bless that
when I find the unicorn
he'll want to come home with me,
and sleep in my room.
And that I can ride him
to school every day.
And he'll use his magical powers
to help me do math.
Amen.
Hi, Gru.
Hey. So...
big day tomorrow.
Yeah, I'm finally gonna
get to see a unicorn.
For reals.
If I do, can I bring it home?
Please?
Yeah. Sure.
Tell you what, every unicorn you find,
you can bring it home.
I'd better build a big pen, right?
But, you know,
there is a chance that
you might not find one.
It might not be good
unicorn-finding weather.
They're tricky to find them.
And...
I don't know. Maybe ju...
Maybe...
unicorns don't...
really ex...
explore that part of the woods.
But... But the man said,
a maiden could find one
if she was pure in heart.
And I'm pure in heart, right?
The purest.
Can we stop talking now?
I need to get to sleep.
Good night, sweetie.
Good night, Gru.
♪ Unicorns, I love them. ♪
I'm ok.
Hey! Give that back!
No! Run!
We've been waiting a long time.
Can we...
No! No!
No, please!
Gru?
La broka.
Buddies!
Googna pota.
Roma allé Gru!
Si!
Gru! Gru!
♪ Because I'm training for, the big day. ♪
♪ Nobody's gonna stop me ♪
♪ Because I am super sassy. ♪
♪ Super sassy, super sassy. ♪
What's today's plan, boss?
What's the plan?
Silly robot.
I'll show you the plan!
Time to watch a very special
episode of Evil Bratt,
to see exactly what I'm gonna
do to stupid Tinseltown.
This week on Evil Bratt.
It's a giant Evil Bratt robot!
Open fire!
I have him in my sights!
Nice try, coppers!
Chew on this!
He's shooting his super sticky,
self-inflating gum!
Run!
Gum one, gum all!
Gum one, gum all.
Seriously, how did this
show never win an Emmy?
And now, it's your turn
to shine, my diamond!
Hey, Clive. I guess you
could say our plan was
out of this world!
Now, that's entertainment!
Come on! Let's make it a reality!
Here we are, in the dark
and creepy Crooked Forest
in search of the mythical unicorn.
For some reason.
And here she is!
The fearless unicorn hunter seeking...
Edith, stop it!
You're gonna scare away the unicorn.
If, somehow, we actually
find a unicorn,
I'm gonna film it and get rich.
Look over there!
This is it!
This is where we're gonna see it.
Unicorns, here we come.
What's that for?
Bait! Duh.
Come on!
Now, all we have to do is wait.
Ok, this is Bratt's lair.
It may not look like much,
but this place is armed with some of
the most high-tech
weaponry known to man.
It's considered impenetrable.
But a piece of cake for us,
right, brother?
Yes. This is not like stealing lollipops.
His security system can detect an
air assault, from any direction.
Ouch! No! Ouch!
Please, stop! Ouch!
So we'll have to approach low
and close to the water.
Next.
Then there are these deadly spikes.
Geronimo!
Covered with enough poison
to blow your mind.
Literally.
Good to know.
So here's the plan.
You're the getaway driver.
So you'll wait in the boat...
Wait, hold on! Wait in the boat?
But, I wanna be in on the actions!
Dru, the getaway driver is the
most crucial part of any plan.
Do you know how hard it is
doing nothing, touching nothing
when all of that adrenaline is
coursing through your veins
and you must wait?
Can I count on you?
Yeah.
I guess so.
So, I'll climb up to the cube
and enter here.
Then once I'm inside,
find the diamond.
I've underestimated Bratt before.
It's not going to be easy.
I think we can handle it.
Dad's villain suits!
This will make us unstoppable!
Ay, chihuahua!
I call the black one.
It's go time!
Hello.
Hi!
Hello, mother of Margo.
I am Niko.
I present you with pig to confirm
my engagement to your daughter.
Hey, what now?
What's going on?
Remember little boots?
Hello, my schmoopsie poo.
Oh! Hey!
He seems to think you're engaged.
What? We're not engaged.
Look Niko,
you seem like a very nice boy,
with a very nice pig.
But you're not engaged.
Ok? It's not happening.
I understand.
Who was I kidding?
A dumpling like me with
a goddess like you.
But I promise,
I will never forget you, Margo.
Never.
I'm pretty sure I won't forget you either.
Bye. Bye, Niko.
That was crazy.
That was totally humiliating.
Taking a bite of that cheese was the
stupidest thing I've ever done.
Why did I listen to you?
Right. But it's over now, so...
Here we go. Niko...
You refuse my son's engagement pig?
What?
May you and your daughter
die a slow death
and be buried with onions.
Alright, lady, that's it!
Nobody...
Nobody curses my daughter!
Ya got that?
Because if you mess with Margo,
you mess with me!
And I promise,
you do not wanna mess with me.
Do you understand me?
Yes. Yes.
Good. Now get!
Bruce forvien.
Topolo minazliva.
Look, Margo I think we just need to...
Yes!
I have to tell Gru!
Can we go back now?
Already?
Just a couple more hours.
We have to be home
before it gets dark.
I don't understand.
I did exactly what the man said.
You mean that one-eyed scar-faced
man that everybody laughed at?
Yeah, it makes no sense.
Look Agnes,
maybe we're not...
My whole life has been
building to this moment.
It's a...
Unicorn!
I can't believe it!
I'm gonna name you Lucky!
Lucky, stop it!
Yeah, I'll let someone else
burst her bubble.
Look at us!
Two brothers pulling a heist!
And that diamond will make us
the richest,
most powerful villains in the world!
Right, brother?
Right. Yep, yeah.
Bravo! Bravissimo!
You're amazing! I'm so sorry.
I'm so embarrassed.
I was very rude.
And you were always such a gentleman.
You did it!
You did it! You got our jobs back!
What? Yeah, right. Sure.
Look. We're here!
I'm going in. Take the wheel.
I still don't see why I can't go with you.
Hey, hey! We discussed this.
Now is not the time
to mess with the plan.
Fine.
Hey, brother!
What? I told you, you are
supposed to stay with the boat!
I didn't think you meant that literally.
What other way could I have meant it?
Alright. Let's move.
Just follow my lead.
Got it.
Help me!
No! The poison spikes!
I'm gonna be impaled!
I'm ok.
I miss the Minions.
Come on!
Coming.
Come on.
It's a scanning device.
Quick! Camouflage mode.
Freeze! And close your eyes!
And cover your mouth!
Ok, take my hand.
Follow me.
Look out!
You were right. I should
have stayed in the boat.
My stomach feels all queasy.
I should not have eaten that pot pie.
Hey, hey, relax.
You're gonna be just fine.
I got your back.
Come on. This way.
Gru népala. Gru nékooga.
Go, go, go!
Peter, hey.
Cé parla.
Hein? Ok. Ok.
Go, go, go!
Hey comme.
Bello goodirl gooden
Kleposup palapo nutela. Comi...
Cava. Cava. Cava.
Hey buddies!
Buddies!
Looks like it's right above us.
Ok, what do I do?
Should I wait in the vent?
No, come with me.
Dru, get off the bed!
Yes, I'd like to thank the Academy...
I can help.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What? I can do it.
Don't! Don't! Don't!
Why, yes.
Yes, Molly Ringwald,
I will take you to the prom.
What? Who? Where? What?
Who's there? Who is there?
♪ 99 of red balloons. ♪
Almost forgot!
Over here.
Stay close.
What?
Dolls.
Looks like Bratt was the only one
stupid enough to buy this junk.
I used to have one of these!
Hey! Come on.
Alright.
We're getting close.
From now on,
every move must be made
with total precision and purpose.
Gum!
Focus!
We're after the diamond,
not the bubblegum.
Got it!
Yum.
This way!
And now, to put this where it belongs.
What...
Look at it, Clive.
It's beautiful!
Will you please shut up?
He's gonna spot us!
Spit it out! Spit it out!
I told you not to touch anything!
Intruders! Intruders! Intruders!
Freeze, dipsticks!
Gru?
There's two of you now?
Then this will be twice as much fun.
Gru.
Give me back my diamond!
Total lockdown!
Go get them, Bratt Pack!
They're gonna get us!
Run!
No!
What does that mean?
Are we gonna die?
We're gonna die! Dru!
What?
Hey, guys. Hold on!
Lucy!
Thank you for saving us.
Look! We got the diamond
and we're going to...
Take it to the AVL
and get our jobs back.
Wait!
What? That's amazing!
And the best part is, you'll never...
ever go behind my back,
ever again.
Right, honey bear?
Yeah! Yeah, right.
Lesson learned.
I'll get the girls and start packing.
And tell them the good news!
We're getting our jobs back. Yeah!
Yes! Yes! Go tell the girls.
Dru...
No! No way!
We can't give the diamond back!
No. I have to.
No, you don't!
Yes, I do.
Give it!
No!
What is wrong with you?
You kicked me!
You... You lied to me!
Hey, I would have told you the truth.
But you're too much of
a wimp to handle it.
That's it. I'm out of here.
You have no right to take that.
We stole it together.
Together?
You got to be kidding me.
You did nothing but screw
up the whole time.
I got this in spite of you.
Yeah? At least I didn't
get fired from my job
like a total loser.
At least I had a job.
What have you accomplished
that was so great?
I'll tell you what. Nothing!
No wonder Dad thought you
were such a failure.
We are no longer brothers.
That's fine with me.
♪ Maladica Lanovo Ladina ♪
♪ Lalanovo Ladina ♪
♪ Lachich Keybab La Risoto ♪
♪ Taka Pousse Lanovo Ladina ♪
♪ Taka Mange Duballon Ladina ♪
♪ Ce Duballon Ladina ♪
♪ Lachich Keybab La Risoto ♪
♪ Lalala Dolce Laviva ♪
Gru!
I found a unicorn!
My life is complete!
Honey, that's...
That's not actually a unicorn.
But, but, he has one horn.
I'm... I'm sorry, sweetie but...
he's just a goat.
Life is just like that sometimes.
We're hoping for a unicorn,
and we get a goat.
Well, you know what?
Lucky is the best goat
in the whole wide world!
Look at that face!
I just want to squeeze it.
I'll take this.
You've been a bad boy, Gru.
Can you get the rest of the suitcases?
Come on, girls. Let's go!
♪ Let's get physical, physical. ♪
Change of plans, girls.
Instead of going home...
Eyebrows!
We're going to Hollywood!
Now, that's what I call acting.
Let's go, Clive! We've got
a giant robot waiting!
Lucy?
Gru! Gru!
Bratt! He took the girls!
What? No!
Dru! Dru!
Go away!
I don't wanna talk to you.
Bratt has the girls!
Listen, brother what...
About what I said.
No, I'm the one...
But I should not have...
I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Gru.
Look out!
What is that?
Mel le planeur!
Le pla...
Ola! Caramba!
Caramba!
Mel?
Gru?
Velachi comeback doc.
Gru! Wait up!
Gru!
Hello, Hollywood!
I'm back and bigger than ever.
I'm scared!
Thank you. Thank you so...
No! No!
No, you can't leave me here!
I'm famous!
Clive, arm the canons.
Chew on this!
Hey, mullet head! Let us out!
Don't worry, girls.
I've prepared a front row seat for you.
Agnes!
Once again, I win and Gru loses!
Enjoy the show, girls.
What in the heck?
I hope the girls are ok.
Bratt! Bratt at nine o'clock...
No! Three o'clock!
He's on the left!
No! I've seen this episode!
He's going to bubblegum the whole
city and send it up into space!
Hurry!
This is it! This is it!
Lights! Camera!
Laser!
Yeah!
Look!
I've got the girls.
You two, go take care of Bratt.
Wait! What are you doing?
Look, you guys, it's Lucy!
Lucy, over here! Help! Help us!
Mama's coming, girls.
Lucy! Lucy!
We're up here!
Look at that laser go.
I love it when a plan comes together.
It's Gru!
Get ready, Bratt.
You're about to be blasted back
to the '80s!
We got him!
No!
Don't worry.
There's more where that came from.
It'll take more than that to stop me.
Bratt Pack, go get that barf bag.
Incoming!
You little...
Get away! Get out of there!
Quick, jump!
Bonus!
Did you see that, Clive?
All gone.
Buh-bye, Wonder Twins.
Olala!
Washi giant bubbles!
Help!
Hang on!
Hang on, girls! I've got you!
I can't! I'm slipping!
No!
Got ya!
Thank you, Lucy!
Let's go! We're not safe yet.
Minions!
Help papa oti lapatira.
Picky kaya la popote.
Yaka pati la popote.
Popi la popote!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Pata cool.
Look at what we have here.
Sorry, Gru.
This is going to be a total burn!
Oh no! No, no, no, no, no, no!
I've been a bad boy!
Nobody messes with my brother!
What? What's happening? No!
Dru!
Hold on! I'm coming.
You've ruined everything!
And now,
it's time to die.
Any last words, Gru?
You know what?
I got two words for you.
Dance fight.
It is on like Donkey Kong.
I am going to enjoy this.
Enough!
My turn!
Game over!
Is this what you're looking for?
No!
Curse you, Gru!
Curse you!
Leo! Par laba.
Robert, too ala pick.
Chop panapick.
Dru?
Dru!
Hey! We did it!
Yes, we did, brother.
Gru!
Uncle Dru!
Gru! Girls!
Gru!
Hey, Mel.
Welcome back.
Love you, Mom.
I'm a mom.
I'm a mom!
Coca!
Pignoo!
Pignoo lepata. Pignoo!
Boys,
time for bed!
We're back at work in the morning.
I'm coming, sweetie.
Good night, Lucy.
See you tomorrow, brother.
Hey, I'm back on the job.
So no villainy tonight?
Got it?
I make no promises.
Love you!
Right.
I love you, too.
Alright, every...
Go! Go! Go to bed!
Hey! Guys! Come on!
What... What is happening?
It's coming from outside!
Hey! I thought we said no more villainy!
Sorry, brother!
Somebody's got to keep
the family tradition alive, right?
Let's get him.
Honey, he's my brother.
We'll give him a five-minute head start.
By LESAIGNEUR
Sync & corrections July 2020