Download Hindi dubbed audio only form
http://hindidubaudio.blogspot.com
Ha Ha Ha
Three weeks, and we're
still no close to cracking this.
Right! Bring him in!
Yes, sir.
This is the best party ever!
Oh, no!
A dragon is approaching!
Ahhh!!
Fear not, for here come
the valiant knights to save us!
What do you mean
she's not coming?
I have a backyard full of these little girls who are
counting on the visit from the Fairy Princess!
Listen! I do not want a refund! I want the
Fairy Princess! Please, please, I'm begging you!
You know what? I hope you can sleep at night,
you crusher of little girls' dreams!
Oh, oh, when's the
Fairy Princess coming?
Any minute now!
Yayy!
Stall them!
Pertunjukan Sulap
Whoa, whoa, okay, okay...
Alright, that's enough
of the magic show!
Aww!
Wait, did you hear that?
It sounded like the twinkling
sounds of magical fairy dust.
It's the Fairy Princess,
She's coming!
Look!
It is I, GruTinkerbell!
The most magical Fairy
Princess of all!
I am here to
wish Princess Agnes,
A very happy birthday!
How come you're so fat?
Because...
My house is made of candy!
And sometimes, I eat instead
of facing my problems!
How come you ha---
Okay, time for cake!
Yay!
Thank you, GruTinkerbell!
You're the best Fairy
Princess ever!
You are welcome, little girl!
I know it's really you, Gru.
I'm just pretending
for the other kids.
Hey there, Gru, Mister
Life of the party!
Hello, Jillian!
So, I'm gonna go out on a
limb here, but my friend Natalie,
is recently single, and...
No, no, no! Get off
the limb, right now!
No limb.
Come on! She's a riot!
She sings karaoke, she
has a lot of free time,
looks aren't that
important to her!
Look, Jill, it's not happening.
Seriously, I'm fine.
Okay, fine, forget Natalie.
How about my cousin Linda?
No.
Oh, I know someone whose
husband just died...
I'm sorry, I did
not see you there.
Or there.
Kyle, Kyle,
Kyle, stop! Stop doing your
business on the Petunias!
There you go, go
to Fred's. Go crazy.
Good boy.
Mr. Gru?
Wha, I didn't, wha.. Yes?
Hi! Agent Lucy Wilde
of the AVL.
Oh... oops!
Sorry.
You're gonna have to
come with me.
Oh, sorry, I'm--- Freeze Ray!
You know you really should announce your
weapons after you fire them, Mr. Gru.
For example...
Lipstick taser!
Oh, it works so good.
Ouch... Where is it...
Oh.. Sorry.
Ughh.. arghhh..
Get, in, there, you, big...
Whoa, curses...
Cannot feel...
Good afternoon, Mr. Gru.
Yeah...
I apologize for our
methods in getting you here.
I don't!
I'd do it again in a heartbeat!
I am not gonna lie,
I enjoyed that. Every second of it,
Gave me bit of a buzz, actually...
That's enough, Agent Wilde.
Sorry.
Okay, this is bogus!
I don't know who you
think you people are, but...
We are the Anti-Villain League.
An ultra secret organization dedicated
to fighting crime on a global scale.
Rob a bank, we're not interested.
Kill someone, not our deal.
But you were to melt the polar
ice caps, or vaporize Mount Fuji,
or even,
Steal the moon...
Then, we notice.
First of all, you got no
proof that I did that.
Second, after I did do
that, I put it back.
We're well aware of that, Mr. Gru.
That's why we brought you here.
I am the league director,
Silas Ramsbottom.
Heehee... Bottom.
Hilarious.
Agent Wilde...
Oh, me now?
Recently, an entire top secret lab
disappeared from the Arctic Circle.
Yeah. The entire lab, just...
Gone. Where did it go?
I don't care.
Hmm...
The lab was devoted to
experiments involving PX-41.
A transmutation serum.
What is PX-41, you ask?
Hmmm... it's pretty bad.
Look.
You usually don't see
that in bunnies.
As you could see,
In the wrong hands,
the PX-41 serum,
could be the most
devastating weapon on Earth.
Fortunately,
it has a very distinct
chemical footprint.
And, using the latest
chem tracking technology,
we found traces of it
in the Paradise Mall.
Huh.. A Mall.
Precisely.
And we believe that one of these
shop owners is a master criminal.
And that's where you come in. As an ex-villain,
you know how a villain thinks, and acts.
The plan is, to set you up
undercover at a shop in the mall,
where hopefully,
you'll be able to...
Okay! I see where
this is going!
impossible stuff,
But no, no.
I'm a father now. And,
a legitimate businessman.
I am developing a line of
delicious jams and jellies.
"Jams and jellies".
Oh, attitude!
That's right!
So thanks, but no thanks.
instead of tasing people,
and kidnapping them,
maybe you should just
give them a call!
Good day, Mr. Sheepbutt!
Ramsbottom.
Oh, yeah, like I
said it better!
Look, I probably shouldn't
be saying this, but...
Your work as a villain,
was kind of, amazing.
So if you ever wanna get back
to doing something awesome...
Give us a call.
Hey, I told you
guys to get to bed!
Oh, sorry.
So, when are you
going on your date?
What?
Remember? Ms. Jillian said she
was arranging a date for you.
Yeah, well, she is a nutjob
and I'm not going on any date.
Why not?
Are you scared?
Hey, did you guys see the
moon landing on TV?
Can you believe
it? It's so cool!
- Yeah, and you know what?
- Excuse me...
Lisa?
Hmmm.. Hey, Lisa,
I was wondering,
Gru touched Lisa!
Lisa's got Gruties!
Scared? Of what?
Women? No!
That's bonkers!
I just, I've no interest in going
on a date, that's all!
Case closed!
I'm not scared!
Of women.
Or dates.
Let's go to bed.
Goodnight, Edith.
Goodnight, Margo.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
Whoa, hold the horses,
who are you texting?
No one! Just my friend Avery.
Avery... Eh? Avery?
Is that a girl's name
or a boy's name?
Does it matter?
No! No, it doesn't matter,
unless it's a boy!
I know what makes you a boy.
Uhh, you do?
Your bald head.
Ohh. Yes.
It's really smooth.
Sometimes I stare at it,
and imagine a little
chick popping out.
Peep-peep-peep!
Goodnight, Agnes.
Never get older.
Hey, yo!
Hey, Tim, nice haircut!
Tommy, hang in there, baby!
It's almost Friday!
So, how's today's
batch, Dr. Nefario?
I developed a new formula which allowed me to
get every known kind of berry in a one flavor of jelly.
Arghhh... Ugh...
That is good!
Love the flavor of...
It's horrible, isn't it?
No, no!
Oh, we're making
great progress!
Here, try some.
Whoa... Okay,
Just because
everybody hates it,
doesn't mean it's not good!
Listen, Gru...
There's something I've been meaning
to talk to you about for some time now.
What, what's wrong?
I miss being evil.
Sinister plots,
large-scale crimes,
It's what I live for!
I mean, don't you think there's
more for our future than... jelly?
Well, I'm also considering
a line of jams.
Umm... The thing is, Gru...
I've now been
recruited elsewhere.
Dr. Nefario!
Oh, come on.
You're kidding, right?
This is a great
opportunity for me...
More evil...
Ah...
Very well...
Let us give you,
the proper send-off.
Minions!
The highest honor awarded,
to Dr. Nefario,
for your years of service,
the 21 Fart Gun Salute!
Uhh, I counted twenty-two.
Farewell, my friends.
This may take a while.
Go about your business!
I miss you already!
Ehh? Oh, Hello!
Are you sure we
can be doing this?
Yes, it's for his own good.
Okay, we need to
choose a picture.
No.
Scary.
Weird.
Ahh!!
What is that?
Good morning, girls, I have
an announcement to make!
Hey, what celebrity
do you look like?
Yuhh...
Bruce Willis.
Hmmm. No.
Humpty Dumpty!
Oooh, that one!
Ha .. ha...
Okay, what are you doing?
We're setting you
off for online dating!
Oh. Okay, what!?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, come on.
It's fun.
And it's time for you
to get out there.
No, stop. No one is ever
getting out there!
Ever!
Okay...
Now, for the announcement.
I have accepted a new job!
Wow, really?
Yes, I have been recruited,
by a top secret agency
to go undercover
and save the world.
You're gonna be a spy?
That's right, baby!
Gru's back in the game!
Gadgets, and weapons
and cool cars!
Awesome!
Are you really
gonna save the world?
Yes. Yes, I am.
Hmm ..
"Bake My Day".
Bleh..
Alright, here is the cupcake
recipe I got on the internet.
And don't go nuts
with the sprinkles!
Ahh!
Hiyatt .. hah
huh ..huh... huh...
Hiya ..hiya... hiyaa
Whooh!
Wasn't expecting that!
Or was I?
Oh, you, you got, you got...
Umm..Umm... A little...
Here, I'll get it.
Uhmm, it's spreading.
Alright, alright. I got this.
I got this.
I'll let you get it.
What you just saw there was a little something
new I've been working on. It's a combination of
Jujitsu, Krav maga,
Aztec warfare, and Krumping.
Okay, that's weird.
Why are you here?
On assignment from Silas.
I'm your new partner!
Yay!
What? No!
No, "Yay!".
Ramsbottom didn't say
anything about a partner.
Well, seems that because of your checkered
past, everyone else refused to work with you.
But not me!
I stepped up!
And I'm new. So I'm gonna have to
do what they tell me anyway.
Voila!
You know this guy?
Yes, he's one of my minions.
Ohh... I'm sorry.
I should have known.
You are free to go!
Earth to Dave!
You can leave now.
So, what do we got?
Who's on the list?
Fire Romantic
First suspect,
The head of Bloom and Top,
proprietor of the floral shop.
No, not her.
Okay.
Moving on...
Chad Kenny, owner
of "Stuff-a-Bear".
I don't think so.
Hello?
Buenos Dias, my friends!
I am,
Eduardo Perez.
Owner of "Salsa
Y Salsa" restaurant,
across the mall.
Now open for breakfast.
And you are?
Gru! And this is Lucy,
and we are closed.
This is just gonna
take un memento.
I am throwing a big
Cinco De Mayo party.
And I am going to need
200 of your best cupcakes.
Decorated with,
the Mexican Flag.
It looks something like this.
What do you think?
Ughh...
Anyway, I have to go. It's all settled.
I'll pick them up next week.
Have a good day!
Come by if you get
a chance, okay?
Ahh...
And welcome, to
the Mall family.
El Macho!
What?
This couldn't be!
Wha-- what couldn't be?
That guy, looks exactly
like the villain named,
"El Macho".
From about 20 years ago...
He was ruthless...
He was dangerous...
And as the name implies...
Very macho!
He had a reputation
Of pulling a heist, using
only his bare hands!
Ah, but sadly,
like all the greats,
El Macho was gone, too soon...
He died in the most
macho way possible.
A shark,
with 250,000 dynamites
strapped to his chest,
into the mouth,
of an active volcano!
It was glorious!
Yeah, sounds like
El Macho's pretty dead?
They never found the body.
Oh, no.
All that was ever retrieved,
was a pile,
of singed chest hair.
That face!
It has got to be El Macho.
So what do you say, you and
I break into his restaurant.
Tonight.
Yes, that's good.
Because I'm telling you, if anybody in
this place has the PX-41 serum,
it's him!
Alright, alright, homework done,
pyjamas on, teeth brushed, time for bed.
What's the big hurry?
I just, I have a
lot of work to do.
Work?
What kind of work?
Very important business.
So hugs, kisses.
Good night, sleep tight,
don't let the bed bugs...
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah...
Wha...?
But you said you'd help me practice
my part for the mother's day show.
Ahhh...
Fine, fine.
Let me hear it, quickly.
"She kisses my boo-boos."
She braids my hair.
My mother is beyond compare.
We love you,
mothers everywhere...
Wow, that was, something else!
I really like the way
you smiled at the end.
Let's try this one more time but
a tinsy-bit less like a zombie.
Okay?
Okay.
"She kisses my boo-boos.
She braids my hair..."
Perfect! Time to go.
I don't think I should do this.
Wha... what do you mean?
Why not?
I don't even have a mom.
Well, you don't need one
to do the show.
I mean,
you did the parents'
day pageant.
You haven't been in combat.
This is different.
Okay, well, then, maybe you
can just use your imagination.
You mean, I pretend
I have a mom?
Yes.
Right? You can do
that, can't you?
Yeah! I do that all the time.
Thanks, Gru!
Okay,
No, hey...
Please...
Kevin, Jerry, watch the
girls for me, okay?
Dave, Stewart, come this
way, with me. Come on!
Come on!
Yeah, yeah!
Download Hindi dubbed audio only form
http://hindidubaudio.blogspot.com
We're stealth ninjas.
We make no sound.
Right.
Hiyah!!
Alright, El Macho,
you're going down.
Wait! Wait.
What?
What are you doing?
Checking for laser
beam alarm triggers.
It's a restaurant!
You never know what kind of
booby traps this guy could've set.
Huh? Come on.
There are no booby traps.
Hah! Booby!
Ugh...
Huh... it's a chicken.
Are you lost, little guy?
You must be lost.
Hah! Some guard dog!
No, no, no!
Get it off of me!
Uh..uhh
uh... ah...
I got you!
Ohhh..oh
ahhhh... ahh...
I got it!
Ah...
Oh..
What is wrong
with that chicken?
Hey, that Pollo is Loco.
No?
Okay, let's go.
You getting anything?
No.
Not yet.
But hey, maybe you can find
something with these X-ray goggles!
Aww.
How is it working,
tell me, tell me!
Ahh!
Ooh!
What's wrong?
Something wrong?
That is an image I'll
never get out of my brain!
Blechh!
I knew it!
The serum's in here!
Ooh, then let's get it!
This is going to be good!
Ah...
A-ha!
What?
Secret Salsa Recipe
This is, Salsa?
Aww, man...
Somebody is going
to die tonight.
Oh.. Paulito!
Paulito,
Paulito, can you hear me?
Who would do this to
such a sweet little chicken?
Who's there?
Uh-oh!
You coming out, or
am I gonna go in?
Stop!
My eyes!
Gru, call in your munchkins!
Get it started, come get us!
Oooh. So long.
Over here!
Over here.
Over...
Here.
Hold tight!
I have you now!
Yay! Ice cream!
Gru! There he is.
Suspect number 8.
Floyd Eagle-san.
Well, Okay.
See if you can get closer.
Go.
Go!
Alright.
What the...
Oh, no...
That's not good!
Hey, wait!
Hi, Gru!
Oh, girls!
What are you doing here?
Well, we thought we'd
come visit you at work!
So, you're saving the world
in a garbage can?
Funny.
Hey! There you are!
Oh, who's this?
Lucy, these are my girls.
Margo, Edith and Agnes.
Girls, Lucy.
Lucy, Girls.
Hello.
Hi.
Are you single?
Oh.. Goodness.
Oh, hey! I have an idea,
Since Lucy and I have
lots of work to do,
Why don't you girls go
and explore the mall?
Here is some money, go buy
some useless mall junk.
Some headbands...
Are you gonna marry Lucy?
Are you out of your gorf?
No! She just works with me.
Plus you love her.
You love her!
You really, really love her!
Okay, stop.
These are sordid lies.
I don't even like her.
Now go have fun.
Almost forgot!
Good luck saving
the world! Bye!
Bye, Gru!
Kids, right?
They're, funny.
Those girls totally adore you.
I think you're a fun dad.
Huh. I'm pretty fun.
That's stealing.
Not if my wish was to ever
get a hundred free coins.
? This rainy day is temporary?
? The contrast is why we got him?
? Cause sunshine due is just a cloud?
? away way way way way way?
- ? The day could change?
- ?  change  change  change?
Cool glasses.
Thanks.
I'm Antonio.
I'm Margo.
I was just going
to get a cookie.
Care to join me?
Uhh... sure...
I'm, Margo.
Uh-Ahemm!
Umm... I'll catch up
with you guys later.
Bye!
Can I be the first
to say, "Eww"!
We got to go tell Gru!
Alright, I'm going in.
If it picks up any traces of the
serum, the center of your belt buckle
will make a sound like this.
Okay. I get it. I get it.
Welcome,
to "Eagle Hair Club".
It's about time you showed up.
Mr. Gru.
You know my name?
When someone moves into the
mall who is follically challenged,
I make it my business
to know all about them.
You're bald.
I know you don't
want to say it.
I'm getting nothing so far.
I think you need
to look around.
Wow, this looks interesting.
What is it?
I take it you're an art lover?
No serum.
Yeah, not so much.
Oh, how about this
impressive trinket?
- I hardly call it trinket, Mr. Gru. International...
- No, thank you.
Yeah, I don't care.
Hold on, I'm
picking up something.
Behind that wall!
Ahh... What do we have here?
These are my trial wigs.
You should take one.
No, thanks.
So what's on the other side
of the wall?
You are! Look at me! Focus!
Gru?
I promise, that this
wig will transform you,
from ugly, to irresistible.
Margo has a boyfriend!
And they're going on a date!
Date?! Boyfriend?! What?!
There she goes!
Oh, you're so funny.
Gross!
Look, they're in love!
Oh, no, no. Do not say that
they're--- no, no, no!
And my dream, is to one day,
play video games for a living.
Wow!
You're so complicated.
Margo.
What is going on here?
Oh, Gru.
Sellama, Antonio.
Mellamo, Margo.
Mellamo Lama Ding Dong.
Who cares.
Let's go.
Get it free on Tuesdays.
Papa!
So good to see you
again, mi compadre!
Oh.. I see you have
already met my father.
What the... father?
Si! Look at this crazy small
world we live in, eh?
Come, sit! Let me get
you something.
Oh, look at you!
Ha ha!
He likes me!
Oh... I'm sorry.
Paulito is usually,
very friendly.
He had a rough night.
Ha ha ha...
Well, we really
should be going.
Girls, come on.
That is a pity.
Young love, is beautiful, no?
No!
They are not in love. They
hardly know each other.
You are right,
cabeza del nuevo.
They must get to
know each other better.
Antonio,
Why don't you invite your
girlfriend? And her family.
To our Cinco De Mayo party.
No, no...
Si!
I'm sorry, El Macho?
Haven't we eliminated him as a
suspect after the whole "salsa" incident?
Yes, but there has been a new
development, and I'm telling
you, this is the guy.
You need to arrest
him immediately.
And!
His deviously charming son.
I'm pretty sure that
the son is involved too.
The son, also!
You got to get the son!
I think that the son
is the mastermind.
There's a look, there's a devilish
look in his eyes, and I don't like it!
Yes, but I don't believe
seeing any evidence...
Evidence, schmevidence, I go with
my gut, and my gut tells me,
that this guy is El Macho.
Lock him up,
lock up the son,
don't forget about the son!
The kid, gives me the creeps!
Oh, dear, oh dear, oh dear...
But, on the less
crazy side of things,
Gru discovered traces of the
serum at Eagle Hair Club!
Hmm. Interesting.
Yeah! And you know who
made that happen?
Huh?
This guy. Nailed it.
Amazing, right?
No, I mean...
Sure, but it's not him!
It is El Macho...
Mr. Gru,
Please...
No, it is him and
I will prove it.
Gru, come on.
He really thinks it's El Macho.
Can you tell him?
? In the summer time when the weather is high?
? You can stretch right up and touch the sky?
? We go fishin' or go swimmin' in the sea?
? We're always happy?
? Life's for livin' yeah, that's our philosophy?
? Sing along with us?
? Dee dee dee-dee dee?
? Dah dah dah-dah dah?
? Yeah we're hap-happy?
? Dah dah-dah?
? Dee-dah-do dee-dah-do dah-do-dah?
? Dah-do-dah-dah-dah?
Give me that!
Huuu...
Kevin,
the wi-fi's out!
Kevin?
Hey, Lex,
Where the heck is Kevin?
Alright, we need to revisit the
number of vacation days you guys get.
I can't find anybody anymore!
Gru, it's Jillian!
I've got good news!
I have my friend
Shannon here with me.
I was thinking you two
could get some grub.
You know, tear it up,
see what happens.
Open up!
Agnes! Agnes,
tell Jillian, I'm not here.
Gru's not here!
Are you sure?
Yes, he just told me!
I mean no, he
didn't just tell me.
Agnes, where is Gru?
He's, putting on lipstick.
He's, swatting a fly.
He's, chopping a head off!
He's... pooping?
I know you're in there, Gru.
There's no way you're
getting out of this.
I have to tell you I was
so nervous about tonight.
I mean there's just so
many phonies out there.
Yes, I hear you.
Ha..ha..ha..
So, do you work out?
Well...
I mean, obviously you don't.
But would you consider it?
Huh?
Physical fitness is very
important to Shannon.
As you can tell, right?
Ah, I can tell.
Call it!
We are in a restaurant,
you know?
Hi, take out for Lucy.
Sure, just a sec.
Ah..well, thank you very much.
I was...
I know someone who
can fix that for you.
And you'll be talking
normal in no time!
Whew... Is it hot in here?
How's the food?
Wait a minute, wait a minute...
Are you wearing a wig?
What?
Ah, I don't think so.
I knew it.
You're a phony.
I hate phonies.
Oh... what? No, these
locks are all mine!
No, they're not!
You know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna rip that
thing off your head
and show everyone what
a bald-headed phony you are.
I don't think so, Miss Lady.
Hello?
Hello...
Are you...
Hey, Gru.
Hello!
Lucy.
How are you doing?
Wow, looks like your
date's out for the count.
It's like she's been shot
with a mild tranquilizer.
Noooo...
Yeah, I'm winking 'cause
that's what actually happened.
Excusi, what's happening here?
She no like?
Oh, she's just, uhh...
Oh.. Oh-ho-ho.. Si! Si.
Shall we take her home?
Yeah, I think you did it.
You just officially had
the worst date ever.
Ohh. Tell me about it.
Don't worry.
It can never get
better from here, right?
But if it doesn't, you can
always borrow my dart gun.
I do use it on, one
or two dates myself.
Yeah, you know
as far as dates go,
I think I'm good
with just, one.
Well...
Good night, partner.
This was fun.
Yes, surprisingly, it was.
Oh, and, uhh...
Just between you and me,
You look much better bald.
See you tomorrow!
? It might seem crazy what I'm about to say?
? Sunshine she's here, you can take away?
? I'm a hot air balloon that could go to space?
So, I take it the
date went well?
No, it was horrible.
? Like I don't care baby by the way?
? Because I'm happy?
? Clap along if you feel like a room without a roof?
? Because I'm happy
Clap along if you feel like happiness is the truth?
Clap along if you know what happiness is to you?
? Because I'm happy
Clap along if you feel like that's what you wanna do?
? Bring me down Bring your Mocking
Bring me Down?
? Because I'm happy
Clap along if you feel like a room without a roof?
Clap along if you know what's best what you wanna do?
Mr. Ramsbottom?
Oh, hello.
What are you doing here?
We got him.
Got who?
Floyd Eagle-san.
Our agents located a secret
room in his shop last night,
and, uh,
discovered this.
It's empty but we found
traces of the PX-41 serum in it.
He is our man.
So, somehow, in spite of your
incompetence, we solved this one.
I was framed!
You won't get away with this!
Get your mitts off of me!
AH..
Alright, so...
What now?
Well, now, you're free to
go back to your business.
Hmmm! Jams and jellies.
And it looks like Agent Wilde will be
transferring to our Australian branch.
Australia?
Yes.
But thank you, for everything.
And by everything, of
course I mean, nothing.
Toodles and cheerio, Mr. Gru.
Hey there.
Hey.
So, we got him.
Yay!
That's great.
And now you're
going to Australia?
Well, it's not definite yet.
I'm still figuring it out.
Already been working
on my accent.
So, umm...
Pretty excited.
Great.
Well, good luck.
Thanks.
You, too.
Oh, here. I wanted
to give you this.
Your lipstick taser?
Yeah, it's just a memento.
Just.. you know.
From, the first time we met.
Oh. Thank you, Lucy.
Agent Wilde?
Well, it looks like
they need you.
So...
Yeah...
I better go.
Bye, Gru.
I brought you an umbrella.
Ah, thank you.
What are you doing out here?
Remember when you
said that I liked Lucy?
Well, it turns out...
You are right.
Really?
Yes, but...
Well, she's moving away.
I'm never going to
see her again.
Is there anything
I can do to help?
I don't...
I don't think so, sweetheart.
Well is there anything
you could do?
Hello, Lucy. This is Gru.
I know...
Up to this point, our relationship
has been strictly professional.
And you're leaving
for Australia and all...
But...
Okay, here is the question.
Would you like to...
To go out on a date...
Ayyy... No.
Okay, that's not helping.
Alright. Here we go.
For real this time.
I can do this.
I hate you.
Be... Dow Be... Dow
Be...
This place is awesome!
Okay, let's party!
But, first, let us go
over the rules!
Because, what is fun
without the rules.
Agnes, easy on the chocolate.
Edith, try to not kill anyone.
Margo,
Hello, Mr. Gru.
Argh.. okay.
Gru!
There must be a
standard 6 feet of space,
between you and boys.
Especially this boy.
Ah, you are a funny man.
There are no rules, seor.
It's Cinco De Mayo!
Come on! Let's party and relax!
So glad you could
make it, mi compadre!
Hey, what's wrong?
Oh, nothing. Nothing's wrong.
I'm just chilling.
With the guac,
from my chip hat.
Gru, please.
I know that look
all too well. It is the
look of a broken heart.
How did you know?
Believe me, my friend.
I, too, have spent many nights
trying to drown my sorrows,
in Guacamole.
You?
Yes.
But,
we are survivors.
There is much more to us,
than meets the eye.
Enjoy the party.
What?
Would you like some
peanuts or pretzels?
Ha..ha..ha...
That's a good joke.
I just did a boom-boom.
I really need you to
make a choice now.
I choose Gru.
I choose Gru!
Thank you, Gru stewardess!
You're welcome!
You have not lost
your touch, my friend.
Ah-ha!
I knew it!
You are El Macho.
That's right!
Nobody believed me!
But I knew you weren't dead.
Of course not.
I merely faked my death.
But now...
It's time for me,
to make a spectacular return
to evil.
Doctor!
I think it's time,
to show Gru,
what we're up to here?
Dr. Nefario?
Nice to see you, Gru!
Whaaa... So this is
your new job opportunity?
Absolutely.
You're gonna like this.
Sorry. I had to borrow
some of your minions,
but it was for a worthy cause.
Oooh.. Kevin!
No, he is not Kevin anymore!
Now...
He is an indestructible,
mindless,
killing machine!
Just watch this.
And here's the best part:
I got an army of them!
Soon,
I will unleash them,
on the world!
And if anyone,
anyone tries to stop them...
The city gets eaten!
We can do it together!
Together?
Together!
I have admired your
work for years, amigo.
Stealing the moon?
Are you kidding?
We would be unstoppable.
Men like you,
men like me...
We, should be ruling the world!
So, are you in?
Woo-hoo!
Oh, yeah! Probably.
Probably?
I mean, yes! Yes,
Of course, yes.
I just, have a lot
going on right now.
I just need to get
some things off my plate,
before we start taking
over the world, that's all.
Excuse me?
No, no, forget it.
100%, I am in.
I think, what is that?
Do you hear that?
I do. That's Agnes
calling me, from undis---
Totally in!
You know what? I am not
so convinced that he is in.
Edith, Agnes, come on!
Oops, sorry!
You need to go home now!
Where is Margo?
Margo!
Come on! We're...
Hey, what's wrong?
I hate boys.
Yes, they stink.
Now, sorry, honey,
you got to go.
Oops...
Sorry.
Hey, Paulito.
What's the matter?
Oh, hey, Eduardo.
Lucia.
I apologize. Paulito, is
usually not like this.
The same thing happened
the other day with...
With Gru...
Oh...
Speaking of Gru,
have you seen him?
I really need to talk to him.
Yes, I think he's
somewhere around here.
You two are close, no?
Oh... I don't know.
I mean, close,
I wouldn't say we're, "close".
Why, did he say we're close?
Did he say that?
It's not what he did say.
For instance,
he never mentioned...
That you were both working
for the Anti-Villain League!
You're coming with me.
Funky.
So Eduardo's actually El Macho?
Cool!
No, it is not cool!
Once I pretty much knew
it was him all along,
so if anyone's cool, it's me.
Gru!
Well, Dr. Nefario.
El Macho's onto you.
He knows you're
working for the AVL.
And, he's got your partner.
Lucy?
Well, that's, impossible.
She's on her way to Australia.
Nefario!
Sorry, got to go.
He's got Lucy?
Not for long.
Come on.
We're getting her out of there.
I don't see anything.
My unicorn!
Agnes, run!
Come on! Hurry!
Move!
What's the matter?
Kevin!
Dr. Nefario! You're back!
In the flesh!
Behold...
The Antidote.
Come on.
It's time we put this horrible
jelly to some good use.
Curses!
Foiled again!
These guys captured me!
Hello, Gru!
Hey! Nice work, Dr. Nefario!
All antidote in the jelly can.
I mean, I'm happy to create an
evil army to destroy the world...
But nobody messes
with my family.
Thank you, Doctor.
Now let's go get the...
Hi!
You brought the girls?
Yes.
Oh. Is that wrong?
You guys, take care of the rest
of the minions. I'm going to find Lucy.
Eat jelly, you furry freaks!
It's over, El Macho.
Now where is Lucy?
Let me show you.
Oh. Hey, Gru!
Turns out you were right
about the Polo Macho thing, huh?
One push of this button,
and I send that rocket,
straight into the same volcano
where I faked my death.
Only this time...
It's for real.
No!
We coulda ruled the
world together, Gru.
But now...
You're gonna die.
Lipstick taser!
Aww. He copied me.
I am not afraid,
of your jelly guns.
Oh, this ain't a
jelly gun, Sunshine.
Don't worry about
me, Gru, I'll be fine!
I have survived locks
worse than this.
Okay, that's not entirely true.
Actually I'm kinda
freaking out up here!
Don't worry. I will get
you out of this.
Hah! Hah!
I really hate that chicken.
Yoohoo!
Is that a red one?
It's definitely the red one!
Gru!
Any time now!
Lucy, we may not
get out of this alive.
So, I need to ask
you a question.
Uhh... Better make it quick!
If I asked you out on a date,
What would you have said?
Are you kidding me?
Yes!
Jump!
Lucy?
Lucy, where are you?
Ah... Lucy!
Gru!!
Sorry.
Guess you, kinda need your
arms to tread water, huh?
They'll be back.
147 dates later...
Oh...!
Can I be the first to say,
Eww!
Okay.
Excuse me!
Hi, excuse me.
Hi, everybody.
I'd like to make some toast...
Okay.
She... umm...
She kisses my boo-boos
She braids my hair
We Love You Mothers Everywhere
And my new Mom Lucy is beyond compare
Download Hindi dubbed audio only form
http://hindidubaudio.blogspot.com