SAM RAIMI. Hello, Marvel fans.
My name is Sam Raimi,
and I am the director of the movie
you're about to see,
Doctor Strange
in the Multiverse of Madness.
Today, is April 12th, 2022,
and I'm joined by our producer
and our writer.
- Let me introduce to you Richie Palmer.
- RICHIE PALMER: Hello.
RAIMI: And Michael Waldron.
MICHAEL WALDRON: Hello.
RAIMI: Richie, you told me that
Marvel makes a new logo
for every picture they make.
Is that true?
PALMER: Yeah, we like to update
with images
from some of the more recent
Disney+ series and movies and make sure
that it's always up to date
with some of the coolest images
from our movies.
This one, we did something special.
I think it was Sam and Bob Murawski,
our editor, and Kevin came together
and said, you know, "We should do
something special for Doctor Strange,
"and put in more images
of Doctor Strange and Wanda in there
"than we've ever seen before."
RAIMI: Michael, it was your idea
to start this movie in this scene.
Um, you wanted to
come into an adventure,
you told me,
that was just reaching its climax
with the audience not knowing
how they got here
and let them play catch up.
WALDRON: Yeah, it always felt like
it'd be fun to feel like
we were really coming in at the end
of another Doctor Strange movie.
- That America has already...
- RAIMI: That's a unique choice.
WALDRON: Yeah, America's already
been through this gauntlet
with another one of these guys.
RAIMI: That's a really unusual choice,
given that you're also
taking these pages
to introduce America Chavez.
To come in on the wrap up,
you don't really get to meet her
in a conventional way
in the movie, in your writing.
WALDRON: And have the first lines
that they're speaking to one another
be in Spanish, too, was just fun and,
kind of, unmooring for the audience.
PALMER: I love this look
of Doctor Strange's in this scene.
We were inspired by some comics,
and I know Sam
and we all worked together
with Graham Churchyard,
our costume designer,
and our Marvel Studios
Visual Development team,
led by Ryan Meinerding and Ian Joyner.
This is one of my favourite looks,
though, in this movie of Doctor Strange.
I love the ponytail.
I don't know about you guys
but I love the red and black suit
and the ponytail and the beard.
RAIMI: I'm not crazy about the ponytail.
(ALL LAUGHING)
But, basically,
I think it's a great choice,
given that we wanted to make him
kind of an Errol Flynn
version of Strange.
Like the... Originally, Michael...
Michael's idea was, he's an even better
version of Strange than Strange himself.
But we're friends.
RAIMI: Until he weakens here morally
and believes that
the ends justify the means.
...your sacrifice is worth
more than your...
RAIMI: Originally, Michael,
you wrote this Strange
as the better version of the man
and then, going back,
we made him a sinner.
And you added a flaw,
where he makes his terrible choice
to save the universe at the expense
of this young girl's life.
WALDRON: Yeah, that was kind of a
late-in-the game decision
that really re—contextualised
Strange and America's relationship
throughout the entire movie,
and then worked.
(SCREAMS)
(EXPLODING)
(DRAMATIC CHORAL MUSIC PLAYING)
RAIMI: So, Michael,
a lot of the movie that you wrote,
you had to follow in the footsteps
of the latest Sewer-Man movie,
No Way Home, and WandaVision.
Is that true?
WALDRON: I think it was always in there
at some point or another,
but maybe at different points
in the movie,
and it showed up later
in the Illuminati sequence.
RAIMI: Did they let you
read the scripts?
WALDRON: Some of them.
WandaVision, I mean,
I'm friends with all the writers.
No Way Home, there was a lot of secrecy.
WandaVision they had shot,
and a lot of it was airing
even as we were making this.
So, that, we were more up to speed.
Excuse me. May I?
Thanks.
RAIMI: In this scene,
there's the great Michael Stuhlbarg,
who I loved
in the Coen brothers classic,
A Serious Man.
WALDRON: He's so great. I was selfishly
just so excited
to write dialogue for him.
He's such a tremendous actor.
Haven't seen you in a while.
Really wanted to give him a lot
to work with even in this short scene.
So were a lot of us.
RAIMI: You did. He has bitter feelings
about Strange's choice,
his egotistical choice, and questions
whether he's always so certain
that he's doing the right thing,
which I really like
for the theme of the picture.
I'm very sorry.
Thank you.
RAIMI: And at this point in the movie,
the way you wrote it, Michael,
he has no self-doubt.
He's certain that
he did the right thing.
Just like the Strange
we saw in Universe 617.
That's what we refer to
as the opening sequence.
For that Strange, he was certain
he was doing the right thing,
sacrificing that little girl.
And it's great
that you later pit him against
other Stranges who are certain
they're doing the right thing.
No, I made the only play we had.
Well, of course you did.
RAIMI: He learns that
he's not always right
and that he doesn't always
have to be the one,
in your words, Michael,
holding the knife,
which I think is great.
He becomes a tiny bit more open,
I thought,
through the course of your screenplay.
(BRIDAL MARCH PLAYING)
WALDRON: Yep.
Nic West gets him right there.
Love this camera move, Sam.
Such a great way to introduce Christine.
RAIMI: It was supposed to capture
Strange's dizzying feeling
when he finally saw the woman
he should have loved
move on with her life without him
because of his selfish choices.
Just like you wrote.
Michael, you're in this scene, right?
You're in the background
as the best man,
but can you see yourself in that moment?
WALDRON: I think I didn't make it.
(LAUGHS) I think I just...
right before they start dancing,
I think I got cut.
I'm about to have a meltdown
on this commentary.
RAIMI: Now you know why they call my
editor, Bob Murawski, "The Butcher".
PALMER: I love that. That's one of
my favourite small moments in the movie.
Him turning the water into wine.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
There's Charlie.
I have to introduce you
because he's kind of...
It's embarrassing,
but he's a big fan, so...
Hey, uh, Christine. Um...
WALDRON: I love this scene.
I should've...
I guess, just 'cause it's dialogue.
But these two are so great.
RAIMI: This scene was originally
a little longer, the way you wrote it,
and I really liked it, too.
Had a little more depth about Strange...
Her asking Strange whether he was happy.
And although that's still in this cut,
we had a little more depth
about him saying...
It was never gonna work out between us.
RAIMI: ..."I saved
over five billion lives in this..."
Why not?
RAIMI: ...from the avengers: Endgame.
"And I can travel
from New York to Tokyo in an instant."
What man wouldn't be happy?
But you can see
or feel beneath the surface
that Benedict was really playing it
like he was and lying for her sake
so that she could get on with her life.
But it caused a point of introspection
that I thought was really
interesting in your screenplay,
specifically in his performance.
WALDRON: Yep. Both great here.
RAIMI: Maybe if there's a longer version
of the movie,
the audience will see that one day.
WALDRON: Remember, Rachel said
she had somebody following her around,
watching all this jewellery and stuff.
There was so much
expensive stuff on her.
I think there were some armed guards
watching all the stuff she had on.
PALMER: Yeah, they were handcuffed
to the briefcase.
Kept making jokes
about making the heist.
(PEOPLE CLAMOURING)
RAIMI: Did they really have that person
handcuffed to a briefcase?
WALDRON: Yeah.
PALMER: Yeah.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(DOCTOR STRANGE THEME PLAYING)
RAIMI: Which, basically, means
you can have a very serious criminal
steal that stuff to lop off that hand.
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
WALDRON: It's so cool there.
RAIMI: Benedict is so elegant
in that moment.
I love how he does that.
WALDRON: Benedict is elegant
in real life.
RAIMI: This New York street scene
was built
by Charles Wood,
our production designer.
He built this entire New York
because Jamie Christopher, our producer,
and ourselves
weren't allowed to go to New York
because of the pandemic at the time.
So, it was Jamie that recommended,
"Why don't we build it in England?"
Build New York, which was a crazy idea,
but it was a smart idea.
And he got Marvel to invest
in an entire construction of, like,
four city blocks of New York.
It was the biggest set
I've ever worked on.
Obviously, we have CG! backgrounds
behind the construct,
but most of what you're seeing
is really there.
The cars were all brought in,
American cars, which they didn't...
they have some of in England
but not a tremendous amount.
I thought it was a very wise thing
that Jamie Christopher did back then
to have Marvel invest
in that great scope
by building it. Very unusual choice,
but turns out, because of the pandemic,
the only logical one in the end.
What were you going to say?
WALDRON: I was saying,
this is the monster Gargantos,
not to be confused with Shuma—Gorath.
PALMER: Fun fact about this Gargantos,
we actually took
Lizzie Olsen's eyeball scan
and had made this eyeball,
model led after Lizzie Olsen's eye
as a little foreshadowing
for the real villain in the movie.
(YELPS)
RAIMI: Because in Michael's script,
obviously, Lizzie Olsen
is puppeting both the Ribbon Monster
and this tentacle monster
in our universe.
WALDRON: A spoiler.
Cause nobody's watching the movie
for the first time with this commentary.
Great way to watch the movie.
PALMER: You know,
it's great to talk about.
(YELLS)
WALDRON: Wong just getting after it.
RAIMI: Benedict Wong, what a great guy
and so gung—ho to do his own stunts
and to put everything he's got into
every moment of the performance.
I was so impressed with him.
WALDRON: One of the first days
on set in London,
watching him just practising
with that rope dart, just...
He was just so amazing with it.
PALMER: I remember that.
It was such a hectic day.
We were running around
doing so many things.
It was in the middle
of one of the first days of shooting.
(CREATURE GROWLING)
(PEOPLE WHIMPERING)
WONG: Help!
(DOCTOR STRANGE GRUNTS)
You're welcome.
WALDRON: Just another day
for these guys.
...bow in the presence
of the Sorcerer Supreme?
PALMER: I'm going to shout out
to Jay Funk, Julian Daniels,
who comes up
with all these magic hand motions,
for us in these Doctor Strange movies.
DOCTOR STRANGE:
Hold it, hold it! Whoa!
(BOTH GRUNT)
(CREATURE GROWLING)
(SCREAMING)
(EXCLAIMING)
WALDRON: Best part of the movie
is coming up here in just a moment.
PALMER: Flames of the Faltine.
RAIMI: Wow. Who is that guy?
PALMER: Ladies and gentlemen,
that is Michael Waldron, our writer.
Charlie's best man.
WALDRON: Sam, how'd I do that day?
My big cameo.
RAIMI: Anyways, Michael, this next scene
is one of my favourites.
This is the destruction
of the tentacle creature.
Kevin really liked this moment.
He was really interested
in making it super gory, I remember.
Finally, we wanted to make
the movie PG 13.
- Is that right, Richie?
- PALMER: Yeah.
Yeah. We really wanted to push it
as far as we could go, while
making sure that families everywhere
could watch this movie together.
So, things like this moment,
we hoped were gory,
but still fun for everybody,
and we took a lot of cues from you,
Sam, and the Evil Dead movies.
And Kevin always talked about
the eyeball
popping out in Evil Dead II
and wanted to pay
a little bit of an homage to this.
RAIMI: That's cool.
This one turned out really well.
That shot's really cool.
It's almost like a dance
as he comes down off the ledge
and lands on the street.
WALDRON: This is New York in LA.
She took my Slingie.
She took your Slingie.
RAIMI: Where did we shoot this?
WALDRON: Shot that...
This is at Paramount.
Oh, my God!
I'm not gonna kill you, kid.
I just bust my ass
trying to save your life, remember?
RAIMI: She pickpocketed his ring.
Giant monsters I can clearly handle...
but what bothers me is that last night,
you were in my dream.
That wasn't a dream.
PALMER: It's a huge idea for this movie
that I think
we all came up with early on.
Just the idea that when you're dreaming,
you're actually seeing
into other universes.
We have experience of the Multiverse.
Most recently, there was an incident
with Spider-Man.
(SCOFFS) What man?
Spider-Man.
He has the powers of a spider.
PALMER: And, see, this is fun
for people following at home.
They remember Spider—Man,
but they don't really
know much about him.
Out of his butt?
- No.
WALDRON: After the events
of No Way Home, the spell of forgetting.
You're gonna get a stomach ache.
I'm from another universe.
How do you know my stomach
works the same as yours?
RAIMI: Charles Wood did
such a nice job recreating
a New York pizzeria.
...which is why I'm still sitting here,
waiting for you to enlighten us.
RAIMI: Seems super authentic to me.
The details that he had in that place...
I'm sorry I couldn't
get in closer on a lot of them.
But the set was just beautiful.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
WALDRON: I feel like Richie and I
ate a lot of pizza on these days.
I left a very nice wedding...
WALDRON: Tested it out.
...to save a smart-ass kid
from getting eaten by an octopus.
- Whose wedding?
- Now tell me... Christine's.
PALMER: I'm pretty particular
about the quality of pizza.
- Do you mind?
- Yes, I do.
PALMER: In this movie.
You need to explain to me
What's going on.
RAIMI: John Mathieson,
our cinematographer,
did a brilliant job
photographing this scene.
He had three cameras
and really kept them alive.
Super long lenses
to give us some New York depth.
What power?
RAIMI: Because, finally, it's
an eight-page, six-page dialogue scene.
It could have just sat in the middle
of the movie
but the actors and the writing
have really helped us get through it.
You don't expect to find
six pages of exposition
in the first act of a Marvel picture,
but there is a lot of catching up to do
and lot of setting up
that we have to do.
Well, you guys knew of
this magical book of pure good
that gives a sorcerer whatever they need
to defeat their enemy.
PALMER: It's really a testament
to Xochitl Gomez's skills
as a young actress to being able
to deliver a lot of exposition,
like you're saying,
and doing it in a fun way
that it really doesn't feel
like you're hearing exposition.
WALDRON: Yeah, this was early
in the shoot, too.
She was tremendous. So, we just
talked about these scenes with...
kind of akin to John Connor
in Terminator 2.
The way he's bringing the audience
up to speed a little bit
but he's got just enough
moxie and attitude
that it goes down in kind of a fun way.
I thought you'd protect me...
but you didn't.
That was the fight in my dream.
That wasn't a dream.
RAIMI: There were so many contributors
to the movie,
from storyboard artists
who came up with great ideas
to visual effects supervisor,
Janek Sirrs.
It was his idea that the Ribbon Monster
infect Strange
with a rapidly advancing alien virus
that ages him and turns him
into a corpse very quickly.
And that's because
Michael came up with the idea
that Dead Strange walks
in this movie later, in the third act,
and we really wanted to have a look
that looked like a classic zombie,
a classic monster picture.
But to get him there...
Janek came up with this idea
because, really, only something like
36 hours or 24 hours had passed
throughout the course
of the whole movie,
so there had to be justification.
And Janek fixed that like he fixed
so many other things in the film.
America Chavez.
WALDRON: Could always count on Janek
to be my partner in a logic battle.
Also Dead Strange, I've got
to give credit to Richie as well.
That was the two of us
sitting in his office in London
and thinking, "Oh, my God,
how do we figure out this third act?"
RAIMI: That was a great idea.
PALMER: And America Chavez
is a character
we've wanted to introduce into the MCU
for, like, a decade
and we're very happy
to do it in this movie.
But it made perfect sense
to do it in this movie,
given that her powers are
opening Multiversal portals.
...did it have the same markings
as the octopus?
WALDRON: Supposed to have a pigeon
pecking his eyeball at one point, right?
This isn't sorcery.
PALMER: As it was scripted.
WALDRON: As scripted.
The script is just a suggestion.
It was a refrain...
...on this film.
- Chocolate!
- Hey!
PALMER: Wanda Maxim off.
So, this is Wanda and Billy and Tommy
in Universe 838.
And this set is based on the house
from WandaVision.
And Charlie Wood,
our production designer,
worked with the WandaVision team
to make a version of the house
that you saw on WandaVision
go through all those different
sitcom eras
and change and adapt by the decade.
But this is the real-world version
of what it would look like
if Wanda Maxim off actually
lived there with her two boys
in the real world in Universe 838.
WALDRON: It's crazy to be shooting this
movie as WandaVision was coming out
and it's just clearly becoming
more and more of a sensation
and the biggest thing in the world.
And every day we'd come in and
we'd think, "Oh, man, this is really...
"We've really got to get this right."
But fortunately, when you've got Lizzie,
it's hard to screw it up.
PALMER: Apples?
WALDRON: Apples?
Apples, right?
RAIMI: Those are actually
cherry blossoms.
Eventually.
(RAIMI LAUGHS)
RAIMI: Those were cherry blossoms
because they were the only thing
blooming at that time that we shot this.
So, all those blossoms
you see on the trees
were put up by Charles Wood
and his very diligent, hardworking crew.
They were fake blossoms,
and that crew was out there for a week
on ladders, breaking their back
to put up all those blossoms.
And our director of photography,
John Mathieson,
designed it
so that they're always backlit.
And he had a plan where we would
move around the orchard,
always having the sun shine
on those fake blossoms from behind,
making this idyllic Wanda world.
With What?
RAIMI: Idyllic because
it's just an illusion. It's a hex.
PALMER: The sheep. One of the best
special effects in the movie
was these sheep, that shepherd.
This guy and his sheepdog
just running around
herding their sheep.
That sheepdog was mean.
I tried to pet him, I almost got bitten.
One that covets her power for itself.
We've taken her to Kamar-Taj,
and we've got our defences...
PALMER: Those guys.
...but we could use an Avenger.
There are other Avengers.
Yeah, but given the choice between
the archer with the mohawk...
and several bug-themed crime fighters...
or one of the most powerful
magic-wielders on the planet...
it's an easy call.
RAIMI: Therefore, because those blossoms
were all plastic,
those are fake blossoms
blowing in the breeze.
Blossom boy! He had a giant wind fan.
We'd get him up in the air
before the dialogues start,
kill the fan and start the take.
I know what it's like
to be on your own...
hunted for abilities you never wanted...
and I can protect her.
WALDRON: Such an exciting scene for fans
to finally get these two
on screen together.
PALMER: That's right.
WALDRON: A lot of times they debate
who's the most powerful person
in the MCU.
These are two big contenders for it,
right here.
You know, the Hex was the easy part.
PALMER: This is the first time we see
Strange and Wanda interact
in one of our movies.
RAIMI: Michael, I remember
your first version of the script,
where you had Wanda be a good person,
uncorrupted throughout
the entire adventure.
It was only in the last scenes
of the film
that she finally turned
and crossed over to the dark side.
And then I think you and me
had discussions about
"Why should we let the greatest moment
of the movie setup
"be the ending and really just
open the door for the next one?
"Let's bring that good stuff forward."
So then, I think, you re-wrote.
Along with a lot of other reasons,
you decided to make Wanda
the villain from the go—get,
so we can see that delicious battle
between Strange and Wanda throughout
the meat of our film.
WALDRON: Yeah, that was when
our movie pushed because of COVID.
We were originally supposed to shoot
in May of 2020
and we pushed until late that year.
And there was an opportunity,
if we wanted,
to blow this thing up and start over,
or what would we do?
Wouldn't you want to go there?
WALDRON: That would be
the most delectable choice.
See, guys,
this is why the movie's so good.
This is why we're at 99
on Rotten Tomatoes. Sam and I are so...
What you're doing is a flagrant
violation of every natural law...
WALDRON: Anyways, why let somebody else
have fun with Wanda being bad?
RAIMI: That's why you're good.
You're the writer extraordinaire.
But she's not a child.
She's a supernatural being.
Such raw power could wreak havoc
on this and other worlds.
Her sacrifice...
would be for the greater good.
Well, you can kiss
the lunch box goodbye,
'cause that's the kind of justification
our enemies use.
Is it the one you used
when you gave Thanos the Time Stone?
RAIMI: I think this really hit
our test audience in a strong, good way,
this scene that you wrote,
because they're not used
to seeing their hero, Wanda,
turn to the side of evil.
It really is a powerful choice
to watch one of their heroes fall.
PALMER: I'm also not sure
they're ready to see our hero,
Doctor Strange,
be put in such a position
where he's being confronted
with that from her.
"You gave up the Time Stone
and look what it did to me, Strange."
We love Wanda, we don't want to see her
go through the pain she's gone through.
And you could lead it all
back to that moment.
WALDRON: I would argue Wanda is making
some pretty sound points here,
and I think that makes
for the best villains,
the villains that you can really,
you know,
believe are the heroes
of their own story.
Erik Killmonger, Thanos, Loki.
RAIMI: I think that was one of your
finest accomplishments with the script,
was that you made our villain
a human being.
And with motives we understand
and, if not root for, just empathise.
We can empathise with her.
WALDRON: Thanks, pal.
PALMER: Anybody see Master Hamir
from the first movie?
One of my favourite characters.
WALDRON: This was day two, right?
This was early.
...or annihilate the cosmos.
She took over a whole town
using her mind.
RAIMI: This was one of the first scenes
we blocked, I think, with the actors.
If she gets America's power...
she could enslave the entire Multiverse.
I love Benedict's reading
coming up here.
He kind of messed up in his line.
Yeah.
Suspend teaching at once
and arm the students.
She doesn't trust him.
That was a great beat, Michael.
And Wong is so commanding.
The bell, the drums.
PALMER: The drums, you want
to talk about those war drums, Sam?
- We had Danny Elf man...
- RAIMI: You talk about it.
PALMER: We had Danny Elf man
very early on.
Before he was really scoring the movie,
he gave us war drums
that we could play on set
so that we can really amp the energy
and know the cadence of those drums
as we're going into this battle.
It was really exciting.
Added something to the day.
RAIMI. That's right.
It was so helpful,
Danny Elf man giving us so much
all throughout the course of this film.
PALMER: Mmm-hmm.
- There he is, that rascal.
- WALDRON: Rintrah.
PALMER: Rintrah is a great character
from the comics
that I believe Michael found.
RAIMI: Adam Hugill plays that role.
He did a wonderful job.
PALMER: We get to see some masters
from other Sanctums.
The Hong Kong and London Sanctum.
RAIMI: I love that East meets West bow,
showing the different styles
of the masters of the Sanctums.
This was another gigantic set
that Charles Wood
and his team designed for us.
I thought it was beautiful.
WALDRON: I was just going to say,
I love the sequel trope
of the sacred base getting attacked.
I feel like that's a thing you see
in a lot of sequels
that I actually like.
We're, I guess, ripping off.
RAIMI: We originally had a sub-theme
that Michael wrote,
with the character of Sara,
who was in the previous scene,
Wong's right-hand woman.
We have a little bit of a love line
between Wong and Sara.
That's Sheila Atim that plays that role.
But that got diminished,
as happens with cuts.
We just wanted to focus
on our main heroes,
and the story took on
a little too many dimensions,
and we had to focus it down,
so that little bit
of a suggested love story was lost.
You had to make terrible sacrifices.
I blew a hole through the head
of the man I loved...
and it meant nothing.
Do not speak to me of sacrifice,
Stephen Strange.
WALDRON: I like hitting that,
the fact that what Wanda did
at the end of Infinity War
actually meant nothing,
that Thanos just reversed it
with the Time Stone
and killed Vision, anyways.
Felt like something
that was just too poignant
to really not run out.
Defensive positions, now!
PALMER: Here we go.
Do not dare to enter
these sacred grounds.
You have no idea
just how reasonable I have been.
Yeah.
Book of the Damned,
calling yourself a witch,
conjuring creatures to abduct a kid...
I don't exactly
call that being reasonable.
Sending those creatures after her
instead of myself was mercy.
And, in spite of your hypocrisies
and insults,
I have begged you
to safely get out of my way.
PALMER: They're both such good actors.
You have exhausted my patience...
but I do hope you understand
that even now...
what's about to happen...
this is me...
being reasonable.
RAIMI: Costume designer
Graham Churchyard
really did a great job with Wanda's
costume, updating it from WandaVision.
We had to keep the basic design
once she'd become the Scarlet Witch
but I thought that he took it
to the next level beautifully.
WALDRON: About a year's worth
and movie's worth of heartache,
I think, go into that blast from Wanda.
I think we earned what's about to happen
on the backs of the great work
that Lizzie has done over the years.
All the great writers and filmmakers
that have been stewards
of this character for us.
PALMER: So cool, Sam. I love
these shots of her in the sky blasting.
RAIMI: Yeah, we had a great
second unit director
that did a lot of this photography,
a lot of this battle photography
and our mechanical effects team
did such a great job with the explosions
along with our stunt coordinator.
And they were all fantastic
on the picture.
And this scene really belongs to them.
And our editors,
Bob Murawski and Tia Nolan,
did a beautiful job
putting it all together.
This scene was mostly Bob.
Tia did some of the other scenes
quite well.
WALDRON: That character's name
in the script was Weasel Sorcerer,
which was a source of confusion
for some people
because they thought it might
just be a giant weasel in robes,
which in this movie, was not...
- Not really that ridiculous.
- (ALL CHUCKLING)
PALMER: Awesome cannons.
WALDRON: Cannons.
PALMER: (LAUGHS) By Charlie Wood...
RAIMI: That's Sara manning that cannon.
PALMER: Wanda's so bad,
they can't even get the second shot off.
RAIMI: These are magic cannons.
Take cover!
(SORCERERS SCREAM)
RAIMI: We had
a much bigger battle scene.
Fire at will!
RAIMI: And it was cool,
but we wanted to get
into the second act a little earlier,
so we cut it down.
I think this helps
the overall flow of the picture.
WALDRON: It was an amazing bit of...
In the animatic of Wanda fighting.
One of the...
Maybe the London master, where she...
I think she cut his head off,
and then puppeteered his headless body
against his comrades.
Probably wouldn't have been okay
for the PG 13 rating,
but that was pretty cool.
RAIMI: Yeah, that was so great.
Storyboard artists did such a great job
depicting this fight.
PALMER: She disintegrates this guy.
WALDRON: These burnt bodies
were very realistic.
It was quite unsettling
to walk around the set,
eating your lunch, for weeks on end.
PALMER: We're about to get into
some of the most fun stuff in the movie.
There's a lot of sequences so amazing.
WALDRON: There's some very Sam Raimi
stuff that was just so exciting
to watch being shot.
You want the girl,
you'll have to go through me.
Fine.
RAIMI: This was Janek's idea
to have the mirror trap.
Our visual effects supervisor.
(SCARLET WITCH GASPS)
(MYSTERIOUS MUSIC CHIMING)
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (RICOCHETING)
RAIMI: Elizabeth Olsen had to perform,
so often, alone in this film,
carry the whole movie on her shoulders.
And I thought she did
such a great, great job doing that.
Very difficult.
WALDRON: Yeah, she spent a lot of time
with second unit
just doing gruelling action work,
a lot of it covered in oil or something,
and was just such a great trooper
and team player.
Wong, what happened?
RAIMI: Yes. Jeff Habberstad
was our second unit director,
and he worked really well with her.
WALDRON: Look at that. Come on, Sam,
that's the stuff right there.
RAIMI: Spooky stuff.
Kevin wanted to make it a spooky film.
PALMER: Yeah, it's crazy to see Wanda
act like this for the first time.
It's so exciting.
And, for fans of the comics,
we were so excited
to bring this to screen
and finally deliver on a promise.
Once you introduce the character
of the Scarlet Witch,
even before she was the Scarlet Witch,
and we introduced her in Age of Ultron,
you know, there was always the hope
that we can bring her
to this place of her
doing things like that or like this.
And it's really exciting.
And she is the best.
If Doctor Strange
is the anchor of the MCU, of Phase 4,
then Wanda Maxim off
is the jewel in the crown.
WALDRON: Nice. Nice line.
SCARLET WITCH: You gave all those lives
just to keep me from my children.
You took those lives.
WALDRON: Pour one out for Master Hamir,
by the way.
PALMER: Yep, bye—bye, Hamir.
WALDRON: I don't know
where those guys went.
They just fell into...
WALDRON: Did we ever figure out, Sam?
PALMER: He's dead.
RAIMI: No, they're dead.
PALMER: He's dead. Master Hamir's dead.
(LAUGHS)
They don't exist.
SCARLET WITCH: Oh, but they do.
RAIMI: I love the dimensionality
that Charles Wood and his art team
bring to the set.
It isn't just a wall
or pillars behind Strange,
but you can see through the wall
to another dimension beyond
that gives it a lot of depth.
BILLY: We're gonna show it.
TOMMY: Mum, watch us. Mum!
BILLY: Go long. Got it!
All right, go on back, go on back.
PALMER: Michael, one of my favourite
lines in the movie coming up right now.
TOMMY: Don't you dare! No!
Of our life together.
- WANDA: Here.
- BILLY AND TOMMY: Yes!
And then back to front.
Back to front.
BILLY: Can I have some?
Please?
WALDRON: When you have a cast like this,
it's really, as a writer,
very freeing 'cause
they can just make anything great.
And every morning...
the same nightmare.
RAIMI: Elizabeth did such a great job
in this scene.
Even after all the death
and destruction she created,
she still makes me
feel empathy for her in this moment.
What happens to their mother?
PALMER: Danny's score is great here.
WALDRON: Sam, I remember you
shooting that shot
and thinking it was the coolest.
It was so early on in the shoot.
And I just remember
thinking how cool it was.
RAIMI. The one on Strange
as he launched the snakes?
I love the hissing.
PALMER: Going from Wong's eyes
to Strange,
and then he launches the snakes.
And Benedict got so into
puppeteering those snakes.
That's actually a thing from the comics,
the Vipers of Valtorr.
RAIMI: Yeah, he was great in that.
He's got a great imagination
that he really puts on full, full steam
commitment when he's Doctor Strange,
just casting spells.
PALMER: Call out Easter eggs
as we go through the portal ride.
Michael, you wrote this.
PALMER: Living Tribunal?
RAIMI. Janek Sirrs did a great job
with his visual effects team
during this sequence.
So many different artists.
PALMER: the "grind house releasing"
billboard.
Stark Industries drone.
Oh, that's the Savage Land. (LAUGHS)
The Animated Universe.
WALDRON: The universe where
Doctor Strange drinks Sprite.
(PALMER LAUGHS)
WALDRON: Shout out to Xochitl.
She does such a great job
every time she's getting
her soul drained.
It was a very physically gruelling
bit of acting,
and she was really game
and did a fantastic job.
PALMER: I remember Sam, you going,
"Xochitl, do you think
you could do the thing,
"you know, where you
roll your eyes up a little bit
"and maybe you can show us
some of the whites there?"
And she did it amazingly right away.
She just went, "Like this?"
And all you saw
were the whites of her eyes.
And we were, like, "Oh, my God."
RAIMI: Yeah, she was so good at that.
Crap.
WALDRON: It's like The Undertaker.
PALMER: Benedict Cumberbatch
is a great collaborator,
but one of the funniest guys.
I'm not sure people know
that he's actually really funny.
That whole vomiting after,
that was all him...
All right, America.
PALMER: ...just doing his thing,
and he was great.
He's a really good physical comedian.
- You just did it.
- Not on purpose.
Wong is back there alone with Wanda,
and I'm the only hope he has.
- I can't control my powers...
- You must be able to control it somehow.
Even I could...
WALDRON: Sam, this became a rooftop
relatively late in the process.
For a while, they landed in an alley
in every universe and I think we...
- DOCTOR STRANGE: What?
- None of them do.
WALDRON: ...realised maybe we'd have
a little bit more fun visually,
I guess, on a rooftop.
And 'cause I never dream.
RAIMI: Yes, we had shot this
in the alley exactly
and then re—did it here on the rooftop
to be able to see the world
we're talking about.
Because they had come
into a new universe,
we wanted to see it visually.
Tell the story through the camera
of their environment.
And the alley didn't allow that view.
I don't know where it is,
so unless there's another Other Me...
We need to go find...
Other Other Me.
This was the alley. So, the scene
used to take place in that alley.
And this was the big reveal.
But we decided, "Why are we
waiting so long for the reveal?"
I think Kevin also wanted it,
to see more of this universe.
He was very on top of us,
making sure that we made
a proper presentation
to the Marvel audience of
what another parallel universe
would look like.
It was difficult only because
we didn't want to go sci-fl.
And we wanted to make sure
it was like our universe,
just a few shades different.
And that's a more difficult thing to do
than just creating a brand-new look.
It's got to be recognisable
but different.
The same but different.
Just like the characters that we meet.
Like Strange's alter egos are the same
but a few percent different.
PALMER: Mmm. Look at those pizza balls.
RAIMI: Richie,
those are your pizza balls.
WALDRON: Ate a lot of those.
PALMER: Thank you, sir.
It's weird you guys have to pay for it.
Hey! You didn't pay for that.
PALMER: There he is.
Crap. Maybe it's not free here.
- Pizza Poppa always gets paid.
- All right, Pizza Poppa...
RAIMI: My buddy Bruce Campbell...
Relax yourself, there, Doctor Strange.
WALDRON: Blast on set. I might imagine.
That feels authentic.
It's not a cape, it's a cloak,
and I suggest you let go.
You took this whole suit from...
PALMER: Charlie Wood, our production
designer, worked with you, Sam,
and Bruce Campbell, of course,
and our editor, Bob Murawski,
and our lead storyboard artist,
Doug Lefter.
Everybody from the world
that worked together on Army at Darkness
came back together on this movie.
And there's a funny story
where Charlie actually has the prop
of the fork from Army at Darkness
that he brought to set that day.
And we actually used as...
If you eagle-eyed viewers,
can see it on that Pizza Poppa cart
later in the movie.
RAIMI: That's right.
That's the fork from Army of Darkness
that the little Ashes use
to stick in Bruce Campbell's buttocks.
(WALDRON LAUGHS)
WALDRON: You might not be able to see
in that scene
but, later, when you see Bruce again,
after the credits,
you should keep an eye out
for that fork.
That's a lot.
WALDRON: There's a lot of amazing
preparation work, Sam, that you did
on these sequences
because there was so much choreography
in how they move about
these city streets,
and a lot of it was also done by Lorne,
your son, who was going out
and shooting test footage
just a couple of days in advance,
with stand-ins and everything.
And it was so awesome for me to see
how you and him worked together,
and he would shoot this footage
and then you'd bring it to life
and everything. That was really neat.
PALMER: Shout out to Lorne Raimi.
WALDRON: Yeah, Lorne was such a real
asset to us on the movie,
and is a heck of a filmmaker himself.
Imagine that.
He's your kid. Of course he is.
Christine, this is...
This is amazing. Thank you.
RAIMI: Cool seeing young Strange.
Yeah, I love that sequence.
PALMER: I love this whole sequence,
and seeing...
This also was an idea
that came up a little later,
getting to see the utopian parallel,
which is a place in the comics
where America's from.
Seeing her mums, like, this
was such a treat
that we got to do this.
Home.
RAIMI: I love these two actresses.
All three of them are great.
WALDRON: Yeah.
They definitely elevate this.
RAIMI: That's Ruth.
PALMER: Yeah, you've worked with her
in the past, Sam.
RAIMI: Yes, in Drag Me to Hell.
She's in the opening sequence
of that film.
- (GASPS)
- (INSECT BUZZING)
PALMER: First time America
ever opened a portal.
(CRACKLING)
ELENA: America!
(SCREAMING)
WALDRON: Think about the little things
that traumatise you as a kid,
and then think about
what she's been through.
You know, you were right.
This is just a waste of time.
Hey, kid.
That was the first time
that you opened a portal, right?
Doesn't matter.
RAIMI: And what studio
did we shoot this on?
I didn't lose them.
RAIMI: Was that Paramount also?
WALDRON: This is Paramount.
No, you did not. Don't even think that.
WALDRON: Yet Strange,
the guy with the...
You know, not the best bedside manner...
Listen, if your mums
are anything like their daughter...
WALDRON:
...trying to comfort this patient,
and it's interesting to see
how far he's come from the first movie
when all he could muster
was an awkward hug
to a patient's family.
Here, he's really making
a strong effort.
Trying to kind of disprove her notion
that all Doctor Stranges are bad.
Yes, that was Christine.
- How do you know her?
- From Other You.
PALMER: I love this location. I love
those trees holding up the High Line.
This universe's version
of the High Line, at least.
RAIMI: Yeah, although we shot
the bulk of the picture in England,
we did additional reshoots
in the United States in California,
and John Mathieson
wasn't able to be there.
He was for the first few weeks,
first part of the reshoot.
But then second reshoot went on,
and then we had to use
his replacement cinematographers,
Dan Mandel, who was awesome,
and the great Russell Carpenter,
who shot Titanic.
PALMER: Yeah, we got so lucky.
John called in
favours from friends for us
'cause we got some of the best DPs
in the world working on this movie
and the luxury of working
with more than one.
WALDRON: This statue was amazing.
I mean, that thing is real,
and it was crazy to stand under it.
You really had to listen
to Benedict on those days.
"Gave his life defeating Thanos"?
Yeah. See? We're not all bad.
If Other You's dead...
who's Master of the Sanctum?
RAIMI: It's cool, that last shot,
seeing another version of the Sanctum.
Oh, shit.
RAIMI: And here we meet alt Mordo.
WALDRON: I loved how you shot this, Sam.
Shot this Quick and the Dead,
and the two gunfighters facing off.
Fun to watch you
put this scene together.
RAIMI: Thanks. And I think Kevin thought
maybe it was a little corny.
And he wanted to cut it out.
But I said,
"Please, Kevin, let me have that."
He went, "Okay, fine.
Have your corny stuff."
It was very, very kind of him, generous.
WALDRON: I'm glad you won.
Because you always suspected
this day would come.
RAIMI: Chiwetel Ejiofor, he's so great
playing the alt version of Mordo.
PALMER: It's another awesome look.
RAIMI: Michael, you had written...
I was just going to say
that Michael had written
an early scene with Chiwetel
where we saw him in our universe, 616,
where he was the Mordo
that we knew from Doctor Strange 1.
Only he had been through many battles
since that. He had a limp,
and he was coming after
the Scarlet Witch to take her power
because he knew she was dark
and terribly corrupted by the Dark hold.
And she killed him and cutoff his head.
Presented it to Strange
in a later scene.
It was really great writing,
but it slowed the beginning down
too much, so we had to lose it.
So she has the Dark hold?
WALDRON: Yeah, that was a fun scene
that just didn't
have a place in the movie.
But it was cool. I think that
she cut his head off
right halfway through his ears
about to say, "The bill comes due."
Damn right.
But if your Dark hold
is anything like ours,
I'm afraid she can do far worse
than just summon monsters
to come after you here.
What do you mean?
There is a spell
contained within those pages...
PALMER: The rest of the movie
is just going to be me saying,
"This is one of my favourite
parts of the movie,"
because this is one of
my favourite parts of the movie,
and this, you know, Sam, you and John
shot awesome stuff for this...
Awesome equipment, like the mesmeriser,
but then it was really Tia Nolan
who brought it to life
in such an amazing and unexpected way.
Along with Danny Elf man, of course.
This is such an amazing
piece of the score here.
838 MORDO: ...enemies from afar.
The possession is not a permanent link
between realities.
But in the fleeting time
they Dream walk...
they can do irreparable damage
to the universe they invade.
So it may not be a demon...
WALDRON: The idea of Dream walking
was a kind of early-on discovery
for, I guess, all three of us.
This notion that you could possess
an alternate version of yourself
in another universe,
that felt like a really creepy,
sinister thing
for Wanda to be able to do
that really kind of became the backbone
of the movie in a lot of ways.
PALMER: Here we go.
The Sands of Nisanti.
Should we talk about it for a second?
Michael, that was one of your
discoveries from the comics.
It's a relic in the comics that
if you're near the Sands of Nisanti,
it strips you of your magic powers
for a temporary...
WALDRON: Yeah, the Sands of Nisanti
shows up in The Oath,
Doctor Strange comic by Mark Millar.
They're actually used by Nic West,
the character that
Michael Stuhlbarg plays
in the comics,
becomes an adversarial sorcerer.
And battles against Doctor Strange
in that comic's run.
And he uses the Sands of Nisanti
to strip Strange of his powers.
And, so, if it's in the comics,
it's automatically cool.
PALMER: It is cool. That's cool.
Mordo uses the Sands to
knock out Strange and America here,
and then we find out in a few minutes
that Christine also knows
how to use the Sands of Nisanti.
WALDRON: I love that iris closing shot.
RAIMI: Danny's score here really rocks.
It's so cool.
PALMER: This shot
was another Janek Sirrs plus,
that is actually really awesome.
I love travelling through the Multiverse
with Wanda's spirit like that.
BILLY: Can we have
a little more ice cream?
TOMMY: Please.
BILLY: Please, please, please!
A little more, please!
838 WANDA: Hey, don't make Mum
out to be the bad guy.
BILLY: You know who's the best?
TOMMY: Who?
BILLY: 2003 Tigers.
TOMMY: They suck.
WALDRON: You gave the kids
some good dialogue to riff Sam
about how the Tigers
had won the World Series
in this alternate universe, right?
Isn't that what they're talking about?
RAIMI: Yeah, the 2003 Tigers,
they're saying are so awesome,
but that was one of our sadder years.
But not in this universe.
In this universe,
my Tigers won the World Series in 2003.
WALDRON: This was a great
horror sequence that, again,
Lorne, I think, did a lot of the...
A lot of the work on.
RAIMI: It wasn't this one.
It was the final scene, I think,
- in Wanda's house.
- WALDRON: Right.
RAIMI: But, yeah, he did.
He did those peas and the cup.
He did some of the some of these
insert shots.
PALMER: You're right.
- The lamp.
- RAIMI: I'm sorry. I stand corrected.
PALMER: The tempest in a teacup.
I know, Sam, you loved...
That was one of the first things...
Charlie Wood came to Burbank to present
to you, you know, ideas for
other universes in the Multiverse,
and I remember him saying to you,
"There's this idea I have
of showing a tempest in a teacup.
"I don't know where to use it,
but it's awesome."
And you're, like, "That is awesome.
We're going to put it in the movie."
And it's here.
I love your explanation of it, that
it's just a little bit of our universe
creeping into this universe.
BILLY: Where are you going?
RAIMI: Yeah, I love that
Charlie came up with the idea
that the scale of water
and how it interacts
would be different in this universe.
In a tiny surface like a cup,
there could be ocean waves in miniature.
It's just awesome.
BILLY: Come on, it's important.
WALDRON: Just now, that was maybe
my favourite shot in the whole movie,
when Wanda looks at the camera.
PALMER: Yeah, that's amazing.
WALDRON: It's so chilling.
PALMER: Michael, this scene
is one of my favourites of your work.
I mean, even in the script stage,
this whole idea
that she is travelling to this universe
and is on a mission
and then hears the voices of her boys
and is just stopped in her tracks
and, instantly,
you know what she's doing.
You know what her mission is.
You get it.
And this, of course, the ice cream song.
(SINGING) We like ice cream
PALMER: Music by Danny Elf man.
Lyrics by Michael Waldron.
Copyright 2022, Walt Disney.
And if we get some ice cream
WALDRON: That's how I'm gonna
get the EGOT.
We promise to be good
PALMER: Shoutout Oswald
the Lucky Rabbit in the background.
In this universe, Mickey who?
Oswald is king.
WALDRON: Kids who play Billy and Tommy
are also really great.
You're alive.
Yes.
RAIMI: That's Sheila.
She was wonderful to work with.
Set me free.
I need to destroy the book.
PALMER: She's so good,
such an intense performer,
and this character
is so cool in this moment.
RAIMI: It takes so many heroes' lives
to defeat Wanda. It's terrifying.
PALMER: And you could feel
there's something between them.
WALDRON: Yeah, Wong's hidden life.
PALMER: I think
we like to think that there was
an unspoken thing between them.
PALMER: Sam, this is one of
the coolest things in any movie ever.
How do you even
think of doing this in the moment?
RAIMI: I don't know. But you're right,
it was a momentary thought on set.
PALMER: You just thought it up
on the spot, and it's just amazing.
That flipping back and forth
between the two universes like that.
It's so heartbreaking.
WALDRON: Watching the technical prowess
of you getting that right,
it was so cool.
PALMER: Yeah. It should have been
a lot harder than it was. That's Sam...
WALDRON: Yeah, it actually
didn't take that long.
Cause the thing that we shot second
was the stuff at Kamar—Taj.
I need the Dark hold...
PALMER: Sam has a habit
of making those things look easy.
Those crazy shots.
Tell me what you know.
WALDRON: Wong's badass in this scene.
RAIMI: It turned out to be a great way
to show Wanda's loneliness,
to be able to show her with the kids
and the same frame in another universe,
without them.
It was very effective.
And she's a great actress,
so, that's really why it worked.
Wanda, please!
RAIMI: I like how she's playing, that
she doesn't really want to torture them.
She's not a villain. She's suffering.
She wants her children, like you wrote.
And that's what
Elizabeth is so genius about.
She knows she's not playing a bad girl.
Just someone who loves too deeply
and will do anything
to be with the one she loves.
WALDRON:
That's a cool, practical effect,
I'm pretty sure, right there. It's...
That's... Little stuff like that
was really fun.
(MUFFLED THUDDING ECHOES)
AMERICA: (MUFFLED) Hey!
- (GROANS)
- Hey!
(GLASS POUNDING)
(GRUNTING)
RAIMI: It was an interesting
movie to direct
because most of the actors
and actresses got to play
alternate versions of themselves.
And because they were such great actors,
they knew it didn't take that much.
It was just a little tweak
in the character.
The tiniest difference
in the personality
was enough to communicate
the difference...
Hey, lab coat.
RAIMI: ...who they were.
DOCTOR STRANGE:
Where the hell are we?
Look, I don't know who you are,
or what you think
you're trying to do here,
but these situations don't usually...
RAIMI: That's Why I like Christine's
performance so much here.
Christine?
WALDRON: This was,
aside from making Wanda the villain,
when we took things apart
and started over...
This was probably
the biggest new choice, was bringing
Christine back into the fold
and really making hers
and Strange's story
his emotional heart of the picture...
You know, I just think
Rachel is such a breath of fresh air
to the movie, really, at this point.
She's so relatable to the audience,
who've been dealing with so much crazy
and miserable stuff.
And she's such a great comic actress,
who comes in here and really just,
you know,
is able to make the audience smile.
Our universe is 838, and we've...
WALDRON: She's great.
It was great to have her.
RAIMI: Yes. She has a great sense
of humour, just like you're saying,
and, also, I was surprised
at what a great action actress she was
when it came time to do her fight scenes
and tumbling and battling.
She was so good at that.
So, how'd you end up working here?
Wherever here is.
WALDRON: Yeah, that day in the sewer,
running through the tunnels,
was her first day,
and she had really
just given birth somewhat,
you know, a couple of months prior,
and was just
haulin' ass through this tunnel,
was like a real action star.
RAIMI: This is one
of my favourite moments.
What were we to each other
in this universe?
PALMER: I love hearing Universe 616
reconfirmed
for our fans of the comics.
You know, that's a big...
The number carries a lot of weight
for the fans.
So, to hear it confirmed
by Dr. Christine Palmer here
is pretty exciting.
Christine, you gotta let us out of here.
PALMER: There was hints of it
in previous movies.
And Thor: The Dark World,
Dr. Selvig hinted it.
Earth-616,
and in Spider-Man: Far from Home,
Mysterio commented on the fact
that our universe was Earth-616.
So, maybe he knew something more
than we thought he did at the time,
but it's really here that we hear it
confirmed for the first time.
Someone from my universe
wants that girl...
and she's gonna rip this place apart
atom-by-atom
until she gets what she wants,
so I don't care if you're from
the Avengers or S.H.I.E.L.D...
We're neither.
WALDRON: Shout out
to Brian Michael Bendis,
Jonathan Hickman...
HYDRA?
WALDRON: I was just trying to get
through the first draft of the script,
desperately, in August of 2020.
Didn't really have
a second half of the second act.
And had no idea
where the hell I was going.
And I just thought,
"Well, why don't I take a swing
"and drop the Illuminati in there?"
PALMER: And swing you did.
Yeah. Those Jonathan Hickman
Illuminati comics were
some of the greatest comics
ever written,
I think, those New Avengers comics
from the Secret Wars era.
But, Michael, I remember reading
your first draft of the Illuminati stuff
and just being in disbelief, going,
"She kills all the Illuminati.
"He had her kill all Illuminati.
"We're never going to be
able to do this. This is a...
"Wait, Can we do this?
I wish we could do this."
(WALDRON LAUGHS)
WALDRON: Yeah, I think I watched Aliens
and was just thinking about
the way those Marines get massacred.
Yeah, it was... I'm glad it worked.
Eons ago, the first demon, Chthon,
carved his dark magic...
WALDRON: I think, originally, the Wasp
was a version, was in the Illuminati,
and the Wasp shrunk down
and flew at Wanda.
And she just clapped her hands
and smushed the Wasp
in the first draft.
PALMER: Yeah. I was so scared
someone was going to tell us
we were going too far,
and nobody ever did.
Sam, you always helped us take it there.
Kevin always encouraged us
to push it further.
Our other bosses,
Louis D'Esposito, Victoria Alonso,
everyone supported us every step
of the way to push this movie...
That far. (CHUCKLES)
WALDRON: These were fun days,
Sam, watching you
shoot this horror stuff.
PALMER: That set was amazing.
Talk about Charlie Wood's
amazing set, Sam. This was...
Seeing that statue of Wanda
on that wall in person...
If you notice to the left and right,
there's details of Billy and Tommy
on the wall next to them.
Like, Charlie's attention to detail
is unparalleled,
the best in the Multiverse.
RAIMI: I agree.
They've been waiting for me.
PALMER: Yeah,
that Wanda relief on the wall,
that is not a visual effect.
That was really there.
It's a throne.
I love Ultron.
RAIMI: One of my favourite
Benedict moments is coming up.
When these robots push him
into the room and...
There were obviously
no robots pushing him.
He just had to fake that body motion,
but he really sells it well.
He's a great physical performer.
838 MORDO: Stephen Strange,
you are now called
before the Illuminati.
I, Baron Karl Mordo,
the Sorcerer Supreme, do hereby...
"Karl"?
- 838 MORDO: Captain Carter.
- (CAPTAIN AMERICA THEME PLAYS)
The first Avenger.
Blackagar Boltagon.
RAIMI: Hayley At well was
wonderful to work with.
Blackagar Boltagon?
RAIMI: Along with An son Mount.
Great Black Bolt.
PALMER: God, having An son Mount
in this movie as Black Bolt is so cool.
WALDRON: Lashana Lynch.
RAIMI: Lashana Lynch
was a pleasure to work with.
Reed Richards of the Fantastic Four.
- RAIMI: So was John.
- WALDRON: There he is.
PALMER: It's so exciting.
A dream come true.
I'm sorry. Is this a joke to you?
PALMER: Truly a dream come true.
Yeah, a little bit.
RAIMI: It's so funny that Kevin
cast John because the fans had a dream
of who the perfect
Reed Richards would be.
And because it's an alternate universe,
I think, Kevin said,
"Let's make that dream come true."
PALMER: It's exciting.
RAIMI: I've always really enjoyed
all of his performances.
PALMER: It's exciting that costume
designed by Ryan Meinerding,
is a really special treat...
The detail of the teleportation device
he uses to get into the scene
is something we took from the comics.
That's Doctor Doom's time door.
WALDRON: Reed Richards is my favourite
Marvel Comics character.
So, it was a real honour to get to
write his first entry, I guess,
here in the MCU.
John's such an amazing performer
and such
a great partner in bringing
this role to life for the first time.
No. No, you cannot. Not unless
you give me The Book of Vishanti.
PALMER: Time Platform.
From our experience, the greatest danger
to the Multiverse, it turns out...
RAIMI: Because your changes
to the script, Michael, came in late,
as far as introducing the Illuminati
as you've said...
You worked on it in August of that year.
It was quite a surprise,
probably, to Graham Churchyard,
to have five new superhero costumes
suddenly thrust upon him
that were necessary for delivery
in such a short amount of time.
He really came through.
I should say six, with Professor X.
What truth?
PALMER: And, while it is not
Professor X's first time on screen,
it is the first time we see that
hoverchair from the animated series
in the live action appearance.
WALDRON: Yeah, I think, especially
for guys like us, like me and Richie,
who grew up with that X—Men
animated series,
to get to bring
that specific look to life
with that music cue was really exciting.
PALMER: It's pretty amazing. We had...
Us three had talked about
the yellow chair
and then Kevin said,
"Take it a step further.
"Talk to Danny Elf man and see if he can
incorporate the animated series theme
into his intro," which Danny did
in a really elegant but still fun way.
In the infinite Multiverse,
there's a cure for every illness.
A solution to every problem.
I won't lose them again.
Try as you might, Wanda,
you cannot control everything.
But I can.
So cool, I'm still thinking
about the Illuminati.
Hearing Reed Richards
talk about Incursions...
WALDRON: Again, that's pretty cool.
I'm thinking about this day, Sam.
I think this is one of the days
we were doing blackjack
training on our phones.
I have a memory of us standing...
RAIMI. That's right.
You found that program, right?
WALDRON: No. You showed me.
RAIMI: I showed you.
And you just excelled at it.
That's right. I showed you.
And then you learned it
so much faster than me.
I went, "Wait a minute.
"I just showed...
How can you be so good?"
WALDRON: We got to take you to Vegas.
There's goes Wong.
PALMER: He's dead. Bye, Wong.
Bye—bye, Wong.
WALDRON: Continuing the long tradition
of heroes in the MCU
dying by being thrown off cliffs.
PALMER: I remember, Sam,
you pitching him the story
and making him...
Benny Wong believe for a second
that he was actually
gonna die in that moment.
RAIMI: When I told it to him
the first time?
PALMER: (CHUCKLES) Yeah, you said,
I remember, "I'm sorry to tell you."
RAIMI: I think I remember that.
PALMER: "I'm really sorry to tell you
that's it for Wong."
And then he didn't know
yet whether or not you were the jokester
that you are.
WALDRON: Witch across the moon.
RAIMI: Yeah, he didn't know,
and he's thinking, "Wait a minute."
He's probably thinking,
"Wait a minute, you idiot!
"I had planned
on a long career with Marvel.
"What do you mean
I die being thrown off a cliff?"
I think that's what he was thinking
for a moment.
PALMER: Another cool detail about
ProfessorX here is Graham Churchyard,
our costume designer, studied
the animated series and found
the exact olive green for the suit.
Like, he was such a nerd over it.
Like we all are, of course, and
it was really cool to do that with him.
And the tie. Like, he really brought
that animated version of Professor X
to life.
But, again, this is an alternate,
alternate, alternate version.
It's not exactly the same version
from the comics...
Everyone in that reality died.
Everyone.
Stephen renounced the Darkhold's evil...
and helped us find
The Book of Vishanti...
a weapon we did use together
to defeat Thanos.
WALDRON: Lashana Lynch is fantastic.
This is really her first time.
Stepping into the role of Captain Marvel
on this alternate universe.
80 cool.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(SOMBRE MUSIC PLAYING)
PALMER: Here, you get to see
an alternate universe version
of the events of Titan.
You know, what if the Illuminati
had fought Thanos on Titan?
RAIMI: Benedict is so good
in this scene.
Just looking at him, you know he's
been through it all, he's sinned,
and knows he has to pay for those sins.
He's caused terrible destruction,
his guilt,
sadness, resolution,
that it's time for himself to die.
PALMER: Sam these are some fun days
on the Mix Stage with Lora and Juan,
coming up with that Black Bolt effect.
RAIMI: Yeah. Juan Peralta
and Lora Hirschberg did such a great job
mixing our sound for us.
It was a big moment when Black Bolt
had to finally release his blast.
We designed it with some
great sound designers
and they mixed it beautifully,
I thought.
It really should be heard
in Dolby Atmos.
You built a statue.
The world needs heroes.
WALDRON: Hayley At well.
Great to finally see
Captain Carter in person.
Every Doctor Strange is capable of.
PALMER: I remember
you coming up with that.
"The world needs heroes" idea.
The statue was a cover-up
for what actually happened.
- It's pretty...
- WALDRON: Right.
I came up with that
at 3:00 in the morning.
I grabbed my wife and
I was, like, "He was bad.
"It was a lie."
RAIMI: Yes, 'cause you originally
wrote him as the hero
that we think he is,
as Strange thinks he is.
WALDRON: Right.
RAIMI: And then when you improved it,
gave it more depth...
You had to...
Because we had already shot the statue,
you had to figure out,
"How are we going to explain that?"
That was great.
PALMER: I love that moment with Wanda
fighting those Ultron statues.
We always had this idea, Sam.
You had said you wanted to see Wanda,
when she's in there with the Illuminati,
looking like Carrie, but how do we
do that with the blood?
And we had all these Ultron robots
that were spewing oil and giving
an even darker version of that look.
It was a really cool idea.
Thank you.
ULTRON SENTRY:
Perimeter breakdown.
PALMER: I love those Ultron robots
voiced by our friend Ross Marquand.
Everybody out.
RAIN“. I loved Carrie, the movie,
but I don't think I ever
consciously wanted her
to look like Carrie.
But I think she's just started
to look like Carrie,
and we started talking about it.
WALDRON: The whole stunts team
did such a great job.
All this stuff.
(SHOTS FIRING)
RAIMI: Incredible job.
My hat's off to them.
ULTRON HEAD: Ultron commands...
RAIMI: And Jeff Habberstad usually led
our stunt team in all this photography.
He did such a great job
as the second unit director.
Oh, no.
(CAPTAIN AMERICA THEME PLAYING)
RAIMI: These were multiple locations
put together
based on the British Museum.
The bio chamber back there
wasn't really there.
This is really patterned after
the lobby of the British Museum.
You've possessed an innocent woman,
but you can still do the right thing.
Let her go.
PALMER: This is one of the most
amazing moments.
Please.
PALMER: In any movie. Now, Sam,
I remember Kevin saying to you,
"Black Bolt's awesome,
and we've got to have him in there.
"But I really don't know how
you're gonna take out Black Bolt.
"He's so powerful, you know.
What could she possibly do?
"If he opens his mouth..."
What mouth?
PALMER: And you turned around
and you said, "What mouth?"
WALDRON: Yeah,
Sam riffed... Just instantly
this was Sam's answer, and it's one of
the coolest moments in the whole movie.
It's also absolutely disgusting.
That is so great.
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
RAIMI: I'm sorry, everybody.
WALDRON: It's so good.
There he goes.
PALMER: That was... Hayley and Lashana
came up with that cool look
between them in the moment.
You know, the idea being
they were a well-oiled machine.
RAIMI. That's right.
We challenged them
to come up with a badass look
and they each did. It was really cool.
PALMER: Sam, that statue
in the Illuminati lobby?
It's pretty familiar-looking.
Who's that statue of?
You are in no position to give orders.
RAIMI: That was patterned after Xena.
And I think it was your idea.
PALMER: I mean,
I 7! take credit for it, sure.
RAIMI: The great Lucy Lawless.
Haven't you had enough?
Oh, I could do this all day.
RAIMI: This scene pays tribute
to female heroes and villains.
She's the embodiment of both, so
it's really appropriate for this moment.
- (SHIELD SLICES)
- (GASPS)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(RUMBLING)
WALDRON: I have to imagine
that moment hurts Wanda.
She was close to Steve.
She would have known Peggy,
known of her.
PALMER: I think both
of these characters, this is, you know,
Monica Rambeau's mother,
who she knew from WandaVision.
This is an amazing thing
we got to do for the fans as well.
To, you know, "Who's going to win,
Captain Marvel or the Scarlet Witch?"
The two most powerful beings
in the universe.
Who's going to come out
of this fight on top?
They both have their powers
from Infinity Stones.
But Wanda is the Scarlet Witch.
So, I don't know that there's
any stopping the Scarlet Witch.
But Captain Marvel comes pretty close.
So what it seems happened
is the Scarlet Witch
siphoned her power momentarily
long enough to dispatch her.
Do you guys think she's really gone,
Captain Marvel, in that moment,
and so, do you think she's really
dispatched her?
WALDRON: Go see The Marvels to find out.
- Maybe. I don't know.
- PALMER: That's a joke. That's a joke.
- That's a joke. I've no idea.
- (ALL LAUGHING)
You know,
you hated me where I came from.
And I bet, secretly, my brother,
you hated me here.
RAIMI: Most of this Illuminati scene
was shot with individual actors.
The other actor wasn't even present,
as is in the case here.
You know nothing of this universe!
RAIMI: And in the whole previous scene,
when you see the line of Illuminati,
they were pretty much
all done separately.
One or two of the actors
were together, and that was it.
They were all composited
into the finished shots.
WALDRON: Really, such an amazing
technical feat by Sam
to make that sequence so compelling.
Yes, those are...
It's exciting to see those heroes
up in that lineup but, ultimately,
it is one character standing opposite
six folks sitting down
and Sam and his team
found a way
to make it so visually dynamic
and working with our editors,
Bob and Tia,
they've really made it come alive and...
And it's more than just a cameo,
saying dialogue.
It's a compelling, exciting sequence,
which is not easy to do.
That was a fake leg.
That was a leg on a broom.
Sam, remember that?
- You said, "Give me a leg on a broom."
- (RAIMI LAUGHS)
WALDRON: Love that one.
RAIMI: It was? I completely forgot.
WALDRON: Yeah, it was a leg on a broom.
PALMER: Michael,
I remember having to go...
I remember you having to walk up there
where Benedict was.
WALDRON: Yeah, I was up there.
Everybody else was on wires.
So, it was, like, "I'm gonna..."
PALMER: It was a really, really
high-up platform that Benedict was on
and, like Michael just said,
everybody was on wires
and then Benedict's, like, "Michael,
could I talk to you for a second?
And Michael had to climb
all the way up on this.
WALDRON: Sam was up there, too.
We were both up there.
Remember that? It was so high.
RAIMI: It was scary. So scary.
Trying not to show Benedict
how frightened I was.
WALDRON: That's what making a movie is.
It's just trying to never show
how frightened you are.
Kind of a perfect representation
of that.
PROF CHARLES XAVIER: Enough!
(PANTING)
What a showdown this is.
PALMER: Sir Patrick Stewart.
WALDRON: He was so great.
PALMER: He's one of the coolest guys.
RAIMI: He was such a gentleman
to work with, Sir Patrick Stewart.
He had such class about him
and he, instantly, obviously,
created this character years ago
for 20th Century Fox
and it was great that he took the best
parts of it and brought him back.
Such a pro.
WALDRON: It's a great scary moment, Sam.
RAIMI: Poor Lizzie. Lizzie had to live
under there for a while.
Grab my hand.
Perhaps, if I can pull you
from under the rubble...
the spell will break.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
RAIMI: She puts everything she's got
into every moment,
whenever she's on camera.
I really admire that about her.
(SCARLET WITCH WHISPERING IN SOKOVIAN)
And she's so different
than the other Wanda
in the most subtle ways.
WALDRON: Lizzie talked about how,
by this point in the movie, she's Wanda.
Our Wanda is just consumed by anger.
She's been pushed so far,
that's really what's driving her
to her madness at this point.
Hey! You all right?
You okay?
Hey.
- You all right?
- AMERICA: Yeah.
Hey.
She fixed him.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Xavier said I built a way point
to The Book of Vishanti.
Can you take us there?
How am I supposed to trust you?
I know what happened,
and I'm sorry for what he did...
but, believe me,
The Book of Vishanti is the only way.
Yeah. Your way.
You sound a lot like my Stephen
right now.
He had to be the one holding the knife.
WALDRON: This is a great moment
for alternate Christine,
where we're seeing
the differences between her
and the Christine of our universe,
that she's been hardened by
the events that she experienced
with her universe's Strange and it's...
Smart kid.
WALDRON: Surprisingly, America comes
to his defence.
(SIGHS) Give me your hand.
PALMER: It's one of my favourite shots
in the movie coming up, Michael.
That goes to what you were just saying
about Lizzie.
Wanda's being so consumed by anger
that she's just using... This shot.
It's her bloody feet
just walking over glass.
She does not care about this body
that she is in at all.
She is going to do whatever it takes.
She is limping. She's got broken bones.
She is just on her mission
and nothing's going to stop her.
And I think that shot really shows you.
WALDRON: This was Rachel's first day.
RAIMI: Bob, our editor,
insisted that shot be in.
PALMER: (LAUGHS) Thank you, Bob.
WALDRON: This is so great.
This is one of my favourite things,
this practical effect right here.
PALMER: And this was Jamie Christopher
and Chris Corbould...
That was another idea
we had in that moment, right, Sam?
It was just Jamie saying, "Hey,
you want to blow up those tables?
"We can do it." Jamie always had this
thing about some of the best effects
you can just achieve if you just
come up with them in the moment.
So, he was always trying to just
come up with practical effects,
and it really was a plus for the movie.
And that was one of the coolest ones.
RAIMI: Yeah, that was a real plus.
And I almost didn't do it
even after he said that.
And Bob Ross, he was on set
and said, "Just do it, Sam.
"It's not gonna take that much time,"
so I said, "Okay, great.
"Great. Let's do it. You're right"
PALMER: It's so cool. This is so cool.
Those shots of Wanda that you did
running through the tunnels are amazing.
WALDRON: You had a motorcycle
in the tunnels, right, Sam,
- with a camera on the back?
- RAIMI: That's right.
Our cinematographer lined us up
with a great device.
You know, it's a little mini steadicam,
on the back of a motorcycle.
It was really cool.
Perfect way to do it.
I had originally wanted him
to give me streams of light,
in concentric circles,
moving in opposing
directions of the camera,
and he quickly didn't do that.
I think he thought it was too hokey,
but I really wanted it to be
more hypnotic and dizzying,
that chase through the tunnels,
but it turned out to be a good move
not to do that.
I warned you.
WALDRON: What a moment that is.
Put together well.
It's such a great scare.
PALMER: Yes, I recall your creation
of the slowing down of the drips
is a really unique thing I don't think
anybody's ever seen before.
- Did you kill her?
- No, just bought us some time.
RAIMI: That was a device
to try and build suspense
and get us to the point
where that scare really delivered.
And Bob did a really good job
of cutting that, I thought.
An enchantment that's specific to me,
something only I would know.
WALDRON: It's a nice opportunity
to call back the watch,
which is a great emotional...
I mean, really, when I watched the
first movie in preparation for this,
I watched it a thousand times
and that watch was kind of
the emotional core of that movie,
so it felt like a cool way
to bring it back.
It's something
that kind of unifies Stranges
and Christines across all universes.
PALMER: It's really cool.
All right.
WALDRON: For a long time,
Sam's editor, Bob,
had Strange open the door,
I don't know where he pulled it.
It sounded like Snake Plissken talking.
As that door's opening, he just goes,
"All right"
PALMER: Sam's editor put it in,
and Marvel's editor took it out.
RAIMI: It was actually...
It was Benedict kind of making fun,
but Bob loved it.
He really wanted that in the picture.
Come on, kid.
You got this.
We got this.
Yeah.
PALMER: This whole sequence
coming up right here,
Benedict Cumberbatch
really collaborated with us
in such a detail-orientated way,
and it's such a cool part
of the movie now,
but he really had
such a specific idea for this moment
that he kept pitching us about,
"We get to the book,
"And then Wanda's gonna show up
and just rip America from our..."
And he always talked about it
and it really came to life
in a great way.
All right, Book.
Give me what I need.
WALDRON: The temp score in the scene
was always James Homer's Aliens score.
It was appropriate
because a reference for this shot
was when Bishop gets stabbed
at the end of Aliens.
Showed Xochitl that before we shot that.
PALMER: You guys notice
that star in the book?
RAIMI: Michael, here, you wrote
about The Book of Vishanti
as that thing which gives the sorcerer
whatever they need
to defeat their enemy.
Yes, and that star is to signify
that the lore of the book is true.
And what Strange needed was
America Chavez, her help.
And that's what he finally
surrenders to
by the climax of the picture.
WALDRON: Correct.
RAIMI: That he doesn't have to be
the one holding the knife,
as Michael wrote it.
My boys.
WALDRON: I always liked the idea
that we could set up this MacGuffin
throughout the entire movie
and then just blow it to hell
as we kind of catapult into
the third act.
RAIMI: That was a great stunt.
Brycen Counts did our stunts.
Incredible stunt coordinator.
PALMER: Shout out Brycen.
They'll never know.
Maybe not.
But you will.
Oh, no.
Oh, crap.
PALMER: (LAUGHS) That "Oh, crap!"
always made Rachel laugh.
838 CHRISTINE: It's like this reality
collapsed in on itself.
DOCTOR STRANGE: Yeah.
- Or two realities collided.
- (WHOOSHING)
Come on.
America doesn't have long.
WALDRON: Really amazing combination
of practical effects.
PALMER: Hey, the Delta 88, Sam.
RAIMI: Wow.
PALMER: That was actually hoisted up.
Again, Charlie Wood and his team.
They got that Delta 88 to the UK.
And hoisted it up on giant cranes
and spun it around for us.
That's all practical.
Here we get to see
the effects of an Incursion.
DOCTOR STRANGE:
Well, I can see why you guys
were so worried about Incursions.
838 CHRISTINE: Whatever happened,
this universe's you didn't do
a very good job of stopping it.
WALDRON: Sam, I wrote so many
different versions of this dialogue.
An infinite Multiverse.
RAIMI: Yes. Originally, you wrote
Christine coming in with Strange.
WALDRON: She came in,
the door shut in her face.
The building teleported her out,
all sorts of different stuff.
RAIMI: So many great artists worked
on the look of this movie,
not just Charles Wood
and John Mathieson, our cinematographer.
But shots like this were designed
after great artists' paintings of what
the clash of universes could be like
for this particular environment.
Strange's place so...
I was always very impressed
with the concept illustrations.
We really went for re—creating them.
That job was done first by the art
directors, and then, later, by
John Mathieson on set and, then,
in post-production by Janek Sirrs.
MAN: How did you get here?
PALMER: I just want to shout out
Cyndi Ochs, our visual effects producer,
without whom none of that stuff
could have been brought to life.
I'm just one of us.
From the Multiverse?
That's right.
Prove it.
We had a sister.
Donna.
PALMER: This is rich, and more lore
straight from the comics...
She died when we were kids.
PALMER: I know, Sam and Michael,
you guys were always keen on hitting
and explaining the part of his backstory
that turned him into who he was
without it feeling like it was something
that we hadn't known about.
...she fell through the ice.
WALDRON: Yeah, the delicate balance of
you don't want it to feel like
that sequel thing of,
"Wow, a foundational pillar."
I couldn't save her.
WALDRON: My personality
just happened to pop up
here in movie number two.
But, in this case, I think that Strange
is such a guarded character,
and it actually makes sense
that it's simply something he never
ever talks about
and only does here in this moment
and never really again.
Until?
PALMER: Yeah, you guys found a very
elegant way of doing it.
To whom?
RAIMI: Michael, you wrote so much
of this movie during production.
Postproduction, too.
I remember we were probably
halfway into production
where you came up with this scene.
Evil Strange. A brand new concept.
It didn't exist when we got to England.
WALDRON: That's true. That is true.
RAIMI: Pre-production.
That's a start.
WALDRON: Yeah, there was another version
where Strange went to a universe
and met a character
that we called Melvin Strange,
a street magician who was a version
of Strange without any magic.
And they had, I guess, a... certainly
a much less adversarial conversation.
It was more of an enlightening,
sweet exchange.
It was good but it wasn't...
it didn't build the tension
and raise the stakes we needed
at this point in the movie.
And so, really,
collaborated with Benedict,
and he pushed us to this point.
We worked with him a lot on this scene.
He made it. He made it great.
PALMER: Yeah, he's so good in this scene
on both sides.
But, yeah, I remember you guys
sitting and working on this.
There was actually
a little toilet bowl in the set dec.
If you look in this room,
there's all these weird artifacts.
There was actually a little toilet bowl
in the corner
that I believe Michael would sit on
and write with Benedict
in the corner on his laptop.
...and wondered why I'd lied.
I never meant for any of this to happen.
I was looking for a world
where things were different.
Where I had Christine,
where I was happy.
But I didn't find it.
RAIMI: Michael, when you put
in this third eye,
that really was an element of the old
Doctor Strange comic books, wasn't it?
WALDRON: Yeah, that was something,
it had shown up throughout
the comic books,
in really Multiversal lore, I guess,
in general.
Felt like a cool, creepy...
The Dark hold exacts a heavy toll.
Okay.
All the more reason to give it a rest
and let me have it.
Here's the deal.
PALMER: One of my favourite lines.
...if you give me your Christine.
Yeah.
I don't think she's gonna go for that.
No?
WALDRON: Benedict,
so unflappable as Strange,
really has a very great
Harrison Ford quality about him,
such a fun hero to get to write.
WALDRON: Sam, tell us
about this sequence. It's so great.
RAIMI: So many artists worked on this.
I knew we wanted something special
for Sinister Strange,
and we didn't want to just have a fight.
Even though we had the world's best
fight choreographers
and stunt coordinators,
and second unit directors,
we really wanted to have
something visually unique.
See Sorcerer vs. Sorcerer,
something we hadn't quite seen before.
So many artists worked on this.
Doug Lefter, my great friend
and a brilliant artist
and great director, really led the way
in this sequence.
And we followed his lead.
And, also, Richie,
who was the great artist
that guided us in the look
of these notes?
PALMER: Bryan Andrews.
RAIMI: Yeah, we owe him a lot.
PALMER: Who has been working with us
at Marvel Studios for a decade,
and he's the director
of our What “I? series.
RAIMI: He was so great.
PALMER: Bryan Andrews.
We did have a lot of great artists, Sam.
Doug Lefter is the best in the biz.
We also had Jeremy Simser, who is
one of the great storyboard artists.
Anthony Chun, who is Michael's friend
from Rick and Mortys world
came in and helped us with the sequence.
It really was a family effort
led by Doug.
And then, of course,
we couldn't have done it
without Danny Elf man and his team.
You know, Bill Abbott and
Ellen Segal, of course.
RAIMI: Danny did such a great job rising
to the occasion for this sequence.
After he did it for us once,
we went back again and...
He was in the middle of a concerto
that he had written.
He was doing the performance in Europe,
and we interrupted him between
two different performances
to do an emergency rewrite
where he was... The music of the battle.
It wasn't the score
so much as it was...
We wanted him to be
the effects designer, so to speak.
What is the noise of those notes?
Let that be the music,
and he blew us away
with his final designs.
PALMER: Yeah, it was so amazing.
That was Danny and Chris Bacon
and Jussi Tegelman.
Whole squad.
RAIMI: Jussi did an incredible job in
our sound design along with Addison.
They both did brilliantly.
And the movie goes
so many outrageous places,
that the sound has to follow,
and, in fact,
the sound has to lead the way
and break new ground,
Multiversal ground.
We needed to hear things
we'd never heard before.
- Like the voice of Black Bolt.
- PALMER: Yeah.
RAIMI. Or what the alternate universe
would sound like.
PALMER: Yeah, that was Addison.
That voice of Black Bolt was so cool.
WALDRON: Such a great physical
performance from Benny Wong.
He really gets the crap beat out of him
in this movie and you feel it.
He's that John McClane kind of hero.
Just getting beat up
and just keeps on going.
- Love him for it.
- PALMER: Phase One, baby.
Hang on, we're coming.
Yeah, this idea of Dead Strange.
What are you doing with the Dark hold?
WALDRON: I mean,
I think it came from, literally,
you were, like, "He's screwed.
He's stuck in this universe."
I mean, we'd really written ourselves
into a corner, and we were...
PALMER: We did such a good job
of making it impossible
to travel between universes
if you are not America Chavez.
So, now what do we do with him?
He's stranded.
WALDRON: And, so, Richie and!
just started working it out,
and it felt like the coolest thing
that Strange could have to do
was Dream walk, and we wondered...
The problem is, there's nobody for him
to Dream walk into in our universe.
Then, the idea came.
"What if that dead body from the
opening made its way into our universe?"
So, then we got really excited
because we knew that
our director was Sam Raimi,
and we were potentially going to be
possessing a dead body in this movie.
PALMER: And it's so cool.
Benedict was all in.
You know, it was not easy for him
to put on that prosthetic makeup.
That Dead Strange makeup.
That's all Benedict. That's all real.
It's all practical.
For the most part, of course.
Janek and the visual effects team had to
fill out the cavity
on the side of his face,
but, for the most part,
it's all prosthetics done.
I gotta give a shout out
to Donald McInnes,
who is Benedict's lead hair
and makeup person,
who really helped us come up
with all the designs
for the various Stranges,
but was there every step of the way
when it came to Dead Strange as well.
RAIMI: I love Danny's score here.
WALDRON: Sammy, you always...
You know, we came to you and it was,
"All right, Sam.
We're going to do a dead body.
"We're so excited."
But you always preached,
"You can't do a dead body
just for a dead body's sake."
Like everything with you, it had to be
story-driven, character-driven,
weren't gonna play it for laughs,
or for gags.
We were going to take it seriously,
and that's why it works.
And that's why, I think, we're able
to have fun with the sequence.
PALMER: Benedict just giving it his all.
RAIMI: I thought it was such an original
idea you guys came up with.
So unique.
That's why I think
the audience likes it,
because I don't think they've seen
something quite like this before.
PALMER: Not in a Marvel Studios...
RAIMI: The idea of it is different.
FEMALE SOUL 1: Cease your Dream walk,
or face the eternal consequences.
(GROANING)
RAIMI: Weta did a beautiful job
with the animation.
Great teams of animation.
Great ideas for movement.
A tremendous amount of artistry
went into their...
the effects here, I was very impressed.
PALMER: This is a classic Sam idea
to plus this
with the souls of the damned
that attack the dead body.
Sam, you want to talk about that?
That was just such an amazing addition.
This sequence, this whole thing.
Those souls.
RAIMI: Yeah, I think I remember
the test audiences,
and maybe, because we haven't
released the film,
the main audiences won't understand
who these antagonists are.
I think that was the problem
in the test screening.
"What is Dead Strange facing?
Why are they trying to stop him?"
The Brazier of Bom'Galiath.
RAIMI: When you guys came up
with that great idea, I wanted...
PALMER: The Brazier of Bom'Galiath.
RAIMI: I love the fact that you came up
with the idea of Dead Strange.
Maybe this is what it takes
to defeat Wanda.
Going to this extent, he's going
to Dream walk into his dead body,
and that'll be cool.
But we needed even that character
to have an antagonist,
and that's really why I wanted
those souls of the damned.
But I do think there's
a little confusion
on the part of the audience.
Even you, Michael, going, "Who?
Why do we want this?"
But I wanted an antagonist.
I wanted even him to have an antagonist.
And then we worked out that
he could take them and use them
and make his cloak of souls out of it.
I think, visually, it came out
to be a plus for the picture,
even if there is a little confusion
as to the idea behind it.
WALDRON: The audience
watching this right now...
(WALDRON LAUGHING)
"I wanted them
to tell us what this was!"
Shout out to
Rachel McAdams there, by the way.
"Go back to hell." She gets it.
I think a kick-ass action line.
I love that moment for Christine Palmer.
And the explanation here is,
I think, that Strange is...
he's breaking the rules.
There's rules to these things.
You know, the realms
of the spirits, whatever...
Cannot possess a dead body.
That's against the rules
in any universe.
You know, there's a toll to be paid.
But he's a guy who's okay
breaking the rules.
PALMER: I wonder if
he'll ever pay that toll.
He breaks the rules
and becomes the hero.
WALDRON: The bill comes due.
PALMER: Yeah, when is the bill going
to come due for Strange?
(EXCLAIMS) Wong!
RAIMI: I remember when Doug Lefter
first showed me those storyboards,
I was so excited.
It's just what I wanted,
for Wong to come back as the hero.
As Michael had written him.
Doug came up with a visual way
to present that, an effective means.
WALDRON: Lizzie called these guys
her animals.
- (WALDRON LAUGHS)
- "These are my animals."
WALDRON: They really have
a tough time in this movie.
RAIMI: They had a much larger
role in the climax,
as originally conceived, and then...
We had to pare it down, as happens,
and just remain with what was necessary.
Dream walking. You hypocrite!
(SOULS SCREECHING)
WALDRON: So cool.
This time, it's gonna take more
than killing me
to kill me.
PALMER: I've just been patting
Michael on the back
every time there's a cool line.
I'm physically sitting here
patting him on the back.
WALDRON: This is the first time
I'm seeing this
with a lot of these finished effects.
Sam, this is incredible,
the way this looks.
RAIMI: The effects teams
did a beautiful job here.
I don't even wanna know.
(GRUNTING)
WALDRON: Sam always called this
"the bag of trash"
when Strange sends over
the bag of trash to Wong.
PALMER: (LAUGHS) "So, now you're gonna
flip that bag of trash over to Wong?"
- (SCARLET WITCH GRUNTING)
- SOUL 1: No!
- SOUL 2: No!
- SOUL 3: No!
RAIMI: Richie, you play one of those
voices of the souls of the dammed
that reach out and grab Wanda's hand.
PALMER: I do.
I'd like to thank you
for that opportunity.
To be a soul of the damned
in a Sam Raimi movie.
RAIMI: I really like the writing.
Love the writing in this scene
and how Benedict performs it.
It's the only way he's going
to have to break through
and go to a place
he hasn't been to before.
We think it's that terrible, low place.
Like you wrote about
in the first scene of the movie,
But he's actually ascending
to a better place.
Xochitl gave a great performance here.
I was very proud of her.
She's a great actress.
We're going to be seeing
a lot more of her in the future.
She also was incredible in the stunts.
Richie, can you tell us about that?
PALMER: Yes, she worked closely with Joe
and Brycen and did a lot of prep work.
Xochitl came to us when,
I believe, she was 14 years old
and she just dived into
all those stunts head first,
and said, basically, you know,
"Let me just do it once,
and then I got it"
And she was right.
She just needed to do something once,
and then
she had it under total control.
We were dropping her on wires
from far heights, from...
For example, in the Gargantos sequence,
when she falls through the bus
and the cloak catches her,
that was actually her falling
from an incredibly high height,
and she did it like a pro,
after only one or two tries.
It was really amazing,
and then, you know,
we had her being
flung around in this sequence
and just doing things
that she had never done before,
but doing it so naturally and so well.
She's a really talented,
talented young actor.
I've got you.
(GROANING)
- (SEARING)
- (YELLING IN PAIN)
(GROANS)
(WIND GUSTS)
WALDRON: Love these candles.
(GROANING)
(AMERICA YELLING)
PALMER:
There's another, Xochitl hitting...
- So cool.
- WALDRON: Yeah.
RAIMI: And then Danny brings
America Chavez's theme into it,
which is great.
WALDRON: That's so cool.
She's stronger than the Scarlet Witch.
Oh, no, never mind.
Nobody's stronger than
the Scarlet Witch. I forgot.
RAIMI: I think the Scarlet Witch
was just surprised briefly...
PALMER: Exactly.
RAIMI: ...that this was happening.
She never felt a Multiversal punch.
WALDRON: This climax was all your idea.
This was all Sam's idea.
Just followed his lead here,
and this is such a tremendously
emotional way to defeat Wanda.
Sam brought this to us
almost fully formed.
PALMER: Yeah, early on, too,
and it never changed.
WALDRON: No.
PALMER: Because why would we change it?
It was perfect.
Get away from them.
- (YELPS)
- BILLY: Mom!
PALMER: Little Easter egg, there,
Snow White in the background.
We worked with
the Walt Disney Animation team.
Thanks to Gordon, one of our animators,
if you notice, animated
Snow White's costume
to match the costumes in Universe 838.
(BOTH WHIMPERING)
Please don't hurt us.
Please.
I would never hurt you.
Never.
I would never hurt anyone.
RAIMI: Jett Klyne and Julian Hilliard
are the two kids, Billy and Tommy,
and they did such a great job.
They are such a pleasure
to work with on set.
Very professional,
and incredibly young to be so good.
WALDRON: This is a long day of them
throwing toys at Lizzie's face.
RAIMI: And Lizzie was always ready
to give the greatest performance,
no matter how many times
we had worked her.
And however long she worked,
or however much emotion
was demanded from her.
I remember going to her once and saying,
"Lizzie, I'm afraid to ask you
do another take
"because you've given so much."
And she turns to me quietly and says,
"Sam, as far as acting goes,
I am a bottomless well of emotion.
"Never be afraid to ask me
for another take or to go deeper."
I said, "Wow, I love it.
All right, let's go again."
PALMER: Well, I think she turned
the audience into a bottomless well
of emotion right now.
RAIMI: I think that's my favourite
shot of the film.
And her performance is also
one of my favourite moments.
WALDRON: Great little bit
of Multiversal forgiveness
between these two.
What now?
PALMER: Strange's arm.
WALDRON: I mean, his face is disgusting.
We have to go. Now!
I opened the Dark hold.
I have to close it.
No one will ever be tempted
by the Dark hold again.
WALDRON: It's an important moment,
I think, to all of us,
the idea that Wanda was not
necessarily just
being controlled by the Book.
She's taking responsibility
for her actions there.
You all right?
- Is it over?
- Yeah.
RAIMI: This scene was one of the last
that we shot for the film.
Shot in the United States.
WALDRON: Yeah, this is one of
the last things I wrote.
PALMER: It's really beautiful.
RAIMI: Richie, will we ever see
the Dark hold again?
PALMER: Only time Will tell.
She did the right thing.
PALMER: She did the right thing.
She destroyed it in every universe.
I don't know how
such a thing could come back.
But where there is good, Sam,
there is evil.
RAIMI: But, technically, aren't there
still Mount Wundagores
in other universes,
where the inscriptions might be?
PALMER: Maybe they all blew up
like the Book just did.
I wish I could show you.
RAIMI: Rachel did such an
emotional job in this scene.
I really love watching her perform it.
- But I have to go.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
It's too bad, though.
WALDRON: Benedict is so great here.
I love you.
PALMER: That exchange.
RAIMI: Yes.
I love you in every universe.
It's very well written.
I loved your lines, Michael.
How every one of him
loves her in every universe?
It's a beautiful sentiment.
WALDRON: It's another...
Worked with Benedict closely on that
to really try to find the right emotion
for Stephen in this moment.
Face your fears...
Doctor Strange.
(PORTAL WHOOSHES)
(TEACHER AND STUDENTS
CHANTING IN MANDARIN)
(CHANTING CONTINUES)
(SIGHS) Ay! How is this so much harder
than a Multiversal portal?
WALDRON: Talked a lot about...
How do we not do a Return of the King?
Have 50 endings.
That movie did win Best Picture, so...
PALMER: Should we have had more endings?
WALDRON: (LAUGHS) Sam,
can we go shoot some more endings?
You used the Dark hold to Dream walk
into your own corpse.
PALMER: I love these two.
I'm fine.
But I do wanna ask you something.
Are you happy?
That's a...
interesting question.
You'd think that saving the world
would get you there...
but it doesn't.
RAIMI: Michael,
this was your setup, wasn't it?
For the Evil Eye appearing on him.
WALDRON: It was.
RAIMI: Is it because he Dream walked...
Is it because he Dream walked
into his corpse?
Or just because he used the Dark hold?
WALDRON: Probably a combination.
He used the Dark hold and did the worst
thing you can do with the Dark hold.
PALMER: Dream walked
and raised the dead...
WALDRON: Yeah.
PALMER: ...in another universe.
WALDRON: I love that bit about happiness
between the two of them.
It's just a...
It's an interesting thing
if you're a superhero.
- 'Sup?
- 'Sup.
WALDRON: This exchange, we wrote about
five minutes before we shot it.
Great.
Your parents would be proud.
RAIMI: I remember. You did.
- It's simple.
- WALDRON: It's one of my favourite bits.
RAIMI: And very, very beautiful.
I'm glad I fell into your universe.
So am I, kid.
So am I.
RAIMI: I really appreciate that
you didn't go for too much.
You just went for what was earned
from the characters.
WALDRON: Learned that from you, pal.
And these great actors,
you don't have to give a lot.
RAIMI: I think when you wrote
that understatement
of their goodbye,
you let the audience fill in
and contribute to it,
which is really nice.
This was one of the first shots
that we did, I think,
also, early in the schedule.
Such a good physical actor
and the music here,
I love that electric guitar
that Danny and his team brought in.
It tells me something's wrong,
goes off key.
PALMER: Cool.
WALDRON: It's so good.
PALMER: I hope you agree, audience-
RAIMI: Well, everybody,
thank you very much for...
for having us be your tour guides
for Doctor Strange
in the Multiverse of Madness.
WALDRON: Thank you. Thanks for watching.
PALMER: Thanks for listening, everybody.
It was a fun ride making it,
it was a fun ride watching it.
WALDRON: Thanks for all the kind
comments on the Internet.
(PALMER LAUGHS)
I know you guys have got
nothing but nice things to say.
That third-eye ending, Sam,
that's pretty cool.
That's so... It was a fun day,
and Benedict was so game
and just having a blast.
I love that... kind of, that
last horror homage.
That kind of fake out, dark ending.
I'm sure there's a term for it.
RAIMI: I remember when you wrote it,
it was very surprising.
When I saw the script, I went,
"What? That happens to him? Really?"
It was like that throughout the entire
process of shooting the picture.
I'd get new scenes and be, like,
"How are we going to do that?"
You know, we can really give him
this shocker of an ending.
He deserves a good ending.
A happy ending, I mean, doesn't he?
But you're right.
It was the right note
to play at that time.
PALMER: Hey, who's to say
it's not a happy ending?
Let's see the next scene.
It's a strange ending.
WALDRON: Once upon a time,
we talked about
having him switch places
with Sinister Strange, right?
How crazy would that have been?
PALMER: How Strange gets trapped
in that universe and Sinister...
Yeah, we talk about the Thriller ending,
and the ending
of the Thriller music video.
He turns around and the third eye opens,
and it's Sinister Strange.
And you hear Vincent Price laughing.
What is this?
Wait, What?
Thought he just had a
gross third eye open up on his head...
Can I help you?
RAIMI: It was really cool
to work with Charlize.
I always wanted to, and this was
only one day together,
but she really nailed the character.
Brought a little zap to it.
PALMER: I mean, she's amazing.
We always wanted to introduce Clea
into the Marvel Cinematic Universe,
into the Decker Strange franchise,
and we always wanted to see this.
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
WALDRON: Karl...
Jamie... Look at these guys.
RAIMI: Now, maybe we could
do our wrap ups.
What do you think?
WALDRON: All right.
PALMER: We'll read everybody's names
as we do the wrap up.
Oh, there's salty Sharp.
WALDRON: Been fun. Thank you, guys.
Thanks, Sam.
Meet your heroes, everybody.
RAIMI: Thank you, Richie.
And thank you, Michael.
It was two fantastic years of my life.
And I really loved spending it
with you guys.
You were great teammates
all along the way.
I won't have done it with anybody else.
PALMER: Well, thank you.
I think we all worked very well together.
I learned a lot from you guys
and it was a fun time,
and I hope everybody listening at home
enjoyed the movie
and enjoyed our commentary.
WALDRON: What are we
going to do together next?
What's next, Sam?
Shall we tell 'em?
PALMER: (LAUGHS) No, no, no. Cut.
WALDRON: Tell everybody right here?
PALMER: Sam! Sam! You say out.
WALDRON: Tell everybody right now.
RAIMI: And cut it.
Cut it out.
- Cut it now.
- (WALDRON EXCLAIMS)
RAIMI: Okay. Let's go, you guys.
That's it.
(GROANING TIREDLY)
(GRUNTS)
(LAUGHING)
It's over.