1
00:03:22,328 --> 00:03:23,629
Yes!

2
00:03:30,753 --> 00:03:33,000
- You failed!
- I didn't.

4
00:03:35,049 --> 00:03:37,009
The gun is in my hand.

5
00:03:37,885 --> 00:03:39,262
I thought I had it.

6
00:03:42,056 --> 00:03:43,975
Sorry, Father.
I'll make it next time.

7
00:03:44,058 --> 00:03:46,185
Never take anything
for granted.

8
00:03:47,395 --> 00:03:48,938
God will take it from you.

9
00:03:50,940 --> 00:03:52,191
Is God bad?

10
00:03:55,778 --> 00:03:57,000
God is fair.

11
00:04:00,616 --> 00:04:03,119
You almost got me,
didn't you, boy?

12
00:04:23,848 --> 00:04:25,975
Did I get my
white hair from you...

13
00:04:26,058 --> 00:04:27,226
...or from Mom?

14
00:04:29,937 --> 00:04:31,397
From your mother.

15
00:04:31,481 --> 00:04:33,941
I can't believe we don't have
any pictures of her.

16
00:04:34,525 --> 00:04:36,799
Everything was destroyed
in the fire.

17
00:04:36,819 --> 00:04:39,947
You know that.
I could only save you.

19
00:04:44,452 --> 00:04:46,162
Was she beautiful?

20
00:04:51,459 --> 00:04:52,752
She was smart.

21
00:04:55,379 --> 00:04:56,606
Like you.

22
00:04:57,840 --> 00:05:00,343
- How many did I get?
- All of them.

24
00:05:03,137 --> 00:05:05,807
So, I get to go
to town today, right?

25
00:05:08,935 --> 00:05:10,478
You failed survival.

26
00:05:12,480 --> 00:05:14,315
It's been three months.

27
00:05:15,691 --> 00:05:18,528
Plus, I just gave you
a killer haircut.

28
00:05:19,195 --> 00:05:20,613
Trust me.

29
00:05:22,698 --> 00:05:25,368
You need to pass
all your tests first.

30
00:05:37,839 --> 00:05:40,550
All right,
apart from the usual,

31
00:05:40,633 --> 00:05:43,261
I have... an order
of five ferns,

32
00:05:43,344 --> 00:05:45,280
two ficuses, and...

33
00:05:45,300 --> 00:05:47,098
...the Columnea grandiosa.

34
00:05:48,057 --> 00:05:50,475
<i>- Gloriosa.
- Gloriosa.</i>

36
00:05:51,561 --> 00:05:53,396
Am I taking Phoenix today?

37
00:05:53,479 --> 00:05:55,773
- Not today.
- It's been a while.

39
00:05:56,482 --> 00:05:57,565
I said, no.

40
00:06:02,321 --> 00:06:03,948
You know, you either
loosen up that leash,

41
00:06:04,031 --> 00:06:06,367
or sooner or later,
she's gonna bite it off.

42
00:06:20,715 --> 00:06:22,008
Go with Hernandez.

43
00:06:26,637 --> 00:06:29,306
- <i>Back by sunset!</i>
- I will!

45
00:06:33,811 --> 00:06:36,564
<i>- Hey, Hernandez!
- Hey, gorgeous.</i>

47
00:06:45,323 --> 00:06:46,991
Fly, bird

48
00:06:47,074 --> 00:06:49,160
Fly, bird

49
00:06:49,243 --> 00:06:52,371
All across the mighty sea

50
00:06:52,455 --> 00:06:53,956
Sing, girl

51
00:06:54,040 --> 00:06:58,127
Sing your little heart
out for me

52
00:06:58,210 --> 00:07:01,297
That's beautiful.
You made that up?

54
00:07:02,465 --> 00:07:05,176
I think my mom sang it to me
when I was little.

55
00:07:05,718 --> 00:07:07,845
That first part's
all I remember.

56
00:07:07,929 --> 00:07:09,472
You wanna pay her a visit?

57
00:07:11,891 --> 00:07:15,227
- But my father doesn't want...
- I won't tell if you don't.

58
00:07:52,890 --> 00:07:54,475
Fly, bird

59
00:07:54,558 --> 00:07:56,352
Fly, bird

60
00:08:13,786 --> 00:08:18,040
<i>Police have issued a statewide alert
for this man, Dr. Thomas Hanniman,</i>

61
00:08:18,124 --> 00:08:20,300
<i>who's believed to be running
an organ trafficking ring...</i>

62
00:08:20,320 --> 00:08:22,752
- <i>...operating in the Detroit area.</i>
- Thank you.

64
00:08:22,753 --> 00:08:26,133
<i>The alarming number of abductions
has recently risen in the city.</i>

65
00:08:26,215 --> 00:08:27,383
<i>This is a developing story.</i>

66
00:08:27,466 --> 00:08:30,094
<i>We'll update you
as more information comes to light.</i>

67
00:08:30,177 --> 00:08:32,847
<i>Right now, let's take a look
at the weekend forecast.</i>

68
00:08:32,930 --> 00:08:35,891
<i>Good morning, everyone.
I'm meteorologist Jerry...</i>

69
00:08:43,899 --> 00:08:46,569
Everyone, pull! Help me!

71
00:08:47,486 --> 00:08:49,030
It's stuck.

72
00:08:51,824 --> 00:08:53,617
Hey, wanna try something?

73
00:08:54,201 --> 00:08:55,411
Okay.

74
00:08:58,748 --> 00:09:00,499
Do it.

75
00:09:09,133 --> 00:09:10,676
Faster, faster!

76
00:09:10,760 --> 00:09:12,053
I'm getting dizzy.

77
00:09:20,227 --> 00:09:22,897
<i>Hey, guys!
Come on in! Dinner!</i>

78
00:09:24,356 --> 00:09:26,025
I don't wanna go inside!

79
00:09:26,108 --> 00:09:27,276
Come on, guys!

80
00:09:29,236 --> 00:09:30,780
"Covenant Shelter."

81
00:09:31,906 --> 00:09:33,949
- Race you.
- Hey, wait up!

82
00:09:40,414 --> 00:09:42,208
You having fun?

83
00:09:42,291 --> 00:09:45,252
- All right, let's go.
- I need to pee.

85
00:09:45,336 --> 00:09:48,464
Okay, well, be quick.
I don't wanna anger your father.

86
00:09:53,844 --> 00:09:55,721
Fly, bird

87
00:09:55,805 --> 00:09:57,640
Fly, bird

88
00:09:57,723 --> 00:10:00,726
All across the mighty sea

89
00:10:00,810 --> 00:10:02,353
Sing, girl

90
00:10:02,436 --> 00:10:06,690
Sing your little heart
out for me

91
00:10:17,159 --> 00:10:18,744
Wow, you're pretty.

92
00:10:21,872 --> 00:10:23,499
What's your name, gorgeous?

93
00:10:23,582 --> 00:10:24,583
Mine's Raylan.

94
00:10:26,585 --> 00:10:27,586
I don't care.

95
00:10:29,672 --> 00:10:32,091
I need to go.
My father's waiting for me.

96
00:10:41,600 --> 00:10:44,812
I snap my fingers
and he'll bite your testicles off.

97
00:10:46,223 --> 00:10:49,365
Wow! Okay.

99
00:10:49,942 --> 00:10:53,154
Well, I'm...
sorry if I scared you.

100
00:10:53,779 --> 00:10:54,947
Who said you did?

101
00:11:07,126 --> 00:11:08,335
I'll see you around!

102
00:11:09,128 --> 00:11:10,337
<i>Come on, Shadow!</i>

103
00:11:18,179 --> 00:11:20,723
- You okay?
- Yes.

105
00:11:20,806 --> 00:11:23,475
- Just a weirdo.
- Yeah.

107
00:11:24,435 --> 00:11:26,604
No shortage of those
around here.

108
00:11:41,035 --> 00:11:42,035
Follow 'em.

109
00:11:52,713 --> 00:11:53,881
Thanks, Hernandez.

110
00:11:54,673 --> 00:11:57,259
We had a lot of fun today.

111
00:11:57,343 --> 00:11:59,617
I can take her again next week
if you're okay with it.

112
00:11:59,637 --> 00:12:00,937
No.

113
00:12:01,013 --> 00:12:02,313
Today was enough.

114
00:12:08,354 --> 00:12:10,074
Look, I know it's none of
my business, but...

115
00:12:10,147 --> 00:12:11,347
You're right.

116
00:12:12,399 --> 00:12:13,699
It's not.

117
00:12:16,528 --> 00:12:17,655
You're a bad man!

118
00:12:21,116 --> 00:12:23,077
A man who's done
terrible things.

119
00:12:28,123 --> 00:12:30,042
At least, I know
you think that.

120
00:12:30,626 --> 00:12:33,003
Just like sometimes
I do about myself.

121
00:12:35,130 --> 00:12:36,799
War changes us all.

122
00:12:37,883 --> 00:12:40,427
No soul returns
holy from it.

123
00:12:42,763 --> 00:12:44,431
But don't make her
pay for that.

124
00:12:48,435 --> 00:12:49,735
Thanks.

125
00:14:01,533 --> 00:14:05,179
You mind moving your vehicle
off the road, please?

126
00:14:05,804 --> 00:14:06,804
This is...

127
00:14:09,558 --> 00:14:11,685
This is the only road
back to town.

128
00:14:13,771 --> 00:14:16,114
- You served?
- Yeah.

130
00:14:16,523 --> 00:14:17,800
We all did too.

131
00:14:19,026 --> 00:14:21,070
- Iraq?
- Yeah.

132
00:14:21,153 --> 00:14:24,782
Dishonorably discharged
from a dishonorable war.

133
00:14:27,409 --> 00:14:30,913
I'd say that makes us...
honorable somehow, wouldn't you?

134
00:14:31,789 --> 00:14:33,089
No.

135
00:14:34,750 --> 00:14:37,586
Can you move your truck
off the road now?

136
00:14:41,632 --> 00:14:44,802
Sure, baby.
Whatever you want.

138
00:15:58,292 --> 00:16:00,586
Lessons next month.

139
00:16:01,795 --> 00:16:03,000
Okay.

140
00:16:03,297 --> 00:16:05,841
I wanna go to school
next year.

141
00:16:06,925 --> 00:16:08,980
- This is school...
- A real school!

142
00:16:09,000 --> 00:16:12,181
- With other kids like me!
- Homeschool is safer.

143
00:16:12,264 --> 00:16:14,141
I don't wanna be safe!

144
00:16:14,224 --> 00:16:17,082
I wanna be normal!
I wanna have friends!

145
00:16:17,102 --> 00:16:18,770
- I wanna live a...
- Enough!

146
00:16:19,563 --> 00:16:20,863
Enough.

147
00:16:22,524 --> 00:16:25,319
I already lost
a daughter once.

148
00:16:25,402 --> 00:16:28,864
- I'm not losing you.
- But I'm lonely.

150
00:16:30,699 --> 00:16:33,285
You have no idea
what it is to be alone.

151
00:16:34,995 --> 00:16:36,121
You have me.

152
00:16:40,459 --> 00:16:41,793
You're not enough.

153
00:17:44,523 --> 00:17:45,899
"Covenant Shelter.

154
00:17:47,150 --> 00:17:48,735
Your new home awaits you."

155
00:19:05,520 --> 00:19:06,820
Shadow?

156
00:19:50,357 --> 00:19:51,657
<i>Shadow?</i>

157
00:24:41,231 --> 00:24:42,532
Shadow.

158
00:24:48,655 --> 00:24:49,956
Oh, God.

159
00:26:52,821 --> 00:26:55,073
The box! Now!

160
00:26:56,740 --> 00:26:58,051
Go!

161
00:27:14,926 --> 00:27:16,469
Go get the girl!

162
00:27:31,985 --> 00:27:33,050
Open the door!

163
00:27:34,612 --> 00:27:35,770
<i>Open up!</i>

164
00:30:02,176 --> 00:30:03,886
What the fuck?

165
00:30:04,470 --> 00:30:05,513


166
00:30:08,766 --> 00:30:09,892
Hang on, brother.

167
00:30:23,823 --> 00:30:24,907
Open your jaw.

168
00:30:26,075 --> 00:30:27,410
Stay still.

169
00:30:32,415 --> 00:30:33,541
Breathe, brother.

170
00:30:51,809 --> 00:30:53,478
The guy's a Navy SEAL.

171
00:31:08,785 --> 00:31:10,661
Fucking dead SEAL, bro.

172
00:32:11,806 --> 00:32:13,558
<i>Better get
outta there, kid.</i>

173
00:32:25,528 --> 00:32:27,280
He's down there with you!

174
00:32:28,072 --> 00:32:30,158
<i>Blind fuck is down there!</i>

175
00:32:48,301 --> 00:32:49,343
Call Raylan!

176
00:33:25,213 --> 00:33:27,590
Metal box is almost
full of water.

177
00:33:31,177 --> 00:33:32,970
You prefer to
see the kid alive,

178
00:33:35,515 --> 00:33:37,058
you come in here.

179
00:33:40,061 --> 00:33:41,395
You think
I'm fucking with you?

180
00:33:46,150 --> 00:33:47,350
No.

181
00:33:49,570 --> 00:33:51,989
<i>There's a live wire
about to reach the water.</i>

182
00:33:52,073 --> 00:33:53,574
<i>Come out, or she's fried!</i>

183
00:34:09,549 --> 00:34:11,008
Clever fuck.

184
00:34:11,968 --> 00:34:13,219
No guns, huh?

185
00:34:14,637 --> 00:34:15,838
No problem.

186
00:36:51,168 --> 00:36:52,336
You're tough.

187
00:36:54,380 --> 00:36:55,673
But you're done.

188
00:37:07,935 --> 00:37:10,000
What the fuck?

189
00:37:10,187 --> 00:37:11,320
Yo, bro!

190
00:38:29,682 --> 00:38:31,018
Breathe!

191
00:38:31,101 --> 00:38:33,103
Come on, breathe!

192
00:38:34,563 --> 00:38:37,148
Breathe. Breathe.

194
00:38:43,948 --> 00:38:45,783
The old blind man did this?

195
00:38:45,866 --> 00:38:46,992
Uh-huh.

196
00:38:50,246 --> 00:38:51,413
Let's go.

197
00:39:08,013 --> 00:39:09,181
I can walk.

198
00:39:09,765 --> 00:39:11,225
I said, I can walk!

199
00:39:14,436 --> 00:39:15,437
What's happening?

200
00:39:27,533 --> 00:39:28,701
Cover the exits.

201
00:39:41,088 --> 00:39:42,548
What the fuck?

202
00:40:10,618 --> 00:40:12,286
They're still down here.

203
00:40:42,691 --> 00:40:43,984
What's happening?

204
00:40:45,444 --> 00:40:47,154
- Who are they?
- I don't know.

205
00:41:32,032 --> 00:41:34,451
<i>You don't need to
be afraid, little girl.</i>

206
00:41:36,704 --> 00:41:39,748
This has all just been
one big misunderstanding.

207
00:41:51,385 --> 00:41:53,554
It's not me you need
to be scared of,

208
00:42:00,102 --> 00:42:02,062
<i>but the man standing
next to you.</i>

209
00:42:05,232 --> 00:42:06,984
Now, I don't know
who he is,

210
00:42:10,779 --> 00:42:12,197
but I know who he's not.

211
00:42:21,420 --> 00:42:22,676
Should I tell her or you?

212
00:42:30,090 --> 00:42:31,175
Finish him, bro!

213
00:42:32,051 --> 00:42:33,352
No!

214
00:42:33,802 --> 00:42:36,305
- Dad! Dad, wake up!
- Aren't you something?

215
00:42:38,432 --> 00:42:39,641
Let me go!

216
00:42:41,685 --> 00:42:42,811
Come on.

217
00:42:43,812 --> 00:42:45,113
No, it's okay.

218
00:42:48,817 --> 00:42:51,819
Yeah, there you go.
There you go.

220
00:42:53,280 --> 00:42:55,074
You really
don't remember me, do you?

221
00:42:56,867 --> 00:42:58,619
Maybe this will help.

222
00:43:09,254 --> 00:43:10,554
See?

223
00:43:15,302 --> 00:43:16,602
What...

224
00:43:19,389 --> 00:43:21,600
Years ago, there was
a fire in our house.

225
00:43:22,392 --> 00:43:23,769
Cops blamed me.

226
00:43:24,603 --> 00:43:27,523
I spent eight years in prison,
wondering if I'd ever see you again.

227
00:43:32,111 --> 00:43:34,363
<i>Hell, I didn't even know
if you were dead or alive.</i>

228
00:43:39,284 --> 00:43:40,994
<i>This creep here
must have...</i>

229
00:43:41,954 --> 00:43:44,039
<i>...found you and
kept you for himself.</i>

230
00:43:45,707 --> 00:43:47,209
<i>Up next in local news,</i>

231
00:43:47,292 --> 00:43:50,754
<i>a meth lab caught fire
in west Detroit this morning.</i>

232
00:43:50,838 --> 00:43:53,549
<i>Police were able to arrest
the primary suspect.</i>

233
00:43:53,632 --> 00:43:56,552
<i>The man was taken into custody
and could face charges...</i>

234
00:43:56,635 --> 00:43:59,721
<i>...for a large number of crimes committed
over the past several years.</i>

235
00:43:59,805 --> 00:44:03,016
<i>You have no idea how much
I've been waiting for this moment.</i>

236
00:44:19,116 --> 00:44:20,367
Did he hurt you?

237
00:44:22,369 --> 00:44:25,998
But he did steal you away from me,
and now he must die, you understand?

238
00:44:28,709 --> 00:44:30,000
Kill him.

239
00:44:30,419 --> 00:44:31,670
- No!
- Fuck are you doing?

240
00:44:32,629 --> 00:44:35,132
Not in front of my kid.
Do it outside.

241
00:44:40,804 --> 00:44:43,750
Wake up, you blind fuck!

242
00:44:46,852 --> 00:44:48,110
Fuck!

243
00:45:10,042 --> 00:45:11,376
Fucking coward!

244
00:45:18,467 --> 00:45:21,000
Take her to the truck
while I hunt this motherfucker.

244
00:45:21,050 --> 00:45:22,300
Let's go.

245
00:45:28,352 --> 00:45:29,978
- Let me go!
- What's wrong with you?

246
00:45:31,104 --> 00:45:32,439
Fucking wanna go home?

247
00:45:58,757 --> 00:46:00,300
I don't care who you are.

248
00:46:00,384 --> 00:46:02,469
I'm gonna teach you
some fucking manners,

249
00:46:03,220 --> 00:46:04,972
you ungrateful
little bitch.

250
00:46:23,991 --> 00:46:25,292
No!

251
00:46:33,375 --> 00:46:34,632
Stop.

252
00:46:35,294 --> 00:46:36,520
Please!

253
00:46:37,212 --> 00:46:38,463
STOP!

254
00:46:54,062 --> 00:46:55,647
Move! Go, go!

255
00:46:55,731 --> 00:46:57,441
Move! Now!

256
00:47:25,594 --> 00:47:26,845
Move!

257
00:47:39,608 --> 00:47:40,650
I'm sorry, man.

258
00:47:44,321 --> 00:47:47,824
- He's back in the house.
- I know. He wants us to follow him.

259
00:47:50,327 --> 00:47:52,079
Enough of these silly games.

260
00:48:09,763 --> 00:48:11,098
It's his jacket!

261
00:48:13,350 --> 00:48:15,770
Attaboy. Attaboy!

263
00:48:17,604 --> 00:48:19,950
Wait! Stop!

265
00:48:22,234 --> 00:48:24,778
- Is it true?
- Move!

267
00:48:24,861 --> 00:48:27,697
- What's my real name?
- Get over here! Now!

269
00:48:27,781 --> 00:48:29,157
When's my birthday?

270
00:48:29,241 --> 00:48:31,159
- My real one?
- Stop it!

271
00:48:31,243 --> 00:48:32,577
No, you stop it!

272
00:48:42,212 --> 00:48:43,460
Go!

273
00:49:52,282 --> 00:49:53,530
Hey!

274
00:51:13,405 --> 00:51:14,614
Phoenix!

275
00:51:15,907 --> 00:51:17,576
Calm down, girl!

276
00:51:20,370 --> 00:51:21,570
Calm down.

277
00:51:41,933 --> 00:51:43,233
Stay.

278
00:51:58,575 --> 00:51:59,826
Put her in the truck.

279
00:52:23,642 --> 00:52:25,143
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!

280
00:52:27,312 --> 00:52:28,438
What are you doing?

281
00:52:29,356 --> 00:52:31,900
- Your dog's in there.
- Dog's dead.

282
00:52:31,983 --> 00:52:33,568
You don't know that.

283
00:52:33,652 --> 00:52:35,195
You wanna go and find out?

284
00:53:32,544 --> 00:53:33,760
No!

285
00:56:28,970 --> 00:56:30,346
Good morning, princess.

286
00:56:39,147 --> 00:56:40,148
How you feeling?

287
00:56:45,528 --> 00:56:46,528
You all right?

288
00:56:48,656 --> 00:56:49,782
Wanna sit with me?

289
00:56:51,826 --> 00:56:53,453
Come, sit with me. Come on.

290
00:56:55,038 --> 00:56:56,330
Yeah.

291
00:56:57,165 --> 00:56:59,708
There you go. There you go.

293
00:57:00,919 --> 00:57:02,219
Yeah.

294
00:57:08,593 --> 00:57:09,594
Door's open.

295
00:57:11,304 --> 00:57:12,931
Not a prisoner anymore.

296
00:57:14,599 --> 00:57:17,310
You mean, I can go?

297
00:57:19,020 --> 00:57:20,021
If you want.

298
00:57:22,357 --> 00:57:25,693
Or you can stay here and...
find out who you really are.

299
00:57:34,494 --> 00:57:36,537
Do I have any
brothers or sisters?

300
00:57:39,207 --> 00:57:40,625
Unfortunately, no.

301
00:57:43,461 --> 00:57:44,879
When's my birthday?

302
00:57:45,463 --> 00:57:46,650
February 20th.

303
00:57:49,217 --> 00:57:50,843
What was my mother's name?

304
00:57:53,221 --> 00:57:54,522
Josephine.

305
00:57:55,848 --> 00:57:57,058
Do I look like her?

306
00:58:00,895 --> 00:58:02,060
Yeah.

307
00:58:04,691 --> 00:58:05,891
You do.

308
00:58:08,319 --> 00:58:09,619
Tara.

309
00:58:10,697 --> 00:58:11,864
That's your real name.

310
00:58:13,950 --> 00:58:15,250
Tara.

311
00:58:16,911 --> 00:58:18,955
Everything that man
told you is a lie.

312
00:58:20,248 --> 00:58:21,499
What happened to him?

313
00:58:23,167 --> 00:58:24,585
He got what he deserved.

314
00:58:26,754 --> 00:58:29,173
Hey! I'm not sorry.

315
00:58:29,841 --> 00:58:32,985
- You shouldn't be either.
- I wanna go.

317
00:58:34,470 --> 00:58:36,305
Where? Where you gonna go?

318
00:58:36,389 --> 00:58:38,099
There's a shelter I know.

319
00:58:39,976 --> 00:58:43,521
Like I said, you're not
a prisoner anymore.

320
01:00:01,349 --> 01:00:04,727
Fly, bird

321
01:00:08,189 --> 01:00:13,778
Fly, bird

322
01:00:17,406 --> 01:00:20,243
Out across the...

323
01:00:23,079 --> 01:00:26,541
...great wide sea

324
01:00:27,792 --> 01:00:32,171
Sing, girl

325
01:00:33,089 --> 01:00:36,843
Sing, girl

326
01:00:37,385 --> 01:00:42,849
Sing your little heart
out for me

327
01:00:44,892 --> 01:00:46,978
Fly, bird

328
01:00:48,938 --> 01:00:50,648
Fly, bird

329
01:00:53,818 --> 01:00:57,238
Fly across the mighty cliffs

330
01:00:58,573 --> 01:01:02,493
Sleep, girl

331
01:01:03,578 --> 01:01:06,455
Sleep, girl

332
01:01:09,584 --> 01:01:13,254
Mama's gonna give you
a good-night kiss

333
01:01:17,675 --> 01:01:18,930
Mom?

334
01:01:21,137 --> 01:01:22,442
Like I said.

335
01:01:23,598 --> 01:01:25,308
Everything he told you
was a lie.

336
01:01:37,987 --> 01:01:39,405
My Tara?

337
01:01:44,410 --> 01:01:48,080
You... got so... big.

338
01:01:52,752 --> 01:01:53,794
Can I hug you?

339
01:02:00,426 --> 01:02:01,650
Come here.

340
01:02:03,304 --> 01:02:04,597
Oh, God.

341
01:02:06,933 --> 01:02:08,309
Oh, God.

342
01:02:12,396 --> 01:02:13,760
Oh, God.

343
01:02:15,483 --> 01:02:17,693
Oh, baby,
we'missed you so much.

344
01:02:23,115 --> 01:02:25,159


345
01:02:25,243 --> 01:02:26,577
There you are.

346
01:02:26,661 --> 01:02:31,624
You were such
a beautiful baby.

347
01:02:42,218 --> 01:02:43,218
Get it out.

348
01:02:43,719 --> 01:02:44,971
Get it out. Come on.

349
01:02:45,554 --> 01:02:48,057
There you go. There you go.

350
01:02:48,140 --> 01:02:49,392
- There you go.
- Sorry.

351
01:02:49,475 --> 01:02:51,686
Nothing to apologize for.

352
01:02:53,229 --> 01:02:54,563
Are you okay?

353
01:02:58,067 --> 01:03:01,237
The same fire that
destroyed our family,

354
01:03:03,406 --> 01:03:06,033
it burned up my insides.

355
01:03:10,830 --> 01:03:13,499
Mom and Dad
used to have a...

356
01:03:17,003 --> 01:03:18,303
...kitchen...

357
01:03:19,839 --> 01:03:21,757
...in the basement
of our house,

358
01:03:21,841 --> 01:03:24,652
where we used to... cook.

359
01:03:28,681 --> 01:03:30,766
It was for our business.

360
01:03:35,187 --> 01:03:36,362
Are you thirsty?

361
01:03:51,329 --> 01:03:52,629
Tara?

362
01:03:54,415 --> 01:03:57,116
- I'm dying.
- What?

364
01:03:58,544 --> 01:04:00,671
The smoke from
the chemicals...

365
01:04:01,922 --> 01:04:05,593
...poisoned my blood
and badly damaged my heart.

366
01:04:05,676 --> 01:04:08,554
I don't think I have
much time left.

367
01:04:08,637 --> 01:04:10,514
Is there anything
you can do?

368
01:04:20,066 --> 01:04:23,361
I heard you left flowers for me
at our old house.

369
01:04:27,073 --> 01:04:28,366
Is that true?

370
01:04:31,827 --> 01:04:32,828


371
01:04:34,580 --> 01:04:40,211
Weren't you wishing
your mama was healthy and alive?

372
01:04:40,878 --> 01:04:42,100
Yes.

373
01:04:55,684 --> 01:04:57,436
I need a new heart, baby.

374
01:04:58,646 --> 01:05:00,314
But not just any heart.

375
01:05:00,981 --> 01:05:03,818
Doctor said
it has to be a, um...

376
01:05:04,527 --> 01:05:06,570
It must be a...

377
01:05:08,030 --> 01:05:09,782
...compatible donor.

378
01:05:13,953 --> 01:05:15,996
Like a direct relative.

379
01:05:18,707 --> 01:05:21,627
You hold the gift
that can save your mama's life.

380
01:05:25,881 --> 01:05:28,217
And, baby,
I need that gift.

381
01:05:47,736 --> 01:05:50,531
We'll finally
be together as one.

382
01:05:52,741 --> 01:05:55,000
You'll live on... 

382
01:05:55,028 --> 01:05:57,413
...in me.

383
01:06:26,692 --> 01:06:27,820
Go home.

384
01:06:29,111 --> 01:06:31,322


385
01:06:31,405 --> 01:06:33,032


386
01:08:20,973 --> 01:08:22,173
Go away.

387
01:08:23,892 --> 01:08:25,102
I said, go!

388
01:08:33,402 --> 01:08:34,702
Stay.

389
01:08:37,740 --> 01:08:39,000
Stay.

390
01:09:10,939 --> 01:09:12,239
Go home.

391
01:09:21,075 --> 01:09:22,300
Go home.

392
01:10:03,742 --> 01:10:06,954
I hope you understand
the high risks of this procedure.

393
01:10:08,664 --> 01:10:11,917
I think I pay you enough.
Shut up and do your job.

395
01:10:13,711 --> 01:10:15,212
Why is she still alive?

396
01:10:16,880 --> 01:10:18,966
If she's dead,
so is her heart.

397
01:10:20,676 --> 01:10:24,346
I can't keep it fresh long enough
without the proper equipment.

398
01:10:25,931 --> 01:10:28,600
I have to cut it out of her
while she's still breathing.

399
01:10:30,978 --> 01:10:32,211
Hey.

400
01:10:32,771 --> 01:10:34,314
Hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey.

401
01:10:34,398 --> 01:10:36,024
Hey, hey.

402
01:10:39,445 --> 01:10:40,611
Thank you.

403
01:11:01,341 --> 01:11:02,676
What's wrong with you, man?

404
01:11:04,636 --> 01:11:06,847
What they're doing
in there is wrong.

405
01:11:08,640 --> 01:11:09,808
She's our cook.

406
01:11:11,518 --> 01:11:13,854
If she dies,
there's no product.

407
01:11:14,646 --> 01:11:17,024
If there's no product,
there's no us.

408
01:11:19,485 --> 01:11:20,694
<i>Comprende?</i>

409
01:11:22,946 --> 01:11:24,615
Still fucking wrong.

410
01:11:32,831 --> 01:11:34,131
Hey.

411
01:11:35,375 --> 01:11:37,211
You ready?

412
01:11:40,380 --> 01:11:41,620
Let's go.

413
01:12:05,614 --> 01:12:06,865
What the fuck?

414
01:12:12,704 --> 01:12:13,964
Go check it out!

415
01:13:31,700 --> 01:13:33,619
You killed my brother,

416
01:13:35,037 --> 01:13:37,039
you blind freak!

417
01:13:59,353 --> 01:14:02,940
I'm gonna carve your fucking head open
like a pumpkin, man!

418
01:14:59,496 --> 01:15:01,264
This is for Shadow.

419
01:15:03,250 --> 01:15:04,550
Oh, fuck!

420
01:15:04,793 --> 01:15:06,816
No!

421
01:15:12,884 --> 01:15:14,125
It's him.

422
01:15:19,349 --> 01:15:22,227
How the hell did he find...

423
01:15:40,579 --> 01:15:44,041
- Disloyal fucking animal.
- <i>Is everything okay?</i>

425
01:15:46,209 --> 01:15:48,045
Yeah, everything's okay.

426
01:15:48,587 --> 01:15:50,297
- Everything's okay, I promise.
- Baby?

427
01:15:51,000 --> 01:15:53,341
- Should I be worried?
- No, no. Not at all.

429
01:15:53,425 --> 01:15:56,720
- I got you. I got you.
- I can't work without power.

431
01:15:57,679 --> 01:15:58,679


432
01:15:59,639 --> 01:16:00,974
Change of plans, then.

433
01:16:02,350 --> 01:16:04,227
Pack your things.
Bring the girl.

434
01:16:04,311 --> 01:16:05,611
Raul!

435
01:16:07,355 --> 01:16:09,649
- Bring the men! Kill the blind man!
- How many of us?

436
01:16:10,233 --> 01:16:11,561
ALL OF YOU!

437
01:16:15,489 --> 01:16:16,789
Let's go.

438
01:17:49,749 --> 01:17:50,830
They're gonna kill her.

439
01:17:56,047 --> 01:17:57,761
And that's not cool with me.

440
01:18:01,469 --> 01:18:02,762
They're leaving now.

441
01:18:02,846 --> 01:18:05,900
The ladder behind you
leads directly to them.

441
01:18:06,000 --> 01:18:07,400
You'd better hurry.

442
01:18:21,406 --> 01:18:22,706
Go left!

443
01:18:24,117 --> 01:18:25,417
That way!

444
01:18:28,663 --> 01:18:29,998
He'll kill you all.

445
01:18:39,925 --> 01:18:42,093
- Fuck it. I'm out.
- Hey! Hey!

447
01:18:42,177 --> 01:18:43,477
Hey!

448
01:19:08,495 --> 01:19:10,205
Good morning, motherfucker!

449
01:19:14,834 --> 01:19:16,200
Baby?

450
01:19:16,670 --> 01:19:18,855
- It's okay.
- Stop it!

452
01:19:52,622 --> 01:19:53,922
Baby?

453
01:19:55,417 --> 01:19:58,295
- Hello?
- <i>I can't see you!</i>

455
01:20:07,679 --> 01:20:09,222
Baby?

456
01:20:41,588 --> 01:20:43,340
<i>Someone's here! Hurry!</i>

457
01:20:44,924 --> 01:20:46,225
<i>Baby?</i>

458
01:21:10,033 --> 01:21:11,534
I got you, motherfucker.

459
01:21:23,421 --> 01:21:24,739
No.

460
01:21:24,839 --> 01:21:27,467
No! No!

462
01:21:36,267 --> 01:21:37,528
No.

463
01:21:39,540 --> 01:21:40,688
No!

464
01:22:32,807 --> 01:22:34,050
Phoenix!

465
01:23:07,484 --> 01:23:08,750
Now...

466
01:23:09,444 --> 01:23:11,321
...you're gonna see...

467
01:23:11,404 --> 01:23:12,822
...what I see.

468
01:24:03,414 --> 01:24:04,715
Phoenix?

469
01:24:15,468 --> 01:24:16,768
Stop!

470
01:24:17,637 --> 01:24:18,937
STOP!

471
01:24:21,975 --> 01:24:23,245
You...

472
01:24:25,687 --> 01:24:27,622
You mustn't come near me.

473
01:24:33,987 --> 01:24:37,657
Everything... he said...

474
01:24:40,868 --> 01:24:42,168
...is true.

475
01:24:48,960 --> 01:24:51,087
I am no father.

476
01:24:55,950 --> 01:24:57,969
I have killed.

477
01:25:03,975 --> 01:25:05,275
I...

478
01:25:06,102 --> 01:25:07,520
...have raped.

479
01:25:08,813 --> 01:25:10,113
I...

480
01:25:13,401 --> 01:25:14,800
...am nothing.

481
01:25:20,617 --> 01:25:21,917
Nothing...

482
01:25:23,911 --> 01:25:25,204
...but a monster.

483
01:25:31,753 --> 01:25:33,000
And you...

484
01:25:33,546 --> 01:25:35,340
...cannot be around me.

485
01:25:37,467 --> 01:25:38,767
Ever.

486
01:25:40,762 --> 01:25:41,962
So go.

487
01:25:45,266 --> 01:25:46,726
Now! Go!

488
01:25:48,019 --> 01:25:49,270
GO!

489
01:26:21,177 --> 01:26:23,244
Oh, God!

490
01:27:13,062 --> 01:27:14,647
Tara?

491
01:27:38,254 --> 01:27:39,555
No.

492
01:27:41,716 --> 01:27:44,559
No. No.

494
01:27:48,890 --> 01:27:50,190
Please.

495
01:27:55,021 --> 01:27:56,856
No, no, no.

496
01:27:58,483 --> 01:27:59,650
Let me help you.

497
01:28:01,694 --> 01:28:02,964
I can save you.

498
01:28:09,035 --> 01:28:10,745
You already have.

499
01:29:56,100 --> 01:29:57,400
Hey!

500
01:29:59,228 --> 01:30:00,428
Hey!

501
01:30:01,647 --> 01:30:03,566
Think there's room
for one more?

502
01:30:05,109 --> 01:30:06,193
I'm sure there is.

503
01:30:08,237 --> 01:30:09,238
What's your name?

504
01:30:13,993 --> 01:30:15,620
My name is Phoenix.

