Hey, I'm Fede Alvarez. I'm the
director and the writer of this film.
Hello, this is Rodo Sayagues.
I'm the writer.
And this is Stephen Lang,
and I play the Blind Man in this film.
And we've gathered to
a screening of the film...
...with our commentary.
It's a bunch of logos.
But there's definitely something
that I think it's...
It's the only interesting part
about the logos, is we always...
We start... The movie starts right away...
Like the soundtrack...
That eerie soundtrack starts on the first
image of the movie, there's no...
That's hopefully when the audience
gets hooked...
...and we never really let them go
until the end.
Detroit.
And there you are, Slang.
-I know.
-Dragging that poor girl...
...down the street for real. Ha, ha.
-That was a... That was a day.
-Ha, ha.
She was a...
She's... She's a... You know...
She doesn't look like she's too big...
...but she got real heavy
that day, somehow. Heh, heh.
Well, we did this shot I think
two or three times.
And... And I demanded
you do all the dragging.
There was no help.
It was just you, all muscle...
...dragging her like three times
down the street.
-Right.
-And this one is the third shot.
And I remember at the end of this one
you were like, "Okay. Hope you got it."
Oh, that's a beauty.
-You got it good.
-Yeah.
It works pretty well, like, the whole...
You think you're...
You're in just suburban America.
And bit by bit, as you get closer
to the characters...
...you realize there's a lot more.
-You know?
-Totally.
You see it.
Don't Breathe.
I've come to really like the title
of this film.
Cool. It used to be called
Man in the Dark.
Well, I was... At the time I was
so wedded to that title.
Me, too.
-...17...
-Yo, kill that already.
Rodo and I, we loved Man in the Dark...
...because it's the name that we stamped
on the script when we finished it.
But we got to love Don't Breathe as well.
Yeah. Actually I think it changed names
more than twice.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-What were the other titles?
-There were a lot of them.
Don't Breathe in the Dark.
The Blind Man was something...
...that we actually were very keen
to title at some point.
-Just Blind Man.
-Uh-huh.
Oh!
I just... I love Danny's character,
you know...
-...just sort of the cavalier nature of it.
-Yeah.
He's swag.
So most of the movie was shot in...
We did Detroit, and we did Budapest.
And this is actually...
Actually in Budapest, like a house
outside a city.
Yeah, I think it's the only location stuff
we did in the city.
Then the rest in Budapest
was all inside a studio.
Except remember, we did shoot
the train station.
True. The train station.
-Which I thought was just great.
-I loved that.
Yeah, it used to be
an old airport, I think.
But here we're definitely in Detroit. Back
flying with the drone around the city.
How many days did we shoot in Detroit?
We spent like a week there.
But we shot like a couple days, I guess.
And this was an entire day of just,
you know...
Is that ladybug real?
-Yes, it is. Heh, heh.
-Did you get...
Did you have like a lady bug wrangler...
-...when you were doing that?
-We did.
We had an animal wrangler
that took care of...
From, you know... From everything...
From the dogs to the ladybug.
But that's one of the strange things of
filmmaking that, of course everybody...
When...
When the page says ladybug, everybody
goes for CG ladybug right away.
And I didn't want to use CG, ha, ha,
if I could help it...
...because it's a movie that
doesn't need it or have it.
So to just have suddenly a CG ladybug
could have been a problem.
And we really went for it,
and we had a couple of them.
It was very, very hot, so ladybugs
don't survive under extreme heat.
So you cannot... You actually can't
put the disclaimer that no ladybugs...
-...were harmed.
-None of them were harmed...
...it was just the fact that
we couldn't find them...
...and some of them just died
before they arrived on set.
But, yeah, we ended up doing it
with a real ladybug.
-We laugh now about this.
-Heh, heh.
We'll hear about it.
This is Detroit.
The family of Alex.
Actually, you were saying there's no...
There's no CGI in this.
And we never... I don't recall
any green screen either.
-Did we?
-No. No, no, no.
-That's a rarity these days, my friend.
-Yeah.
But I guess... You know, I like when...
If you can pull it off...
...I think it's good, make it more classy.
But that was the whole approach
of this movie, since day one...
...I was trying to do this, you know,
in a very classy way.
Not doing anything that was,
you know, top of the line...
...CG or visual effects,
because stuff like that gets old.
And a good story, I think,
will never get old.
Was this script inspired by any events
you read about in the paper?
I think it was life, right?
Rodo and I were actually driving back
from San Diego one day and thought...
We kind of created the character
of the Blind Man.
And all the story kind of
came out of that.
But... Yeah, but there
were stories, right?
Yeah, with that case,
I remember exactly where it happened.
This guy that kept a girl
in a basement...
...for many, many years.
Yeah, there was one in Switzerland,
I think ages ago.
Unfortunately, there's been many others.
And probably there's others we don't
know about. Those are the scary ones...
-...the ones that are ongoing.
-So we thought what if burglars...
-...break into that guy's house?
-Right.
And find this... This...
Crime going on.
So we thought that would be cool.
Which is kind of the fun of this movie,
like, nobody is good.
So you were in the car and you just sort
of spun the story out to each other?
-Yeah, I guess so.
-Something like that, yeah.
Something like that.
I mean, we knew that...
That we wanted to...
Because the whole girl in the cellar thing
kind of came later.
I think the first part of the idea was...
...to tell the story from
the point of view of robbers.
Because it's something that you
don't see often and...
And as far as real life goes...
...like, house robbers,
they do have scary and...
And very particular adventures every day.
Regardless of the judgment...
...of what they're doing, whether it's
a bad thing, at the end of the day...
...they're kids that enter a house,
and try to get away with things...
...and they might get shot,
and might get killed.
And that happens every day.
And it's kind of a strange world
that we don't really see often in movies.
This kind of down and dirty,
greedy group of kids...
...that are breaking into peoples' houses
and taking stuff.
And the challenge was obviously getting
the audience to care about them.
So that's why once we learn more about
what's going on in the house...
...it becomes that thing of
they might be bad but there's...
Perhaps there's even more evil stuff
happening inside the house.
But at that point, I mean, that comes...
We've gone a substantial
way in the film...
...at that point and...
Before you turn everything on its ear.
Because to have these kids
be the perpetrators...
...and my character
essentially be a victim...
...you establish that.
-Yeah.
-And it works beautifully, I mean, then...
And then the way you just
kind of turn that on its ear...
-...Is pretty fascinating, I think.
-Heh, heh.
It's good to see how the audience
empathy switches...
...from one side to the other.
And kind of constantly does that
throughout the movie.
Which is really fascinating,
but it's just... There I am.
I don't know if you spot me there.
That was me in that newspaper.
-I was an illegal immigrant.
-Your Hitchcock moment.
It said something like, "Illegal immigrant
was blamed for two murders."
Something like that.
That's my face in there, blurred out.
This scene is all about that, right?
The empathy.
-Why she does what she's doing.
-Sure.
It's just a few months
till he can find a new job.
I remember
this scene used to be different.
She used to live with his father.
And his father was an abusive father...
-...a violent guy.
-Mm-hm.
But then we thought that
it would have been even better...
...if she lived with a mother,
just negligent.
And... And then we added that
character sitting next to her.
Doing nothing.
Just being very menacing.
Well, he's got a swastika
on his right hand.
-Yeah.
-So if it was not clear enough...
-Right.
And she's such a sweet, you know...
-...charming little beauty.
-Yeah.
She doesn't do a lot in the movie,
but does everything she needs to do...
...just by being there, showing someone
that really represents innocence.
And in that environment, you know
that's not gonna last long.
And so we felt it was a good
clock ticking for her life.
Everything is a little bit extreme
in this scene...
...but I think it works.
We needed to set this up
in like two minutes.
-And I think it worked.
-It's...
I don't know... I don't know that
I would've called it extreme.
I think everything is on the nose...
-...but it kind of has to be.
-Yeah.
It's a way of delivering
exposition quickly.
Yeah, that's the thing with TV,
the difference between TV and films.
In TV, you have a lot of time to develop
these things.
And in this kind of movie,
you have to hit it hard...
...and you need the audience to get it
right away and have those few minutes...
-...to get a point across.
-Mm-hm.
I think it helped, I mean...
At least then from that point on,
the audience hopefully will understand...
...that it's very unlikely that she's
gonna back away from her goal...
...which is take the money
from the Blind Man.
And I think it's a really interesting
choice that you've made...
...because we're kind of approaching
the end of when we're gonna be outside.
And we have not encountered
one other person.
-Yeah. It's true.
-You know...
...no one on the streets at all.
It was kind of to give that
sense of desolation...
...that Detroit might have in places,
in particular this kind of neighborhood.
So, yeah, it's true that you don't really
see anybody else except for the characters.
Even when they're at the restaurant,
nobody's there. It's just that...
That sense of, "They have to get out.
They have to go to someplace else.”
- ;
- Is that a new tattoo?
Yeah.
I got it last night.
-Is it a...?
-Ladybug.
The ladybug again.
Of course, it's the...
I don't know what we thought. But I think
it was always representing that idea.
Kind of the freedom
that she's looking for...
...and she's desperate to get.
My mom started drinking
and she told me that...
Also, they're...
I've always associated them with luck.
Yeah. In the folklore I think it's...
Ladybug... You see a ladybug,
it's always a happy moment.
"Oh, look, a ladybug."
So it's good.
And, yeah, I think in Uruguay folklore
it's always something...
...that you associate with good fortune.
Which is not really coming her way now.
But I think eventually in the movie
it comes around...
...when she sees it
at the right moment.
I think this back story as well
used to be longer in the script, right?
Yeah.
When I reach California,
I'll color this tat...
...and that's the last time
I will mark my body.
Yeah, and this is
the last time in the movie...
...they will have a moment of peace.
I think from this point on
it's gonna be nonstop.
There used to be actually a shot here,
a short insert that...
That you'll find on the extras
of the DVD on the deleted scenes. But I...
But I love it. You should check it out.
Which is when we get a glimpse...
...of what the Blind Man is doing.
Not right at this moment,
but right before this moment.
And we get to know that he's a gard...
-He does gardening.
-The gardening scene.
-Yeah, remember?
-I enjoyed the gardening scenes.
-Yeah.
-I saw the deleted scene.
Oh, that dog.
The dog...
-The dog gets an award. Ha, ha.
-Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Particularly for the one day
we were on set and we know...
...that he wasn't hitting his marks
all the time.
-Yeah.
-But in the movie he really, you know...
He does what he has to do.
He's very menacing and it's that
extension of the will of the Blind Man.
Yeah, I think the first draft that
we wrote didn't have the dog.
-Uh-uh.
-And... And I think it was Fede's idea...
...this guy should have a dog.
How come he doesn't have a dog?
-Right.
-The dog turned out to be one of the...
A really important element in the movie.
That's it. That's it for daytime.
Now we go into nighttime.
For good.
-I love this shot here.
-Mm.
It almost looks like they're in space.
Ha, ha.
There's something very strange about it.
I just read the silhouettes. It looks like
three cosmonauts somewhere.
In the middle of nowhere.
Which is what I love about that house,
that it's...
Usually in a scary movie...
...every time you wanna portray
the house as creepy...
...you have a bunch of nice houses and
you have a scary house in the middle.
And the one that is run down
and not well-kept, that's the scary one.
-Here it's the other way around.
-Kind of the opposite.
It's the house that is in good shape,
in a bad neighborhood.
And ends up for that reason
being the one that is unsettling.
-Now we're in studio here.
-Yeah.
-But...
-Just like that.
And the fact that the house
is well-maintained...
...that was an important thing
for my character.
It says an awful lot about the...
You know, the order
that he maintains in his life.
Yeah.
-That was CGI, right?
-That was CG.
Yeah. That was the only...
Well, not the only, I think there's a
couple of CG moments in the movie.
That's probably the fanciest CG effect
in the whole movie, ironically.
The piece of treat, of hot dog,
that is thrown to the dog.
It had to fly over the fence and land.
All that was done actually in Uruguay,
in our country.
Because the money's in there...
...and the paranoid fuck
doesn't trust nobody.
Let's check for a side door.
All this, like here,
I think this is the moment...
...when they cross that gate
is when the real tension starts.
And it's really what inspired
the whole movie, I guess...
...was that idea that there's something
very scary about...
...not just having people...
Seeing scenes about people breaking
into someone's house.
But even if you're with them,
and you're with the house breaker...
...it's always something very tense...
...because for us,
and I think for everybody...
...the private space
and the private property...
...is something that we value
so much in the idea that, you know...
...we feel safe inside our house
and there's a...
There's a common agreement in society...
...that you don't walk into
someone else's property.
And so when you see it happen...
...it's fascinating how we all
collectively, and in theaters...
...and everybody watching,
as soon as they cross that line...
...and they walk into a space
that is not theirs...
...it puts everybody
in a very, very tense mode.
And that's something that we knew. And
actually what started the conversation...
...when we started talking
about this movie.
When we were thinking about
what to write after Evil Dead.
And... And based on that feeling,
we thought:
"Okay. What would be a story
that would take place in that space?
And that could have you on that edge
all the time."
And that's when we thought
about this group of kids...
...and who they were
gonna break into...
...and the character
of the Blind Man came out.
There's a bolt here. I can feel it.
And they're all in their own way...
-...extremely likable kids.
-Mm-hm.
I think... I mean you
kind of understand...
...where they're coming from...
...their needs and everything.
But when they go...
When they go over that fence...
...they kind of...
It's all bets are off, in a way.
They put themselves in a...
A morally indefensible position,
it seems to me.
It's, you know, so...
In other words, "Well, you're
gonna get what you deserve."
-Even though you like them.
-Yeah.
Yeah, that's what is strange
and fascinating about the film as well.
And so far, today, we're doing
this commentary...
...and the movie hasn't come out yet.
But so far just the reaction of the world
based on the trailers...
...and what the concept of the movie is...
...It's very interesting to see
how much debate it caused...
...based on what you said.
They're gonna get what they deserve.
And a lot of people see
the trailer and they go like:
"Well, they get what they deserve."
Now people say:
"Well, but the Blind Man was doing
his own things as well there."
But that doesn't mean it's legal for him
to chase them and kill them.
If you feel threatened,
and he definitely does.
Particularly because,
as we're gonna see now they...
They brought a gun into the house.
Which the Blind Man's not gonna...
Not gonna stop to argue with them...
...and ask them if they plan
to shoot him with that gun.
So that's why we think it makes for a...
For a very morally conflictive
story to see.
Which is the kind of story that we like.
We don't like to spoon-feed the audience
with the answer, the moral answer.
This sequence here is kind of classic...
...almost James Bond stuff.
You know... Ha, ha. You know
you have to kind of...
The clock is ticking down
before the bomb goes off.
Before the alarm goes off or whatever.
So it's a nice piece of suspense.
And here for me is one of the...
It's the first time that,
I think in the movie...
...when Pedro Luque, the DP,
starts showing off. Heh, heh.
-He's showing off big time here. Beautiful.
-I say that in a good way.
Because it's one of the most beautiful
shots. How the light from the street...
...hits her eyes as
she's realizing that...
...there's something in this house
that's more than what you think.
-This was a really interesting beat.
-I love that beat.
-The picture upside down.
-Upside down.
It really tells you that, yeah,
the guy is really, really blind for sure.
But it's also heartbreaking
in its way too.
Because in some weird way,
it makes him vulnerable.
-Yeah.
-Yeah, you think, "Oh, he did that."
It also tells you
that he doesn't have many friends.
Like there's no people coming
to the house and telling him:
"You put that picture upside down.
You should fix that."
He's a very lonely man right now.
Right. Right.
Yeah, I found that shot,
when I saw the film, to be really moving.
Here, of course, is our long hero shot.
That's gonna... Basically the goal,
obviously, is to get from the start...
It's basically a shot that switches
points of view in the movie...
...and shows you the story
from their point of view.
And it's gonna end up
over the shoulder of the Blind Man.
Showing how scary it is for him to be
home-invaded without him knowing it.
Obviously, it's showing all the pieces
that are gonna play a part in the movie.
But, I mean, you know,
it's fascinating...
...because what you just
showed there was a tool room.
An orderly tool room.
And there's nothing intrinsically
threatening about that.
-Mm-hm. Yeah.
-You know?
I mean, it's tools that he's laid out
to do jobs around the house.
But the audience knows.
Of course, in context.
The audience can see the hammer.
We push into that like we did.
These are all pieces
that are gonna come back.
The bell, that is the alarm system
that the Blind Man has...
...for what's happening in the cellar.
-We're still in one shot here?
-It's one shot that starts at the door...
-Amazing.
-...and ends up upstairs.
Of course, we'll know that the money
is right somewhere there. Closet.
And the door to the cellar.
It's all the pieces.
Remember that we always
talked about this movie being...
...kind of a chess game
between these two parts.
So this is a moment
where we show kind of the rules...
...and who are the players.
What door is locked, what door is not.
-Right.
-Before the game starts.
Right. Stake out the terrain a little bit.
Also, here you start...
I think also this is the first time
that you start feeling Roque Banos.
A magnificent soundtrack
which is, like he said...
...the whole music
was actually done through...
...not classical instruments...
...but mostly pipes
and weird instruments that he found...
...made by a guy in Tucson that created
his own instruments in his back yard...
...and called it an orchestra.
And in this whole shot,
we really get to enjoy that soundtrack.
And like Roque said, "It's like if the
house was singing this unsettling song."
Right.
And you get a glimpse of the daughter.
Which is curious. Of course the TV's
there, but he doesn't watch the TV.
So I thought it was interesting
to have it pointed in a strange way.
Not towards the bed.
But he uses it just to fall asleep
to the sound of his daughter.
Sure, it provides the soundtrack
for his life, I think.
Yeah.
And it's like a lullaby for him.
Here we are.
Just like that, we switch point of view
and now we're with him.
As he's the main character
of his movie, right?
He's the hero of his movie.
He's just sleeping,
not bothering anybody...
...and there's a guy walking
into his room.
What does a tree need to grow?
Water, seeds...
A very cocky guy, by the way.
-Very. Yeah.
-Ha-ha-ha.
I love what Danny does there.
He just stops and enjoys
his moment of bravery, right?
That was an interesting
and cool cut you did there.
Not even seeing the rise up, you know?
I think this moment
is kind of setting the tone...
...and the dynamics
of the whole movie.
Yeah, the idea that
he really can hear anything.
He has a well-trained ear.
And the detail
of the cross on the wall...
...which is again an amazing job
of Naaman Marshall...
...the production designer.
Had so many little details there.
And you see the cross.
It used to be a cross on the wall...
...If you take a look above the bed.
You see the shape of the cross,
but it's not there anymore.
So it tells a little bit
of the faith loss of this guy.
Done!
What the fuck, dude?
The guy's gassed out.
He's out.
I think the fact that the dog went down...
-...the same way, got neutralized...
-Mm-hm.
...I think it makes
the guy getting neutralized...
...almost a complete,
immediate buy as well.
Yeah.
If you think about it,
you know he's gonna wake up.
But somehow it's very helpful.
First the dog, and then him.
Yeah.
It supplies them
with the feeling of confidence...
...that they can make noise.
Yeah, I think...
Looking at the movie now,
we realize all the little details...
...that we draw that we had
to do research on.
You know, experts on
how to do all these crimes, right?
How do you put someone to sleep?
The gas thing,
the gas bottle, actually...
...we never got to the bottom of it...
-...if it was a myth or reality.
-Mm-hm.
But there's a lot of that myth
running around in Europe.
People say that if you take
a night train in certain parts...
...of Europe,
people walk into the train...
Robbers may go into your wagon...
...and basically smoke you
while you're sleeping...
-...and you just fall into a deeper sleep.
-Hm.
And they will rob
whatever you have with you.
Then we read that it was actually a myth.
That nothing can actually do that to you.
But we preferred
to believe that it works.
It doesn't matter.
Urban myth is powerful.
But the cool thing is that we may think
that maybe they thought it was true.
But it clearly didn't work.
-Yeah.
-Right.
And this is another one, like,
the silencer...
...made with a bottle, which again,
I never saw in a movie.
We just... We read about it
and heard from a lot of people.
And the gun expert in this movie
actually told us about it.
There's a way to do a homemade silencer
which is just with a bottle.
And then of course, like YouTube...
...you have a lot of videos of people...
...shooting guns in bottles
to show it works.
-And it definitely works.
-Mm.
It muffles the gunfire.
But obviously,
it didn't muffle it enough.
Because here we are.
Who's there?
This is definitely one of those moments...
...that when we were writing the script...
...you knew it was gonna be
an intense scene, right?
Yeah, this was always my favorite scene.
This is the first time that
Stephen Lang's character speaks.
And he sounds like
a normal, harmless man.
-He's scared, right?
-He's scared, yeah.
We talked about this a lot, remember,
when we were shooting this.
And did it quite a number of times...
...trying to modulate...
...you know...
...the amount
of fear with strength.
That's what I love
about your work in the scene.
I can see how, knowing what I know...
...about the character,
knowing all his secrets...
...right there, I can see how
at first his reaction, of course...
...he doesn't know
how much they know.
Maybe they took her away already.
Maybe she's gone. Maybe she's...
Maybe that precious cargo
he has in the cellar...
Maybe she's not there.
By this point, I can see
how you start realizing...
...that they haven't
opened the door yet.
Well, they did,
but they're not down there yet.
They don't sound like
they know what's going on.
And how you go from...
...being startled and scared
to suddenly, "I can see.
I can hear your thoughts as you go.
Okay, I gotta do this.
-I have to."
-Yeah, it's interesting...
...to see how he made a choice
in a second.
Like, "I have to take care of this guy.
-There's no way around it."
-Yeah.
-Whoo!
There was a point that we actually...
We never really seriously
thought about doing it...
...but I fantasized about the idea
of making this movie black and white...
...because there's something
so classic film noir of Hollywood.
You have a section coming up
that is total noir.
Yeah.
-Right? I mean, you did it.
-Heh, heh.
And the colors are so rich,
I think, that it's...
It makes it a pleasure to watch...
...even when what you're watching
is not all that pleasurable in a way.
This is a very important moment
for Money's character...
...because at the end,
he redeems himself, right?
In saying that it's just him...
...in the house...
...when the Blind Man asks,
"How many of you are there?"
Before he dies he's doing something...
-At least something good.
-Yeah, he's doing good for her.
He might have cowered up
and asked for help...
...or told him there's a witness
there as well...
...and maybe that perhaps...
...he might have thought
that was gonna save him.
I don't think it would have, but...
Poor Danny.
You really rough him up there.
I think I told you
about the story when...
...the first kind of really rough
encounter that we shot...
...was actually later in the movie.
It was you against...
Against Alex, right?
-Played by Dylan Minnette.
-Mm-hm.
And after that day,
Dylan was like, "Oh, man."
He went to Danny Zovatto,
who plays Money...
...and warned him about that.
He warned him like, "Look.
If you ask Slang to bring it,
he'll bring it.
You better be ready
because it's gonna be a tough scene.
Your body is gonna be in pain
for the rest of the week."
You know, I've heard that.
And the thing is, I take slight exception
to it because we were pretty careful.
-Of course it's safe.
-It's rugged stuff.
-You know what I mean?
-There's no way to fake that.
There's no way to fake that.
As a director,
the last thing I want is to see...
...that thing
being faked too much.
And remember that Danny
always tells the story...
...that he actually asked you,
"You've got to bring it. Just bring it.
I'll take it."
But then at the end of that day,
I remember him coming back to me.
Like, "Oh, man." He was terrified.
But that's a great thing.
I think that's something you really
brought to the film and the set...
...that every time you walk on set,
I could feel these kids.
Because a lot of them, they're just
making their second, third movie.
Except for Dylan over there,
who made like 20 movies.
He's been working since he was 5.
But there was a sense of respect and fear
that I enjoyed so much watching.
-And you can see it.
-think a lot of that fear...
Because as a rule, I was
just pretty quiet in between takes.
-Just sitting there quietly.
-Yeah.
I think that it was them
doing their work.
That they were projecting an awful lot
of intimidation from me.
And I was just sitting there.
They were doing my work for me.
They were just wonderful, I thought.
So game.
-Yeah.
-So canny.
Each one of them, they really brought it.
The physicality in the way
that you guys play those scenes...
...IS very important.
One of the things that
we were kind of nervous about...
...when we came up
with the idea is that...
...if this guy is a blind guy...
...and there's three kids, people will
think, "Why don't they take on him?
Why don't they fight him?"
Why don't they just jump on him
and that's it?
But in that scene
where you fight Money...
-...and start punching the wall...
-Mm-hm.
...then it's clear
that it's not an easy task.
So that makes the whole premise work.
Otherwise, I think
it would have collapsed.
There's not a single moment
of this movie when you feel...
When you think as an audience,
"Oh, they should just jump on him."
Heh. There's no way.
Like, this kind of shot,
it establishes dominance.
Even though he doesn't know he's here,
he's dominating the house in a way.
And they're just cowering in corners.
I was gonna say, look at that...
-...how small he is right there.
-That's a great shot.
And also,
let's not forget that part of the thing...
...that makes your presence so menacing
and makes all this so real...
...were the contact lenses
that you were wearing.
How much could you see?
You couldn't see a lot, right?
So remember that somebody
would bring you to the set?
And you were really becoming
that character on so many levels.
Just the fact that you
got to know that house pretty well.
I don't remember seeing you
bumping against anything...
...during the whole making
of the movie.
-And you could barely see with those.
-Right. Right.
The lenses were extremely helpful...
...because they're
a constant obstacle...
...and a constant reminder.
Because it cuts
your vision down by 70 percent.
And the rest of it, that other 30 percent,
you kind of just let go.
-You just sort of glaze out, I think.
-Yeah.
So it was extremely helpful.
But so much of the blindness,
when I watch the film...
...Is really sold by the direction
that you would give me...
...when you would say, "Slang,
just tilt your head that way more."
And it all had to do with
how the camera was perceiving me...
...and perceiving my relationship
with whoever was in the room...
...or what I was listening to.
So that was a good duet,
I thought, between actor and director.
Or trio really, between actor,
director, and the camera itself.
One of the things
that I loved that you brought...
...is the idea of those marks in the wall.
That was not on the script, obviously.
The fact that the guy...
...he gets around the house
touching the wall.
-Touching the wall all the time.
-There should be stains on the wall.
Those marks that have been happening
for a long, long time.
That's the production designer.
Naaman Marshall had
so many details like that...
...that you can really believe...
...that this house is a place
that he has lived for a long time.
Rocky, hey, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Maybe... Maybe we should
call the cops before he does.
I like this moment. It's the last...
...moment of Alex
trying to do the right thing.
He believes they should call the cops.
And if they do that, perhaps,
they might hear their...
They might go to jail perhaps,
but at least they're not gonna die.
And Alex is really trying
to get her alive out of here.
But she has different plans.
She's the boss.
She really is the boss.
And it's really cool
how things went south.
-Money got shot.
-Ha, ha.
But at the same time,
they find the money.
And it's even a lot more money
than they thought it would be.
-So that raises the stakes.
-It's good we never show it.
Watching I realize the camera...
...never shows you like,
"Look, money."
It never pushes inside the box.
It never shows you the bag.
You just see the blocks of money.
And they're even blurry
in most of the shots.
Because the story
was never really about the cash.
But you know they have
something that they want.
Well, her movie is about the money.
-Ha-ha-ha.
-Yeah, of course.
But the way it's played over there...
...It's so much more about...
...what she wants to do against
what he wants to do at some point.
That was... Why did you go outside
there? Why were we on that door?
Oh, because he said... I love this moment.
He said out loud that that's the way out.
And he says the storm door cellar.
It was a brief reminder to the audience,
what was that door?
And I think it really helps the audience
to know where we're going...
...and what they're trying to achieve.
I don't like when in stories like this
the audience gets confused...
...about where they're heading.
Where they're going. What's their plan?
I wanted be very clear and precise about,
what's the plan here for these kids?
That makes a lot of sense.
I think this scene is kind of like
the spirit of the whole movie.
This is where we wanted
to get with the idea of...
-This is one of my favorite moments.
-...the guy being blind.
It's when we start thinking about
the movie and the idea of the movie.
Thinking about these moments
is when we thought:
"Oh, it's gonna be special.
This is worth making.
I've never seen this scene before."
And right here,
it's almost like a ghost story.
It's almost like for you, right,
the Blind Man, it's a ghost story.
There is a presence in his house...
...that even though he can't see it...
...he suspects it might be there.
But it's such a strange thing.
And it works so well.
It's ghosts that you can shoot.
That's right.
Here's when the title
really comes back to you.
I'm really waiting for the end.
The breathing you hear
is the Blind Man's.
Heavier than anybody else. It's great.
I can see that he's worried.
And he suspects there might be someone.
This is the best.
And also, this moment is very important.
That already happened before.
Something we want
to get out of the way is...
...we want to make sure the audience
doesn't suspect the twist...
...of this movie was gonna be
he can actually see.
That would be terrible.
So, with scenes like this one...
...is when you know that we're not
hiding anything from the audience.
And also how dangerous he is.
He hears the cell phone and reacts...
...in a fraction of a second
and shoots spot on.
Yeah, this is a time...
By this moment,
the movie has introduced, like...
...this is them against him.
And this is how good they are,
and this is how good he is.
So we'll see if they manage
to get away with the money, right?
That could happen right now.
-Yeah.
-From our point of view.
Yeah.
I guess, yeah, I'm curious...
I don't know if the audience expected it,
if they know what's coming.
I'm sure they know
there's something more to it.
I think at least the first screenings
that we had of this movie...
...because people were coming in
without seeing any trailers...
...they didn't know about it.
And the moment that's coming right now...
...Is such a huge surprise
for everybody.
This is a great moment as well.
We're exploring all his senses.
We already explored
how he can hear anything.
Now we can explore
how he can smell anything.
Again, I think people tend to believe...
-...blind people have better smell.
-Mm-hm.
But it's not really that. It's just
that they pay more attention to it.
They have developed that more
just by using it more than we do.
But it's not a super sense.
We never went too far in that aspect.
I mean, anybody can smell a pair
of smelly shoes, heh, heh, in a room.
And Money's shoes are the first ones
he found. I'm sure they're quite smelly.
Yeah, things are gonna
turn upside down pretty fast.
That money's gone.
Yeah, I love
how vulnerable you are there.
How the audience will feel,
"Oh, man, they fooled him.
They made a fool out of him...
...by looking over his shoulder
and seeing the code."
That's what's going through his mind.
He's so frustrated.
At the same time...
...that's the moment that,
in the whole movie I think...
...it's that moment there when
the Blind Man realizes he's been...
You know,
he's just been fooled by these kids...
...Is when your empathy
is really with him.
It's so strongly with him.
I think most of the audience...
...at this point is like,
"Why'd they do that to him?
-Right.
-And at that moment...
...we change everything around
by showing this girl.
That was the piano moment there.
-Remember the sitting on the piano?
-Yeah.
I loved that.
You actually can hear some of that.
But also it's a great job
of Gardner Gould...
...the editor,
when he would basically decide...
...let's not show her right away.
We see a jump,
we see that someone shows up.
But instead of staying
and showing the audience...
...we just cut back upstairs
to the Blind Man and stay with him.
And basically get the audience
to be desperate to go back in there...
...and find out what that was...
...and who was that girl?
What?
Rocky? Rocky.
Rocky, listen. Hey, that's our exit.
He did a good job.
The Blind Man did a great job
taking care of her.
With the cushions and the plants,
to have oxygen.
Yeah. It kind of gives new meaning
to the term man cave, doesn't it?
-Completely.
-Ha-ha-ha.
-We have to get her out of here.
-No, no, no.
So that first
short glimpse of the newspaper...
...Is basically when they find out...
...that she was absolved of the crime.
That she actually did something terrible.
But she was found innocent.
But that doesn't mean she was innocent.
I believe she was very, very guilty.
But the law found her innocent.
And we'll find out more eventually
when the Blind Man talks about it.
But this is actually the first...
Yeah, probably the first
or second shot...
...you did in character as the Blind Man.
-Really?
-This is the first day on set, I believe.
-I hang off the thing and look down.
-Yeah.
Mislead the audience to believe
that you're going after them.
-2-9-7-8.7-8, 7-8.2-9-7-8.
-2-9-7-8.
It's something that during the writing...
...and not just the writing
but the making...
...we were always trying to keep
close attention to those details...
...and make sure that every movement
they make made sense.
And here it wasn't just
for the value of the shock...
...of what's gonna happen next.
But I think...
I don't know if you agree, Slang.
I think it made complete sense
that if he went after them...
...that might have gone wrong.
He was expect...
That's how smart he is.
He knows that if they took the money
out of his safe upstairs...
...they know the code.
If they know the code...
...he knows
it's the same as downstairs...
...which means they might
have the keys already.
Which means if he decides
to go after them...
...and maybe he doesn't manage to get
to them and block a door or something...
...they will get to this door before
he does and they will be out.
And that's not good for him.
So that's why I think he very quickly
put all that together.
Turns around and decides
to wait for them on the other side.
Absolutely.
Since they've gone
down the rabbit hole...
...he knows they're coming out.
There's only one way to come out.
And he's doing more than that.
By this point he already...
We'll find out later.
But at this point,
he already took the dog.
He put him inside the house.
And he went after them probably.
Because now he's gonna go after them.
But we'll see that the dog
is already inside the house.
So he's done all that very quickly.
He ran out, took the dog inside,
closed the door...
...and went after them.
So it's incredible.
I would love to see
this movie over again...
...from his point of view.
And realizing the clever things
he's doing...
...one after the other.
I think this is an interesting twist.
We just introduced this girl,
and she's dying already.
Yeah. Everybody thinks it'll be about...
Now it's all gonna be about:
"Okay, are they
gonna be able to save the girl?"
But very quickly, she's gone.
Well, you've already established
your credentials as somewhat merciless.
You know, heh, heh,
and I mean that in a very good way.
Because the dispatching
of Money is quick, and it's early.
Yeah.
And he's a substantial character.
He cuts a wide swath while he's there.
If you kill him off...
...well, then you dudes
are capable of anything.
And that was
one of the first ideas that we got.
Like, these guys break into
this Blind Man's house.
-And one of them dies right away.
-Mm-hm.
That will make you nervous and tense
throughout the whole movie.
You will know that he doesn't hesitate.
The Blind Man didn't even...
He asked one question.
The only relevant question was
"How many people in the house?"
And hoping that he might
or might not be honest.
Or maybe he might have caught him lying.
No!
I love this scene too.
This raises a lot of questions as well.
Like, why is he feeling this so much?
Yeah.
You did an amazing job here, Slang.
It's one of those that...
When you're shooting...
...it's hard to get into the scene.
For the director, it's hard to get
into the emotion of the movie.
There's so much you pay attention to.
This one was one of those
that while I was watching the shot...
...I felt like I was in the theater
watching the movie.
I was so excited.
Just an emotional transformation
from being in hunter mode...
...and realize what they just did,
and, oh, man, now it's personal.
Before it wasn't.
It was like, I don't care who you are.
You're just gonna die
because you know my secret...
...and I cannot let you go.
-Now I think it's personal.
-Right.
I mean, the thing that...
The prevailing thing that goes on...
...when he knows who it is...
...is this feeling of being
bereft immediately, you know?
But there's no time for that.
There's no time for grief at all.
Because he's in a war zone here.
You know?
Yeah. Because his feelings
about that girl are rather complex.
-Yeah.
-They are.
Because mostly... I mean, he definitely
has... I'm sure he has feelings.
And he's not a guy that is taken by hate.
I don't think he's in
that place right now.
He's past that probably.
But he definitely...
You know, we'll find out later
she was pregnant.
So that scene there
is his daughter dying again.
-Right.
-That's why it's so powerful.
Because he's been through that already...
...when he found out
about his daughter dying.
And we always imagine
that he was actually on that day...
...when his daughter got run over...
...he was right there in his house
and ran to her body.
So I think that for him,
it's just going through that pain again.
So that's why he makes it so determined.
Because from this point on
there's no hesitation.
There's no fear whatsoever
from the point of view of the Blind Man.
He's completely, full-on in hunter mode.
But you know if he had the moment
to think about it...
-...he wouldn't have been surprised.
-Yeah.
Because everything that life's given him
has just been a kick in the ass.
I love that fan thing, by the way.
He knows every detail.
And this scene,
it's one of my favorites in the movie.
But it's sort of whimsical in a way
because he could just touch the fan...
-...but he gives it a little spin. Heh, heh.
-Heh-heh-heh.
This scene was also
one of the earliest ideas that we got.
We knew that we were gonna
kill one of them pretty quick.
We knew that we were gonna have
this full dark scene.
This took so much preparing and thinking.
Just in the early stages of preproduction
with Pedro, the DP.
We were like, "There are many things
we need to solve here.
But the main one is how are we
gonna do the darkness scene?"
On the page it says,
"Well, he flips a switch...
-...and everything goes completely dark."
-Mm-hm.
Which of course gives us moments
like this one we're looking at now.
Which are unique.
But look at the way she's...
She's just selling it beautifully there,
isn't she?
Totally.
You really believe what she's doing.
You see? I don't know if you notice...
...but every time you shoot the gun,
there's color pumped into the shot.
Of course, the logic is, if there's
no light, there's no color. Right?
And so that's why I think
the audience buys it so well.
Black and white and no shadows...
...that indicates that there's no light.
But every time we shoot the gun,
there's a muzzle flash.
By the way, for anybody that's thinking,
"Conveniently he ran out of bullets."
We actually counted them.
It's precisely how many bullets
there are in that gun.
The ones that he shot
are exactly the gun's...
The bullets that you have in that gun.
-I remember that discussion as well.
-Ha-ha-ha.
We counted all of them,
particularly when we were editing...
...because you might have shot
more shots like in the shooting itself.
But then when we cut the movie,
we made sure...
...that we had the exact amount
in that gun.
This way. This way, come on.
This way, come on, come on, come on.
Oh, come on. Where am I?
This was a combination...
...of the light from the camera
and the whole treatment.
But as well they had contact lenses
making their eyes look dilated.
Their pupils dilated.
But of course, Jane Levy
and Dylan Minnette did an amazing job...
...selling the full darkness.
They did. And it's not just the eyes.
Also it's the open mouth.
-Yeah.
-You know, in a way.
Ha-ha-ha, that is a great shot.
Ha-ha-ha.
When you think it's over,
it's just beginning.
That's what happens constantly
in this movie.
Try the blue key. Do it.
Ha, ha, that dog.
There are three dogs in this movie.
Three different dogs that you see.
I'm trying to remember names.
Oh, gosh.
-Athos, that's one of them.
-Athos.
Athos. There was...
What was the other one?
-Porthos and Aramis. I don't think it was.
-Ha-ha-ha. Exactly.
I love this twist when suddenly,
he decides to sit down...
...which obviously wasn't in the script.
We were shooting the moment.
When the dog was supposed
to be looking fierce...
...he decided to sit down.
But I ended up keeping it.
I thought it was a really good twist
that he talks to him.
Maybe he'll talk him down.
Some dogs, if you talk to them calmly,
they might respond to that.
He's also a little hungover.
Yeah. Yeah. Definitely.
And the dog was actually chasing them.
-So there was no faking there as well.
-Ha-ha-ha.
Yeah.
We were guaranteeing them
that the dog wasn't gonna attack.
But they weren't counting on the promise.
They were just running...
...like maniacs, trying to get in the room
before the dog got to his mark.
You're back.
They felt the same way about the dog
that they did about me.
That we're both
just sort of slavering maniacs.
And the dog was a sweetheart,
just like me.
See, that's the thing here.
It's one of those stories where...
What are you doing?
Regardless of what the Blind Man does...
...there's no question at any moment.
Everything he's doing, if you were him,
you would do the same thing.
There's nothing to talk about
with them, there's nothing to...
There's no conversation.
The Blind Man has to get rid of them.
Because there's no way
he can let them go...
...and trust that they're not gonna
tell his secret or anything like that.
There's no way around that.
I remember we talked about this.
His goal is not to make them suffer.
He really doesn't want to punish them
or make them suffer.
It's not about that.
He has to kill them.
But, you know, there's this...
To me, there's this
sense of outrage in this film.
That this outrage was perpetrated
against him, against his life.
You know, he's gonna talk about it a
little bit, in terms of God and everything.
But, um...
-Whoot! Eh...
-Whoa.
And it's just, um...
He just will not allow that.
He needs... He becomes proactive.
It's almost... It's everything he's doing.
Yeah, it's against these kids,
but it's really against the world.
It's against the cosmos.
It's against God.
It's against this everything
that has just destroyed his being.
I think that
what you're saying is really spot on.
And that is a common thing
for all the characters in the movie.
Rocky's character
kind of feels the same way.
She feels like
life hasn't given her anything.
In fact, she's been very unlucky
with the life that she got.
And she's, in a way,
trying to bring justice on her own terms.
And she feels entitled to do this,
to go get that money.
She feels like she deserves that.
I think all the characters are trying
to bring justice...
-...in their own way.
-Mm.
That's the moral of the story, I think.
It's like if all of us
just decide to violate all the rules...
...and just go and get whatever we want
and feel that we deserve...
...like, you get these scenarios, right?
Like, because she will find out...
She basically finds someone that thinks...
...ironically, just like her. The Blind
Man and Rocky have a lot in common.
Just the Blind Man's
been through a lot more than she did.
But they both believe
that they have the right...
...to break the rules
just to get what they feel...
...they deserve and...
We'll leave to the audience
to believe if that's right or not.
But that was definitely the...
Thematically was the strong, you know...
Just the way... I just wanna cut in
and say the way that the dog, Athos...
...the way he has to crouch
his way through there...
...and everything like that, it just...
That in and of itself,
it's in two shots, is just so alarming.
He sort of looks like
a gigantic rat in a way.
-Yeah. Heh, heh.
-You know?
I remember we were writing the script,
we had this experience on Evil Dead...
...with the dog
that we used in that movie.
And it was so hard
to get that dog to do anything.
Like, the smallest things, like,
"Hey, come here," he wouldn't do it.
And then we wrote
all the scenes with the dog.
And we were like, "We're never gonna
find a dog that's gonna do that.”
-Ha-ha-ha.
-And fortunately this amazing dog...
-Oh, the Hungarian dogs are very, very...
-Yeah.
-They're the best.
-Yeah, the best.
That's a great twist as well.
How you think the Blind Man's gone...
...actually went upstairs
and fools him again.
He's always showing up
in places that you don't think he will.
It's great because you're just exploiting
the geography of this house...
...you know, to... Almost to the max.
But about what you were saying...
...you know,
both for Jane and the Blind Man...
...um...
...they're taking responsibility for their
lives as well. I mean, it's kind of...
They're making the existential choice
that they're not gonna, you know...
They're not gonna go quietly
into the dark.
They're not just gonna let life, like...
They're not gonna accept that...
"Well, that was just bad luck."”
And it's the life they got.
-It's like they're gonna...
-Right.
They're gonna take matters
in their own hand...
...and change fate.
It's almost like they know they...
They're going... They might take a path
that is just gonna be constant darkness.
And they're just trying to find a way
to break out of there...
...right, by all means necessary.
That's what they're all doing.
There's, again,
a beautiful moment of mixing a lot of...
...beautiful techniques of cinema.
It's just the silence,
the camera work, the light...
...everything worked so well
for me in this montage here.
And the title comes in right... Heh.
Comes to you again, like, don't breathe.
It, like, makes it in that...
He made a mistake breathing.
Here we fool
the audience with a montage a little.
They don't know it
but it's been a time jump there.
That was fun to shoot.
This was a rugged set to be on
right here.
Because it's all... This was all real.
Not like there was a lot
of rubber stuff going on here.
-Aah. That hurt, I remember that.
-That hurt.
Because I think he missed
the countdown or something...
...and he surprised you with it,
like, ahead of time.
I like that this is the first hint that
we give that if there's a sound...
...a loud sound in the place,
then his powers disappear.
Heh. Like, that's his weakness,
too much... Too much noise.
And eventually it'll be
some sort of demise for him.
But even...
Like, when you're watching the movie,
like, I get this...
Do I want him to grab the gun
and shoot the Blind Man in the head?
I don't really know if I want that.
I don't think the audience wants that.
They want them to live
but that, that's what makes it...
I think that's what make
the movie effective...
...Is that you understand that...
...even though he's doing
something terrible, he's in his house.
And a lot of things he's doing,
he has the right to do them.
And that makes it
so complicated and so complex...
...on that level, like, you don't...
If Alex would have reached that gun...
...and shoot the Blind Man in the head,
and leave, I don't think...
...the audience would've been satisfied.
They would be like... Like he just...
They break into this guy's house,
they murder him...
...take his money away.
Like, it would be a terrible ending.
That's why it puts the audience
in a place that they want them to leave...
...but they don't want them
to shoot the Blind Man.
It makes it so complex
and puts the audience...
...In a great place to be.
Because they want to know
how it's gonna end up.
Yeah, yeah. Well, I mean, the Blind Man,
from my point of view has...
...at this point earned...
He's earned a lot of points. I mean,
there's reasons for his sickness...
...and his, you know, his pathology.
But there's a lot about him that...
You know, he's got his own integrity.
Seems to me,
and I think people respond to that...
...to an extent.
Yeah, well, and obviously,
just the fact that he's...
He's a blind character
that at first we all see...
Kind of almost...
...the audience look at the movie
and when they...
When he gets introduced,
kind of look down on him.
Like, "Oh, poor guy."
We kind of feel pity for him.
And you realize now that... You know,
that you should feel pity for the kids...
...and not for him.
So it's such a, it's...
And I think that's a
quality that's in the...
Regardless of what he's doing,
and the terrible things he's doing...
...like, the audience admires that.
The fact that a character
that was introduced...
...in a way
that make them feel pity for him...
...because he was blind,
and living by himself...
...and all this tragedy.
Like, not really how capable he is.
And how he doesn't let something
like blindness, like, stop him.
-No, there's a...
-Be fully functional.
No, I mean, the first time you see him,
he's walking the dog.
He's doing, like, you know,
kind of an all-American activity.
Here again.
I think as soon as she's hitting that...
...the audience knows
she shouldn't be making that sound.
-That's a CG hand.
-Heh.
That's actually the only CG hand.
One of the biggest CG elements
and that's something I personally did...
...on my computer when I realized
I didn't get the shot because you...
Originally, you grab her hair.
But it wasn't on the shot...
...and it wasn't so effective.
And I remember cutting the movie,
I just opened my laptop and, like...
...let me put something together
and I did the shot.
And I thought
it was gonna be a mock-up...
...and it end up in the movie.
It ended up being that shot over there.
I love this moment.
Something that I stole from Hitchcock...
...who said that he shot...
He shot love scenes like death scenes...
...and death scenes
like love scenes.
And this definitely looks
more like a love scene...
...on the setting and there's no cuts.
It's just like this long agony, right?
And I particularly like what...
Using those short punches.
You know, there's nothing...
Many times in movies,
you have these long loping punches.
I mean, these are just...
Those are little... Three short punches.
Yeah, they look so painful.
What's interesting about that moment
is that I'm not exactly sure when...
...he realized that this...
That there was a girl...
...in this pack of thieves.
And he made the choice, "Okay, this is...
-This is actually good."
-Mm-hm.
-I might need that girl.
-Well, yeah...
I don't know when exactly it happens
but it could have happened...
...also when he found the shoes.
When he smelled her shoes,
I think he knows.
We were joking, he knows there's a girl.
And he knows that.
He maybe even knows...
...that she's having her period, ha, ha,
like, stuff like that. Like, "Hm..."
I don't think she has her period.
That would have save her, actually.
Yeah, but I mean, the idea
that he can use her...
...because the other girl is dead...
-When does that happen?
-Yeah.
I mean, I think if you wanna
project it into that...
...into the kind of weird
love scene upstairs...
...that we just saw, you can do that.
You know, but that's for...
Please, let me go!
I think dialogue's
come back here, which is, uh...
-The funny and interesting thing...
-Nobody's said anything for 40 minutes.
You wanted her to pay.
I understand that.
I won't tell anyone.
You understand nothing.
And the audience...
...doesn't understand.
It's one of those moments...
...that you'll find out the truth
about who he is.
Between a father and his child.
Yeah,
I love this speech. It used to be longer.
And we ended up cutting a bit out of it.
I think on the deleted scenes
you hear more about it.
Which it was, of course,
not because it wasn't great...
...I think it was amazing,
but it was one of the things...
...that less was more.
The more mystery
we could keep around him...
And we'd never wanna do the villain...
...that just over-explains
his life and his plans.
So I think we do have the exact amount
that we needed there, I guess, for...
That's what I thought when I saw it.
I couldn't remember exactly...
...what was not there,
but I knew there was something.
But it didn't seem
that it was missing anything.
-Yeah.
-And then I saw the deleted scene.
And I went, "Oh, yeah,
that stuff. That was good too."
It was great.
But at the end of the day...
...it's like that thing.
He doesn't have...
He doesn't need to talk with her.
He's past all that...
...like, he explains himself or like...
I think part of him wants to feel human
and less evil about what he's doing.
That deep inside
he knows that it's a bad thing.
But he's trying to be...
He's just, of course, turning a blind eye
on what he's doing.
That's why I think
he explains himself a bit:
"Hey, I'm not a monster.
If you could see
the things that happened to me...
...like, you'll understand, right?"
I love Jane's reaction, her acting here...
...where she kind of, like,
starts putting the pieces together...
...and realizing what's coming.
It's really good.
I like this reveal as well.
That's almost kind of silly
but it kind of makes sense, right?
He was laying right on top of the body,
and the Blind Man just struck down and...
And actually if he...
There was a longer version of the shot
where you could see that the...
The blade actually scratch his cheek
and his ear and so he missed by nothing.
Here's the moment of, obviously, Alex...
...starting to turn into, you know...
...the different person, like really...
He started doubting himself so much...
...and being so scared
of everything. And now he's, like...
He's been through so much that...
Again, like, moral of this character...
...Is he's, like,
ready to do something about it...
...and not just be
cowering behind shelves.
He takes a hammer
and he's gonna do something about it.
-Ah, yes...
-Oh, the tar.
-This famous scene.
-Heh, heh.
Franciska,
the girl that played that character...
...she really took it.
She had to stay there still.
It was really a black
thick paint to the...
It was harmless
but still, it was terrible.
And had to just stay there
and let the paint go up...
...and not breathe and...
Because if she blew it...
...doing the whole thing again
was impossible.
-Yeah, no, she did a yeoman job.
-Yeah.
I love that the Blind Man has everything
kind of planned ahead of...
Like, he knew that
if she died, he wasn't gonna go...
...and bury her in the backyard.
And risking someone seeing him do that.
So he had this plan
to bury her in the cellar.
Or maybe
you could even think that once the...
She gave birth to the child...
-He'd get rid of the body.
-That's what I thought...
Yeah.
...it was gonna be
because he really couldn't release her.
But you never know
what would happen by then...
...you know? I mean...
Probably he didn't know. I think that...
In that aspect, I think,
because he's such a...
Emotion is so complex for him,
I think he was trying, you know...
...on the plan to do with her,
trying to figure out...
...he will cross that bridge
when he gets there.
It's a joke.
It's a bad joke.
You tell me what God would allow...
Once again, that...
The audience thinks they know
what's gonna happen.
They think it's gonna be a rape scene
or some sort of...
Just gonna be there.
And the whole motivation
behind everything...
...all the weirdness,
is that this is gonna follow.
It was that
it was all for the sake of the character.
Like, we knew
that the Blind Man being who he was...
...and having the codes
that he had... Like he says now...
...I love the line
that, "I'm not a rapist."
Like, that really put things...
Gets you thinking about
what he's gonna do now.
Aah. No. No, no.
Like I said, what follows that...
...really was for the sake
of not just being perverted...
...or doing something super twisty.
It was just that being who he was...
...we needed to protect him,
and we didn't wanna have a scene...
...where he puts his pants down.
He's gonna be an animal.
He would still have his morals.
And he was gonna do it
in a way that didn't require that.
Right.
And, again, for people that are thinking
this is some twisted movie thing...
...that we came up with,
turkey baster in the...
And the sperm.
It's actually the way you do it.
It's actually medically accurate.
If a single mom
wants to have kids at home...
...they don't wanna go
through the sperm bank and...
It's still pretty twisted.
It is, but at home insemination
is the way you do it. It's not...
I mean, to be honest...
You take a turkey baster
and that's the way you do it.
It was a twisted idea.
But it happened to be that
then it was something that occurs.
That may be
the single most disgusting moment...
...in the film right there.
It's so weird. At the end of the day...
...like, it's what we thought
is fascinating about it.
If that was blood and that was a knife...
...nobody will even flinch.
-Right.
-They go like, "Ah, whatever."
"Oh, but it's sperm
in a turkey baster?"
And everybody loses their minds.
Heh, heh.
-And that I don't get.
-I believe there was a hair in...
-Heh-heh-heh.
-Yeah, there was a hair.
I remember seeing it with the audience.
The audience covered their mouth...
...and getting all grossed out
and I was like:
"If it was guts and blood,
nobody cares.”
It is sperm and everybody freaks out.
I think that's fascinating and it tells
a lot about who we are as a society.
There's something strange about that.
And nothing actually happened.
Like it's...
We leave everything
for the audience's imagination.
Really nothing gets to happen there.
He doesn't really get to do anything.
You know, I saw it
with a room full of journalists.
And they were reacting
just like a normal audience.
They were reacting the way you described.
I love this beat. I remember,
this was not in the script.
And Fede called me...
...during the shooting
and said, "Hey, I added this small beat."
-Oh, the upcoming one?
-Where she... Yeah.
Where she grabs the turkey baster
and stick it in his mouth.
-Yeah, see, I'll tell you what, baby...
-And this is all... This is all you, Slang.
Just because I was... I don't even know
how I dared to ask you to do that and...
But I did and I was...
I was 100 percent...
I had so many answers prepared
for when you were gonna say no to me.
I was like,
"I know he's gonna say, 'No way.
I'm not gonna do that
because it's not in the script."
Then suddenly out of nowhere...
...when I'm about to roll out
my list of answers...
...why you should do it,
as soon as I told you, you go:
"Yeah, bring it, let's do it." Heh, heh.
Which I thought it was funny.
-Well, you know...
-You did it...
It's like that old saying, you know,
"Suck one turkey baster," you know?
But I guess it is her revenge,
and she deserves it. I think...
And it's like watching it
with a female audience is...
They definitely, after suffering
that moment of just pain...
And what they thought
was gonna happen didn't happen...
...I think, it's a great payback,
and deserved payback on her side.
To give it to him
and see him doing that...
...as much as it's hilarious
and weird and funny it is...
...I think it's a deserved moment...
...for the audience,
just to get that payback, so...
It's totally earned is what it is,
I think. And that makes it just fine.
-Okay.
-This one.
Let's get out of here.
I think here, again, one moment...
...you suspect that it may be over but
the music is not giving you anything...
...the audience knows
that this is not over.
If the music was playing
a refreshing, you know, conclusive tune...
...you might think it's gone. But it's
not. You know, something's gonna...
It's just amazing that you take him out.
Yes, the audience think it's gonna be her,
ironically. I think a lot of people...
They know someone's gonna die
because the music is not playing.
And they're just at the door
just looking over their shoulder.
And there has been enough time
with the movie...
...to know
that something's gonna happen.
But they don't know who is gonna die,
who is gonna come out.
Here's one of those moments that you...
You're begging for her to run
as fast as she can.
And this is... You can see it in her eyes,
this is really the end of the shooting.
And this is probably
the last two days of shooting.
And she's exhausted,
and she's been through so much.
And it really reflects
what's going on in the story.
-And here comes the dog.
-Heh.
Shit.
Again, this is another
nice transition between Detroit...
...and this is Budapest, actually.
-Is it?
-Yeah, we changed countries...
...just like that.
That's the beginning of the shooting.
That's Detroit. That's Budapest, sorry.
-Of course.
-So, yeah. She goes over the fence.
We have the same fence
in one country and the other.
And we managed to do that stitch.
That was completely different, right?
Originally in the script.
This wasn't like this.
This came out later.
I think this might have been my first...
Actually this is...
You're completely right.
This is actually the first moment
you showed up on set.
This scene must...
It was definitely the most complex scene
for me to shoot in the whole movie.
And we actually...
It was an ongoing thing.
It was... I think there wasn't...
Basically there was...
Every week almost...
...of the shooting of this movie,
out of the 45 days of shooting...
...like, there was every five days,
something like that...
...we were coming back
to this car to pick something up.
Because it was so complex and so
tricky to get it to move around the car.
And most importantly, it was so tricky
to get the dog to do things he had to do.
Because Jane was doing her job
fantastically as you can see right here.
But the dog was so...
It was so demanding for the dog,
and so we were constantly coming back.
And during the making of the movie,
there was always a second unit...
...like adding shots to this sequence...
...which I think
makes it complete at the end.
-It works so well for me.
-Yeah.
But it was very, very demanding.
It was actually two cars.
One of the cars was cut in half.
And in order to get the camera in there.
This is actually the half car.
My God.
You know the Blind Man's coming.
Like, the audience knows
the Blind Man's coming.
Whatever she's gonna do,
she better be fast.
-Yeah, but she's so intrepid, you know?
-Yeah.
The dog is around,
so there's no way to come out.
One of those tricky puzzles.
And this is actually, um...
We were trying to figure out
how she was gonna come out of the car.
And what was the thing
she was going to do.
And because we changed this
from originally what was in the script...
...and in pre-production and...
And I remember it was Mathew Hart,
the line producer on this movie...
...looking at the car,
and all of us scratching our heads...
...looking at the car and trying to figure
out how to come out of this situation...
...If we were Rocky. And he said...
And Mathew came out
with the idea of, "What about this cord?"
Basically the whole idea
of like, at the end...
...using the cord to trap the dog
inside the house, inside the car.
-This was...
-This is where the scene gets gnarly.
Yeah.
Because that was all real,
like that was real, like...
But it was so tricky to do,
the punching the face, the click...
Did the dog actually
get that close to her?
No, no, I think the...
The side shot is a composition of shots.
But, yes, there was a stunt double,
which was the owner of the dog.
And it was this woman
in some of those shots.
There's a combination of many things.
And actually if you take a close look...
Oh, there you go. That's your
first moment he has in the movie.
I think this one here's actually,
the punch.
And the cut to this moment here.
And, uh...
-And back at the beginning.
-Back at the beginning of the film.
Which is one of those strange things
where, you know...
...even though you start there...
...the audience tends to forget about
those openings.
But they've been through so much,
the ones that are overthinking it...
...maybe they remember,
but a lot forget.
Then suddenly, you're back there.
And you go, "Yeah.
-Right, exactly.
-They told me about it.
I should have known better.
She was gonna get caught.”
It's elegant.
And this,
this is definitely one of those...
...moments that we got so lucky
on the shooting.
Like, again, very hot day.
The wrangler showed up,
and he had just one ladybug.
Just literally one ladybug and I...
And completely determined
to not do a CG ladybug...
...because I didn't do it at the
beginning, I wasn't gonna do it now.
And he puts the ladybug on her hand,
and does the perfect thing...
...that spread the wings...
...and flies away
like right in front of us.
But the first time he did it...
...the ladybug did it, we weren't rolling.
Did it so fast, and we didn't roll on it,
and we lost the ladybug.
And then it was everybody in the room
trying to find the ladybug.
And someone finds it on the drapes...
...takes it, put it back in the hand,
and it happens.
And we managed to get
that beautiful shot.
No! Aah!
Don't!
Again, I can't help
but feel pity for the Blind Man now.
Like, it's one of those,
you know he's done.
If he cannot hear anything,
like, that'd be very hard for him...
...to get her.
And Rogue music,
Roque Banos' score like starts...
Now this is all...
This was all pretty freewheeling here.
This was all...
Remember the camera.
We didn't have a...
Yeah.
We had a blueprint,
but, uh, kind of making it up...
-Yeah.
-...as we went into shooting.
-Here she comes.
-Yeah.
There was again, I think in the script,
there was many versions of this ending.
Because it was hard for us morally
to understand what was...
To really find an answer to
what was the right thing to do...
...and how the movie should end.
Because we thought that if he died,
the audience might feel bad about it...
...like strangely being such a...
You know...
...being a guy that did something so
terrible. Still, just dying like that...
...in his house
was something that felt wrong.
But most importantly what was
the thing that we really changed...
...in the script many times,
and it was...
-...if she was gonna get away with it or not.
-Mm.
I don't know if you notice that, but I
love how you can see the glare in his eyes.
You can see a couple spots of light that
kind of tells you he might not be dead.
It's gorgeous.
-Little pin pricks of light.
-Yeah.
And here in this moment,
there used to be...
One of the endings
that I still like was that she...
That was in the script
that we never shot that she heard...
...the sirens of the cars, of the cops,
but they were gonna be closer.
You're gonna see lights
coming through the windows.
I mean, not the lights.
You will notice the cars outside.
And what she would do is she will take
the money, and put it back in the safe.
And that was the only way to get saved.
She wasn't taking the money.
There was no way to prove
that she was trying to steal anything.
And she was trying to get away with that.
But it was one of those
that we felt it wasn't realistic...
...or even if that happened,
it would have been very complicated.
So at the end,
we said, like, "Okay, she's gonna...
We're not gonna do a Hollywood ending
where she gives back the money."
Which was in the script. There was
a version where she went to the police...
...and gave back the money. Yeah.
I think at the end, we decided that
this was gonna be some sort of pact...
...between criminals...
...when she learns that the guy is...
The Blind Man is still alive.
And the Blind Man
is not saying anything about the money.
And she got away with the money,
it's like a pact between them.
They're gonna be...
They're gonna keep that secret,
and they're gonna be safe.
Well, it would be a huge disappointment
if she didn't keep the money.
Heh. Yeah, of course.
I mean, for everyone.
-I mean, including the viewer, I think.
-Yeah.
You know. I... Yeah, the money.
I mean, everything would have been
completely meaningless...
...if she didn't have the money,
because it becomes about her sister.
It becomes about the dream of California.
-Yeah.
-And it becomes...
Now becomes about
the possibility of the sequel.
Yeah, but here I love this moment.
They're like so eerie.
Like, you don't... Even though
it looks like a happy ending...
...like, story-wise. It definitely doesn't
look like a happy ending.
-We thought that...
-She's leaving with the money.
And with her sister.
Everything seems well.
But, oh, you know
she's never gonna sleep well anymore.
Yeah, she knows
she's a criminal from now on.
Remember when we shot the, um...
-The Blind Man in the train station?
-Yeah, yeah.
Actually that shot, if that continued...
...you were gonna show up in there,
you'd see the Blind Man behind her.
You were never gonna see the face.
It was one of the things...
...you might think it was him or not.
But I'm happy with the end
the way it is that you know there...
There's a price she's gonna pay
that she's never gonna be at peace.
And she knows that
that guy is alive, and who knows?
He might go after her someday.
This is the title sequence
I personally designed.
-I love it.
-I did it, I just...
I didn't wanna have black titles against...
You know, white titles against black.
-And I created this sequence.
-No, it's totally cool.
Just to revisit the places in the house
that we spent so much time in.
Well, and that concludes this commentary.
-Thanks so much, guys.
-Thanks for watching.