My name is Federico Alvarez.
I'm one of the screenwriters
and the producer of this movie.
I'm Rodo Sayagues,
screenwriter and director.
And I'm Pedro Luque,
I'm the director of photography.
And we're going
to watch the movie with you
and tell you a bit about the anecdotes
and what this movie meant for us.
We're from Uruguay.
We did this in Spanish,
to do it in our native language
so it would be more natural,
but also to give an alternate version
of the commentary done by Rodo in English,
which I'm sure you can find somewhere.
The fist logo of our company, Bad Hombre,
the production company.
This is the first movie under that logo.
Well, let's begin.
-The majestic city of Detroit.
-Exactly.
This take was an attempt...
It represents the first movie well.
On the first one, we started with Pedro,
we did the aerial take,
but this one is more sophisticated.
It's an homage to the first one
and an introduction to the same world.
More special effects.
A girl walking in 3D.
Tell us, Rodo, why is the girl in 3D?
Why is the girl in 3D?
Well, because she's three years old
and it was literally impossible
for her to do that, so...
Besides, I imagine you'd be...
For how long were you filming in Detroit?
-One day.
-Right, one day.
-Two days, right? One or two.
-One or two days.
Well, here they are in...
Here we are in
the middle of Serbia, in a remote forest.
What's that?
Nobody was able
to tell us what that was,
but we thought it would be good
to include it in the scene.
Especially keeping in mind
the apocalyptic or semi-apocalyptic world
of Don't Breathe.
I imagine it's some sort of--
It looks like a generator, right?
Like some type of generator.
I think it was from a water
treatment plant or something like that.
I think the idea was...
we're opening with a scene
that takes place in a forest,
to include elements that will help us make
the transition from forest to city,
even if it's a city
half swallowed by nature...
and it looks like a city
in the middle of a jungle.
But the idea was that,
to urbanize that forest.
Also this,
the basketball hoop in the background,
elements that bring you
slowly to the city.
Correct. Because originally,
in the script, it was like an auto plant.
I think the first version we wrote
was an auto plant, right?
Yes, as a matter of fact
it does have the spirit of a junkyard.
It's Detroit.
When we went to Detroit, we noticed
that there were rotten cars all over.
And we were thinking
of creating the climax of the movie
in the same auto plant at a given time.
We thought that what would happen
in the third act
was that they would leave home and
they would get to the abandoned factory.
But then we thought about how many movies
are set in an abandoned car factory.
How could we do that?
Stephen Lang appears here,
the Blind Man.
Was this the first time
you filmed him in character?
No. We did a screen test
which was brutal.
That's where he shows up for
the first time, but it's not in the movie.
For us, that was the moment
we saw him be reborn.
-Reborn.
-Yes, that was exciting.
This shot is in Detroit.
This shot-- No. This shot is also...
It's half Detroit, half Serbia.
Half Detroit, half Serbia, right.
-This house is...
-Which half?
That part with the forest
below, that's in Serbia.
And the house.
And the top part is Detroit.
But the house was 3D.
It's 3D. The house is 3D.
We built the house, the next shot,
the ones that come after.
You can tell
there was a real house,
but I remember seeing the shot
without a house.
I thought it was Detroit.
The shot without a house
is in Detroit.
Here we are.
This was one of
the first scenes we filmed.
Yes.
This was the first day filming.
It was my first day of filming
as a director. I was pretty nervous.
Of movies.
We had done several commercials.
-Everyone was nervous.
-I was nervous, too.
I remember that it was
the first daily I saw from home.
During the pandemic,
you were making the movie
and I was here, at home,
and I hit play and started watching.
And I remember saying,
"Fantastic! It looks like a movie!"
"Not too bad."
The tender moment between...
The guy is still a toughie.
I also remember
that we talked a lot
about the idea of starting filming
with this scene
because it was a scene
that required a lot of Madelyn,
playing the role of Phoenix,
and she was nervous as well
about having to start with a scene
where she was the protagonist.
But the truth is she did very well.
You can read the hat, right?
Yes, man. Shameless advertising.
We had to put something.
It was Stephanie's first movie,
like we said before.
This is in the study,
the close-up of the girl.
It's also Madelyn's first movie.
I said no.
This was interesting,
the idea of the blind man's only friend.
The only person who, more or less,
dares to say something to the blind man.
When I saw it,
I thought this shot looked great,
with the reflection
of the blind man there.
It was longer in the first cut,
where there was a bit more
of the guy's reflection.
We cut this scene quite a bit.
It used to be...
This was one of the few scenes
we reshot some things for, right, Rodo?
Yes.
After filming,
we realized some shots were missing.
It was much more complex
and ended up looking simpler
in the final edit, and it works perfectly.
But we used that shot we missed.
We made it better in the same shot.
Yes, yes. A couple of days later.
A couple of days later
we said we were missing a shot.
Then we shot this one
and ended up using it.
I just noticed there's a sign
that says "underpass.”
That was added in post, right?
-Yes.
-No, we placed it there.
-We did?
-Really.
Madelyn was in
the first casting.
Yes, yes.
I think my mom sang it to me
when I was little.
She was there
early in the process.
Yes. Right away.
You wanna pay her a visit?
And she had not
made movies, only TV.
No, some TV shows,
but never a movie.
But she did great.
-This is Detroit.
-Back in Detroit.
We had to find identical trucks
in Detroit and another in Belgrade.
This ended up looking very nice.
And these ashes that float,
I remember that it was Fede's idea.
A few days before filming he said,
"Are they going to have ashes floating?"
And I said, "What ashes?"
And the truth is without those ashes,
the scene...
It gives it a certain magic.
In Evil Dead,
I remember the first time
the cabin door opens, it's the same.
I don't know where I saw it,
but I remember asking for it.
They had this technique with a mop.
-One of those sticks with a thing.
-Mop.
They came with the thing
and shook it in front of the lighting,
they kept going and then, "Action!"
This time they used
what they call stone candles.
Remember?
The ones we used in Spider's Web.
I love this,
without any subtlety we planted it there.
It must be said,
this is a cardinal sin
for screenwriters to place exposition
on a TV that is just...
Of course. Most of the people
who are watching this with the comments
have already seen the movie.
People already know how the film ends.
Upon second viewing, you realize
that here, in the first few minutes,
they're already telling you
where the plot is going.
The secret twist of the third act
is already there.
The story changed in editing.
Obviously,
the original scene was like this.
She would come and do all this
in the script, when we wrote it.
Later we realized in editing
that it worked better
if we saw the scene,
but then we pushed it back
and made it feel
like it was all a daydream,
like she was dreaming.
We also gave it
a more saturated look.
All the colors go up
and then get pushed back.
Really good effects.
You have to give credit
to all those people,
because they did all this,
Aparato did all this.
This is a location in Serbia.
Everything was built,
except the background.
The city in the background
was done by Aparato, in a very good way.
You can't see the chroma.
You can't see the blue screen at all.
-It feels like Detroit.
-Totally.
There is a section of Detroit
that looks exactly like this.
Yes, we stopped
on a street in Detroit...
For a public bathroom
in Detroit, the floor is pretty clean.
They swept it.
It's a family place.
-I really like this shot.
-This shot is great.
It was one of the first shots I saw
and said, "Good, they're making a movie."
They're filmmaking.
It looks nice on the big screen.
This is the shot
I like the most.
This is Rodo's shot.
I don't know why,
but I like it.
This is your shot,
you planned it, envisioned it.
We had the mirror made
with those dimensions.
And with the red wall behind,
because we thought, with great aspiration,
we thought later in the film
we would find out
the two of them were related
with blood ties that united them.
And the red line in the middle
which linked the two of them
seemed like fun to us.
This man is great.
It's like he's excited
to see his daughter for the first time.
Like he wants to hug her.
That finger is me.
Yes, Brendan is a great actor
and it was hard to play that role
because it has many different sides
and you can tell he was excited
to see her for the first time.
You okay?
The anamorphic lenses
they chose are amazing.
In the previous shot,
you can clearly see it on the left.
You can see the deformation.
Pedro, explain those lenses.
Why do they look all deformed?
Because it's a lens
that compresses the image laterally.
So, if you look closely,
out of focus they have an oval shape,
because what it does...
It's an old cinema invention.
It compresses the image laterally
so it fits into a small square
on the screen, and then it's stretched.
This looks great to me.
It was a very wise decision,
because it gives the whole movie
a feeling that this is not exactly
the real world,
that this takes place in the dimension
of dreams, of nightmares.
But it's something very dreamlike
which separates it from the real world
and allows the fable
to make more sense as well.
Of course.
That's the famous made-up world.
And it also allows us
to do what we want
where we create the things we want,
which stretches the credibility
of the real world.
It also gives it
a very "retro" feeling.
All the movies we loved
from the '80s and '90s,
they all used anamorphic lenses.
Something else caught my attention here.
I hadn't seen it in a while.
I remember when I saw it, I said,
"Wow, the sides are, like, tangled,
or circular."
It doesn't always happen
when they use long lenses,
it happens in some moments.
Incredible, the house of... What's his name?
-Dave Warren.
Dave Warren.
Look at the amount of detail for a set.
This is not a real house,
but there's so much detail.
I also liked that they kept details
from the first movie,
where you can see the wear in some walls
that he's slid his hand across many times.
Where you can see the wear in some walls
To guide himself.
Here you see the details
of the labels in Braille too.
The red labels in Braille.
And it's full of it.
There's one thing I noticed,
that I mentioned to Pedro at the time,
and I don't know if you noticed,
that all the paintings on the wall
are 3D paintings.
-Yes, incredible.
-3D paintings.
This shot was filmed
in the first movie, right? The open shot?
No, no.
At one point, we considered recycling
some shots from the first movie,
but we didn't do it.
They don't appear after all.
Here's our dear Hernandez.
She's out of focus.
I'm picking up the phone.
Who's there? Raul, Rocci.
This is the only road back to town.
Of course, she's military, too.
Everyone except Madelyn,
the character of Phoenix,
they're all ex-military.
It's a way to give realism
to this idea of who they are,
so capable with weapons and everything.
When you think of mercenaries
and things like that in movies,
it seems a bit fake to me.
But in the United States,
there are a lot of former soldiers,
young veterans.
Yes.
Sure, baby.
Whatever you want.
I like the story about how
this guy started barking in the back
and you didn't like it.
From my perspective
his bark seemed brutal.
A good example of how actors sometimes,
if they don't have many lines,
they look for ways
to make their character...
Contribute.
To catch your eye.
I think it's smart.
He also does it again later,
he barks again.
He found something there.
What's the name of the actor?
-Bobby.
-Bobby Schofield.
Or, as we called him, The Bobby.
-The Bobby.
The way this moment
was captured is very good,
because I felt like these two will have
an encounter later on.
That look tells you that they'll face off
by the end of the film,
and it ends up being much quicker.
Ooh! Of course.
This scene had its complications.
It was all practical effects.
That blood, it's real?
-It's all real.
-All real.
It was complicated.
It was not easy, because the truck
was moving and we wanted her to crash...
While still looking forward.
Looking forward while Jim-Bob
was hitting her with the hammer.
-That wasn't easy to do.
-But it was done.
That's Braille as well, right?
On the wall, on the bottom left.
Let's see, in her scene...
Yes, she wrote on her wall.
Instead of writing like a normal child,
she wrote with...
She wrote, "Daddy, I love you,"
so he could read it.
-It says that?
-It says, "Daddy, I love you."
How ironic. He's very good.
You have no idea what it is to be alone.
I think here's a phrase
that we added. It wasn't in the script.
He tells her he lost a daughter before.
Which makes me wonder,
what does she think about that?
Did she know her sister?
I suppose she thought
it was from a previous marriage,
from before she was born, obviously.
This shot is great too.
This was Juanjo, the cameraman.
He said, "What do you think..."
He's a Spaniard.
"If we finish with the mirror,
it'll look great." And I said, "Yes."
The shot is great.
And the isolation as well.
Of course.
She's alone in that tower.
She's, like,
trapped in the mirror.
And it's perfect to end the scene,
showing she's trapped in that place.
We built the tower
exactly for that purpose.
There's a lot of symbols in her room.
Another dog
in our dog-killing movies.
Doing what people love
to see in movies, dogs dying.
In Evil Dead they died...
They always die out of frame.
You can't kill a dog on camera.
There was a short flashback.
In the first Don't Breathe,
a dog dies, right?
The dog doesn't die.
That was to create
constant suspense in the movie,
whether it was going to die or not.
It was like John Wick where
they kill the dog and shit goes down.
This is our second one.
This shot is like an echo
of the first movie.
Totally. Totally.
When they show the house at night
in the other movie.
Who named the dog Shadow?
-That was him. It was Slang.
-Slang, right?
He had a dog named Shadow.
-Really?
-Yes.
He started early in the movie.
Was that in the script?
No. It wasn't in the script.
He always called him
by whistling or something.
Yes, but we hadn't named him.
Where are the boys?
-It looks amazing.
-Amazing.
This was built in two houses.
This is the set that was built
on location, in order to film exteriors.
But everything that is inside
is in the same house
that was built in a studio.
Incredible.
Also, very good construction.
It depends on the quality level
of the local builders.
-Look at the roof.
-It's incredible.
The roof,
the things, the plants.
It looks like that climbing plant
has been there for years.
And the size of the thing.
That's important.
-It was gigantic.
-And here we cut to the studio.
That was the exterior,
and this is in the studio.
And this is the famous shot.
They don't know he's blind
until this moment,
when they realize he can't see.
They thought it would be easier.
It would've been easier
to shoot him right there.
How would they know?
Once again,
it's what we said in the first movie,
where they have prejudices
towards a blind man who cares...
The Rubik's Cube is also Braille.
Yes.
I didn't know they existed.
We all thought that,
and then Phoenix says to the blind man,
"It looks perfect."
-Here comes that shot.
-Yes.
Here is the first cut.
Right. There is the cut.
Very well done. Impeccable.
Very well. Here it is.
In the first one
there is a similar moment.
The door opens,
they are looking at the cameraman.
Yes. This Is a classic trick
that is hard to miss.
Nobody thinks,
"The door opened there."
That's incredible, the dance
of the choreography between the camera.
People don't understand
the complexity of all this.
Everyone exactly in their place.
I mean, people don't understand
everything that can go wrong.
Every moment of this shot.
You can spend all day doing this.
This, I remember, was also
one of the first things in the script.
We found a scene that is not here.
Besides, at this moment we are back 100%
in the world of Don't Breathe.
Totally.
Here is Rocci, our favorite MMA fighter.
Is he as tall as he seems?
No, he is not as tall,
but he looks tough.
And he is strong.
-He left it all.
-Because he is a fighter.
-MMA fighter, yes.
-MMA, right.
He has several fights on YouTube.
-Has he made movies?
-Yes.
He was in White House Down, one of those.
With Jason Statham.
There is one on each side.
What do we do in that moment?
To be honest,
that is incredible.
-Bye, light.
-Oof.
The timing is great.
One very good thing, which looking at it
seems very good to me,
is the casting of all these guys.
These movies sometimes,
when there are the famous henchmen,
as they call it,
it could have potentially been
super generic
and all exactly the same,
and actually there is something,
they all have their personalities
and they have their details.
Yes, they are all different.
And they have
their particular way of moving
and their strengths are different.
Really good.
This is something
that came up here. We added that bit.
Yes, that was not there.
The plan was to go to the door there.
They are moving.
-No cut there? There could not be a cut?
-No.
Not there. Here either. This crossing.
Adam is one of the nicest
and sweetest persons
that exist in the world,
with a psychopathic face.
In the overalls.
He has his name there.
Yeah. JB. We always thought
he worked in a mechanic's shop,
So now every time he goes to do
a dirty job, he wears his overalls.
Did he have that haircut?
No, we gave it to him.
A lot of flat iron.
Lucky for the person
that is doing the captions for this,
the flat iron.
A lot of iron.
What is in those boxes
from the Blind Man?
The truth is
we don't have the answer to that.
No, I remember
that the first time
we had put all the things
that the man needed.
We had put all the things
He had lost his sight at a time
when he was quite old,
so there was a room that only had chairs
that he had taken out of the way.
In the first one there was
that room that was full of stuff, a TV.
A TV, obsolete things for him.
But this is a new house.
I don't know what he took there.
That moment is very...
And at the level of script,
the moment for people,
as the act of the dog playing dead comes,
there is some effect,
there must be something.
That is the real dog,
but the actor is touching it.
It's, like, paused.
He is not breathing...
His breathing is paused.
And this was always
in the script.
If there is something
that was going to make people
at least start to feel pity
for the blind guy,
it was going to be this moment, right?
Finding his dog, he discovers
that someone put a bullet in him.
A bullet.
Where did you get
the scar on the face?
Did you make it based on the first movie?
-Yes.
-Did they imagine it?
Well, they took pictures
from the first movie and...
I remember
that there was something,
I don't know if the contact lenses
were the same or...
Contacts from the same person,
the same person who did everything
took it and did it all again.
-Oh, it was the same person.
-Yes.
The house is very familiar.
A lot of people watch the movie
and think it's the same house.
The hall inside looks alike.
On the outside it doesn't look like
the house in the first movie.
This one looks
like a country house.
These Detroit houses
are all real houses.
It looks more country because
there is nothing else on the block.
Of course, but remember
the first one was square.
Thirty years ago,
that block was full of houses.
They started burning and falling apart,
and then Detroit gets the block back
and they cut the grass.
For those looking for the turkey baster.
Did it show up yet? It did.
Yes, it did.
The turkey baster
was on the wall in the back.
A good pause.
Before Jim-Bob shoots.
The infamous turkey baster.
You don't see it again.
Ouch. What a hit.
It was one of those things
when you think
you don't need the Blind Man,
now you beg for the Blind Man to come.
The propane was well placed there.
It's the shot
from the second unit.
"Go and make that shot."
And the gas there, it shows.
The first was the same.
We were constantly filming a unit
and sending the second unit to re-film,
to pick up details, close-ups,
and little things that are left behind.
The second unit always
owes something. This and that.
But they are indispensable.
You went and directed that unit,
and then you would let him do it
and then watch it after?
No. Sometimes I went.
Many times I went.
-To be close.
-Yes.
I went many times to see
what they were doing.
-Who played basketball there?
-Someone put it there.
It was a big argument.
What are we going to do
with the basketball hoop?
-Let's leave it.
-Leave it.
It was there before.
Probably the Blind Man
never noticed it was there.
Maybe Madelyn played.
We shall see.
The puzzle if this is on location...
This was on location after all, right?
The garage?
Can't remember.
It was all on location.
For example, the truck.
Who is driving?
I think the truck
wasn't his, either.
These things, as we said,
as the world of the Blind Man moves,
it seems to me that he did not
buy this house.
He didn't buy it.
I think someone who died
used to live in this house,
someone died of an overdose
living there and they used it
as one of those crack houses
and he took it and repaired it.
I don't think it was--
A lot of the things we see
on the wall there
don't belong to the Blind Man, I'm sure.
Because he didn't have so many things.
If those were all his things,
movers would have been involved
from the other house with all his things,
and he would have ran away
after the events from the first movie,
and he wouldn't have stayed there
for even two minutes.
The Blind Man is hiding there
in the truck, clearly.
He wants something else.
That is the brother.
It's hard to put things together.
Since they all call each other "brother,"
it seems they are all brothers.
My kids asked,
"Dad, is that really your brother?"
I say,
"No, that's what we call each other."
That was one of the first gags
that we thought of.
This one is so good.
He was going to
fill his face with...
It was difficult to film that,
because the guy couldn't breathe.
He was very uncomfortable.
Is that makeup?
It's makeup,
but he had to keep his mouth closed,
because if he opened it,
the illusion would fail.
That's me making the sound,
you can't hear it, but I went...
We recorded it like this in the consensus
that we had some sounds that worked.
They brought me a microphone
and I started to do it.
-My contribution.
-You did it like Mel Gibson.
They say he does that in the sessions.
In the audio mix sessions
and things like that.
I think this was in the first one, right?
I knew he was military.
Oh, what a moment.
His mouth was full of blood
because they put a hole in his cheek.
And his lip is cut--
a great challenge.
What's the need, God.
"Dead SEAL, bro."
Bro, I love this. "Bro."
Bobby added a lot
to that character.
We had to restrain him
because he was always adding things,
and we cut it a bit,
but what was left is great.
The Blind Man here...
is thinking about his next move.
Does he know that she is in the box?
Yes, he yelled at the box.
Well, I think he trusts that
she reached the box, but he isn't sure.
Phoenix is very well-trained.
He trusts that he trained
her well and that she has arrived.
Especially if he hears noises
in the house still.
They're in the house because
they haven't found her yet, right?
If not, they would have already left.
But this is also
one of the first times in the saga
that you see him vulnerable, in trouble,
thinking about what he's going to do.
Of course. It was like the shark
was there. He didn't know where he was.
It appears and disappears
in general,
but this is the first time
we started to see it.
Only a little bit, because there are
very few windows the film gives you
to see what is happening with him.
I love this shot, there it is.
That shot from The Shining.
That shot from The Shining
always needs to be there.
Especially if you have an actor
with that look, you have to do it.
Place the camera down there.
When you know
where the movie is going,
I think they knew as well--
They knew he was not going to kill her.
He has to take her. He's trying.
He is trying to make her get out,
like smoking a beehive.
He is pushing her.
This is where the accent
pops out. What is that accent? Irish?
-British.
Alvacast there
breaking everything.
Very good records.
Alvacast,
for those who don't know,
is a Uruguayan heavy metal band.
From the '80s, early '90s.
But why Alvacast?
The Uruguayan element amused you more?
Well, because we wanted
to put a patch
with a half motorcycle logo
on this guy's back,
and we thought, "Let's do
something Uruguayan that looks cute."
And the truth is
that Alvacast's typography is great.
It's great. It looks very good
and it also meant something
because I also moved a lot
in that metal scene of those times,
so it was good.
Yes, and they are also
one of those pioneering bands
at a time when no one did that,
that is something admirable.
Do you remember that he also
wore that shirt in Spider's Web?
I love the "no gun" concept moment.
If the guy shoots
and blows up the whole place,
then he has no choice
than to hit the shovels.
I love that, it was his idea,
what Stephen did,
-entering with his hand like asking...
-Almost apologizing.
Apologizing,
as if asking for peace, with fear.
It's like he's hiding the...
Yes, but he has a club
in the other hand.
When he steps on the cap,
was that his idea?
Could be.
That fight is brutal.
It took days of filming.
We filmed parts and the second unit.
Yes.
It's one of those things
in post-production,
a shame that people
are left without listening
to one of the music queues
that were better
than those that Roque did for this fight.
He made a brutal composition
with flamenco stomping,
with orchestra and everything,
it was amazing.
But then we realized, at some point,
that without music
it was rawer and had more tension,
and in post-production,
we ended up taking it out.
The truth is the fight is very good, raw,
you hear every little noise
of the knife, the hand.
Now, when he grabs his fingers,
you hear the fingers breaking.
-And there you have it.
-They are not faking it.
No, they fought hard, for real.
Besides, Rocci is a fighter,
and Stephen Lang is like a method actor,
he goes all out.
Yes, you can tell
that these two...
I remember
when they were done filming this,
Stephen Lang, who likes to brag
about his physical strength,
when they finished, he said,
"Rodo, this guy is tough, for real."
He is a professional fighter.
Poor Phoenix
in the box full of water.
It made sense
because water was always the idea
and the logic is that water pressure
doesn't let the door open.
There is going to be
so much outward pressure
that it doesn't allow her
to open the door.
I remember reading
after we had written all this,
that in real life
that cable won't kill you.
That the water has to be very salty
for it to transmit electricity
in a way that kills you.
Oh, I see.
But it makes you feel
a little bad, maybe.
Probably...
But in the movie, you see it
and they are going to touch the cable.
We had our Hollywood moment here.
It was a real explosion.
-With real fire.
-We did it for real.
With real fire, total wild card.
Christian Zagia.
-Stellar appearance.
-Uruguayan actor.
About to make his entrance in the movie.
How is the basement not on fire?
Maybe the Blind Man painted the walls
with fire-resistant stuff.
Oh, no, Phoenix is dying.
Go, man!
We have to recognize
Stephen Lang,
who crawled on that basement floor
for a week, nonstop.
-Nonstop and giving ideas.
-Yes.
How does he have
the strength to throw that box?
And to move
the boxes full of water.
Yes, that weighs three tons.
This guy has superpowers.
Look what he does.
Against the wall,
he for sure can.
-There he goes back to the movie.
-Go on, go on.
Here he is opening...
Breathe.
You said the other day
that this line was not there,
when he says, "Breathe."
-It wasn't in the script.
-It wasn't in the original script.
A journalist talking about
the movie found it interesting
that he said "breathe" so many times...
for a movie called Don't Breathe.
You saw that painting there on the wall,
the painting that is there,
the squares are in 3D
so that the blind can touch them
and appreciate the art.
This moment is great, and it's all makeup.
-All makeup.
The eyes as well?
I think there is a bit
of post-production in the eyes
to make them red, but it's 99% makeup.
Like ten hours in the chair.
They made, like, a prosthesis,
too. A long time.
For one take,
the things that are done.
Cover the exits.
Incredible that the bad guy
really comes back into story.
I don't know
what he was doing all this time.
He was taking care of the bridge there.
We asked him what he was doing.
He didn't want to get his hands dirty,
and he probably thought,
“I'm going to buy something
and you guys go find the little girl
and we'll see you at home."
Because he thought
it was going to be that easy, right?
Clearly, he realized that it was not.
They're still down here.
There is no flare in the movie.
There are no lenses there.
Yes, there is a little bit
of anamorphic flare.
But there's not a huge flare.
It's not a big deal,
but there is some.
Yeah.
There it is.
Good.
It looks like the same door
from the first one, but--
Yes. All those...
This is something that always
got me very excited about the script.
That it tells you more
about the blind guy's life,
what he does, the idea that
there would be half a house.
I remember they were talking about this,
that there's a section
of the greenhouse he uses,
and then the other is neglected
and all overgrown.
I remember he said it was
like a representation of the character.
There is a part of himself that he
can control, and another out of control.
Luque) Yeah.
The Blind Man has to deal with life.
Here he's entering the part
that is all overgrown.
He hits like an I, right?
Yes, he goes behind the house,
the part totally out of control.
It's not me you need to be scared of...
This greenhouse is also set in a studio.
The character's clothes
look nice, too.
-'80s style.
-Yeah.
That's Carlos Rosario,
our costume designer,
who also worked on the first one,
and he always likes to spice up
the characters, not leave them plain.
-It's a gender issue, right?
-Yeah.
I feel it enhances them,
gives them certain importance.
It removes the generic quality.
Luque) Yeah.
No!
But the blind guy
looks almost the same.
The blind guy has to be iconic.
It's like his uniform.
Yeah, the military pants
and the muscle shirt.
This scene is amazing.
You really don't remember me,
do you?
He kneels down to her height.
This is so good.
What would the audience think here?
How many people already knew?
Surely they didn't know
how things would unfold, right?
But imagine what that was like for her,
thinking about her mother all the time,
and suddenly this shows up.
This is in a studio, you said?
Yes, it's all set in a studio.
So no sunlight, but studio
lights gleaming through the glass.
Yes, it's all based on street lights, the lights from the house...
that always create these two tones
which were also present
in part one, right?
We go back to that opening
scene in which he finds her in the street.
Ashes from the house fire
are still falling down.
A terrible fire.
I think this is the only time
during the saga you may see him home,
at daylight, a nicely lit scene.
-Yeah.
-With a hopeful feeling.
Here he's choosing to stay
there and be this girl's father,
when he hears on the news
where she really came from.
And here it's when Raylan
runs into her, finds her.
I like it when these mystery
movies show you a flashback
that gives a new meaning to what
you already saw and adds a new piece
for you to keep building up the story.
Most movies would use it like
-a climax scene, in the last 20 minutes.
-Yes.
The good thing about
this movie, Don't Breathe,
is you do nothing in the first 45 minutes.
We're here and we have 45 minutes left
with twists and turning points.
With twists.
Doing this was fun.
This reminds me of RoboCop.
Yes. A bit of RoboCop
and Predator, too.
Predator.
Speaking of the jungle.
And the Vulcan spinning,
chopping down trees.
Take her to the truck
while I hunt this motherfucker.
So good, this set.
The wood turned out great.
Yes.
In part one, the blind guy
also had his plants, his indoor growth.
It's the small one,
you can barely notice it.
Most people miss it.
They won't understand it.
Thing is, in part one, entering
the basement means something else.
I find it amusing
how this scene turned out,
especially thanks to Bobby.
I find his physical performance amazing.
Yes.
It's scary, this guy
totally out of control, with a crazy face.
I feel that even knowing he can't
hurt her now, he'll slap her anyways
-for sure.
-He can't help himself.
See.
It seems like he grabbed her.
Luque) Yeah.
Oh, this is a great scene.
Bobby's face...
Everything is quite complex,
there's a lot of...
of prosthetics, right?
Oh, also this scene
with that shovel.
That shovel!
That shovel is super heavy.
We could not find any.
-We had to ask for it to be made.
-Yes.
Amazing, that scene.
Another great moment
is watching the shots
and watching that head tilt. Amazing.
The guy is drooling.
The idea here in the script is
that Phoenix would see him
for what he really was,
that she'd see this violent nature of his
that obviously she'd never seen before.
He had a monster inside
that finally came out.
It was provoked and it came out.
And here's Jim-Bob
seeing that his brother has died.
-What a scene...
-A lot of repression.
Look at his face there, God.
He looks like
a Francis Bacon painting.
For God's sake.
You always want these
characters to take this personally.
It's known here there's a fight
coming, like in every classic action film
from the '80s and the '90s,
whenever one of the brothers gets killed--
Well, you know.
In Die Hard, he was killed...
Enough of these silly games.
All these emotions, nicely done.
Yes, it's great.
It's also important being able
to connect, at least, with these guys.
Even if they're the bad guys.
Interestingly,
the dynamic between them changed.
He's dragging her.
He's the monster he's always been.
-And she is starting to notice it.
-And she's like...
You never thought of using
that weapon in the opening long shot?
Showing there was a weapon there?
I can't remember
if we thought of it or not.
That came in late.
You called me at some point
and told me we had to plant a gun
for the Blind Man.
I don't know if this was something
Slang said, or someone else...
who said he wanted--
He needed to bring his own weapon.
Thing is, this gun shows up
at the beginning, when they're training.
The gun is in the beginning.
People say, "One dog was killed
already. Please don't kill two."
This dog was mean, this pit bull.
It was?
There was a good one
and a bad one.
There's always a good one
And you had a doll too.
We had a doll, actually.
Pedro and I acted like puppet masters.
Where is it?
Did you bring that doll?
It must be with the guy
who made it, quite a big shot.
Yes.
Those are expensive, and they
can be used later for something else.
That doll was nicely done.
Very nice, yeah.
The difference in part one,
remember, is we had
a stuffed dog we bought at some gift shop.
And this is Phoenix's stunt?
Yes, this is...
-Dunja.
-What's that?
-That was on a set?
-No, on location.
This is in the studio.
For short shots.
See the background.
And this is on location.
It was raining.
You can see the raindrops there.
That was a tricky day,
5:00 in the morning and raining.
This is a different set.
Rain would flood that house.
This is the doll.
That's me.
Sometimes it's me
and sometimes the real dog.
You were acting
as puppet master.
At some points I did, I liked it.
Look here, there's a scene
where we act as puppet masters.
Let's see, that one there. That one, yes.
It works fine.
You have to take it seriously,
as funny as it might be.
It would never cross your mind
that what you're seeing,
the back of the dog's head,
is fake, it's a doll.
The back of the dog's head,
Such a great scene, this one.
When he decides, "I can't kill him, dude."
-"Enough dogs have died today."
-I remember talking to him--
We realized while shooting this scene
that what was at stake
for the character wasn't his life,
because the dog wouldn't kill him.
He had a gun.
He could easily kill the dog.
It was his honor at stake.
He was going to break his moral code.
So, he may be a monster and all,
but at least
on a certain level,
if there's something he loves,
it's animals, he's a dog lover.
Sure.
Phoenix!
Well, he took her.
He listens. He's got a fine ear.
For Raul,
this is his first scene,
and then you realize he's not a bad guy.
He does it carefully, with compassion.
I loved that in the script,
the way in which he was going to cross
to the other side and leave the dog caged.
That metal frame
was really heavy,
remember, super heavy,
and Slang lifted it like it was nothing.
It was something
totally custom made,
because such a thing didn't exist.
It was something we had in mind,
but it didn't have an equivalent
in real life.
Raylan.
They had this all planned out, I think.
Where's the cooler?
Didn't they carry organs?
That was a magic trick.
Of course, at the beginning
after the ad, you could see that cooler...
and that was another step forward
in the arc.
What are you doing?
Have you gone crazy? Your dog is in there.
A great thing here,
is we just saw that
there's a difference between them.
The blind guy couldn't kill the dog,
even though it was not his,
but this guy, being its owner,
does not care.
So they have quite different moral codes.
With the script,
we also wanted to raise the topic of...
fatherhood, and who has--
Whether or not you are entitled
to your children's love,
in a story about this guy, the blind guy,
who loves her
like she was his own daughter
and takes care of her,
despite being such a monster.
Takes better care of her as a father
than the other one,
who is her real father,
but willing to kill her for his reasons.
It was a question about who deserves
the affection of these children.
So this guy with a dog,
the story with the dog also represented
this same question.
In a certain way, the dog's father,
who was Raylan,
wouldn't hesitate to kill him,
so the blind guy ends up being
a better father for that dog.
At least he takes care of him
and eventually earns the dog's affection.
-Yes. It's the same thing.
-And he'll save him.
Here, fire is destroying the house,
and he risks himself to set the dog free.
He risks his own life
to save this dog.
We'll have to investigate
in another Don't Breathe story,
when there are more movies,
what happened to him.
Surely a dog saved his life at some point.
-Yes.
-Sure, in war or somewhere.
There must be a past story
that made him love animals so much.
Maybe through the loneliness
this character experienced
when he lost his daughter,
maybe the dog helped him through it.
The dog saved him, in a way.
That was a fantastic job
from the stuntmen
who jumped head first like that,
just like you saw it.
Another reference to part one.
But the other way around.
It's his turn now to be up there.
-And much worse.
-Yes.
With fire underneath.
He then remembered Alex
from the first movie, and was like, "Oh."
But well, he was lucky enough
to fall on top of that.
This shot must be
the most epic shot in the whole movie
because all the fire,
or most of it, is real.
-It's real.
-So it was very time-consuming
and all the Belgrade firemen were there,
and everything was set up
for Stephen Lang to do this...
with the house actually on fire.
Remember we struggled
to put that fire out?
Yes, yes.
You also set
the real set on fire, right?
-Yes.
-It was useless.
Useless. It had windows
with bars that were on fire.
What I'd like to know
is if those were called flame bars.
No, look what it was.
Well, it was like that, but much larger
and also the house caught on fire
in two minutes.
Of course, that's madness.
In Detroit.
It's the third time
we've burned a house for our movies.
Yeah, I have a lot of experience
with burning houses.
The cabin caught fire.
The Girl in the Spider's Web
also ended with a burning house.
That huge hotel, remember?
We should've set
this one on fire.
This is Detroit, right?
-Well, the exterior is.
-Yeah, the exterior.
-This is...
-Close to the Latin Quarter.
This is Serbia.
Yes, it's Serbia.
Yes, it's a small town
called Arandelovac.
Arandelovac.
I saw that fish tank and said,
"Wow, that must explode."
Like every '90s movie,
if there's a fish tank...
Those always explode
in slow motion.
Showing a fish in the back
gasping for its last breath.
Yes.
This scene was longer.
We censored the original scene
in which Raylan showed her how to smoke.
This image is amazing.
I thought it was great,
because I felt it was
a good way of representing
the idea of, if you were thinking
that it wasn't that bad
that Raylan had taken her,
the worst scenario is bad parenting,
but you see he's showing her how to smoke
in the first scene. Off to a bad start!
Off to a bad start.
-But we did shoot it, right?
-We did.
The scene ended up being too long
and it didn't get to the point.
The key is always to enter a scene
close to the point you need to make clear.
Also I think the rating would
have killed us, we'd become NC-17.
Yes, it was sort of troublesome.
Although, in Stand By Me,
there is a boy smoking.
Those times were different.
People smoked inside a hospital.
What was my mother's name?
I love how this scene turned
out, how the shots get narrowed.
She starts asking
increasingly intimate questions,
more relevant for her.
There's some sort of intimacy here.
I really like...
the way we shot from the sides.
Yes, more and more closed.
He touches her,
she lets him touch her,
like she's falling under his spell.
She's falling into the spiderweb.
Remember what we said?
Everything that man told you is a lie.
What happened to him?
Yes, it scares me to think where
the spider might be, it will show up soon
but it's around somewhere.
Hanging from the ceiling.
See the excess of ramps in this room.
That's why it's there now.
Jesus.
We knew exactly what we were writing
up to this point.
From here on is
when we had a bunch of alternatives.
It always started here. I think the first
version was the one with the heart,
and everything
that's going to happen next.
Then we moved on
to two alternative versions
and then we went back to the one
with the heart, that was great.
And for the ones with a great memory,
those who remember that "wanted" face,
his face is on TV, on the news about...
Organ trafficking.
-Organ trafficking, right?
-There's a man.
That's the gang of bad guys
who are really bad.
But they were nice people.
With their criminal records.
Genius. I think this moment is...
Here's where everything goes away.
An iconic scene of this saga.
It's like you convince yourself
her mother is dead,
but you don't realize the whole story
is a lie from the blind guy.
Until now.
She looks like Elvira.
The one from The Addams Family.
The mother's good.
Who's the actress?
Fiona. She's amazing.
She spent just one week
doing the few scenes she had,
but the truth is
something unbelievable happened,
that didn't happen before during filming.
Every time she was on set
and every time she performed,
there was a deathly silence
because everyone was mesmerized by her.
-Everyone stared at the monitor.
-It was amazing.
Her presence was magnetic.
I had seen her in a series,
Utopia, a very good English series.
They've been trying to make
the American version for a long time.
I remember watching all the chapters
of the English version at one point
and she was so good there.
Here, she's perfect. She's amazing.
This shot is also very good.
The work with the light,
how she gradually appears.
You can't see her face up to that point.
This for me is the scariest moment
of the whole movie.
Yes! It's the scariest moment.
Maybe because
I know what's next.
If you don't know what's next, you can't...
But it's clear that this woman
won't bring anything good to the story.
Normally this would've--
In any other movie,
this scene would've been
a scene of reunion and hope.
She was reunited with her mother.
Heidi there with the mother...
And you know from the way it's filmed
that clearly nothing good is going to
come out of this union. Brilliant.
Now, what nerve the mother has
to pull all these theatrics.
She's genuinely excited.
No, she's totally excited.
She appreciates her own life
more than her daughter's,
but she is excited.
I think she's more excited
to see hope that she will live...
Right, selfishness.
Yes, total selfishness.
We also talked about...
She also hugs her lovingly! Scary.
-She hugs her inside her heart.
-All those lies.
We talked with Fiona.
Like the Blind Man
crying over Cindy's murder
in the first one, but he actually cries
because of what's inside her, the kid.
What we talked about with Fiona
is that either way,
she's her biological daughter,
from her womb,
as we see in the photo,
so she's moved somehow.
Perhaps when she planned all this,
she didn't consider
that when she saw her in person,
she was going to be moved, so it makes her
more insane and conflicted,
and she has to go even more crazy
to be able to continue with the plan.
Yes, she has to delve into...
That's why at this moment
she starts coughing up the blood.
She reminds herself that, well...
She has no other choice.
This couple, for me,
is one that--
On Halloween,
I want to dress up like them.
Bonnie and Clyde.
Everything goes wrong.
No, because I really believe
the love between the two of them.
There is no doubt that they are in love.
They make a great couple on screen,
very good.
Yes.
He'll do anything for her.
He's madly in love with her.
He's a prisoner of the spell,
too.
-Right.
-He's a follower. She's the emperor.
Exactly.
She's the one
that really carries out all of this,
since everyone does what they do for her
because the others will say it too.
She is the cook...
She's the one who cooks
the product that leaves them...
-Everyone is dominated by her.
-Yes.
And like we were saying,
she behaves like a spider here.
She's going to get on her feet
and start getting close to her.
Completely a spider.
A lady spider
that makes its prey sleep.
The smoke from the chemicals...
Also, the animal print in the back
that Carlos brought...
A lot of texture.
Yes, yes,
the underwear is spider-like.
It seems furry.
Yes.
Little by little
we begin to reveal that there's...
a surgery room behind them.
I can't imagine
what the audience is thinking...
since they don't know
what we know when we watch this,
where this is headed
and what the mother will propose.
This is difficult for her.
She's about to cry.
It's something that affects her.
And the truth is
that her performance is great.
-It's amazing.
-It's great.
-She was completely into it.
-Yes, 100%.
She was on the edge and there...
Doctor said it has to be a...
It must be...
She's great.
...a compatible donor.
And it was also a comment from us,
as the first one had
a lot of social commentary
on the subject of weapons,
and that, if they invade your home,
if you have the right to kill or not
just because someone came in to steal.
You remember?
With this, we also used
a bit of social commentary
in that the most helpless people,
like Raylan and his wife,
if they need an organ transplant,
they will never get it.
It's true.
We read a lot,
we did research on it
and if people with few resources
need a heart transplant
or something very big like that,
they go to the bottom of the list,
obviously.
We'll finally be together...
So, we knew that madness
was justified in their heads
and that they knew that
never by right, never by law,
would they get what they needed.
I don't know about the real world,
but in the world of Don't Breathe,
it's totally impossible to get an organ
for a transplant.
I loved that light.
Suddenly, there's a flair, almost like
the light of hope is turned on.
That's the idea.
Is he dead? No.
Is that the location
or another one?
It's the house next door.
We did a repurpose of the house next door.
It was rebuilt and made...
True, because
the neighbor's house was burned down.
Yes. It was made in a similar
shape to the house we already had.
We changed the mailbox. Those things...
We had to set the mailbox
and automatically...
-The greenhouse, too.
-Yes.
The greenhouse
was built next to it.
A great moment is when he
almost thanks the dog for saving his life,
and the dog is just there...
From here on, the dog
becomes like the comic relief.
That's true.
The story's funny part
is the dog and their relationship.
All the moments with the dog are funny.
That moon that was just seen there
was real, right?
It was real. That moon was there.
And as if this poor man didn't
suffer enough punishment in this movie,
now he comes to find out
that his only friend
is dead and it's because of him.
Well, it's one of the moments
that starts to build his arc,
that will make him see what he sees
in the last scene,
that the monster in this movie is him,
because she...
Hernandez was an innocent being
who pays for his crimes.
If he hadn't taken Phoenix,
Hernandez wouldn't have died.
You always feel very sorry
when you see someone
who clearly doesn't show
that much affection,
but he clearly loved her
more than one can imagine.
With this story,
I think he begins to see who he is
and the damage he's causing.
Also, one of the great ideas--
I don't know where they came from,
but we came up with how to make
the Blind Man find the house.
Because at that time, two minutes before,
you'd think there's no way
that he will find that hotel.
This was your idea.
I remember at one point,
we were stuck with how he would find it,
and you came up with the idea that
if you tell the dog to go home, he will.
He will.
Luckily, they lived in the same state.
They were nearby.
You get it from the fact
that Raylan was in his mother's house
that we know is not very far from there,
and that they're all there.
And if he was looking for Phoenix,
he was doing so in the neighborhood
near that place.
It was logical to expect
that their location wasn't very far.
Well, here begins the shot
of total madness.
It feels like another movie.
That dropper shot
was the last one filmed.
-It's true.
-In the whole movie?
-Yes.
-A highly glorious shot.
The dropper shot.
That's when we realized
that the dropper was missing!
My God. This is terrifying, too.
I hope you understand
the high risks of this procedure.
He's great.
This actor has
a lot of experience in theater and cinema,
all in England...
Great actor. He came to play a small role,
but the truth is that he crushed it.
Another example
of invisible special effects.
This had been filmed differently,
and at one point,
we decided that, for realism,
it would be great
if they wore medical clothes,
because they were in,
like, more civilian clothes.
-The girls?
-Yes. Both.
The hospital clothes they're wearing
were added in post-production.
-That's amazing, really.
-Amazing.
Not just the clothes were added.
I think the mother's feet...
the mother's arms
and feet were too, I think.
The feet, not the arms.
The feet.
Look at that texture.
So good, yes.
Here we have the fellas, waiting...
There's Raul,
the one who's going to have his--
His story is really well told.
Honestly, you...
you believe him
when he takes that turn in the end.
He gets the credit
for these minimal scenes.
Basically, Raul can't believe it.
They weren't told
what would happen.
Not exactly.
No, they were told
that it was important
to save her, to go get Phoenix.
But they were never told
what would happen to her.
Still fucking wrong.
The feet are CG, I think.
-Right.
-All the clothes are CG.
And if you look
at the mother's legs,
they're a bit gangrenous
because she doesn't use them that much.
-Right.
-They're kind of rotten.
This movie
and the previous one, 100,
are so rich in detail...
in those kinds of details.
And it's something that's fun to do,
and it takes thinking about it,
getting yourself thinking about the story.
That's also what
making a movie is about,
is to think about all those little things.
And it also comes naturally because
every question they ask you
about how we do this here,
what we put here, what the closure's like,
and you pay attention to small details
that end up building up to what it's like.
Yes, as long as
you always focus on the story,
you don't have to look for answers.
When there is a good team,
each department
is thinking about all those details.
-That's true.
-They're thinking about
what to do regarding the clothing
to tell the story,
the art of the house to tell the story.
That's the pleasure
of working at this level in these films,
in which everyone, the team leaders,
are top-notch people
-who help a lot to tell the story.
-Yes.
Well...
-Ugh.
-Those rats are real.
This is a set
built in the studio.
Yes.
Great. I don't know.
Were there initial plans to build this?
No. All of this came up
in the process and thank God...
And when we went scouting,
we really visited
sinister locations, right?
Yes, from other movies
in those sinister locations.
Luckily, this time
we didn't have to visit those.
Here, Jim-Bob has to...
get it together.
Originally...
in the first conception of the film,
at the script level,
we thought that, from here on,
the entire third act
was going to be filmed with the mode--
With the kind of night vision
that we invented in the first film.
And that all this was going to be,
like, in total darkness.
We said, "Well, it's a moonless night
and it's going to be total darkness."
That was the original concept.
Honestly, this is better because it looks
more interesting, of course,
and for now, he doesn't need it.
-No.
-He doesn't need the dark,
but then the idea came up of what comes
afterwards, the cans and the smoke.
The epic red smoke.
Oof! He swallows the bell.
The bells
that were in Hernandez's car.
What does he say when he kills him
in the final version?
For Hernandez or for the dog?
For the dog.
That day
he didn't say anything, right?
No.
In post-production,
we decided he had to kill...
This shot of the fall is epic.
That, when he Kills him,
he tells him the reason why.
I think that in post-production,
we first put, "This is for Hernandez."
Then, the studio, I think
out of their few notes seeing this--
-Do you remember?
-Yes.
We wondered
if they'd give us freedom.
The only note that the studio had was,
“It's great, but it'd be better
if when he Kills him,
he says, 'This is for my dog.
-"For the Shadow."
-"This is for Shadow."
And I think the note was very good.
"This is for Shadow."
Here, he hits the floor
next to him with a hammer.
-Yes.
-This shot was very dangerous.
He'd hit it so hard,
I was afraid the hammer would break.
-And Bobby was so scared.
-No, Adam.
Adam was so scared
that he'd break his head.
This guy was wearing his contact lenses.
He could barely see.
He couldn't see.
That day was intense.
-That day was...
-Intense.
-Adam was left broken.
-Yes.
Later, he was filming
with the second unit...
-Yes.
-And in that part...
Isn't he a dancer?
-He's a dancer.
-Yes.
-Well, he had the agility.
-But he was left broken.
He was psychologically compromised
for a few days.
Yes, compromised and exhausted.
-Really?
-Yes.
During all that fight, the whole day
of filming was very intense for them.
Those post-production clothes, amazing.
They're so good.
I think maybe I won't wear anything
for the next movie.
All in post-production.
So good.
-The set looks so nice.
-He's Gary Oldman now.
Yes.
This one was also brave
because there is no light, supposedly.
Although, now in the story,
in the internal story clock,
it's beginning to... to clear up.
Yes. It could be street lights.
But as they say, the light comes
from the same place as music.
Exactly. But, well,
here the idea was a bit
to establish this same set
in a different way.
Raul and the new henchmen
that appeared.
Yes. His friends.
Yes. Great shot.
When did you decide to make it all blue?
I'm not sure.
We were talking about it.
I can't remember exactly.
For me, it was a bit...
It was natural because
the hole above this basement,
in the fantasy, it's like an air hole
that's between the buildings.
The light got there
from this dawn gloom.
Of dawn. This is awesome, though.
It was a way of depicting
how to use even more senses.
-Yes.
-Now, touch.
He used smell in the first one.
He'd smell the shoes.
Yes.
Obviously,
he uses hearing all the time.
We have to create a way
for him to use taste.
I don't know how.
And here,
Raul's arc is completed.
Here,
the Blind Man could have died.
-He could've killed him, yes.
-Almost killed.
But Raylan made a mistake
that was to cross the moral line and...
that's not cool with Raul.
You'd better hurry.
Act cool, Raul.
That was
a great missed opportunity
when he says, "That's not cool with me."
He should've said,
"That's not cool with Raul."
-Raul here... great.
-Here, he makes sure that
he's loosening up now,
because he was also convinced
that the machete would fly into his head.
Here, we get into
the epic scene of the movie.
This was the biggest scene.
Actually, it was the most demanding scene.
Tito's pool.
Marshal Tito's pool.
Yes, that was the palace,
one of the palaces used by the generals.
That location was--
It was one of the houses, right?
One of the houses in Serbia and...
Belgrade. That was the house of...
There was more than
one pool in that house, right?
-Yes.
-It had an outdoor pool.
But that pool was an indoor one.
This pool,
it seems that it never worked well.
-Really?
-Apparently, it always had leaks.
Look at the depth of that, wow.
-Yes, it's amazing.
-It's not real.
Right.
It was enlarged
in post-production.
It's a big scene
with lots of things happening.
I think it took us
like a whole week to film.
A week and a half.
-Yes.
-It was very complicated.
It's normal.
The good climaxes of any movie
have to take up 25% of the shooting time.
Well, the lighting setup
is also very complex.
It took days to put that together.
Right,
it was a physical location.
-You had real lights outside.
-Yes.
We had to cover up all of this
with a big tent. It was raining.
Right, I was going to ask
what would happen if it rained.
Yes. It was raining hard outside
and we had to put up a big tent.
The grips there saved the day.
I remember we tried
so many different colors for this part.
This was such a great find.
We made it dark without it being dark.
It was daytime
and they were all in the same condition.
With all the smoke,
you couldn't see anything.
It has a samurai movie vibe.
Some parts seem as if they were taken
from a Kurosawa movie.
You have knives,
contrast, and it's all red.
It's exasperating, right?
Not knowing where it can come from.
Absolutely.
It feels like one of those movies,
of a samurai fight in the fog.
The knives.
Yes, a bladed weapon.
Zatoichi.
This part replicates the first one.
Where the Blind Man kills Cindy.
He kills a loved one.
Unintentionally, he kills someone
he was trying to protect.
The consequences of such violence.
"NO!"
Of course, when he screams,
he reveals his position
and that's when he attacks.
But Raylan is furious now.
Luque) He is.
He now has
the strength he needs.
This drives me crazy.
All this was so hard to shoot.
-So hard.
-Yes.
Each shoot has its own thing.
This is metaphorically
the cutting of the umbilical cord.
The bond with her mother.
Since the beginning,
you see there's something
that won't let her move on.
That's right.
Her mom. Who she is.
But her mother
wasn't what we all expected.
She needs to let her go.
-Ah.
-God.
Phoenix!
She falls anyway.
She falls, but it saves her.
Who comes in?
Was that a puppet?
There's one.
There's a real dog attacking its trainer
and here's a puppet, a rubber dog,
that he throws out the window.
There's a broken fake arm,
there's the head biting the arm, too.
This also demanded
a lot of second unit work.
What's funny about
this phrase you'll hear now,
"Now you're gonna see what I see,”
wasn't in the first movie,
but was invented
by Sony's marketing department
for the trailer.
And the people liked it so much that--
There comes the pudding...
This part was complicated, too.
There's digital compositing there--
The tricky thing
was putting the eyes back on.
Melting them was easy.
There's digital compositing there.
There's a silicone head
with that pus inside, and it bleeds.
The eye juice.
Poor Phoenix.
She's alive at least.
He hears her.
Stop.
Stop!
You...
You mustn't come near me.
The good news is
the Blind Man finally saw.
At the last moment,
he stopped being morally blind at least.
True.
I think he realizes who he is
when he leaves the house
and finds Hernandez dead,
that's when he has the revelation.
The only reason he went there
is to tell Phoenix what he feels.
To tell her the truth about himself.
And he's punished for it.
-He pays the maximum price.
-The ultimate price.
His own life.
Not only does he pay
by losing her,
because she won't stay in his life,
but he also pays with his life,
for having stayed there.
He also went there
to set her free
so that she won't come back
and try to find him.
He wants her to know who he really is
and what he has done.
He's pushing her away.
He hopes she can move on with her life.
It's really hard for her.
Stephen Lang is brilliant in this scene.
-He is.
-He was made for this scene.
Go!
In addition to
all the technicalities it required,
it had this super special moment.
We spent most of the time
shooting the action scenes,
but not the final monologue.
Just a few days.
That's what happened.
We did a good job.
We took the time
that was needed.
He came prepared
and nailed it on the first try.
True.
If the hand had rested
a bit longer on his shoulder,
you'd have thought it was Phoenix
telling him, "It's okay."
-Yes. But no.
-But no.
The Blind Man doesn't fight back.
-He's given up.
-He's ready to die.
That's all.
He believed
what he had said to her.
Saying goodbye to her was like dying.
And by staying there, that's what he got.
He got stabbed in the back.
Yes.
That's all for him.
So Shakespearean.
Totally. And she came back.
These two are...
The loss of his eyes,
it's all a Greek tragedy.
But they are together.
Together in death.
It's crazy.
And now comes the famous scene.
You can't end without one.
You have to do it
at some point.
Leonardo continues
to influence us.
This whole moment is
about feeling sorry for the wounded.
-It's about mercy.
-Yes.
One of the best decisions for me,
completely counterintuitive but incredible
that made this moment
very rare and special,
that suited this character perfectly,
is that in any other movie,
there would be music.
There would be music in the background
that would make you sad about his death.
But we consciously decided,
for all the crimes he committed,
he doesn't deserve any music.
-Nothing.
-Not even a trumpet.
Nothing at all.
So we removed it in post-production.
And it created
a very demeaning atmosphere.
We wanted him to die like a dog.
He didn't deserve any recognition.
-That's what we tried to express.
-Right.
That's what we tried to convey.
But she can't help feeling sorry for him.
That's what any kid her age would do
in her situation.
She can't change what she feels,
which is why this ending
is like a tragedy.
She's also heartbroken.
Finding out must be really hard.
It's tragic for her,
for the audience,
who might have expected
a more painful punishment.
But I think what we did here
is more relatable.
If he'd received the perfect punishment,
it wouldn't feel real.
It would be too Hollywood.
And here...
the texture and the light change a bit,
like the world changed.
-And this is Detroit again?
-This is Detroit again.
A new dawn
in the life of Phoenix.
The lighting
was quite expressionistic.
But it fits perfectly.
Now she's accepted, she's free.
She hasn't accepted her past.
But she's accepted that she's free
to choose who she wants to be.
She's now in control of her life.
-At the end of the story.
-Yes.
And she accepts the name, Phoenix,
which he gave to her.
I don't know if it has to do
with her relationship to her father.
We don't know yet how she feels
about that relationship.
Not just yet, but what we do know now
is she's in complete control of her life.
She has taken control
and she knows everything now.
She can now have a better life.
So, this is it. The Spanish commentary
for the movie Don't Breathe 2.
That was our movie.
I hope you have enjoyed
our anecdotes and commentaries.
See you soon
for Don't Breathe 3.
See you.