Hello, everyone. My name is Rodo Sayagues.
I am the co-writer and director
of this movie
that we're about to see together.
This is a...
Logos and more logos
of all our producing partners
that helped us make this movie.
Ghost House Pictures.
That's Rob Tapert's
and Sam Raimi's company.
I always love that. That logo's beautiful.
And this is our company
with Fede Alvarez, Bad Hombre.
This is the first time that we see this.
So, here we go.
[siren wailing]
That is Detroit.
If you know the city, you would recognize
the skyline in the back.
This drone shot refers to the opening
of the first movie.
We wanted to open this one
in the same fashion,
but, you know, what's happening
is a little bit different this time.
This is a three-year-old little girl.
Just escaped that fire
walking down the street,
and she finally collapses on her knees.
We recognize that white lock of hair.
Understand that it's the same girl.
She's grown up now.
[bird caws]
[wings flapping]
And this was all shot in Serbia, actually.
And we discovered this place
in the middle of the woods
that had that piece of junk over there.
I'm not sure what it is.
No one knew what it was,
but what I liked about it is that,
although we open in the middle--
in the woods,
there's still elements that bring you
to a more urban setting.
[dog barking]
And we'll soon realize
that this is Detroit still.
A dystopian version of Detroit
where nature has claimed back its turf.
So, a basketball court.
We understand already
that we are in a city in the US.
[barking continues]
And that dog, actually, is one of the dogs
that we used in the first movie.
It's the same one, the same Rottweiler.
Which is crazy, but true.
Here we go. We discover...
Norman Nordstrom
for the first time in this movie.
You failed.
I didn't.
The gun is in my hand.
I thought I had it.
Sorry, Father. I'll make it next time.
Never take anything for granted.
God will take it from you.
Is God bad?
God is fair.
And this, right here, this beat
is something that we talked about.
We gave it a lot of consideration with
Fede and Stephen Lang in the first movie.
Norman said that there is no God,
and you clearly saw that it was a man
that was disenchanted with the idea
of a God and he's--
He used to believe in a God
and now lost his faith,
because he felt that that God failed him.
In this movie--
Now, we always thought that he...
at one point, thought that God
gave him a second opportunity
when he brought Phoenix to him.
And so, now he says, "God is fair."
In a way, he believes
that God and him are now even,
because God owed him something
and then gave him...
a daughter again.
So there's already movement in the journey
and the personal journey of Norman.
You failed survival.
It's been three months.
Plus, I just gave you a Killer haircut.
Trust me.
You need to pass all your tests first.
And this scene--
This is the first scene that we shot.
This was day one.
I was, of course, a little bit nervous.
It was my first day directing.
And it was also Madelyn's first day
doing a movie of this size.
She had worked in TV,
but not in a movie like this.
So, it was a first time for both of us,
and I think she did a great job already,
and it was a very demanding scene for her.
She had a lot of lines, and...
The drama in the scene
demanded a great performance,
and she came through
and she did a great job.
[door opens]
Go with Hernandez.
Back by sunset!
I will.
Hey, Hernandez.
[Hernandez] Hey, gorgeous.
He's not sure
if he did the right thing or not,
but it felt like
there was no way around it.
Eventually, he's gonna have to
at least give her something
and let her have a little bit of fun.
[singing]
This is actually Detroit.
The streets, the houses.
And that's exactly the way it looks.
There's these neighborhoods
that are completely abandoned,
and they make part of the universe
of Don't Breathe,
the setting of Don't Breathe.
That very particular look
is because of this.
[door creaking]
I really enjoyed shooting this scene.
Those ashes flying in the air,
that's something that
we were not planning on doing
until a couple of days before shooting,
and then Fede called me and said,
"Hey, make sure
you have those ashes floating."
And I was like, "Yeah,
but does it really make sense?
Because this fire happened
eight years before this scene."
And he was like, "It doesn't matter.
It's gonna look great. Trust me."
And he was so right.
[footsteps, floorboards creaking]
[reporter] Police have issued a statewide
alert for this man, Dr. Thomas Hanniman.
He's believed to be running
an organ trafficking ring
operating in the Detroit area.
The alarming number of abductions
has recently risen in the city.
This is a developing story.
We'll update you
as more information comes to light.
Right now, let's take a look
at the weekend forecast.
Good morning, everyone.
I'm meteorologist Jerry...
[kids laughing, chattering]
[boy] Everyone, pull. Help me.
It's stuck.
Hey, wanna try something?
Okay.
This scene wasn't originally like this.
This was actually happening.
This is something that Phoenix would do,
and then she would have a conversation
with these kids.
But in the editing process,
we discovered that it was better
to play it out as a dream sequence, right?
[bell ringing]
And she's just daydreaming
about mingling with this kid,
and having friends and connecting.
And I think it's so much more effective.
It gives a window into her character,
and we clearly understand
what her hopes are.
And it really pays off so much better
at the end of the movie
when she finally decides to come in
and talk to them and present herself.
Okay, well, be quick.
I don't wanna anger your father.
[toilet flushes]
[singing]
I love this shot. I love how we reveal...
Raylan here, our antagonist.
Wow, you're pretty.
Also, this shot is
one of my favorite shots in the movie.
I think the idea was that that mirror
would reflect the red wall in the back
and then create some sort of...
blood-colored stripe
that links these two characters together.
Which is something that we will understand
further down the road in the story,
how these two characters are connected.
So, we thought it was a nice way
to start presenting that idea.
Well, I'm sorry if I scared you.
Who said you did?
And that is my cameo in the movie.
That hand.
The tight shot of that hand,
that's actually me,
because, you know,
Brendan had to have his lunch break.
And you're always rushing
when you're shooting movies,
so I said, "I'll do it."
[door closes]
You okay?
Yes. Just a weirdo.
Yeah.
No shortage of those around here.
If you take a closer look,
Hernandez's hat says "Bad Hombre."
That's the name of our company.
Follow them.
[Phoenix] Thanks, Hernandez.
We had a lot of fun today.
I could take her again next week
if you're okay with it.
No. Today was enough.
-I know it's none of my business, but--
-You're right.
It's not.
You're a bad man.
She clearly knows how to
push this guy's buttons, for sure.
At least I know you think that.
Just like sometimes I do about myself.
War changes us all.
No soul returns holy from it
But don't make her pay for that.
Thanks.
I like it how, throughout the first act,
he is slowly coming to understand
that he's not going to be able
to keep her locked in this house forever.
She's growing up.
She just wants to go out
and, you know, explore the world,
and there's no stopping that.
So he sees-- He can sense and feel
that a storm is coming.
Here we introduce that red metal box.
I like it how, at this point,
it just raises questions.
"What is that thing?
What is he locking inside that thing?"
And we'll come to understand
the purpose of that box...
in a few scenes at this point.
[honking horn]
[barking]
You mind moving your vehicle
off the road, please?
You know, we're introducing the gang.
This is the only road back to town.
You served?
Yeah.
We all did, too.
-Iraq?
-Yeah.
Dishonorably discharged
from a dishonorable war.
[slurping]
I'd say that makes us honorable somehow.
Wouldn't you?
No.
Can you move your truck off the road now?
Sure, baby.
Whatever you want.
[engine revving]
[barking]
[dog barking]
[engine starts]
I really like this stare down
between the two of them.
It's like a standoff.
It makes you feel like we're setting up
a fight between the two of them
that will play later on in the movie,
but then, we just--
[choking]
We just Kill her right away.
[grunting, gasping]
[gasps, thud]
[tires screeching, grunts]
[horn honking]
[hammer thudding]
That was intense.
It was a lot of fun shooting that scene.
It wasn't easy, you know.
The van was actually moving
and the actors were playing the scene
with the moving van looking forward.
So we were pushing from behind,
and it had to crash
against those containers
while Jim-Bob was swinging on her.
So, it was complicated,
but, you know,
it turned out great, I think.
I don't wanna be safe.
I wanna be normal. I wanna have friends.
-I wanna live a--
-Enough!
Enough.
I already lost a daughter once.
I'm not losing you.
But I'm lonely.
You have no idea what it is to be alone.
You have me.
You're not enough.
Oh. She hits him with that line.
I always thought it was like a dart
that she spits on to him...
and it hurt.
I love this shot, too.
How we end up with her
being locked in that tower alone.
After that scene,
I think it's clear what she wants
and what Norman fears.
And that's the source
of the conflict between them.
[sniffing]
[gunshot]
"Covenant Shelter.
Your new home awaits you."
She's just dreaming
about a different life.
If you take a look
at the design of the house,
you realize that it's very much
a normal, suburban Detroit home,
but there's-- On that corner
where her bedroom is,
there's some sort of tower.
And that comes out of the idea
that there's a lot of elements
of a fairy tale in this story.
She's a princess locked in a tower,
and there's this dragon-like figure
that's guarding her
and keeping her locked there.
Because for him, it's his treasure, right?
His most precious thing.
And there's these guys that are coming
to rescue her, in a way.
At this point in the movie,
it feels that these guys are...
[rattling]
...you know, a threat to her.
But it's gonna be revealed later
that they're actually coming to save her.
It's a band of knights
that come to slay the dragon
and save the princess.
Shadow?
Here we start a continuous shot
that is going to go for six minutes.
[whistles]
And this is inspired by that shot
in the first Don't Breathe,
when the robbers break into the house
and the camera goes around the house,
showing us the space
where the story is gonna happen
and pointing out elements
that are gonna play out
in the movie later on.
So, we wanted to do
kind of the same thing,
but expand a little bit more,
put some more action in it
and make it even longer.
It was complicated for sure.
It took us, like,
three weeks to prep this maybe,
and three or four days to shoot.
A lot of rehearsal with the actors.
There's pretty complex
choreography happening.
[footsteps]
But I think the result is great.
It elevates the suspense
and the tension in the scene.
The sound design is also beautiful.
It tells you what's happening off-screen
and why characters
are doing what they're doing.
[switch clicks]
It's just a great tool...
that plays phenomenally in this movie.
[floorboards creak]
[door creaking]
The guy turned the light on.
That's how she is able to tell
that this is not Norman.
Norman does not need
to turn the lights on.
And, of course, the footsteps,
she recognizes
that there's something weird.
It's just not her father.
And she's trained to react quick.
So all of the training that
she's been doing pays off at this moment.
[door creaking]
[footsteps]
[door opens, shuts]
[alarm beeping]
[footsteps retreating]
[door opens, closes]
And we made a conscious decision
to not use any music during this scene,
because we thought
the sound design was crucial.
We just wanted to let it play
and come to the--
And take a front seat
during the whole scene.
And I think it works so well.
Just puts you in there.
[footsteps]
[doors opening]
[creaking]
[whimpering]
[footsteps]
[grunts softly]
[clattering]
[thud]
[rattling]
[footsteps]
This is Adam Young.
An amazing actor.
I think he looks so scary.
Total psychopath.
This sequence was also shot
during the first week, so it was--
You know, we're--
All of us were just warming up,
and we had to do
this very complicated scene.
Everybody was on top of their game.
The actors did great, and, you know,
Adam already had
this very demanding beat to play,
and already close-ups and everything.
He just nailed it.
[footsteps]
[breath shuddering]
[footsteps thumping]
[sniffing]
Shadow.
[sobbing]
I know there's a rule that says
that you don't kill dogs in movies,
and we had to break this rule.
We had to.
But, uh...
there's gonna be a reward to this.
Some sort of reward.
The Blind Man is gonna find
a new companion.
[footsteps]
We're back in the house.
And Phoenix is still hiding.
She can hear the guys upstairs,
so it makes sense that maybe
she can make a run for the door
to get out of there.
[footsteps]
[gunshot]
I love that shot.
Here he comes.
[grunting]
The box! Now!
-[screams]
-Oh, that hurts.
Go!
[Phoenix screams]
[grunting]
Go get the girl.
Open the door.
Now we understand
the purpose of that red box.
Norman had been preparing for
something like this for quite some time.
[panting]
Here, I think the prosthetics
did a great job.
That looks very real.
Oh, and painful.
And look at these guys, the gang...
I like that they are all very unique.
Usually in these kind of movies,
the henchmen, they all look the same.
But we made sure
that each one of these guys
had a different quality and look.
And I think we achieved that,
and we made sure that we got
really good actors to play these roles.
And Bobby, I love him. He's amazing.
There's a certain physicality to his role
and the way that--
What he can do with his face.
It always amazed me. Very skilled actor.
[squelching]
[scream echoing]
The glue.
The superglue set piece.
This was an idea that-- One of
the first ideas that we had with Fede.
We thought it would be great
if the Blind Man would use superglue
to do something like this
to one of these guys
and just let him suffocate.
And [ think it plays great.
Bobby did a great job.
He actually couldn't breathe
when we were shooting that,
so we could only shoot for a minute or so.
So it was challenging to shoot this scene.
He's actually not been able to breathe
at that point.
-Breathe, brother.
-[struggling to inhale]
[gasping]
[whimpering]
The guy's a Navy SEAL.
We had informed in the first movie
that Norman used to be--
He was a war veteran, but we didn't...
explain that he was a Navy SEAL,
which ups the game.
This guy's not playing around.
[groaning]
Now we're in the water tank.
This was also...
hard work to shoot,
but Madelyn, she has so much energy
and she was actually looking forward
to shooting that.
Since she read the script, she said,
"That's the scene
that I'm most looking forward to shoot,"
because she loves swimming
and swimming underwater.
Uh, and we spent a couple of days
shooting this scene
and she wanted to keep going and shoot
more days inside that water tank,
which was very demanding
because she had to perform underwater
and, you know, not easy,
but she just killed it.
Call Raylan.
I love this moment,
this standoff between Duke
and the Blind Man
and how he comes up with this whole idea,
you know, he's trying to smoke him
out of his hideout
and also force the girl to come out
of the box at the same time.
Metal box is almost full of water.
You prefer to see the kid alive...
you come in here.
You think I'm fucking with you?
No.
There's a live wire
about to reach the water.
Come out, or she's fried!
[thumping]
[gun cocks]
[metal clanks]
But Norman is smart.
He knows how to disarm this guy.
Clever fuck.
No guns, huh?
No problem.
I love how he's approaching, you know,
with this hand forward,
kind of like coming in peace.
You know, "Let's just talk things over.
No need to fight."
But with his other hand,
he's holding that iron rod...
and off we go.
[both grunting]
I think this fight is so intense and--
Most of it was the actors themselves.
You know, there's a couple of shots
where it's stunt doubles,
but most of the fight is, you know,
just Stephen Lang
and Rocci Boy Williams just going at it.
And Rocci Boy,
he used to be an MMA fighter,
so he's very tough, very, very tough
and he knows how to fight.
So he challenged Stephen Lang
who's also a guy that's,
you know, is very strong
and likes to train a lot,
so he pushed him to his limits,
and they just went at it.
I remember after--
And this went on for, like, two days.
When we finished--
When we finished shooting,
Stephen Lang said to me,
"Rodo, that guy is actually
really tough, for real." [laughs]
[grunting]
Both of them ended up
with bruises all over themselves.
[grunts]
[gasping]
[groaning]
[muffled scream]
[grunting]
[panting]
[groaning]
You're tough.
But you're done.
That blast we actually did for real.
You know, it was probably the more
Hollywood-like moment on set,
having a real explosion.
A lot of fun, to be honest,
and we did it, like, two or three times
with an actual actor-- an actual
stunt double that was lit on fire.
So we had the whole
Hollywood experience on set,
and it looks great, I think.
[clanging]
[thud, grunts]
[clanging continues]
[grunting]
That red box is heavy.
It probably weighs a ton
when it's full of water,
but, you know,
the Blind Man is really strong,
he's a tough guy
and he manages to tip it over.
[grunting]
[sputtering]
Breathe.
-[gasping]
-Come on, breathe.
Breathe.
The old blind man did this?
Uh-huh.
Let's go.
I love the shot
when she sees the aftermath
of the fight that she was only hearing,
and now she sees what happened
and is like, "Oh, my God.
My dad did that to that guy?"
[laughs]
I can walk.
I said I can walk.
[clanging]
What's happening?
Cover the exits.
What the fuck?
By the way, that's all real prosthetics.
It took, like, five hours
for them to apply that
on the actor
and it's great.
They're still down here.
What's happening?
-Who are they?
- I don't know.
[gunshot]
I love this scene. I love the lighting.
I think Pedro Luque, our DP,
did an amazing job.
I mean, throughout the whole movie
it looks amazing.
But this set...
I think is the one
that I like the most, how he lit it.
That mix of warms and cools,
it's beautiful.
[Raylan] You don't need
to be afraid, little girl.
This has all just been
one big misunderstanding.
It's not me you need to be scared of...
I love Stephen's performances
at this point
and then Madelyn's as well.
...but the man standing next to you.
Now, I don't know who he is.
But I know who he's not.
She's like, "What is he talking about?"
[chuckles]
There's some truth
that's about to come out.
Should I tell her or you?
[Norman screams]
[grunting]
Finish him, bro.
No!
-Dad! Dad, wake up.
-Aren't you something?
[grunting] Let me go!
Come on.
No, it's okay.
I love this, and I think Brendan did
an amazing job.
You really don't remember me, do you?
Maybe this will help.
Now we reveal the true identity
of these guys.
And going back to the idea
of the fairy tale,
we now realize
that these are actually knights
that are coming to save the princess
from the dragon.
Years ago, there was a fire in our house.
Cops blamed me.
I spent eight years in prison,
wondering if I'd ever see you again.
Hell, I didn't even know
if you were dead or alive.
[dog whimpering]
This creep here must have...
found you and kept you for himself.
[newscaster] Up next in local news,
a meth lab caught fire
in west Detroit this morning.
Police were able
to arrest the primary suspect.
The man was taken into custody
and could face charges
for a large number of crimes committed
over the past several years.
[Raylan] You have no idea how much
I've been waiting for this moment.
And in a way, she knows this is true.
She knows it.
Did he hurt you?
But he did steal you away from me,
and now he must die, you understand?
Kill him.
[gun cocks]
-No.
-Fuck are you doing?
Not in front of my kid. Do it outside.
[chuckles] I love it how suddenly
he's got a dad's consciousness.
He's a responsible dad.
He doesn't want to traumatize her.
[groans]
But then if he needs to shoot, he does,
and then he'll just go crazy. [laughing]
That tells you already that this guy
is not a more stable person.
[glass shatters]
[grunting]
Fucking coward.
Take her to the truck
while I hunt this motherfucker. Let's go.
-Let me go!
-What's wrong with you?
Fucking wanna go home?
[both scream]
I love this moment.
I love Bobby's performance here.
He looks so scary
and frustrated and pissed.
I love it.
And because he's such a crazy dude,
even though you know
that he should not hurt her,
he's so pissed right now
that you feel like he would do it.
I don't care who you are.
I'm gonna teach you
some fucking manners, yo.
You ungrateful little bitch.
[grunting]
[screams]
And this is moment where Phoenix
sees the monster in Norman.
You know, she sees her father
letting out that monster.
And she's never seen that side of him,
so she's very shocked and surprised.
Here it comes. Ooh, the head smash.
That was a dummy.
We didn't want to do any CG.
We wanted to do everything practical,
so we created-- we had a dummy made
after Bobby, the actor.
And then we just smashed the dummy
with a real heavy iron shovel,
and I think it looks amazing.
Now we'll reveal
that these two guys are actually brothers,
so this makes it personal, you know,
and that's something that you
always want to see in these movies.
You know, make it personal,
SO you know
that we're building up a nice fight
between the Blind Man
and this guy, Jim-Bob.
Move!
At this moment,
she's looking at her father--
Well, she now knows
that he's not her father,
but she's looking at Norman
with different eyes.
She just saw that he's also a monster.
So she's just, like,
having all of these thoughts
and emotions swirling inside of her.
So many questions
and then she decides to confront him.
It's his jacket.
Attaboy.
-[sniffing]
-Attaboy.
[Phoenix] Wait. Stop.
Is it true?
Move.
What's my real name?
Get over here now!
When's my birthday?
-My real one?
-Stop it!
No, you stop it!
[barking]
She's questioning everything now.
She knows that she's going
to have to restructure her whole identity,
that she's been living in a lie.
[barking continues]
This scene was also a lot of fun
to shoot with that dog.
The animal handlers did an amazing job.
The dog did exactly everything
that we needed him to do.
We also had a puppet
that looked very realistic.
I think that shot was a puppet.
Now she escapes.
This was shot on location.
So, with this house we have--
We built it on location
to shoot the exteriors of the house
and then we built the interior
of the house on a set.
So we had to build it twice.
And this is shot on location.
But this is on set,
so this is not in the heights.
The closer shots, I mean,
and the wider shots are on location.
That's the puppet right there.
I think it looks great.
And then the real dog, of course.
-[groans]
-[dog snarling]
I love this moment,
I think it's more about
whether he's going
to be able to kill a dog or not.
This is something
that we talked with Stephen Lang.
This scene is not about
whether he's going to survive or not,
because he knows he's got a gun
and eventually,
he can shoot the dog and kill it.
But what's at stake here is his morals,
his ethics, his moral compass,
you know, is he going to be--
Is he going to break that code
that he lives by?
Because we know how he relates to dogs.
Is he going to break it or not?
And he just can't.
[distant barking]
-[grunts]
-[Phoenix screams]
-[dog snarling]
-Phoenix!
-[grunting]
-Calm down, girl.
So they finally capture her.
[dog whining]
This is the only way
that we could figure out
for him to be able to--
To get away without hurting the dog.
Put her in the truck.
So they got her and now, of course,
what are they going to do?
Set this thing on fire.
Now we reveal what was inside this cooler.
The idea that when we reveal--
When we showed it in the first act,
the idea is that you connected it
to the organ trafficking ring,
but now you would understand
this is not about that...
for now, of course.
I love how this character, Raul,
is having second thoughts, you know.
He's maybe not that okay
with this guy's methods.
And he's gonna--
He's gonna have a bigger arc
by the end of the movie.
And by the way, that guy Raul
is another character
that was in the first movie.
In the first movie, the robbers--
You know, there's this guy
in the back of a van
in an empty parking lot
that gives one of the robbers the tip
about the Blind Man
that's got this money and all that.
That guy is Raul, who is Christian Zagia,
an actor from Uruguay,
who I think did a great job in this movie.
So all of this fire that you're seeing
is real, most of it.
We set the whole house on fire
on location, it was crazy.
[dog barking]
I loved how, even though he knows
that the house is catching fire,
he just has to come back
and save that dog.
Which eventually is gonna--
Is gonna save his life
because the dog is going to repay him.
So all of that fire is real.
We put Stephen in--
In a very harsh position there.
It was hot as hell on that set.
Of course there's--
Those flames are not real, those ones.
There's some that are CG.
But 80% of it is real.
And this is an homage to the first movie.
We did the same thing
with one of the characters, Alex.
But now, you know, the tables are turned
and it's his turn to be there
and experience--
And experience that ordeal.
[explosion, glass shatters]
[grunting]
I love this shot of--
The camera pivots around him
and we discover the house...
set on fire and, again, this is all real.
We had every fireman in Belgrade...
[chuckles] expecting the worst,
because we were shooting this.
This is in the woods,
so there's a lot of trees
that could potentially catch fire.
So it was risky, but it was worth it.
She wakes up in this weird place.
And we love the idea of working
with our production designer, Dave Warren.
He's an absolute genius.
He-- We came up with the idea
that maybe this used to be the bar
at the hotel,
but this guy just repurposed it
and made it into his bedroom...
which makes a lot of sense to me.
Like, this guy would definitely do that,
you know?
You all right?
Wanna sit with me?
Come, sit with me. Come on.
This is a-- I feel like this is
a very intimate scene,
and we decided to--
To shoot all this
with very tight close-ups.
And we actually keep getting tighter
as the conversation unfolds
and she starts asking questions
about her past
and getting more intimate with her father.
And the use of the light,
there's a warmth to it.
We wanted to make it feel
like a safe place for her,
so you would feel like maybe, you know,
she's just going to stay here
and live her life with her family.
Do I have any brothers or sisters?
Unfortunately, no.
When's my birthday?
February 20th.
What was my mother's name?
Josephine.
Do I look like her?
I love this.
Yeah.
Because she's been asking--
These are the questions
that she's been asking the Blind Man
for her whole life,
and she never got straight-up answers,
especially when
she would mention her mother.
And we saw that
at the beginning of the movie,
she asked about her mother
and the Blind Man
just doesn't want to go there.
And now she's finally being able
to ask that question,
"Does she look like me?
Do I look like her?"
And she finally gets the answer that
she wanted, and Raylan just says, "Yes."
I'm not sorry.
You shouldn't be, either.
I wanna go.
Where? Where you gonna go?
There's a shelter I know.
Like I said,
you're not a prisoner anymore.
And this guy is doing
what Norman never did,
which is, you know, "It's your life,
and if you decide to go somewhere else
and whatever you want to do,
it's fine with me.
You're not a prisoner."
I love this beat.
You know, she walks out and there's
all these dudes outside, just waiting.
And this guy-- And if you remember,
we saw this guy on the TV
that was playing that news report
about the organ trafficking ring.
I love this shot.
It just creates a lot of tension
because, in a way,
you can't believe that these guys are
just going to let her go just like that.
And there's the door.
Is she going to leave?
Is she going to leave or not?
So I think it works really well.
But then they have
this card up their sleeves.
[woman singing]
This is one of my favorite scenes
in the whole movie.
This reveal that, actually,
Mother was still alive.
[singing]
I love Madelyn's performance here.
Her reaction made it feel
like that song that she sang
in the beginning of the movie is, like,
pushing every cell of her body,
every memory.
It's just tapping into her memories
that were buried
and it's all coming out.
And she knows what this means
and she knows what it is.
She's just in deep shock.
This is Fiona O'Shaughnessy,
a wonderful actress from the UK.
And I can't imagine anyone better fit
for this role.
She just killed it.
She got so emotionally invested
in the character.
She just gave an absolutely
astonishing performance, I think.
Like I said...
everything he told you was a lie.
It's a family reunion, finally.
Now we know her actual name, Tara,
and she-- It's new to her.
You... got so big.
[laughs] She looks so creepy.
Come here.
And this hug is real, you know?
Phoenix is really feeling it.
It's like this is what she always wanted,
you know, her mom,
and finally she's here. She's alive.
Oh, baby, we missed you so much.
Mmm. There you are.
You were such a beautiful baby.
And this scene is also one of the most
important scenes in the whole movie.
You know,
we're now gonna reveal what the--
What their motivations actually are.
-[Raylan] Get it out. Come on.
-[coughing]
There you go. There you go.
-There you go.
-Sorry.
[Raylan] Nothing to apologize for.
Are you okay?
The same fire that destroyed our family...
I think these two have
a lot of chemistry together.
They make a really creepy
and wonderful couple.
Mom and Dad used to have a...
kitchen...
in the basement of our house,
where we used to cook.
It was for our business.
Are you thirsty?
Phoenix is slowly connecting the dots.
[chuckles]
[Josephine] Tara?
I'm dying.
What?
The smoke from the chemicals...
poisoned my blood
and badly damaged my heart.
I don't think I have much time left.
Is there anything you can do?
[Josephine giggles]
I heard you left flowers for me
at our old house.
I love it how, the approach, and going
back to the idea of the fairy tale.
Right now, we realize that
these knights that saved her
were actually working for the evil witch
and the evil witch, what she wants,
just like in Snow White,
she wants to absorb the youth
out of Phoenix for herself.
It's very, of course, twisted.
I need a new heart, baby.
A very twisted concept,
she being her mother.
Her thought process is, you know,
"I gave you life once,
and now I need it back.
And you should give it to me
gracefully and willingly."
Like a direct relative.
Which is what she's trying to do.
Because she just might as well
just move ahead with the surgery,
and that's it.
But she wants to convince her
to give out her heart willingly
out of love for her.
That's what she wants.
So that she can sleep at night
without any sort of remorse.
And this shot, I think,
is very much of a fairy tale,
the hand hovering on top of her
as she passes out.
Going back to the Blind Man, a light
of hope on the horizon as he wakes up.
[grunting]
[groaning]
[dog panting]
[Norman] Go home.
[metal clinking]
-[dog whines]
-Shh.
-[whines]
-Shh!
[metal clinking]
I love how the sound design
plays into the story here
and how we get into the Blind Man's head
and experience how he perceives the world
through his hearing.
And that guides him to discover
Hernandez's van and her body.
[clinking]
[sobs]
At this point, we feel that the Blind Man
is starting to slowly understand
all the pain that he has caused,
all the death,
the trail of death that he's left behind
because of his actions.
Because Hernandez would be alive
if it wasn't for him.
[dog panting]
Stay.
I love this idea on how he finds a way
to track down these guys...
and get to Phoenix using the dog.
He knows dogs and he knows that the dog
is going to go back home,
wherever that home is.
So he just has to follow the dog
and that's it.
I think that idea, at a script level,
it took us months
to come up with that idea
and figure out how the hell the Blind Man
was going to find these guys.
Go home.
But at the end, I think it works great.
I think was Fede's idea,
and I think it's genius.
Go home.
[dripping]
I think this is the last shot
that we shot in the movie.
[chuckles]
[drill whirring]
I hope you understand
the high risks of this procedure.
[Raylan] I think I pay you enough.
Shut up and do your job.
Why is she still alive?
[surgeon] If she's dead, so is her heart.
And I can't keep it fresh long enough
without the proper equipment.
[laughing] That is so creepy.
And I like this beat,
you know, Mother just calls her
and says, "Thank you."
I think that is so creepy.
And that is tied to that idea
that the mother convinced herself
that Phoenix was doing this willingly,
you know, and she just thanks her.
What's wrong with you, man?
Come back to Raul, and we show how
he is growing a conscience
and he's slowly switching sides.
You know, he's not--
He probably didn't know exactly what
these guys were going to do to that girl.
And now he just feels like
he can't go with it.
It's just too much.
I love it when you give these villains,
these henchmen,
when you give them some depth,
and you get to understand
what their moral compass is
and, you know, what their code is.
There's things that they would do,
but some things they wouldn't.
Of course, Jim-Bob, the other guy,
is a total psychopath. He's cool with it.
He just cares about their business
and the money
and they need her and that's it.
[drill whirring]
Boom.
What the fuck?
[crash]
Go check it out.
[door opens, closes]
[rats squeaking]
Rats. Real rats.
I love this next shot.
It will reveal the Blind Man.
I think it's beautiful.
-[grunting]
-[gunshots]
Of course, the sound of the water
pouring down makes it very difficult
for the Blind Man to locate Jim-Bob.
He's confused.
His radar is off.
And he just takes a beating.
But he's got his tricks, of course.
[groaning]
I'm gonna carve your fucking head open
like a pumpkin, man.
[grunting]
-[bones crack]
-[screaming]
[choking]
I love this idea.
Jim-Bob needs to make a run for the gun,
but he's going to make a sound as well.
But he takes a risk. Boom.
[choking]
[grunting]
This is for Shadow.
Oh, fuck.
No!
That hammer went down really hard.
And it was a heavy hammer,
because it's a one-piece iron hammer.
And Stephen Lang, you know,
just went at it.
And Adam was actually there
when Slang was hitting the ground.
So he had to move in order
to avoid getting hit by the hammer.
So it was very stressful for Adam
to shoot that scene.
Disloyal fucking animal.
I love it how the dog
also has an arc in this movie.
-Everything's okay, I promise.
-Baby, should I be worried?
No, no. Not at all.
I got you. I got you.
I can't work without power.
Change of plans, then.
Pack your things. Bring the girl.
Raul.
-Bring the men. Kill the blind man.
-How many of us?
All of you!
Let's go.
I love the scene that's coming up next.
On paper, you know, we made total sense.
We thought of the idea with Fede
that these guys are going to walk
into that pool,
and the water ripples are going
to make contact with the Blind Man's hand
and then he knows where these guys are,
and he shoots.
But then, you know, shooting that on set
was a different story.
You know, being able to capture
those water ripples,
it was a huge challenge
in terms of lighting and camera movement.
It wasn't easy,
but we got very, very lucky.
And our team were such professionals
and so good at what they do.
They were actually able
to pull it off pretty quickly, I think.
I think this next shot, this is the camera
following that actual water ripple.
It was just perfect.
[spluttering]
In this moment, I love it, because
the Blind Man is totally defenseless now.
He's at the mercy of this guy.
They're gonna kill her.
And that's not cool with me.
But now he switched sides.
He's grown in consciousness.
And because of that,
you know, he saves the day.
He actually saves the girl.
But he's relieved.
Go left.
That way.
He'll kill you all.
Now we enter the biggest scene
in the whole movie.
This, I think, took, like,
seven or eight days to shoot--
To shoot the scene,
plus a couple days of second unit.
And this place is actually--
This is Belgrade.
And this swimming pool is in--
Marshal Tito,
who was the leader of Yugoslavia,
it's his palace.
[Josephine] Baby.
Shh. It's okay.
-Stop it.
-[grunts]
The swimming pool is not that deep,
but we enhanced it in CG
and we made it to be a diving pool,
which are usually 20 feet deep
or something.
Deep enough to where if you fall into it,
you've probably killed yourself.
I love this red smoke scene.
Very intense.
[Raylan] I can't see you.
-Baby?
-[clattering]
[grunting]
[footsteps running]
[man grunting]
[grunting]
[coughing]
[panting]
[Josephine] Someone's here! Hurry!
Baby?
[grunting]
[coughing]
[gun clicking]
I love this moment.
This is connected to the first movie where
the Blind Man accidentally shoots Cindy,
the girl that he trapped in the basement.
He thinks he shot one of the intruders,
but he ended up killing her.
And this is the same thing.
Raylan thinks that he got the Blind Man,
but he just killed his wife.
No.
No!
[grunting]
[Phoenix] No!
[wheels skidding]
[screaming]
I love this.
This is one of those "good news, bad news"
action set pieces, you know.
Good news, Mother is dead.
Bad news, she's now going to drag
Phoenix into the swimming pool.
Good news, there's a machete.
Bad news, I cannot chop the arm in time,
and I'm dragged into the swimming pool.
And also the Blind Man
appears to be losing his fight.
-[grunting]
-[screaming]
[bones crack]
Phoenix!
[barking]
And this is the payoff, you know,
because the Blind Man saved this dog,
now this dog is loyal to him
and saves him.
Karma, you would say.
-[dog growling]
-[grunting]
[barking]
[laughing] This is a lot of fun.
Now...
you're gonna see what I see.
Actually, that line
was not in the first movie.
It was just in the promotional material.
"Now you're going to see what I see.”
We decided to include it in this movie.
And [ think it plays great
for the eye-gouge thing.
The good news, she landed on top
of her mother and she was saved.
She didn't get hurt.
Now, this scene is the most important
scene in the whole movie.
This completes Norman's arc.
To this point, you don't know
what he's going to do
when he finally gets to Phoenix.
And this is a surprise.
He actually sets her free
by confessing his crimes
and his past sins
and telling her who he truly is.
Everything he said...
is true.
He confesses his things to himself
as well, which is the hardest thing to do.
I have killed.
I--
In the first movie, he made it very clear
that he was not doing anything wrong.
He was just amending things.
Like he would just come up
with excuses for his behavior.
He said, "I didn't do this,
I didn't do that,"
and now he's coming around,
coming to terms with his true nature,
and with the horrible things
that he's done.
And I think...
he's actually feeling, himself,
the pain that he's caused to others.
The misery that he has caused to others.
And he feels it. He understands it.
And only then, he truly repents.
-Go!
-[gasps]
And releases her.
"He has integrated his shadow,”
Carl Jung would say.
And he accepts his destiny.
He's embarrassed.
And I think Stephen Lang gave an amazing,
awesome performance here.
Very honest and very raw.
[thud]
And now, he understands he's going to die.
He's not even fighting.
He just accepts his fate
and his punishment.
[thud, grunting]
Tara?
[grunting]
I love this setup.
The lighting here is beautiful.
The sun is slowly coming out.
[Phoenix] No.
[grunts]
No.
Please.
And the Blind Man makes it clear to her
that it's his time
and that he's okay with it.
Let me help you.
I can save you.
And he says that she already saved him
because she pushed him to confess
and come to terms with his true nature
and acknowledge the monster
that lives inside of him.
And to stop living in denial.
And we decided to keep this scene,
this beat without any music.
Because, you know, sometimes music--
It only kicks in here at the end,
but throughout the scene,
there's no music.
It tells you how you should feel
about a scene,
and we wanted this
to be very somber and raw.
You know, the man is dying.
He deserved to die at that point,
and we're not giving him a heroic death.
It's just-- It is what it is.
We're just witnessing how he slowly
fades away without glorifying anything.
And I think it works great.
I love this shot here.
This is a new beginning for her.
Her performance is beautiful, too.
And what Pedro did with the light
in those shots is also amazing.
[Phoenix] Hey.
Hey.
Think there's room for one more?
I'm sure there is.
What's your name?
My name is Phoenix.
And there we go.
[rock music playing]
These final credits here,
our editing team put this together.
They did an amazing job.
I think they look beautiful.
[electric guitar playing]
By the way, that guitar playing there
in the back, that's me.
Roque Banos asked me to record it.
So it was a privilege
to be able to play that.
I love this one, particularly.
[rock music continues]
So there it is.
Thank you guys so much.
I hope you enjoyed the movie.
Oh, we got this one coming. Yeah, sure.
The final coda.
Is he alive, huh? We don't know that.
Thank you, guys. Thank you, guys.
I hope you enjoyed the movie
and you enjoyed this commentary.
And I hope to see you around soon.
Thank you.