® Arun's collections ®
(♪♪♪)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(SIRENS WAILING IN DISTANCE)
(♪♪♪)
(LOW GRUNTING)
(KEYS JINGLING)
MAN 1 :
Are you sure you have the right keys?
MAN 2 :
Trust me, it's the right key.
WOMAN :
Okay, then, open the door.
MAN 1 :
It shouldn't be taking so long, man.
(ALARM BEEPS)
WOMAN :
20, 19, 18...
ALEX:
Rocky, those are very slow seconds.
MONEY :Yo, kill that already.
WOMAN : ...17, 16...
MONEY :Dude, come on.
ROCKY : ...15, 14, 13...
(BEEPING CONTINUES
THEN MONEY CHUCKLING)
MONEY :This is what I'm talking about.
ROCKY : ...12, 11, 10, 9...
(ALARM STOPS)
I told you this was gonna be fancy.
All right, so, just like last time.
No cash.
The total take has to fall below ten G's.
Yeah, yeah. Whatever, Judge Judy.
- Come on.
- Let's do this.
(♪♪♪)
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
ALEX:
Okay, let's get out of here.
(ALARM BEEPING)
(ALARM WAILING)
(♪♪♪)
Hey, Rocky, did you hear
that Kopecky's moving away?
Everybody's leaving.
You know, if we keep hitting
houses like today's...
...Rocky, and...
Bye-bye, Detroit.
And hola, California.
Wait, wait.
You're going away, Rock?
Yeah, as soon as I can.
When are you,
when are you coming back?
Never.
You should come with us.
Uh...
ROCKY :
What?
Everyone else is gone.
I got my dad here.
I'll miss you, then.
(♪♪♪)
Dad?
You home?
(♪♪♪)
Yo, this is it, man?
Minus my 40 percent.
Take it or leave it.
There's a fucking Rolex in there, bro.
And what do you think...
...I'm going to put it up
for auction at Sotheby's? Heh.
Do you know how much...
...people on the street pay
for a hot Rolex?
Heh. You want money?
Then steal money.
Fucking bullshit, bro.
Do you want this new tip or not?
MONEY :
All right, let's hear it.
1837 Buena Vista Street.
House is with
your dad's security company.
I already checked.
Guy who owns it
is an Army vet loner.
No family.
Just him in the house.
That part of the city is a ghost town.
It looks like a dump.
That's actually good news.
How's that good news?
The story goes...
...some preppy girl
a few years ago...
...ran over this guy's daughter.
- Jesus.
- The daughter dies...
...and this preppy,
rich-ass family...
...pays him off...
...gives him a big-ass sediment.
Settlement.
Blow me, Your Honor.
All right, this guy
is sitting on at least...
...300K.
Boom!
I mean, if I deliver
this stake to Raul, man...
...he will shit his pants.
Do you think the money's
in the house?
I don't know.
Let's go find out.
Guys, no. We don't do cash.
Above ten K, it's major larceny.
That means ten years
if we get caught.
- We won't get caught.
ALEX :Okay, and then what?
That amount brings
a serious cop presence.
They'll do an investigation.
My dad could get in trouble.
I knew you'd bitch out, man.
I just knew it.
Alex, if we do this right,
we never have to do it again.
Where are you going?
We're not doing this one.
Seriously?
Give us the fucking keys, man.
- We'll fucking do it.
- Alex!
(PHONE BEEPS)
(♪♪♪)
"Gulf War veteran reaches
six-figure settlement."
Six-figure settlement.
All right.
REPORTER (ON TV):
The suspect was leaving...
...the rear entrance of the club.
Are you done, Diddy?
Be a doll and get your mother...
...a large four-cheese from Tony's.
(MICROWAVE BEEPS)
- So Trevor's living here now?
MOTHER : Don't be a bitch, Roxanne.
It's just a few months
till he can find a new job.
You have no money in here.
MOTHER :
You pay for it then.
I know you're making money.
(SIGHS)
I'm done.
Your lips look sore.
That's how you're making
your cash out there?
Ha, ha. Huh?
(TREVOR CHUCKLES)
Okay, Diddy,
let's go for a walk.
I want to go to the beach.
Yeah, well,
it's not summer, monkeyhead.
I want to be a surfer.
There's no surf in Michigan.
- Not fair.
- Yeah, well...
(SNIFFLES)
...some things
you can't change, baby.
(PHONE BUZZES)
No matter how unfair they are.
What a bummer.
Hey, you know
where there is surf?
(WHISPERING)
California.
What do you say
you and I move there together?
Would you like that?
Okay.
I promise then.
(BOTH EXHALE)
(♪♪♪)
(BIRD SCREECHING)
(SIGHS)
Is that a new tattoo?
Yeah.
I got it last night.
ALEX :Is it a...?
- Ladybug.
Why a ladybug?
What?
When my dad left,
my mom started drinking...
...and she told me that...
...my dad's leaving was all my fault.
And I missed him a lot, so I'd cry.
She got so fed up with the crying...
...that she would lock me
in the trunk of her car.
Sometimes for hours.
But there was this, um...
A little hole in the trunk...
...and one time a ladybug flew in...
...kept me company.
It made me feel safe.
When I reach California,
I'm gonna color this tat...
...and that's the last time
I will mark my body.
If we get this money,
I'm going away with you guys.
I know you will.
(FOOTSTEPS THEN DOOR OPENS)
At least four blocks around,
houses aren't occupied.
No people means
no Five-0 on patrol.
It's gonna be a piece of cake.
The guy's a shut-in...
...hasn't left his house
in, like, five days.
I say we do it with him
in the house.
I'll get a chloro-bomb.
(BARKING)
ROCKY :
Oh, shit!
- Jesus.
- Fucking A.
Get off my fucking car, dog shit!
(BARKING CONTINUES)
(MAN WHISTLES)
(BARKING FADES)
Shit, that's our guy.
(♪♪♪)
Wait, is he blind?
MONEY :
He lost his sight in Iraq or something.
That's kind of fucked up
to rob a blind guy, isn't it?
Just because he's blind don't
mean he's a fucking saint, bro.
(SIGHS)
We do this tonight.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(♪♪♪)
(DISTANT BARKING)
ALEX :The whole neighborhood
is fucking empty.
This guy's the last man standing.
MONEY :
The lights are out.
He must be asleep.
He's blind.
Lights off doesn't mean anything.
ROCKY :
It's 2 a.m.
He's sleeping.
Let's take care
of that dog first, yeah?
(BARKING CONTINUES)
(DOG BARKING)
MONEY :
Come on, man.
(BARKING CONTINUES)
He's chewing it.
It'll be lights out in a sec.
(DOG GROANING)
There's four locks.
You got the other keys?
- I only have the one.
- Ah. Fuck me.
Why wouldn't he give backup
keys to the security company?
Because the money's in there...
...and the paranoid fuck
doesn't trust nobody.
ROCKY :
Let's check for a side door.
(GRUNTS)
(SNORING SOFTLY)
(WHISTLING SOFTLY)
Sweet dreams, pup.
What's that?
We just have to point this
in the general direction...
...of the master keypad,
and it'll kill the alarm.
Okay, open the fucking door, Dexter.
ALEX:
Yes. Got it.
Shit.
ROCKY :
What's wrong?
It won't open.
(GRUNTS)
MONEY :
This guy isn't messing around.
There's a bolt here.
I can feel it.
- Come on.
ALEX :That's too loud.
- That's too loud.
- Fucking stop.
What about that window?
There's no bars on it.
- I can fit in there.
ALEX :What?
No, we're not sending you
in there alone.
Nobody's sending me anywhere.
I'm going myself.
Help me up.
ALEX:
Here, Rocky.
You only got 30 seconds.
ROCKY :
Okay.
MONEY :
Here. Come here.
(♪♪♪)
(CHIRPS)
(BEEPING STEADILY)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(GLASS CRUNCHING)
(BEEPING INCREASES)
(CHIRPING THEN BEEPING STOPS)
(PANTING)
(PANTING CONTINUES)
(♪♪♪)
MONEY :
Slow your roll, fool.
She must have got it by now.
She's fine.
Yeah, like you really give a fuck.
What'd you say?
That's my bitch in there.
Of course I give a fuck.
Let me give you some advice.
Be a good friend...
...and stay in the fucking
friend zone, all right?
(CREAKS)
Are you okay?
Yes.
Shoes off.
(♪♪♪)
(FLOORBOARD CREAKS
THEN GASPING)
(SCOFFS)
- What the fuck?
- Hey.
(DOOR CREAKS)
(SIGHS)
MONEY :
Hey. Hey.
ALEX:
Okay.
(FLOORBOARDS CREAKING)
GIRL (SINGING ON TV):
♪ I love you ♪
♪ Yes, I'll be your valentine ♪
♪ Valentine, valentine ♪
♪ I love you ♪
Just three seeds, right?
Just three?
One, two...
...and three.
Put three seeds in there...
...and the cup is all empty.
Now you water it?
Okay, now we water it.
Okay, Mom.
Then it takes the water.
Just three seeds.
WOMAN :
What are you doing?
GIRL : Planting a tree.
WOMAN :
How big is the tree going to get?
GIRL :
As big as the sky!
WOMAN :
Wow.
(DOOR CREAKS)
What does a tree need to grow?
GIRL :
Water, seeds, soil...
...and sun.
WOMAN :
Sounds good.
(GASPS)
GIRL (SINGING ON TV):
♪ Yes, I'll be your valentine ♪
♪ Valentine, valentine ♪
♪ I love you ♪
Then it will grow.
Mom, can I have more water?
(GROANS)
(DOOR CREAKS)
Done!
(GASPS)
ALEX:
What the fuck, dude?
MONEY :
The guy's gassed out.
He's out.
He's in Sleeping Beauty mode.
- It's fine.
- Guys.
That's a big-ass lock.
ROCKY :
If the money's in the house...
...probably in there.
ALEX:
You think you can crack it open?
MONEY :
Yeah, I got this.
(WOOD CREAKING)
(MONEY GRUNTING)
Fuck.
(GRUNTING CONTINUES)
ROCKY :
Jesus.
(PANTING)
Do you have anything else?
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
I've got a more powerful tool.
What the hell is that?
It's a nine millimeter Beretta.
Gangster-style, bitches.
Why did you bring a gun?
This is a soldier's house, Alex.
Like I'm gonna come in here
without some chrome.
ROCKY :
Money, you've never shot a gun before.
Yeah, well, it's time
to pop that cherry, baby.
Because I'm going to pop that
shit like a fucking tuna can.
ALEX :Do you have any idea
what bringing a gun...
...to a burglary means?
Yeah, it gives me...
...a better chance
to defend myself, Alex.
ALEX :No, it means
you just gave this guy...
...the legal right to shoot us.
Rocky, let's go.
No, no, no, no.
I think we should stay.
We have to leave.
This is not good.
MONEY :
You don't really think just because...
...you jerk off
to her Instagram selfies...
...that makes you a Romeo?
Think again, bitch.
(GUN CLATTERS)
Fuck, I'm so out.
Alex.
(GASPS)
(DOOR CREAKS)
Who's there?
Okay, man, just chill, all right?
Look, um...
I was wasted...
...and I wandered in,
so that was my bad, all right?
So, I'm just gonna...
I'm just gonna leave, okay?
Stay right fucking there.
Don't you fucking move.
(GASPS THEN GUN COCKS)
Yeah, that's right.
I know what's in there,
and I ain't leaving without it.
You got me?
Now, you do as I say, all right?
Don't take one single step,
all right? Huh?
(PANTING)
Well, do you hear me or what?
What, are you blind and deaf
all of a sudden?
Huh?
Motherfucker, I said stop.
I think you fucking heard me.
- Sorry.
- Don't you move.
What the fuck are you doing,
you old man?
I'll fucking shoot you.
(GASPING)
Don't you fucking test me.
(GUNSHOT)
You're a fucking pussy.
(MONEY PANTING)
What are you gonna do now,
huh? Huh?
You better fucking stop. Stop!
(♪♪♪)
(MONEY GRUNTING)
(MUFFLED)
Don't make me fucking kill you, man.
(MONEY GROANING)
(MONEY GROANS THEN SPUTTERS)
(STRAINED)
Please.
Please, just let me walk.
Let me walk.
Leave me alive.
(GASPING AND MUTTERING)
Please.
How many of you are there?
What?
How many?
(BLIND MAN GRUNTS)
It's just me, man...
...all right? It's just fucking me.
Just let me go!
(CRYING)
Please let me go.
Please.
(GASPING)
Just let me go.
(MONEY PANTING)
(WHISPERING)
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Okay, I swear to God...
(♪♪♪)
(THUMPING AND SOFT CRYING)
(MUFFLED CRYING)
(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(HEAVY BREATHING CONTINUES)
(CLATTERING)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(LOCK CLATTERING)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(CLATTERING)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(ALEX GASPS SOFTLY)
(HAMMERING CONTINUES)
(♪♪♪)
(PHONE BUZZING)
(GUN COCKS)
(FOOTSTEPS SHUFFLING)
(♪♪♪)
(BUTTONS BEEP)
(WHIRS THEN BLIPS)
(METAL CREAKS)
(LOCK CLICKS)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(WIND WHISTLING)
(♪♪♪)
(GASPS)
Rocky, hey, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Maybe... Maybe we should...
...call the cops
before he does.
We'll come clean...
Wait.
What?
(BEEPS)
(BEEPING)
(WHIRS THEN BLIPS)
(GASPS)
(♪♪♪)
Oh, my God.
(BLIPPING THEN DOOR SHUTS)
There's a lot more
than 300 grand in there.
That's got to be
about a million dollars.
Okay, let's get out of here.
(♪♪♪)
The storm cellar door.
The door's bolted from the inside.
That could be our way out.
Let's go.
(GRUNTS)
(BLIND MAN GRUNTS)
(PLASTIC RUSTLING)
(GRUNTING)
(FLOORBOARD CREAKS)
(HEAVY BREATHING)
(SIGHS)
(PHONE BUZZING LOUDLY)
(BUZZING CONTINUES)
(GRUNTS)
(BODY BEING DRAGGED
ACROSS THE FLOOR)
(GRUNTING)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(♪♪♪)
(GRUNTS)
Let's go.
This way.
What?
Oh, shit.
The phone died.
Oh, fuck.
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
(DRILL WHIRRING)
(GASPS)
(SNIFFING)
(♪♪♪)
(GASPS)
(SNIFFING)
Hmm.
(♪♪♪)
(PANTING)
(BEEPS)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(♪♪♪)
(GASPING)
(DOOR SHUTS)
(BEEPS AND BLIPS)
(SHOUTS)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
ALEX :Where's the door?
- I don't know.
ALEX:
Where is it? Do you see it?
(MUFFLED SHOUTING
AND SCREAMS)
(JINGLING)
(GASPS)
(♪♪♪)
(PANTING)
(MUFFLED MOANS)
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
(MUFFLED)
Please help me! Please!
ALEX :We need to get the fuck
out of here right now.
Come on. Let's go.
Look, the door's right here.
(MUFFLED SOBBING)
(MUFFLED)
Look! Look at it!
Please!
What?
Rocky? Rocky.
Rocky, listen, listen.
Hey, that's our exit.
The door's right fucking there.
We can leave right now.
(MUFFLED)
No, no, no, no!
(♪♪♪)
She's the one
who killed his daughter.
We have to get her
out of here.
No, no, no.
Rocky, we don't have time.
We'll... We'll get out of here,
and we'll call the cops...
...and then they'll
come find her, all right?
(MUFFLED)
The safe! The safe!
There's the safe!
(HEAVY FOOTSTEPS FROM ABOVE)
(MUFFLED SOBBING)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(♪♪♪)
(PANTING)
The code
from the safe upstairs.
- You remember it?
- Um...
2978, 78, 78, 2978.
ALEX:
2-9-7-8.
Oh...
Okay, got them.
(THUDS THEN RATTLING)
He's coming.
- Hurry up.
ALEX :Okay, one more, one more.
Fuck, fuck!
I almost have it.
Almost... okay.
ROCKY : I don't care what you did.
I'll get you out of here.
ALEX:
Go, go, go!
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
(DOOR CREAKS)
ALEX :There's the door.
ROCKY : There it is.
(♪♪♪)
Are you okay?
Okay.
(GRUNTING)
ROCKY :
What's wrong?
(RATTLING)
ALEX :It's locked.
ROCKY : You have the keys.
Don't you have the keys?
Fuck.
One of these should open it.
ROCKY :
Come on.
(CLATTERING)
- Come on.
- Okay.
Oh, yes.
Come on.
(CREAKS THEN MUFFLED SCREAM)
(GASPS AND GRUNTS)
(ROCKY SCREAMS)
(ALEX & ROCKY SCREAM)
(GUNSHOTS)
(GROANING)
(♪♪♪)
(BLOOD DRIPPING)
(SLIGHT GASP)
(ALEX GRUNTS)
(BOTH PANTING)
(GLASS BREAKS)
He shot her.
(BLOOD SLOSHES)
(GASPS)
No...
(♪♪♪)
Oh.
(SOBS)
No!
Oh! Oh! Oh!
(SOBBING)
My baby.
No!
(♪♪♪)
(SOBBING AND GRUNTING)
(KEYS JINGLING)
We have to go back upstairs.
Yeah, listen.
Listen, okay?
These keys, they match
the locks on the front door.
All right?
If we get up there,
we can get out.
Okay?
(CLICKS)
(♪♪♪)
Let's go now.
(GUNSHOT)
(ROCKY PANTING)
Shit.
(GUNSHOTS)
(ROCKY SHRIEKS)
(PANTING)
Alex?
(GUNSHOT)
(GASPING)
(PANTING)
(SPUTTERS)
(CLANGING)
(SHORT, RAPID BREATHING)
(PANTING)
(LOW SHUFFLING FOOTSTEPS)
(FOOTSTEPS CONTINUE)
ALEX:
Rocky?
(GUNSHOT)
(SLIGHT GASP)
(PANTING)
(SIGHS)
(ALEX GRUNTING)
(GUN CLICKING)
Please don't...
(GUN CLATTERS)
No, please...
(CHOKING)
(BELLOWING)
(SHUFFLING FOOTSTEPS)
ALEX:
Rocky?
Alex! Alex.
Rocky, Rocky.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
This way. This way, come on.
This way, come on, come on, come on.
ROCKY :
Okay.
ALEX:
Oh, come on. Where am I?
Where is it?
Light. I see light!
Come on, come on.
(RATTLING)
(ROCKY GASPS)
(ALEX GRUNTING)
Don't...
...run.
(GROWLING)
Rocky...
(KEYS JINGLE)
...go to the door.
Try the blue key.
- Do it.
- Okay.
(DOG SNARLING)
ALEX:
Easy.
Easy, buddy.
(GRUNTS AND DOG
CONTINUES GROWLING)
Fuck.
(ALEX BREATHING UNSTEADILY)
- Rocky?
- Yeah.
(GRUNTS)
- Come on.
- Easy, buddy.
Easy...
(GROWLING STOPS)
It's okay.
(ROCKY GRUNTS)
Okay, that's a good boy.
That's good.
All right.
That's...
That's good. That's good.
(POUNDING THEN DOG SNARLING)
Oh. Fuck.
Rocky! Rocky.
Run, now. Go, go, go!
Upstairs, now. Go. Go, go!
(CONTINUES SNARLING)
Go! Hurry, hurry!
Go!
There's a door! Come on!
Let's go.
(DOG BARKING)
Hey, move this.
Come on.
(GRUNTS)
Damn.
- Are those blocked up too?
- Yeah.
ALEX:
We're trapped in here.
(HEAVY FOOTSTEPS)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(♪♪♪)
(CYLINDER SNAPS)
(CLICKING)
(SNAPS)
Rocky, the remote.
Do you have it with you?
Come on. Okay.
(REMOTE BEEPS)
- What are you doing?
- I'm pressing the panic button.
If I manage to get in range,
the system will call 911...
- ...and the police will come.
- No. Wait, we can't go to jail.
No. No, we won't. Okay?
This is robbery
versus kidnapping and murder.
The police won't care about us...
...or why we were here
in the first place.
We would have helped them
get this guy.
But then we wouldn't
keep the money.
(LOUD BANGING)
- We need to get out of this room.
- Up there.
(FOOTSTEPS)
(BANGING CONTINUES)
Go!
(ALEX GRUNTING)
(CREAKS)
(PANTING)
Alex!
ALEX:
What are you doing? Go!
(ROCKY PANTING
AND GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(DOG SNARLING)
No! No, no!
(ALEX YELLS)
(PANTING AND GRUNTING)
(GLASS CRACKING)
(GRUNTS)
(DOG BARKS FAINTLY)
(DOG SNIFFING)
(SNARLS SOFTLY)
(SNARLING)
(GRUNTING)
(♪♪♪)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(DOG GROWLS)
(GRUNTS)
(DOG BARKS THEN ROCKY GASPS)
(GRUNTING AND
BARKING IN DISTANCE)
(♪♪♪)
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTS)
(GLASS CREAKING)
(GLASS TINKLES)
(SIGHS)
(GLASS CRACKING)
(♪♪♪)
(GROANING)
(GLASS TINKLING)
(BEEPS)
(GRUNTS QUIETLY)
(WHEEZING)
(WHIMPERING)
(WHEEZING CONTINUES)
(♪♪♪)
(SWITCH CLICKING)
(CLOTHING RUSTLES)
(MUFFLED GRUNT)
(INHALES)
(♪♪♪)
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
(BANGING)
(HEAVY FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(BONE CRUNCHES
THEN BLIND MAN SCREAMS)
(ALEX GRUNTING)
Oh!
(ALEX SCREAMS)
(BLIND MAN GRUNTS)
(CHOKING)
(GROANS)
(WASH CYCLE STARTS)
(GRUNTING)
(WASHER WHIRRING LOUDLY)
(GROANS)
Hey!
(WASH CYCLE FADES)
Huh, huh!
(ALEX GROANING AND GASPING)
(CHOKING)
(BLIND MAN GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
(♪♪♪)
(SPUTTERING)
(BEEPS)
(WHEEZING)
(BLADE CLANGS)
(BLIND MAN GRUNTS)
(FAN TURNS ON)
(GASPS)
(QUIETLY WHIMPERS)
(FAN BLADES WHIRRING)
(GROANS)
Ah...
(GROANING)
(GROANING AND GULPING)
(WHIMPERS)
(♪♪♪)
(HISSES IN PAIN)
(GRUNTING AND PANTING)
(AIR WHISTLING)
(INSECTS TRILLING)
(RATTLING)
(GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
Ah.
(CLANGS)
(GRUNTS THEN GATE CLANGS)
(CLANGING)
(THUDS)
(SIGHS AND GASPS)
(♪♪♪)
(PANTING)
(SHRIEKS)
(GASPING)
(BOTH GRUNT)
(SHRIEKS THEN GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(ROCKY GROANING WEAKLY)
(GASPING)
(♪♪♪)
(ELECTRIC BUZZING)
(SIGHS)
(CHAIN RATTLING)
(WHIMPERS)
(SOBBING)
Please, let me go.
Please, let me go!
I...
I understand you.
She killed your daughter.
You wanted her to pay.
I understand that.
I won't tell anyone.
You understand nothing.
Only a parent could know the...
...bond between a father
and his child.
She should have
gone to prison, but...
...rich girls don't go to jail.
None of this is going
to bring your daughter back.
That's not really true.
Cindy took my child
away from me.
I thought...
...it's only fair...
...that she give me a new one.
She was pregnant with my baby.
You killed them both.
- No.
- Well, they would be alive...
...if you hadn't broken
into my home.
No.
You have
to be held accountable.
(♪♪♪)
(ALEX WHEEZING)
(GRUNTS QUIETLY)
(DOG BARKING)
(PANTING AND DOG SNARLING)
(♪♪♪)
(VALVE SQUEAKS)
(HINGE SQUEAKS THEN LID SLAMS)
(WHIMPERS)
(PANTING)
(GASPING)
(KEYS JINGLING)
(BREATHING RAGGEDLY)
(DOOR CREAKS)
Please.
Please, God.
God?
There's no God.
It's a joke.
It's a bad joke.
You tell me what God
would allow this.
What are you doing?
(CREAKING)
I'm not a rapist.
I never forced myself on her.
Stop.
I promised I would set her free...
...just as soon
as she gave me a child.
But now she's gone.
But I'm done waiting.
Ah! No. No, no.
(SCISSORS SNIP)
(GASPS)
You can't do this to me.
There's nothing a man cannot do...
...once he accepts the fact
that there is no God.
ROCKY :
No!
No. No, no, no, no!
(SOBBING)
No!
BLIND MAN :
You're strong.
(ROCKY WHIMPERING)
You're young.
You'll breed well.
No. Get away from me.
No! No!
No!
(SOBBING)
No...
Stop.
BLIND MAN :
Shh, Shh, shh.
Nine months...
...and I will give you
your life back.
(GASPING)
(CRUNCHING)
(EXHALES)
(ALEX GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(STRAPS SLIDING)
(GASPS)
(WHEEZING)
ALEX:
Are you okay?
Rocky. Okay, yeah.
Rocky, did he...?
Did he hurt you?
Rocky?
You fucking bastard.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Fuck you!
(GAGS AND CHOKES)
ALEX :Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hey, Rocky. Rocky.
Rocky. Rocky, it's over.
Come on.
How's that taste?
- Now what?
- Come on.
You're going to rot in prison
for what you've done.
Rocky, we can't
involve the cops now.
If we steal a million in cash...
...and then lead the cops here,
he'll tell them about us.
Our blood is all over.
They'll get to us in a second.
You got what you came for.
(GAGS)
Now take it.
Get out of my house!
(♪♪♪)
Look, he's buying our silence.
He needs us to take the money.
It's one or the other.
Whatever you choose,
I'm with you.
- Okay.
- This one.
Let's get out of here.
I need to find the key.
All right.
That key won't...
I got it.
(GUNSHOTS THEN ROCKY GASPS)
(GASPS)
(♪♪♪)
(BODY THUDS)
(PANTING)
You're worthless out here.
(DOG SNARLS)
Fuck.
(DOG SNARLING
AND ROCKY PANTING)
Shit!
(BARKING)
(DOG WHINES)
(SNARLING)
(GROWLING)
(BARKING)
(DOG GROWLING)
(BARKING CONTINUES)
(WHINES THEN BARKS)
(HEAVY THUD THEN SNARLING)
Fuck.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
Ah, fuck!
(SOBBING)
(DOG BARKS AND GROWLS)
(♪♪♪)
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
(LATCH CLICKS THEN LID CREAKS)
(GASPS)
(BARKING AND GROWLING)
(♪♪♪)
(MUFFLED GROWLING)
(DOG WHINES)
(SNARLING)
(BARKING)
(SHRIEKS)
(DOG WHIMPERS)
(BARKING)
(GASPING)
(MUFFLED BARKING)
(♪♪♪)
(GASPS)
(ROCKY GRUNTS)
(♪♪♪)
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN
THEN ROCKY GASPS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(BLIND MAN PANTS)
(KEYS JINGLE THEN LOCK CLICKS)
I'm sorry, Alex.
I'm so sorry.
(♪♪♪)
(PANTING)
(BEEPS)
(BUTTON CLICKING)
(ALARM PAD WHIRS)
(ALARM PAD BEEPING)
(ALARM BLARING)
No!
(SCREAMS)
Don't!
(GROANING)
Ah, no...
No. Ah...
(GRUNTS)
(GUNSHOT)
(ALARM CONTINUES)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
Ah! Don't...
(GUNSHOT)
(GROANING CONTINUES)
(SCREAMS)
(GUNSHOTS)
(GUN CLICKS)
No.
(SHELLS CLATTERING AND
ALARM CONTINUES BLARING)
(ALARM SHUTS OFF
THEN FLOORBOARD CREAKS)
(CLICKS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(ROCKY SCREAMS AND GRUNTS)
(GUNSHOT)
(PANTING)
(♪♪♪)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(PANTING)
(SIGHS)
(SIREN APPROACHING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(♪♪♪)
What is that?
You and me at the beach.
ANNOUNCER (OVER PA):
Train service to Los Angeles...
...will be boarding shortly
on platform six.
REPORTER (ON TV): This house
behind me on Buena Vista...
...belongs to a retired Army vet...
...who fought
for our country in Iraq...
...and lost his sight as a result
of a grenade splinter.
Last night, two burglars
broke into his home...
...and attempted to rob
and brutally attack him.
This visually impaired man
was able to defend himself...
...shooting and killing
both his attackers on the spot.
Now, the man did
sustain some injuries...
...but doctors say he is
in stable condition.
He'll be released
from the hospital soon...
...and able to return to his home.
No goods were reported stolen
by the victim.
I'm Dayna Clark, WADL News.
(♪♪♪)
***********************
® Arun's collections ®