Yes.
You failed.
I didn't.
The gun is in my hand.
I thought I had it.
Sorry, Father. I'll make it next time.
Never take anything for granted.
God will take it from you.
Is God bad?
God is fair.
You almost got me, didn't you, boy?
Did I get my white hair from you
or from Mom?
From your mother.
I can't believe
we don't have any pictures of her.
Everything was destroyed in the fire.
You know that.
I could only save you.
Was she beautiful?
She was smart.
Like you.
How many did I get?
All of them.
So I get to go to town today, right?
You failed survival.
It's been three months.
Plus, I just gave you a killer haircut.
Trust me.
You need to pass all your tests first.
All right, apart from the usual,
I have an order of five ferns,
two ficuses,
and the Columnea grandiosa.
Gloriosa.
Am I taking Phoenix today?
Not today.
It's been a while.
I said, no.
You either loosen up that leash,
or sooner or later, she'll bite it off.
Go with Hernandez.
Back by sunset!
I will.
Hey, Hernandez.
Hey, gorgeous.
Fly, bird
All across the mighty sea
Sing, girl
Sing your little heart out for me
That's beautiful.
You made that up?
I think my mom sang it to me
when I was little.
That first part's all I remember.
You wanna pay her a visit?
-But my father doesn't want--
-I won't tell if you don't.
Fly, bird
Police have issued a statewide alert
for this man, Dr. Thomas Hanniman.
He's believed to be running
an organ trafficking ring
in the Detroit area.
Thank you.
The alarming number of abductions
has recently risen in the city.
This is a developing story.
We'll update you
as more information comes to light.
Now let's take a look
at the weekend forecast.
Good morning, everyone.
I'm meteorologist Jerry...
Everyone, pull.
Help me.
It's stuck.
Hey, wanna try something?
Okay.
Do it.
Faster, faster.
I'm getting dizzy.
Hey, guys. Come on in. Dinner.
I don't wanna go inside.
Come on, guys!
"Covenant Shelter."
Race you.
Hey, wait up!
You having fun?
All right, let's go.
I need to pee.
Okay, well, be quick.
I don't wanna anger your father.
Fly, bird
All across the mighty sea
Sing, girl
Sing your little heart out for me
Wow, you're pretty.
What's your name, gorgeous?
Mine's Raylan.
I don't care.
I need to go. My father's waiting for me.
I snap my fingers
and he'll bite your testicles off.
Okay.
Well, I'm sorry if I scared you.
Who said you did?
I'll see you around.
Come on, Shadow.
You okay?
Yes.
Just a weirdo.
Yeah.
No shortage of those around here.
Follow them.
Thanks, Hernandez.
We had a lot of fun today.
I'll take her again next week
if you're okay with it.
No.
Today was enough.
-It's none of my business, but--
-You're right.
It's not.
You're a bad man.
A man who's done terrible things.
At least, I know you think that.
Just like sometimes I do about myself.
War changes us all.
No soul returns holy from it.
Don't make her pay for that.
Thanks.
You mind moving your vehicle
off the road, please?
This is...
This is the only road back to town.
You served?
Yeah.
We all did too.
-Iraq?
-Yeah.
Dishonorably discharged
from a dishonorable war.
I'd say that makes us honorable somehow.
Wouldn't you?
No.
Can you move your truck off the road now?
Sure, baby.
Whatever you want.
Lessons next month.
Okay.
I wanna go to school next year.
-This is school--
-A real school, with other kids like me.
Home school is safer.
I don't wanna be safe.
I wanna be normal. I wanna have friends.
-I wanna live a--
-Enough!
Enough.
I already lost a daughter once.
I'm not losing you.
But I'm lonely.
You have no idea what it is to be alone.
You have me.
You're not enough.
"Covenant Shelter.
Your new home awaits you."
Shadow?
Shadow.
Oh, God.
The box! Now!
Go!
Go get the girl.
Open the door.
Open up!
What the fuck?
Hang on, brother.
Open your jaw.
Stay still.
Breathe, brother.
The guy's a Navy SEAL.
Fucking dead SEAL, bro.
Better get out of there, kid.
He's down there with you!
Blind fuck is down there!
Call Raylan.
Metal box is almost full of water.
You prefer to see the kid alive...
you come in here.
You think I'm fucking with you?
No.
There's a live wire
about to reach the water.
Come out, or she's fried!
Clever fuck.
No guns, huh?
No problem.
You're tough.
But you're done.
What the fuck?
Yo, bro.
Breathe.
Come on, breathe.
The old blind man did this?
Let's go.
I can walk.
I said, I can walk.
What's happening?
Cover the exits.
What the fuck?
They're still down here.
What's happening?
-Who are they?
-I don't know.
You don't need to be afraid, little girl.
This has all just been
one big misunderstanding.
It's not me you need to be scared of...
but the man standing next to you.
Now, I don't know who he is.
But I know who he's not.
Should I tell her or you?
Finish him, bro.
No!
-Dad! Dad, wake up.
-Aren't you something?
Let me go!
Come on.
No, it's okay.
Yeah, there you go.
There you go.
You don't remember me, do you?
Maybe this will help.
See?
What...?
Years ago, there was a fire in our house.
Cops blamed me.
I spent eight years in prison,
wondering if I'd ever see you again.
I didn't even know
if you were dead or alive.
This creep here must have...
found you and kept you for himself.
Up next in local news,
a meth lab caught fire
in west Detroit this morning.
Police were able
to arrest the primary suspect.
The man was taken into custody
and could face charges
for a large number of crimes committed
over the past several years.
You have no idea how much
I've been waiting for this moment.
Did he hurt you?
But he did steal you away from me,
and now he must die, you understand?
Kill him.
-No.
-Fuck are you doing?
Not in front of my kid. Do it outside.
Wake up, you blind fuck.
Fuck!
Fucking coward.
Take her to the truck
while I hunt this motherfucker. Let's go.
-Let me go!
-What's wrong with you?
Fucking wanna go home?
I don't care who you are.
I'm gonna teach you some fucking manners.
You ungrateful, little bitch.
No.
Stop.
Please!
Stop!
Move. Go, go.
Move. Now.
Move!
I'm sorry, man.
-He's back in the house.
- I know. He wants us to follow him.
Enough of these silly games.
It's his jacket.
Attaboy.
Wait.
Stop.
Is it true?
Move.
What's my real name?
Get over here now!
When's my birthday?
-My real one?
-Stop it!
No, you stop it!
Go!
Hey.
Phoenix!
Calm down, girl.
Calm down.
Stay.
Put her in the truck.
What are you doing?
-Your dog's in there.
-Dog's dead.
You don't know that.
You wanna go and find out?
No!
Good morning, princess.
How you feeling?
You all right?
Wanna sit with me?
Come, sit with me. Come on.
Yeah.
There you go.
Door's open.
Not a prisoner anymore.
You mean, I can go?
If you want.
Or you can stay here
and find out who you really are.
Do I have any brothers or sisters?
Unfortunately, no.
When's my birthday?
February 20th.
What was my mother's name?
Josephine.
Do I look like her?
Yeah.
You do.
Tara.
That's your real name.
Everything that man told you is a lie.
What happened to him?
He got what he deserved.
Hey. I'm not sorry.
You shouldn't be either.
I wanna go.
Where? Where you gonna go?
There's a shelter I know.
Like I said,
you're not a prisoner anymore.
Fly, bird
Out across the
Great wide sea
Sing, girl
Sing your little heart out for me
Fly, bird
Fly across the mighty cliffs
Sleep, girl
Mama's gonna give you a good-night kiss
Mom?
Like I said...
everything he told you was a lie.
My Tara?
You... got so big.
Can I hug you?
Come here.
Oh, God.
Oh, baby, we missed you so much.
There you are.
You were such a beautiful baby.
Get it out.
Get it out. Come on.
There you go. There you go.
-There you go.
-Sorry.
Nothing to apologize for.
Are you okay?
The same fire that destroyed our family,
it burned up my insides.
Mom and Dad used to have a...
kitchen...
in the basement of our house,
where we used to cook.
It was for our business.
Are you thirsty?
Tara?
I'm dying.
What?
The smoke from the chemicals...
poisoned my blood
and badly damaged my heart.
I don't think I have much time left.
Is there anything you can do?
I heard you left flowers for me
at our old house.
Is that true?
Weren't you wishing
your mama was healthy and alive?
Yes.
I need a new heart, baby.
But not just any heart.
Doctor said, it has to be a...
It must be a...
compatible donor.
Like a direct relative.
You hold the gift
that can save your mama's life.
And, baby, I need that gift.
We'll finally be together as one.
You'll live on in me.
Go home.
Go away.
I said, go.
Stay.
Go home.
I hope you understand
the high risks of this procedure.
I think I pay you enough.
Shut up and do your job.
Why is she still alive?
If she's dead so is her heart.
I can't keep it fresh long enough
without the proper equipment.
I have to cut it out of her
while she's still breathing.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
Thank you.
What's wrong with you?
What they're doing in there is wrong.
She's our cook.
If she dies, there's no product.
If there's no product, there's no us.
Still fucking wrong.
Hey.
You ready?
Let's go.
What the fuck?
Go check it out.
You killed my brother!
You blind freak!
I'm gonna carve your fucking head open
like a pumpkin, man.
This is for Shadow.
Oh, fuck.
No!
It's him.
How the hell did he find...?
Disloyal fucking animal.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, everything's okay.
-Everything's okay, I promise.
-Baby, should I be worried?
No, no. Not at all.
I got you. I got you.
I can't work without power.
Change of plans, then.
Pack your things. Bring the girl.
Raul.
-Bring the men. Kill the blind man.
-How many of us?
All of you!
Let's go.
They're gonna kill her.
And that's not cool with me.
They're leaving now.
The ladder behind you leads
directly to them. You'd better hurry.
Go left.
That way.
He'll kill you all.
Fuck it. I'm out.
Hey, hey!
Hey!
Good morning, motherfucker.
Baby.
It's okay.
Stop it.
Baby?
Hello?
I can't see you.
Baby?
Someone's here! Hurry!
I got you, motherfucker.
No.
No!
Phoenix!
Now...
you're gonna see
what I see.
Phoenix?
Stop.
Stop!
You...
You mustn't come near me.
Everything he said...
is true.
I am no father.
I have killed.
I...
have raped.
am nothing.
Nothing...
but a monster.
And you...
cannot be around me.
Ever.
So go.
Now. Go.
Go!
Oh, God.
Tara?
No.
Please.
No, no, no.
Let me help you.
I can save you.
You already have.
Hey.
Think there's room for one more?
I'm sure there is.
What's your name?
My name is Phoenix.