8 ANS PLUS TARD
Yes.
You failed.
Tu as échoué.
I didn't.
Non.
The gun is in my hand.
J'ai le pistolet en main.
I thought I had it.
J'ai cru que je l'avais.
Sorry, Father. I'll make it next time. Never take anything for granted.
Désolée, papa. La prochaine fois.
Ne tiens rien pour acquis.
God will take it from you.
Dieu te le prendra.
Is God bad?
Dieu est méchant ?
God is fair.
Dieu est juste.
You almost got me, didn't you, boy?
T'as failli m'avoir, mon chien.
Did I get my white hair from you or from Mom?
Ma mèche blanche, je la tiens de toi ou de maman ?
From your mother.
De ta mère.
I can't believe we don't have any pictures of her.
C'est dingue qu'on n'ait aucune photo d'elle.
Everything was destroyed in the fire.
Tout a été détruit dans l'incendie.
You know that.
Tu le sais bien.
I could only save you.
Y a que toi que j'ai pu sauver.
Was she beautiful?
Elle était belle ?
She was smart.
Elle était intelligente.
Like you.
Comme toi.
How many did I get? All of them.
- J'en ai réussi combien ? - Tous.
So I get to go to town today, right?
Alors, je peux aller en ville ?
You failed survival.
Tu as raté l'épreuve de survie.
It's been three months.
Ça fait trois mois.
Plus, I just gave you a killer haircut.
Et je t'ai fait une coupe de malade.
Trust me.
Fais-moi confiance.
You need to pass all your tests first.
Réussis toutes les épreuves, d'abord.
All right, apart from the usual, I have an order of five ferns,
En plus de la commande habituelle,
two ficuses, and the Columnea grandiosa.
il me faut cinq fougères, deux ficus
et la columnea grandiosa.
Gloriosa.
Am I taking Phoenix today?
J'emmène Phoenix ?
Not today. It's been a while.
Pas aujourd'hui.
Ça fait un bout de temps.
I said, no.
J'ai dit non.
You either loosen up that leash,
Lâchez un peu la laisse,
or sooner or later, she'll bite it off.
sinon, un jour, elle la rongera.
Go with Hernandez.
Va avec Hernandez.
Back by sunset!
Rentre avant la nuit.
I will.
Promis.
Hey, Hernandez.
Hey, gorgeous.
♪ Fly, bird ♪
Vole, petit oiseau
♪ All across the mighty sea ♪
Au-dessus de l'océan majestueux
♪ Sing, girl ♪ ♪ Sing your little heart out for me ♪
Chante, petite fille
De tout ton coeur pour moi
That's beautiful.
C'est joli.
You made that up?
Tu l'as inventée ?
I think my mom sang it to me when I was little.
Ma mère me la chantait quand j'étais petite.
That first part's all I remember.
Je me rappelle que du début.
You wanna pay her a visit?
Tu veux lui rendre visite ?
- But my father doesn't want... - I won't tell if you don't.
Mon père veut pas.
Je dirai rien si tu dis rien.
Je t'aime, maman
♪ Fly, bird ♪ ♪ Fly, bird ♪
Vole, petit oiseau
Police have issued a statewide alert for Dr. Thomas Hanniman.
La police recherche le Dr Thomas Hanniman,
He's believed to be running an organ trafficking ring in the Detroit area.
soupçonné de trafic d'organes
Thank you.
dans la région de Détroit.
The alarming number of abductions has recently risen in the city.
Un nombre inquiétant d'enlèvements a été constaté.
This is a developing story. We'll update you as more information comes to light. Now let's take a look at the weekend forecast.
L'affaire est en cours, nous vous tiendrons informés.
Good morning, everyone. I'm meteorologist Jerry...
Et maintenant, la météo du week-end.
Everyone, pull.
Help me.
It's stuck.
Hey, wanna try something?
On essaie un truc ?
Okay.
D'accord.
Do it.
Démarre.
Faster, faster. I'm getting dizzy.
- Plus vite ! - J'ai le vertige !
Hey, guys. Come on in. Dinner.
Allez, on rentre. On va dîner.
I don't wanna go inside.
J'ai pas envie de rentrer.
Come on, guys!
Allez !
"Covenant Shelter."
Le refuge de l'Alliance...
- Race you. - Hey, wait up!
- You having fun? - Mm-hm.
Tu t'es amusée ?
All right, let's go.
Allez, on s'en va.
I need to pee. Okay, well, be quick. I don't wanna anger your father.
Je dois aller faire pipi.
Dépêche-toi. Je veux pas fâcher ton père.
♪ Fly, bird ♪ ♪ Fly, bird ♪
Vole, petit oiseau
♪ All across the mighty sea ♪ ♪ Sing, girl ♪
Au-dessus de l'océan majestueux
♪ Sing your little heart out for me ♪
Chante, petite fille
De tout ton coeur pour moi
Wow, you're pretty.
T'es jolie, toi.
What's your name, gorgeous? Mine's Raylan.
Comment tu t'appelles, beauté ?
Moi, c'est Raylan.
I don't care.
Je m'en fiche.
I need to go. My father's waiting for me.
Je dois y aller. Mon père m'attend.
I snap my fingers and he'll bite your testicles off.
Je claque des doigts
Wow.
et il vous arrache les testicules.
Okay.
Well, I'm sorry if I scared you.
Désolé si je t'ai fait peur.
Who said you did?
Qui a dit ça ?
I'll see you around.
A plus.
Come on, Shadow.
Viens, Shadow.
You okay? Yes.
Ça va ?
Just a weirdo.
Juste un type bizarre.
Yeah.
No shortage of those around here.
C'est pas ce qui manque, par ici.
Follow them.
Suis-les.
Thanks, Hernandez.
Merci, Hernandez.
We had a lot of fun today.
On s'est bien amusées.
I'll take her again next week if you're okay with it.
On peut le refaire la semaine prochaine.
No.
Non.
Today was enough.
Aujourd'hui, ça suffit.
It's none of my business, but...
Ça me regarde pas, mais...
You're right.
Exact.
It's not.
Ça vous regarde pas.
You're a bad man.
Vous êtes un homme mauvais.
A man who's done terrible things.
Vous avez commis des horreurs.
At least, I know you think that.
En tout cas, vous le pensez.
Just like sometimes I do about myself.
C'est ce que je pense de moi, parfois.
War changes us all.
La guerre nous transforme.
No soul returns holy from it.
Aucune âme n'en ressort pure.
Don't make her pay for that.
C'est pas à elle de payer.
Thanks.
Merci.
You mind moving your vehicle off the road, please?
Vous pourriez dégager la route ?
This is...
This is the only road back to town.
C'est la seule qui mène à la ville.
You served?
Ex-militaire ?
Yeah.
We all did too.
Nous aussi.
- Iraq? - Yeah.
Irak ?
Dishonorably discharged from a dishonorable war.
Renvoyés pour déshonneur d'une guerre déshonorante.
I'd say that makes us honorable somehow. Wouldn't you?
Ça nous rend honorables. Tu crois pas ?
No.
Non.
Can you move your truck off the road now?
Vous pouvez bouger votre pick-up ?
Sure, baby.
Bien sûr, ma belle.
Whatever you want.
Tout ce que tu veux.
Lessons next month.
Les cours pour le mois prochain.
Okay.
D'accord.
- I wanna go to school next year. - Huh.
Je veux aller à l'école, l'année prochaine.
- This is school... - A real school, with other kids like me.
- Tu y es déjà. - La vraie, avec d'autres enfants.
Homeschool is safer.
Tu es en sécurité, ici.
I don't wanna be safe.
Je veux pas être en sécurité.
I wanna be normal. I wanna have friends.
Je veux être normale.
- I wanna live a... - Enough!
Je veux des amis, je veux...
Ça suffit !
Enough.
Ça suffit.
I already lost a daughter once. I'm not losing you.
J'ai déjà perdu une fille. Je ne veux pas te perdre, toi aussi.
But I'm lonely.
Mais je me sens seule.
You have no idea what it is to be alone.
Tu ne sais pas ce que c'est, la solitude.
You have me.
Tu m'as, moi.
You're not enough.
C'est pas assez.
"Covenant Shelter.
"Le refuge de l'Alliance.
Your new home awaits you."
"Ta nouvelle maison t'attend."
Shadow?
Shadow ?
Shadow.
Oh, God.
Mon Dieu.
The box! Now!
Le container ! Vite !
Go!
Vas-y !
Go get the girl.
Rattrape la gamine !
Open the door.
Ouvre !
Open up!
What the fuck?
Putain !
Oh!
Hang on, brother.
Accroche-toi.
Open your jaw.
Ouvre les mâchoires.
Stay still.
Bouge pas.
Breathe, brother.
Respire.
The guy's a Navy SEAL.
C'est un soldat des forces spéciales.
Fucking dead SEAL, bro.
Un soldat qui va crever.
Better get out of there, kid.
Je te conseille de sortir.
He's down there with you!
Il est près de toi !
Blind fuck is down there!
L'aveugle est en bas.
Call Raylan.
Appelle Raylan.
Metal box is almost full of water.
Le container est presque plein.
You prefer to see the kid alive...
Si tu veux revoir la petite,
you come in here.
tu viens ici.
You think I'm fucking with you?
Je déconne pas !
No.
There's a live wire about to reach the water. Come out, or she's fried!
Un fil électrique va toucher l'eau.
Montre-toi ou elle grille.
Clever fuck.
Pas con, le mec.
No guns, huh?
T'es pas armé, hein ?
No problem.
Pas de souci.
You're tough.
T'es un dur.
But you're done.
Mais t'es foutu.
What the fuck?
C'est quoi, ce bordel ?
Yo, bro.
Salut !
Breathe.
Respire.
Come on, breathe.
Breathe.
The old blind man did this?
C'est l'aveugle qui t'a fait ça ?
Uh-huh.
Let's go.
On y va.
I can walk.
Je peux marcher.
I said, I can walk.
Je te dis que je peux marcher.
What's happening?
Qu'est-ce qui se passe ?
Cover the exits.
Bloquez les sorties.
What the fuck?
C'est quoi, putain ?
They're still down here.
Ils sont toujours ici.
What's happening?
Il se passe quoi ?
- Who are they? - I don't know.
- C'est qui ? - J'en sais rien.
You don't need to be afraid, little girl.
N'aie pas peur, petite.
This has all just been one big misunderstanding.
Ce n'est qu'un énorme malentendu.
It's not me you need to be scared of...
C'est pas moi dont tu dois avoir peur.
but the man standing next to you.
C'est de l'homme à côté de toi.
Now, I don't know who he is.
Je sais pas qui il est.
But I know who he's not.
Mais je sais qui il n'est pas.
Should I tell her or you?
Qui lui dit, toi ou moi ?
Finish him, bro.
Achève-le !
No!
Non !
- Dad! Dad, wake up. - Aren't you something?
Papa !
Sacrée gamine.
Let me go!
Lâchez-moi !
Come on.
Viens.
No, it's okay.
T'inquiète.
Yeah, there you go.
Oui, voilà.
There you go.
You don't remember me, do you?
Tu te souviens vraiment pas de moi ?
Maybe this will help.
Et ça, ça t'aide ?
See?
Tu vois ?
What...?
Years ago, there was a fire in our house.
Il y a des années, notre maison a brûlé.
Cops blamed me.
Les flics m'ont accusé.
I spent eight years in prison, wondering if I'd ever see you again.
J'ai passé huit ans en prison à me demander si je te reverrais.
I didn't even know if you were dead or alive.
Je savais pas si t'étais encore en vie.
This creep here must have... found you and kept you for himself.
Ce taré a dû te trouver et il t'a gardée pour lui.
Up next in local news,
Information locale :
a meth lab caught fire in west Detroit this morning. Police were able to arrest the primary suspect.
un labo de crystal meth a pris feu à Détroit, ce matin.
The man was taken into custody and could face charges
La police a pu arrêter le principal suspect.
Il a été placé en détention et devra répondre
for a large number of crimes committed over the past several years. You have no idea how much I've been waiting for this moment.
de nombreux crimes commis ces dernières années.
J'attends ce moment depuis si longtemps.
Did he hurt you?
Il t'a fait du mal ?
But he did steal you away from me, and now he must die, you understand?
Il t'a volée à moi, il doit mourir. Tu comprends ?
Kill him.
Tue-le.
- No. - Fuck are you doing? Not in front of my kid. Do it outside.
Qu'est-ce que tu fous ?
Pas devant ma gamine. Dehors.
Wake up, you blind fuck.
Réveille-toi, gros con d'aveugle !
Fuck!
Fucking coward.
Couille molle !
Take her to the truck while I hunt this motherfucker. Let's go.
Mettez-la dans le pick-up, je vais trouver cet enculé.
- Let me go! - What's wrong with you?
Qu'est-ce qui te prend ?
Fucking wanna go home?
Tu veux rentrer chez toi ?
I don't care who you are.
Rien à foutre de qui t'es.
I'm gonna teach you some fucking manners.
Je vais t'apprendre la politesse !
You ungrateful little bitch.
Petite conne.
No.
Stop.
Arrête !
Please!
S'il te plaît !
Stop!
Arrête !
Move. Go, go.
Bougez-vous, allez !
Move. Now.
Move!
Avance !
I'm sorry, man.
Je suis désolé.
- He's back in the house. - I know. He wants us to follow him.
- Il est retourné dans la maison. - Il veut qu'on le suive.
Enough of these silly games.
On arrête les conneries.
It's his jacket.
C'est sa veste.
Attaboy.
Cherche !
Wait. Stop.
Attends, arrête.
Is it true?
C'est vrai ?
Move.
Avance.
What's my real name?
Quel est mon vrai nom ?
Get over here now!
Viens ici !
When's my birthday? - My real one? - Stop it!
C'est quand, mon anniversaire, le vrai ?
Arrête !
No, you stop it!
Toi, arrête !
Go!
Sauve-toi !
Hey.
Phoenix!
Phoenix !
Calm down, girl.
Calme-toi.
Calm down.
Stay.
Bouge pas.
Put her in the truck.
Mets-la dans le pick-up.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What are you doing?
Qu'est-ce que tu fais ?
- Your dog's in there. - Dog's dead.
- Ton chien est là-dedans. - Il est mort.
You don't know that.
T'en sais rien.
You wanna go and find out?
Tu veux aller voir ?
No!
Good morning, princess.
Bonjour, princesse.
How you feeling?
Comment tu te sens ?
You all right?
Ça va ?
Wanna sit with me?
Tu t'assieds ?
Come, sit with me. Come on.
Allez, viens là.
Yeah.
There you go. There you go.
Voilà.
Yeah.
Door's open.
La porte est ouverte.
Not a prisoner anymore.
T'es plus prisonnière.
You mean, I can go?
Ça veut dire... que je peux partir ?
If you want.
Si tu veux.
Or you can stay here and find out who you really are.
Ou alors tu restes,
pour savoir qui tu es vraiment.
Do I have any brothers or sisters?
J'ai des frères et soeurs ?
Unfortunately, no.
Malheureusement, non.
When's my birthday?
C'est quand, mon anniversaire ?
February 20th.
Le 20 février.
What was my mother's name?
Ma mère s'appelait comment ?
Josephine.
Do I look like her?
Je lui ressemble ?
Yeah.
You do.
Oui.
Tara.
That's your real name.
C'est ton vrai prénom.
Tara.
Tara...
Everything that man told you is a lie.
Ce type n'a fait que te mentir.
What happened to him?
Qu'est-ce qu'il est devenu ?
He got what he deserved.
Il a eu ce qu'il méritait.
Hey. I'm not sorry. You shouldn't be either.
Je regrette rien. Tu devrais faire pareil.
I wanna go.
Je veux partir.
Where? Where you gonna go?
Pour aller où ?
There's a shelter I know.
Je connais un refuge.
Like I said, you're not a prisoner anymore.
Je te l'ai dit, t'es plus prisonnière.
♪ Fly, bird ♪
Vole, petit oiseau
♪ Out across the ♪
Au-dessus...
♪ Great wide sea ♪
de l'océan infini
♪ Sing, girl ♪
Chante, petite fille
♪ Sing your little heart out for me ♪
De tout ton coeur pour moi
♪ Fly, bird ♪
Vole, petit oiseau
♪ Fly across the mighty cliffs ♪
Au-dessus de l'océan majestueux
♪ Sleep, girl ♪
Dors, petite fille
♪ Mama's gonna give you A good-night kiss ♪
Maman te fera un bisou pour la nuit
Mom?
Maman ?
Like I said...
Je te l'ai dit.
everything he told you was a lie.
Il a fait que te mentir.
My Tara?
Ma Tara ?
You... got so big.
Comme tu as grandi.
Can I hug you?
Je peux te prendre dans mes bras ?
Come here.
Viens là.
Oh, God.
Oh, baby, we missed you so much.
Chérie, tu nous as tellement manqué.
Mm. There you are.
Te voilà.
You were such a beautiful baby.
Tu étais
un si joli bébé.
Get it out.
Crache.
Get it out. Come on.
There you go. There you go. - There you go. - Sorry.
Voilà.
Nothing to apologize for.
- Pardon. - Ne t'excuse pas.
Are you okay?
Tu es malade ?
The same fire that destroyed our family...
L'incendie qui a détruit notre famille
it burned up my insides.
m'a aussi brûlée, à l'intérieur.
Mom and Dad used to have a...
Maman et papa avaient...
kitchen...
une cuisine
in the basement of our house, where we used to cook.
au sous-sol de la maison, où on cuisinait.
It was for our business.
Pour notre commerce.
Are you thirsty?
Tu as soif ?
Tara?
Tara ?
I'm dying.
Je vais mourir.
What?
Quoi ?
The smoke from the chemicals...
Les vapeurs de produits chimiques
poisoned my blood and badly damaged my heart.
m'ont empoisonné le sang et m'ont abîmé le coeur.
I don't think I have much time left.
Il ne me reste plus beaucoup de temps.
Is there anything you can do?
Y a rien à faire ?
I heard you left flowers for me at our old house.
Il paraît que tu m'as déposé des fleurs à notre ancienne maison.
Is that true?
C'est vrai ?
Oh...
Weren't you wishing your mama was healthy and alive?
Tu n'espérais pas que ta maman soit vivante et en bonne santé ?
Yes.
Si.
I need a new heart, baby.
Il me faut un nouveau coeur, chérie.
But not just any heart.
Mais pas n'importe lequel.
Doctor said it has to be a, um...
Le médecin a dit
It must be a... compatible donor.
que ça devait être
un donneur compatible.
Like a direct relative.
Comme un descendant direct.
You hold the gift that can save your mama's life.
Tu as en toi le cadeau qui peut sauver ta maman.
And, baby, I need that gift.
Et, chérie, j'ai besoin de ce cadeau.
We'll finally be together as one.
On peut enfin être réunies.
You'll live on in me.
Tu continueras à vivre en moi.
Go home.
Rentre chez toi.
Shh.
Shh!
Go away.
Va-t'en.
I said, go.
J'ai dit : "Rentre chez toi !"
Stay.
Reste là.
Go home.
Rentre chez toi.
I hope you understand the high risks of this procedure.
J'espère que vous comprenez que l'opération est très risquée.
I think I pay you enough. Shut up and do your job.
Je vous paie assez cher.
Fermez-la et faites votre boulot.
Why is she still alive?
Pourquoi elle est encore en vie ?
If she's dead, so is her heart.
Si elle meurt, son coeur meurt aussi.
I can't keep it fresh long enough without the proper equipment.
Je ne peux pas le garder frais sans le matériel adéquat.
I have to cut it out of her while she's still breathing.
Je dois lui retirer pendant qu'elle respire encore.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
Thank you.
Merci.
What's wrong with you?
Ça va pas ?
What they're doing in there is wrong.
Ce qu'ils font là-dedans, c'est mal.
She's our cook.
C'est notre cuisinière.
If she dies, there's no product.
Si elle meurt, on n'a plus de marchandise.
If there's no product, there's no us.
Sans marchandise, on n'existe plus.
Comprende?
Still fucking wrong.
Quand même, c'est dégueulasse.
Hey.
- You ready? - Mm.
T'es prête ?
Let's go.
On y va.
What the fuck?
Putain, quoi encore ?
Go check it out.
Va voir.
You killed my brother!
Tu as tué mon frère !
You blind freak!
Putain d'aveugle !
I'm gonna carve your fucking head open like a pumpkin, man.
Je vais te découper la gueule comme une citrouille.
This is for Shadow.
Ça, c'est pour Shadow.
Oh, fuck.
No!
It's him.
C'est lui.
How the hell did he find...?
Mais comment il a trouvé...
Disloyal fucking animal.
Putain de traître.
Is everything okay?
Tout va bien ?
Yeah, everything's okay. - Everything's okay, I promise. - Baby...
Oui, tout va bien.
- Mm-hm? - ...should I be worried?
- Ça va, promis. - Chéri ?
No, no. Not at all. I got you. I got you.
- Je dois m'inquiéter ? - Pas du tout.
I can't work without power.
Je suis là.
Je peux pas travailler sans électricité.
Uh...
Change of plans, then.
Changement de plan, alors.
Pack your things. Bring the girl.
Remballez. Emmenez la petite.
Raul.
- Bring the men. Kill the blind man. - How many of us?
- Appelle les gars, tuez l'aveugle. - A combien ?
All of you!
Tout le monde !
Let's go.
Allons-y.
They're gonna kill her.
Ils vont la tuer.
And that's not cool with me.
Et ça, ça me va pas.
They're leaving now.
Ils vont partir.
The ladder behind you leads directly to them. You'd better hurry.
L'échelle derrière toi te mènera à eux.
Dépêche-toi.
Go left.
A gauche.
That way.
Par là.
He'll kill you all.
Il va tous vous tuer.
Fuck it. I'm out. Hey, hey!
Merde, je me casse.
Hey!
Good morning, motherfucker.
Bonjour, enfoiré.
- Baby. - Shh, shh, shh.
Chérie !
It's okay.
Tout va bien.
Stop it.
Arrête !
Baby?
Chérie ?
Hello? I can't see you.
Tu es là ?
Je te vois pas.
Baby?
Chérie ?
Someone's here! Hurry!
Y a quelqu'un. Fais vite !
Baby?
I got you, motherfucker.
Je t'ai eu, enfoiré.
No.
No!
Phoenix!
Phoenix !
Now...
Maintenant...
you're gonna see what I see.
tu vas voir ce que je vois.
Phoenix?
Phoenix ?
Stop.
Arrête-toi.
Stop!
You...
You mustn't come near me.
Ne m'approche pas.
Everything he said...
Tout ce qu'il t'a dit...
is true.
est vrai.
I am no father.
Je suis pas un père.
I have killed.
J'ai tué.
I... have raped.
J'ai violé.
I...
am nothing.
Je ne suis rien.
Nothing...
Rien...
but a monster.
qu'un monstre.
And you... cannot be around me.
Tu ne dois pas rester auprès de moi.
Ever.
Plus jamais.
So go.
Alors, va-t'en.
Now. Go.
Va-t'en maintenant.
Go!
Oh, God.
Tara?
Tara ?
No.
Please.
Je t'en supplie.
No, no, no.
Let me help you.
Laisse-moi t'aider.
I can save you.
Je peux te sauver.
You already have.
Tu l'as déjà fait.
Hey.
Salut !
Think there's room for one more?
Il reste une place ?
I'm sure there is.
J'en suis sûre.
What's your name?
Tu t'appelles comment ?
My name is Phoenix.
Je m'appelle Phoenix.
Visa d'exploitation n° 155359
Sous-titres traduits par: Hélène Monsché
Sous-titres ENG + FRE fusionnés par Zorg2412