DON'T BREATHE - LA MAISON DES TÉNÈBRES
- Sure you got the right keys ? - It's the right key. - Okay, then, open the door. - It shouldn't be taking so long, man.
- T'as les bonnes clés ? - Oui, t'inquiète.
Alors ouvre.
Pourquoi c'est si long ?
- Twenty, 19, 18... - Rocky, those are very slow seconds.
20,
19, 18...
- ...17, 16... - Yo, kill that already.
Rocky, accélère tes secondes.
- Dude, come on. - ...15, 14, 13, 12...
Eteins ça, grouille-toi.
- This is what I'm talking about. - ...11, 10, nine....
Ça déchire !
... 10, 9.
I told you this was gonna be fancy.
Je t'avais annoncé du lourd.
All right, so just like last time. No cash. - The total take has to fall below 10 G's. - Yeah, whatever, Judge Judy.
Comme d'hab, pas de cash. On prend pour moins de 10 000.
- Come on. - Let's do this.
Bien, monsieur le juge.
C'est parti.
Okay, let's get out of here.
On se casse.
Hey, Rocky, did you hear that Kopecky's moving away ?
Rocky, tu sais que Kopecky déménage ?
Everybody's leaving.
Tout le monde s'en va.
You know, we keep hitting houses like today's, Rocky, and....
Si on se fait d'autres baraques comme celle d'aujourd'hui...
Bye-bye, Detroit.
Adieu, Détroit.
And hola, California.
Hola, la Californie.
- Wait, wait. You're going away, Rock ? - Yeah, as soon as I can.
Tu comptes partir, Rock ?
Dès que possible.
When are you-- When are you coming back ?
Et tu reviens quand ?
Never.
Jamais.
You should come with us.
Viens avec nous.
What ?
Quoi ?
Everyone else is gone.
Tout le monde s'est barré.
I got my dad here.
J'ai mon père, ici.
I'll miss you, then.
Alors tu vas me manquer.
Dad ?
Papa ?
You're home ?
T'es rentré ?
ENTREPRISE DE SÉCURITÉ
Yo, this is it, man ?
C'est tout, mec ?
Minus my 40 percent.
Moins mes 40 %.
Take it or leave it. - There's a fucking Rolex in there, bro. - What do you think...
A prendre ou à laisser.
- Y a une Rolex, merde. - Tu crois quoi ?
...I'm gonna put it up for auction at Sotheby's ?
Que je vais la vendre aux enchères ?
You know how much people on the street pay for a hot Rolex ?
Tu sais combien ça se revend dans la rue ?
You want money ?
Si tu veux du fric,
- Then steal money. - Fucking bullshit, bro.
vole du fric.
Arrête tes conneries.
You want this new tip or not ?
Tu veux un bon plan ou pas ?
All right, let's hear it.
Vas-y, balance.
1837 Buena Vista Street. House is with your dad's security company.
1837 rue Buena Vista.
I already checked.
La maison est surveillée par ton père, j'ai vérifié.
Guy who owns it is an Army vet loner.
Le proprio est un vétéran solitaire.
No family. Just him in the house.
Pas de famille, y a que lui.
- That part of the city is a ghost town. - Looks like a dump.
- C'est un quartier fantôme. - C'est une ruine.
That's actually good news. How is that good news ?
- C'est plutôt un bon point. - Comment ça ?
Well, the story goes...
Il paraît
...some preppy girl a few years ago ran over this guy's daughter. - Jesus. - The daughter dies...
qu'une gosse de riches a renversé la fille de ce gars.
Sa fille meurt
...and this preppy, rich-ass family... ...pays him off, gives him a big-ass sediment.
et la famille de gros bourges le dédommage.
Settlement.
- Un arrangement à l'aimable. - "A l'amiable."
Blow me, Your Honour. All right, this guy is sitting on at least...
Je m'en branle, votre honneur.
Ce gars est assis sur au moins...
...300K.
300 000 $ !
I mean, if I deliver this stake to Raul, man... ...he will shit his pants.
Si je file sa part à Raul, il va se chier dessus.
Do you think the money's in the house ?
Le fric serait dans la maison ?
I don't know. Let's go find out. Guys, no. We don't do cash.
- Je sais pas, faut aller voir. - On a dit pas de cash.
Above 10 K, it's major larceny. Ten years if we get caught.
Au-dessus de 10 000, c'est 10 ans si on tombe.
- We won't get caught. - And then what ?
On tombera pas.
That amount brings a serious cop presence. They'll do an investigation.
Ok, mais après ?
- My dad could get in trouble. - I knew you'd bitch out, man.
Les flics vont mener une enquête. Mon père risque...
Je savais que tu te dégonflerais.
- I just knew it. - Alex...
J'en étais sûr.
...if we do this right, we never have to do it again.
Si on fait ça bien,
on aura plus à le faire.
Where are you going ?
Tu vas où ?
We're not doing this one.
On laisse tomber.
Seriously ?
T'es sérieux ?
Give us the fucking keys, man. - We'll fucking do it. - Alex !
File les clés, merde ! Nous, on le fait.
JE DOIS LA SORTIR D'ICI.
TU VEUX BIEN LE FAIRE POUR MOI ?
"Gulf War veteran reaches six-figure settlement."
"Un vétéran obtient un dédommagement à 6 chiffres."
Six-figure settlement.
All right.
The suspect was leaving the rear entrance.
You done, Diddy ?
T'as fini, Diddy ?
Be a doll and get your mother a large four-cheese from Tony's.
Sois gentille, va me chercher une 4 fromages chez Tony.
- So Trevor's living here now ? - Don't be a bitch, Roxanne.
Trevor vit ici maintenant ?
It's just a few months till he can find a new job.
Fais pas chier, c'est juste le temps qu'il retrouve
You have no money in here.
du boulot.
You pay for it then.
Y a rien là-dedans.
T'as qu'à payer.
I know you're making money.
Je sais que t'as de l'argent.
I'm done.
J'ai fini.
Your lips look sore.
T'as les lèvres irritées.
That's how you're making your cash out there ?
C'est comme ça que tu te fais du fric ?
Okay, Diddy, let's go for a walk.
Diddy, on va se promener.
I want to go to the beach.
Je veux aller à la plage.
Yeah, well, it's not summer, monkeyhead. I want to be a surfer.
C'est pas l'été, tête de linotte.
Je veux faire du surf.
There's no surf in Michigan.
On fait pas de surf dans le Michigan.
- Not fair. - Yeah, well...
C'est pas juste.
...some things you can't change, baby.
On fait avec ce qu'on a, ma belle.
No matter how unfair they are.
Même si c'est pas juste.
What a bummer.
C'est trop nul.
OK. ON LE FAIT.
Hey, you know where there is surf ?
Tu sais où on fait du surf ?
California. What do you say you and I move there together ?
En Californie.
Would you like that ?
Ça te dirait qu'on aille vivre là-bas ?
Okay. I promise, then.
OK, je te le promets.
Is that a new tattoo ? Yeah.
Nouveau tatouage ?
I got it last night.
Oui, je l'ai depuis hier soir.
- Is it a... ? - Ladybug.
- C'est... - Une coccinelle.
Why a ladybug ?
Pourquoi une coccinelle ?
What ?
Quoi ?
When my dad left, my mom started drinking... ...and she told me that...
Quand mon père est parti, ma mère s'est mise à boire.
Elle me disait
...my dad's leaving was all my fault.
que mon père était parti à cause de moi.
And I missed him a lot, so I'd cry.
Il me manquait, alors je pleurais.
She got so fed up with the crying... ...that she would lock me in the trunk of her car.
Quand ça l'énervait, elle m'enfermait dans le coffre de la voiture.
Sometimes for hours.
Des heures, parfois.
But there was this....
Mais y avait...
A little hole in the trunk...
un petit trou dans le coffre
...and one time a ladybug flew in...
et un jour, une coccinelle est entrée.
...kept me company.
Elle m'a tenu compagnie.
It made me feel safe.
Je me suis sentie en sécurité.
When I reach California, I'll colour this tat... ...and that's the last time I will mark my body.
En Californie, je ferai colorer ce tatouage
et je toucherai plus à mon corps.
If we get this money, I'm going away with you guys.
Si on trouve cet argent, je pars avec vous.
I know you will.
Je sais.
At least four blocks around, houses aren't occupied.
Y a personne à moins de 4 pâtés de maisons.
No people means no Five-0 on patrol.
Pas d'habitants, pas de patrouilles de flics.
It's gonna be a piece of cake.
Ça va être du gâteau.
The guy's a shut-in, hasn't left his house in like five days.
Le mec est pas sorti de chez lui depuis 5 jours.
I say we do it with him in the house. I'll get a chloro-bomb.
On le fait quand il est là, j'aurai du chloroforme.
- Jesus. - Get off my fucking car, dog shit !
Dégage de ma bagnole, sale clebs !
Shit, that's our guy.
Merde, c'est lui.
Wait, is he blind ?
Il est aveugle ?
He lost his sight in Iraq or something.
Il a dû perdre la vue en Irak.
Kind of fucked up to rob a blind guy, isn't it ?
Ça craint de voler un aveugle.
Just because he's blind don't mean he's a fucking saint, bro.
Ça fait pas de lui un saint, mon pote.
We do this tonight.
On le fait cette nuit.
The whole neighbourhood is fucking empty. This guy's the last man standing.
Y a pas un rat dans ce quartier.
Ce mec est le dernier survivant.
The lights are out. He must be asleep.
Les lumières sont éteintes, il dort.
He's blind. - Lights off doesn't mean anything. - It's 2 a.m.
Il est aveugle, ça veut rien dire.
Il est 2 h,
He's sleeping.
il dort.
Let's take care of that dog first, yeah ?
On s'occupe d'abord du chien.
Come on, man.
Amène-toi.
He's chewing it. It'll be lights out in a sec.
Il mâche. Y en a plus pour longtemps.
There's four locks. You got the other keys ?
Y a 4 serrures, t'as les autres clés ?
- I only have the one. - Fuck me.
J'en ai qu'une.
Et merde.
Why wouldn't he give backup keys to the security company ?
Pourquoi il a pas donné les doubles à l'entreprise ?
Because the money's in there and the paranoid fuck doesn't trust nobody. Let's check for a side door.
A cause du fric. Cet enfoiré de parano est méfiant.
Y a peut-être une autre porte.
Sweet dreams, pup.
Dors bien, toutou.
What's that ?
C'est quoi ?
We point this in the general direction of the master keypad, it'll kill the alarm.
Si je l'oriente vers le boîtier, ça désactive l'alarme.
Okay, open the fucking door, Dexter.
Ouvre cette putain de porte, Dexter.
Yes. Got it.
J'essaie.
Shit.
- What's wrong ? - It won't open it.
Y a un souci ?
Ça s'ouvre pas.
This guy isn't messing around.
Il plaisante pas, le type.
There's a bolt here. I can feel it.
Y a un verrou, je le sens.
- Come on. - That's too loud. That's too loud. Fucking stop.
Moins fort.
Lâche-moi.
What about that window ?
Et cette fenêtre ?
There's no bars on it. - I can fit in there. - What ?
Y a pas de barreaux, je peux passer.
No, we're not sending you in there alone.
On t'envoie pas là-dedans toute seule.
Nobody's sending me anywhere.
Personne m'envoie,
I'm going myself.
je veux y aller.
- Help me up. - Here, Rocky.
Aidez-moi.
- You only got 30 seconds. - Okay.
Tiens, t'as 30 secondes.
Here. Come here.
Slow your roll, fool. She must have got it by now. She's fine.
Détends-toi, flippette.
Elle a géré, elle va bien.
- Yeah, like you really give a fuck. - What'd you say ?
- Tu t'en tapes de toute façon. - Quoi ?
That's my bitch in there. Of course I give a fuck.
C'est ma meuf, je m'en tape pas.
Let me give you some advice. Be a good friend...
Ecoute-moi bien.
...and stay in the fucking friend zone, all right ?
Sois un bon pote et rien de plus.
You okay ?
Ça va ?
Yes.
Shoes off.
Enlevez vos chaussures.
- What the fuck ? - Hey.
T'es malade !
Hey. Hey.
Okay.
Just three seeds, right ?
3 graines, c'est ça ?
Just three ?
Que 3 ?
One, two...
...and three.
Put three seeds in there... ...and the cup is all empty.
On plante 3 graines
et le pot est vide.
Now you water it ?
Okay, now we water it.
Okay, Mom.
Then it takes the water.
Just three seeds.
3 graines.
What are you doing ?
Que fais-tu ?
Planting a tree.
Je plante un arbre.
How big is the tree gonna get ?
Il sera grand comment ?
As big as the sky !
Il ira jusqu'au ciel !
What does a tree need to grow ?
De quoi un arbre a-t-il besoin ?
Water, seeds, soil...
D'eau, de graines,
...and sun.
de terre et...
de soleil.
Sounds good.
C'est bien.
Then it will grow.
Mom, can I have more water ?
Done.
C'est bon !
What the fuck, dude ?
Quoi, putain ?
The guy's gassed out.
Le mec est HS,
He's out. He's in Sleeping Beauty mode.
c'est genre la Belle au bois dormant.
- It's fine. - Guys.
Les gars.
That's a big-ass lock.
Sacré verrou.
If the money's in the house...
Si le fric est dans la maison,
...probably in there.
il est là-dedans.
You think you can crack it open ?
Tu vas pouvoir l'ouvrir ?
Yeah, I got this.
Oui, c'est bon.
Fuck.
Jesus.
- Do you have anything else ? - Yeah.
- T'as pas autre chose ? - Si.
Yeah, yeah.
I've got a more powerful tool.
J'ai un truc plus efficace.
- What the hell is that ? - It's a 9 mm Beretta.
- C'est quoi, ça ? - Un Beretta 9 mm.
Gangster-style, bitches. Why'd you bring a gun ?
- En mode gangster, les meufs. - Pourquoi t'as un flingue ?
This is a soldier's house. Like I'm gonna come in here... - ...without some chrome. - Money, you've never shot a gun before.
Je viens pas chez un militaire sans calibre.
Money, t'as jamais utilisé un flingue.
Yeah, well, it's time to pop that cherry. I'm gonna pop that shit like a tuna can.
Ce sera mon dépucelage, chérie, je vais faire sauter ce merdier.
Do you have any idea what bringing a gun to a burglary means ?
Tu sais ce que ça implique, un flingue ?
Yeah, it gives me a better chance to defend myself, Alex.
Oui, plus de chances de me défendre, Alex.
No, it means you just gave this guy the legal right to shoot us.
Tu donnes le droit à ce mec de nous tirer dessus.
Rocky, let's go.
Rocky, on s'en va.
No, no, no. I think we should stay.
On devrait rester.
We have to leave. This is not good.
Faut partir, ça craint.
You don't really think just because you jerk off to her Instagram selfies...
Tu te branles devant ses selfies sur Instagram
...that makes you a Romeo ?
et tu te prends pour Roméo ?
Think again, bitch.
Réfléchis bien, bouffon.
Fuck, I'm so out.
Je me casse.
Alex.
Alex !
Who-- Who's there ?
Qui est là ?
Okay, man, just chill, all right ?
Reste tranquille, mec.
Look...
...I was wasted, and I wandered in...
J'étais déchiré
...so that was my bad, all right ? So I'm just gonna-- I'm just gonna leave, okay ?
et je suis entré, j'aurais pas dû.
Je vais partir, ok ?
Stay right fucking there.
Tu bouges pas de là.
Don't you fucking move.
Plus un geste !
Yeah, that's right. I know what's in there, and I ain't leaving without it.
Eh oui, je sais ce qu'il y a là-dedans et je partirai pas sans.
You got me ?
Pigé ?
Now, you do as I say, all right ?
Alors écoute-moi bien.
Don't take one single step, all right ?
Tu fais plus un seul pas.
Well, do you hear me or what ?
T'entends ce que je dis ?
What, are you blind and deaf all of a sudden ?
T'es devenu sourd aussi ?
Motherfucker, I said stop.
Enfoiré, j'ai dit stop.
I think you fucking heard me.
Tu m'as bien entendu.
- Sorry. - Don't you move.
- Désolé. - Bouge pas !
What the fuck are you doing, you old man ? I'll fucking shoot you.
Fais gaffe, le vioc, je vais te buter !
Don't you fucking test me.
Me cherche pas.
You're a fucking pussy.
Sale fiotte.
What are you gonna do now, huh ?
Et maintenant, tu fais quoi ?
You better fucking stop. Stop !
T'as intérêt...
Don't make me fucking kill you, man.
M'oblige pas à te tuer !
Please. Please.
Please, just let me walk.
Pitié, laisse-moi partir.
Let me walk. Leave me alive.
Laisse-moi la vie sauve.
- Please. - How many of you are there ?
Pourquoi tu fais ça ?
Vous êtes combien ?
- What ? - How many ?
Quoi ?
Combien ?
It's just me, man, all right ? It's just fucking me. Just let me go !
Y a que moi, mec, je t'assure.
Please let me go.
Laisse-moi partir !
Please.
Just let me go.
Laisse-moi partir.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Okay, I swear to God....
Je te jure...
IL A TUÉ MONEY
Viens m'aider
Je suis dans la maison, t'es où ?
dans la penderie
Rocky, hey, are you okay ? Are you okay ?
Rocky, ça va ?
Tout va bien ?
Maybe.... Maybe we should call the cops before he does.
On devrait appeler les flics avant lui
We'll come clean--
et se livrer.
Wait.
Attends.
What ?
Quoi ?
Oh, my God.
There's a lot more than 300 grand. That's got to be about a million dollars.
Y a bien plus que 300 000,
il doit y avoir un million.
Okay, let's get out of here.
Faut sortir d'ici.
The storm cellar door. The door's bolted from the inside.
L'abri anti-tempête.
That could be our way out.
La porte est fermée de l'intérieur, ça se tente.
Let's go.
Viens.
This way.
What ?
Oh, shit. The phone died.
Merde, mon portable est mort.
Fuck.
- Where's the door ? - I don't know. Where is it ? Do you see it ?
- Où est la porte ? - J'en sais rien.
Tu la vois pas ?
We need to get the fuck out of here right now.
Faut dégager tout de suite.
Come on. Let's go. Look, the door's right here.
Viens. La porte est juste là.
What ?
Quoi ?
Rocky ? Rocky.
Rocky, listen. Hey, that's our exit.
The door's right fucking there. We can leave right now.
La porte est juste là,
on peut sortir.
Cindy Roberts innocentée de l'homicide involontaire
She's the one who killed his daughter.
C'est elle qui a tué sa fille.
- We have to get her out of here. - No, no, no. We don't have time.
Faut la sortir de là.
We'll get out of here, we'll call the cops...
Non, on a pas le temps.
On appellera les flics,
...and then they'll come find her, all right ?
ils viendront la chercher.
The code from the safe upstairs. You remember it ?
Le code d'en haut, tu t'en souviens ?
- 2-9-7-8. 7-8, 7-8. 2-9-7-8. - 2-9-7-8.
2978.
Okay, got them.
Je les ai.
He's coming.
Il arrive.
- Hurry up. - Okay, one more, one more.
- Vite. - Plus qu'une.
Fuck, fuck !
Merde.
I almost have it. Almost.... okay.
J'y suis presque.
I don't care what you did. I'll get you out of here.
Peu importe ce que t'as fait,
je vais te sortir de là.
Go. Go !
Allez !
- There's the door. - There it is.
- La porte. - Elle est là.
You okay ? Okay.
What's wrong ?
Qu'est-ce qu'il y a ?
- What's wrong ? - It's locked.
- Qu'est-ce qu'il y a ? - C'est fermé.
You have the keys. Don't you have the keys ?
Les clés, tu les as ?
Fuck.
- One of these should open it. - Come on.
- Ça devrait le faire. - Vite !
Come on.
Vite !
- Come on. - Okay.
Oh, yes.
Come on.
He shot her.
Il l'a tuée.
No.
My baby.
Mon bébé...
No !
We have to go back upstairs.
Faut retourner là-haut.
Yeah, listen.
Listen, okay ? These keys, they match the locks on the front door.
Ecoute-moi.
All right ? If we get up there, we can get out.
C'est les clés de la porte d'entrée.
Si on remonte, on peut sortir.
Okay ?
Let's go now.
Maintenant.
Shit.
Merde...
Alex ?
Rocky ?
Please don't....
Pitié.
No, please.
- Rocky ? - Alex. Alex.
Rocky, Rocky. Let's go. Let's go. This way. This way, come on. This way, come on, come on, come on.
On se tire.
Par ici.
Okay.
Oh, come on. Where am I ?
Where is it ? Light. I see light !
C'est où ?
Come on, come on.
Je vois de la lumière.
Don't...
Ne...
...run.
cours pas.
Rocky...
...go to the door.
Va à la porte.
Try the blue key.
Essaye la clé bleue.
- Do it. - Okay.
Vas-y.
Easy.
Easy, buddy.
Fuck.
- Rocky ? - Yeah.
- Come on. - Easy, buddy.
Tout doux, mon pote.
Easy.
Tout doux.
It's okay.
Okay, that's a good boy. That's good.
Bon chien. C'est bien.
All right.
That's good.
That's good. That's good.
C'est bien.
Fuck.
Rocky. Run, now. Go, go, go ! Upstairs, now. Go. Go, go !
Les escaliers, vite !
Hurry, hurry !
Go ! There's a door ! Come on !
Let's go.
Hey, move this. Come on.
On pousse ça !
Damn.
- Are those blocked up too ? - Yeah.
Tout est barricadé ?
We're trapped in here.
On est coincés.
Rocky, the remote. Do you have it with you ?
T'as la télécommande ?
Come on. Okay.
- What are you doing ? - Pressing the panic button.
- Tu fais quoi ? - J'active l'alarme.
If I get in range, the system will call 911. - The police will come. - No. We can't go to jail.
Si ça marche, la police va venir.
No. No, we won't. Okay ? This is robbery versus kidnapping and murder.
- Je veux pas aller en prison ! - On ira pas.
Cambriolage contre enlèvement et meurtre,
The police won't care about us or why we were here. - We helped them get this guy. - But then we wouldn't keep the money.
la police s'attardera pas sur nous si on leur livre ce mec.
Mais on perdra l'argent.
- We need to get out of this room. - Up there.
Faut sortir d'ici.
Go !
Vas-y !
Alex !
What are you doing ? Go !
Dépêche !
No ! No, no, no !
Hey !
Please, let me go.
Pitié, laissez-moi partir.
Please, let me go !
Laissez-moi partir !
I....
I understand you.
Je vous comprends.
She killed your daughter.
Elle a tué votre fille.
You wanted her to pay. I understand that.
Vous vouliez qu'elle paie, je comprends.
I won't tell anyone.
Je dirai rien à personne.
You understand nothing.
Tu comprends rien.
Only a parent could know...
Seul un parent peut ressentir...
...the bond between a father and his child.
le lien
qui unit un père à son enfant.
She should have gone to prison, but...
Elle aurait dû aller en prison,
...rich girls don't go to jail.
mais les filles de riches n'y vont pas.
None of this is gonna bring your daughter back.
Rien ne pourra vous rendre votre fille.
That's not really true.
C'est pas tout à fait vrai.
Cindy took my child away from me.
Cindy m'a pris mon enfant.
I thought...
Je me suis dit...
...it's only fair...
qu'il était légitime...
...that she give me a new one.
qu'elle m'en donne un.
She was pregnant with my baby.
Elle portait mon bébé.
You killed them both.
Vous les avez tués.
- No. - Well, they would be alive...
Ils seraient en vie
...if you hadn't broken into my home.
si vous n'étiez pas entrés chez moi.
No.
You have to be held accountable.
Tu vas en subir les conséquences.
Please.
Pitié...
- Please, God. - God ?
Pitié, mon Dieu.
Dieu ?
There's no God.
Dieu n'existe pas.
It's a joke.
C'est une blague.
It's a bad joke.
Une mauvaise blague.
You tell me what God would allow this.
Tu crois que Dieu laisserait faire ça ?
What are you doing ?
Vous faites quoi ?
I'm not a rapist.
Je suis pas un violeur.
I never forced myself on her.
J'ai jamais abusé d'elle.
Stop.
Arrêtez.
I promised I would set her free... ...just as soon as she gave me a child.
J'avais promis de la libérer quand elle me donnerait un enfant.
But now she's gone.
Mais elle n'est plus là.
But I'm done waiting.
Et j'ai assez attendu.
No. No, no.
You can't do this to me.
Vous pouvez pas faire ça.
There's nothing a man cannot do...
Rien n'est impossible
...once he accepts the fact that there is no God.
quand on s'est fait à l'idée que Dieu n'existe pas.
No ! No !
No, no, no !
No !
- No ! - You're strong.
Tu es forte.
- You're young. - No.
Tu es jeune.
You'll breed well.
Tu feras une bonne génitrice.
No. Get away from me.
Non, ne m'approchez pas.
No ! No !
No !
No.
Stop.
Nine months...
Dans 9 mois,
...and I will give you your life back.
tu pourras retrouver ta vie.
Are you okay ? Rocky. Okay, yeah.
Ça va ?
Rocky, did he-- ? Did he hurt you ?
Il t'a fait du mal ?
Rocky ?
You fucking bastard.
Espèce d'ordure.
Fuck you !
Hey, Rocky. Rocky. Rocky. Rocky, it's over. Come on.
C'est fini.
How's that taste ?
C'était bon ?
- Now what ? - Come on.
You're gonna rot in prison for what you've done.
Tu vas pourrir en prison pour ce que t'as fait.
Rocky, we can't involve the cops now.
Rocky, on peut plus appeler les flics.
If we steal a million in cash, then lead the cops here... ...he'll tell them about us. Our blood is all over.
Si on vole l'argent et qu'ils débarquent, il nous balancera.
- They'll get to us in a second. - You got what you came for.
Y a du sang partout, ils nous retrouveront vite.
Vous avez ce que vous vouliez.
Now take it.
Prenez-le
Get out of my house !
et fichez le camp !
Look, he's buying our silence. He needs us to take the money.
Il achète notre silence, il veut qu'on prenne le fric.
It's one or the other.
C'est l'un ou l'autre.
Whatever you choose, I'm with you.
Dans les deux cas, je te suis.
- Okay. - This one.
Celle-là.
Let's get out of here.
Allons-nous-en.
I have to find the key. All right.
Attends, je cherche.
That key won't....
I got it.
C'est bon.
You're worthless out here.
Tu fais moins le malin.
Fuck.
Shit !
Merde.
Fuck. Fuck, fuck, fuck !
Fait chier !
Fuck !
I'm sorry, Alex.
Je suis désolée, Alex...
I'm so sorry.
tellement désolée.
No !
Don't !
No. No.
Don't....
No !
No.
What is that ?
C'est quoi ?
You and me at the beach.
Toi et moi à la plage.
--will be boarding shortly on Platform 6.
This house behind me on Buena Vista belongs to a retired Army vet... ...who fought for our country in Iraq...
Cette maison de la rue Buena Vista appartient à un vétéran retraité
qui a défendu notre pays en Irak
...and lost his sight as a result of a grenade splinter.
et perdu la vue suite à un éclat d'obus.
Last night, two burglars broke into his home... ...and attempted to rob and brutally attack him.
Cette nuit, 2 cambrioleurs se sont introduits chez lui
et l'ont violemment attaqué.
This visually impaired man was able to defend himself...
L'homme non voyant a réussi à se défendre,
...shooting and killing both his attackers on the spot.
tuant sur place ses deux agresseurs.
Now, the man did sustain some injuries... ...but doctors say he is in stable condition. He'll be released from the hospital soon and able to return to his home.
Il a cependant été blessé, mais son état est stable.
Il sortira bientôt de l'hôpital et pourra rentrer chez lui.
No goods were reported stolen by the victim.
Aucun vol n'a été signalé par la victime.
I'm Dayna Clark, WADL News.
Dayna Clark pour WADL News.
Traduction : Belinda Milosev
HIVENTY
Sous-titres ENG + FRE fusionnés par Zorg2412