- When do you have to resume work?
- Don't know.
How are we going to run the house?
[Rudra] Pray to God that no one has
to face such a situation.
I wasn't able to find a job.
And my wife was going around
with the scratch marks
by some other man on her body.
[Ranjana] Free me from all this.
Won't you?
- [Madhu] You have to kidnap.
- Kidnap who?
- My daughter.
- What?
[Madhu] Yes. It is matter
of one crore.
She is also a partner in this.
[Song playing over radio]
[Door closes]
[Moaning, panting]
[Cell phone rings]
[Panting stops]
[Ringing continues]
[Breathing heavily]
- Hello.
- Why are you out of breath?
Papa, I was in the bathroom. So...
Tell me.
Did you call?
It's Roopa's ring ceremony.
So all my friends are going there.
Why do you ask repeatedly?
I don't like saying no
to you repeatedly.
You can see the law
and order situation, right?
Tell me if there's anything else.
No, Papa.
[Madhu] Govind Tyagi.
The biggest problem
of Anusha's life.
He loves his daughter so much
that if he hugs her,
the girl would suffocate to death.
Govind has imposed
all the restrictions
you can possibly think of
on Anusha.
You call your husband by name.
Now I can't call him a moron.
And I'm not the homely types.
You should respect a person
from the heart.
I can't fake it.
[Madhu] Govind has
three sugar mills.
But he has his tea without sugar.
He is such a scrooge that if
he wants to buy an undergarment,
he waits for a sale.
He loves just two things.
His money and his daughter Anusha.
And he has security for both.
- Security?
- [Madhu] Yes.
[Madhu] Anusha goes out with
security and returns with security.
He is very lonely.
No one even talks to her.
How can anyone?
If anyone even looks at her
all hell breaks loose.
Poor thing.
She holds herself responsible
for it.
She is really unhappy
about her face and body.
Her confidence is almost zero.
Facebook is all she has.
Her father owns the college.
That's why she is able to go.
Or she is not allowed
to even step out of the house.
Any reason for such strictness?
Govind fears that someone
might kidnap Anusha.
I can't do this.
- [Madhu] Wait. Wait.
- [Door opens]
- Hear me out.
- [Door closes]
Who can do this job
better than you?
The police has given you medal.
You know kidnappers inside out.
And the police too.
If Govind Tyagi's
daughter disappears,
you'll see only police vans
in the city.
Nothing of that sort
is going to happen.
Do you know?
The minister's boy had
disappeared a few years ago.
And the boy was killed because
of the interference of a policeman.
They were going to kill
the boy anyways.
I just tried to save his life.
Whatever.
But you did a noble deed.
Since then no one goes
to the cops in this area.
Govind won't either.
And as far as Anu is concerned,
there is a wedding
in Ghaziabad next week.
Anu too will go.
You will find everything
on a platter in Ghaziabad.
It's the wedding scene.
So there will be lesser security.
I'll send you an invitation.
Just sit in a corner.
Anu herself will sit in your lap
and say,
"Come on, uncle.
Take me from here."
That's it. Job done.
[Chuckles]
Don't think so much.
30 lakhs is not a small amount.
You tried finding a job.
If not about yourself,
think about your wife.
How long are you going
to make her do overtime?
I want to meet Anu first.
[Title Montage]
[Theme song playing]
[Clock ticking]
[Alarm ringing]
[Door opens]
- [Door closes]
- [Cell phone ringing]
Her lectures are
on the first floor.
Ask her to meet me
at the ladies washroom at 12.30.
Ladies washroom?
Why are you hell bent
on becoming a painter?
At 12.30 ladies...
How do you have so much money?
I found it in your pant.
- [Song playing over radio]
- I have found a job. That's how.
What job is this
where you get so much of advance?
[Bell rings]
It's not mine to keep.
I have to forward it.
Once the deal is finalized
I might have to go out of town.
When will you know if it's final?
Today.
Listen. I'll make do if you have
to agree for little less.
Just don't
let the opportunity slip.
Anusha College
[Car honking]
Hey, madam is here.
Go. Hurry.
Move. Move. Madam is here.
[Gate closes]
- [Car door opens]
- [Car doors closing]
[Car doors closing]
Look at this.
Big boast small roast.
She has such security as if people
are lining up to pounce on her.
Jerk.
You can run your house
because of this girl. Moron.
Munna, let's go to the class.
Boss, send someone else.
We have been doing this
for the last three months.
Had I attended so many lectures
I would've been an IS.
[Man 1] How are you doing?
Lovely chicks.
Want to send a message to someone
in the college? Will you?
Why don't you go yourself?
Listen, want to send a message to
someone in the college? Will you?
Certainly. Tell me.
Who is the recipient?
Tell the guard that
you want to talk to Anusha Tyagi.
Send her out.
- Let's go.
Listen. I'll just be back.
[Man 3] Which one?
[Man 2] That Sania...
She is on leave.
[Man 2] She will beat me up badly.
You always talk about girls.
Hey, where are you going?
- Call Anusha Tyagi.
- Why?
Moron. I am asking you to call her out.
So call.
- How dare you abuse me?
- You prick.
[Man 1] Don't beat me.
Don't beat me.
[Door opening]
[Rudra] There is no age to learn.
And that's why I went to college.
To learn that
the God gives a person
who already
has cancer diabetes too.
Toilet
Come to the 1st floor washroom,
now.
This washroom is closed, baby.
You will have to go downstairs.
[Man 1] Let's go down, baby.
What happened, baby?
Nothing.
- [Muffled screaming]
- [Door closing]
Shh, shh, shh!
- Quiet. Quiet. Quiet.
- [Sobs]
[Breathing heavily]
- Is what your mother told me true?
- What?
Don't you know?
- The kidnapping thing?
- Yes.
You know what will happen
if the plan fails, don't you?
The police will hang us.
Hang us? Then let's cancel it.
- [Exhales sharply]
- I wanna get out of here. I swear.
- What if your dad goes to the cops?
- He won't.
Trust me.
He will not go to the cops.
Listen. You will get your money.
[Anusha chattering indistinctly]
Listen to me carefully.
Tell me. Everything's
going to be alright, isn't it?
- I wanna live a little. That's it.
- [Woman shouting]
- There is someone in the bathroom.
- [Man 1] Come on. Who is it?
Baby.
Baby. Baby.
[Gunshots]
[Door opens]
- [Door opens]
- See where he went.
[Man 2] Check. Check.
[Man 2] Stop. Rascal.
Or I'll shoot. Stop.
Stop.
[Glass shattering]
[Gunshots]
[Gunshot]
[Ranjana] My papa was right.
You should never be friends
or enemies with a policeman.
Look at my love.
I'm in a relation with one.
It's good.
You and your love
will get protection. For life.
Really?
And what will you get from me?
Give me the government files.
To hell with the government.
What are you going to get from me?
I have got you.
Huh? Don't try to trick me.
Has a policeman ever agreed
without his benefit?
I have found my home in you.
Prison is nothing compared to that.
When you talk to me like that
I feel I'm your sister.
I swear not, sister.
You're the only one
I have in my life.
[Rudra] Mother, father,
wife, friends.
Now who do I have?
[Song playing over radio]
[Inhales sharply]
Ranjana. Give me a kiss.
Give me a kiss.
- Not today, Mr. Dubey.
- Why?
I already gave you advance.
Are you fasting today?
I have booked a suite for you.
I don't feel like doing it today.
Never mind the feeling.
- Be a horse.
- What do you mean?
I have learnt something new.
It's English.
Come on. Be a horse.
[Chuckles] Good. Good girl.
Ready. Steady.
- Who's your daddy?
- Hey...
Who's your daddy?
- Tell me. Who's your daddy?
- Ved Prakash Mishra.
Huh? Who's this?
My daddy. You just asked.
No. No.
When I ask who your daddy is,
take my name. My name.
Be a horse.
Good girl. Ranju. [Panting]
Who's your daddy?
- [Cell phone ringing]
- Rudra.
Don't ruin my mood
by mentioning Rudra.
It's his call.
- Hello.
- Ranjana.
Yes. Yes, Rudra? Tell me.
Well...
Well, the job...
I'll not be able to do the job.
Why?
It wasn't the right job.
Are you listening?
Yes, I am. I wish you got it.
Listen. I'll find something...
Move.
Ask. Who's your daddy?
Yes. Good girl.
Ready, steady.
- Who is your daddy?
- Satyanarayan Dubey.
[Moaning]
One more time.
- Who is your daddy?
- Satyanarayan Dubey.
[Growls]
Yes.
[Cell phone ringing]
What is it, witch?
[Madhu] Why are you talking
like that?
I told you not to take the risk
of meeting Anu.
[Whispering] I heard
there was firing in the college.
Find someone else. I can't do this.
Listen. You're really angry now.
Darn it. The girl's condition
is such that she'll pee
if someone asks her name.
- I can't do this.
- Hear me out.
I was expecting what happened.
That's why I was forbidding you.
But you were hell bent
on becoming Tarzan.
Let's talk about this at leisure.
I don't want to talk.
I have spent three years
in jail for no reason.
Do you want me
to repeat the same mistake?
If you need it so badly
you get into it.
Yes, I need it.
And also my daughter.
And you and your family too.
I will manage my family.
You don't worry about it.
What are you going to manage?
Will you be able to?
Your family gets bedded
at some brothel every other day.
- What are you going to manage?
- Shut up, you witch.
Abusing me is not going to help.
You also know the truth.
Your wife works at the factory,
right?
Her employee exploits her
every day.
He is doing the same even now.
Go to Hotel Ishan's top floor
and see for yourself.
Will you be able to see?
- [Door opens]
- [Song playing over TV]
[Door opens]
- Rascal.
- [Ranjana] Rudra. Rudra.
[Dubey screaming]
- [Rudra] You like to sleep around.
- [Ranjana] Rudra.
- [Screams]
- Rudra.
You couldn't find anyone
but my wife to sleep around.
- Rudra.
- [Screams]
- Rudra. Rudra.
- Don't beat me!
- Oh my God!
- He's gonna die!
- [Screams]
- Rudra!
Keep quiet or...
Brother.
Brother, why are you beating me?
Did I rape her?
She comes willingly.
[Breathing heavily] And I am not
sleeping with her for free.
I am talking about this program.
I give her money whenever she asks.
I give her advance month
every month. Do you know that?
She owes me 70,000.
But I have never asked.
I swear on my wife and children.
Ranju, you tell. You tell.
Ranju.
I feel like shooting you
in the head.
What are you? Explain to me.
- At home you behave as if...
- [Screams]
...you'll die without me.
And you're running
this business outside.
I used to see.
I used to see the marks
and scratches on your body.
But I am an idiot
for I did nothing.
Don't I satisfy you?
[Breathing heavily] Huh?
So what could I do?
Die in your memory?
Or go beg on the streets?
Did you leave
behind a treasure for me?
I wasn't getting salary.
My family told me to leave you
if I needed any help.
So what should I have done?
Left you?
Tell me.
Yes. I took money.
But not for myself.
[Crying] Not for myself.
Do you know how much
the lawyers charge every month?
Ever since you've come,
I have told you a thousand times.
Free me from this job.
And you get sloshed every day.
How have I been arranging money
for your booze
since the last three months?
Have you ever asked?
This salary isn't sufficient
even for food.
That man will take something
in return for all that help.
I don't have money on me.
He is using me.
- Hello.
- [Rudra] I will do your job.
But now the ransom
will be 2 crores.
I'll take one crore 30 lakhs.
Agree?
Agree.
[Rudra] This was the biggest mistake
of my life.
[Theme music playing]