[Madhu] You have to kidnap someone.
Kidnap who?
- My daughter.
- What?
It's a matter of one crore.
She's also a part of it.
Firstly I would like to meet Anu.
[Muffled scream]
- I'm really scared.
- [Panting]
I don't want anything
to happen to me.
That girl is so scared
that she'll pee
if anyone raises
their voice in front of her.
I can't do this.
Your wife works in a factory,
doesn't she?
Her boss uses her everyday.
Go and check the top floor
of Hotel Ishan.
He's still with your wife
right now.
I'll do this but now
the ransom amount is two crores.
[Song playing over radio]
[Rudra] The second chapter
of my life starts from here.
And the title is
"Honesty my foot."
The manhood that arose after
watching my wife sleep with Dubey.
Now it was ready to become a brute.
Ranjana has given
the test of her love.
Now it was my turn.
[Rudra] This is 10,000.
Inform at your factory that
you're resigning from tomorrow.
We have a debt of 70,000.
We'll pay it back.
You said that the work is not nice.
I've changed my mind.
I'll return by tomorrow afternoon.
I thought we'll go somewhere
out of town... to roam.
Listen, I have endured it
for so many years.
I will endure it
for a few more days.
You don't have to do anything
that doesn't make you happy.
Or which
you are not supposed to do.
[Rudra] I had a chance to escape,
but I didn't listen to her.
[Man 1] Ticket!
One to Ghaziabad.
- Give me change.
- I don't have it.
The ticket cost is 150.
I haven't sold that many
tickets to give you change.
Give me change.
From where do I give
if I don't have it?
Talk with respect.
Why are you talking rudely?
Sharman, stop the bus.
[Man 1] Get down.
I'm not traveling for free.
I'm paying you.
I'm shouting and telling you
to give me change.
I don't have it.
- Please get down.
- [Cell phone ringing]
- Idiot.
- Yes.
Did you get the wedding
invitation card?
- Yes, I got it.
- [Man 1] Get down.
- So what's your plan?
- I'll call you back.
- Please give me a minute.
- Enough now.
But you must have
thought of something.
- You bloody...
- Rascal.
You'll touch me?
[Stammering] Sharman, take this bus
to the police station.
Yes, take it to the police station.
It's just 1.5 km away.
Tell SHO Mahender Passi
that you have caught me.
Sir, please take change
of 2,000 from me. Okay?
Thank you.
Listen, start the bus.
[All] Yes!
Sir, are you in the police force?
No. I was bluffing.
- This is India. So it works.
- Okay.
[Title Montage]
[Theme song playing]
Ghaziabad
[Song playing over speaker]
[Rudra]  The wedding
was in Ghaziabad.
The girl had a friend named Riya.
I had to go inside
with the wedding procession.
And later kidnap Anu from there
at night.
Anu left for the wedding
in the morning as per the plan.
But her father also
came along to drop her.
[Yawns]
According to Hindi dictionary,
scoundrel means a fool.
But in reality there's a difference
between scoundrel and a fool.
How's that?
Well, the people moving
ahead of us are fools.
And we're scoundrels
that we're following them.
Please elaborate.
Who goes to the wedding early
in the morning?
Idiots!
The entire morning routine
got messed up.
Eating breakfast at
the time of getting fresh
and at the time of breakfast
I am sitting in the car.
Now we won't even get
a breather the whole day
because we will be
guarding this girl.
- Forget using the toilet.
- [Cell phone ringing]
- Yes, sir.
- Did you keep the gifts?
Yes, we've kept it.
It's in our car.
Thank you.
- Bloody rascal! Idiot!
- [Laughs]
Why are you laughing?
[Cell phone ringing]
[Madhu] Listen, I spoke to him.
Please dance. That's how
the plan will be executed.
What plan?
Hello!
- Hello?
- Who's it, Dad?
Your mom had called.
She said, "Please dance. That's how
the plan will be executed."
What's going to happen there?
Dad, dancing is a must
in weddings.
There's a dance performance.
I'll leave it if you say so.
Dear, I'm your father...
not your enemy.
[Man 1] Five! Six! Seven! Go.
[Song playing over speaker]
Cut! Cut! Cut!
Riya, what are you doing?
You're the bride.
- She's got more energy than you.
- [Giggling]
Listen! Riya, you are
playing the role of groom.
You know,
that cool swag style of boys.
That intimidating passion.
Why don't you show us
how to do it, sir?
[Song resumes]
[Man 1] Mr. Tyagi, please come.
[Song playing over speaker]
Our business will be ruined
by all this nonsense.
Riya, come on. Anusha has arrived.
- Anusha has arrived?
- Yes.
- When?
- Right now.
Sir, what are you doing?
- She's the bride.
- So what?
Sir, this is UP, not Mumbai.
These people will
beat us very badly.
We'll go Mumbai via Haridwar
in an urn.
[Man 1] Dude, just wait and watch.
Tonight she'll be mine.
Is the security and
everything alright?
Well, this is a family wedding.
All are family people.
Why are you worried?
Look at this.
I've installed new CCTV
in the entire house.
And there are 16 cameras
everywhere including garden.
Even if someone scratches his butt,
it'll get captured on the camera.
[Laughs]
Where is the monitor room
of these cameras?
[Door opens]
- Yes. This will be nice.
- [Door closes]
We'll keep an eye on her from here.
We will be away from all the drama.
[Tyagi] Dear,
my good wishes are with you.
See you. Bye! Okay!
It was really great
to have you here.
It would have been nice if you
had stayed until the wedding vows.
[Tyagi] I'll reach by 11,
before the wedding vows.
- My daughter is still here.
- Dad.
I also love you a lot.
Always remember it.
I'll come by 11, dear. Okay?
I will take your leave.
- [Engine starts]
- [Door closes]
[Rudra] Tyagi will come back
by 11 in the night.
[Clock ticking]  The wedding
procession is at 7 p.m.
It's an Indian wedding.
Consider it 8 p.m.
It means we'll have 3 hours
of working time.
There are two cameras
outside the house.
Two on the side
and two behind.
Also on the inside.
25 guards, 4 personal.
We will leave from the backyard.
Parking number 3 has less light.
The game will end over here.
But when your luck is bad...
Gurgaon
...how will you prosper.
Listen.
Tell ma'am that
I'll be free soon.
I'll pick Anu from
the wedding house by 9 p.m.
9 p.m.
The wedding procession will
enter the house at 7 p.m.
Why didn't you tell me before?
[Madhu] I didn't know.
I just got the message.
There are cameras and I've
no knowledge what's inside.
What will I do in 2 hours?
Look, do whatever you have to do
because we won't get
this chance again. Please.
- [Crackers Bursting]
- [Drums playing]
[Gunshots]
[Cell phone ringing]
- What's your plan?
- [Rudra] Let me go inside first.
I'll call you back
once I find a way to leave.
Did you explain everything to Anu?
- Listen...
- [Man] Ma'am, food is ready.
I'll eat later.
You'll have only 2 hours.
Just call and tell her
the meeting point.
I won't call Anu. I'll call you.
[Man 1] Hey, why are you talking
on the phone? Come and dance.
Let's dance.
Shucks! Look at that bomb!
Zoom it! Zoom it!
Wow! She's showing her assets.
[Cell phone ringing]
Yes, Munna.
Please keep an eye on the Sardar
standing in front of baby.
Calm down.
I can't hear anything.
Idiot.
[Munna] Can you hear me?
I was asking you to keep an eye
on the tall Sardar
standing in front of Anu.
Because I saw him
staring at Anu.
Are you drinking during shifts?
Stop ogling at girls. Continue bird
watching and enjoy the situation.
Hang up.
[Line ringing]
- Hello!
- There are cameras everywhere.
You didn't inform me
about this arrangement.
What to inform you?
Wouldn't I have kidnapped Anu
if it was so easy?
Police have given a medal to you,
not to me.
[Door opens]
He is the same guy
who was downstairs.
So sorry, big guy, so sorry.
So sorry.
No. No problem! Is there
a bathroom here?
The one downstairs
isn't working.
Dude, go to any room.
All are open.
[Man 1] Listen, I wanted a drink.
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
[Man 2] Hey, Anu has arrived.
[Girls laughing]
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
[Window opens]
[Window closes]
I'm on the first floor.
[Cell phone ringing]
Yes. Tell me.
Go to the last room
on the first floor.
Go fast. He's there.
How do I leave now? I'm with Riya.
I'll move out later...
But... Listen!
[Woman] The number you have called
is currently busy on another line.
[Line ringing]
[Cell phone ringing]
[All clapping, cheering]
[Breathing heavily]
[Cell phone ringing]
[Madhu] I'm calling you
from so long.
Sorry, I couldn't hear.
Yes. I am leaving. Please
stay on line till I go upstairs.
[Man] Okay now. The bride's
family's first presentation.
The bride's friends are coming.
[People clapping, whistling]
Listen, tell him to
wait for 5 minutes.
Why? Is everything okay?
Yes.
But I will not move out
without dancing.
Are you out of your...
You said that your daughter will
come on her own. Where is she?
Please calm down.
Look, if I'm stuck over here
because of your daughter...
[Cell phone beeps]
[Line disconnects]
[Breathing heavily]
[Cell phone chimes]
[Song playing]
[Line ringing]
[All clapping]
[Cell phone ringing]
- [Line ringing]
- [All clapping at distance]
[Song playing over speaker]
[Cell phone ringing]
Where?
What do you mean?
Where are you going?
We're going with you.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Do any one of you want to watch
what's under my skirt?
- What are you saying?
- No. Please come.
Never mind! Please go.
[Munna] We'll stay here.
You please carry on.
Anu, what are you doing here?
Come here.
I'll come with Anu.
Come fast.
[Anusha] Actually I was going
to the bathroom.
[Riya] Go in this one.
Come on.
We'll stay here.
[Man 1] You please go.
[Door opens]
This is ridiculous.
[Door closes]
She thinks we're pervert.
How did I dance?
- Incredible.
- Really.
Like a hot dancer.
[Giggling]
What happened?
- What?
- Aren't you going to the bathroom?
Oh yeah!
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
[Knocking on door]
Who's there?
[Door opens]
- Riya ma'am.
- Sir, you?
Actually I was
doing some touch up.
Oh sorry! Actually I came to
tell you bye because I'm leaving.
So early?
You should have stayed
till the wedding.
I'll have to leave for Mumbai because
I've a shoot day after tomorrow.
Sir, thank you so much.
[Chuckles softly]
I know. It's okay.
- [Slaps]
- You rascal! How dare you?
What do you think of yourself?
Wait! Catch that bloody rascal.
He tried to kiss me.
- Wait, let me show you.
- [Man 1] Hey!
[People clamoring]
[Man 1] Look. A fight is going on.
Oh man! Beat him.
[Man 3] Beat him!
[Riya] He was trying
to be over smart. Huh?
I will teach you a lesson!
Beat him! Romeo, my foot!
[Rudra]For one moment I got unnerved
to see that girl over there.
That inner conscience
of right and wrong.
But that time I was sure that I'll
become a fraud for a minimal time.
So I stopped
the voice of conscience
and moved ahead.
[Man 1] Beat him! Right! Left!
Someone has taken Anu
inside the room.
Call now. Hurry up.
[Door opens]
[Door closes]
What happened?
Someone pushed Anu
in the bride's room.
No one's over here.
He's only watching.
Tell them to close
all the gates.
[Car trunk shuts]
[Man 1] There's a man with black
turban having a moustache and beard,
he shouldn't go out.
Stop the car.
- [Man 2] He doesn't have a turban.
- No. No.
- [Man 3] Let him go.
- [Man 2] Please go.
[Rudra] Anu is with me.
I'll keep you informed.
[Rudra] At that time I didn't
know the truth
that this night will be
the most historic night of my life,
Until today I used to
stop crime.
But now I had committed a crime.
Thus we three went towards
the path of my destruction.
Yes, three of us.
Can't I take the window seat?
- [Rudra] Me, the girl...
- No.
...and my bad luck.
[Theme music playing]