[Rudra] Your daughter
is safe with me.
[Trunk closing]
Arrange for two crores by evening.
Leave for Rishikesh right now.
Baby should be back safe
and sound at any cost.
[Tyagi] Mister, listen.
I haven't been able
to arrange for money.
What!
[Rudra] Listen.
Don't come tomorrow.
The work isn't over.
And money?
If not tomorrow, then I will get it
by day after tomorrow.
[Rudra] You will be identified even
if you stand in a crowd
of thousands.
The veil won't be able to save you.
Don't irritate me.
Get in the bus that
is going to Dehradun.
Money is very powerful.
Once you get hold of it, then your
wrong doings also seem right.
[Knock on the door]
[Knocking]
[Window closing]
[Rudra] Coming.
[Door opens]
The singing troupe has come
for the veneration.
- So?
- So they will need the room.
They had booked it 20 days ago.
I will leave in half an hour.
Shall I send someone
to clean the room?
- No. Not now.
- So?
20 minutes.
[Door opens]
[Panting]
[Breathing heavily]
[Door opens]
- [Man] Look. Is this fine?
- No. A bigger one. A bigger one.
A bigger one?
- Look.
- No, Bigger than this.
I want a big bag.
Explain to me properly.
How big?
What do you want to put in it?
- My wife...
My wife has come
to her maternal home
for the first time after marriage.
[Man] I understood.
Chotu. Bring that suitcase.
Mister, I have understood.
I will give you such
a wonderful suitcase
that all the gifts for your
wife's in-laws will fit in it.
Give me. Give me fast. Be quick.
Here, mister.
This is amazing.
- Fine.
- Rs.726.
[Panting]
[Rudra] It's said that after
dying, body becomes heavier.
The girl's idiocy
added to that weight.
Which she had garnered
by committing suicide.
This weight was
going to break my back.
[Title Montage]
[Prayers]
- [Knocking on door]
- [Man] Mister.
Mister.
[Panting]
[Rudra] Coming. Coming.
Why are you creating a din?
[Door opens]
I am sorry for coming suddenly.
The singing troupe
is getting impatient.
That's why I had to come.
I am done.
Give. I will carry your luggage.
No. No. I will do it. I will do it.
You are going alone.
Your wife isn't to be seen.
She is downstairs.
I saw her at the banks a while ago.
What do you mean?
She was talking to a woman
at the banks.
[Man] Sir.
Take this red cloth too.
For the peace of the soul.
Listen. Is there
any isolated bank here?
Where we can immerse it peacefully?
Go straight and take a right turn.
[Unzips]
[Car honking]
[Car approaching]
Who has come?
[Car squealing]
[Man and woman moaning]
It will go on.
You see, there is nobody
here in the evening.
So my sir comes here.
Who died?
Anyone close?
Shall I do it?
I am a professional.
I will charge Rs.150. Rs.150.
I work part-time as a driver.
Shall I come?
[Woman moaning]
[Man] Come here. Come here.
[Chanting in Sanskrit]
[Anusha] Since childhood
my hands and legs
have never been dirtied in mud.
I got one day's freedom.
At least let me live it
the way I want.
Whether you remember me or not,
it's your choice.
But I will always remember you.
[Door closes]
[Woman moaning]
Immerse it.
Hey! Hey!
Sir. Sir, what have you done?
You had to immerse
the ashes in the water.
You put the entire pot inside.
This isn't how you are
supposed to immerse the ashes.
You are changing the entire ritual.
Rs.150.
- [Man] Give me.
- Hey!
[Man] Hey! Money! Hey!
[Song playing]
[Crowd cheering]
[Unzips]
[Retching]
It's my fault. My fault.
[Slapping]
I made a mistake.
[Crying] My fault.
[Song playing over radio]
[Man] Come on.
Mister.
Where are you bringing this?
If you bring this, where
will I make the passengers sit?
On my head?
The suitcase will go on top.
It's important stuff.
I want to keep it with me.
Yes. So?
Is there a gang of robbers
on the roof?
The luggage will go on top.
- Carefully. Carefully.
- [Man grunts]
Carefully.
- That's it.
I will lose my balance.
That's it.
[Man grunting]
[Chanting in Sanskrit]
Move.
[Grunting]
[Chanting in Sanskrit]
Carefully.
[Man 1] Glory to Hanuman!
[Man 2] Don't drop it.
[Grunts]
[Song playing over radio]
Stop. Stop.
- What happened?
- I will get down here.
[Water running]
[Van approaching]
[Man] Hey! What are you doing here
so late at night?
- I am going home.
- [Man] Is that so?
Where did you steal the bag from?
I am an army man.
36th Garhwal Rifles.
My mother has expired.
So I am going for her last rites.
I didn't get a bus.
So I am going walking.
Where is your mother?
In the bag. Do you want to see?
Why don't you army
people talk straight?
You policemen don't
ask direct questions.
Fine. Fine. Sit.
I will drop you.
No. I will go. I am used to it.
We will adjust. Get in.
[Man] Dharampal, make some space.
Come, soldier.
Come on.
This is not a safe place.
[Man 1] Come on. Come on. Come.
[Man 2] Give me the bag.
What are you looking at?
Give me the bag.
[Man 1] Give me.
[Man 2] It's quite a heavy bag.
[Phone ringing]
Hello.
[Madhu] It's 5:30.
Anu hasn't returned yet.
5:30.
No. I will call.
I will call her.
Sir.
It's quite late.
She should have come by now.
Shall we inform the police, sir?
[Song playing over radio]
[Dubey] Do you know swimming?
No? So why are you
going in the water?
Come up. Come on.
Yes. Come on.
What is it?
No. Day before yesterday
you had told me very haughtily.
"Dubey, tomorrow I will
throw the money on your face."
My face was waiting the whole day.
But it was not hit with money.
I had begged you.
I had begged you yesterday.
Don't leave me.
You were not in
your senses yesterday.
So I have come today
to recover my money.
Policeman, come here. Come.
Come here. Yes.
Stand here.
You have only seen
my affection till now.
Affection.
Now I will show you my temper.
- I will show you my temper.
- [Ranjana grunts]
Dubey, what are you doing?
Don't twist her hand.
- Let's leave from here quickly.
- It's personal. It's personal.
My husband has gone out.
He has the money.
So call him.
Call him. He likes to beat people.
If I don't chop off his arms
and dump it in the Ganges
then tell me.
Is Rudra Shrivastav at home?
No, he ran away.
And he has left this bloody whore here.
Who are you?
My name is Dubey.
I have come to recover my money.
[Man 1] Okay. Leave her hand.
If I don't let go of her hand,
what will you do?
Look. I am explaining in Hindi.
Let go of her hand.
- Leave her.
- Hey, look at him?
Why are you interfering?
Do you have a warrant
to enter the house?
Do you have an FIR?
We are the FIR.
And we are the warrant.
Look from top to bottom.
Let us do our work peacefully.
Or else I will give you
a tight slap.
Is that so? Look at this.
- What is this?
- [Man 1] Look.
[Dubey] I won't spare you.
I told you. His free tea
will get us into trouble.
Scoundrel.
Sir. Sir, I made a mistake.
Never again.
Sir, try to understand.
Sir. Sir, try to understand.
- It won't happen again.
- [Man 1] Shukla.
Take him aside.
Teach him a nice lesson.
- Come on. Do sit ups.
- Sir.
The winner will beat the other two.
- [Man 2] Sir.
- [Shukla] Come on.
They enter the house
without a warrant.
- Rudra Shrivastav?
- He isn't at home.
- You?
- We have come from crime branch.
Where is he?
[Gate opens]
Pick up the phone.
- [Slaps]
- [Shukla] Here. Here you go.
- Hey! why so slowly?
- So gently for him compared to me.
- Sir, this is cheating.
- Okay.
Continue. Continue.
What is the matter?
No. I want to talk to him regarding
a kidnapping case.
Kidnapping?
[Awasthi] Look, Shukla.
Take her statement.
Record it and send Joshi quickly
to submit it in the police station.
The commissioner is calling me.
There is a problem in the signal.
Call from your phone.
We should know what the problem is.
Shukla, have you sent him
to make betel leaf?
From the time I have come he
is not be seen.
[Man] Sir. Sir.
How are you, sir?
Are you going out?
Didn't you recognize us, sir?
We had met.
While peeing.
We had greeted you.
-  Shall we do it again?
- No.
You are here?
Sir, we are waiting for you.
The crime branch officer has come.
- Crime branch?
- Yes, sir.
- I will carry this.
- No. No.
- Give me.
- No. It's my bag.
- I will carry it.
- Sir.
- [Man 1] Hold it.
- Give me.
[Man 2] Give me.
[Rudra] It's said that God's blow
is silent.
When you are in deep trouble
there is still no noise.
The man who had left from home
in the hope of two crores
had returned home
with a young girl's body.
It's quite heavy, sir.
[Rudra] There were
policemen everywhere.
It was very important
to get Ranjana out of here.
But how?
- [Man 1] Come, sir.
- I didn't have the answer.
Rudra Shrivastav?
Yes.
I am Dhiraj Awasthi
from crime branch.
Do you know Govind Tyagi?
He is a rich man.
The owner of a sugar mill.
Yes. I have heard his name.
Look. We suspect that
his daughter has been kidnapped.
- Kidnapped?
- Yes.
Look, since a long time
people have not been
reporting ransom cases.
That's why we had informed all
the banks that whenever a person
withdraws a large amount
from his account,
they should inform us immediately.
The bank has informed us
that Mr. Tyagi
has withdrawn 1 crore
from his account.
We have also found out that
his daughter is missing
since two days.
Do you suspect me?
[Laughing]
Why are you kidding, sir?
Look, sir.
The entire police force know
what had happened with you, sir.
But what to do, sir?
You know that we have no power
in front of politics.
Govind Tyagi's daughter
has been kidnapped.
It's a high profile case, sir.
Who doesn't know, sir?
For such cases there
is no better crime expert
than you in our department, sir.
So the new minister has issued
orders of your return, sir.
Yes, sir.
You are in-charge of Govind Tyagi's
daughter's case, sir.
Congrats, sir.
[Man 1] Congrats, sir.
Congrats, sir. Welcome back.
The case will be solved now.
[Theme music playing]