[Awasthi] You are being appointed
the in-charge
of the Govind Tyagi case, sir.
[Rudra] We have to stop this
investigation at any cost.
[Awasthi] Look at this, sir.
We suspect this tall man.
We will do everything
to solve this case.
Catch all men.
Get anyone you suspect.
[Rudra] Damn Madhu. You witch.
You are trying to strangle me.
Once I find her,
I will teach that witch a lesson.
We have found a body, sir.
We need to go to the hospital.
Rascal.
The entire city is mourning here.
But where is the girl's mother?
[Madhu] Do you need to perform
all investigations now?
- You?
- I am his wife.
Madhu Tyagi.
[Rudra] Has your luggage ever got
exchanged while traveling?
I had gone through that.
In the journey of life.
In my luggage I had a pretty wife.
Job as a policeman.
All in all, I had a happy life.
But when I opened my luggage,
I found a corpse,
a conviction
and I found death waiting.
There was only one way
for me to escape.
If I find Tyagi's wife.
But the face, I have been trying
to find with the name Madhu
today I have only got that face.
I don't even know her name.
I had to die.
So, I just had to find
the best method to die.
I swear on God.
If the greatest morons
of the world were judged...
you would have won the list.
For choosing me.
Forget it.
I had chosen
an honest policeman for myself.
That policeman started being
a moron later.
[Chuckles]
That damned Anu only found me.
If she wanted
to hang herself to death,
she could have done that
in her house.
[Scoffs]
Now I am in the market
with a bowed head.
Anyone can cut me up
and take my pieces.
Listen.
What will you do
if I go for a long time or if I die?
I haven't thought about it.
Think about it.
May I tell you something?
Don't mind.
Everyone is a criminal
in jail, right?
Everyone would be looking
at each other with the same idea.
But in this neighborhood,
I was the only one...
whose husband was convicted.
The entire world would look
at me in the same way.
I don't have the strength
to go through that again.
If you want to save me...
then save yourself.
[Rudra] Damn it.
Now, I even cannot die in peace.
[Temple bell tolling]
Rishikesh
[Man] Sutli.
Sutli.
Listen.
Come out fast.
I have to show you something.
I am not going anywhere.
After this I am going to the temple
for worshipping.
God has answered your prayers.
Thank Him and come out fast.
Rascal!
I am already feeling crazy.
I have left all that.
Come on. Hurry.
I have learnt my lesson.
Look at this.
[Title Montage]
[Woman moaning]
[Boy] Papa.
- Papa.
- Hmm.
Someone has come
to see you downstairs.
- Who?
- There he is.
- Yes?
- My name is Lakshman Saxena.
I am Govind Tyagi's
security adviser.
May I speak to you?
Yes, tell me.
Son, please go outside and play.
Do you know a woman called Ranjana?
I was thinking about her just now.
Tell me.
- [Door opens]
- Rudra.
Rudra.
[Man] Sir.
- [Man] Sir.
- Who is it?
- Sir.
- Wait in the jeep. I am coming.
Sir. Sir, that...
Madam has been called
to the police station.
Why her?
Sir, there has been
a complaint filed against her.
And you have been asked
to come along too.
[Rudra] Tyagi loved only two things
in the world.
One was his money.
And the second was his daughter.
Since his daughter died,
his love for money ended too.
10 crores rupees.
Who announces such a reward,
son of a gun?
[Man] Sir, do you see the crowd
at the police station?
For a reward of 10 crores, even
the dead will come with evidence.
Take the other route.
[Phone ringing]
Who filed the complaint, Shukla?
[Whispering]
Was something lacking that day?
Rascal! I will bury you here.
[Lakshman] Don't do that,
Mr. Policeman.
Anyway,
the common man doesn't have
much confidence in the police.
You are doing this and hurting
their reputation further.
What is he doing here?
You might know him.
Dubey had taken money from him.
He couldn't return it.
So, he filed
a complaint against him.
He is saying that he needs
to take money from madam.
So, he filed
a complaint against madam.
I told you, we will pay you back.
Sir, I am ready to wait.
But he is not able to.
[Lakshman]
That's what money is, madam.
When you need it for yourself,
it's a necessity.
And when someone else asks for it,
it becomes a ransom.
If you had paid on time,
this wouldn't have happened.
Right?
I had paid 10,000.
There was a balance of 60,000 but...
[Lakshman] But?
Your husband didn't hit
the jackpot?
And where did you get
the 10,000 from?
Mr. Shukla ask him,
where they got the 10,000 from?
- Madam.
- Why are you asking her?
Talk to me.
Whom have we complained against?
Madam. Madam, please tell.
Madam, please tell.
He had got a job.
He got an advance of 10,000.
Is it?
Who is so generous here?
The one who is handing out charity.
An advance of 10,000.
Another 60,000 after two days.
Madam, tell me where he is.
I will go there and get the money.
Listen.
You are in the police station
that's why...
That's why I am thinking
of getting arrested.
Of the criminal.
We will get him arrested.
10,000 a day before baby
got kidnapped.
And 60,000 after two days.
That was the promise
made to you, right?
That means
a day after getting the ransom.
Shukla,
the calculations are correct.
And listen.
You had some trouble...
in a hotel a few days ago, right?
Which hotel was that?
Hotel Ishaan.
I will beat the daylights out of you.
Policeman, what's the matter?
- What do you want to say?
- I don't want to say.
I want to rise.
The man
who would have local liquor
by borrowing small amounts
of money from his juniors...
I am sorry,
that tall man.
Where did he get so much money?
[Slaps]
[Man 1] Stop sir. Stop sir.
[Man 2] Stop, sir.
[Man 1] Sir.
[SSP] Mr. Saxena.
What will happen if you start
accusing the police like this?
Sir, may I ask him something?
I will ask only one question.
Just tell me where were you
from 21st to 24th.
Why should I tell you?
Who are you to ask me that?
- Look at this. No.
- Mr. Saxena...
Sir,
just because he has a position
that doesn't mean that
no one will ask him questions.
Let me tell you now.
You were supposed
to go and meet Mr. Tyagi.
Two people knew about that.
Your department.
And our people.
We have checked on all our people.
We found nothing there.
You are sitting in front of Tyagi.
And at that time, that man calls.
That cannot be a co-incidence.
Ask Gupta, sir.
After you went
to Mr. Tyagi's office,
did he call you to talk or not?
Tell me that I am lying now.
I have seen the CCTV footage, sir.
- The man was tall.
- Again, tall.
Shall we arrest Mr. Bachchan?
He is tall too.
Whom are you comparing
yourself too?
Mr. Bachchan doesn't have
to kidnap someone to earn money.
He can do that by working
in a few movies.
Now you are crossing your line,
Mr. Saxena.
You have been appointed here
in some capacity.
Don't forget that.
- Okay?
- Sir.
Yes.
Sir, we have received
the forensic report.
Yes. And...
She was first strangled to death.
And then the corpse
was hanged, sir.
And after that the corpse
was thrown in the river.
Why would someone work so hard?
I am confused.
- Sir, there is another point.
- Hmm.
We have found some hair
on the victim's body
which doesn't belong to her.
It is possible some other woman
was involved.
Who can that woman be?
Why are you looking at me?
I am not married.
You are.
And your wife also has long hair.
I saw that.
I mean...
I am sorry, I interrogated you
without evidence.
I will get the proof next time.
And then I will interrogate him.
- Is everything okay, inside?
- No.
The girl hadn't committed suicide.
She was murdered.
Murdered. How?
Leave for Rishikesh at once.
Nobody else should find that phone.
At any condition.
Do you want me to go alone?
[Rudra] You will have to go alone.
I cannot leave this place.
Sir, that was awesome.
You treated that
watchman Saxena well.
When such people
cross their limits,
I feel like killing them.
And a woman
is involved in this case.
Now even women have started
this business.
You cannot even fathom where
women have their presence, Awasthi.
[Tyagi] Yes?
Any news?
No, sir. Not yet.
Then what are you doing here?
Leave.
Come, when you have any news.
Sir, was Anu friends with anyone?
Friend. Relative.
Anyone she used to talk to.
Meet them.
I knew whom she used to meet.
But...
I don't remember anyone special.
Why?
There must be someone close to her.
No. She didn't have
any friends in college.
The girl whose wedding
we attended,
she used to talk
to her over the phone.
In this city?
No, there is no one.
Sir, please think about it.
We have found out that a woman was
responsible for Anusha's murder.
Think about it properly, sir.
Your daughter was protected.
Only a spy could have broken it.
Some woman?
Who can be that woman?
[Madhu] Whom are you trying to save?
Why? And till when?
Don't talk without my permission.
[Madhu] Will we gain anything
by keeping silent?
Every channel is talking
about baby since yesterday.
Did she even call to ask?
Malini.
She is Anusha's maternal aunt.
But she was always concerned
with baby.
May I speak to her?
Yes, please do so now.
This contains her address
and phone number.
This is also her picture.
We have located Ms. Malini's house.
But sir, no one lives there.
Someone just visits there
every other month.
And yes, sir.
She is also not very neighborly.
Come, sir.
This is the lane, sir.
[Door opens]
Two people go there.
[Awasthi] You three, check that side.
[Door opens]
This was the man, sir.
I swear on my education. I swear
on my mother. Sir, this was the man.
He is walking peacefully
with a girl.
And you are saying
the girl was kidnapped.
Sir, if someone has aimed
a gun at you
then even you
will walk straight like her, right?
Actually,
I saw the pistol in the beginning.
I am a family man.
Why will I mess up
with such a person?
So, I gave him a change
for 2,000 rupees.
I said, take your change
and take away your gun.
And he was troubling
the girl the entire way.
The girl doesn't look troubled.
Sir, you are trifling with me now.
I have left my work
and have come to help the police.
Don't you want
to give the ten crores?
We are not paying.
The girl's father is paying.
But we need to find him first.
Look. Did he look like him?
Yes, he did somewhat look like him?
What do you mean somewhat?
Is it him or not?
Sir, please let me see
the real him.
I will identify him at once.
If we have to get him,
then why do we need you?
Did he look like him?
Sir, he is the one.
He is the one.
[Window opening]
[Door opens]
[Cell phone ringing]
Yes, tell me.
Mr. Policeman,
why are you wasting your time
in that old deserted mansion?
Malini is in Rishikesh.
We have found her.
She has been detained
in the Ghantaghar police station.
Please come,
so that you can meet her too.
Awasthi.
You can meet her today,
Mr. policeman.
[Cell phone ringing]
Listen, Rudra.
[Rudra] Yes, have you reached?
- Yes, I have, but...
- But what?
Someone else has taken the phone.
They were saying
some man came in the morning
and took the phone.
What will you do now?
Stay there. I am coming.
- Where? Rishikesh?
- Yes.
[Temple bell tolling]
[Door opens, closes]
[Lakshman] Come, Mr. policeman.
You are very punctual.
- Where is Malini?
- She is not here.
But you got wings as soon
as you heard her name.
You have reached here
in record time.
Listen.
You might have time
for this nonsense. I don't.
You don't have the time, sir.
You are correct.
As they say, your time is up.
I told you, that next time
I will see you with the evidence.
Meet him.
You went to Ghaziabad in a bus.
Change for 2000.
Hello, sir.
You are unique couple.
[Lakshman]
You sent a message for Anusha
at her college through him.
[Slaps]
And you stayed
in a public lodge in Rishikesh.
I was asking his wife,
why have you come here?
And here is your biggest surprise.
My trump card.
Come on.
The bag of money you ran away with.
The one which contained the corpse.
Did it belong to him?
Yes.
Speak loudly.
Did it belong to him or not?
It belonged to him.
It was.
Mr. Policeman.
Check.
Mate.
[Theme music playing]