[Rudra] Damn Madhu. You witch.
You are trying to strangle me.
We have found a body, sir.
[Madhu] Do you need to perform
all your investigations now?
You?
- I am his wife. Madhu Tyagi.
I have seen the CCTV footage, sir.
- The man was tall.
- Again, tall.
Shall we arrest Mr. Bachchan?
Mr. Bachchan doesn't have
to kidnap someone to earn money.
He can do that by working
in a few movies.
[Rudra] I only had one way
to escape.
If I find Tyagi's wife.
But the face, I have been trying
to find with the name Madhu,
today I have only got that face.
I don't even know her name.
[Laxman] I told you that next time
I will see you with the evidence.
Check. Mate.
[Rudra] After I was exposed,
there was a sudden silence.
There was just a long dead sound.
And suddenly I started
to hear music.
[Song playing]
[Rudra] And then I started seeing
Ranjana everywhere.
And then I was only sorry
about one thing.
Damn! Why did I get married?
Now shall I save myself
or Ranjana?
And if I want to save Ranjana
then how to save her?
I was stuck in this quagmire.
And then he said his dialogue.
You are tall, Mr. Policeman.
But your deeds are very small.
What did you think?
You will investigate
the murder you have committed.
The world is foolish.
Nobody will find out anything.
But you forgot that there
is always someone over everyone.
If you want,
you can start revering me.
In future with my blessings
you will solve all cases easily.
Only if you have a future left.
Right now.
On the charge of kidnaping
and murder of Anusha Tyagi...
please arrest him.
[Rudra] Enough respect.
I will lay your mother.
There was no option left now.
I had to show my real self.
[All screaming]
[Gun cocks]
- [Gunshot]
- What are you doing? Sir.
Sir, wait. Sir.
He will be caught, sir.
This is a very small town.
It is not a big challenge
for you to worry so much.
Shukla, I am not troubled
about challenges.
I am troubled by the morons
surrounding me.
A man came in the police station
and left after assaulting
so many men.
Nobody could do anything to him.
They are shooting outside.
- On whom?
- Sir.
One is bound to shoot the criminal.
You need to catch him, rascal.
[Title Montage]
Sir, we have found him.
Send a troop near
the Pushkar temple.
Where is he?
Catch him. Hurry.
[Man 1] Sir,
we have tracked his phone.
- [Man 1] Triveni Ghat.
- [Man 2] Triveni Ghat.
Anybody there at Triveni Ghat.
We are in Triveni Ghat.
Tell us the position.
Take right from Dhyanchand Ashram.
Hurry.
[Man 1] Walk fast.
Dhyanchand Ashram. Fast.
- Hello, Bhatnagar.
- [Bhatnagar] Yes, sir.
Shoot the rascal on sight.
[Man 1] Walk absolutely straight.
[Man 1] The phone is getting tracked
in Ved Niketan.
Anyone at Ved Niketan?
Send a troop near Ved Niketan.
[Rudra] I want to be a millionaire.
And I have used all my lifelines.
Fate has made such
a game out of life
where every level
was much harder than the previous.
And if that
was not enough for me,
I had also called Ranjana here.
And it was impossible
for her to escape from here.
And also for me to save her.
[Man 1] Walk straight from the lake.
He has changed
his way towards Gita Bhawan.
- Walk straight from Gita Bhawan.
- What the...
Turn left from Gita Bhawan. Hurry.
Walk towards Laxman Jhula.
Walk towards the shops
near Laxman Jhula.
[Man 1] He has entered
the shop Tirupati Gems.
Go there.
Send one troop there.
Hurry.
Go to Tirupati Gems.
He has entered Tirupati Gems.
Tirupati Gems.
[Panting]
Stay outside.
We will go and check inside.
Awasthi, call him.
- [Gun cocks]
- One minute. What are you doing?
We can at least shoot his leg.
Call him.
[Cell phone ringing]
- It is ringing inside.
- Shh.
- [Cell phone ringing]
[Line ringing]
[Awasthi] Hello, sir.
Awasthi, did you catch him?
No, sir. He has vanished.
How can such a tall huge man vanish
in front of you?
Sir. Sir, he is tall.
He is not a moron.
[Cell phone ringing]
- Hello?
- Where are you?
[Ranjana] What is this number?
I will call from here.
Where are you?
I am in front of the Ashram.
Leave that place now. At once.
Take the bus and don't go home.
What do you mean?
Where do I go?
Go wherever you want to.
- What happened?
- I will tell you later.
- Okay, listen.
- [Line disconnects]
Sir, don't worry.
He won't be spared, sir.
Yes.
Sir.
It would have been better
if you speak to the ministry.
[Mishra] Shut up, jackass! Can't you
answer my question properly?
I have already related
the entire tale.
I told you that in my life
I never had any personal...
Shut up!
Otherwise I will shoot you.
Always speaking in Tamil.
Can't you speak in Hindi?
Look, it is time for me
to start my prayers.
You are making me
sit here forcefully is
trespassing on my wishes
and rights...
[Gun cocks]
Please have
the work done peacefully, Mr. Sage.
Otherwise we will shoot you.
Your prayers
will get completed here.
Look there carefully.
And did the government
only give you a stick?
No. I have a gun too.
Then, why aren't you using it?
Stop.
- Sir.
- Huh.
Is this the same woman?
The one who came to the collect
the phone from you. Look carefully.
I am not sure.
I cannot see her face.
[Sobbing]
[Gun cocks]
[Chanting in Sanskrit]
Her face is hidden.
"Hare Krishna. Hare Krishna."
"Hare Rama. Hare Rama."
Get that policeman's wife's photo.
Right now. At once.
Which policeman, sir?
- [Slaps]
- Damn!
The policeman who just fooled you
a little while ago and ran away.
[Door opens]
[Cell phone ringing]
- Hello?
- [Rudra] Where are you?
You told me to go to bus stop.
I am there. Where are you?
Listen. Leave for Shandila at once.
- Listen.
- [Line disconnects]
Sir. One minute.
Shandila.
[Woman] There is a curfew all over.
Anusha Tyagi's murder had
been planned by no one else
but the most able policeman
of the force.
Rudra Shrivastav.
He is the same Rudra Shrivastav
who was also punished
for three years for taking bribes.
And we have just got
a huge revelation
about this case just now.
And look at this.
[Cell phone ringing]
What happened?
Have you left?
How do I leave?
Didn't you see the TV?
[Man on TV] Look carefully
at these two faces.
According to the police
senior inspector of
Haridwar, Rudra Shrivastav
had committed this murder.
And his wife Ranjana Shrivastav
is also his ally in this crime.
Look at them carefully.
Rudra and Ranjana Shrivastav.
They together killed
an innocent child.
And then threw her body
into the river Ganga.
No one could imagine
that Ranjana Shrivastav
who looked like a simple
housewife could be a murderer.
[Rudra] Till now I was lying,
that I had done all this
for Ranjana.
When the truth the result
for what I have done to Ranjana
was in front of me.
In spite of her telling me not to,
I chose the evil way.
And now even Ranjana has
to pay for my sins.
- [Ranjana] Now what?
- Listen. Leave.
Walk towards Ram Jhula.
I will call you.
Rudra, I am scared.
Listen. You will be fine.
I won't let anything happen to you.
Please leave.
[Man] Near Siddharth Ashram.
Seen near Siddharth Ashram.
Hurry.
[Cell phone ringing]
- Where are you?
- I...
[Panting]
I won't be able to run anymore.
Why are you running?
The police are after me.
I am bound to run.
You will stand out if you run.
Why didn't you tell me that before?
I can feel that
I will be caught now.
Where are you?
[Ranjana] Chandan Chowk.
[Man] Check near Hanuman Temple.
Listen. Walk towards
Kailash Gali and Maya Kund.
I know where they are.
Go down and turn left.
- Rudra.
- Go.
[Woman] Look at these
two faces carefully.
According to the police,
senior inspector of Haridwar,
Rudra Shrivastav
had committed this murder.
And his wife Ranjana Shrivastav
is also his ally in this crime.
Rudra and Ranjana Shrivastav.
They together killed
an innocent child.
And then threw her body
into the river Ganga.
- Look at them carefully.
- These two have been trapped.
And Malini?
Get lost!
I don't know where I am.
Go to some other lane besides
Kailash Lane and Maya Kund.
Whom do I ask?
People will recognize me.
Ranjana, ask someone.
Left, right. Any lane.
Take that.
Dear, which one
is Maya Lane and Kailash Kund?
Aunty, there they are.
[Rudra] I was trying my best
to save Ranjana.
But I don't know why,
she started being an idiot.
I won't be able
to escape like this.
I should surrender.
Don't talk like an idiot.
Just listen to me.
Look, we might not meet again.
So, listen.
I have not sold your police medal.
I had hidden it so
that wouldn't get stolen. [Sniffs]
It's in the flour canister
in the kitchen.
It's in the fourth flour canister.
[Man] Go straight from Anand Dham.
I was angry,
so I said that for effect.
Keep it safely. Okay?
[Man] Look towards Ganga Ghat.
Turn right. Turn right. Now.
I am here. Now?
[Man] We can see a boy
in black shirt near Gaud Ashram.
Check him.
There's police everywhere.
Ranjana, nothing will happen.
Walk straight. Listen to me.
They are coming towards me, Rudra.
They are coming towards me.
Look down and walk straight.
[Man] Go straight from Anand Dham.
Walk straight.
Go left from Durga temple.
Check there.
Turn left.
I have kept your insurance...
...papers under my saris.
In the wardrobe.
Please take them.
Listen.
Does one get insurance money
if one gets hanged?
Ranjana, stop talking nonsense.
And continue to walk straight.
[Man] Look towards Peri road.
They are behind me.
They will move.
Go straight and take a left
from Chandrabhag road.
Rudra,
I think they have recognized me.
[Man] Check near Betal Ashram.
Near Betal Ashram.
They are also coming towards me.
Drop your bag and bend down.
Now walk straight.
And listen.
Don't think about what happened
with Dubey.
I did all that for your sake.
I really love you a lot.
I will wait for you even
in my next life.
Do you see Ram Jhula?
Are you even listening to me?
Do you want me to concentrate here
or listen to you?
- Where are you?
- In hell.
You are not listening to me at all.
Ranjana,
this is not the time to joke.
I am on the other
side of Ram Jhula.
Come here. So, that
I can take you to a safe place.
Where are you?
I am in Ram Jhula. Where else?
I saw you. Come ahead.
Phone...
Walk ahead.
[Gun cocks]
- Awasthi, move.
- No, sir.
Don't put me in trouble, sir.
I consider you my idol.
Sir, I cannot believe that
I will have to arrest you.
And sir, please.
Don't do anything rash.
Don't make me shoot, sir.
Please.
- Awasthi, my wife...
- No.
Sir.
I am Awasthi, sir.
This is my service revolver.
Please return it.
I will lose my job.
I am losing everything, Awasthi.
I will need this
if I want to save something.
- I can't return it.
- Look, sir.
I am already divorced once.
I have somehow got
a second match, sir.
If I lose my job,
I will also lose the girl, sir.
- Try to understand my situation...
- [Gunshot]
Damn! [Sighs deeply]
[Cell phone ringing]
Hello.
Stop this investigation, Mr. Tyagi.
I am requesting you.
My wife has been nabbed.
And Awasthi was killed
in front of me.
That was bound to happen, you dog.
You and your lowly wife.
Don't say anything about her,
Mr. Tyagi.
Keep her away from all this.
I accept that
I kidnapped your daughter.
But my wife is innocent.
I am begging you, Mr. Tyagi.
Everything will go wrong.
You have already done
the wrong deed.
Now you are going to pay for it.
Everything will go wrong for you,
Mr. Tyagi.
Everything will go wrong for you.
I don't have anyone
but Ranjana in my life.
If anything happens to her then
to hell with the police
and damn you.
I will find you.
And I will be damned
if your daughter's memorial
and your funeral is not observed
on the same day.
If you think I am lying,
then you can wait and see.
[Screaming]
[Theme music playing]