[Rudra] I only had one way
to escape.
If I find Tyagi's wife.
I am his wife. Madhu Tyagi.
[Laxman] I told you,
that next time
I will see you with the evidence.
Check. Mate.
Shukla, I am not troubled
about challenges.
I am troubled
by the morons surrounding me.
[Rudra] Stop this investigation,
Mr. Tyagi.
I am requesting you.
My wife has been nabbed.
And Awasthi was killed
in front of me.
That was bound to happen, you dog.
I don't have anyone
but Ranjana in my life.
If anything happens her, then to
hell with the police and damn you.
[Sighs]
[Sighs deeply]
He is a great rascal.
He used him as a shield
and escaped. Tell me.
- [Man 1] Stop. Stop.
- [Glass shattering]
- [Man 1] Stop the truck.
- [Man 2] Check both the bikes.
[Man 1] Give me the papers.
[Man 2] Constable.
Check that truck.
[Man 3] Yes. Yes. I will check it.
- [Man 3] Come on.
- [Truck door opens]
Show me your papers.
[Man 3] Look carefully. Check.
Check the side. Check there.
Look there.
There is nothing here.
Let's go to the next vehicle.
Move. Let the truck go.
- Let me go.
- Look...
Kiss me again.
How much more should I kiss you?
I have already kissed you a lot.
Kiss me again.
And kiss me so hard that I shiver.
- [Door opens]
- [Woman screams]
Who is it? Goodness.
Sir. Sir Rudra.
Sir. Sir. Listen.
She is my lawfully wedded wife.
Teechku is having exams.
So, we can't make noise
in the house.
That's why we have come
to the hotel, sir. [Sobbing]
Sir, I am telling the truth.
I swear. I swear on my mother.
Listen, sweetheart.
Show him your nuptial thread.
She is my lawfully
wedded wife, sir.
What are you doing, sir?
I have done nothing, sir.
[Title Montage]
[Man] Mr. Dubey?
The phone
with an international number.
Where one cannot trace the number
the call came from.
Give me that phone.
I am in a hurry.
[Man] Is everything okay?
Nothing is okay.
I can't even tell you.
Please give it first otherwise my
family will get in danger. Hurry.
[Man] Okay. Wait.
- [Man on TV] Who's your daddy?
- [Woman moaning]
Who's your daddy?
- Tell me. Who's your daddy?
- [Woman moaning]
Who's your daddy?
- [Man] Who's your daddy?
- [Woman moaning]
[Man] Sorry, Dubey.
Daddy. Sir. Mr. Gupta,
give that please. Please hurry.
[Dubey] Sir, this is an
international number.
It is the number you wanted.
Sir, can we leave?
[Cell phone ringing]
- Hello?
- Mishra. [Panting]
Has someone come to ask
for ransom money for my wife?
[Mishra] Sir, where are you?
Don't ask questions.
There is no one here, sir.
[Breathing heavily]
Listen. Give me a number.
[Cell phone ringing]
Hello?
This is Rudra calling.
[Panting]
I called your husband.
But he didn't understand,
so I am talking to you.
Look,
I cannot stop Mr. Tyagi.
I don't want you
to request anyone on my behalf.
I just need one help.
Tell me where is Malini.
No one stays
at the address you gave us.
Do you have any other address
where I can find her?
There is no one in her family.
She has an uncle.
But if he is alive or not...
Yes, give me his address.
I will find her there.
Look, Rudra.
These are not good people.
You are already in deep trouble.
Don't mess this up further.
Just save your own life.
I am trying to save my life,
Ms. Madhu.
I am just scared that if something
happenes to my life...
then I will kill many people.
I will have a blood bath
in this city.
Give me the address now.
[Gunshot]
- [Door opens]
- [Gunshots]
[Door opens]
- [Gunshot]
- [Rudra groans]
[Footsteps, panting]
[Rudra] I had only bowed
to two people in my life.
One was God.
And the other was Mr. Dilip Kumar.
There was a dialogue in his movie.
When man has lost everything,
he can only win.
But I was dying.
I lost faith on God,
three years ago.
Today I lost faith
on Mr. Dilip Kumar too.
After the flat incurred
in the journey of life...
it was difficult to move ahead.
And here, on the bridge
on top of river Ganga.
I was lying here
and thinking when...
When and at what time?
[Wind blowing]
[Footsteps approaching]
[Woman laughing]
The fair moon's teasing
rays of lights.
They were playing
in the water bodies.
The clean moonlight
was spread on the earth and sky.
- You wrote this?
- Yes.
Tell me the truth.
You made Brother Pankaj write it,
right?
I wrote it myself.
If that's the case then recite it.
- Show me.
- Why?
If you have written it,
you should remember it too.
I wrote it. I haven't memorized it.
I don't have such a strong memory.
May I say?
There was a poet called
Maithili Charan Gupt.
He had written a similar poem.
Did he steal from you?
Forget it. Forget it.
- Hey.
- No. No.
There is no value
for initiative nowadays.
Why are you getting angry?
Okay, listen, Rudra.
Turn around.
You don't have a strong memory.
But do you have
a strong heart, right?
Will you be able to bear my love?
Test and see.
I will be with you always in life.
[Groans]
Ah!
Will you have tea?
[Panting]
You?
I want to say sorry to you.
I was the one who suggested that
you should be made part
of this game.
I am embarrassed that...
you are in this condition
because of me.
Who are you?
Harish Chowdhari.
I am Malini's uncle.
Take this.
I didn't have you attacked.
And I don't even stay
in that house.
Don't worry.
Right now, there is no danger here.
Where... Where is Malini?
I will tell you.
Before that,
you need to know a few things.
[Turns the stove off]
Malini's dad, Mr. Narayan Dixit...
was my brother-in-law.
He owned Narayan Sugar Mills.
Tyagi would only work for him.
Mr. Narayan had two daughters.
- [Kids laughing]
- [Harish] Yamini and Malini.
There was a difference
of 11 years between them.
Mr. Narayan made his will
the day he started his third mill.
That after his demise everything
will be owned by his two daughters.
And after the daughters,
their children will own them.
Yamini was smart so
after a few years brother-in-law
gave the responsibility
of the business to her.
And retired himself.
Tyagi used to work under Yamini.
But who knows
what this rascal did...
but Yamini became crazy about him.
Even brother-in-law
raised no objections.
He got the two married.
Brother-in-law died and
Yamini fell ill at the same time.
She was suffering
from tuberculosis.
And maybe a golden chance
for Tyagi.
He didn't get Yamini
treated properly.
He just got a nurse
for her as a show off.
She would keep an eye on her
instead of taking care of her.
- [Coughs]
- When Yamini's condition worsened,
she was forced to assign
power of attorney to Tyagi.
- [Clapping]
- [Man] Congratulations, sir.
[Harish] One by one, Tyagi sacked
the people close to Yamini.
Even I was the legal adviser
of this company for many years.
Malini was not interested
in business.
But she owned half the business.
That's why on Yamini's request
she started coming to office.
And Tyagi didn't like that.
And he started a big game.
[Harish] After Yamini's death,
he brainwashed Malini.
He started telling her
that no one can take better care
of Anu than her.
He cried in front of her.
Begged her.
In the end... he slept with her.
And one day he fooled her
into signing off
her share of property to him.
Malini was already crazy in love.
She signed the papers
without reading them.
The very next day,
Tyagi threw her out of the house.
And this is how this rascal
took over the property
of both the sisters.
Anu was there.
And then she died too.
[Rudra] That rascal Tyagi.
Even I had become
a part of the list
whom he had ruined in his life.
[Bottle shattering]
- [Song playing]
- [Clapping]
- [Man 1] Damn.
- [Man 2] It's my turn now.
- Sir.
- Yes.
Look, he is watching a video.
Yes, show it to sir.
What?
- Show. Show.
- Sir.
- Yes.
Is it very expensive abroad?
Yes, it is. Do you want to go?
I want to.
I have seen on the internet that
the girls are very forward there.
They lie easily on the sea beach
in their underwear.
And they don't even mind
if you make a comment.
I am sick of taking off saris here.
[All laughing]
If you are not able to pay
then the same girls will have you
screwed from behind.
[All laughing]
You should continue with the saris.
That's what suits you. Okay?
- This rascal wants to go abroad.
- [All laughing]
- [Cell phone ringing]
- [Man] Abroad?
Mr. Policeman, I have been
waiting for your call since 3 days.
You could have at least told me
if you are dead or alive.
Your wife is ready here
to give you a surprise.
I will have her talk to you.
Why talk?
Why don't you look at her?
The thing is madam
is a little under today.
We have dosed her well.
I think she is drunk.
Right?
Why are you running around,
Mr. Policeman?
If you have committed the crime
then just surrender yourself.
Otherwise, look behind you.
Dubey is standing.
He has lost his trousers.
Dubey, show your hands.
Show your hands.
Do you see that? Huh?
We have already got him ready.
We just need to tell him to go.
Anyway your wife
is his old flame.
The oil bottle.
Show him the oil bottle.
He has applied that at home.
Make me talk to Ranjana.
Of course. She is your wife.
Talk to her.
Take.
Take this.
It's your husband. Talk to him.
Tell him, how you are
going to have fun today.
Rudra.
[Breathing heavily]
Do you remember the song from
the movie 'Kabhi Haan Kabhi Naa?'
[Rudra sing "Ae Kash Ke Hum"]
I had promised you, right?
Dubey, wear your trousers.
And listen,
you poor man's James Bond.
Yes, Mr. Policeman.
If you even touch Ranjana...
then apply Dubey's left over oil
on your behind.
[Sniffs] You made a huge mistake
by nabbing my wife.
You want me, right? Right?
I am coming.
And you will only
try to finish me off.
But don't hurry.
Because I have got
all the records of your sins.
What are you saying, Mr. Policeman?
[Laughs]
You can hear it tomorrow live.
If you think this is nonsense...
you are allowed to shoot my wife.
[Theme music playing]