I am his wife. Madhu Tyagi.
[Laxman] I told you,
that next time I will
see you with the evidence.
Check. Mate.
[Rudra] Stop this investigation,
Mr. Tyagi.
I don't have anyone
but Ranjana in my life.
That was bound to happen, you dog.
[Gunshot]
- [Rudra] You?
- [Harish] I am Malini's uncle.
I didn't have you attacked.
And I don't even
stay in that house.
[Laxman] Why are you running
around, Mr. Policeman?
If you have committed the crime
then just surrender yourself.
I am coming.
And you will only
try to finish me off.
But don't hurry.
Because I have got all
the records of your sins.
[Gun cocks]
[Cell phone ringing]
- Hello?
- [Rudra] Meet me at Har Ki Pauri
at 10 o'clock.
I want to show you something.
And listen.
Get your entire army.
Anything can happen today.
Even you know
what is going to happen.
[Rudra] No, Tyagi.
Maybe only I know.
Be ready.
[Title Montage]
[Theme song playing]
- Yes, sir.
- [Tyagi] Saxena,
that policeman was calling.
He has called us
at Har Ki Pauri at 10 o'clock.
I am sending you his number.
Find out his location.
Right away, sir.
And yes.
What papers does he have?
[Muffled voice]
Sir. Sir, one minute.
[Gargles, spits]
Sir, whatever papers he might have
they will be confiscated.
Don't worry about that.
Finish of that rascal
at any condition today.
Finish off both, him and his wife.
Sir, let us deal with him first.
We can deal with his wife later.
[Cell phone ringing]
Hello?
[Laxman] I have sent you a number.
- Find out where is it from?
- Yes.
This looks like
a number from Khuswad.
That means the policeman is there.
Yes.
Do one thing. Finish that rascal.
He has called us to Har Ki Pauri
at 10 o'clock.
We will conduct that
rascal's last rites there today.
- Okay. Leave.
- Yes, sir.
Yadav.
[Jeep door opens]
[Jeep door closes]
I will shoot you,
if you make a sound.
Just drive as I tell you to.
[Engine starts]
[Door opens]
[Panting]
- Where is Ranjana?
- I don't know.
Where is Ranjana?
You...
[Grunts]
I won't ask again.
Where is Ranjana?
I won't tell you. You scoundrel.
Kill me. I am not scared.
- [Man] Don't shoot, sir.
- [Door opens]
He is a great rogue, sir.
Not you, sir. We will kill him.
He killed Awasthi.
Have you lost it?
- You will kill me, rascals.
- Shut up!
[Gunshot]
- For Awasthi.
- [Gunshot]
[Thud]
[Cell phone ringing]
Yes? Is the job done?
How will the job get done?
He has been shot dead.
He is not ready to move.
Get up. Come on.
Come.
[Jeep door opens]
[Jeep door closes]
We have got some stuff. Evidence.
That rascal Tyagi.
[Panting]
Only the one at top are real.
[Car door opens]
- [Engine starts]
- [Car door closes]
[Car door opens]
[Car door closes]
Spread out.
I want a man in every corner.
Cover the entire Ghat.
Leave in two in every direction.
Be alert. Hurry.
And listen, keep your phones
and walkie-talkies on.
Come on.
- [Car door opens]
- [Car door closes]
[Car door closes]
Look there.
He is not here, sir.
[Cell phone ringing]
Hello? Yes, sir.
[Tyagi] Has he come?
No, sir. Not yet.
What is this man thinking, Saxena?
He has called us
in such a crowded place.
With the entire force.
Even I am trying
understand that, sir.
As to what he is thinking.
He might be fooling us.
Sir, maybe he won't come.
He is bound to get scared
to come out in such a place
- to such a huge army, sir.
- [Laughing]
- I mean he will get frightened.
I will keep you updated, sir.
- What? What?
- No.
What no? What no?
I am here.
He will come.
What?
- We'll have to deal with two of you.
- [Cell phone ringing]
- Yes, what?
- Remove your hand from her hair
otherwise I will cut your hand off,
watchman.
Listen. Listen. Listen. All of you.
The policeman is here. Find him.
Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. I saw him.
He is going towards
the temple lane.
Follow him. Follow him.
And listen.
Cover the other end of the lane.
Finish him off as soon
as you see him. Got it?
[Screams, growls]
Has anyone see the policeman?
No. None of them had seen me.
[Laughing]
Rudra.
[Cell phone ringing]
Has he come?
Yes, sir, he is here.
So?
Nothing, sir.
We will surround him now.
We will finish him off today.
[Man 1] Sir,
he is coming towards me.
If he is coming towards you
then kill the rascal.
Why are you telling me?
There are a lot of people here.
How do I shoot?
Shoot. I will deal with everything.
Come on, shoot.
- [Cell phone ringing]
- Hello?
If you want, we can play
this game the entire day.
Huh? Send men,
and I will continue to kill them.
But the matter won't get resolved.
- What do you want?
- Let Ranjana go.
I am coming to the Ram Temple
with the papers.
Oh no.
Mr. Policeman,
you cannot call the shots now.
Hold the documents.
And stop making conditions.
I am sending you a video.
Watch it.
Maybe you will change your mind.
Ram Temple.
[Laughing]
- [Cell phone ringing]
- Yes?
[Laxman] Sir, he has called us
behind the Ram Temple.
And sir...
he has nabbed your wife.
[Bone snapping]
- Sir, where are the other people?
- Huh?
- Where did the two go?
- Hey!
You are still doing drama,
Mr. Policeman.
No matter what you do, rascal.
Don't expect to return alive.
Tyagi, I am sure that
I will return alive.
And with my wife.
You lied to me that
you had documents, right?
I have got your birth chart.
To become the owner
from an employee,
you first killed Malini
and then Anu.
Are you trying to say
that I have killed Anu?
Yes, rascal.
She was my life.
Then why did you send
fake currency as ransom.
Fake...
What are you saying?
Why would I do that?
I didn't send any fake currency.
Trust me.
Rudra.
[All screaming]
Ma'am, it is not right here.
What are you doing?
Someone might get shot.
Run away from here.
Don't go towards him.
He will surely shoot you.
[Gunshot]
The bullet was so
close to my ear, Rudra.
I can still hear it tinging.
[Rudra grunts]
Did you save me
so that you can kill me?
Good, that you have a very bad aim.
Otherwise I would be with
my grandpa in heaven and crying.
Why are you beating him?
- He will not run...
- Shut up.
[Rudra grunts]
You are also getting beaten.
- [Car door opens]
- [Engine starts]
[Tyagi] Hurry. Hurry.
Drive fast. Drive fast.
Have you lost your mind?
I told you to go home?
Where are you going?
Don't you want
to see the documents, Mr. Tyagi?
I am taking you to show you that.
You...
Rascal.
Kill me if you want to.
First check out the documents.
What documents are
you fooling me with?
I don't know. Look for yourself.
[Screaming]
- [Car door opens]
- Come, Tyagi. Come.
- The documents are here.
- [Car door closes]
- Come. Come.
- [Car door opens]
- [Shukla] Come.
- [Car door closes]
Come. Inside.
- Where is it?
- It's ahead. Go ahead.
Go. Go.
[Door closes]
Hey. Hey. Hey. Rascal.
Open it.
Rascal.
Why have you locked me here?
Hey. Open it.
Open...
Who is there?
Damn.
[Footsteps]
- You?
- What happened?
Are you shocked to see me here?
You killed Anu?
Don't blabber.
And don't accuse me
for what you have done.
As per the police records,
a woman's hair was found
on Anu's body.
And I know that they belong to you.
If you hated me then
you would have dealt with me.
You killed that innocent child.
You made the plan with
that rascal policeman, right?
Yes.
And Anu was also a part of it.
I had planned it after asking Anu.
And we were sure that you
won't let anything happen to Anu.
Because you love, Anu.
Do you even understand
what you are saying?
Or are you just blabbering?
Will I kill Anu?
The day Anu died,
I met her in Rishikesh.
My hair was found on her body
because I was trying to save her.
From your minion, Laxman.
I think we have reached
at the right time.
[Grunts]
You always knew
where they were taking Anu?
Rascal. You wretch.
You betrayed the one who
employed you for so many years.
[Laxman] You did it for
your selfish reasons, Mr. Tyagi.
Since the truth is getting revealed
so pay attention.
And then I will be
able to die in peace.
I killed your daughter.
[Laxman] The day I went to
meet Malini at her home,
I checked her phone.
I had doubts so I left
a man to keep an eye on her.
I had gone to take
the ransom from bank.
But I changed the currency
before giving them to you.
When you made me
get down from the bus,
I got word that Malini
has left her home.
I followed her.
[Knocking on door]
The work would have become easy
if Malini was not there with baby.
Let her go.
[Grunting]
[Choking]
[Laxman] I thought Malini had died,
so I threw her away.
Unfortunately for me, she lived.
You betrayed me for such
a small amount. Rascal.
It was not small, Mr. Tyagi.
Narayan Sugar Mills.
[Mishra] When will this climax end?
And you are talking
about betrayal, Mr. Tyagi.
You must be used to it.
You got your wife murdered.
By her nurse.
I know because...
[grunts]
...I had got that nurse appointed.
My wife-to-be.
Madhu.
The plan was to kill both,
you and your daughter.
So I thought,
I will kill baby first.
[Gunshot]
No. No.
[Sobbing] No.
[Crying]
[Rudra] I understood her,
when she gave me uncle's address
and there I found
the police to welcome me.
I just didn't know
which team was she rooting for.
And today, even after seeing you,
she started to advance
towards Laxman.
And Laxman lost grip over his gun.
And then it struck me.
You really escaped, Mr. Tyagi.
It was your turn next.
And then she would
become the only owner
of Narayan Sugar Mills.
You...
[Gunshot]
Hey.
Put it down. Put it down.
Turn off the phone.
Shoot. Kill everyone.
Start from me.
I have lost the fear
to die a long time ago.
But I will give you
something before dying.
Do you want to see?
Uncle.
Seema. Our daughter.
The owner of Narayan Sugar Mills.
Unfortunately, you are her father.
[Mishra] Another twist.
The climax is not getting over.
Do you think I will believe you?
Malini, I don't trust you at all.
It doesn't matter
if you believe it or not.
The court will believe this.
DNA test.
The day you threw me
out of the house,
I knew that
I was pregnant with Seema.
You needed two crores for her?
For her treatment.
She is also your daughter, right?
There is problem with her blood.
She needs to undergo transfusion.
I needed 70 lakhs.
The rest was for him.
[Mishra] I think my phone memory
card will get full.
But their climax will not get over.
What can I do for her?
What can I do?
You just need
to stay away from her.
You know about the will.
Once she is 18 years old,
she will come on her own
to ask for her rights.
And you know.
Anu used to feel suffocated
in the prison of your house.
She herself wanted
to get out of that place.
So live, Govind.
Live in your jail.
Alone.
And count your days.
Malini.
[Gunshot]
[Thud]
- Are you okay?
- Hmm.
Did they beat you a lot?
They beat me for three days.
And then they also made me drunk.
But it was awesome, boy.
Top quality.
Listen.
Find out where they
got the stuff from.
[Muffled laugh]
I am correct.
There is no one to ask.
Everyone is finished.
Let's go home.
Try to shake them a little.
They might still be alive.
Ask them kindly.
They will tell you.
There is no one left to ask kindly.
Let's go home with the policeman.
What policeman?
Who made you a policeman?
You cannot find out about stuff.
They don't allow you
to wear the uniform.
And I have seen
your humanity today.
It's nothing.
[Laughs]
You have no quality
to be a policeman.
[Laughs]
[Theme music playing]