written and sync : Hadi Farsi
Hadi.Farsi@Yahoo.Com
Do you know what they did to my brother , and my mother ?
I lie awake all night , thinking about how they died
What good is power , if you can not protect the ones you love ?
We can avenge them
Well that time I was gone
The world's fallen apart
Always keep your foes confused
If they don't know who you are or what you want
They can't know what you plan to do next
Some times it is better to answer injustice with mercy
I will answer injustice with justice
This Spring
running out of time
I will not become a page in someone else's history book
The New Season
If fat boy's still walking , it's cause you let him go
Begins
You're a Targaryen
you're the mother of dragons
i need to be more than that
Who can we trust ?
Ourselves alone
We must not disappoint father
You've done nothing wrong
I've done plenty wrong
Game Of Thrones
Premieres Sunday : April 6 9 PM
written and sync : Hadi Farsi
Hadi.Farsi@Yahoo.Com