Writen And Synchronized By : Hadi Farsi
H a d i . F a r s i @ Y a h o o . C o m
Joffery ...
Cersei ...
Tywin Lannister ...
The red woman !
I can't sleep until I say the names
The names of every person in westeros !
Only the ones i'm going to kill
A NEW SEASON BEGINS
Rob Stark is dead
I lie awake all night , thinking about how they died
He was betrayed by his own men
All we can give him now is justice
If you want justice ...
You've come to the wrong place !
THIS SPRING
I will not be the page in someone else's history book
What do we do to those who hurt the ones we love ?
A day will come when your joy will turn to ashes in your mouth ...
And you'll know the debt is paid !
Ther Lannisters are not the only ones who pay tehir debts
I would do what queens do
I will Rule
GAME OF THRONES
VALAR MORGHULIS
ALL MEN MUST DIE
Writen And Synchronized By : Hadi Farsi
H a d i . F a r s i @ Y a h o o . C o m
THE FIRST PUBLIC PERFORMANCE ON :
SUNDAY ... APRIL 6 ... 9 PM