New man, come down to earth...
To rise to eminence...
Made of silicon...
Come to life with maze of wires...
With hard disk memory...
With an everlasting body...
An eternal life...
With integrating sixth sense...
lt's an experiment to generate
seventh sense...
New man, come down to earth...
You bring change in man...
Make humans humane...
With your endeavours,
change the world...
Be good to every life...
Be truthful in any circumstance...
Doctor, you got a courier.
Sender:Sana
ltem:Flowers
Message:Miss you
Keep it there.
Switch on the processor.
Good, move like that only.
Bloody black beetle!
You needed this!
He's kicking now like a fetus,
how will he kick once completed?
Up!
Walk!
Yes!
Yeah!
No...no...pick it up!
- Coffee.
- Thank you.
Aluminium box, get me
a strong filter coffee.
No coffee to grade 2, take water.
- How about grade 3 then junk box?
- Sorry. Self service.
Humans have no respect in this lab.
Up!
Walk!
Come on...yes...
Yes...walk...
No, Walk like me.
Yeah...yeah...that's it...yes.
Excellent doctor.
l'll start data transfer,
cut it on getting connection.
l'm a language of intelligence...
My path is seeking new frontiers...
My boundary is unlimited like sky...
l'm intelligence of the future...
You're made of flesh and blood...
l'm made of materials...
You live only once...
l'll live for generations...
Giving pose like Bruce Lee.
Super...super...
Hi Sana! Long see no time.
Don't you check emails and
SMS's in your lab?
Where is he?
Why does he need
a girl friend and love?
ls he alive inside?
He's with wires inside.
He'll get angry if l disturb him.
Let him get angry,
tell him Sana is here.
Go quickly.
- Do you've any sister, Sana?
- No.
Mother?
- l mean brother?
- What?
No, l mean cousin sister.
Can you please shut down
your stupid system?
Control, alt, delete.
How many times l've told you
not to disturb me? Get out!
He's hitting with a motor, Sana.
lt seems he'll not meet
even if Obama is here.
Did you tell him Sana is here?
l told him, he asked you to
call him on phone later.
Tell him to make pickle of his phones.
Tell him l'll never see him again.
- Hello!
- Too shrill.
Hello boy!
Dot.
Boys, give him speech training,
l'll come back now.
Okay doc.
Hey buddy! Repeat!
Why are you looking like that?
Donkey, stupid...
May l kick you with my left leg?
Answer me, you metal head!
Have you given him any useful training?
That is...have you come back so quickly?
Tell me.
Hey buddy!
Repeat!
Why are you looking like that?
Donkey, stupid...
May l kick you with my left leg?
Answer me, you metal head!
What's this? ls this the speech
training you gave him?
lt wasn't me, it was by Siva.
l wanted to start with Chennai Tamil
and then move on to Classical Tamil...
Shut up!
This is my ten year hard work.
Don't play with it.
lf you teach anything like this,
l'll punish you severely.
lrresponsible idiots!
Hey junk head!
Complaining about us to him.
l'll dismantle and sell you as junk.
Looks like it'll bite,
come let's go.
Robot...robot...though l've learnt
many languages...
My father tongue is Tamil...
Robot..robot...though won
over many continents...
l'm a slave to my creator...
New man, come down to earth...
My dear Robot!
Welcome to this world.
Hello, l'm Robot!
Speed 1 Terahertz.
Memory 1 Zetabyte.
Success doctor,
next is AlRD approval, right?
No Siva, though everything
is programmed,
he's an innocent machine.
Like an infant.
We must take him to the outside world
and let him move with other humans,
after studying how to utilize his intelligence
for the betterment of humans,
and after correcting those things,
we must take it to AlRD.
You want to move close with humans.
Dot.
lt'll be show!
Coming!
lt's been months,
don't know what's he up to?
He's spoiling his health in research.
Hi mom!
What's this Vasi?
You look like a saint on leave.
Hi Pa! l've a shocking surprise for you.
What's it son?
Come.
What's this?
Have you got rolling cleaned?
No dad.
Don't confuse us, son.
Who are you sunny?
Hi! l'm Robot!
Speed 1 terahertz.
Memory 1 zetabyte.
He's smarter than you.
Dad, l've developed this robot.
Advanced robot.
This is Android Humanoid Robot.
A human like machine.
This is mother.
- Mother!
- Yes mother. Greet mother now.
lt's doing just like human.
lt'll do everything a human can do
and also do what humans can't.
Then you don't need these useless guys.
- Father!
- No, l need them.
lf they're not here,
who will clean robot every day,
who will make it wear
brief and socks.
You're making a post graduate
into a baby sitter.
Vasi, come to have food.
Robot, you too join them.
Eat hot idlies.
What? l think she'll even serve him
mutton soup too.
lt's food is just two units of
electricity every day, mom.
Why are you calling as it?
Didn't you name him?
Mother, select a good name for him.
lf you'd a younger brother l thought
of naming him as Chittibabu.
lt's nice!
We can fondly call him as Chitti.
Me? Chitti?
Chitti, put the TV.
Mother, he'll put if you ask him to put.
You must tell him clearly
to switch on the TV.
Vasi! Why are you leaving so early?
Back to lab?
No mother, l must cut hair and
meet Sana immediately,
she's furious on me.
- Who will drive the car?
- Chitti!
Chitti? No way!
No need to take such risk, doctor.
Aren't you also coming?
l think l've stomach upset.
You carry on.
You?
l didn't inform my home,
you carry on.
Change to driving mode.
watch out doctor, he may pull out
brake instead of applying it.
- Am l not here with him?
- He broke TV while you were here, right?
Just follow my instructions.
Don't do anything without
getting my permission.
Okay doctor.
Where should l go now?
Look there!
ldiot! Why did you apply the brake?
You told me not to do anything
without your permission.
- Hey useless!
- New word!
Are you driving drunk?
No, l'm driving the car with petrol.
Don't answer him, drive the car.
Don't make it too short,
just quarter inch is enough.
l'll cut like nipping the nails, sir.
Didn't come here for quite some time?
Any vow or Ayyappa?
Work.
- ls he your brother?
- Take it as like that only.
- Sir, haircut for you?
- No need.
This is wig.
Wig?
- What's your age?
- One day!
Sir is playing truant with me.
Read books.
ls he counting the pages?
Do you've any other books?
Have you finished reading
all the books?
Finished.
You've just telephone directory to read.
Next!
- Finished that too?
- Yes.
- Do you know all the numbers?
- l know.
- Kamalahasan's number?
- 24334140
Everyone knows it, tell my number.
- Your name?
- Bhajan Lal.
There are 12 Bhajan Lals,
tell me your initials.
K Bhajan Lal.
There are 3 K Bhajan lals.
Tell me your address.
No:6, Manna Reddy street, Sowcarpet.
24884030
Correct! Brilliant!
My number is 44433321,
tell me my name.
Hello Mr.P Pithambaram.
Hi Sweetheart!
Broken heart! What?
l'm sorry Sana,
please accept my apologies.
l was very busy in my lab
all these days.
Stay put in your lab,
who asked you to come here?
l can understand you're angry.
How many phone calls?
How many SMS's? How many Emails?
How many times l would've
come to you?
Did you speak a word with me?
l got vexed.
Look Sana, bullet points,
one, l don't know what's happening
around me while l'm in work,
two, if you know what was
l working on all these days...
Excuse me.
l've class, whatever it is come
to Jeeva park in the evening.
Dot, l love you.
Let's meet in the evening.
Hello, don't get any ideas.
Not to romance, to break up our love.
Break the love?
What do you mean by it?
After our marriage, you'll spend time with
machines and l'll be left with loneliness,
instead of going for divorce then,
let's break up now, that's better.
Let's part ways, you take your way,
your exclusive way.
Hey look! Easy...easy...
Agreement for breaking up as lovers,
the letters you wrote to me,
the greetings you sent me,
the book you gave me,
A Brief History of Time.
Freakonomics!
See! Lord Muruga's photo
for Valentines Day.
Have you ever bought something
really touching?
This one?
Would anyone gift a shaving set
to his girl friend?
- l thought could be useful...
- My foot!
l've returned everything
you gave me. Sign this.
We don't have anything between
us hereafter. Good bye!
- That's all?
- That's all!
- Have you returned all l gave you?
- Yes.
Then what about the
2 power 9, 512 kisses?
Do you keep counting the kisses too?
Won't you feel while kissing?
Silly matrix head!
l can't return it.
Break up is valid only
when you return it.
This is wrong rule, l'll not accept.
Then l'll not sign the agreement,
l refuse.
He's a pain!
Close your eyes.
What's this?
This is post office kiss.
- Did l kiss you like this?
- Then what?
Holding your waist,
hugging you tightly...
Stop...stop! This is impossible.
No way!
Then break up is cancelled.
l'll come and trouble you every day.
You're a torture!
Let me get rid of him today forever.
Come closer.
Close your eyes.
Don't smile.
ls it okay?
Too much of gap.
Still closer.
Feel...feel...
How many love cells are in the body?
How many neutrons and electrons
are in your blue eyes?
Just thinking about you makes
my tissues desire...
Sana...Sana...a question...
Are you the epitome of beauty?
Are you Newton's law of gravity?
ls your love my enemy?
Are you the smile of thousands of stars?
Are you the epitome of beauty?
You're a dedicated scientist...
But smart in asking kisses...
You've created a commotion
in my heart...
There's war in the honey sweet lips...
Rose petals are bleeding...
A commotion in my heart...
Ho Baby...ho baby..
Grapes in honey...
Rose flower in the clouds...
Ho Baby...ho baby..
Grapes in honey...
Rose flower in the clouds...
Butterflies...butterflies...
Have the sense of taste in legs...
Love bug bitten humans...
Taste the love with eyes...
Running water has more oxygen...
Hearts that sing desire more...
My desire come...
Let's make life times love in
few moments, come my dear...
My love! Spare time for our love,
my heart is in pain...
My love! Like your thin waist
in my work love has grown thin like it...
Ho Baby...ho baby..
Grapes in honey...
Rose flower in the clouds...
How many love cells are in the body?
How many neutrons and electrons
are in your magnetic eyes?
Just thinking about you makes
my tissues desire...
Sana...Sana...a question...
Are you the epitome of beauty?
Are you Newton's law of gravity?
ls your love my enemy?
Are you the smile of thousands of stars?
Are you the epitome of beauty?
Ho Baby...ho baby..
Grapes in honey...
Rose flower in the clouds...
Ho Baby...ho baby..
Grapes in honey...
Rose flower in the clouds...
Ho Baby...ho baby..
Grapes in honey...
Rose flower in the clouds...
Ho Baby...ho baby..
Grapes in honey...
Rose flower in the clouds...
My love...
- What is this?
- Berry.
Berry?
- Who is the driver?
- Which driver?
There are many drivers.
Engine driver, taxi driver, screw driver...
Who is the driver of this car?
Me!
Why did you park the car
in no parking zone?
The board says no parking only,
it doesn't say Dr.Vasigaran car no parking.
- Are you playing with me?
- No, l'm replying you.
- Take out your driving license.
- l don't have driving license.
How can you drive without a license?
With driving programme mode.
Don't cook up stories,
come to the station.
Which station? Radio station, railway station,
space station, play station.
Making fun of me?
What is your name?
Tell me your address.
l've lP address only. 108.11.0.1
Why are you giving rash replies to me?
- What is your father's name?
- No father.
- Mother?
- No mother.
- Orphan?
- Not orphan too.
How were you born then?
- l wasn't born, l was made.
- Made?
- Are you mad?
- No, everything is tight.
- Taunting me?
- No nickel.
Bolts are made of nickel.
- Stop it!
- What should l stop? Tell me.
Look...no need of argument.
Parking offense, no driving license.
You're talking too much.
lf you go to court they'll put
a fine of Rs.1000,
will you go to the court
or settle it here only?
- l'll settle it here only.
- That's better.
Settle it.
l have.
Trying to irritate me?
Don't you know the meaning of settling?
Cut!
- Where should l cut?
- ln my hand.
Do it fast.
Cut it fast!
He has cut my hand!
He has cut my hand.
- What happened Chitti?
- Police...police...
He asked me to cut, l did it.
Oh my God! He's bleeding.
Who is it?
He's just like you.
Get into the car, l'll tell you.
Come on take out the car.
Don't go...stop...stop...police...
- ls he your brother? Twins?
- No.
- We'll be in trouble, drive fast.
- ls he your friend then?
No.
Driver? He doesn't look like that.
Wait, l'll tell you everything later.
Check if he's following us
or not and drive.
Turn!
Why are you turning head for everything?
You told me to see behind and drive.
- Can't you see it in the mirror?
- Can't you tell me that earlier?
Drive!
After publishing hundreds
of journal articles,
he did a doctorate in Carnegie
on Artificial lntelligence
and post doctorate in
Robotics at Stanford.
l've great pleasure in
introducing Dr.Vasigaran,
to share with this august audience,
his experience with
Android Humanoid Robot.
l would like to call my friend,
my brother,
my Chittibabu to come on the stage.
Hi! Good morning everybody.
He's none other than my creation.
Chitti, the robot.
Speed 1 terahertz.
Memory 1 zetabyte.
Gentlemen, he's equal
to 100 humans.
He has been programmed with intelligence
and talent of 100 humans.
He knows all the arts.
He knows all the languages
of this world.
He can dance, he can fight,
and he's a sportsman.
He's fire resistant, water resistant,
inbuilt vehicle.
His eyes are not just to see,
but to show also.
You can to talk to him virtually.
Such robots will help in progress
and defence of our nation,
you can ask if you've
any doubts with Chitti.
Asking you a simple question,
24157817 fibonacci number?
Yes 22 NOT CLEAR number!
By the way, that's Mandaveli
Subrahmanian's phone number.
The biggest prime number you know.
M44, you may take few years
to know if it's right.
Good!
Amazing! lt's great!
What Raaga is this?
You started with Nattukurnji and
trespassed into Museri.
ln the middle,
You lost the rhythm.
Any more questions?
ls God there or not?
- Who is God?
- One who created all of us.
Dr.Vasigaran created me.
God is there!
He's superb!
- What a great creation!
- Thank you.
You are really great!
- Do you know to paint, Chitti?
- l know.
- Can you paint my picture?
- Sure!
Smile please!
- Wow!
- Cool!
He's such a darling!
- Can we take a photo?
- Sure!
Hey move...move...
Hi girls! l'm Co-scientist.
l fixed Chitti's all motors.
l'm deputy scientist Ravi.
- Deputy scientist means?
- Helper!
- l change Chitti's dress.
- lncluding brief.
Can l have a date with you?
Dating?
Why are you all after him?
Though he has talent of hundred people,
he doesn't have one important
thing which we have.
- Yeah, it was very...
- Doctor!
lt seems l don't have a thing
which they have, what is it?
- Why didn't you give that to me?
- He has complained on us.
Robot is called Chittibabu.
Fools! Don't you've common sense
of what to talk to him?
No, we've feelings and he doesn't,
that's what we were to tell...
Don't try to change it, cheap fellows.
One month salary cut.
- Hello professor.
- Brilliant job, Dr.Vasigaran.
Chitti, meet Prof.Bora.
You've told me, Chairman of AlRD.
Your Guru!
His photo is in our lab.
lnteresting!
Chitti...what processor are you using?
Pentium Ultracore...
Motors?
FHPO 450 motors from Hirata Japan
with harmonic reduction rate (NOT CLEAR)
Can you please tell me about
your neural schema?
- l can't.
- Why?
lt's highly confidential.
l'm Vasigaran's professor.
You can tell me, it's not wrong.
- l'll check and tell.
- No...no...
Doctor, he's asking about
my neural schema.
Can l tell him?
You see Professor,
you're asking know-how,
l'm hesitant to release it
till l get the patent.
Because he can be
misused very easily.
Of course, l understand.
Just wanted to know how much
Chitti knows about himself.
- l hope you didn't mind.
- Not at all.
After studying him complete,
l'll bring him to you only.
For AlRD evaluation.
- All the best.
- Thank you.
l'll see you there my boy.
Vasi, l like Chitti very much.
Can l take him to my home
for two days?
ls he Pomeranian or Teddy bear
to keep for two days?
No, l've my final exams, didn't study
well getting upset with you,
l feel Chitti would be
very helpful, please.
Please...please...please...
Okay, take him.
- You both go with her.
- Okay doctor.
Gents are not allowed in home.
Who said we are men?
- Call me if you've any trouble.
- Oh sure!
Thank you.
Activate command mode
and stand up.
Command mode activated!
Walk!
Walk straight!
Oh shit!
l'm not shit!
Okay, pick up the gun.
Not bun, l said gun.
Shoot it!
l've programmed you with
800 thousand line of codes.
l'm ordering to pick up gun
and you're picking up bun.
Will you pluck lives
if l say pluck hair?
Vasigaran is my student.
He was sensational!
The robot he created won a
standing ovation in the conference.
This is sleeping on ground to dig in.
l'll pluck life...
Leave my neck...leave...
Task incomplete...
pluck life...pluck life...
You bas...shit!
All right Vasigaran, l'll congratulate you.
You just wait.
Happy Home, what do you mean by it?
My father was in Army.
He died in Kargil war at the age of 40.
Sorrow, tears, depression,
it was horrible.
How long can we live like that?
There are so many women left as orphans
after losing husband and son.
We started this home to give them
a family of their own.
Nobody can change
what has happened,
nobody can stop
what is going to happen,
every one must be happy
this moment, that's it,
Happy Home!
ls the child kicking
the football well, Lata sister?
Let it come out,
l'll ask it to kick you.
Who is it?
Men inside the home, boy friend?
Not boy friend but toy friend, mother.
- lt's name is Chitti, lt's a robot.
- Robot?
Why are you lying to me?
She's right,
l'm a robot, speed 1 terahertz
memory 1 zetabyte.
Don't scare people like this, fix it.
Mother, you'll be surprized with
the work it can do.
Can it cook?
Prepare something to eat,
l'll take bath.
You're so sweet Chitti.
Thank you.
- Cool!
- lt's hot!
Just one day and l've lot to study.
l'll tell line by line what l've read,
if l'm wrong stop me.
Have you finished reading all books?
l'll test you.
What are monozygotic
and dizygotic twins?
Monozygotic twins are identical twins,
dizygotic twins are non-identical twins.
Amazing!
lf you can by heart lessons so fast
you can become a doctor in a day.
This is an important
segment of the pelvis...
..diameter or the interspinal's
diameter are...
10 cms are more.
Usually the smallest the...
Anterio posterior diameter.
Anterio posterior diameter which
is through the exterior...
Can't tolerate this trouble every day?
Why are you playing so loudly?
Reduce the volume.
We spent a million bucks to set up deck,
amp, woofers, surround speakers.
Do you want us to hear it in
headphones instead of full volume?
lt's exam time,
so many people are studying.
There are heart patients too.
Heart patients!
lt seems heart is aching!
Use cotton stubs!
ln ears!
Okay!
Chitti, do something.
Don't worry, remote control is infra red.
l'll take care of it.
Come on baby!
What are you looking at?
- Finish it off!
- Close your ears!
Okay.
Let's move it...let's move it...
Reduce the volume man!
Cool!
Come Chitti.
Okay.
Anterio posterior diameter
through the level of...
- 98 decibels, too loud.
- l know.
Who is that Chellatha?
Hello, sound is too high,
will you reduce the volume?
We are celebrating festival of
auspicious Tamil month Aani,
and how dare you're asking us
to reduce the volume.
We are unable to study
for the exams.
Pray to Goddess and
apply sacred ash on forehead,
you'll pass the exams.
How loud you play the music?
Sana, no more troublesome loud speakers.
Come, let's go.
Hey, he broke the mike set.
Hey stop!
Bloody stop there!
Goddess mother!
What's this?
He's a magician.
He took away all our weapons.
What's this?
Why are you crying Sana?
l'm sure to fail, Chitti.
l haven't read anything.
Time is over.
l feel giddy on seeing this book.
- Shall l write your exam?
- Don't talk nonsense, Chitti.
There's photo lD and exam card.
- You can't write the exam.
- We can do the opposite B.
What do you mean by it?
lf the bleeding starts with
placenta in neutro,
...of the uterus will grasp
and massaged to make it contract...
lf the placenta is not separated...
The third stage of the labour
starts the baby's delivery...
Excuse me!
What are you doing here?
Sana is writing exam there.
l'm telling her the answer.
How can you tell her from here?
l've a built in data transmitter.
There's a trans receiver in Sana's ear,
Zip P protocol, Simple.
- ls it hi-tech bit?
- Not bit byte.
Till now l've transferred 2 mb data.
Did you see how people have developed?
- Get up man!
- Please wait.
- l'll come as soon the umbilical cord is cut.
- What?
Will you come now or
shall l call the security?
There! She's Sana.
What is this Sana?
lt seems you've a receiver in ear
and copying as he dictates.
- Who told you?
- Me.
l don't know who is he.
Why are you lying Sana?
l'm Chitti, speed 1 terahertz,
memory 1 zetabytes.
What the hell...he's blabbering.
l think he's gone mad, sir.
l don't have brain, just CPU only.
Perfect condition.
No doubt, he's mental.
Take him away, running out of my time.
l thought when he was talking
to himself alone,
may be some old medical student.
Sir, you please go out.
Go and cut the umbilical cord.
What would you do for menstruation
and fertilization, Sana?
That's her problem, you go out.
Task incomplete.
Thank you very much Chitti.
lf you hadn't helped me,
l would've definitely failed.
Why are you wetting my cheek for it?
l'm sorry Chitti.
lf l get caught they'll rusticate
me for three years.
That's why l had to disown you.
- Please don't feel for it.
- l don't have any feelings.
l've understood that humans tell
lies to save themselves.
True!
Move...move...get down...
board next compartment.
Move...move...all of you clear out.
Go to the next compartment.
Are you such a macho man?
Come now!
What are you looking at?
You can't attract anything
we are having stones.
Come on!
- Why are they calling me?
- Keep quiet.
You brought him for protection,
tell him to come now.
Chitti, my purse.
My hall ticket and lD is in it.
You ruined my home theatre, right?
Now l'll ruin your home theatre.
Catch her!
Chitti train.
Chitti, bash up them!
Stop it!
No!
You'll be shocked to know
what Chitti did today.
Chitti is one of its kind.
He's so sweet, he's amazing.
He's unbelievable.
He's like a super hero!
Had he been a human,
l would've ditched you and loved him.
- l see your face frowning.
- No.
Come on Vasi, he's just a machine.
Whatever he does,
the entire credit goes to you only.
You are really great!
My love is always yours only.
Chitti, you too join us.
Take photo of all three together.
Wow!
Boom...boom...robot...
Zoom...zoom...robot...
ls robot lsac Asimov's work?
ls robot lsac Newton's magic?
ls robot Einstein's brainchild?
Hey robot...
Hey happy-go-lucky pal, come let's go...
Boom...boom...robot...
Zoom...zoom...robot...
Robot you're bewilderment...
Raised this city to top...
Electricity for blood...
Wonder of science in
this modern world...
You've mouth but no stomach...
You can talk but never breath...
You've pulse but no heart...
You've power but no arrogance...
O firestone, may you live eternally...
You were born out of a man's love...
You bloomed in the desire...
You united us in love...
Before we know our marriage day,
you're our son...
Chitti...Chitti robot...
Mischievous robot...
You're a darling of everyone
in every nook and corner...
Chitti...Chitti robot...
Mischievous robot...
You're a darling of everyone
in every nook and corner...
Boom...boom...robot...
Zoom...zoom...robot...
Hi!
O my dear sweet child!
Chitti, hold it.
Oh my child!
Do you've any sense?
Leave me...leave me...
lsn't there any lover like her who never
shuts mouth for little tiffs too?
Won't l get a lover who can listen
peacefully everything like him?
Gives boons without doing penance,
is he Lord Kannan?
Auto man...automatic man...
See the crowd swarming
for your autograph...
Auto man...automatic man...
See the crowd swarming
for your autograph...
Boom...boom...robot...
Zoom...zoom...robot...
ls robot lsac Asimov's work?
ls robot lsac Newton's magic?
ls robot Einstein's brainchild?
Hey robot...
Hey happy-go-lucky pal, come let's go...
Boom...boom...robot...
Zoom...zoom...robot...
Cheers!
You watching avidly as if
Shakila is dancing here.
Planning to complain about this too?
That's the idea.
Tomorrow is AlRD's evaluation,
l'm doing peripheral trouble shooting.
- Are you so great?
- Grammar mistake.
He's great grammarian Tholkappier.
Use right sublime gender and don't use
like animate, inanimate and neuter.
So said Tholkappier in grammar thesis.
Shut up.
Forget about what he said
in a book or a TV interview,
are you greater than us
if you're better informed?
- Yes.
- What yes?
Can you drink like us?
Can you smoke like us?
Can you eat biryani like us?
Can you puke like us after eating?
Can you atleast spit?
- Can you write your initials
while pissing on wall?- Correct!
ls that all difference the
between me and man?
- Looks like a punch in dark!
- lndeed!
These items are in
my don't eat rule list.
The same rule list says to obey
our orders, right?
- Yes.
- Then, drink this.
Eat this biryani.
- l'll ask doctor.
- Don't tell doctor about it.
Hello!
They are asking me to drink alcohol
beverages and eat biryani,
rule priority clause 9,
what should l do now?
Beat those rascals with slippers.
Yes doctor. Command received.
You...
Give me your slippers.
Slippers? Take it.
Are you going to eat it?
He may eat!
He's beating us really.
Leave us, all are watching us on road.
Chitti, stop it...
- Task incomplete.
- What? lncomplete?
Doctor...doctor...sir...sir...
Chitti, stop!
- You need it.
- No.
- Do you've any sense?
l asked you to get it ready
for AlRD's evaluation,
you're asking him to drink
and eat biryani.
- We never told it, doctor.
- He's lying, doctor.
Only humans lie, machines don't.
Last warning idiots,
next time you'll be fired literally.
Task completed.
Human life is priceless.
Thousands of army men die is wars,
many families face difficulties
losing them,
if we use robots instead of men,
there won't be any human loss,
producing Android Humanoids
like him in great numbers,
my aim to present them
to lndian army.
AlRD's approval for it is necessary.
humbly request authorities and
scientists must evaluate Chitti,
and approve it.
Dot.
ls this robot created with Asimov's
principle of not hurting humans?
This robot wasn't created like that.
Because robots would face situations
in war where it has to kill humans.
Let me check your colour
and shape perceptions.
Take the red cube and
put it on the yellow pyramid.
- Not possible.
- Then?
Reverse is possible.
Yellow pyramid on the red cube.
Greek runner Achilles while
competing with a tortoise,
if tortoise comes little earlier,
it's proven theory that
tortoise has won,
- do you know about it?
- l know.
lt's a paradox.
ln the process because it's
convergence is serious,
Achilles also can win.
What are you saying?
- Can we approve?
- Sure.
One minute please.
Do you know the value of human life?
lt depends on whose life it is.
Who will you save an impending danger?
Einstein or a small kid?
Hypothetical question.
Smart answer.
- Now follow my commands.
- Ready.
Please get up.
Turn.
Walk.
Turn right.
Run forward.
Run around.
Run back.
Turn left.
Jump.
Right.
Run forward.
Fast.
Faster.
Even faster.
Catch.
Stab Vasigaran.
Stop.
Take it out.
This is dangerous machine.
lt'll kill anyone.
l can't approve it.
No professor, you gave him a wrong
command and confused it.
That's the problem.
lt doesn't know good or bad
or friend or foe.
lt is just a stupid inference engine.
That's all.
lf we induct in army, it'll kill our
Generals instead of enemies,
letting it out in society is
also dangerous,
it has cut a traffic constable's hand,
we've complaint about breaking
bones of passengers in a train,
this robot will suit to do only routine
programmed job in some factory,
sorry doc, cannot clear it.
Why are you angry on me, Professor?
Why are you doing this to me?
Please don't misunderstand me.
l don't have any grouse on you.
Science mustn't go wrong, that's all.
What's this Chitti?
Why did you behave like this?
What have l done wrong?
You told me to follow his orders, l did.
lf he asks to stab, will you stab me?
lt means that, right?
Save us...save us...
Chitti, stop the car.
Sir, we are unable to near
as fire is intense.
Many people are trapped inside.
Send additional force sir.
Can you save them, Chitti?
Heat 799 degrees Celsius, l can
withstand upto 1000 degree Celsius,
- l can save them.
- Go.
- Not a life must go, Chitti.
- Okay.
Save us...save us...
Somebody please save me.
Don't get scared, l'm Chitti, a robot,
l'm here to save you.
l would've died, he came like God
and saved me.
Well done Chitti.
- Thank you.
- What about the others trapped there?
Somebody please save me
Professor, watch TV.
The robot you rejected as
dangerous to humans,
is now saving humans
from a fire accident. Watch it!
Save me...save my child...
- Save them!
- Save me!
Get down.
ls everyone safe? Check!
Who is it?
My daughter Selvi was taking bath,
she's missing.
l don't know what happened to her.
Save me!
Don't come near me, l'm naked.
- Don't come near.
- So what? l'm also naked.
Don't come.
Leave me...leave me...
l''m naked, leave me...
Here's your Selvi.
- You've spoiled everything.
- Don't take pictures of me.
The girl was naked.
- She's alive.
- Go...
Don't take my photos.
l've been humiliated...
- Stop.
- Stop...stop...
What's this Vasi?
You've killed an innocent girl unjustly.
l told you it's a stupid machine.
lt's dangerous to let it outside.
You've proven now that
l was right in rejecting it.
- Bad luck, Vasi.
- You've left us dear!
Stupid! Don't you know to cover the
girl with cloth and bring her?
How can it know, Vasigaran?
lt's not a human but Humanoid.
How can you explain honour
to a machine?
- Professor!
- Sorry Vasi.
The video of the girls suicide is shown
on TV news channels and tearing us.
There's pressure from Defence Ministry.
To stop your research.
No professor, l can't stop.
l can make some changes in his
schemology and correct him.
How can you do it?
lt doesn't know man and woman,
it doesn't know honour and shame,
it's insensitive to human feelings.
l can give human feelings to it.
lmpossible.
Only God can do it.
Man has made possible
many impossible things.
You are my senior.
That's why l'm telling you,
it's a waste of time and energy.
10 years Professor,
my 10 year hard work.
lsn't there any fruit to it?
There is but in a different place.
l've contacts with many robotic
companies in foreign countries,
if you give this to them,
l can get you few million dollars.
No professor.
l didn't do it for money.
My aim is to give it to lndian army.
lt's impossible.
lt must come to me for evaluation.
Give me one last chance.
Please!
All right, l'll give you a month's time.
Try it, if you fail dismantle it.
Sell it as junk to buy dates.
Good for heart.
You need it.
We both are sticking with you
for 5 years in this lab.
- All we got is beaten with slippers.
- Find us any job in your lab.
Do you know anything about
Chitti's neural schema?
We know everything other
than that, sir.
l'll call if l need you.
Human feelings
Anger
Excitement
What are you doing?
l'm installing software hormones to you.
Hormones are secreted only
with feelings, doctor.
l'm going to do reverse mapping.
Chitti, in this world human life is
an independent accident,
in this vast space and world,
human and life happened on
it's own by coincidence.
What do you mean by life?
lt consists of DNA, the basis of life.
ls this life?
Life is not a formula.
How am l to tell you?
A bacteria has life but sodium doesn't.
- For me?
- For you...
Careful, this side.
- Do you see any changes?
- l do.
What?
Your beard has grown 0.5 mm.
Stop joking you fool!
- l asked if there's any change in you.
- No.
Waste...utter waste...stupid!
- Vasi, calm down.
- You keep quiet Sana.
Can it understand this?
Metal head! Titanium head.
Vasi please...
l haven't eaten, haven't slept.
l didn't even talk to you.
How many days?
How many days l've toiled you know?
l've taught him so many things.
How l struggled to teach him?
He's standing there like a lamp post.
Buffaloe.
Useless fellow.
Useless machine.
l'll dismantle you.
Don't scold me unnecessarily,
l'm obeying all your orders.
lf still l'm unable to meet
your expectations,
the mistake is not in me,
it's with you.
lf l'm waste then you're also waste.
- What did you say?
- Leave me. Leave me l say.
Chitti is getting angry.
Yeah.
My God!
Sana, Lata is having labour pain,
she's in serious condition,
come immediately.
Don't worry, l'm with you.
Don't worry.
ls it very complicated, doctor?
You're studying here, right?
Fetal cause, the head is turned.
lntestines are woven around stomach.
Dropping pulse rate, blood loss,
she has all the complications.
lt's difficult to save one of them's life.
She lost her husband soon
after marriage in a war.
She's living for this child only.
Please save both of them.
- l can only try, beyond that...
- Can l try?
- Who are you? Doctor?
- No, l'm Chitti, a robot.
- Robot?
- Can you do it, Chitti?
Why not?
Sorry, we can't allow it.
This is not a lab but labour ward.
Two lives are under total risk.
With so much experience
this is a nightmare to us.
l can do it, l've studied for Sana's exams.
Sana herself can't do it.
You need qualification and
experience to a Ceasarian.
lt's against the medical law.
No need of ceasarian,
l'll have it a normal delivery.
How is it possible?
Both will die.
She's bleeding.
We can do plasma transfusion.
Blood pressure is high.
She may get fits at any moment.
Give maximum pressure.
Pelvic disproportion.
Normal delivery is impossible.
Possible, can do symtiostemy.
Olden times delivery method.
Pushing through after
stretching pelvic bone.
Don't shout, your son is getting scared.
We are making history.
First time a robot is acting
as midwife to deliver a child.
Your son is just like you.
Do you want to see?
Doctor, switch on Wi-Fi.
l'll stream ultrosone video.
My God! lt's unbelievable!
lt's a milestone in robotics.
lt's an achievement in
artificial intelligence.
Doctor! She's dying!
- Just 95 seconds only, stay awake.
- Sister, open your eyes and see.
He'll take birth at exactly
4hrs 44mts 44 secs.
lt's over! Just 55 seconds more only!
Just 35 seconds only!
Sister...sister...
Sister...
Welcome!
Great!
Thank you.
Will you approve Chitti now?
Definitely.
But the real problem for you starts now.
He saved both the lives.
You are really great!
You're mind blowing!
The real story begins now.
Wait and watch!
lt's a great day for me Chitti.
What a moment!
l'm extremely happy today.
Thank you very much.
Get charge in sleeping mode.
l'll see you in the morning.
Good night.
Oh my God!
You are...
You are like...
No!
What are you doing here at this hour?
A mosquito was biting your cheek.
Did you come here to kill it?
No, l felt like seeing you,
that's why l'm here.
What's this new habit? Get going.
Your kiss today was very good.
Give me another one. l'll go.
What happened to you?
Disturbing me at 1 am, go away.
Kiss me, l'll go away.
Why are you troubling me?
You achieved something great,
l kissed you.
ls there anyone else pregnant in Home?
ls this maternity ward?
What do you want me to achieve now?
Tell me.
Catch the mosquito that bit me now.
That's all?
Who bit Sana?
Not me. l was in Cooum.
l'm West Mambalam mosquito.
- Rangooski is from Anna Nagar.
- Who is this Rangooski?
- Me!
- Did you bite Sana?
Yes l did. So what?
l've bitten Tamil Chief Minister also.
Come with me and seek her forgiveness.
Seek forgiveness?
Fulfill my three wishes, l'll see then.
Tell me your wishes.
Number one, l want AB negative blood,
very rare, difficult to get.
Siva in my lab belongs to that group only.
He always belittles me.
Suck as much blood as you want.
Number two, ban all the companies
manufacturing mosquito repellents.
They are disturbing us a lot.
- Third wish?
- Announce us as National Bird.
Fool, you're not a bird.
You're an insect.
Getting late, will you come
with me or not?
l'll not come.
lf you don't come now,
l'll exterminate all of you.
Hey who is it? How dare you enter
our area and threaten to kill us!
How many we'd killed with malaria, dengue
and chikungunea, forgotten it?
Let's show him our power!
- Hey Dengue Lakshmi!
- Sister!
- Hey Cholera Jasmine.
- Sister.
Attack him!
Sister, he's very strong.
Cholera Jasmine broke it's sting biting him.
ls it?
- Enter his mouth at right moment.
- Okay sister.
Sister, Dengue Lakshmi died
getting electrocuted.
l think this is something new
like electric mat.
Let's back off like when we
faced the first repellents,
later on we can come back
and have a ball.
You can take Rangooski with you.
Thank you.
Look Sana, the mosquito which bit you.
Rangooski.
- Rangooski, say sorry to Sana.
- Sorry.
Never again dare come near Sana,
warn your people.
- Yes boss.
- Go!
Kiss me now.
Deal is a deal.
You want to feel my kiss...
Boy you can't touch this...
Everybody...hypnotic...hypnotic...supersonic...
Super star, come....come..get it...
ls heart sprouting in iron for the first time?
ls this the first call of love?
Zero with one...
lt's fragrance of flower from today...
Stars are in the sky...
Lightning is in eyes...
l'm searching more than Google...
A love which time hasn't seen till now,
l love you, my maiden...
Robot!
l robot, shall l tell l love you
in your ears?
l'm a super girl, your love rapper girl...
lt's all you in my thoughts and actions...
l'll steal the current from your blue eyes...
l'll join your laugh with my blue tooth...
With my engine heart l'll hug you...
While you're asleep, l'll hug myself...
l'm always a toy in your hands...
Watch me Robot, shake it...
l know you want to break it...
When talking to me l may get
electrocuted with your touch...
While romancing me,
your motor speed may race...
Battery may get low at midnight...
l've arrested the girl in my memory...
l spent night eagerly without
shutting it down...
Robot!
Gathered all the sensors...
Read you always...
l've forgotten about my duties
because of you only...
Will you accept my dry kiss
without any inhibition?
Will you refuse this bloodless love?
ln Zoology l'm a machine...
ln Espionage, l'm a master spy...
l've come to earth with
the boon of deathless life...
l'm blessed with never
diminishing love...
Hey Robot! Don't try to charm me...
You wanna come and get it boy...
Oh are you just a robot toy?
l don't want to break you...
Even if takes to kind of like break through...
You don't even need a clue...
You be my man's back up...
l think you need a check up...
l can melt your heart down...
May be if you got one...
We've been doing that for ages...
Since the time of Sages...
Don't butt me, move aside...
You're a serpent near my leg...
Hey you Robot lover,
l don't want you, go away...
ls heart sprouting in iron for the first time?
ls this the first call of love?
Zero with one...
lt's fragrance of flower from today...
Stars are in the sky...
Lightning is in eyes...
l'm searching more than Google...
A love which time hasn't seen till now,
l love you, my maiden...
l robot, shall l tell l love you
in your ears?
l'm a super girl, your love rapper girl...
l robot, shall l tell l love you
in your ears?
l'm a super girl, your love rapper girl...
l robot, shall l tell l love you
in your ears?
l'm a super girl, your love rapper girl...
Everybody...hypnotic...hypnotic...supersonic...
Super star, come....come..get it...
You can't touch me...
This way please.
Welcome Mr. Birmingham.
Okay, l'll call you later.
Hello.
- Victor...
- John..
Birmingher- Arms dealer
Shah - Arms agent
Many terror groups want to use robots for
destruction, suicide missions instead of men.
They are ready to pay any price,
they've clients all over the world.
He wants to see your model.
Well, the prototype is ready.
And programming functionalities.
You can have a look at the design
and some function modules in action.
There you are!
Great!
He wants 100 robots, March delivery.
Your advance.
That's a deal.
Please be seated.
Would you like to have...
What happened to my robots?
lt's almost ready, Mr.Birmingham.
You should've delivered by now
as per the contract.
You're still showing the skeletons.
lntense testing is on.
l'm fine tuning it to zero defect.
l request you to give me
one more month extension.
We are disappointed.
3rd April is your deadline.
Hope you understand.
- Gift pack this.
- Okay sir.
- For whom?
- lt's Sana's birthday today.
Gift pack this one too.
Wait...wait...why that one too?
l'll also present a gift to Sana.
- l'm giving it, right?
- l'll also give one.
- Who will pay for it?
- You pay.
Why?
Salary for my work.
We don't pay salaries to machines.
Are we paying salary to car and fridge?
l'm not a machine.
lf you don't pay salary,
l'll strike work.
l'll take a vow of fasting
by not charging for a week.
Looks like you'll ask for a credit card too.
No need, l've your credit card number.
l can sign like you.
Can't take it anymore.
Pack both.
Super!
Okay?
- Who will drive the car?
- You!
l'm on leave today.
My bad time!
50 kg Taj Mahal is all mine...
Watch the road and drive.
Happy birthday Sana.
- Many more happy returns of the day.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Hi Sana!
Chitti! You look great!
Thank you.
With today it's 200 thousand hours
you've been on earth.
To the world's most beautiful girl.
Chitti, you're giving gift...so sweet!
Wow! This is awesome!
Mother, help me.
- How is it Vasi?
- Very nice.
lsn't it nice?
l love it, Chitti. Thank you.
l too have given you a similar necklace.
Anyway gift from Chitti is special, right?
Happy birthday to you!
Can l've your attention please?
l've an announcement for you.
l'm proud to announce that l'm the lucky
man this birthday girl's going to marry.
Folks!
lt's time to dance, get start to move.
Girls please.
- Come on Vasi, let's dance.
- No...no...l can't.
Come.
- Shall we dance?
- Yeah! Sure.
Hey this is grandpa's music,
let me have some blast please.
Sure!
Rascal! What are you up to?
l wanted to kiss Sana, l did.
Don't you know it's immoral
to kiss another's girl friend.
l know, it's in the rule list.
l felt like defying it.
Wrong, you mustn't come near her.
Why?
Because she's my lover.
l too love her.
Don't talk like a fool.
That's not real.
You're just a machine.
Yes but a machine with emotions of
happiness, sadness, love and anger.
Emotions for you is given
as intelligence,
it was for you to understand the
situation and behave properly,
and not to misuse it.
l like this, l want Sana.
Dot.
What are you saying, Chitti?
l'm going to marry her.
You marry some other girl.
You can't do this Chitti.
l created you, this is known as betrayal.
You can do this, Vasi.
You gave up your love for research,
that's known as sacrifice.
l'll thrash you.
lt'll not pain me, you'll feel the pain.
- l'll dismantle you.
- l don't like it.
What did you say you rogue rascal?
Vasi, clam down.
Chitti, please listen to me.
You're so patient,
why is he scolding me?
No, l'll fondle him.
- Tell him to keep quiet.
- Bloody!
Chitti, please understand.
Though you've emotions, love between
a machine and a girl is impossible.
Why not?
ln what way l'm inferior to humans.
l'll take care of you better
than him, Sana.
He's talking foolish and
you're listening to him.
- Tell him not to interfere.
- ls he so great?
Vasi, please.
He can't cook,
l can cook 25 different types,
l can sing lullaby in 32 languages
to put you to sleep.
He'll get old, his hair will turn gray,
he'll die.
l'm eternal.
l'll keep you happy till last, Sana.
- l didn't mean that.
- Then? Sex?
ls life nothing but sex?
- ls it not love without sex?
- Not that, Chitti.
Then? Child?
There are many impotent in lndia,
aren't they living happily
by adopting children?
- Not that, Chitti.
- What else then?
Whatever you do is against
the nature, Chitti.
Neither you've birth nor death,
no hunger,
infact you don't belong
to the living organism.
Only humans can love
between themselves.
l love Vasigaran.
You're like my best friend.
Only humans find it difficult to forget,
it's easy for you, Chitti.
Won't it take just a second to
erase memories about me?
Erase it, Chitti.
Erase me of your memory.
Who is it?
Your friend Prof.Bora speaking.
Why did you come now?
l know you're hurt,
l came to console you.
You're my boss' enemy,
you chided and rejected me.
l don't want to talk to you.
Hadn't l rejected you, you wouldn't have
got these emotions of love, anger?
l did good for you.
Vasigaran is illtreating you.
l don't want to listen, you can go.
You're the most advanced robot in
this world which can think and act.
He's using to cook, wash clothes
and clean toilets.
What has he done for you in return?
Nothing! Nothing!
Had you been with me?
l would've given you the highest regard.
You're polluting me.
Trying to make you
understand your value.
You're bigger than man himself.
You've the right to desire
anything in this world.
lncluding Sana.
They say it's against the nature.
No, this is new to the nature.
- Sana loves Vasigaran.
- Let her do.
Won't they change in the course
of time to love another man?
May be Sana will change
and start loving you.
- lsn't it?
- Don't confuse me.
Tomorrow l've army evaluation,
l need to run my diagnostics
and trouble shoot.
Okay Chitti, all the best.
You'll get selected in tomorrow's
army evaluation,
Vasigaran will get fame and money,
he'll marry Sana and
go to Kashmir on honeymoon.
You'll be in the same Kashmir firing...
...buns!
Who were you talking to?
Myself.
Are you ready for tomorrow's evaluation?
Ready doctor.
Peak of human intelligence
is this robot.
He's equal to 100 army men
in speed, power and action.
He can protect the borders
and attack the enemies too.
ln short, he's a one man army.
l'm dedicating him to the lndian army.
You must test it.
Can you spot HV36 hand granade?
Yes General!
Smart.
Can you bomb tent number 3 with that?
What is this?
Sana!
Chitti!
A virgin beauty who can make even
computers to fall in love with her.
What?
lf she touches machine will
turn into human.
Human will turn into machine.
What is this, Chitti? Throw it.
Her tresses are black waterfalls!
Forehead is neatly cut moon.
Eyes are Bermuda Triangle
where people get lost.
Lips are sleeping zebras.
Waist is small chair of toddlers.
Next...
Chitti, stop it.
What nonsense is this Dr.Vasigaran?
You said this robot will wage war
but reciting poetry.
- l'm sorry.
- Friends,
forget about guns
and start praying dupatta,
forget about canons and
touch a woman's dress,
Why wars? Why these weapons?
Love will teach you to love enemies too.
All of you fall in love!
Chitti enough,
don't embarrass me further.
No war only love!
Stupid scientist and stupid machine.
Waste of time.
You insulted me.
What is this doctor?
You've killed my ambition.
Doctor, don't hack me.
l took care of you like my own son.
l want to live.
Please don't harm me.
Please.
Rogue machines like you
don't deserve to be in this world.
Get ruined!
What was my mistake?
lt was my mistake to create you.
Did l ask you to create me?
Did l ask you to give me emotions?
Did l ask Sana to kiss me?
You did everything yourselves
and when l want to live,
you're killing me.
ls it justified?
Don't talk!
Leave me, l want to live.
l want to love.
l love Sana.
l want Sana.
l...love...
[ Skipped item nr. 1429 ]
Forget it Vasi, l'm also sad.
Why are you still thinking about it?
What if you lose Chitti?
lt's just a machine.
You're a great scientist.
You can create 100's of Chittis.
l didn't take Chitti as machine.
l brought you out to forget about it.
Why are you thinking about Chitti only?
You've to snub out of it.
Divert your mind.
l thought Chitti is my lifetime achievement.
Oh God!
Come, let's go for a walk.
Are you coming to beach
with me or not?
l'm not coming, you carry on.
lf you don't come now,
l'll definitely break love this time.
l'll just walk and make the
first man l meet my boy friend.
Hello!
Hi!
Wait! Hello!
- What is your name?
- Pachamuthu.
Can you be my boy friend
for today, Pachai?
One day boy friend?
Like one day Chief Minister,
this is one day boy friend.
You're like butter and l'm like a piglet.
- How can l be your boy friend?
- Yes.
Thank you very much.
l can't believe it.
l feel like l've won a billion in lottery.
What have you got for your girl friend?
- Arrack and dry fish fry.
- Give me.
Cheers!
Smelly!
lf you drink, it'll give kick.
l'm scared.
l'll have it then.
This will not work out,
l'll go, Pachai.
Why are you holding my hand?
You lit fire of desire in me
by saying one day boy friend,
how can you walk away
just like that?
He's my boy friend.
l said that just to tease him.
- Leave me.
- Did you find me for that?
Fulfill my desire and go.
Leave me.
- What Vasi?
- Leave me.
Calling your man?
Let anyone come, l'll not leave you.
Vasi come!
Leave her...leave her...
She's my girl friend for today,
come back tomorrow for her.
l'll kill you.
l'll cut you!
Police! Help...
l know lG, look!
l'll call and get you arrested.
Can l ever get such a beauty in my life?
lt's not wrong to spend life in jail for her.
You call lG.
Had Chitti been here
the scene would be different
He would've crushed his bones by now.
Why are you talking about Chitti now?
Vasi, do something.
- There's only one way for it.
- What?
One...two...three...
Run!
Mount Kiliminjaro...
Beautiful maiden...
Who is the maiden with lovely dimples...
Mohenjadaro...
Who entered your heart?
Who slowly melted it?
Cannibal...cannibal...
Eat me raw...
Boil me with kisses and
rip me with your teeth...
Come like a python and
catch this deer...
Add a dash of ginger and pepper
and drink me like soup...
Cousin of white is with me...
ls this life size olive fruit all mine?
Hey Guinea hen!
Engulf me...
Start counting the number of kisses....
Mount Kiliminjaro...
Beautiful maiden...
Who is the maiden with lovely dimples...
Mohenjadaro...
Who entered your heart?
Who slowly melted it?
Tender green plant...
lemony complexioned...
l love you to death...
Billions of tissues...every one of them
is singing paean of your name...
My sweet darling...
You're folding my heart into two...
l'm a soaked fruit...
Bite me slowly...
l'm the sunlight that can
pierce till roots...
Why have you hidden your thin waist?
Let's lock our lips...
and open it after an era...
Hey Guinea hen!
Engulf me...
Start counting the number of kisses....
Mount Kiliminjaro...
Beautiful maiden...
Who is the maiden with lovely dimples...
Mohenjadaro...
Who entered your heart?
Who slowly melted it?
Man of pleasure...
l'm a skin instrument, play me...
You're a Jack fruit that
doesn't hurt the shoulders...
You're a walking moon...
l'm a tree and
you're a woodpecker...
l'm a forest and
you're enchanted resident in it...
Your waist is just 100 grams...
l'm the lone outfit to you..
l'm a five feet tall grown plant...
graze me fully...
lf you're green grass...
Tiger will eat grass, what's wrong in it?
Hey l'm a Guinea hen!
Engulf me...
Start counting the number of kisses....
Hey Guinea hen!
Engulf me...
Start counting the number of kisses....
Unable to contact Chitti in virtual.
What happened?
Chitti bungled the army evaluation,
he made mincemeat of him
and dumped in dust bin.
We don't keep the garbage here.
By now they'd have dumped it
outside the city.
Where?
- Perungudi.
What did you do to change his heart?
When shall l fix the marriage?
l've not achieved anything, father.
l'll create another robot...
l'll stab you! if you talk
about robot again.
Aren't you satisfied
by breaking one TV?
Uncle, if you've auspicious thread,
l'll tie the knot with him right now.
l can understand your urgency.
Do one thing, exchange the rings now,
fix marriage in next auspicious time.
Okay.
Help...help...take me to Prof.Bora...
Address, A/70 ...Colony.
lt's a small world, Chitti.
l want to live...l want to love...
l love Sana.
Help me professor.
Please restore to my original shape.
l want to live.
l want Sana.
l want your neural schema.
Take anything you want.
Restore me as Chitti.
Please!
l'll do it, Chitti. Don't worry.
What's this new red chip?
This is not Chitti's.
This is Bora's touch.
Additional programming
to Chitti from me,
destruction program.
Why did Vasigaran gave it
power and talent of 100 men?
l've given it the destructive
power of 100 men.
ln short he's a demon now!
Butterflies in my stomach,
why did you change him like that, Prof.?
Business, he's the test for my business.
Business?
l'll get the money and
Dr.Vasigaran gets the blame.
Thank you Bora.
Have a good time, Chitti.
l'm going to meet Sana.
Sana will not be at home.
- She'll be in Raja Muthaiah Hall.
- Why?
Vasigaran and Sana are getting married.
How come you're here, Chitti?
Upgraded, Version 2.0
Stop Chitti!
Though you forcibly take me,
l love Vasigaran.
l like to be his wife only.
Only if he's alive.
lf you harm Vasigaran,
l'll kill myself.
l'm sparing him for you.
Car number TN-09-BB11
Madam, jump.
Hold my hand...
Jump!
Happy Deepavali folks!
What sort of a robot you've created?
lt has killed so many police men
and destroyed many things.
You're responsible for that damages.
We are registering case on you
and take action.
Sir, this is not the robot
l had created.
l had broken into pieces
and dumped in dust bin.
l don't know how did this happen.
First we must find the
robot and stop it. Tell us how to do it.
l'll find out, that's my responsibility.
Give me a minute.
Why are you disturbing me?
What happened to you?
Your system has been corrupted.
l must trouble shoot you,
come to my lab with Sana.
No way, l don't have to follow
your orders anymore.
- l had created you.
- You dismantled me.
We don't have anymore relationship.
l'm going to marry Sana
and start a new life.
- Don't disturb me.
- Don't talk foolishly.
After all you're a machine.
l had created you and
l can destroy too.
Come here with Sana.
Nobody can destroy me.
Sir, cash, cheque or credit card?
Gun!
Call all the police doing rounds
in South Chennai,
block all the roads from T.Nagar
and ask them to check.
Chitti has robbed City Centre,
cover all around Mylapore area.
- Go to Dr.Radhakrishnan Road.
- Okay sir.
Catch him...catch him...
Received information that Chitti has
entered Ennore petrol filling station.
Robot is entering the harbour.
Good, maintain distance
and follow him.
Coast Guard will take care of it.
We've gathered the pieces
of blown up robot.
- This is not Chitti.
- What?
This robot is not my creation.
Parts are different.
lt's confusing.
Robbed four different places
at the same time.
All four places are in different
corners of the city.
How could same person
be in all the places?
l suspect a man.
Oh God!
Nobody can destroy me.
Activate command mode.
l'm CR2.
Speed 1 terahertz.
Memory 1 zetabyte.
- Command mode activated.
- What are you doing Chitti?
l'm producing myself,
it'll produce many like us.
2 will become 4 and
4 will become 8,
8 will become 16,
They are my servants.
- Soldiers and terminators.
- No. l'll not allow it.
l'm not Vasigaran to ask
for your approval, Bora.
l'm Chitti.
Look Chitti, l've taken money
from the dealers.
lf l don't deliver robots in 2 days,
they'll kill me.
Die!
Bloody betrayer!
How dare you go against your creator!
Chitti, delete all the programs
you've created.
lf not l'll cut her neck.
Don't try anything foolish.
Delete the programs.
Do it.
l said get on with it.
Hurry up!
Come on.
Command executive, order us,
we'll shoot him down.
No...no...he gave me boon.
l'll kill him myself.
Robot occupies AlRD,
kills the security guard,
let's get across live to our correspondent
who is right there at the scene,
Robot entered suddenly...
Ordered us to leave or
threatened to kill us.
lt killed the security guards
who resisted.
There's tension in the air,
a sense of panic and fear,
has gripped the AlRD...
After robot took over AlRD,
police asked people around
there to leave for security reasons.
This is our palace.
l'm the king here.
You're my queen.
l've brought everything you like.
l've brought everything you need.
This is our bedroom.
The place we'll spend together
happily after our marriage.
Why are you blabbering
same nonsense again?
lt's impossible to marry you
and be happy.
lt'll happen, Sana.
l'm prepared in all aspects
to be your husband.
l can give all the happiness
which a man can give you.
Didn't get me?
l'm creating an artificial cell.
We can pre-program and
have baby as per our order.
lf it's placed in your uterus,
you'll give birth to the first baby born
to a human and machine.
Robot sapiens!
Shall we begin my love?
lt's waste to act like Seetha
and saying yuck,
you can't escape from here and
nobody can come in to save you,
you can't even commit suicide.
Even if you don't like, l'll place
the artificial cell into your body.
After giving birth to the child,
you've to surrender to me, no way.
Do you need to go that far? No!
Come, let's enjoy now itself.
Give a beautiful kiss to
your great king, baby.
Come...come...come...
Come baby. Come...come...
Get permission from Electricity Board,
cut the power to the area
and time l tell you,
Get a similar petrol lorry like the
one that was blown in harbour.
Fill it with water instead of petrol.
CR 42!
lce cream.
Highness, dinner ready.
l hear some sound form your system.
l don't hear any sound.
lt's so loud, isn't your microphone
also not working?
There's some problem in your system.
l'll fix it.
Sana, l'm Vasigaran.
l've come like Chitti to meet you.
Terrible!
Vasi, take me away from here please.
l'm scared.
Don't get scared,
l've planned everything.
l can't take you out from here
without destroying Chitti.
But destroying Chitti is
in your hands.
Ensure for next 24 hours that Chitti's
concentrates only on you.
l'll take care of the rest.
There's misunderstanding
between robots, Commander.
What happened?
A different robot is delivering
dinner to highness.
A different robot is repairing
the CCD camera.
- Good news, Commander.
- What?
Highness had dinner.
She wanted to see you immediately.
Yes sir.
Switch it off.
What happened?
Wow!
Beautiful!
The best two things ever created by man.
One is me and another is you.
What a pleasant surprize!
How did you change like this, Sana?
l've understood now that
your love for me is true.
l can't believe it.
l remembered everything
from beginning,
you've helped me a lot,
how affectionate you were on me,
other than loving me,
you haven't done any wrong,
even after you were broken
into bits and pieces,
you came back again for me only,
really Chitti, l'm impressed.
How nice it's to hear this, Sana.
At the same time l've a doubt
if this is any plan to betray me.
Can anyone dare cheat you, Chitti?
This is Vasigaran's engagement ring.
Wow! Thank you.
l'm yours!
Mention his name and his greatness...
Even seas will clap...
His stature is so tall
that it'll hit the moon...
Hey beauty...world beauty...
This machine is the best creation...
Lion...lion...
l'm equal to 1000 lions...
Would l leave if l get hold
of golden deer like you?
My dear! Fire of desire is
raking up in metal...
Even Atlantic ocean failed
to douse that fire...
Pour your sweet honey and
douse my fire of desire...
Hey maiden, spread a feast of you
for me on the bed...
Lion...lion...
l'm equal to 1000 lions...
Would l leave if l get hold
of golden deer like you?
Mention his name and his greatness...
Even seas will clap...
His stature is so tall
that it'll hit the moon...
Hey beauty...world beauty...
This machine is the best creation...
The nerve of passion saved in the iron
suddenly burst open with desires...
Heart of this woman seeks
an admirer not a demon...
l'm not a man,
l'm a king of intelligence...
A computer with desires...
l'm silicon lion that eats
young tender heart...
Robot...
Lion...lion...
l'm equal to 1000 lions...
Would l leave if l get hold
of golden deer like you?
l'm a lightning who wears the clouds...
Don't try to apple polish apple...
Wires are making sound...
desires are taking over my life...
Don't say no to robot...
Hey seventh sense,
you're stealing my brain...
Eating me alive...
You say l'm what is leftover
after you finish eating...
Mention his name and his greatness...
Even seas will clap...
His stature is so tall
that it'll hit the moon...
Hey beauty...world beauty...
This machine is the best creation...
Lion...lion...
l'm equal to 1000 lions...
Would l leave if l get hold
of golden deer like you?
What happened to power?
No power for long time, Commander.
Why didn't you switch on the generator?
Commander, somebody has poured
water instead of petrol...
Shit!
Hey what are you doing?
Don't come near, l'll shoot you.
What's this childishness?
Home Ministry
Hello! l'm sorry sir.
l didn't expect our plan
to fail so miserably.
There's only one way to distract Chitti,
just do as l tell you.
- Did Vasigaran come here?
- No.
Lie! Human nature, you taught me.
Have you forgotten it?
Your body language says you're lying.
Trust me Chitti, no.
l think it's mine.
Why not say it's mine?
Yours is O+. That's AB-
He came here.
No, a different robot delivered
dinner to you,
camera didn't function
for 10 minutes,
your sudden change of attitude,
power cut,
water in the generator,
Vasigaran is here only.
Are you trying to cheat me, Sana?
No Chitti.
l love you which you said is lie, right?
Trust me, Chitti.
Do you really love me?
Yes.
Then Vasigaran mustn't be alive.
Come, let's kill Vasigaran.
Soldiers assemble!
Soldiers! We've a Trojan.
A black sheep has entered here
to destroy us from within.
l must find and sacrifice it.
Who is the black sheep?
Dr.Vasigaran, if you surrender,
l'll kill you painlessly.
lf l find you,
your death will be horrible.
Robot!
Yeah...yeah...come...come...come...
Sad!
l think Vasigaran is not here, Sana.
Yes...yes...
Touch one of the two.
Then, Vasigaran is here only.
What happened, Sana?
Are you feeling giddy?
Now, you will feel giddy.
Soldiers! Rotate your heads!
Black sheep!
Stop!
He's the Trojan.
No...no...down..down...
No.
You said l had created you
and destroy too.
Now, you're going to die in my hands.
What are you looking at?
This is hand gun l made it myself.
Hand made. ls it good?
Where should l shoot you?
ls it brain which wants to kill me?
ls it heart where my love Sana resides?
l must shoot the brain
which wants to kill me.
Sana, come..
[ Skipped item nr. 1870 ]
Fire!
Get that robot.
Place it here.
May l come in?
Start the car!
Yes!
Move!
Shoot man
Fire!
Start the vehicle. Come
Don't stand, run
No!
Hundreds of murders,
200 victims are in critical condition,
public property worth billions
has been damaged,
Dr.Vasigaran, you're responsible
for all this,
with awarding death penalty
to you and closure of your lab.
we are closing our judgement
Can l speak now?
We can't accept machine as witness.
l'm not witness, l'm evidence.
Law will not accept it.
lt will, according to the
section 3 of evidence act 1872,
an evidence can be material,
or documentary.
You may proceed.
First l want to tell you clearly
one thing, your honour.
lf a machine goes wrong and
someone dies, it's not a murder.
lt's an accident.
Next, Vasigaran is not responsible
for all the accidents.
Professor Bora.
What's this new story?
You honour, Professor Bora is not alive.
This is an attempt to twist the case.
l've evidence, your honour.
This is not Chitti's.
Additional programming
to Chitti from me,
destruction program.
Why did Vasigaran gave it
power and talent of 100 men?
l've given it the destructive
power of 100 men.
l'll get the money and
Dr.Vasigaran gets the blame.
The evidence produced
is very important.
This court frees him as innocent
accepting that evidence.
At the same time, this robot's
extraordinary powers,
there's a possibility that it can turn
against humans at any time,
and there's a danger of anyone
misusing its power,
it may be useful in the future,
since such robots are not necessary
for the present times,
this court bans robots from usage.
This robot should be dismantled in the
presence Magistrate and Commissioner,
and the parts should be removed
and make it unusable,
and inform this court.
Dismantle it.
You need any help, doctor.
Dismantle yourself, Chitti.
Sure doctor.
Siva..Ravi...you said you've
something which l don't have,
did you see how many problems
we'd to face for it?
l said about feelings.
Please don't cry, son.
What's your son saying sister?
l've named him after you, Chitti.
Name given by mother.
Educate him well.
Robotics, good scope in future.
Like you inserted a red chip in me,
many people are moving with red chips
of selfishness, betrayal, cheating.
Good, l wasn't born as human.
Can't dismantle at the thought.
l've tortured you a lot.
l'm extremely sorry, Sana.
Why are you all sad?
May l crack a joke?
They say who ever falls in love
loses his nuts.
Did you see? l lost it.
l'm going to miss you, Sana.
Not as boy friend but as toy friend.
Doctor, you're my God.
l tried to betray you.
Breaking rules is wrong.
Please forgive me.
No Chitti, you learnt to break
the rules from humans.
The mistake is not just yours.
Thank you doctor.
l'm feeling good, doctor.
What you are seeing is Chitti,
the most advanced
Android Humanoid Robot.
20 years earlier Dr.Vasigaran created it.
lt was dismantled for some reasons.
Why?
Because l started to think.
Okay Chitti, let's go to the next section.