® Encoded By M@X. Enjoy ! ®
Illuminat...
(CHUCKLES)
(CLEARS THROAT) Illuminat...
(GIGGLES)
Illuminat...
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(FARTS)
(SNIFFS AND GROANS)
(GIGGLES) Illumination!
(FARTS) (GROANING)
The year was 1985,
and the number one
show on TV was...
Evil Bratt!
HOST: The show starred young
Balthazar Bratt as a child prodigy
and criminal mastermind
bent on world domination.
(LAUGHING) There
he is! Get him!
(ALL GRUNTING)
I've been a bad boy!
Bratt was the biggest
child actor of the 1980s,
striking a chord with
audiences all over the world.
(BOTH CHEERING)
(BALTHAZAR LAUGHING)
There he is! Get him!
HOST: But it all came to an
end in Season 3, when...
I've been a bad boy!
HOST: The young star experienced
an unexpected growth spurt.
Boy? Ugh!
The show was canceled.
Hollywood rejected him
and Bratt quickly plunged
into a downward spiral,
starting to actually believe he was
the character he played on TV.
What are you looking at?
HOST: Leading us
all to wonder,
where is he now?
(BALTHAZAR LAUGHING)
(CHUCKLING)
You know what, Clive?
Playing a villain
on TV was fun,
but being one in real
life is even better.
Heist music!
Here it comes.
(ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
(EXCLAIMS IN DISGUST) What?
Clive, what are you doing?
How is that heist music?
Sorry. My bad.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Ew! (GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Mommy!
Stop or I'll... (GROANS)
(ALARM BLARING)
Sir, the ship has been boarded
by some kind of monster!
Wait! That's not a monster.
That's a man wearing
shoulder pads!
There's only one supervillain
whose fashion sense
is quite that dated.
Balthazar Bratt.
Blast it! The Dumont
Diamond is on that ship.
I want every agent in the area
on the scene immediately!
(MINIONS LAUGHING)
We're already here. Agents
Grucy are closing fast.
Yes! Wait. What
did you call us?
"Grucy." You know, Gru and
Lucy mushed together. Try it.
Oh! I like it, but not a lot.
I don't like it.
Stop! On the ground!
(BOTH YELP AND GRUNT)
(CHUCKLES)
(AGENTS CLAMORING)
Go, go, go!
Eh? (ALL SCREAM)
Too late again, Gru! (LAUGHS)
Wha?
He's getting away!
That's what he thinks.
(MINIONS WHOOPING)
Go! Go! Go...
Go! Go! Go! (GRUNTS) Go! Go!
I don't think we
can make it, Gru!
We can make it!
No, we can't!
Ahh!
Get ready!
Get ready for...
(GRU AND MINIONS SCREAMING)
Hey. How you doing? (GROANS)
(COUGHING) (GIRL GASPS)
GIRL: Are you okay?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(CHUCKLES) You
guys are so cute.
Go get him, Gru-Gru!
Hello, Gru.
How's your transition coming?
You know, from world's
worst villain
to world's worst agent?
Oh, that's hilarious.
You should be on TV.
Oh, that's right. You were!
But then you got canceled!
(CHUCKLES) Ha-ha!
What about that? Ugh!
What? Oh, girls! Oh!
(GRUNTING)
Dance fight!
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
(SCATTING)
Ow!
(CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHS)
Alpha Team, the diamond is secure.
Come and pick up the package.
ALPHA TEAM LEADER: Copy that.
Alpha Team in approach.
Gru!
Did you actually think
I was unconscious?
Huh! It's called
acting, hoser.
And clearly, I've
still got it!
(SCREAMING)
(PLAYING KEYTAR)
(GRU CONTINUES SCREAMING)
I've been a bad boy!
(CACKLES)
ALPHA TEAM LEADER:
Freeze! Don't move!
Son of a Betamax!
SOLDIER: Go, go! Get him!
He's getting away! (YELLING)
This isn't over, Gru.
You hear me? This is not over.
Yeah? Well, I still
have the diamond.
(LAUGHS)
ALL: (SINGING) Happy
birthday to you.
Happy birthday to...
Happy birthday, dear Dan.
Happy birthday to you
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS)
(PEOPLE YELPING)
(GRU GROANING)
I can't believe Bratt
got away again.
How is this possible? How?
(GRU LAUGHS)
And it's not just
that he got away,
it is he's so smug about it.
"Ooh, I've been a bad boy!"
Gah! Edna, hey!
Looking hot today.
Got cats on you.
And it was so humiliating, dangling
there in the bubble-gum Speedo.
And I didn't have time to
go to the gym this week,
and I had a big breakfast. And
was feeling a little bloated.
You know what? He's not
even worth talking about.
I don't even want to waste
another breath about the guy.
And another thing!
Next time I see Bratt, I will
moonwalk all over his stupid face!
(MIMICS DANCING)
Thank you all for coming
at such short notice.
It is with great sadness that I
inform you that, as of today,
I am retiring as
head of the AVL.
(ALL GASP)
Oh, no!
Your new leader is coming
directly from head office.
Effective immediately.
She is the very gifted,
very ambitious, Miss
Valerie da Vinci.
As I look out over
all your faces,
I am flooded with
so many memories.
Oh, boy! This is
a snooze fest!
Excuse me, this is my last...
Blah, blah, blah!
We understand.
You're old, you're
fat, you're done.
Let me breathe in. (GRUNTING)
(SILAS GROANS) (ALL GASP)
Ooh, broke a little
sweat, there. (CHUCKLES)
First order of business,
(CLEARS THROAT)
which one of you
losers is Agent Gru?
Oh, that would be me.
Although, I don't know if
I'd say "loser," per se.
Kind of is... (GASPS)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(GRUNTS)
Oh, it's the girls!
Not a good time.
Hey! Ahh!
Yes, sir! (GASPS) Uh...
Ma'am? You're
making me nervous.
How could you let
Balthazar Bratt,
the AVL's most wanted villain,
just get away?
That is the opposite
of what we do here!
Okay, okay.
Yes, maybe he got away. Again.
But he didn't get the diamond.
And I am this close
to bringing him in.
This close.
Huh. Interesting.
You're fired!
(GASPS) What?
That's totally not fair.
Gru is a great agent!
You know what?
If you fire him,
you're gonna have to
fire me, sister-sister.
And do you really
wanna do that?
Do ya?
GRU: No, no, no!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(GRU GRUNTING)
Well, I guess she did.
Honey, you didn't
have to do that.
I know how much you
love your job.
Well, I love other
things more.
You know, we're gonna
have to tell the girls.
Can you do it?
The whole "mom" thing is
still kind of new to me.
Oh, sure.
Huh?
Psst! (SPEAKING GIBBERISH)
(BOTH YELLING)
Hello?
(ALL CRYING OUT)
(GIRLS CHUCKLING)
GIRLS: Aloha!
LUCY: Oh!
This is unexpected.
Well, you never got to
go on a honeymoon, so...
We made you dinner!
It's a luau!
We got pineapples and
coconuts and ukuleles!
Oh! Yay! Yay!
(SINGING IN MINIONESE)
(CLEARS THROAT) The
soup of the day.
Madame and Monsieur.
The gummy bears were my idea.
Mmm! Looks too
good to even eat.
Am I right? (CHUCKLES)
But I made it for you. Oh.
(MUFFLED GROAN) Mmm-mmm-mmm!
Good soup! I love
the combination
of gummy bears
and meat.
(SPUTTERS)
I'm gonna hold it in my mouth.
'Cause it's so good, I
don't wanna swallow it.
So, how was work?
Ooh, did you take that guy
down? Did anything explode?
Well, actually,
today, Lucy and I were
invited to not work
at the AVL anymore.
(UKULELE STRING
SNAPS) (GASPS) No!
You got fired?
Oh, no! No, no, no.
(LAUGHS)
Yes. (GIRLS GASP)
But don't worry.
I'm sure we'll get
new jobs. Real soon.
Even better ones. (SCOFFS)
What's better than being
super-cool secret agents?
Ooh, I know! You
could gamble online!
That's what Katie's dad does.
Okay. We will definitely
look into that.
That's a good suggestion.
And let's not go over to
Katie's house anymore.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hmm?
(GRU GRUNTS) (CELL
PHONE RINGING)
GRU: Guys! Shh! I don't
think you heard me right.
No, no, no.
This does not mean that we are
going back to being villains.
(MINIONS GROAN)
(GRUNTS AND SPEAKS MINIONESE)
Okay, all right. I get it.
Look, I know it's been
a little tough lately.
Especially with Dr. Nefario accidentally
freezing himself in carbonite.
(DRILL WHIRRING) (GROANS)
But our life of crime is over!
(SIGHS)
Mel! Mel, you're with
me on this, right?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(ALL CHEERING)
(ALL BOOING)
(ALL GROANING)
(ALL CHEERING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(ALL CHANTING IN MINIONESE)
Guys, listen to
me! Read my lips!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(ALL LAUGH)
What? What?
Oh... What did I say?
It's not "comquit"?
Ah, okay.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Don't take that tone with me!
We're not going back to villainy.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Yes! And I don't want to
hear another word about it.
(ALL BLOWING RASPBERRIES)
Look, if you guys don't stop right
now, there will be consequences.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Hey! Don't say anything
you're going to regret.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
What? You quit?
You're serious? Come on!
(GRUNTING)
(CHUCKLING)
Dave! Jerry! (CHUCKLING)
Great news, guys. You
have been promoted.
You're in charge
now. Huh? Not bad.
(BOTH LAUGH)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(SIGHS LOUDLY)
Jeesh!
(GUARD GASPS)
(GRUNTS) Ah, Monsieur Pompeux!
To what do we owe the presence
of the world's
foremost gem expert?
The chief of police sent me.
He was concerned that during
the recent heist attempt,
the Dumont Diamond was
replaced with a phony.
(ALL GASP)
(SNIFFING)
Ooh, la-la!
You have been duped!
(GASPS) What? We have?
Yes.
By me!
(GRUNTS) (GASPS)
But, what is...
(GRUNTS AND GASPS)
Oh, no! Help!
(GROANING)
(CACKLING)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
Ooh! (CHUCKLES)
I've been a bad boy!
Or should I say...
(SPEAKING IN FRENCH)
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
Oh!
(SNORING)
(CHIMING)
Hey, Gru.
What you doing down here?
In the dark. Alone.
Oh, nothing. Just thinking.
You okay?
Oh, yes. Yeah, I'm
fine. I'm fine.
It's just... (SIGHS)
I don't know. I guess
I just feel like
a failure.
Like I don't have a
purpose anymore.
Hey, mister, you
are not a failure.
If only I could
have nailed Bratt.
So many times, I
almost had him.
But now I'll never
get the chance,
'cause I have been
kicked to the curb.
Gru, you've got
to let this go.
It's time to look forward.
Things will get
better. I promise.
(GRU SIGHS)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Excuse me.
Pardon me, young people?
Would you tell me how
to get to this address?
(STAMMERING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
I'm looking for a Mr. Gru.
(BLOWING RASPBERRY)
(ALL CHATTERING IN MINIONESE)
(GRUNTING)
Idiots.
(GROWLING)
GRU: No! Kyle!
Stop! Kyle, let go!
No! No!
You've got to be kidding me!
Lucy, did you...
AGNES: He helps you if
you have nightmares.
And he's really good
to snuggle with.
Oh, no, no, no. Agnes! Agnes!
So (SNIFFLES) take
good care of him.
Thank you! (CHUCKLES)
Agnes, what are you doing?
You sold your unicorn?
Well, I just wanted to help,
since you don't have a job.
I got two whole
dollars for it.
(BOTH SIGH) (FRITZ
CLEARING THROAT)
Uh, excuse me?
Sorry, buddy, the sale's over.
Yes, but this will
only take a...
Hey, eyebrows, get
off the lawn.
Yeah, but... (SIGHS)
Hey, could you...
Oh, uh, of course.
Now, as I was saying, I...
Uh... Oh.
Goodbye! (SQUEALS)
(CHUCKLES)
Listen, Agnes, you don't need to
worry. We're going to be fine.
For real?
For real.
Now, come on, let's
pack this stuff up.
FRITZ: Ow! Ow! Seriously?
Buddy, you're not
getting the hint.
Excuse me, Mr. Gru,
but I really must
have a word with you.
How do you know my name?
Allow me to introduce
myself. My name is Fritz.
(KYLE BITES) Ow! (GROANING)
(GROWLING) Good puppy.
And I am inquiring on behalf
of your twin brother, Dru.
He needs your help.
What? Twin brother?
Twin brother?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Oh, ja.
He would like to fly you
to Freedonia to meet him.
Your father has recently
passed away and...
(LAUGHS) Okay, cuckoo.
I'm sorry, but my dad
died when I was a baby,
and I don't have any brother.
You got the wrong guy.
Really? Well, then, how
do you explain this?
(GRU STAMMERS)
(MAN HUMMING)
VINCENZO: (CHUCKLING)
Bellissimo!
(GRU'S MOM LAUGHING)
Oh, hello, Gru.
Hi, Mom.
It's important to keep active
in one's golden years.
(CHUCKLES) Oh! (GURGLING)
There you are, you cutie, you.
Oh! (CHUCKLES)
Uh, these are my
diving instructors.
Vincenzo und Paolo.
(GROWLS AND LAUGHS)
Ciao, boys.
(SIGHS) So, what do you want?
Mom, do I have a twin brother?
Ah! How did you find
out? Who told you?
Wait, what? It's true?
You never told me
I had a brother!
And you told me that Dad died of
disappointment when I was born.
Ja, ja. (STUTTERS) That
was the agreement.
Agreement? What are
you talking about?
(SIGHS)
Shortly after you and
your brother were born,
your father and I divorced.
We each took one son
to raise on our own
and promised never to
see each other again.
Obviously, (CHUCKLING)
I got second pick.
I have a brother!
Hey, girls! How are
things in Row B, huh?
I put together some fun
activities for the trip!
Who is up for some gin rummy?
Yeah, um...
We're good.
Oh, okay.
I'll just sit here
and play solitaire.
I hope I win.
I wonder what Dru
will be like. Ooh!
Maybe we'll have
the twin thing
when you can read each
other's minds, no?
How cool would that be?
Um, super cool! (CHUCKLES)
(MINION LAUGHING)
(SIGHS) Ooh! (SHUTTER CLICKS)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH SHRIEK)
(AGNES WHOOPING)
GIRLS: Freedonia!
Freedonia! Freedonia!
(SNORTING) Hi, piggy, piggy!
(GASPS) Whoa! Look
at that house!
It's like a castle!
I can't wait to
meet my brother!
Ugh. What's with all the pigs?
This is the family business.
The largest pig farm in
the whole of Freedonia.
(SNORTS) (GASPS)
Okay, nice pig. (GROANS)
No! That's my private part!
(SQUEALING) (SCREAMING)
GRU: This pig has issues!
FRITZ: Please, come in.
(MINIONS EXCLAIMING)
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
(SCREAMING) (FRITZ GRUNTS)
(SIGHS AND GASPS)
Oh, this is amazing!
Ah, it's like the Sistine
Chapel! But with pigs.
(DRU LAUGHING)
My brother!
BOTH: My brother!
Gru!
Dru!
(LAUGHING)
Oh!
Brother! I am hugging
you! (GRUNTING)
I'm so happy!
After all of these years,
finally I'm meeting you!
Yup. All right. Good.
Oh, look at that.
You must be the
beautiful wife.
Beautiful? Oh! (CHUCKLES)
Stop it. Sweet talker.
How is my brother
finding a wife like you
when he is so bald? (LAUGHS)
(GRUNTING) I'm joking!
(GIGGLING)
(WHOOPING) These
must be my nieces!
(GASPS) You're Agnes! You
are small with big eyes.
And it makes me wanna
put you into my pocket.
You can't do that!
I'm too big.
Edith! I can tell that you
are a little mischievous.
We're gonna have to make
a little trouble later.
I already have! (LAUGHS)
Ow! Ow! Please!
Why are you doing that? Ow!
Fist bump for
mischievous behavior!
And Margo. Oh, you
are so mature!
I'm guessing... Mmm... 15?
15?
She's 12. She looks 12
and will always be 12.
So, Dru, this
place is amazing!
I mean, you just walk through
the doors and you're like...
(GRUNTS AND LAUGHS)
Oh, it's nice, I guess, sure.
I'm not really into things.
MARGO: This is so cool!
AGNES: Look at that!
EDITH: Oh, my gosh! He's
even got a helicopter!
AGNES: This is the best!
Yes, the best!
(WHISPERS) All right,
let's go home now.
Home? Why?
I don't know. This guy with
the mansion and the cars
and all of the hair, with the
silky smooth, luxurious hair.
I feel worse than I
did before I came.
But he's your brother,
Gru. Give this a chance.
Oh, I was thinking,
while Gru and I
catch up on some
brother stuff,
you girls should go with Fritz.
He has a surprise for you!
ALL: Yay! Awesome!
I love surprises!
Oh, this is perfect!
Mother-daughter bonding time.
Let's do it! Woot-woot!
Bye! You boys have fun!
(LAUGHS) Whoopi!
ANNOUNCER: Now you can be
as evil as Balthazar Bratt
with the Evil Bratt
action figure.
Featuring music-activated
breakdance mode.
Also featuring bubblegum-launching
shoulder pads!
And the all-new
Mega Diamond Laser!
No more math!
I've been a bad boy!
(LAUGHS)
ANNOUNCER: The Mega Diamond Laser
does not actually incinerate books.
(SIGHS) How could
Hollywood cancel a show
that produced toys
like this, Clive?
Evil Bratt was a masterpiece!
Does no one value
true art anymore?
It's a disgrace and
a travesty, sir.
Well, now that I've got the
diamond, it's payback time.
Oh, it's too bad Gru won't be
around to try and stop me.
Oh, wait! No, it's not.
I hate that dweeb!
And you, Hollywood!
This time, I'm canceling you
and all the losers
who rejected me!
(EVIL LAUGHTER)
Oh, piggy, piggy!
So, how are things going
for you career-wise?
(CHUCKLES) Great!
So, so great!
Crushing it.
Well, I've got
something that I think
you will find
very interesting.
Hold onto your face, brother.
(CHUCKLING) (CLICK)
(METALLIC THUDDING)
(BOTH YELLING)
Yee-haw! Yah, yah!
(GRUNTING)
(PIG SQUEALING)
(DRU CONTINUES SCREAMING)
GRU: Ow! (GRUNTS)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(SQUEALS)
(GROANING)
Come on! Come on!
(CHUCKLING) (GRU GASPS)
What is all this?
DRU: The pig farm was just a cover
for the real family business.
(LAUGHING AND
SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Now, feast your eyes on.
Dad's lair!
Ta-da!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait.
So, our dad was a villain?
No, no, no, not
just a villain.
One of the greatest
of all time!
He was known as
the Bald Terror!
That's him? Our dad?
He was so proud of you. And
what a great villain you were.
(GASPS) He was?
But me, eh, not so much.
To Dad, I was just a failure.
He never thought I had what
it took to be a villain.
But now, you can help
me prove him wrong!
Brother,
teach me the art of villainy!
No.
No, no, no. I can't do that.
What? (STUTTERING) But
it's our family tradition!
You can't say no to that!
Look, I'm sorry.
I left that life behind
me. End of story.
Oh.
Okay. I understand.
Hmm! I wonder what this does.
(SHRIEKING)
Holy moley!
Dad's villain wheels!
Pretty slick, huh?
Hey, you wanna take her out for
a spin? Just for some fun?
Mmm!
(DRU WHOOPING)
GRU: Oh, oh, oh!
Look out! (YELPING)
(GRU GRUNTING)
(LAUGHS)
What a beautiful day!
Zero to 400 in three seconds.
Able to withstand
a nuclear blast.
Armed to the teeth.
(CHUCKLES) Okay,
that's pretty nice.
And it's a hybrid. Look out!
(SCREAMING)
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(GRU GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
Help me!
I am not enjoying this.
(DRU CACKLES)
(MEN SINGING)
Whoa! What is going on here?
Welcome to the annual
Freedonian Cheese Festival.
Go!
(CROWD CHEERING)
(GASPS) Look, look! Look
at all the candies!
(CHUCKLING) Whoa!
Eep, eep, eep!
Lucy, can we get
these? Please.
(SIGHS) Okay, but only
one each. I mean it.
Aw! Oh, man!
No, I don't. (CHUCKLES) Get as
many as you want. I don't care.
Yay! Awesome!
Uh... What?
Well, it's okay to tell them
no sometimes, too, you know?
Moms need to be tough.
Right, right. Tough. Good one.
I can totally do that.
You know, still figuring
out this mom thing.
Gettin' my sea legs,
matey! (AGNES SCREAMS)
It's a unicorn!
Can we go in there?
Please, please, please!
(MEN GROANING)
Um... Sure! Yeah! You
know, but first let's...
Um... (GASPS) Oh, look!
It's a traditional
Freedonian dance.
How amazing does that look?
ALL: (SINGING) Say,
say, say cheese!
Cheese! I love this.
The little girls go and get the
cheese from the little boys.
That's adorable!
Aw, look at that poor little
guy. With his little boots.
Nobody picked him.
Oh, Margo, why don't
you go up there?
No way!
Okay.
Wait a minute.
No!
Go take a bite of his
cheese, young lady.
Right now! What?
I'm being tougher, you
know? Like you said.
No! I meant be tougher
on them. Not me!
Oh, come on, just do it. What's
the worst that could happen?
Mmm...
Fine.
(GASPS DEEPLY)
Wow!
Hey, there. I'm Margo.
Hello, Margo!
I am Niko.
Would you like
some of my cheese?
Mmm...
ALL: (SINGING) Say,
say, say cheese!
Yes! Thank you, Margo.
Thank you! (WHOOPING)
Bam! I am a great
mother! (CHUCKLES)
Did you see that, girls?
I laid down the...
Oh, no! Where are they?
Oh... Agnes? Edith?
Hello. (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
(GASPS) Look! A unicorn horn!
My little brain is
going to explode!
(GROANS) Agnes, that's fake.
(CHUCKLING)
It's real, all right.
(GASPS)
That horn came from
the Crooked Forest.
The only place on earth
where unicorns still live.
(ALL PATRONS LAUGH)
Huh! (SPITS)
Laugh, laugh, all of
you. (MIMICS LAUGHING)
They all think I'm crazy.
But I'm telling you,
I saw one once.
With my own eye.
Wait, wait, wait. You saw
a for-real live unicorn?
What did it look like? (GASPS)
Did you pet it? Did
it smell like candy?
Was it fluffy?
It was so fluffy,
(SIGHS) I thought
I was gonna die.
Mmm! Do you think maybe
I could find one, too?
Oh! They say if a
maiden pure of heart
goes into the Crooked Forest,
the unicorn will
come and be hers.
Forever.
Hmm...
(AGNES SQUEALING)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(GASPS) Agnes!
(GRUNTING)
Goal!
Excuse me. (BOTH SOBBING)
Girls, don't worry. I'm here.
(PANTING) Are you okay?
Yeah, we're fine.
Are you?
Unicorns are really real!
And I'm gonna find
one! (GROANING)
Sorry. Went a little
mama bear on ya.
You know, I heard
a scream and...
(PATRONS GROANING) Yeah,
okay, have a good one.
Wait for me here.
(GRUMBLING) Stop that!
Ah! You kicked me.
(ALARM BLARING) Hey!
Hey! What are you doing?
Did you just steal
candies? Yes!
That's a lot of effort
for two lollipops.
(SIRENS BLARING)
(BLOWING WHISTLE)
(BELLS CHIMING)
Oh, no! The police!
What do we do? What do we do?
Come on! This is gonna be fun!
(POLICEMEN CLAMORING)
The police are gonna get us!
(SHRIEKS) I'm freaking out!
Pigs!
Cops! (CLAMORING)
(POLICEMEN GROANING)
(LAUGHS)
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
Whoa! They're back!
All right!
(POLICEMEN CLAMORING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Oh, man, that was crazy!
We were so close
to getting busted.
Tell me about it.
I thought you were going
to pee your pants.
DRU: I did!
GRU: You did! (BOTH LAUGH)
(MINIONS GROANING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(STOMACH GROWLING)
MINION: Pizza! Pizza! Pizza!
(GASPS)
Hey! What are you doing?
Intruders! Intruders!
There they are! Stop!
(DOGS BARKING)
Hey, you, don't move!
Halt!
(MINIONS SCREAMING)
Call for backup!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(AUDIENCE GASPS)
(AUDIENCE MURMURING
INDISTINCTLY)
Ooh, uh...
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(SINGING IN MINIONESE)
(SIGHS)
(ALL SINGING IN MINIONESE)
Get 'em! Go! Go!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(ALL PANTING)
(JUDGES CHEERING)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
GUARD 1: Hey, you!
Freeze! Don't move!
GUARD 2: Hands in the air!
(SIGHS)
Face it, Gru. Villainy
is in your blood.
You can't tell me you don't
miss the rush. A little?
Uh...
Eh, maybe a little. (CHUCKLES)
And now you've got the
chance to get back on top.
Get your mojo back.
Become Gru again. How
awesome would that be?
GRU: Hmm.
Oh, please, come on.
Just one heist.
There's got to be something
out there, somewhere
that you still wanna
steal. (CLICKS TONGUE)
GRU: Huh.
There is something.
(GASPS) How about we steal
the largest diamond
in the world?
Yes! I love it!
(WHOOPING) Oh, thank
you, brother!
Thank you from the
bottoms of my heart.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Oh, you know what? We should
do something to celebrate!
(CHUCKLES) Oh!
I've got the perfect idea.
(AGNES CHEWING LOUDLY)
Fritz, my good fellow, could you
get me another napkin, please?
Ah, yes. Of course,
Miss Edith.
(AIR HORN TOOTING)
(BOTH LAUGH)
(CHUCKLING)
Hey, where are Gru and Dru?
Here we are!
Oh, how's it going?
(BOTH SNICKER)
It's me! Gru.
And me, Dru.
I hug everybody whether
they like it or not.
Why are they pretending
to be each other?
(SCOFFS)
Ah! What's for dinner? I
probably won't like it.
I'm so grumpy all
the time. Hmm.
I laugh a lot. And I'm
kind of an idiot!
(BOTH LAUGH LOUDLY)
(DRU AND GRU
CONTINUE LAUGHING)
Oh, I'm busting a gut!
Look at them!
They had no idea!
GRU: Total burn.
Oh, look, it's me, Gru!
And I'm Dru! We
switched places!
Oh, it's so nice to see you
two are getting along.
Oh, we're getting...
Along perfectly.
Wait. Did we... Just finish...
Each... Other's...
Sentences? Sentences?
(BOTH LAUGH)
Oh, that's delightful.
Not creepy at all.
And you're gonna stop
now though, right?
Sorry, it's a twin thing.
Uh-huh...
So, uh, what did
you guys do today?
(AGNES CHEWING LOUDLY)
BOTH: Nothing.
Okay. What does it...
All done! (PANTING)
Pardon me! Out of the way!
Good night, everybody!
Hey! Hey! Put the brakes
on. What's the rush?
I need to get to bed so I can
wake up and find a unicorn!
Good night!
What was that about?
Agnes thinks she's gonna find a
real unicorn in the woods tomorrow.
(SCOFFS) She's totally
freaking out.
(SIGHS) I feel like someone's
gotta tell her the truth.
Not it!
Oh, don't worry. Parenting
101. I got this.
AGNES: Um...
And please bless that
when I find the unicorn
he'll want to come home with
me, and sleep in my room.
And that I can ride him
to school every day.
And he'll use his magical
powers to help me do math.
Amen.
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
Oh, hi, Gru.
Hey. So, big day tomorrow.
Yeah, I'm finally gonna get
to see a unicorn. For reals.
(GASPS) If I do, can I
bring it home? Please?
Oh, yeah. Sure.
Tell you what, every unicorn you
find, you can bring it home.
I'd better build a
big pen, right?
But, you know,
there's a chance that
you might not find one.
Huh?
(STAMMERING)
It might not be good
unicorn-finding weather.
Um... They're tricky
to find them.
And I don't know. Maybe...
Maybe unicorns
don't really
explore that part of
the woods. (CHUCKLES)
(SNIFFLES)
But the man said a maiden could
find one if she was pure in heart.
And I'm pure in heart, right?
The purest.
(AGNES GRUNTS SOFTLY)
Can we stop talking now?
I need to get to sleep.
Good night, sweetie.
Good night, Gru.
(SINGING) Unicorns,
I love them.
Unicorns, I love them.
Huh! (SCREAMS) (THUDS)
I'm okay.
(PEPPY MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey! Give that back!
(ALL YELLING)
Oh, no! Run!
(ALL PRISONERS SCREAM)
(MEN GROANING)
We've been waiting a
long time. Can we...
No! (LAUGHING)
No, please! (GASPS)
Gru?
Uh-oh!
(WHIMPERING)
Ha!
(SOBBING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(LAUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
Huh? (GASPS)
(SIGHS AND CHUCKLES)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(SINGING) Because I'm
training for the big day.
Nobody's gonna stop me
'Cause I am super sassy.
Super sassy, super sassy.
What's today's plan, boss?
What's the plan?
(CHUCKLES) Silly robot.
I'll show you the plan!
Time to watch a very special
episode of Evil Bratt
to see exactly what I'm gonna
do to stupid Tinseltown.
ANNOUNCER: This week
on Evil Bratt...
(ALL SCREAMING)
It's a giant Evil Bratt robot!
Open fire!
I have him in my sights!
Nice try, coppers!
Chew on this!
(OFFICER SCREAMS)
He's shooting his
super sticky,
self-inflating gum!
(GASPING) Run!
Gum one, gum all!
(CACKLING)
(CHUCKLES) "Gum one, gum all."
Seriously, how did this
show never win an Emmy?
And now, it's your turn
to shine, my diamond!
Hey, Clive. I guess you
could say our plan was
out of this world!
(EVIL LAUGHTER)
Now, that's entertainment!
Come on! Let's
make it a reality!
Here we are, in the dark
and creepy Crooked Forest
in search of the
mythical unicorn.
For some reason.
And here she is! The fearless
unicorn hunter seeking...
Edith, stop it!
You're gonna scare
away the unicorn.
If, somehow, we actually
find a unicorn,
I'm gonna film
it and get rich.
(GASPS) Look over there!
EDITH: Whoa!
This is it!
This is where we're
gonna see it.
AGNES: Unicorns, here we come.
What's that for?
Bait! Duh.
Come on! (YELPS)
Now, all we have
to do is wait.
Okay, this is Bratt's lair.
It may not look like much,
but this place is
armed with some of
the most high-tech
weaponry known to man.
It's considered impenetrable.
But a piece of cake for
us, right, brother?
Yes. This is not like
stealing lollipops.
Whoa!
His security system can detect an
air assault from any direction.
(SCREAMING) Ouch! No! Ouch!
Please, stop! Ouch!
(MUFFLED COUGH)
So we'll have to approach
low and close to the water.
Next. Ah...
Then there are these
deadly spikes.
(CHUCKLING) Geronimo!
GRU: Covered with enough
poison to blow your mind.
Literally.
Ouch! (LAUGHS)
Ah, good to know.
So here's the plan. You're
the getaway driver.
(GASPS) So you'll
wait in the boat...
Wait, hold on!
Wait in the boat?
(SCOFFS) But I wanna
be in on the actions!
Dru, the getaway driver is the
most crucial part of any plan.
Do you know how hard it is
doing nothing,
touching nothing
when all of that adrenaline is
coursing through your veins
and you must wait?
Can I count on you?
Yeah.
Ah, I guess so.
So, I'll climb up to the
cube and enter here.
Then once I'm inside,
find the diamond.
I've underestimated Bratt before.
It's not going to be easy.
I think we can handle it.
Dad's villain suits! This
will make us unstoppable!
Whoa! Ay, chihuahua!
I call the black one.
It's go time!
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Hello.
Oh, hi!
Hello, mother of
Margo. I am Niko.
I present you with
pig to confirm
my engagement to your
daughter. (SQUEALS)
(LAUGHING) Hey, what now?
What's going on? Uh,
remember little boots?
Hello, my schmoopsie
poo. Whoa, hey!
He seems to think you're
engaged. (CHUCKLES)
What? We're not engaged.
Look, Niko, you seem like a very
nice boy with a very nice pig.
Uh... But you're not engaged.
Okay? It's not happening.
I understand.
Who was I kidding?
A dumpling like me with
a goddess like you.
But I promise, I will
never forget you, Margo.
Never.
Oh, I'm pretty sure I
won't forget you either.
Bye. Bye, Niko.
Wow! That was crazy.
(CHUCKLES) Whoa!
That was totally humiliating.
Taking a bite of that cheese was the
stupidest thing I've ever done.
Why did I listen to you?
Right. But it's
over now, so...
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
Oh! Here we go.
Niko... (GASPS)
You refuse my son's
engagement pig?
What?
May you and your daughter
die a slow death
and be buried with onions.
(BOTH SPIT)
(GASPS)
All right, lady, that's it!
Nobody...
Nobody curses my
daughter! Ya got that?
Because if you mess with
Margo, you mess with me!
And I promise, you do
not wanna mess with me.
Do you understand me?
(MUFFLED) Yes. Yes.
Good. Now get!
(SPEAKING IN FREEDONIAN)
Look, Margo, I think
we just need to... Oh.
(LUCY CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Yes!
(SIGHS HEAVILY) I
have to tell Gru!
(DRU LAUGHING)
(YAWNING) Can we go back now?
Already? Just a
couple more hours.
We have to be home
before it gets dark.
(SIGHS) I don't understand.
I did exactly what
the man said.
You mean that one-eyed scar-faced
man that everybody laughed at?
Yeah, it makes no sense.
Look, Agnes, maybe
we're not...
(TWIG SNAPS) (GASPS)
(RUSTLING)
Ooh, my whole life has been
building to this moment.
(SCREAMS)
(GASPS) Um... It's a...
Unicorn! (GIGGLING)
(BLEATING) I can't believe it!
I'm gonna name you Lucky!
(CHUCKLING) Oh,
Lucky, stop it!
Yeah, I'll let someone
else burst her bubble.
Look at us! Two brothers
pulling a heist!
And that diamond will
make us the richest,
most powerful villains
in the world!
Right, brother?
Oh, right. Yep, yeah.
Bravo! Bravissimo!
You're amazing! I'm so sorry.
I'm so embarrassed.
I was very rude.
And you were always such
a gentleman. You did it!
You did it! You got
our jobs back!
(CLEARS THROAT) What?
Oh, yeah, right. Sure.
Oh, look. We're here!
I'm going in. Take
the wheel. (GROANS)
I still don't see why
I can't go with you.
Hey, hey! We discussed this.
Now is not the time to
mess with the plan.
Fine.
Ha-ha!
(MUFFLED) Hey, brother!
What? I told you, you are
supposed to stay with the boat!
Oh, I didn't think you
meant that literally.
What other way could
I have meant it?
(SIGHS) All right. Let's
move. Just follow my lead.
Got it. (GRUNTS)
Whoa!
(GRUNTING) Help me!
Ow, ow, ow!
Oh, no! The poison spikes!
I'm gonna be impaled!
(SCREAMS)
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY) I'm okay.
(SIGHS) I miss the minions.
Come on!
(GROANING)
(GASPS)
Coming.
(GRUNTING)
(DRU PANTING)
Coming.
(STRAINING) Come on.
(SCREAMS)
(GASPING)
It's a scanning device.
(SCANNER TRILLING)
Quick! Camouflage mode.
(PANTING) Freeze! And
close your eyes!
And cover your mouth!
(DRU SQUEALS)
(SIGHS)
Okay, take my hand.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
Ha-ha! Follow me.
(CHUCKLES)
(YELPS)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
GRU: Ha-ha!
(DRU CONTINUES SCREAMING)
DRU: Look out! (YELLS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Oh, you were right. I should
have stayed in the boat.
My stomach feels all queasy.
I shouldn't have
eaten that pot pie.
(GROANS)
Hey, hey, relax. You're
gonna be just fine.
I got your back.
Come on. This way.
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(GUARD SIGHS)
(MINIONS GRUNTING)
Huh?
Hmm?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(GRUNTING)
(MUFFLED SPEECH)
(CHUCKLES)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(MINION YELLING)
GRU: Looks like it's
right above us.
DRU: Okay, what do I do?
Should I wait in the vent?
GRU: No, come with me.
(DRU STRAINING)
(SIGHS)
(GASPS)
(MUMBLES) Dru,
get off the bed!
Yes, I'd like to
thank the Academy...
I can help. No, no, no.
What? I can do it.
Don't! Don't! Don't!
Why, yes.
Yes, Molly Ringwald, I will take
you to the prom. (MUSIC PLAYING)
What? Who? Where? What?
Who's there? Who is there?
(MUSIC PLAYING OVER
SPEAKERS) (ALARM BEEPING)
(SINGING) 99 of red balloons.
Whoops! Almost forgot!
(SIGHS)
GRU: (SHUSHES) Over here.
Stay close.
(GRU GASPS)
What?
Dolls.
Looks like Bratt
was the only one
stupid enough to
buy this junk.
Oh, I used to have
one of these!
(DRU IMITATES LASER FIRE)
(GROANING)
Ow! Hey! Shh! Come on.
All right. We're
getting close.
From now on, every
move must be made
with total precision
and purpose.
(GIGGLING)
Gum!
GRU: Focus!
We're after the diamond,
not the bubblegum.
Got it!
Mmm. Yum.
(WHISPERS) This way!
And now, to put this
where it belongs.
(BUBBLEGUM POPS)
What...
BALTHAZAR: Look at it,
Clive. It's beautiful!
(DRU GRUNTING)
Will you please shut up?
He's gonna spot us!
(GROANING)
(GASPS) Spit it out! Spit it out!
I told you not to touch anything!
(CHOKING)
(GRU GRUNTING)
Intruders! Intruders!
Intruders!
(BOTH GASP) Freeze, dipsticks!
Gru? There's two of you now?
Then this will be twice
as much fun. (LAUGHS)
DRU: Gru.
(SCREAMS)
(LAUGHING) (GASPS)
Give me back my diamond!
Total lockdown!
(ALARM BLARING)
Oh! Go get 'em, Bratt Pack!
(DOLLS CHATTERING)
(DRU YELLING)
They're gonna get us!
(BOTH YELLING) Run!
(GRU YELLS)
(WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Oh, no!
What does that mean?
(DEVICE BEEPING)
Are we gonna die?
We're gonna die!
(SCREAMS) Dru!
(DRU SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING) What?
Hey, guys. Hold on!
Lucy!
(DRU SCREAMING)
(DRU GASPING)
Thank you for saving us. Whoo!
Look! We got the diamond
and we're going to...
Take it to the AVL and
get our jobs back.
(CHUCKLES) Wait!
What? Oh, that's amazing!
And the best part
is, you'll never...
(GROANS) ...ever go
behind my back...
(LAUGHS, GROANING) ...ever
again, right, honey bear?
Yeah! Yeah, right. (SIGHS)
Lesson learned.
I'll get the girls
and start packing.
And tell them the good news!
(SINGSONG) Ah! We're getting
our jobs back. Yeah!
Yes! Yes! Go tell the girls.
Dru...
No! No way! We can't
give the diamond back!
I have to.
No, you don't! Yes, I do.
Give it! (STRAINS) No!
Give it! (GRUNTS) Ow!
What is wrong with you?
You kicked me!
You... You lied to me!
Hey, I would have
told you the truth.
But you're too much of
a wimp to handle it.
That's it. I'm out of here.
You have no right to take
that. We stole it together.
Together? (LAUGHS)
You got to be kidding me.
You did nothing but screw
up the whole time.
I got this in spite of you.
Oh, yeah? At least I didn't
get fired from my job
like a total loser.
At least I had a job.
What have you accomplished
that was so great?
I'll tell you what. Nothing!
No wonder Dad thought you
were such a failure.
(GASPS)
We are no longer brothers.
That's fine with me.
(EXCLAIMS IN FRUSTRATION)
(SINGING IN MINIONESE)
(ALL SINGING IN MINIONESE)
(ALL SINGING UPBEAT
TUNE IN MINIONESE)
(MINIONS LAUGHING)
(GROWLING) (AGNES LAUGHING)
Gru! I found a unicorn!
(SCATTING)
My life is complete!
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
Honey, that's...
That's not actually a unicorn.
Huh?
But, but, he has
one horn. (SNIFFS)
I'm... I'm sorry, sweetie...
but he's just a
goat. (GOAT BLEATS)
Life is just like
that sometimes.
We're hoping for a unicorn,
and we get a goat.
(GOAT BLEATS)
Well, you know what?
Lucky is the best goat
in the whole wide world!
Look at that face! I
just want to squeeze it.
AGNES: Mmm!
Whoo-hoo! (SCATTING) Whoo!
I'll take this.
You've been a bad boy, Gru.
Can you get the rest
of the suitcases?
Come on, girls. Let's go!
(SINGING) Let's get
physical, physical
(CONTINUES SINGING
INDISTINCTLY)
Change of plans, girls.
(STRAINING) Instead
of going home...
Eyebrows! Ow! (GRUNTS)
We're going to Hollywood!
(LAUGHING) (ALL GASP)
Now, that's what
I call acting.
(CHUCKLING) Let's go, Clive!
We've got a giant robot waiting!
(CLIVE LAUGHS)
(BANGING)
Huh? (BANGING CONTINUES)
(GASPS) Lucy?
(MUFFLED YELLING) But...
Bratt! He took the girls!
What? No!
Dru! Dru!
Go away! I don't
wanna talk to you.
Bratt has the girls!
(GASPS)
Listen, brother. (SIGHS)
About what I said...
No, I'm the one...
But I shouldn't have...
I'm... I'm sorry.
(SIGHS)
I'm so sorry, Gru.
Aw!
Ooh, look out!
GRU: What is that?
(SNORING) (GASPS)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(ALL YELLING)
Mel?
(GASPS) Gru?
(SPEAKING MINIONESE
AND STRAINING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(PEOPLE CHATTING INDISTINCTLY)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(BALTHAZAR LAUGHING)
(CONTINUES LAUGHING)
Hello, Hollywood!
(ON SPEAKER) I'm back
and bigger than ever.
(AGNES SCREAMING)
I'm scared!
Thank you. Thank you so... Oh!
(ALL SCREAMING)
CELEBRITY: No! No!
No, you can't leave me here!
I'm famous!
(LAUGHS) Clive,
arm the canons.
Chew on this!
(SCREAMING)
(BALTHAZAR LAUGHING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(WHIMPERS AND SCREAMS)
(SCREAMS)
Hey, mullet head! Let us out!
Oh, don't worry, girls. I've
prepared a front row seat for you.
(ALL GASPING AND SCREAMING)
(ALL CONTINUE SCREAMING)
(AGNES SCREAMS) MARGO: Agnes!
BALTHAZAR: Once again,
I win and Gru loses!
Enjoy the show, girls.
(ALL GASP)
What in the heck? Oh!
I hope the girls are okay.
Bratt! Bratt at nine
o'clock... No! Three o'clock!
He's on the left!
(GASPS) No! I've
seen this episode!
He's going to bubblegum the whole
city and send it up into space!
(GASPS) Hurry! (DRU GASPS)
This is it! This is it!
Lights! Camera!
Laser!
(ALL SCREAMING)
Yeah!
(HIGH-PITCHED SCREAMING)
LUCY: (GASPS) Look!
I've got the girls. You
two, go take care of Bratt.
GRU: Wait! What are you doing?
(GRUNTING)
Look, you guys, it's Lucy!
Lucy, over here!
Help! Help us!
Mama's comin', girls.
EDITH: Lucy! Lucy!
MARGO: We're up here!
BALTHAZAR: Look
at that laser go.
I love it when a
plan comes together.
CLIVE: (SCREAMS) It's
Gru! (ALARM BEEPING)
(GRU LAUGHS)
Get ready, Bratt.
You're about to be blasted
back to the '80s!
(GRU LAUGHS) DRU: Whoo-hoo!
(LAUGHS) We got him!
(MACHINE CREAKING)
(BALTHAZAR YELLING)
Oh, no! Don't worry.
There's more where
that came from.
It'll take more than
that to stop me.
Bratt Pack, go get that
barf bag. (CLIVE LAUGHS)
(DOLLS CHATTERING)
Oh, incoming!
(GRUNTING IN PAIN)
You little...
(GRUNTING) Get away!
Get out of there!
Quick, jump!
(BOTH YELL)
Bonus!
Did you see that, Clive?
All gone. (CLIVE BEEPS)
Buh-bye, Wonder Twins.
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS AND GROANS)
(STRAINING AND GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
(GASPING AND
SPEAKING MINIONESE)
AGNES: Help! (ALL SCREAM)
Hang on!
(GRUNTING)
(GIRLS SCREAMING)
Hang on, girls! I've got you!
I can't! I'm slipping!
(STRAINING)
(ALL SCREAMING) No!
(ALL SCREAMING) Got ya!
Thank you, Lucy!
Let's go! We're not safe yet.
Minions! (SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(ALL CHEERING)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(ALL YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(DEVICE BEEPS)
BALTHAZAR: (CHUCKLES) Look
at what we have here.
Sorry, Gru. This is going to
be a total burn! (LAUGHS)
Oh, no! No, no, no!
I've been a bad boy!
(LAUGHING)
(GRUNTING)
Nobody messes with my brother!
(SCREAMS)
(SCREAMS) (GLASS SHATTERS)
(ROBOT POWERING DOWN)
What? What's happening? No!
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(STRAINING)
Dru!
Hold on! I'm coming.
(GASPS)
(PANTING)
You've ruined everything!
And now, it's time to die.
Any last words, Gru?
You know what?
I got two words for you.
Dance fight.
Oh, it is on like Donkey Kong.
I am going to enjoy this.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(LAUGHING) (BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(LAUGHS)
(GASPS) Enough!
(GRUNTS) My turn!
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
(LAUGHS)
Uh-oh.
(GRUNTS) (MUSIC STOPS)
(GROANS AND GASPS)
Game over! (LAUGHING)
Is this what you're
looking for?
No!
(PLAYING MUSIC)
(BALTHAZAR GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
(GROANING)
No!
Curse you, Gru! (GROANS)
Curse you!
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(LAUGHS)
Dru? Dru?
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHING) (GASPS)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Hey! We did it!
Yes, we did, brother.
LUCY: Gru! EDITH: Uncle Dru!
MARGO: Gru! Girls!
(ALL LAUGHING)
(BUBBLEGUM POPS) (ALL GASP)
(MINIONS CLAMORING)
(MINION SCREAMS)
(MINIONS SCREAMING)
Gru!
Hey, Mel. Welcome back.
(MINIONS CHEERING)
(SLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
Mmm.
Love you, Mom.
I'm a mom. (GASPS)
I'm a mom! (LAUGHS SOFTLY)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
(ALL CHATTERING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
(LAUGHS) (SPITS)
(SPEAKING MINIONESE)
Boys, time for bed!
We're back at work
in the morning.
(ALL YELLING) I'm
coming, sweetie.
Good night, Lucy.
See you tomorrow, brother.
Hey, I'm back on the job.
So no villainy
tonight, huh? Got it?
I make no promises. Love you!
Uh-huh. Right.
(MUMBLES) I love you, too.
ALL: Aw!
"Aw!" All right, every...
Go! Go! Go to bed!
(DOOR CLOSES)
(WHISPERS) Hey! Guys! Come on!
(ALL LAUGHING)
GRU: What... What
is happening?
LUCY: It's coming
from outside!
(LUCY GASPS)
Hey! I thought we said
no more villainy!
Sorry, brother!
Somebody's gotta keep the
family tradition alive, right?
(ALL CHEERING)
(LAUGHS)
Let's get him. Ugh.
Honey, he's my brother.
We'll give him a
five-minute head start.
(LAUGHING EVILLY)
(LAUGHING)