It's coming! Run!
Father!
Run!
Good fight.
You, too.
Do not fear.
Quickly, inside the gate!
The wonders of the world await you.
Follow Gilgamesh and Enkidu into battle.
Be forever inspired
by their bravery and strength.
You and your fellow man...
...will go on great adventures.
And become legends of your own!
I needed to get enough artifacts
to make a good trade.
Just lie to her.
I can sense vibrations.
Even the tiniest movement.
Including your voices when you speak.
Did you two just waste my time?
The Emerald Tablet you're searching for...
...is a myth!
When humans have conflict,
Ajak tells us not to interfere.
If you don't tell,
I won't tell.
See you.
Let me help you.
You are very kind.
I am very beautiful.
May the gods hereby
bond you in matrimony.
Congratulations.
We had to split up.
Stay strong.
But she won't be Thena
anymore.
Welcome.
Legend of Ikaris
The world is ending.
You need to go home.
Good afternoon.
Hey. We're looking for Druig.
Is he here?
...Yes.
How do you know Druig?
We're friends...
...from college.
Miss?
You're ok?
What's happening?
Quit procrastinating, Phil, and take
care of your business.
Ready to go home?
So you mean...
I've been waiting for centuries
to go back to Olympia,
and now you're telling me...
...it doesn't exist?
And the world is ending.
At last my boredom is ending.
Have you seen my movies?
I don't have a DVD player.
Miss me?
Are you two...
Get ready for it.
So suppose Druig can, say...
put Tiamut to sleep--
Then what?
I found Tiamut.
Why did Sprite go with Ikaris?
We need you.
Thank you for all you've done...
...for humanity.
It's been a great honor.
I will miss you all.
You've never been able to do it before.
By being connected to the Celestial
as it emerged.
We became one...
...even Ikaris and Sprite
all because of Tiamut.
The kid is ten...
...not stupid!
When are you guys leaving?
...because the truth will
set them free.
It's been weeks.
We haven't heard from any of them.
It's like...
they've disappeared.
I feel it, too.
Thanos' brother?
Death is my reward.