I've got a bad
feeling about this.
What kind of bad feeling?
Like, "We're going to need a new
planet" kind of bad feeling.
RADIO OFFICER: Medical
casualty, C-53. Two men down.
They're still on the ship.
Lock down the ship!
Is everyone all right?
OFFICER 1: All good, Chief.
Is everyone accounted for?
OFFICER 2: (ON RADIO) Just
heard something on Level Four.
Raikes, up.
(SCREAMS)
Hey! Move, move!
HOPPER: What do you see?
Did you see it?
No, sir.
I got nothing, sir!
Nothing.
How is he?
Not good, sir. Not good.
You two, get him
to medical, now!
Raikes, you're with me.
Let's go!
(FAINT HYDRAULIC HISSING)
(LOUD BANG)
Get out of here!
No!
(YELLS)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
Yo! Hey!
(GROANING)
HOPPER: Raikes...
Get your ass to CIC.
Now!
Come on.
(GRUNTING)
Raikes, you better be there.
Come on, come on, come on.
Mahalo, mother...
We got to get
off this mountain.
The cop left the keys
on his belt.
You've got to go
down and get them.
You can do it.
(SNORTS)
(HYDRAULIC HISSING)
(WHIMPERING)
Now.
(STATIC CRACKLING)
This is an emergency call.
Can anyone hear me?
Radio check.
Can anyone hear me? Over.
Hey, wait up!
Don't leave! Don't leave!
Stop right there!
Don't shoot!
Who are you?
I'm Cal Zapata.
We sent out a beacon.
Oh, shit, is he a cyborg?
Are you guys with them?
If he's human, could you
have him put the gun down?
SAM: Mick,
put your gun down.
I told them that something
like this could happen.
I said, it's going to be like
Columbus and the Indians,
or the Conquistadors
and the Incans.
They just thought,
"No, they will be sweet."
They killed my grad student.
(GASPING)
Okay, calm down.
I can't.
Slow. Sit down.
I can't breathe.
SAM: Slow breaths,
slow breaths.
You're freaking
him out, Mick.
I doubt it takes
much to freak him out.
We need the Marines. We need the Army.
We need all of them.
NOGRADY: It is the strong
belief of the Chinese
that what crashed
into Hong Kong
was some sort of
communications ship.
You're saying that
a flying telephone cratered
and took out 25,000 people?
What I'm saying is that our visitors
seem extraordinarily concerned
with establishing a line
of communication home.
If they have lost their communication
ship, how could they do that?
The same way we did.
Our communications station
in Hawaii has the ability
to send a message to deep space
via the Landsat 7 satellite.
I believe it's for that asset
they have domed the islands.
We're looking at
an extinction-level event.
The most critical part
of any military operation.
Establish communications,
reinforcements, follow-on forces.
You're saying E.T.
wants to phone home?
That would be incredibly,
incredibly bad.
So far, only five ships
have made contact.
If five ships can do this,
what do you think 50 can do,
or 500 or 5,000 or 500,000?
JIMMY: Sir, if I could
just have a minute.
If you'll just
give me one second...
Why am I staring
at a lizard?
Because this is my pet lizard, sir.
Penelope the Third.
And? And they have
the exact same eyes.
You have 15 seconds. Go.
Okay, sir,
I put the helmet on,
and the helmet is, basically,
extreme sunglasses.
And it's some hydration
and some oxygen saturation,
and a bunch of other stuff
I don't understand.
But we took Penelope to the beach one
time, which was a terrible idea.
She went absolutely crazy because
she can't handle the sunlight.
You see? I don't think that they
can handle the sunlight either.
You try anything else on?
Negative, sir.
Just the helmet.
Scientists have confirmed
there was a UFO landing
in the Pacific Ocean,
off the coast of Hawaii.
Today I want to update
the American people
on what we know about
the situation in Hawaii.
First, we are bringing all
available resources to bear.
(ALARM WAILING)
(SPEAKING JAPANESE)
NEWSCASTER: The news has sparked
global unrest as populations panic,
unleashing an unprecedented
wave of chaos across the world.
Many governments have
declared martial law.
MAN: Just scramble
the jets, Admiral.
We need to get in there!
I'm far from more aware than you
of the need to get inside there.
But wasting lives
will not help.
You want me to
send up another plane?
I'll do it the second
you come up here
and put your ass in
the co-pilot's seat, sir!
Are they transmitting?
They could be, but it
wouldn't do them any good.
There's no satellite
to receive the transmission.
We beam to Landsat 7.
What's Landsat 7?
It's our deep-space satellite.
It only orbits into range
once every 24 hours.
When is the satellite
in position?
8:43 a.m.
We've got about five hours.
And then they will use it to
slingshot their transmission.
Slingshot where?
I don't know.
Wherever it is they're from.
HOPPER: Pearl Harbor here,
we're approximately here,
and they, whatever they are,
are somewhere in the middle.
We're trapped out here.
What we know right now
is we can't target them
unless we have
a plain line of sight.
Without radar, we have no
way to track them, correct?
Correct. But I don't think
they can see us, either.
Why?
Because we are still alive.
Okay, so they can't see us
and we can't see them.
And we have no way to hit
them from a safe distance.
There is a way.
Away?
Away of seeing them,
without seeing them.
You're going to reference Art
of War right now, aren't you?
What are we supposed to do, fight
the enemy where they aren't?
Move like water?
Because I've read that thing six times.
It makes no sense.
That book is Chinese.
It still makes no sense.
My way is much more simple.
We've been doing it to
America for 20 years.
Water displacement.
How do you track
water displacement?
Tsunami buoys.
Tsunami buoys?
You have them
surrounding your islands,
transmitting
displacement data.
We hack into their
transmissions, form a grid.
You can't track
anything without radar.
I don't need radar.
Just the radio frequencies.
Turn off Aegis radar, please.
JIMMY: Who is this guy?
Chief Moore.
OFFICER: Sir.
Secure SPY.
OFFICER: Securing SPY, sir.
Display NOAA data.
NOAA data?
That's correct.
You heard him.
Display NOAA data.
(CLEARS THROAT)
CORA: What the hell is that?
HOPPER: It's a buoy.
If it gets hit by a wave,
it transmits a signal.
(BEEPING)
Bring up chart plot.
Chart plot. Bring it up.
So we can track
without radar.
We would practice it
as a contingency plan.
You dirty,
cheating, sneaky...
Rough world.
I like it.
Captain.
My chair is your chair, sir.
My brother would
have done the same.
I wish we could
get a hold of Hopper.
Who's Hopper?
He's a tactical
actions officer
on an Arleigh Burke
class destroyer.
It has the resources that could
take this entire mountain out.
Great, that makes a lot of sense.
Let's call him.
We can't.
Everything is jammed.
They're using an electromagnetic
field to block our signals.
It's more like a pulse, it's not a brick wall.
There are gaps, okay?
From inside the barrier, we might
just be able to get a call out.
If I could get to my spectrum
analyzer, then, theoretically,
we could find a frequency
we could broadcast on...
Do you have a piece of equipment
that can make a call?
Yeah.
Get it.
I can't because it's down there,
in that nest of aliens.
You're going to go get it.
No.
Yes.
SAM: Yes.
We are looking for patterns
of water displacement.
HOPPER: That buoy
is underwater.
That's a ship.
Get on your gun.
Yes, sir.
Target, Echo-1-1.
CORA: Roger. Echo 1-1.
Ready to fire.
When we fire,
they will know where we are.
Fire!
Ordy, anything?
JIMMY: Negative, sir.
It's a miss.
It's heading towards us.
You ready?
I'm sorry, but there is no possible
way that I'm going down there.
I do not possess
that kind of courage.
Right now, you're going
to acquire that courage,
or I'm going to break my
steel leg off into your ass.
You feel me?
I feel you.
Go, now.
Acquiring courage.
What?
Foxtrot, 2-4.
CORA: Foxtrot, 2-4.
Ready to fire.
Fire!
Ordy, anything?
JIMMY: Negative, sir.
It's a stupid,
nincompoop idea.
There's another one.
JIMMY: Incoming, incoming!
Sir, they're coming from both directions!
Engines, back, full.
Incoming, incoming, incoming!
India 3-7.
India 3-7. Loaded.
Second coordinate,
Romeo, 2-6.
Romeo 2-6.
Sir, we're hot over here.
Missiles good to go.
Let's light them up,
Captain Nagata.
Fire!
Holy shit!
A hit, sir! Hit!
(EXCLAIMING IN JAPANESE)
(ALL CHEERING)
MICK: Any station this net, any station
this net, this is a call for help.
Any warship, police or military
personnel, please respond, over.
This is U.S.S.
John Paul Jones,
state your identity
and position. Over.
Hopper?
Sam?
Sam, are you okay?
Where are you?
Thank God. I'm okay.
Listen, they're here at the satellite
array at Saddle Ridge, do you copy?
They're going to transmit a signal
and establish communication.
You need to destroy the facility.
We have four hours.
Four hours, I copy.
Hopper.
SAM: Can you hear me?
Babe, you need to
get out of there.
Hopper? Hopper?
No, they're gone.
They're gone.
MICK: We better
get gone, too.
I'm thinking an Arleigh
Burke class destroyer
is about to rain hell
down on this mountaintop.
Are you ready to
kill another one?
Tango 1-9.
Tango 1-9. Loaded.
Whiskey 2-5.
CORA: Whiskey 2-5.
Raikes, can you get
a track on their ship?
Negative, sir, it's
moving all over the place.
I can't get a line on it.
This sucker's
really jumping around.
Very intelligent.
What time is sunrise?
CORA: Forty minutes, sir.
Let's take these bastards
somewhere they don't want to go.
CORA: General quarters,
general quarters.
All hands, man
your battle stations.
I need to know when we round this
point if we can hold her tight.
Right around
Diamond Head, here.
WALTER: There's
a brutal current there.
It will take a miracle
to keep her off the reef.
Ordy, is it possible?
Can you do it?
It's not impossible.
Sir, I can try,
but I don't know what...
Can you do it,
yes or no?
Contact is seven miles out,
and closing fast.
Yes, sir, I can do it.
Check safe, check clear.
Get some.
Captain Nagata,
how good is your aim?
Excellent.
OFFICER: All right, let's start this turn!
JOOD: Aye, sir!
Left, hard rudder!
Left, hard rudder, sir!
How are we looking?
It's all reef.
Ordy, you are way
too close! Come left!
Easy...
We're about to kiss
these rocks, Ordy!
Ordy!
HOPPER: Where did you
learn to shoot?
I'm not sure how
you say it in English.
Natsu campu.
Summer campu.
How about now?
GUNNER: Still a little tight.
I can see fish, Ordy.
Come on, man.
CORA: Contact,
two miles out.
Contact ETA, 21 seconds.
Summer camp...
CORA: Contact,
700 yards out.
Summer camp.
Champion, when I was 12.
Are you kidding me?
Here we go.
On my mark.
Three.
Two.
One.
Light them up.
Boom.
(ALL CHEERING)
OFFICER: (ON RADIO) Three miles
until Saddle Ridge is within range.
Status of weps.
JOOD: Sir, they're bringing up all the
rounds from the lower mag right now.
JIMMY: Sir.
Clear the bridge.
Clear the bridge!
Shit!
(GRUNTING)
Ordy, get up! Let's go!
Go, go, go!
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
SAILOR 1: We've got
two down, sir!
Get up.
SAILOR 2: Go, go, go!
Get in the water! Go!
It's going down!
Come on.
(ALL CLAMORING)
(GASPS)
Raikes!
Right here!
You're almost there, come on!
Let's go,
we have to jump!
(BOTH SCREAMING)
SAM: That's the
John Paul Jones.
That's Hopper.
Relax, Sam. I'm seeing a lot
of lifeboats in the water.
You say that satellite will be
in position in three hours?
Yeah, that's correct.
So if they miss it,
they have to wait.
My uplink never misses.
It's not going to miss.
How are your driving skills?
What does that mean?
How are my driving skills? They're horrible.
Not your driving.
Sam, how are your
driving skills?
Good.
Let's see if we can't buy
the world another day.
Who talks like that?
MICK: Just get in the vehicle.
Let's go.
I'm not getting in.
This is your show, now.
I don't have a death wish,
thank you very much.
Goodbye, everyone.
Stop! Stop.
This is my property.
It doesn't end like this.
What do you want
us to do, Hopper?
We have no ships left.
We have one.
We have got a battleship.
Are you crazy?
That's a museum.
Not today.
This ship is 70 years old.
It's totally outdated.
The firing systems
are all analog.
The engines haven't been
started in a decade.
Which would be fine,
but they are steam,
which I have no idea
how to fire up.
And even if I had
a user's manual
and six weeks to
go through it all,
we still don't have
enough crew to fire it up.
I don't know what
you're thinking, sir.
Is everyone all right?
Yes, sir. We're okay.
You men have given so much
to your country,
and no one has the right
to ask any more of you,
but I'm asking.
What do you need, son?
I need to borrow your boat.
Son.
Sir.
What the hell? Are you going
to stand there, staring at me?
Get your goddamn eye
on that spotter!
Eye on spotter, sir.
Been working on a
destroyer, haven't you?
Yes, sir.
Are you ready to play
with the big boys?
Oh, yes, sir.
Come on.
We need the help.
Awesome!
Best cover your ears.
(STEAM HISSING)
(POWERING UP)
Purrs like a kitten.
Bridge, main control.
I got eight boilers hot.
Ready to rock and roll, sir.
How are we looking on fuel?
600 long tons, sir.
Just enough for a maintenance run.
Ordnance?
We scraped together what we could, sir.
But it's not much.
All right, let's get her to sea.
We have got work to do.
Roger that.
Engines ahead, flank.
All engines ahead, flank.
Aye, sir.
You good?
VETERAN: Good, sir.
Good, sir.
Good.
Status of turret one?
Center line, barrel, armed.
GUNNER: Stop!
WALTER: Clear!
GUNNER: Loaded.
VETERAN: Status of turret two?
Starboard side, armed.
VETERAN: Status
of turret three?
Port barrel.
Ready to rock and roll.
Port side, armed!
Sir, are we really
firing on Oahu?
Sure looks that way.
Holy shit!
CORA: Saddle Ridge will be in
weapons range in five minutes.
Oh, brother, somebody is
going to kiss the donkey.
Hopper!
I didn't think
that one moved.
Me neither.
My God.
Are you kidding me?
Art of War.
HOPPER: Fire control,
weapons status?
Aimed at target.
Train all three
turrets to 2-1-0.
CORA: But, sir,
that's the wrong direction!
I'm well aware
of that, Raikes.
What the hell is he doing?
He's losing his mind,
all over again.
Hard left rudder.
Hard left rudder. Aye, sir.
Drop port anchor.
What?
Drop it now!
We are going to die.
You are going to die.
I am going to die.
We are all going to die.
Just not today.
Let's drop some
lead on those mother...
Fire!
Reload! Reload!
Firing mechanism reset!
Secure the hatch.
Port side ready!
Release the anchor.
Incoming! Incoming!
(SCREAMING)
You all right?
They ain't going to sink
this battleship, no way.
Hit it!
Everything you've got!
Whoo!
(SNARLS)
I want every available plane
on this ship in the air, now!
I can't believe
that worked!
Yeah, Art of War.
Fight the enemy where they aren't.
After all these years,
that finally just clicked.
But that's not
what it means.
Really?
Not even close.
MICK: Keep going!
Oh, shit!
Mick, my leg is stuck.
Mick!
HOPPER: Status of weapons?
VETERAN: Turret three is down.
We got one round of high-explosive
back-aft in turret three.
Tell them to have it
ready when we get there.
I got this.
Beast, update.
I need that round.
We need to bring it to turret two.
Sir?
Turret two is 500 feet away.
This round is over
a thousand pounds!
How do you expect
us to get it there?
(ALL GRUNTING)
(GROWLING)
Raikes! Get to the gun plot,
finger on the trigger.
Yes, sir.
Come on, easy. Easy.
GUNNER: Gentle, boys.
Gentle, gentle.
Get out of here!
We got to go.
Calm down, okay?
I'm going to frigging save you.
Closed, number one is armed.
Coordinates?
Train, 3-3-0.
Elevation?
2-2-0.
There! Go!
Let's go!
She's armed.
You better not be up there.
Let's go! Come on!
Hopper!
We only have one
round left, right?
Yeah.
It was an honor serving
with you, Captain.
The honor was mine.
Fire.
Locked on target.
(ALL CHEERING)
SHANE: We take great
pride in honoring
the many men and women who
demonstrated exceptional gallantry
in the face of
overwhelming enemy force.
Valor and courage
were exhibited by so many
that I cannot honor them all.
It is my great
privilege to recognize
those few whose actions
deserve special note.
Lieutenant Colonel, United States
Army, retired, Mick Canales.
(CROWD CHEERING)
The President of the United
States takes great pleasure
in presenting the Navy Cross
to Commander Stone Hopper
for extraordinary heroism.
Receiving this award,
on behalf of his brother,
Lieutenant
Commander Alex Hopper.
Stand fast, Mr. Hopper.
It is my great pleasure to
present you with a Silver Star
for your exceptional heroism and
gallantry in combat operations.
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
And I look forward
to seeing you at sea
on a ship of your
own command, soon.
Thank you.
(ALL WHOOPING)
(INDISTINCT)
Ordy, stop talking
for a second.
Come on, take
the picture, Beast.
Say "Navy."
Navy!
(LAUGHS)
Mildly impressive, Hopper.
You ready to get your ass
off that big gray monster,
get out to Coronado and get your
hands dirty with the big boys?
Yes, sir.
You think you've got what it takes?
I hope so, sir.
Call me, Hopper.
It just might be too
much sleep, though, sir.
A little too much sleep for you?
Yes, sir.
We will have to
see about that.
Come on, Hopper,
cozy up to Nagata.
You look so cute.
You guys make a great couple.
Are we dating now?
You look dapper.
"Navy." Say, "Navy."
Yeah, I don't know.
Oh!
Bad timing.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
How are you?
Good, how are you?
I love you.
I'm a pretty lucky guy,
you know that?
Which is why I think it's a perfect
time for you to talk to my dad.
Where is he?
I wish he was standing right here.
That's perfect,
because look!
Your wish came true,
honey. Go get him.
Thumbs up, that helps.
(SIGHS)
Sir.
(CLEARS THROAT)
What is it?
I want you to know
that I am in love with Sam.
And I am asking your permission
to marry your daughter.
No.
Thank you, sir.
I mean, it's...
What?
No.
Sir...
I saved the world.
Saving the world is one thing, Hopper.
My daughter is quite another.
But...
No means no, Hopper.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm late for lunch.
I think I will have
a chicken burrito.
Chicken...
Sir.
Come along, Hopper.
We will discuss the terms
of your surrender over a meal.
Yes, sir.
She told you about that?
You got nothing on Jay-Z.
I mean, even I
couldn't get Beyonce.
I couldn't get
Beyonce either.
No way.
Whoa.
What the...
THOM: What is that?
Don't get too close to it.
Whoa, guys! Look at this!
ANGUS: Don't go too close!
THOM: Don't run to it.
Do you think that looks like a door?
ANGUS: A door?
Hello?
Anyone home?
ANGUS: That's not
going to help, is it?
This really helps.
(HORN HONKING)
THOM: Do you know
what that is?
RONNIE: We think there's
something inside of it.
THOM: Are going
to open it, Jimmy?
If Jimmy says he's getting
in, he's getting in!
Come on, Jimmy!
Whoo!
Jimmy!
That's it. Come to daddy.
(MUFFLED CHEERS)
ANGUS: Jimmy! Oh, my God!
Yes!