Marshmallows remind me
of going camping with my daddy.
I could eat them all night long.
Of course he did make me cough them
back up again for breakfast.
This one time,
I coughed up an entire Dalmatian.
That ain't nothing.
I coughed up a whole tribe of pygmies.
They started looking at me weird.
I remember them.
They was quite friendly.
I found a human spinal column
in my fecal matter once.
You might want to get that looked at.
Pass the beans, Beans.
- Sheriff?
- No, thanks.
Mr Rango? Can you tell us
about the Spirit of the West?
- Yeah, tell us about that.
- Is it true what they say?
Yes, the Spirit of the West!
The eternally unattainable ideal.
They say he rides in
an alabaster carriage
with golden guardians to protect him.
But he only appears to those
who have undertaken an epic quest!
And have made it
to the other side.
The other side of what?
It's a metaphor.
My eye!
That's gonna heal right up.
Sheriff? What are you going to do
about Rattlesnake Jake?
What? Where?
Sorry about that. Word is
you come against him once or twice.
Yeah.
Jake. You mean my brother.
- Your brother?
- That's what I said!
But he's a snake and you're a lizard.
Well, Momma had an active social life.
Did he ever bite you?
Sure enough did. Look at that baby.
Go ahead, you can touch it.
That's interesting.
That there's a belly button.
Luckily, I'm immune to his venom.
Put some in my coffee
just to give it a little tang.
Is it true he's only scared
of them hawks?
Them's what we call
his natural predator.
All this talk of that serpentine devil
is putting my quills on edge!
I ain't sleeping tonight. No, sir.
Don't you all worry about a thing.
Come tomorrow, we'll locate that water
and return to a hero's welcome.
Friends, before we bunk down
I'd like us all to join hands
for a moment,
say a few words
to the Spirit of the West.
That's a good idea.
Ain't always spoken rightly to you,
Spirit of the West.
But tonight I want to thank you for
bringing Sheriff Rango into our lives.
It's a hard life we got.
Sometimes I don't know how
we're gonna make it.
But somehow, Sheriff Rango
makes me think we will.
We needed a brave man
and you sent us one.
Nice to have someone
to believe in again.
Thank you, Spirit of the West. Amen.
- Amen.
Just checking.
- It's a little cold tonight.
- Thank you.
You ever feel like those things
are looking at you?
That's a Spanish dagger.
But around here,
we just call them the Walking Cactus.
Walking?
There's an old legend they actually
walk across the desert to find water.
When I was a little girl, I'd stay up late
watching them, to see if they'd move.
I thought if I could follow them,
they'd lead me to someplace wonderful.
Someplace with enough water
for everyone.
Night after night, I watched them.
I never saw them move.
But you're still watching.
Who doesn't want to find
someplace wonderful?
We'll find the water, Beans.
I promise you.
That's such a lonely sound.
You ever get lonely?
Sometimes.
I can't imagine it. You're such a charmer
and everyone likes you so much.
- I never made friends easy like that.
- No?
No, we're pretty isolated
out there on the ranch,
sort of like being sealed up
in a little box.
Don't really see a lot of folks.
I wouldn't know what that's like.
There someone special
in your life, Rango?
There used to be.
But she couldn't keep her head.
Besides, my life's too dangerous
for that kind of thing.
You know, it's an awful solitary
existence out there on the prairie.
Riding the ranges and the suchlike.
Beans?
I'm gonna skin you alive, boy! I'm gonna
whup you like a red-headed stepchild!
Choleric varmints, ain't they?
Dysfunctional family. Need intervention.
What's that coming?
It's the water.
I have a plan, and each and every one
of you has a part to play.
What do I do?
Spoons, you got
the most important job of all.
You stay up here on the ridge,
and if anything goes wrong,
you give the signal.
Hey, Beans.
What size dress you wearing?
- He got it!
- Hallelujah!
- He found the water!
- You did it, son.
Well, actually...
Why can't you be all brainy
like your brother?
Pappy, about that water.
There's something I gots to tell you.
Hush up, now. Somebody's coming.
Good sirs, gracious good afternoon
to thee and thee and thee.
May I present Madame Lupone's
Terpsichorean Troupe
of Travelling Thespians!
- What is that?
- I think they's thespians.
Thespians?
That's illegal in seven states!
The stage is set. The princess
prepares to take her own life.
I yearn for love.
Meanwhile, the lone sentry
stands watch at the castle gate.
Stands watch at the castle gate...
Hark! Who goes there?
This plot is highly predictable.
Quiet! This is my favourite part.
Arriving to great fanfare
'twas her aged father,
strucketh by Cupid.
Prithee, unhand my fair daughter
and reach for the...
- Line?
- "Reach for the sky!"
What was that?
Must be that immersive theatre.
We got you surrounded!
You and your entire family get
your hands up where I can see them.
My entire family?
Grits and spit and collard greens
Waffle chitlins, monkey brains
Refried bones and booger blood
Pickled eggs and flaps of mud
It's a full house.
Looks like we're gonna have ourselves
a good old-fashioned standoff.
I'll have you know, you're not looking
at our entire contingent.
What's that supposed to be?
That's the signal.
That's the signal!
Something must have gone wrong!
So something's supposed to happen?
I am open to suggestions.
Run!
Get on the wagon!
Should we have ourselves
some sport, chill'ens?
I likes it when they run.
Maybelle, give the holler!
Looks like we made it!
That audience was quite responsive.
Yeah, well, I think that
chromosome pool is about dried up.
We got bats!
Here! You drive.
Looks like there's gonna be
soup tonight!
Come on, let's get some!
What in tarnation?
Don't shoot the water!
Jedidiah! It's time for
the Alabama squeeze box!
Okay, Pa!
I am sensing hostility.
Incoming!
Hello!
Goodbye!
Lasso that swine!
I suggest we take evasive action!
I suggest you shut up and shoot!
- What happened to the Sheriff?
- He had a previous engagement!
Boseefus, give them some gumbo now!
What was that? Go check it out!
What is it? Is there a problem?
You could call it that.
Headache.
Is that all you got?
That wasn't altogether unpleasant!
Eat lead!
Here, hold these.
Get your hands off me!
Oh, I'm sorry.
Jump!
It's impossible.
It can't be. It's empty.
There's no water!
No water?
Then what the hell we been fighting for?
Sir, you have defiled and desecrated
the very sustenance of our livelihood!
I think that there fella in the purty dress
is the Sheriff.
That's the same fellow what give us
a prospecting permit?
- A what?
- Irrelevant! Obfuscation.
You and your kin are under arrest
for bank robbery
and the murder
of our beloved financial advisor
Johannes Merrimack the Third,
AKA, Fluffy Joe.
Sheriff, we didn't kill nobody.
We done tunnelled into that vault,
but there weren't nothing in it.
Somebody done robbed that bank
before we robbed it.
Then where'd you get this here jug?
That's what I been trying
to tell you, Pappy.
I found it in the desert.
Then why in tarnation
did you bring it here?
Hold on! You're saying this here jug
was empty when you found it?
That's right.
I don't believe a word of it.
- Let's hang them, Sheriff!
- String them up!
Who'd dump water in the desert?
Wouldn't be the first time.
It's a puzzle!
It's like a big old mammogram!
What's going on, Sheriff?
I don't know.
But I'm going to strip away this mystery
and expose its private parts.
You and your kin are coming with me.
They're coming!
Here they come!
Looks like they got them robbers.
Where's the water?
There weren't no water.
Where is he going?
He's going to see the Mayor.
He's got to be pleased with that.
That's a good one, boss!
That's interesting.
I do apologise for the shoes, Mr Rango,
but there's a certain protocol
to this game, you understand.
I'm a bit of a stickler for protocol.
Well, that's good, 'cause you got
a few questions to answer
and I've got my own protocol.
But why would anyone dump water
in the blooming desert?
It does seem a bit naïve, taking the word
of admitted bank robbers.
Besides, once they hang,
your job is done.
- Bravo!
- Job well done.
But what if somebody did rob the bank
before they got there?
And who would do that, Mr Rango?
I was hoping you could tell me.
That sounds marginally
near to an accusation.
Take it any way you like.
Something you said keeps rattling
around in my frontal lobe.
What's that?
"Control the water
and you control everything."
Come now, Mr Rango.
You attribute divine power to me.
How on earth
could I possibly control the water?
You've obviously mastered this game.
Well, I've been playing it
for many years, sir.
I was here before the highway split
this great valley.
I watched the march of progress,
and I learned a thing or two.
Perhaps it's time you started
to take the long view,
begin to appreciate
the broad sweep of history.
Look out there, son.
You can almost see time passing.
What are you building out here?
The future, Mr Rango, the future.
One day soon,
all this is going to fade into myth,
the frontier town, the lawman,
the gunslinger.
There's just no place
for them any more.
- We're civilised now.
- That's right, civilised.
That's what the future holds.
You can either be part of it,
or you can be left behind.
Is that what happened to
Mr Merrimack? Did he get left behind?
Careful, Mr Rango. You seem to forget
you're just one little lizard.
You seem to forget
I'm the law around these parts.
Our new sheriff has been
playing the hero for so long,
he's actually starting to believe it.
Call in Rattlesnake Jake.
But Jake's the Grim Reaper.
He never leaves
without taking a blooming soul.
Do it!
Now be still. You gotta look
presentable to meet your maker.
Death has arrived
How will the hero survive?
The Mayor has bought up
all the land in the valley,
except for your ranch, Miss Beans.
That just don't make no sense.
Without water, that land is useless.
Unless he controls the water.
Like a monkey's bladder!
Then he could bring it back
once he's bought up all the land.
But how does he control the water?
Well, you gotta spend some time
and train them.
'Cause you know monkeys, when
they do go, you rub their nose in it.
Sheriff, we got a problem.
Hold on, Beans.
That won't be necessary.
- Hang him till his head turns blue!
- Give us them robbers!
Hold on! Calm down, everyone!
Let me talk!
- Nail them to the courthouse!
- Now, calm down, everybody.
Get them out here
so we can cut off their giblets!
You, too, Spoons?
They done taken that water.
They taken everything we got!
No one's stringing anyone up.
Not while I'm sheriff.
But this is all his fault!
You said you's gonna
bring the water back.
It's just, we got no hope
without that water.
We got nothing left to believe in.
You see that sign up there?
As long as that sign says "Sheriff,"
you can believe that there's
law and order in this town.
But without law and order,
ruminate on that. Oh, yeah.
Starts out slow, like a fungus.
Somebody says a cross word.
Accusations start flying.
Neighbour turns on neighbour.
Pretty soon, we're eating our children!
And then dogs and cats
are getting together
to create all sorts of unnatural
mutant aberrations!
So, you want something
to believe in, Spoons?
Believe in me.
Believe in that there sign.
For as long as it hangs there,
we got hope.
Hello, brother.
Thirsty?
Long time, brother.
How you been keeping?
Well, you know...
I hear you been telling about how
you killed all them Jenkins brothers.
With one bullet, wasn't it?
Isn't that right?
All these good folks here
believe your little stories, don't they?
Why, they believe you're just
a stone killer, don't they?
Seems these folks trust you.
They think you're gonna save
their little town.
their little souls!
But we know better, don't we?
So why don't you show your friends here
what you're made of?
Show them who you really are.
Why don't you just pull your gun
and shoot me?
But, of course, you won't need all these.
Just one, right?
Go ahead, hero. Pull the trigger.
You got killer in your eyes, son?
I don't see it.
You didn't do any of them things
you said, did you?
You didn't kill them Jenkins brothers.
You ain't even from the West!
Are you?
- Say it!
- No.
Speak up.
I don't think your friends here heard you.
No.
All you've done is lie
to these good people.
You ain't nothing but a fake
and a coward. Isn't that right?
Yes.
- Louder!
- Yes.
Listen close, you pathetic fraud.
This is my town now.
If I ever see you again, I will take
your soul straight down to hell!
Who are you?
Who am I?
I'm nobody.
Golden guardians.
The alabaster carriage.
The Spirit of the West.
Excuse me? Mister Spirit, sir?
There's a beaut. Sometimes you got to
dig deep to find what you're looking for.
So you made it.
Is this heaven?
If it were, we'd be eating Pop-Tarts
with Kim Novak.
Yeah.
No kidding.
What are you doing out here?
Searching, same as you.
I don't even know
what I'm looking for any more.
I don't even know who I am.
They used to call you
the Man with No Name.
These days they got a name
for just about everything.
Doesn't matter what they call you.
It's the deeds make the man.
Yeah, but my deeds just made things
worse. I'm a fraud. I'm a phoney!
My friends believed in me,
but they need some kind of hero.
Then be a hero.
No. No, no, you don't understand.
I'm not even supposed to be here.
That's right. You came a long way
to find something that isn't out here.
Don't you see? It's not about you.
It's about them.
But I can't go back.
Don't know that you got a choice, son.
No man can walk out on his own story.
So you made it.
That's right, amigo.
The other side of the road.
Did you just see that?
We each see what we need to see.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah.
It is.
Come, my friend.
I want to show you something.
Many years ago, this entire
valley was covered in agua.
Now only one question remains.
Where did it go?
They follow the water.
They follow the water! Come on!
That just don't make no sense.
Without water, that land is useless.
What are you building out here?
The future, Mr Rango.
You can either be part of it,
or you can be left behind.
I was here before the highway split
this great valley.
I watched the march of progress
and I learned a thing or two.
Control the water
and you control everything.
Come now, Mr Rango.
You attribute divine power to me.
How on earth
could I possibly control the water?
What now, amigo?
No man can walk out on his own story.
I'm going back.
But why?
Because that's who I am.
You got a lot of nerve showing up here,
lawman. What is it you want?
Your pappy and them boys are about
to hang for something they didn't do.
But I've got a plan.
I appreciate how difficult
this is for you, Beans.
But you're making a practical decision.
Decisions, decisions.
There's no need for any more suffering.
Your family's ranch is nothing
but a wasteland now.
Sign the deed and relieve yourself
of your father's burden.
My daddy was not a burden!
Keep your blood money
and I'll keep my land!
Do what he says or,
by all the fires of the black pit,
I'll squeeze them pretty brown eyes
out of your skull!
Now, hold on, Jake.
There's no need to...
Let me do my job! You brought me in.
Now we're gonna play this thing
out to the end!
Sign the damn paper, woman!
Go to hell!
Where do you think I come from?
Look into my eyes.
I want to see you die.
Jake!
I'm calling you out!
This day
just got a little more interesting.
Put her down.
Or what, little man?
You going to kill me?
That's just about the size of it.
- Get your filthy paws off me!
- Shut your gob!
All right, Sheriff, make your move.
Now, amigos!
- Heave! Heave!
That was a bad idea.
Thirsty, brother?
Here it comes!
No. No!
It's a miracle!
Look out!
- Lookee there!
- What is that?
It's our salvation, Pa!
It's a jailbreak, boys! We're busting out!
I'm gonna blow so many holes in you,
your guts'll be leaking lead!
Well, then
it's a good thing I brought some backup.
What?
Ain't no hawk.
Ain't nothing but bats!
Stick to the plan, boys!
Let's bleed that devil dry!
It only takes one bullet.
You ain't got the nerve.
Try me.
Oh, Mr Rango.
Aren't you forgetting something?
Hand me your gun, Sheriff.
Now, Mr Rango.
Beans! Hold on.
Don't worry, I got a plan.
Help!
Open the door!
Okay, plan B.
Beans, you're mumbling.
All my problems taken care of
except for one.
It's a new West, Jake.
There's no room for gunslingers
any more. We're businessmen now.
Yeah, we got new hats.
Where I come from,
we call this improvisation.
You came back.
What was that?
No need to panic,
but I think you just swallowed plan B.
What?
Okay, panic time.
You and the Sheriff are more alike
than you think.
You're nothing but legends.
Pretty soon,
no one will believe you even existed.
One last bullet to kill one last outlaw.
How fitting.
Sheriff, I'm sure if we work together,
we can reach a mutually beneficial
solution to our current situation.
You better take it up with him.
One bullet.
I tip my hat to you,
one legend to another.
What was that you said?
"Pretty soon,
no one will believe you even existed."
No, Jake! No!
Rango!
You brought the water back,
just like you promised.
You really are a hero.
Well, the thing about heroes is,
whenever you...
Don't spoil it.
Right.
Well, I don't know about you all,
but I could sure go for a dip.
And so the lizard completes his journey
from humble beginnings
to the legend we sing of today.
And although he is certain to die,
perhaps from a household accident,
which account
for 65% of all unnatural deaths,
the people of the village
will honour his memory
even as they abandon their dignity.
- I'm going in.
- How about a cold one, there?
Water ain't money. Money is money.
Well, I ain't got no...
We have a problem.
Who let Snuggles in the pool again?
I really think you complete me.
Prithee, unhand my fair maiden.
- Cut. Cut. Everybody, take five.
- How can they take this any more?
Oh, you kids.
What did you do that for?
I was just checking.
I hope you don't get too sunburned.
You can peel a man's face right off.
- What is it?
- That there's some human spleen.
Don't touch it.
That's the second time
that's happened to me.
This water thing's great.
I'm urinating right now.
Adult swim, next five minutes.
Stay between the buoys.
I packed your lunch. Danish is in there
and I picked the raisins out
just the way you like it.
Don't forget, your nasal spray is
in your saddle-bag...
- Beans!
...and your moisturising lotion...
- Now, Beans! We've talked about this.
- Lotion?
That's for my gun. That's gun lotion.
Sherriff, where are you headed?
There's trouble down a dry creek.
Bad Bill's been acting up again.
Now, honey, you come back
with all your digits.
And don't go trying to be a hero.
Beans, you are missing the point.
I got an image to protect now.
Where's my Tic Tacs?
- I found them.
- What's going on?
You know, in order to satisfy the needs
of the collective,
the hero must abandon the self
and solidify his image as an icon
that will forever be remembered.
So, this is the sunset shot.
Give them a good one, amigo.
Ready, Excelsior?
My fellow comrades.
There will be times
when you doubt yourself.
When you feel pummelled
by the cataclysms of life,
remember this moment.
Remember me.
Know that I will be there watching you,
sometimes at inappropriate moments.
That's part of the deal.
And remember, within all of us resides
the true Spirit of the...
Let's take it from the top.