Ambulances are on the field! I had to .../ by email7
Jack! Don't worry, you've already won the season. And it doesn’t matter if you didn’t win the last race!
- The engine failed in the last laps.
- Let's take a look! Get the cables fast!
- Jacob *
-	Counties.
- How are you, Dad?
- Did you notice anything?
There is a large oil puddle in the second round. Bell doesn't risk it, Corbin goes wild, his sponsor is on the podium.
- Watch out for the 23rd.
- Linder.
SECURE RECEPTION INTERMEDIATE
Natural psychopath.
Wow, there's a puddle of oil in the second round!
I'll lure you there.
Damn it!
What do you see, Dominic?
He wants revenge on you ...
... surround to the left.
So you are our luck!
I need the name of that damn bookmaker!
Melbet!
Fuck harder!
Now get up and show me how to register online.
You can now win a great prize!
Give me the key for three to eight.
Now give me ... six extensions.
Are you sure?
Remember what I told you?
Pay attention to the details.
Big things are made of small things. Now look.
Did Dad succeed?
Do you remember the steps?
The eighth key was not needed!
I agree.
The boiler does not work again.
That’s the price of living away from the world.
Do you want to help us here?
Are you waiting for someone?
Brian, do you remember where you had to hide?
Easy, my friend!
We came in peace!
Lehel! Both!
It's just me!
Iran!
Maybe they don’t recognize me because I tanned for a week.
Brian, okay, get out of there.
Why then do you take out your bazooka later? This is to kill elephants.
We would call ...
... you just don't have a phone.
So no way.
- Brian baby.
- Hello!
- Large enough!
- All in one car ...
What the hell is going on?
Help! Hurry They attacked us! One of us is a traitor!
I urgently need it
There is little time left! I have a very important load here! Gather your team quickly!
I live, but this ...
Mr. Nobody's machine sent an alarm. There is a lot of encrypted data that I need to decrypt.
- Has anyone else seen this?
- That's the point, he was just looking for us.
This is very strange.
He caught Cipher
... but he was attacked in the air and escaped.
I'm sure your plane crashed here ...
... in the northwest of Montequinto.
We have to try to find it. He could survive. But it is not realistic to get there, but a closed area. And he has a lot of military staff.
I withdrew from these matters.
Wait, Dominica ...!
It's about Cipher ...
... your child's mother's killer.
Everything is in the past.
Well, we left at 8 in the morning. If you change your mind.
Thanks.
iPápi! Do you know where God lives?
And where?
In your heart
So, and yours too.
But the most important thing is that ...
I ... will always be in your heart.
How are you, dear?
I have a gift for you.
Your father gave it to me.
I'll give it to you now.
Very special.
Don't lose.
Sweet Dreams
This kind of life is not for us.
Brian and Mia left these things when their children were born.
We are different.
They attacked us!
One of us is a traitor!
They're in! I have a very important load here! Gathering their team ...
They will all kill ...
Who else lives! Stop ...
MONTEQUINTO
The signal source is only a few miles away.
In the area controlled by the montequinto army. Are you all ready?
Sure! They always make fun of me because I choose the style, not the practicality!
"But today I'm the most practical of them all!"
- We noticed, brother.
Freud's grandfather would have accurately estimated the size he had chosen.
- I'm going first!
- Careful.
"Be careful" is for the losers!
The military is also coming here. We'll have ten minutes.
There is no sign of Mr. nearby, but we must act as quickly as possible.
They must not fall into their arms.
- Let's go there.
- He's closing us.
Here the alarm was broadcast all the time.
Someone tried to open the safe.
But the plane went down before they reached.
To save the safe, no one could crash the plane.
The idiots wanted to cut in the door. But I have an express method.
Dominic.
There is no one nearby.
There is no sign of Nobody.
Ready.
- So what the hell is this?
"Who knows, but he wanted it to be with us."
How ...?
We're leaving here!
They are there! They are there!
Hey guys! Who are they up to?
Do you think I'm scared?
Rome, where are you?
And how you like it, Freud, your mother!
"Dangerous mines"? And what does that mean?
Test how fast you have to go.
- No, that's a bad idea. Fuck, I want to live.
- So what does "dangerous mines" mean?
- Can we pass them?
- I don't know, brother.
Are you ignoring it?
What do these two words mean?
I'm literally translating!
- Watch out, there are mines!
What ?!
- Do you need speed?
- Considering the half-second start delay ...
- ... and the radius of the explosion, we need 80 miles per hour.
- Fails! The speedometer has a maximum of 70!
What to do?
Hit the gas hard! And pray!
MINES
Let's go to the palm plantation, there are no mines!
To the mother ...!
Rome, are you alive?
yes only my ass is on fire.
No! High! There is a mine!
"How did you survive after that, my friend?"
I'm in shock too. Come on.
You guys are ready to figure out how we can get away.
"There's a bridge on the border a few miles away."
-Cool! The sooner we get out of here, the better.
Letty, be careful, it's true.
Where is the device?
get off
That was Jacob, right?
The main road is ours, asshole!
- And this is a bridge ...?
- Do we have to go through this ...?!
Well, yes, it's a bridge ... too narrow.
iiiMámiü!
These maniacs will not leave us alone!
We have to go to the other side of the border!
Where is the bridge?
No, no! Do not you dare!
What kind of father am I flying with ...
The danger is over.
But you made a lot of noise there.
The press has arrived.
- The spy plane crashed into enemy territory.
"And the special agents waged war there."
Of course I raise them ...
... but this is where my help ends.
Thanks for your help.
It's time to finish the help.
And what's next, Ramsey?
HEARTS OpUOp V?
Well, I was able to decipher the data that was on Mr. Nobody's alarm ...
... and I found the GPS coordinates there ...
... obviously intentionally hidden.
Did you know about Jacob?
Question. Who is Jacob?
Jacob ... Dominic's younger brother.
Really? Curse!
I'm sorry, but that's too much.
Your brother?
So you have a brother? Who else is megaspy?
With your own pocket armor? Can you perform such crazy stunts?
Jump into cars from high altitudes and land on an oncoming plane?
f
He is ill?
Not sick.
This is Toretto.
My father is there!
z
- She's dead!
- We have to get it out!
Let me get it out! My father is there! My father is there!
My father is there! Save my father!
He's still alive! Save him! Please! Help him!
My father is there!
You just have to sign
waiver of all claims.
And a few more letters.
The car cover is there, in a special parking lot.
Hey!
No one should touch it.
Are you the youngest son of Toretto?
Unfortunate mediocrity.
Now what?
Get out.
Get out!
Can't I say goodbye to the legend? Is that what you're talking about?
No.
Not possible! You killed him!
The race killed him. He knew I was hitting his back. He knew. And how he reacted after that ... I don't know.
- I swear ... if you don't disappear now ...
-... You will have to ...
- Call Buddy.
Fast!
Large! Now comes Father's pride.
Get out of here.
Do you want to threaten me too?
Please, I'm not threatening you.
The Toretto family is always considered more sacred than the Pope!
Do you want to reveal a secret to you?
You, your father and I ... are in a boat.
And we will all be together until the end of the days.
We have to agree.
You're not with my dad.
- But I'm alive, man.
-	What did you say?
Fuck!
No, Dominic! Enough! Stop! Stop, calm down! You will kill me!
Come on, your footprint.
Come on
Jacob!
I can't believe the idea for the magnet worked. It turned out to be amazing.
Watch the video directly from the plane.
- Where to put ...?
- He ... almost caught up.
Did you agree?
No. Yet.
When I see it, it turns on right away.
But at the same time very scary. Strange, huh?
Thousand I II
I
Excellent work.
They were abducted from the plane in the air and crashed.
It's worth what I pay you.
Do you know who I am?
Of course I know.
What about you
Childhood in East Los Angeles is not Disneyiandia.
Also more talented in the shadow of your brother. Is that correct?
And all his life he tries to be faster than Dominic. Smarter than Dominic ... Stronger than Dominic.
It's true ... that I hate it
keep you awake at night ...?
... and does it bother you ... even after all these years?
It was my fault that I last contacted his brother. I should contact you.
- I don't work in the race.
- Naive ...
... to think that you are my competitor.
Said the mouse out of the box.
I
You want that?
The second part was buried somewhere inside the Agency.
I want you to find it.
To do this, remove the master plate from the plane.
Everything else - comes from ancient times. In front of the internet.
Not to pirate with what you are not asked to do.
And if you get what you wanted ... a weapon that can wipe all of humanity off the face of the Earth ... what will it do?
Are you going to do an apocalypse?
Do you sell to the most generous? Oh, I seem to know.
He wants to shake the rotten system.
But in your heart you dream of being hugged.
- Did you find my school profile?
- I found everything. Even graduation photos.
It's my job.
He has ... a huge jaw.
The Toretto family mixes a wide variety of blood, but its northern presence came as a real surprise.
Edinburgh The right component.
Finding two halves of the Ares project is as simple as peeling a pear. But he lures his brother into business ...
■ ■ •
very unlikely.
Trust me, I can handle it.
Hasa Han.
What?
Brother of Genghis Khan.
No one knew about it.
CASPIAN SEA
They hid very well.
yes whoever built this ... this guy was so paranoid.
If all of a sudden the ninja turtles attack us, here I go!
I don’t think the Agency would know about this hole. Mr. Nobody seems to be a secret nest.
What's next, Dominic?
We became Jacob eventually ...
. and whatever you do or do ...
My fault.
And I have to fix it.
No. It's not that easy ... to get rid of us.
So, let's get to work.
Strange business. We went through so many dangerous things. And ... yet ... we're still alive.
yes, so far we have not twisted, we have not devoured.
We were lucky.
No, no, no, they don't understand. Just think about it!
We travel around the world, doing crazy tasks. And quite often.
We'll do ... what others think is fucking. And I don't have a damn scar.
Seriously! Take a look at my coat!
Bullet holes. They wanted to blow my head off a lot of times!
But they couldn't! We are obviously smarter than cars, trains and tanks. And any plane, compared to us, is a sparrow!
- And we're all still alive ...
- I'm talking about this!
Ramsey, when tests of a theory give the same result, what does that mean?
Let this hypothesis be a fact. But you don't mean ...
I see, but ... when miracles happen again and again, it's not just luck.
Maybe we're really special ...?
And that's what I think! Obviously, we are special!
Well ... just to clarify ... you really think you're ...
superheroes?
- Maybe.
But more likely
■ ■ ■
that you're just crazy!
Your brain is as leaky as your coat.
He did a great job today.
Do you miss your old life?
What about you
Every day.
Hello
We have guests
No need to present.
- Nice to see you new.
I missed them.
Thanks.
Willingly
Why didn't you tell me?
You have a right to know.
Jacob and my brother. I couldn't help but come.
By being involved in this matter, you are jeopardizing everything.
and to your new life
and his children.
We are all risking something here.
Dominic, listen to me.
My children ... and your child is completely safe now.
Brian is with them.
We have something to save.
And I am aware of the risks.
The protection of these antiques proved to be adequate. But I uploaded it to the port and played with the protocols ...
I sank into the brain and
... I'll introduce you to the Ares secret project.
- What is that?
- What we got safely out of the plane ...
... part of the project.
Ares - can subdue any binary device.
Any computer is vulnerable.
And it doesn’t matter where and how much protection you are under.
For example, if Arest loads a satellite, it spreads like a virus.
And then you can control any weapon ...
... conventional, nuclear or new developments.
And you can apply them anywhere.
With that, Jacob ... will be the lord of the world ...
... in an instant.
Ares is the God of War, right? If Jacob takes control of Ares ...
... to truly become God, and not good at all.
To reduce the risks, Mr. No one withdrew the prototype and divided it into two equal parts.
Both are useless without the activation key.
Jacob has a party.
Now he's trying to find the other one.
But the key is missing.
Disappeared.
We will find it.
But to catch up with Jacob, we have to be separate.
Rome, Milk: My German friends help us get everything we may need.
- Pack it up!
- Wait, there's one more thing.
In Mr. Nobody's message, the name associated with the key was encrypted.
Now it will be a surprise, you better sit down.
Not possible.
I said exactly the same thing.
So ... Khan's death is part of this crazy mix?
At least there is a connection. I'll take care of that.
Milk, can you send me all the information about Khan?
I'm going with you.
- Come on.
- Letty ...
... I got this on the day of his death.
Mexico.
Now look at the stamp. That's the end of the clues.
You have to find everything.
Tokyo
What did you decide about Jacob?
I will find it.
How?
With the help of a friend
But imagine ... that you could buy a house for a Chorizo? What can you buy then?
Money is an illusion!
Illusion ...? If you have too many illusions, I take them. You are not going anywhere without money! Money is a reality.
- It's an illusion!
- Reality!
Hey, what do you say?
Is money an illusion or a reality?
Does not matter.
It's just a matter of perception.
Here! I was right again!
- I'm Leo.
- I'm Santos.
I'm Dominic.
- Why are they locked up?
- Not white.
- And for the bank robbery.
- You don't understand anything!
The police stopped us because we are black! And not because we robbed the bank.
- Okay ... you're right about that.
- Oh, stop, stop, be careful.
There is a crack in the fuel line.
If air enters - the car will drown.
This ...
An old trick mechanic is manipulating a car race.
But if the crack gets bigger and sparks come ... everything will explode to hell.
Hey dude, you're the best!
Who is next?
Who will challenge me?
I try.
Dominic?
When did he get out of jail?
Are we talking or driving?
All right, Dominic.
Do you want to call Buddy in the trash?
The driver is more important than the car.
The conditions are as follows.
If you win ...
you come home.
If you lose ... you run from here ... and you never come back ...
'eouriN
What is this nonsense, brother?
I know what you did.
The same day, my father complained about engine failures. You remember?
You last got under the hood.
And he died a minute later.
Tell me why you killed Dad.
Let's go now.
Robbery in the Eco-Park!
The 4th Street Bridge is free!
Come on, come on, come on!
Fuck!
For your tickets ...
Attention!
Now!
Too early
No!
Nothing has changed here.
I left everything as it was with Jack.
I'm looking for Jacob.
There is no possibility.
I know you took it after my father died.
Toretto's worst dream ...
it is the expulsion of the family.
And that's what you did to him.
Some people love you, wait for you, care about you.
Jacob has no one. Your hostility will not end until one of you dies.
I know you did what was best for him, you cared about him.
But we both understand that something is going wrong.
As much as I could, I helped Jacob.
But I'm not Jack Toretto.
So they have a chance for the future ...
they must accept the past.
He's in London.
That's all I know
Dominic.
I hope they reconciled.
The last chance to die in this race.
TOKYO
Origato.
- I think we're at a dead end.
"Does Jacob know that Khan is involved in the project?"
If you have the same information as us ... then you know.
Dominic didn't know ...
... that I kept my relationship with Jacob a secret.
He lived with Buddy for a year ... then ... he disappeared, leaving a note where he asked not to look for him.
After such a strange act, I was willing to do anything to find it.
I even went into the police file, but ... it didn't help me.
Really? At the age of sixteen?
I wanted to find it.
sure
And how are you?
In general?
Is quiet life over?
I just remembered
Who am I
Everything has changed a lot. And it slowed down.
I only find peace in chaos. I have to collide with the world to feel alive.
I watch Brian rush ... to hide from the armed intruders ...
■ ■ ■
I got up.
To hide - not for us.
Dominic is my brother, but he can always trust me.
You and I have something we don’t have to talk about.
What?
I can not believe my eyes ...
What are you talking about?
Remember what Han always said about Tokyo?
He joked that in the old westerns, cowboys ran out of justice in Mexico.
Tokyo was Mexico.
Oops.
RETROPULSION INVESTIGATION AREA. SUBURB. GERMANY.
The car is ready to fight.
Wait ... No! No! John!
Why did you make a valve for the liquid oxygen tube?
Brother, don't worry, this is a significant step forward. Everything will be great. So I won us half a second.
Do not worry ?! This is not a bloody fighter! You can't get out of the car!
My friend, calm down. Everything will be great.
When he discovers what is happening due to excessive pressure ... he tells his opinion.
But now
do not participate.
But you said, "Stay out of it, genius!" Certain?
I was reminded of the use of rocket engines. And how to make money from it.
- That's my idea.
-Who do you entrust your incarnation to?
Is this the crazy mechanic?
Or a rocket scientist? If it weren’t for me, you’d be changing the oil in an fryer now!
Guys, calm down. Why fight? We all contribute.
Your only contribution is that you pee every time you take off, you silly orc.
Did I hear correctly?
Are you an aerophobic smuggler?
Are you the silent orc?
So ... you two ... the wise leprechaun and the giant hobbit?
I ... I'm not offended by the nickname "orc".
So ... are you tolerant of orcs?
Aren't you ashamed?
He's not serious.
Time for you guys!
Large!
Did you hear?
More than a quarter of a mile in ten seconds?
And our car can do it. For two damn seconds!
They put a rocket engine in a Pontiac Viera ...?
Cool? I know.
No ... Dude ... it's not cool at all.
Come on, take it out! The competition begins!
Take it off! Go! Go! Go!
Cool!
Yes!
We did it! Yes!
Yes, friends, we did it!
Mm
Why are they so happy?
The machine clearly won them.
The car did not explode.
It didn't even melt.
It stands like new.
Fireworks to the top?
Well, I already warned you.
But you are deaf.
We were secretly told ...
Can you get the cars?
Just please ...
these are not the cars that explode ...
Can they do it?
- Mortgage office three miles from here. "Dominic Toretto sent us.
Who the hell is Toretto?
London
Beautiful necklace, Magdalene.
Diamonds and emeralds look very good on you.
Dominic Toretto ...
I heard they were put in jail.
But I didn't stay there long.
They will never learn ...
that the cage does not belong to all birds.
Are you looking for one of my children?
You had no idea.
Take it and 15 percent of the sale is yours.
I stopped this a long time ago.
But not ...
So ... are you going with me?
Looking for somebody.
He came here recently.
And with a great team.
With lots of money and connections.
Anyway, yes, here’s a foreign team in which the boss is American.
.
He bought a gun from a local dealer and heard that there was something serious in Edinburgh.
c / k a local seller, huh?
Who likes to steal the most expensive trinkets?
He gave me a lot, I’m not stupid if I refuse money.
It was about its height.
And he looked very much like you.
Oh, damn it. Did I confuse you with your cousin?
With my brother.
Honey, apply the parking brake.
It turned out
not only my relatives are crazy.
z
He offered you money
head.
.
TO
obsession
For man, nothing is more important than the love of his family.
But it turned love into anger.
And there is nothing more dangerous.
you
Dominic?
Don't let him kill you.
You are my favorite American.
.
I think you like this party?
The best girls, the best cars.
All the best. And the best security.
I'm Otto, your brother's partner.
Specifically, I am your investor.
But since my father is a dictator, I am not any rich child. No no no.
Everything you see here is mine! Even the girls. If you want one or two or three ...
... Just tell me. They are in payroll. In addition, I pay them for the dentist.
Do you understand
Where is Jacob?
In the palace.
The brother you met ...
... is in the past.
He is not here.
And I still see the same coward who killed my father.
You are very wrong.
Don't neglect your back
... in my world.
My suggestion
... it used to be the same as yours.
Get out of here. Just now.
Without speech.
And he never comes back.
Never
wake up
I was sorry that day!
But don't expect more mercy from me.
- Here!
- The object is here.
iToretto!
My father is the head of state.
And I'm a senior man.
This is the palace embassy. It turned out that you entered my country for the purpose of murder.
Of course, I had to go to Interpol for help.
If you continue to delve into the past ...
you dig your own grave.
Well, I was nervous about my idiot father.
But your family ... damn ... even crazier.
Well ... we neutralized your brother. Time to go through Edinburgh ...
... for the second part of Ares.
And then ... it's not a sin to relax, is it?
- And the key?
- My people will get it soon.
In a week ... no great power will be able to urinate without our permission.
In a week ... your father will beg you to lend him the money.
It would be good.
I can not wait.
Dominic!
How are you handsome boy? Ah?
Thank you very much, Leisa.
Seriously! If it weren't for you, I'd still steal gasoline in my country.
"How about working with Magdalena?"
- I'm like a princess there. As his best student.
- Kara's sister is a fire.
- Fire?
Did you see my ass in a dress? So shut up if you don't understand!
This whole team is my daughters! You understand? I brought them from all over the world.
I almost forgot.
Van. It will be useful.
The weapon is programmed according to your brother's biometric data. Now you can find it without any problems.
Hey, Letty.
- what?
-	Seeing.
Who is he?
Han never mentioned it.
Letty, Mia!
On the ground, fast!
What ...
Are you okay
EDINBURGH
■
.
CASINO
Welcome to the cathedral.
The history of this holy place dates back more than 9 centuries.
First of all, it is famous for ...
Everything is ready.
Ramsey, right?
I copied Jakob's biometric data from his gun.
The program indicates that your people are a stone’s throw away from us.
Within a radius of about one hundred meters.
About a hundred meters?
yes, there is room.
There are really a lot of people here.
Then.
You obviously don't know where he is
the secret safe Jacob wants to blow up?
That's why it was called a secret.
Clean.
He read a lot of books, braided braids, wore glasses, but he didn’t get smarter.
It’s weird that we didn’t use a good old beacon
That would have led us directly to this guy.
But not! Instead, we’re confused with biometrics and facial recognition!
Now, like idiots, we are looking for a white man in a white room.
yes, true, but there is a detail.
They are always attentive to the marker.
This means they can discover the dry cleaner where the pants were brought with this beacon.
But with biometrics, it’s impossible to shit that.
What
■ ■ ■
Guys, I ... We have a problem.
All cameras are broken.
And the technique is flawed.
Jimmy, what the hell?
Alarm, the cameras don't work!
Damn it
Do you see anything strange?
Where do we start?
First of all, I feel weird around these tourists.
And those two women out there are outraged.
They want to look like George and Washington sexy.
I feel like I'm on Count Dracula's birthday.
Ramsey, we've been around every corner ... we've already got real calluses!
And nothing!
- Wow!
-	What?
Did you notice?
What are you talking about?
The ears.
It's broken many times.
These guys are warriors.
To see.
Roman!
Hey brother, I asked you for shoes.
Three weeks have passed and still nothing!
Consider my opinion!
Do we think first and act later?
Dominic, go quickly to the cathedral.
Our genius hit the messengers, he didn’t like their ears.
Stop, stop, stop.
How much did you pay for it?
Platinum does not appear to be magnetized.
shut up, please.
I'm tired of me!
Ramsey, for example, has a huge electromagnet on the truck.
It disrupts the technique, doesn't it?
Including security systems.
I found out ... That's how Jakob would enter the safe!
Guys! Hello?
Police officers flew in from all directions, closing the district.
He won't get away with a car.
Ramsey, I saw Jacob.
I see Otto.
I'm looking.
He goes out with a blue Jaguar.
Follow me!
Me? I can not!
Why
Okay, it's not time, but ...
I don't have permission. I don't know how to drive. Absolutely.
Few people in London drive.
I thought you needed something else.
- Isn't that right?
- And who else?
Jolin.
Guys, that's enough, we can always agree.
And with everyone. Truth?
Okay, how can that be ...
Ramsey, cut off the magnet!
Come on, fast!
The brake is on the left and the accelerator pedal is on the right.
Fuck ...
Fuck!
It was unintentional!
God!
I'm sorry!
Definitely not my fault!
And here I am definitely mine.
You see! I told you!
Not a single scratch!
iOtto, send new coordinates!
Accepted, I come to you.
Otto, where are you?
I'm coming, but I can't see you.
You made a bad street.
This is my cochom!
iDominic!
Go further!
Fuck!
You have talent.
Did you doubt it?
Listen to me!
I need 50 best fighters.
Armed with cars.
And with fighters even better.
Even with the starship with Chewbacca, if you succeeded.
I'll pay for everything, hair.
Live!
What?
What do you find funny?
For me ...
I was reminded of a regular movie scene.
I
v *
Just the moment the villain bounces off losing his plans.
He starts doing nonsense and eventually the main characters get their heads.
There is no crime
But you have no idea about our plans.
Here we are the main characters.
I'm like Luck, the fucking Skywaiker.
Are you sure you weren't wrong?
You already have a conflict with your father ^ but ...
Evaluate your progress.
Are you sure you're Skywaiker?
You're right.
I'm more of a Han Solo.
No
«■ ■
- You're Yoda.
- Yoda?
- No, green monster?
- Yes.
No.
Oh, I see.
Because he's the best Jedi, right?
No.
Because it's a baby.
Fucked from her ass.
What shall we do?
There is no escape from the past.
And yours got to you too.
Shit I've never seen such strong civilian or military electromagnets.
- And his power is unreal.
- Exactly.
.
Hey, do you want a joke?
- His face now ...
- Do you think it's funny?
I'm hungry!
Hi there.
We have guests.
Fucking bunker.
So many years
Did you get the postcard?
I can't believe it.
How to survive
After Gisele died, I ...
He didn't know how to live.
Why fight
■ ■ ■
- Disappeared.
-	Naturally.
Can you tell me how you survived the car explosion?
Very strong I want to know.
Roman, can you catch me once?
We had plans.
And we had dreams.
Well, what's our next adventure?
Maybe we can try to settle somewhere?
But exactly where?
In Tokyo. We dream of living in Tokyo.
Good choice.
Our dreams took me there.
Tokyo at last
It became my home.
But one day Mr. Nobody came for me.
I worked with Gisele.
As a CIA employee, he fought local drug cartels in Central America.
Good times
He was the best on the team.
An agent can die at any moment.
Of bullets, knives or strangulation.
But Gisele was deceived by her love for you.
What do you need?
I want to offer you a job. They have.
Here in Tokyo.
- Why me?
- I saw how they worked together.
I realized he trusted you.
That means I can trust you too.
And this is very rare in our difficult business.
The first task was to steal a technology from a family of scientists.
But, as usual, Mr. Nobody said everything.
He silenced the most important thing.
I was 11 years old.
My parents took me to the movies on Saturday when I got good grades at school.
But one day, before I left, I forgot to bring my raincoat.
I had to go back.
And I didn't find it right away.
I heard an explosion and looked out the window.
Mom and Dad died.
Turns out I wasn’t the only one looking for this thing.
Kill him! We don't need witnesses.
That's it, I found it.
Here.
Hide!
Han saved me. Realizing that they will always hunt me now ...
He taught me to survive.
I became my family.
Are they always hunting?
Why
Because he's the key.
Everyone was looking for a lifeless object.
And the key turned out to be a person.
Parents feared the Ares project would fall into the wrong hands.
And they put their key in their DNA.
And I'm her daughter.
Then Mr. Nobody gave me information that one of his agents was a traitor.
And when Deckard Shaw appeared ...
We use it.
But he died in that accident, Han.
Mr. No one is a master of special effects.
The performance was very spectacular.
It was still better.
Stay dead
It will be harder.
My death
That was the only way to survive.
- What the hell?
- The program has started, it looks like a virus.
Look at me, look at me!
Stop!
Well done, don't move.
If you don’t move, everyone will still survive.
Jakob.
Sorry, Mia.
I'm the traitor.
Surprised?
Didn't you think Mr. Nobody came to you?
Do you think he chose you for no reason?
For years, he supervised and carried out his missions from here.
I've been looking for this key for a long time.
But you brought it to me.
I already told you.
Watch out, brother.
Here.
He has a great team.
Do you trust them?
I trust that.
Do you know what's good about a father's death?
If I hadn’t died, I would have lived in your shadow.
And now
You will spend the rest of your days in mine.
The only advantage in the death of the father ...
That I didn't see who you were.
Real disgrace or for the Toretto family.
Do you think you met Dad? No ^ you didn't know, you lick ass!
Sure?
Do you want to know the truth?
He died because he wanted to play.
The family is in debt.
Not to disappoint
He addressed me.
How did I know the car would explode?
A good boy would have convinced him.
And a good brother would have told you.
Are you sure?
He took my word not to say it.
And I did it!
Now you know the truth.
I'll take the key.
Jakob!
I'll stop you.
Big brother word.
No!
Now, leave now.
Come on. Fast.
- Brother, how are you?
- Get up.
.
Get off!
Come on, fast! Fast!
Because here!
Come out fast!
They didn't go too far!
Come on!
Here!
I'm in your heart.
Forever
No no!
Boy
Did you notice anything?
Such cars are immortal.
Old chargers are so well made ...
That with proper care they can work forever.
What, forever?
The same goes for the family.
A good family does not die.
Create such a family.
Apu!
Kis Brian.
When are you coming home?
Soon
No, I pay on time.
I give you my word of honor!
I already have problems within 2 laps!
I'll see, bring the cables!
- Jakob!
- Now.
Ready.
iNoooo!
You saved me
Without you, the meaning of my whole life will disappear.
Did you understand?
We are the same.
We have little time, Jakob already has all the elements.
Once activated, just spread the signal on the planet.
And it doesn't stop. Absolutely.
You must launch a pirated satellite to amplify the signal.
Broadcast of all satellites in orbit.
We found it, thwarted his plans, saved Elle.
We have a 0 chance here, Han. The satellites are easy to track, but we don’t have time to do it before departure.
The point is, we have 2 goals.
- Jacob is on the ground
- And he has an army.
- And the satellite in the sky.
What you have to crack and need to be done manually.
At high altitudes.
When the satellite is in orbit.
On the field?
We need help, otherwise there is no solution.
We solve it ourselves.
And we prove it many times.
No. No ^ no, no.
You do not understand?
I can't see because he would be scared otherwise!
Like all normal people!
Track? This is a free space!
There are strangers!
What will we do?
How do we kidnap a transfer?
Or are we hitting the rockets in the back?
That is exactly what we are going to do.
What?
TBILISI
This is the end
on the Pope's diplomatic relations.
Now all the city police are running here.
We better get out of here.
To take away.
It seems to work.
As soon as the satellite is in orbit ^ begins.
What a trap!
What?
Hole Only one air leak would be missing.
Really?
With spacesuit ribbon?
Yes. Everything here is based on the sling and duct tape, even on our clever plan.
Dude, you don't seem to be feeling well.
Let's go to fucking space!
It's not like we went out in slippers for a beer!
Act like an astronaut, or you'll all go to hell!
- I'm going home myself.
- We'll be there in freefall.
Are we going to fail?
Explain it to me.
This means that the calculations cannot lie!
Trust the laws of physics and everything will be fine!
This is the fifth grade of the school.
I should have listened to the class!
We'll start in 4 minutes, are you ready?
We still haven’t covered all the holes, the electrical tape is missing.
Nothing, Milk.
Guys, we can't wait any longer, he's had enough. We are both ready.
No! The same car that exploded after the test drive.
Are you ready! Well, I don't want to die, Milk.
Without panic, I applied a lot of polymer ceramics to the hull.
Now heat resistant.
This is it.
All 8 engines are in good condition.
Hey, aren't you tired of the game anymore?
The Virgin Galactic took off from 9,000 meters.
NASA's pendulum tested 15,000.
Given our current weight, we need to go higher.
Much more! Without doing so, they can be immediately injured or even ignited.
Hey, we're watching you!
Don't worry, we're doing everything right.
Are you sure we won't burn them?
With the help of the thermal imager, Elle is in that vehicle.
I also found the sign "Ares". He's in the first armored car.
By the time the boys arrive, we need to deactivate “Ares”.
Ramsey, come on.
The satellite is already in low orbit.
We started.
Loading data.
Excellent, we have passed 15,000!
Be optimistic, guys!
Well, how do these ancient costumes help?
They dived with them in the first world championship!
How whimsical you are! We are astronauts, we have to endure it all!
Look, they’re just as good as normal spacesuits and can withstand pressure drops!
It can blow us up like a balloon, of course, but just a little bit.
That's the only difference.
- Now! We are at the height of departure.
The countdown will begin soon! Ready?
You are crazy? I’m not even jumping into a kids ’pool in this fucking spacesuit!
Don't listen, we're ready!
- We?
-Exactly!
Do you think he is invulnerable?
Let's see now!
- Press the button!
- No, Milk!
Fuck!
- I do not want to die!
- i Motor!
Fuck!
We are already astronauts!
My calculations were correct.
Very good person!
Did you eat that much chocolate?
Forgive me, I am attracted to stressful sweets.
You said you guessed it.
One minute Hey, kill these bastards right away!
Well, Han, Mia, come on!
■ SOUIBA
Letty.
Crazy! That's how he's going to kill us!
No, not all of them.
Now.
The satellite you're looking for must be somewhere ...
There. It's there, see?
I see it. Just promise to treat me.
My friend, did I bother you with your calculations?
So don’t bother driving.
Two guys from the ghetto are in space.
But, as always, no one will believe them.
Shame.
Apparently something is wrong with the antennas.
There is a lot of intervention.
I'll take care of it.
Han.
Sit behind the wheel. It starts.
I want to join their channel.
- What's going on there, Otto?
- Sorry, the download is in full swing.
Anyway, I have a new business partner, you know him.
That little mouse in the box, Jakob.
I already told you.
I don't consider him a racer.
Otto, listen carefully.
Come on, last word.
You're ugly, stupid fucking, and I'll kill you.
No one would have explained it to you ...
Stupid ugly fucking lord of the world.
■ so LUGA
What is there?
We seem to be left without courtship or guard.
And without Jacob. And Dominio is doing everything he can to ruin our vacation, but bullshit, don’t worry, honey.
I have to do everything.
Well, we tested the armor of this monster.
Are you ready
To the maximum.
If we don’t break through, at least we’ll stop them.
Don’t think about stopping and the download is almost complete.
Dominic, we have to go now, or we'll die.
- Letty, go back and stay with her.
-	What?
If we can’t slow down or pierce, we’ll turn it around and open up the gut!
The villains are here!
Why do I have to show you everything? Kill them!
- Power line!
- You read my mind! Go in front of me!
Dominic, I can't come in.
But I know.
Great, the satellite is close. Now put on the magnets and fry.
The point is calm.
Let's go.
- Milk!
- One second.
Come on! On the go!
Please!
Fuck! Fuck!
Hey! Why is there no problem?
During startup, the cables appear to be broken from overload.
You idiot! I could have foreseen it.
Guys, what would be there?
Data upload is almost complete!
Or maybe we'll just destroy it?
- Destroy all the shit and that's it.
- No.
If we smash,
we will most likely die.
Even if we survive, we will use all the fuel.
And we will stay here forever.
We can be lucky ^ brother.
Luck cannot be calculated.
You know what, Milk?
Looks like you were right.
We are not superheroes.
We always seem to have had great luck.
It's over now.
But he knows my friend
■ ■ ■
If we die ...
We do it on top of the world.
Guys, why are you silent? Seconds left!
Attack! It's going.
Five! Four! Three! Two!
one
The charge is complete.
Error, loss of communication.
We did it!
Come on
Yes!
Wow! Fuck!
Not bad, man.
Excellent attack.
Be careful!
The connection has been established.
"Ares" is found, the magnet is activated.
Large!
- The connection was lost.
- How stubborn.
The connection has been established.
Damn it!
The connection to the drone was lost.
Here are yours.
You have crossed the road with many, they are taking revenge.
I know.
I chose this path.
Our father was not without sins.
But he loved us both.
I was rescued once after I got the car keys.
It changed my life.
Now I will do the same.
I already lost you.
And I don't want to lose you again.
Air traffic control center, do you see that too?
It looks like a very strange car.
We come in peace!
Hello!
But why do they wear a suit
.... one of his minions?
This is the last time I saw your grandfather.
He led this course.
So you led here too?
No, but it affected me.
Here I learned the most important thing in my life.
Right?
True.
Everything will be fine, Jakob.
yes, it will not be easy for us.
But everything will work out.
Because we are a family.
- For us.
Oops!
Not possible!
- Hello.
-	Are you alive!
I didn't believe you survived.
It's a long story.
Let's enjoy the moment.
I'll introduce you to Elle.
Hi Elle. I'm Sean.
- I am glad.
-	Hello friend.
- What the!
-	How are you?
Ramsey, this is Santos. Saints, this is Ramsey.
Hello! I've heard a lot about you.
And where is Leo?
That’s why he opened a restaurant in Brookiyn.
- Seriously?
- The food sucks.
But hippies love it.
- Everyone has their own.
- Hello.
Hello
How long can I wait for my food?
No, seriously, I'm hungry.
The pipes in space make me hungry.
Oh yes? Are there any chocolates in the tubes?
The ones you ate.
But they saved me.
- Well, wasn't my hunger important?
- Are we cooking soon?
Okay, I'll leave you.
Do not fight.
Well, you're like Dad.
- Right?
- Yes.
You know ...
We met your mom and there.
Imagine he is looking straight at you from the sky.
© @ {^ 51 - © S © @ ® © © ®
SECURE RECEPTION INTERMEDIATE
Hello!
- Hello!
Little Brian is ready to thank himself.
Again!
No hurry.
Someone is still missing.
He's coming now.