That's the cleanup crew up on the track,
and that's a lot of racers
involved there, folks.
Jack, you realize
you got this in the bag, right?
Season's wrapped up, man.
Doesn't matter where you place.
I'm telling you, I got intermittent miss.
Last two laps.
On it!
Get those plug wires!
Jakob! Now.
Hey, Pop.
Tell me what you see, Dom.
Got an oil spill going into turn two.
Bell's driving safe. Corbin's got a sponsor
in the stands, so he's pushing it.
Talking about me?
You got a real problem with car 23.
- Linder.
- About to whip your ass, Toretto!
Settle down, pretty boy!
That's right. Yeah, you. You want to tell
your driver he's gonna get somebody hurt?
- Hey! Leave it!
- Go home! You suck!
He's just pissed I got that spot in
the Busch Series next season, not him.
Life's got no shortage of guys
like Kenny Linder.
You're good!
It's not about being
the stronger man, Dom.
It's about being the bigger one.
I swear to God, this guy.
Pop, turn two, turn two!
Got it. I'm walking him in.
Shit!
Tell me what you see, Dom.
He's gonna come at you for that.
Get ready on your left.
Three-eighths ratchet.
Three-eighths driver.
Six-inch extension.
Are you sure?
Remember what your daddy told you.
Be precise in life.
It can make all the difference.
Now, watch this.
- See how it's working now?
- Mm-hmm.
And you see what's happening?
It's turning the screw.
You're right.
Water heater's out again.
It's the price we pay for peace and quiet.
Want to come and give us a hand?
Are you expecting someone?
Brian, remember what we practiced.
Yo, yo!
We come in peace.
We come in peace!
It's me!
Roman? Maybe you don't recognize me
'cause I've been tanning all week, bro.
B, come out, son.
What you gonna do with that thing, man?
What, you out here trying
to kill elephants or something?
We would've called first.
Except you actually need phones in order
to get phone calls. You know that, right?
- Little B!
- Wow, you're so big.
- Hi.
- Wow.
Now, I know you don't carpool.
So what's up?
Mayday! Mayday! My plane is
under attack by a rogue agent!
We're being boarded.
I've got dangerous cargo on board.
I need you to assemble the team.
...still alive. I'll explain...
It's an SOS transmission
from Mr. Nobody's plane.
It came through with
a mess of encrypted data,
most of which I'm still trying to crack.
- Did anybody else get this?
- Well, that's the thing.
He sent it only to us.
Why just us?
He caught Cipher.
But there was a midair attack,
and she was extracted.
It seems his plane crashed
somewhere here,
over the northwest region
of Montequinto.
If Mr. Nobody survived,
we need to find him.
But the whole area's sealed off.
Isolationist, run by military.
We're not on call anymore.
Wait, wait.
Dom, this is Cipher.
The woman who killed
the mother of your child.
Things change.
Listen, we're wheels up at 8:00 a.m.,
if you change your mind.
Thank you.
Daddy, do you know where God is?
Where is God?
In your heart.
He's in your heart, too.
And you know something?
I'll always be in your heart.
Hey, little guy.
I have a gift for you.
Your father gave this to me.
And now I'm gonna give it to you.
It's very special.
Take care of it.
Good night.
This isn't who we are.
Brian and Mia got out of the game
when they became parents.
We're not them.
...under attack by a rogue agent!
We're being boarded.
I've got dangerous cargo on board.
...assemble the team.
...still alive. I'll explain...
...alive. I'll explain...
Coming up on the signal, two miles.
It's deep in the militarized zone of
Montequinto. I hope everyone's ready.
Ready? Y'all want to make jokes
about me not making practical decisions?
This is as prepared as it gets.
We all see you, man.
Nobody thinks you're compensating
for anything.
I'll take point.
Careful.
Careful's when you get hurt.
Right now, we have a ten-minute window
between patrols.
Mr. Nobody's signal is close,
but we've got to move quickly, guys.
We do not want to cross paths
with the military here.
-  It's inside.
-  Cover us.
The source of the SOS signal is
coming from inside this thing.
Somebody wanted in.
Plane must have gone down
before they could cut through.
Or it was sent down on purpose to stop 'em.
Yeah, well, their mistake
was trying to cut into it.
But just give me a minute. I can get in.
Dom.
There's not a soul in sight.
No sign of Mr. Nobody.
Got it.
What the hell is this?
Whatever it is,
Mr. Nobody wanted us to find it.
How's that work-
Go!
What? You don't know who I am?
You think I'm scared?
Roman, where the hell are you?
Who's compensating now, Tej?
"Peligro minas." What does that mean?
Tej, how fast we got to go
to clear 'em?
Please don't tell me you're thinking
what I think you're thinking.
Why?
What does "peligro minas" mean?
Tej, how fast?
I don't know, man.
Somebody answer me!
What does "peligro minas" mean?
"Peligro minas" means "danger, land mines"!
What?
How fast, Tej?
Assuming a 50-foot blast radius and a half
a second trigger delay, I'd say about 80.
I can't! My speedometer only goes up to 70.
What do I do?
You put your foot to that floor,
and you pray!
Get to that palm plantation,
and then we're clear.
Whoa!
Roman, you good?
My ass is en fuego!
Tej! Wait! Land mine!
How in the hell are you not dead?
Wait, okay, I think
I found us another way out.
Two miles to what looks like
a bridge across the border.
Good. The sooner we get out of here,
the better.
Letty, on the right.
The device.
Get in.
That was Jakob back there, wasn't it?
Always check your mirrors, bitches!
Oh, hell no.
Are we supposed to drive across that?
Well, I said it looked like a bridge.
Oh, my God!
The military's not giving up.
We got to get past the border.
Where's the bridge?
No. No, no.
Dom.
Well, that was new.
Look, we're in the clear.
But this thing is a mess.
The headlines out there?
Secret spy plane crashes
in a hostile country?
Followed by some kind of
covert ops firefight?
I'll get you where you need...
and then I'm gonna need to back off.
I appreciate the favor.
I got to stop doing so many favors.
What we doing, Ramsey?
Like, where are we going?
I-I was able to decrypt the data that
came through with Mr. Nobody's SOS,
and I found GPS coordinates,
definitely included on purpose.
You knew about Jakob?
Question: Who is Jakob?
Jakob is...
...or was Dom's brother.
Oh, my... my bad. I'm sorry.
I'm just processing.
Brother?
You got a brother?
Who also happens to be some kind
of super spy with his own private army,
who drives literally like
a bat out of hell,
who preplanned an aerial jump and
landed at the bottom of an airplane?
Who does that?
A Toretto.
That's my dad! That's my dad!
He's gone! He's gone!
We got to get him out of there.
We got to get him out of there!
That's my dad!
That's my dad! That's my dad!
Get him out of there!
That's my dad!
There's a couple of release forms
we've got to sign.
Few clearances.
Everything else is down there
around the corner.
Hey.
Nobody's supposed to be around here.
You Toretto's other son?
You're the useless one, right?
What is that?
Get out of here. Go.
So a man can't pay his last respects?
That's what that is?
No.
No, not you.
You're the one that killed him.
No, racing killed him.
Look, he knew that I was gonna
pit him into the wall. He knew that.
Now, I don't know if he dropped gear.
I don't know.
I swear...
I swear to God,
if you don't get out of here...
What? What?
Go find Buddy.
Now!
All right, well, now we got the golden boy.
Leave.
You here to make threats, too?
"Leave" is a simple word.
Man, what is it with you Torettos where
you're all the heroes in your own stories?
Look, I'm gonna tell you a secret.
You, your dad, me... we're all stuck,
going round and round
in the same shitty circle.
And we ain't never getting out.
You ain't half the man my dad was.
At least I'm alive, asshole.
What did you say?
Get off me!
Dom! Dom!
Dom!
Dom, no! Dom!
No, man!
In here.
Jakob.
I simply cannot believe
that magnet trick actually worked.
It looked so damn cool.
Look at this here.
I got this off the cockpit feed.
Oh, I love being rich.
It was sloppy. He almost had me.
- She say anything?
- Nope. Nada.
You know, I look at her
and I feel creeped out.
And sort of turned on at the same time.
Is that weird?
Nice operation.
You snatched me off Mr. Nobody's
plane midair without a scratch,
and you took him down.
Money well spent.
Do you know who I am?
I know who you are. Do you?
East L.A. is a tough enough place
to grow up.
But it was your brother's shadow
that turned you into this.
Isn't it?
So your whole life, you pushed yourself
to be faster than Dom. Smarter than Dom.
Stronger than Dom.
Tell me, do you hate him enough
that it keeps you up at night?
Still?
All these years later?
I should've just hired you
instead of coercing your brother
a couple of years back.
I don't work for the competition.
That's cute.
You thinking you're the competition.
Says the woman in the box.
Look familiar?
The other half's hidden
in one of the agency's thousands of vaults.
I need you to find out which one.
We secured the master drive here
from Mr. Nobody's plane.
The rest of the hardware is a bit dated.
Pre-Internet.
To make sure you don't go hack into
anything we don't want you to.
Say you get what you're after.
A weapon so dangerous it shouldn't exist
for another half century.
What would you do with it?
Launch some global attack?
Sell it to the highest bidder?
Or maybe you see yourself
as a necessary shock to the system.
I bet all you ever wanted was a hug.
You read my psych eval. Good for you.
I read your second-grade report card.
That's what I do.
Your chin, it's distinctive.
I know the Torettos have
quite the mixed bloodlines,
but I never detected a Nordic strain.
Finding the two halves of Project Aries
is the easy part.
Add in your brother Dom to the mix?
You don't have a chance.
Plans are in motion.
Qasar Khan.
What?
Genghis Khan's little brother.
Nobody's heard of him either.
Talk about off the grid.
I don't think they had grids
when this place was built.
If a Ninja Turtle pop out on me,
tell you right now, I'm out.
No way this place was sanctioned
by the agency.
This was definitely
Mr. Nobody's secret hideout.
What now, Dom?
Whoever Jakob has become...
...and whatever he's up to...
...it's on me.
And me alone.
Nah.
Whatever's on you, it's on us.
Let's get to work.
Y'all ever thought about
how many wild missions we been on?
How we somehow... always survive?
Yeah. So far, so good, I guess.
It's just luck.
No, no, no, see, y'all not listening.
Think about this.
We've now been on insane missions
around the world,
doing what most would say is
damn near impossible.
And I ain't got one single scar
to show for it?
I mean, look at my jacket.
Those are bullet holes from
14 dudes trying to take my head
clean off its shoulders.
We've taken out cars, trains, tanks.
I'm not gonna even mention the submarine.
And yet we're still here.
Exactly.
Ramsey, what happens when you test
a theory over and over again
only to come to the same result?
A hypothesis becomes fact.
But you're not actually suggesting that...
I don't know,
but when the improbable happens
again and again, that's more than luck.
Maybe we're not so normal.
That's what I'm saying.
We are not normal.
Okay, um... just to clarify,
are you two maybe suggesting
that we're what,
invincible?
Maybe.
Or maybe... you're just a dumbass.
Take your dumbass jacket with you, man.
Pretty impressive driving out there.
You miss the old life.
Do you?
Every day.
Guys.
We got a little company.
Think you know this person.
It's so good to see you.
I missed you.
Thank you.
Of course.
You should've told me.
She deserved to know.
Jakob's my brother, too. I need to be here.
You get involved here,
you put everything you have at risk.
Your kids and the whole world
that you built.
We're all risking something.
Dom, listen to me.
My kids and yours are in
the safest hands possible.
With Brian.
Our world's grown, Dom.
I got this one.
The firewall on this old thing
is actually pretty good.
But, you know, port scan, UDP message peek,
pop to root shell, and...
...say hello to Project Aries.
What is it?
It's what we got from Mr. Nobody's plane.
Or at least part of it.
Aries was designed to override and
assimilate anything that runs on code.
Any computer anywhere. If it operates on
zeros and ones, it's vulnerable.
If you take Aries
and upload it to a satellite,
it'll spread like a virus.
Then it'll be a matter of time before
someone can control any weapon system,
traditional, nuclear,
stuff we haven't even seen yet,
and just point it wherever they want.
Jakob reboots the world order
within minutes.
Ares is the god of war, right?
If Jakob gets his hands on this,
he'll be the god of
damn near everything.
Because of how dangerous it was,
the Aries prototype was recovered
and split into two halves by Mr. Nobody.
Both of which are worthless
without the activation key.
Jakob now has one of the pieces.
He'll be going after the other half next.
As for the key, it's... it's vanished.
So we find it.
If we're gonna beat Jakob to it,
we're gonna have to split up.
Roman, Tej,
I know a couple of guys operating out of
Germany that could get us anything we need.
I'm on it.
Wait, there's one more thing.
Mr. Nobody's transmission had
one name connected to the key.
You guys are gonna want
to brace yourselves for this.
No way.
That's exactly what I said.
So you're saying Han's death is connected
to all of this?
He has to have something to do with it.
I'll look into it.
Tej, can you send me all the files
you have on Han?
Yeah.
I'll go with you.
Letty.
I got this the day Han died.
Mexico.
Check the postmark.
Whatever he was up to, it ended here.
Tokyo.
What are you gonna do about Jakob?
I'm gonna find him.
How?
An old friend.
Yo, what do you think?
¿Es una ilusión o es real?
It doesn't matter.
It's all about how you choose to see it.
Shit. I told you I was right.
I'm Leo.
Santos.
Dom. What are you guys in for?
Driving while brown.
You see that?
Hairline crack in the fuel line.
Air gets in there,
you got a lean condition.
Lean condition?
Yeah! Yeah, Jakob!
That's what I'm talking about!
Who wants next?
I said, who wants next?
I got next.
Dom.
Well, when'd you get out, man?
I said I got next.
Come on, Dom.
You don't want to race me
in Buddy's old Charger.
Car don't make the driver.
Here's how this goes.
You win... you can come back home.
You lose... you keep driving,
you don't stop,
you don't ever come back. Ever.
What do you mean, Dom?
I know what you did.
The day we lost him, Dad kept talking
about a misfire. Remember?
You were the last one
under his hood that day.
A minute later, he was gone.
Tell me why you killed Dad.
Now let's race.
Armed robbery in Echo Park.
Fourth Street Bridge is open.
Clear, clear, clear!
Ready?
Set.
Go.
Too soon.
No!
Line drive over the head of Gonzalez
on the field for a base hit.
Up next...
Place still looks the same.
Just like your dad left it.
I'm looking for Jakob.
Can't help you, man.
I know you took Jakob in
after my father died.
The worst thing you can do to
a Toretto is take away their family.
That's what you did to Jakob.
You've got people who love you,
count on you, care for you.
He ain't got no one.
You get in his way, this ain't gonna end
until one of you guys are in the ground.
I know you did the best you could, Buddy.
But we both know he's about
to cause a lot of hurt.
I did my best to take care of Jakob.
But I'm no Jack Toretto.
You've got to make peace
with the past if you...
...if you want hope for the future.
He's in London.
That's all I know.
Dom.
I hope you find your peace.
The chance for peace died
that day on the track.
Arigato.
This place is a dead end.
Do you think
Jakob could be onto the Han connection?
If he has all the information we do,
probably.
I never told Dom...
I stayed in touch with him for a while
after what happened.
He was over at Buddy's for about a year,
and then he was gone with
a message not to follow.
But after he disappeared, I was so
desperate to find him that I would've...
...would've done anything.
I even broke into a police archive,
but I didn't find anything.
You what? You were like 16.
I did what I had to do.
Yeah.
How about you? How are you doing?
It's a change of pace, huh?
Just as I was remembering...
...who I was, everything changed.
It slowed down.
There's peace for me in the chaos.
It's like I... I need to face the world
head-on or something to feel alive.
Seeing Little Brian hiding in a hole
because we had unexpected company...
...that got to me.
We never used to hide.
Hey, Dom's my brother,
but you will always be my sister.
Funny how we all have secrets.
What?
You got to be kidding me.
What is it?
Remember what Han used to say
about Tokyo?
You mean how in all the old Westerns,
cowboys would make a run for the border to
get away from the law, how Tokyo was his...
Mexico.
No way.
She's ready to roll.
No.
No! No, Sean!
Tell me you are not modding
the quick disconnect valve on the LOX line.
Hey, man, chill out.
All right? It's all good.
That tweak just saved us 0.4 seconds.
"All good"? This isn't Top Gun, Maverick.
You don't follow the rules here, you die.
Hey, come on. That's a bit much.
When you know what too much pressure
in the LOX line can do, come talk to me.
Till then, stay in your lane.
Yo, you're lucky to even be in my lane.
In case you forgot,
I'm the one that figured out how to let
us build rocket engines and get paid.
This whole thing was my idea.
So who are you gonna trust
with your brilliant idea,
this glorified mechanic...
...or a rocket scientist?
Without me, you'd be working at Jiffy Lube.
Guys, guys. Look, it's all good.
Who cares about who did what?
Kind of hard for you to do anything
when you pee your pants
every time you fly, Twinkie.
Did I hear that right?
You a runner and you afraid of flying?
"Twinkie"?
So you must be Ding Dong and Snoball.
Right?
Yo, uh... I don't go by that name anymore.
You went by that name ever?
Like, ever?
I... That's, that's, that's...
Hey! We're up.
Oh, good.
Hey, fellas.
Y'all seen ten-second cars?
Well, say hello to the two-second car.
Is that a Pontiac Fiero
strapped to a rocket engine?
Impressive, I know.
No.
No, that's not impressive.
Eyes up! Here it comes!
Let the race begin!
Plane's taking off!
Go, go, go, go!
Yes!
We did it!
Uh... I'm confused.
Y'all didn't actually beat the jet.
It didn't explode.
- Yeah, or melt.
- Yeah.
She's still in one piece.
You mean "pieces"?
Hey, Jiffy Lube, next time,
will you listen to me?
Look, we heard
y'all could get us some wheels.
Preferably the kind that don't explode.
Is that possible?
Well, the Honda dealership's
about 3,000 miles that way.
Dominic Toretto sent us.
Who's Dominic Toretto?
Hmm.
Nice necklace, Queenie.
Diamonds and emeralds
never looked so good.
Dominic Toretto.
The word on the street is
you got locked up.
Yeah, well, in and out, you know.
When are they gonna learn?
Some birds can't be caged.
Are you looking for one of me sons?
Not tonight.
You do the driving,
I'll cut you in for 15%.
My thieving days are over.
Mine ain't.
You coming?
I'm looking for someone.
Would've shown up in town
a little while ago.
A lot of guys, a lot of resources.
Oh, yeah, yeah, word did go round on a crew
that just turned up, led by an American.
Yeah, he bought some arms
off a local seller.
Rumor had it he was into something big
up in Edinburgh.
Local seller, huh?
She wouldn't happen to be wearing
a stolen necklace, would she?
He paid well. What was I supposed to do?
This geezer was about your height,
actually.
Similar features.
Oh, bloody hell, he's not your cousin
or something, is he?
He's my brother.
Get the hand brake for me,
would you, darling?
Glad I'm not the only one with
a family full of eccentrics.
He offered payment for something else.
You.
You know, nothing's more powerful
than the love of family.
But you turn that into anger
and resentment,
nothing's more dangerous.
Dom?
Don't get yourself killed, okay?
You're my favorite American.
This is your kind of party, isn't it, Dom?
Beautiful women, best cars, best
everything. You know, best security, too.
I'm Otto. I'm your brother's partner.
Well, f-financier.
But, you know, my dad, he's a dictator, so
we're not talking regular people rich here.
No, no, no, no, no.
Everything you see here, I own.
These girls, if you want to meet
one of them, maybe two, maybe three,
just let me know.
They're on the payroll.
I offer a bomb-ass dental plan, too. Huh?
Where is Jakob?
He's inside.
The brother you're looking for...
he's from an old life.
He's long gone.
All I see is the same scared little kid
that killed our father.
That's your mistake.
The spy game...
...this is my world.
So here's my offer.
It's the same one you gave me.
You leave.
Now.
You drive away, and you never come back.
Ever.
A deal?
I showed you mercy!
And I won't show it to you again.
Toretto.
Since my dad is head of state,
it makes me a foreign dignitary
and this place an embassy.
Which means you just trespassed
into my country and attempted murder.
So, naturally, I called in a little favor
with all my good friends from Interpol.
You keep digging around in the past, Dom,
you're not gonna like what you find.
And here I thought my dad
was a pain in the ass.
But your family is a train wreck.
Well, now that your brother's
finally out of the game,
it's time we go to Edinburgh.
Get the second piece,
maybe do a little sightseeing, huh?
Any news on the key?
Don't worry about it.
Our men are closing in.
One week from now,
there won't be a superpower in the world
can take a piss without our permission.
One week from now, your dad
will be asking you for an allowance.
I'd like that.
Whew.
What's up?
Well done, Leysa.
Please. If it wasn't for you,
I'd still be stealing gas in the D.R.
So Queenie treating you right?
Like a princesa.
I'm her number-one pick, you know.
Cara's little sister done good.
Good?
You saw my fine ass in that white dress.
You see how I been rocking shit?
All this crew, this is mine. Huh?
I been around the world.
Oh, I almost forgot. You might need this.
Your boy Jakob biometrics
are encoded to this gun.
You'll have no trouble tracking him now.
Hey, Letty.
Yeah.
Come look at this.
What the hell?
Han never mentioned a girl, not ever.
Letty, Mia!
Down, now!
You okay?
Welcome to Saint Giles'
Cathedral of Edinburgh.
The High Kirk has a history
stretching back over 900 years.
Renowned for its stained glass windows,
you can see the intricate craftsmanship...
We're a go.
Ramsey, talk to me. What do we got?
I pulled Jakob's biometric signature
off the gun,
and the algorithm I've run says
Jakob's team is right on top of us.
Anywhere between 80 and 100 meters.
80 meters? That's a lot around here.
This whole area seems pretty packed in.
So, we don't know where the secret
vault facility Jakob is looking to hit is,
now, do we?
Wouldn't be a secret if we did.
You know what?
I'm starting to think your little English
accent makes you sound smarter
than you are.
Man, can I point out that
a good old-fashioned tracking chip
would've put us within
like six feet of this dude?
But, nah, instead, we out here with
biometrics and facial recognition imaging.
Feels like we looking for Where's Waldo
in Harry Potter world.
Yeah, uh, strong argument there,
Tej, but tracking chips follow the chip.
Before we know it,
we'd be chasing some expensive
yet tacky jacket to the dry cleaner's.
Biometrics, on the other hand,
are impossible to...
Wait.
Guys, okay, we have a problem.
Cameras are going down all around us,
and my equipment is freaking out.
What the hell, Jimmy?
Security alert. Cameras are down.
Damn.
You see anything suspicious?
Uh, where do I start?
First of all, all of this
looks a little spooky.
I even seen these two ladies walking
with George Washington wigs
on their head from the 1700s.
I feel like I'm in Transylvania
or some damn where.
Ramsey, we're looking everywhere.
I just grew a new bunion.
This is hopeless.
What?
You see that?
See what?
The ears. They got cauliflower ears.
They fight for a living.
Don't worry about it.
Roman.
Hey, man, I ordered a pair of Crocs
three weeks ago, and I'm still waiting!
Where are my shoes, man?
Man, we really need to work
on your planning.
Hey, Dom, you should get down
to the cathedral.
Dumbass here just attacked some delivery
dudes 'cause he didn't like their ears.
Wait, wait, wait.
H-How much did you say
you paid for that again?
You know silver ain't magnetic, right?
You know what? Just shut up.
Just shut up.
Ramsey, say we had a big electromagnet
turned up right around here.
Wouldn't that disrupt
all electronic signals?
Including security systems. That's it.
That's how Jakob's getting into the vault.
Guys?
Okay, we've got police coming from
all sides. The area's locking down.
He ain't using roads.
I got eyes on Jakob.
I see Otto.
I'm gonna tail him.
He's heading towards a blue Jaguar.
Okay, follow him.
Me? I can't.
Why not?
Okay, this is a bad time to tell you this,
but I don't drive.
Okay? I never got my license.
I don't know how to drive.
And, you know,
no one really drives in London.
Okay? And that is not my contribution
to this group.
It's you or no one.
Shit.
Guys, come on, man.
I feel like, between the six of us,
we can work this out, right?
Okay. I've got...
Ramsey, shut it off!
Shut it off!
Go, go, go!
Okay. Uh...
Brake is on the left, accelerator right.
Oh.
Shit.
Hey!
Oh! Sorry!
Whoa!
Oh, no!
Move!
Hey, that was not my fault!
Okay, that one was my fault.
See?
What'd I tell you?
Not even a scratch.
Otto, sending you new pickup location.
I've got it. I'm headed to you now.
Otto, where are you?
Jakob, I'm there. I don't see anybody.
It's because you're on the wrong street.
That's my car, pal!
Dom!
Go!
Damn it.
You're a natural.
Of course I am.
Okay, listen up!
I want 50 of the best men!
I want guns! I want wheels,
freaking X-wing fighters, I don't care!
The Millennium Falcon, Chewbacca
if you can get ahold of him.
Money's no object. Go.
Go!
What?
What's so funny?
I...
I was thinking, if this was a movie,
this would be the moment where
the villain has an unexpected setback,
overcompensates without thinking it
through and gets crushed by the good guys.
No offense, but you have no idea
what we're about to do.
And for the record,
we're the good guys.
Me? I'm Luke freaking Skywalker.
Are you sure about that?
I mean, I get the daddy issues, but...
Look at what you've built.
Really? Luke?
You're right. No, I'm more of a Han Solo.
No.
You're Yoda.
- Yoda?
- Mm-hmm.
No. The little green guy?
- Yeah.
- No.
Ah, shit, I'll take it.
Because he's a powerful Jedi, right?
No.
Yoda's a puppet.
With someone's hand up his ass.
So what now, Dom?
No one outruns their past.
And yours just caught up to you.
Man.
There is literally zero industrial
or weapons-grade electromagnets
I can find that are this powerful.
Look at the pull strength level here.
It's crazy.
Yeah.
Wait, watch this.
Every time. I can't believe it.
What are you doing, bruh? I'm hungry.
Hey, guys.
Surprise.
Nice clubhouse.
'Sup, man?
Nice to meet you.
So you got my postcard, huh?
I'm just still trying to figure out
how are you still alive.
Well, after Gisele died,
I didn't know what to do.
I was aimless.
Lost.
Absolutely.
But can you get to the part where
the car exploded and you're still alive?
Like, I'm trying to...
Roman, can you...
can you just be quiet for one minute?
We made plans.
We had dreams.
So what's our next adventure after this?
How about... we stay in one place?
Where you thinking?
Tokyo.
We always talk about Tokyo.
Tokyo it is.
You know, it's funny, Gisele led me there,
and I wasn't even looking for it.
But it became home.
Then one day, Mr. Nobody came calling.
I worked with Gisele.
Back when I was a CIA operative
running the drug trade in Central America.
The good old days.
Gisele was my best.
You can lose an asset at any time.
Bullet, knife, wire.
But I never thought I'd lose her...
to love.
What do you want?
I'm offering you a job, Han.
Here, in Tokyo.
Why me?
'Cause I saw your work with Gisele.
I saw that she trusted you.
And that means I can trust you.
And that is very rare in this line of work.
And all I knew was that I had to steal some
tech from the home of a scientist couple.
But as usual...
...Mr. Nobody didn't tell me everything.
In fact, he left out
the most important part.
I was 11.
My parents would take me
to the movies on Saturdays
if I tried hard in school during the week.
I was so excited to go
I forgot my raincoat, so I went back in.
At first, I didn't see it.
By the time I looked out the window...
Mom and Dad were gone.
Turns out I wasn't the only one
looking for this thing.
Get down!
Han saved me.
Wouldn't leave me behind.
He knew I'd always be a target,
so he taught me how to survive.
We became a family.
"Always be a target"?
Why?
'Cause she is the key.
Everybody's been looking for a thing.
It was a person all along.
My parents didn't want Project Aries
to fall into the wrong hands,
so they locked it with their own DNA,
something we share.
And then, one day,
Mr. Nobody gave me the heads-up
that one of his best agents went rogue.
So when Deckard Shaw came calling,
we used it as cover.
But you got killed in a car crash, Han.
Mr. Nobody had a way of
making things look real.
Pretty nifty magic trick.
Yeah, I've done better.
Now for the hard part.
Keeping you dead.
My death...
Became the best way to stay alive.
What's happening?
It's some kind of hidden subroutine
the system follows.
That's it, right there.
Yeah, nobody moves,
everybody lives.
Jakob.
I'm sorry, Mia.
I was the rogue agent.
Me.
Dom, you ever think about
how Mr. Nobody found you?
Think he just dropped out of the sky
and chose you?
I ran missions with Mr. Nobody
out of this place for years.
I've been looking for that key
for a long time, Dom.
And you just handed her over.
I told you.
This is my world.
Got it.
Got a lot of guys here.
You trust 'em?
Trust this.
You know the only good thing
to come from Dad dying?
If he hadn't, I'd have spent my entire life
in your shadow.
And now you're gonna spend
the rest of yours living in mine.
Only good thing about Dad dying...
...was he didn't have to watch
what you became.
You never deserved the Toretto name.
You think you knew Dad, huh?
What, 'cause you were his favorite?
You don't know shit!
Okay?
You want the truth?
Dad died 'cause he was trying
to throw that race.
We were in deep debt.
'Cause of how he felt about you,
he had to ask me for help.
How was I supposed to know
that car was gonna blow?
A good son would've said no.
And a real brother would've come to me.
Come to you?
He made me promise
you would never find out.
And through all of it...
...I kept that promise.
The girl comes with me.
Jakob!
I will stop you. And that's my promise.
Hey!
Sue. Sue. Ah.
Come on. Come on.
Down!
Go! Go! Come on!
This way!
I'm always here.
Tell him.
No!
Dom.
Tell me what you see, son.
See, cars like this are immortal.
'70 Chargers are designed so well
that if you take care of 'em,
they'll run for 100 years.
Immortal?
Just like a family, Dom.
Build it right, you take care of it...
...it'll live beyond you.
Daddy.
Little B.
When are you coming home?
Com...
No. You know I'm good for it.
I promise I'll deliver.
I'm telling you, I got intermittent miss.
Last two laps.
On it!
Get those plug wires!
Jakob! Now.
You're good!
No!
You came to me, Letty.
None of it is worth a thing if I lose you.
Do you hear me?
Is this who we are?
Yeah.
From here, things move quickly.
Jakob has all the pieces he needs.
Once he activates Aries, all he needs to do
is send the signal global.
And then there's no stopping him, ever.
He'll have to launch
some kind of pirate satellite,
something that'll act as an amplifier,
infecting other satellites in orbit
one by one.
So we find him, stop him,
and then we get Elle back.
Our odds are zero here, Han.
Satellite equipment is
easy enough to track,
but we're not gonna beat Jakob to a launch.
Which gives us a two-target problem:
Jakob on the ground...
With his own private army.
And the satellite.
Which can't be hacked.
Not remotely.
We'd have to do it physically,
50 miles above ground
while the satellite is in orbit.
Orbit?
We need help.
Otherwise, we have no chance.
We do it ourselves.
It's where we've been
that got us this far.
No. No, no, no, no, no.
Do y'all not understand?
Clearly, y'all don't.
Because if you did, you'd be pissing
your pants like a normal person.
Orbit.
That's outer space.
That's another level.
What we gonna do? Hijack a space shuttle?
Put rockets on our backs?
That's exactly what we're gonna do.
What?
There goes my father's diplomatic ties
with Eastern Europe.
This place is going to be crawling
with every cop in the city.
Time to get the hell out of here.
Keep her close.
It's activated.
As soon as the satellite reaches orbit,
we start the uplink.
Ah, damn.
What?
You see that?
We can't have an air leak, man.
Are you really patching yourself up
with duct tape?
Yes.
I don't know if you noticed or not,
but this whole operation is
Band-Aids and duct tape.
Man, this is insane.
We are headed to outer space.
You acting like
we on our way to Home Depot.
This is ridiculous, man.
I'm about to abort this whole mission
and take my Black ass home.
We're literally gonna be
in a perpetual freefall.
Freefall? What does that even mean?
Roman, it means numbers don't lie.
As long as we obey the laws of physics,
then we'll be fine, okay?
It's just all math and science.
I knew I should've listened to my teachers.
Four minutes to launch.
You fellas good to go?
Yeah, we just up here putting
a bunch of duct tape on shit.
You know, that's what Tej do.
Man, please hurry up
so I can stop hearing his damn mouth.
Yes, we're good to go.
We're not good.
This is the same car that we watched
do a test run and explode.
This is not smart, Tej.
Don't worry, man.
With my ceramic polymer coating,
you're gonna be just fine.
You're 100% fireproof.
Exactly.
All eight thrusters fully functional.
Hey, please don't tell me
you're still running launch simulations.
Virgin Galactic launched at 36,000 feet.
The space shuttle tests around 50,000 feet.
Our last test run with this load means
we'll have to go higher, way higher!
If we don't get them high enough,
these guys are gonna be pancakes at IHOP
before the coffee even gets to the table.
Hey! We can still hear you!
Don't worry, guys. We got this.
We do got this, right?
I've run thermal imaging.
Elle's in the armory truck.
And I've got a lock on the Aries signal.
It's coming from the beast up ahead.
We need to get in there to deactivate it
by the time Roman and Tej are in position.
Ramsey, power us up.
Satellite is in low orbit.
Begin.
All right, we're passing 50,000 feet!
Time to get ready, boys.
What we supposed to be doing
with these old-ass suits
that ain't been used since World War I?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Astronauts "R" Us was closed
for shopping today.
Listen, these suits are
just like space suits.
They both account for
pressure differential.
Only thing is we may blow up like balloons
just a little bit.
- That's the only difference.
- What?
We just hit the launch altitude.
You guys ready for a five count?
No, man! I'm barely ready to go
scuba diving in this old-ass thing.
Don't listen to him. We ready!
- "We"?
- Yes, I said "we"!
I thought you was invincible.
Let's see how invincible
your Black ass is after this.
- Punch it!
- No! Tej!
Oh, my God! I don't want to die!
Ignition!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
We're in outer space!
Told you numbers don't lie.
This is crazy, bro!
Man, how much candy did you eat?
Well, I-I... I eat candy
when I get nervous.
I thought you said you took care of this.
Yeah.
Hey. You take them back to
the freaking junkyard right now!
All right, Han, Mia, you're up!
Now.
Letty.
Han!
Not all of us.
Now, the satellite we looking
for should be somewhere...
There. Right there. You see it?
Got it.
Tell me you know
how to work the thrusters.
Tej, numbers is what you do, right?
Driving is what I do.
Two dudes from the ghetto... outer space.
You know ain't nobody gonna believe us,
right?
You're right.
Something's wrong with the satellite array.
It's, uh, interfering with the uplink.
I'll handle it.
Han?
Grab the wheel. Something's up.
I think I can link into their feed.
Something you want to tell me, Otto?
My bad.
Satellite uplink is actually
going splendid.
Oh, and by the way, I have a new
business partner. Maybe you know her.
Guess who's out of the box, Jakob.
But I did try to warn you.
You were never my competition.
Otto, there's something you should know.
Yeah, go on. Lay it on me, dude.
You're a spoiled rich prick,
and I'm gonna kill you.
Oh, man, I am so sorry.
No one told you, huh?
Spoiled rich pricks run the world.
Come on.
Go.
What's happening?
Uh, well, we appear to have lost
our escort and Jakob.
And, well, Dom is making things
a little bit difficult here, but it's fine.
Really, it's peachy.
Don't worry, don't worry.
I'll finish this myself.
All right, let's see
what that beast is made of.
You ready, Elle?
Crank it.
If we can't break through, we stop it.
Guys, that thing is not slowing down
and the download's almost done.
Dom, we don't get out of here now,
we're dead.
Letty, drop back and line up
with the front tires.
What?
If we can't slow it
and we can't punch through,
we flip it and we hit the underside.
Goddamn it! Why do I have to say this?
Flatten these clowns!
Letty, the wires.
You read my mind. Han, get in front of me.
Dom, I can't get to you.
But I can.
All right, the satellite is in range.
Let's power up these magnets and fry it.
All right, take our time.
Okay. All right.
Tej!
Hold on.
Come on, baby. Power up. Power up.
Shit. Shit, shit, shit.
What?
Talk to me. What's going on?
The pressure of the launch, it must have
jammed the cables to the power source.
Damn it, how did I not think of that?
Guys, where are you?
The upload is almost complete.
Why don't you just kill it?
Let's smash it. Let's run it over, right?
No. If we crash into that satellite,
we'll probably die.
And even if we don't,
the fuel that it would take to smash it,
we'd be stuck out here forever.
You got to have faith, bro.
Faith? Faith is not numbers.
You know what, Tej?
You're probably right.
We're not invincible.
We probably just been lucky
this whole time.
This might be it.
But you know what?
If we're gonna go out...
...let's go out on top of the world.
Guys, what's happening up there?
We've got seconds left.
Let's do it.
Let's go.
Five, four, three,
two, one.
We did it.
We did it!
Let's go.
Yes!
Shit.
Not bad, man. Not bad at all.
Hold on!
Dom!
Yes!
Got to be kidding me.
Shit!
Think these belong to you.
There's gonna be a lot of people
coming after you, Jake.
Yeah.
This is the world I chose, Dom.
You know, Dad wasn't perfect.
And he loved us all the same.
Someone once gave me a ten-second car...
as a second chance.
I owe you that, little brother.
I lost you once.
Don't let that happen again, okay?
We come in peace!
Hey!
This was the last place
I saw your grandfather.
This is where he raced.
Did you race here, too, Daddy?
No.
But I'll tell you something.
Everything I needed to know about life,
I learned on this track.
You did?
I did.
It's all gonna be okay, Jakob.
We got some rough times ahead...
...but it's gonna be okay.
'Cause we're family.
- Fellas.
- Hey.
What?
No way.
What's going on?
I couldn't believe it
when I heard you were alive.
It's a long story.
But for now,
let's just enjoy the moment, huh?
Guys, this is Elle.
Hey, Elle. I'm Sean.
- Just call me T.
- I'm Earl.
Nice to meet you.
Mia.
Hi. Nice to finally meet you.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
How much longer on this food?
Like, I'm-I'm... I'm ready to eat now.
I've been eating space food for weeks.
Oh. So Tootsie Rolls are space food?
'Cause that's all you ate.
It was fat free, bruh.
Snickers and Twix fat free, too?
My forehead hungry.
- Yeah, okay. I'll see you later.
- Your forehead is overweight.
Oh!
You drive just like your dad.
- I do?
- Mm-hmm.
Do you know, this is... this is where
I met your mom for the first time.
Right there.
She's watching over you from heaven.
- She is?
- Mm-hmm.
I think Daddy has a question for you.
You ready to say grace, kid?
But I don't know what to say.
Oh, it's easy.
Just say whatever's in your heart.
- You ready?
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Little Brian's ready to say grace with us.
- Uh-huh.
- Nice.
Now, hold on. There's still an empty chair.
He's on the way.
Thank you.
Please. I tell you where the drive is,
the plans we stole. I tell you where it is.
You mean this drive?
These plans?
But you already got it.
Yes, mate.
How else do you think
I stay in this good of shape?
Don't go anywhere.