yeah, corona
its too bad about Dwight, having the Feds infiltrate your house the
same night before we make the team
it’s a little unfortunate
I wish I could say I was a surprise to see you here
whats to stop selling and telling people you’re a cop
probably the same thing that is
keeping me from telling why you're really here
-what up fellas
-hey, how you doing?
Having a good time, - yep a good time
yeah, great time
hows your car?
it took a nasty bump
it would be ready
I also heard that you just got out of county
yeah
you know a guy called Jim Garcia
no, big place, there’s lots of names lots of faces
and you ? you want to buy a lot
of people homes
well that kind of heat isn’t good for business
yeah, well that depend on how you look at things
I go down, I do time
I do REAL time
I don’t know about the other drivers
but when I see flashing lights in my mirror
I don’t stop
Do you know each other?
He used to date my sister
I see
-you're lucky man
- how's that ?
- you're still breathing
to the ladies we loved and the ladies we lost
salute
so, what's Braga "about"?
You know, he just one of us
you know, he's just one of us
came out from the streets down for albarrio
Now, he's shot caller
Boss of bosses
see all these cats in here?
Anyone of them will die for Braga
including you?
Especially me
enjoy the party fellows
the clubs is yours, what ever you want,
booze, broads, its all there
Braga's mine
I’m taking the whole house down
Good luck
something interest you about this car?
Just admiring the body work
are you one of those boys who prefer cars to women?
I'm one of those boys who'd appreciates
the fine body regardless to the "mink!"
Is it your car?
It's Phoenix's car
you'll meet him at the rendevous
He will be leading you
so now
that I know your taste in cars
tell me, what about your women
well starts with the eyes
she got have those kind of eyes that
can look right through the bull shit
to the good in someone
20% angel, 80% devil
down to earth
ain't afraid to get a little
engine grease under her fingers nails
that doesn’t sound anything like me
it ain't
-hey
- I got a gift for you
-Alright
a dirty shot glass, just what I always wanted
I got these from the club last night
there’s two set of prints
here run it both
I know that one of these is
Campos and I think that the other might be Braga's
and you have to go beyond the interpol
so that means I have to contact
individual agencies that could take weeks
ok
DOWNLOADING DATA COORDINATES
Yeah
that’s your third traffic violation in less than three blocks
slow it down, O'Conner
sure thing dad
( tracking system transmitting)
He stopped
we lost him
-he killed the tracker
- We don’t know that
-l’m telling you he killed the tracker
-We don’t know that yet
get the bird overhead
I’m heading to the north
33 56
All clear
[base : black night, I'm angel 5]
I don’t have a tally on the target, repeat
-l don’t have a tally on the target
-there’s no one down there
-damn it
( dialling numbers )
They said nothing about being locked in the trunk
tell me about it
-where do you think that they're taking us?
Don’t matter
we're all just along for the ride now
Welcome to Mexico, boys
there're helicopters and surveillance cameras
that scans for heat signature of the border
but there are blind spots that I
can guide you through the satellite
there can be no margin of error
so you must follow my every direction
Any questions?
I thought that Phoenix is gonna be here
He will meet you out there
Alright everybody, sync up
Good luck gentlemen
( Speaking Spanish)
Satellite link up engaged
keep proceeding north bound at current speed
stay close to Phoeniix
he'll lead you across
( satellite blinking )
I got a heat signature north bound along Regarda Ravine....
thermal imageing window on the Mexico side
is gonna be down for about 45 seconds?
Get the camera on it
manual over-ride
re-routing camera to designated coordinate
Hurry up, you guys been tagged
SHIT..
Toretto, we got bad information
reimaging commensing
I don't see anything
they're gone
get the helicopters to cover it
34.7 sec from regardo ravine
they're sending a helicopter
you have 30 seconds
its on 32.33 +01.64
The window's closing fast, you need..
you need to get out of there
before they send the ground to floor
15 seconds
target is at 2 miles
your running out of time
you need to get out, NOW
there is 116 to 49
There’s no visual contact,
there’s no-one round here to serve confirmation
sloppy
very sloppy
what are you doing man?
Come on
get up
come on man, let’s go
hey don’t touch me, don’t touch me
I said don’t touch me man
-hey look dog I said don’t put your hands on me
- chill bro
what’s up with your boy?
Hey boss man
what did you say?
I said only pussies run nitro meth
you looked under my hood?
I’m talking to you
you got something on your mind?
'70 plymouth
her name was Letty
yo
where’s my money?
Somebody wrecked the car
I wrecked the car
you remember her face?
Because I don’t
last time I saw her
it was burning
Now what?
I'm enjoying what happens next
GET IN
come on, get in the fucking car, let's go
HURRY UP
what have you got Trin?
We're contacting agencies in multiple countries
unfortunately most of them have to
manually scan their prints for us to upload
O'Conner is on line 5
Sir you should see this
thank you
talk to me, O'Conner
-where the hell have
you been?
- I got the shipment?
or we got the shipment?
What are you talking about?
Traffic cams in the area picked up
pictures of you and Toretto together
listen to me O'Conner
bring in the shipment and bring in Toretto
I thought the point was to get La Braga
we got the opportunity here
Brain, the clock stopped ticking
bring them in, are we clear?
Conner?
So this's what sixty million dollars looks like
hey, you need a doctor
we have to find a place to hide this
I got a spot
( breaks squeaking)
5021 wreckless I need a 48 hour hope
out back, any spot you can find
are you sure about this?
Yeah, the last place they'll check
their own impound yard
trust me
you know, I'm thinking when you blew up
your car back there, you blew up mine too?
Yeah
yeah
now you owe me a 10 second car
is that right?
Yeah
now we're even?
-is this you're way of keeping me
away from him?
-Your answering his calls
-he's my brother of course
bullet's not in there
-I'm gonna clean it, and stitch it up
it's gonna hurt
I bet you're gonna enjoy this
a little
Do you want this?
yeah
Spicy
Hmmm
Dom, what are you doing?
- you eat first! you should say grace
thank you lord
for blessing this table
with food and family
and friendship
You asked me why I let Dom go?
I think because at that moment
I respected him more than I did myself
one think that I learnt from Dom is that
nothing really matters unless you have a code
And what’s your code, Brian?
I’m working on it
(Evidence envelope)
( Mobile dialling)
( Mobile ringing)
Oh, Shit
Hey Dom,
- when you were gonna tell me?
-Dom what you doing
- when you were gonna tell me
that you were running Letty?
- let me explain this - when would you tell me!?
Stop, Stop
- You don’t understand
- I don’t want to understand
Stop!
Stop, Stop it, please Stop!
She did it for you Dom
She did it for you
Letty came to me to clear your name
in exchange for bringing down La Braga
she just wanted you to come home
I’m sorry Dom, I'm sorry
you better have one hell of an explanation
you disobeyed the direct order
-where’s the shipment?
-its safe
it’s safe
look, we could use the shipment to parade in front of the media
that you get a few hudred pounds of heroins off the streets
but La Braga's gonna send another shipment
next week
and the week after that
let's use the shipment to lure La Braga out
and lop the head off of a multi-billion dollar Cartel
and how do you suggest we do that?
A hand to hand exchange with La Braga
he'll never show up
he can't afford not to
You got a plan?
There’s a price
we bag La Braga, you let Toretto walk
- Yes
-hey star
I was just thinking about you
you know when I gave you my number
l was hoping that you'll call
but not under these circumstances
what circumstances?
Me, being alive!
Don’t take it personally
... it’s just business
I got some business of my own
get Campos
is for you
was that how La Braga inspires loyalty
killing his drivers?
One can always find more drivers
its just good for business
I want to trade
La Braga does not negotiate
Fine
fine how can you explain to him how
all of the sudden 60 million dollar
worth of product disappeared
I know that can't be good for business
what do you want?
6 million cash, delivered by Braga himself
I don’t like being shot at
I ain't gonna put my neck out again
unless he has got something to loose to
he'll never go for it
either I deal with Braga or you do
when and where?
Sir, clear's are on site
holding positions at a perimeter
alright, listen up every body stay frosty
we don't move a muscle until conner gives the signal
when we get some money you know what to do
well, the good news is that when we get this guy
you walk out here a free man
-is that what they told you?
- yeah that’s the deal
you still put milk and cookies out for Santa Claus?
Yeah
here, incase things go shitty
-Just like old times
-Yeah
oy, you dropped something
-That’s what you wanted right?
- Hold on
he's harmless don’t worry about him
and he's really sorry about, Letty
where’s our stuff?
You mean the stuff that used to be in here right?
-well, you'll see it when we see Braga
that was the deal
No worries
Braga keeps his word
( Fingermatch identical)
2 million
you get the rest when I get my property
- it's Stasiak
- we got a match
fingerprint's La Braga
is a hundred percent
just waiting a facial confirmation via fax
I got a question for you
I got a question for you, you were in peak
when your clawing your way out of la barrio
tell all the agents to move in
we got a confirmation
primary suspect is wearing gray suit
let's move
- sir, O'Conner hasn't given us the signal yet
- what part of that didn't you understand,
we just get confirmation, do it
secure primary suspect in gray suit, repeat
secure primary suspect wearing a grey suite
your thinking what I’m thinking, right?
He ain’t Braga
oh shit
-Drop your weapon
-FBl
look out
get out of here
get out of here, Dom
run him down
Campos is Braga
come on
found primary target
primary suspect is secure
let’s go
get up
he was under your nose the whole time
Braga's escaped
tried exiting south
be long across the border right now
-you have any idea what kind of touble
you are in, now, O'Conner
I was doing my job
-this ain't the first bad guy you helped
escape the law's grasp
as of now you’re being taken off active duty
untill we make a formal inquiry
- what about Braga?
- that's not one of your concerns
- we now know where Braga is, right ?
- customs checked him via satellite
his home base is in Mexico
- Mexico is out of our jurisdiction
... the fact is
the press will be so busy
holding press conferences over the seizure
-we'll skate under the radar
- I thought we signed on to do the right thing
- everyone's looking for you
I’m right here
-is nice to see you've gone with the times, and Switched to an electronic fuel injection
-it looks good
possibly, it can look good
I’m going with you
I don't plan on bringing anyone back
I know
hit that throttle
-hate to say goodbye to my only brother
you don’t
( U. S MEXICO BOADER)
I thought you wasn’t going to show up
you saved my life
I’m willing to return the favour
this will help get you to Braga
Dom
going in there is suicide
I have no choice
you must have loved her very much
( Speaking Spanish)
So this's where my jurisdiction ends?
This, is where mine begins
( Speaking Spanish)
Amen
you ain't forgiven
you boys want to arrest me?
( Speaking Spanish)
No it's beyond that
you can't buy your way in this one
you and me
you and me, we are not so different
you're no hero
you're right
and that's why you're going back across the border
but Phoenix's mine
you got it
oh.. Shit
we'll make couple of miles out if you're lucky
you know where you’re going?
You want to borrow my GPS?
Where you're boys at?
Are they going to show up or what?
Be careful what you ask for
just stop, just stop the car
right behind you
Dom, head to the tunnel
let's use the tunnel
Get out of here, Brian
you sure you know where the tunnels are?
Yeah, hold on
this might hurt
it’s now or never baby
that’s it baby, end of the road
now what?
-Ah game over
-No No No
Come on
hey, get me out of here
PUSSY
Let me see that
hey, just keep the pressure there
you'll be alright
you have to get out of here
I ain't running anymore
-can I ask you something
-yeah
you know I would of won that race if you didn’t cheat, right?
You did hit your head hard
don’t make me laugh
All rise
please be seated
please rise, Mr Toretto
I've listened to the Testimony
... and taken into special consideration
agent O'Conner's
appeal of clemency on behalf
of Mr Toretto
his action directly resulted in
the apprehention to known drug trafficer
Arturo Braga
however
this Judiciory finds
one right does not make up for
a life time worth of wrongs
... and as such
I find that I'm forced to
level the maximum sentence under California law
Dominic Torretto
you are here by sentenced to serve 25 years to life
at the lamppon maximum security prison system
without the possibility of early parole