Alright, we good to go
you got this
l got your ass papa
Lets make some money
everyone in position?
I thought that we would be robbing banks by now
we got some gas truck in the middle of no where
down here gas is gold pa, pa
( speaking Spanish)
Kill the cheddar, game time
I wouldn’t piss them off guys
( speaking Spanish )
Ok guys we got to hit this hard
we got 14 left before they drive away
locked and loaded
( speaking Spanish )
This is all you, Han
liquid gold
ha, ha
were clear
ok
Tego you up
let see if you can get out of
this big stride this time, heartbeat
( speaking Spanish )
More like three come on Tego
keep it real
just one k left we running out of roads
get in there brother
I got it, I got it
( speaking Spanish )
Oh shit
Tear cut lose un-hitch, un-hitch
( speaking Spanish )
Break the hitch
l don’t have a hammer
just do it
hold on, hold on
oh shit
hold on to something tight
cara
give me your hand
I can't reach
jump
Cara jump
I got you
Dom
Credits to original uploader
Fixed by "StRiKer"
( Spanish music )
( speaking Spanish )
The cops just raided our garage in Baricola
they're really interested in you
pizza will send up a flare that will lead them right to us
I said we move out first thing in morning
it’s me they want
and they catch me
they fall in big numbers anybody with me
Han we had a good one
it’s time for you to go do your own thing
heard they doing some crazy shit in Tokyo
you seen Letty
there she is
I here Rio is nice this time of year
the cops are getting hungry
I guess we are doing our job
i'm a walking target.
I don’t want you around when they catch up to me
ride or die remember?
Dom how long have we been doing this?
And now all of a sudden out of nowhere, it’s too dangerous
come on
we'll figure it out, we always do.
Move
move out of my way
I got a gun.
-l don't know shit, I don't know shiit
-give me a name!
David park, David park is the guy you want.
Please
( someone is talking far away)
Oh thank god.
He's in the mood because yesterday was his cheap day
and today some geniuses bought him some doughnuts.
Oh great
sorry I’m late
the complaints keep rolling in
after your little down town Olympics, O'conner
tell me that reinstating you wasn't a mistake
I got a name
David park
is that it?
Is that all you got
David park?
I could throw a fortune cookie out of this window and get
50 David Parks right now?
-its korean not chinese
-what ever
Park is a scout who recruits street racers
to be mules for the Braga cartel
we find park,
and we bust the bad guys
( kid speaking Spanish)
(Speaking Spanish)
Whats up?
Mia I told you not to call me here
Dom its Letty
she's been murdered
We're gathered today to witness this soul...
facial recognition solves the match deride
about 2 minutes after you
crossed the border
I don't get it
thought he'd it show
I told you not to come, they are staking the place out
what if they find you?
They won't
come on
look at you
Letty wouldn't let them junk it
even though it is a god damn curse
when she came back,
she was always in here
working on it, day and night.
It was weird
it was like she knew you were coming back
I want to see the crash site
I just got off the phone with deputy director Lawson
if we don't make serious in roads
on La Braga case in next 72 hours
there are going to shut us down
I know I'm new-bie here but why the clock now?
Because it’s been two years
and the last
three agents We sent in to infiltrate this organization
have come back in body bags
he's moved more heroin across the border
than Escobar did in ten years
this guy is becoming one of our biggest national threats
and we don’t even have a picture of him
we don’t have prints not even a god damn DOB
what's the status on David Park?
Isn't he our ticket into La Braga organization?
Well, we are running the name through city
and county databases sorting the possibilities
we have got over 500 already
parks is an insignificant,
sounds like another jerk off to me.
He's not, without Park, Braga wouldn't have drivers to move a shipment
cross check traffic
illegal modifications, street racing
this guy will definitely have a record
We will find him
we better
oh what do you know, your boy Toretto
has been seen in his old neighbourhood
we could bring his ass in
not in your code you’re not.
Straight ahead
you found something back there
there were brown marks on the ground
the kind that could be only caused by natural methyl
there is only one guy
on all of L.A. who sells that
nothing you can do is
gonna bring her back, Dom
if I were Letty, I would ask you..
No, I would beg you, please let this go
before it’s too late
it’s already too late
I love you
(looking at paper work)
Miss Torretto
I am Michel Stasiak, FBl
would you and I have little chat ?
Hey, this is Forsyth in evidence
I need Stasiak right away to sign some greens
thanks
I narrowed it down to 50 or so of David Park
and I like you make this one
to make a model for each one of them
you didn’t tell me, we got a transfer
you mind coming with me
what?
-Torretto, when did you get back in town?
I am looking for a car that you did an engine mod on
natural methane tank, fort full size, continental tires
what.. what you doing? coming here like this
this ain't your scene anymore boss
don’t you put your hands on me again.. okay?
Say hi to your sister for me
Korean kid brought it in
David Park
Green Ford Torino
don’t drop this on me
almost done
why don't you tell me why you dragged me here Brian?
You know they're gonna capture Dom
maybe worse
I don't want you get tangled up in this
stay away from him
that's what you have to say to me after 5 years
all of the sudden you care what happens to me
what I did to you was wrong
I am sorry
it was, it was hardest thing I ever had to do
I’m sorry too Brian
I’m so sorry that you had to come
into my home and pretend to love me
I’m so sorry that you ripped my family apart
I’m very sorry that was hard for you
I lied to you
I lied to Dom, I lied to every body
that’s what I do best, that’s why the feds recruited me
maybe you're lying to yourself
you’re not the good guy pretending to be a bad guy
maybe you’re the bad guy pretending to be the good guy
you ever think about that
every day
You know I always wondered
why did you let my brother go that day?
I don't know
Oh shit..
BRIAN
Brian, I got a crosschecks on
David park pack I have a list of possibles
what do you got?
A 45 year old male, in a '60 with three reckless driving tickets
No
an '01 Chevy Tahoe
two Mini Coopers a 6 and a 7
and a Toyota Hybrid
no
a '98 Saturn
a '95 Sebring
'98 Nissan 240 with an illegal mod
-that’s it
- what
-the 240 with illegal mod
-how do u know?
-cause that’s something that I'd drive
Green Torino, running nitro, whose car?
I don't know man, I am just a middle man I swear
l am just.....
wait... wait, I don’t know shit man, I swear
I just run cars for Braga
alright all I do is get you in the race
that's all I can do
what race?
Come on man, I don't know shit, just let me up
bring him up, Dom
bring him up
are you here to take me in, O'conner
oh.. Shit
Shut up
they used my friend too.
You aren't anyone's friend
Can you guys talk about this later?
and pull my ass up
she was running for this guy Braga and the things went bad
please
I’m gonna get these guys, Dom
now let me do my job, and bring him up
I am gonna kill this Braga
and anyone else that gets in my way
don’t let go
Conner
conner if you ever....
-that enough
-Don’t touch me I’m fine
THATS ENOUGH
- You are through conner
- I said that’s enough
Stasiak, go and get yourself cleaned up
what? he hit me first
..... this isn’t cop scouts
-Now Go on your bleeding on my floor
O'Conner, do you know the difference
between a cop and a criminal ?
-what?
-one bad judgment call
keep your shit in the line son
have a good time
take a seat
good news, we have intel that La Braga's
no. 2 Ramon Campos
will hold a street race in korea town
tomorrow night to fill a slot in his team
they already chosen three drivers from previous races
our newest informant Mr. David Park
has been kind enough to get us into the race
O'Conner
You’re up
let me guess, winner gets the slot
all right, so these are all the imports that
the city has in impound
-okay nice
-pick your poison
Alright 22 '06
l crashed one of those
and a 27 '65
Okay, so which one do you want
I want them all
the standard issue tracking device
the boss wants to know where you are all the time
( people laughing)
Hey.. what you looking at nut sack
I don’t know you tell me
the whites want the scout,
see ladies the whites already on their team
you gotta be fast
if you drive for Braga
is there a problem here?
No
-are you one of Parks guys?
-yeah.. yeah I am
follow me
See you later punk
you too punk
Bulls eye, come on
Ohm... it looks so thin.. Lama lama
Do you all know why you are here?
Good drivers
are a Dime a dozen
every corner's got a chinga lead a tuner....
that's not what Braga got me
to looking for
Braga wants someone that will sell
their vileta to be behind the wheel
someone that rides in a 10 sec cars but not in a straight line
but to push it, and make it through
places that no one else would take it
Real drivers, you getting this
so, what are we hauling?
You're here for the money which Braga's
paying, so you don't need to know
you just said you wanted real drivers
a real driver knows exactly whats in his car
YEAH, real driver...
nobody is forcing you to race?
You’re the boss?
Or I’m I talking to the boss?
Do I look like the boss?
Papi! my job is to find the best drivers... period
whoever wins the race gets the info
are we cool?
ARE WE COOL?
YEAH, we cool
nah, we ain't cool, man
who's closing the streets ?
No one
thats the point,
please wait while direction's are downloaded
procced to the highlighted route
Are you sure you want to do this?
a lot has changed
-your are right
GO
RIGHT, TURN AHEAD
YOU ARE NOW 5 MILES FROM YOUR DESTINATION
I’m first you cheater bag
Little Smurf
Dead man driving
Come on
right, turn ahead
oh.. Shit!
Yeah!
Re-routing
re-routing
proceed straight ahead
Re-routing
-re-routing
-Shut Up!
2.6 miles till your destination
oops, I didn’t see you
you are now 4 and half miles to your destination
-U-turn if impossible
-Are you kidding me?
You now 4.2 mile from your destination
short cut
your now 1 mile from your destination
guess who's back, Dom
let’s go
nice car baby
bitch
your now 1/4 mile to your destination
to early Dom
(noise from nitrous)
Still a buster
your have reached your destination
good bye
at least we know you can't beat me straight up
I didn't know there were any rules
-that I call real driver
-no that bulls shit man
now go cry to your mama
you work for Braga now
when GPS calls you follow
driver licence?
What driver licence?
Thumb
cell phone number
the prints for, campus
the number is for me
yo nut sack
let me tell you something man :
muscle beats import every time
you know what am saying
EVERY TIME!
Ladies let’s get back in to papa's land
papa wants you
to take off your shoes
wipe your feet
Take off the shoes
So beautiful
I like this foot alot
-FBl
-Freeze
come with us
l didn’t do nothing man
what did I do?
Hey stay, where you going?
-bye Dwight
-what did I do?
Your under arrest for disturbing meth
meth? I never touched that shit bro
you have now?
You, that ain't mine
-get off
-that’s never gonna stick right?
Nah, its not suppose to