There's a big gap.
This feels like the only
route, let's keep going.
You okay?
It's all right, kid.
Never be easy.
Okay.
One...  Be careful.
...two, three!
You okay?
Okay.
Oh, my God.
Never better.
Okay.
Whoa, whoa, you're good.  Shit.
You're good. Yeah?
You're good?
No.
Okay, you've done
way scarier than this.
Remember A.J. Hackett,
Snake Dike.
Stupid singing competition.
God, you married
this sad sack,
for Christ's sake.
Yeah? Okay.  Okay.
One... Two...
Three!
Come on! I got you.
That's my girl.
Ew! Gross!
You guys, get a room!
Here comes Ethan Hunt.
Careful, H, there's loose
rock around the elbow.
Worry about
your ropes, bitches.
I'm fine.
Try to keep up!
Taking your time there,
hotshot.
Hunter, you show off!
Dan!
Hold on, Dan.
Hold on, I'm coming.
Dan, are you okay?
Just hold on.
I'm coming down.
Come on. Come on.
I can't make it.
Oh, my God.  Okay, Becky, Becky.
I just need
a little more length.
Can you un-clip?
Are you secure?
Are you secure?  Yeah.
Yeah, I'm... I'm secure.
Just un-clip and I'll be able
to swing to the rock.
Okay.  I think I can reach it.
Ready?
Can you reach it?
Just...
Just one second.
All right.
I think I can make it.
Hold on, Dan.
I'm almost there.
Just need
a little more momentum.
Okay.
No!
Dan!
Hey!
Hey,
this is Becky and Dan.
Leave a message.
Hey, Becky, it's me.
Look, I've tried to console you
every way I know how.
But I...
I can't help you
if you don't pick up the phone.
Sweetheart,
I'm worried about you.
So whenever
you stop hating on me,
I am here.
Hey, what's up?
This is just the voice mail.
You've reached Dan.
Just leave a message,
I'll hit you back when I can.
Get it off at the beep.
Hey.
Miss you.
Dad, what?
Are you stalking me now?
No, I just don't know
what else to do,
'cause you're not
answering your phone.
Take a hint.
I... I think this is getting
a little bit ridiculous.
"Ridiculous"?
You told me I shouldn't be
so broken up about him,
because he was an asshole.  No.
I said that maybe he didn't
belong on this pedestal
that you were
putting him up on,
that he wasn't this martyr that
you've been making him out to be.
This is how
you console your daughter?
I just want you to be able
to move on with your life.
I don't want to move on.
I miss him!
Every day, I miss the way
he looked at me.
I miss the way
he made me feel.
Sweetie.  Don't!
Don't what?
What do you think
you're doing, Becky?
Getting away from you.
You are not driving. Stop it.
Fuck off!
You don't get to
talk to me like that.
Your mother and I, we
raised you better than that.
So getting shit-faced
and pushing the people away
that love you,
it's not gonna work.
All right, look,
a horrible thing
happened to you,
but you have to start
living your life again.
All right?
There's a whole big wide
world out there that needs you
and believe it or not,
I need you.
Let me give you
a ride home.
I'd rather walk.
Let me ask you something.
If roles reversed,
if it had been you
that had fallen that day,
do you think Dan
is standing out here alone?
Drowning in booze,
grief, sorrow,
whatever the hell this is?
He's not.
And you damn well know it.
God damn it, Becky,
I need you to try.
Do you know
what I need, Dad?
I need you
to leave me alone.
God damn it.
The number you have called
has been disconnected.
No.
No!
Hi!  Hey.
You look, um...
Awful.  Yeah.
Yeah, like
really freakin' awful.
Well, come here.
So, what brings you back?
Are you finally ready
to rest?
I'll rest when I'm dead.
I have something
that's planned.
And I need
a partner in crime.
Look, your dad called me
a few weeks ago.
He didn't know
who else to turn to.
And he said that
you were in a bad place.
He had no right to do
that.  He's worried about you.
It's coming up on a year.
He doesn't want you
to be alone.
Look, the only thing
that drives me crazier
than Dan's boxed ashes
collecting dust in there,
is my best friend
stuck in here with him.
So I have something
that I wanna pitch you.
You're not gonna like it,
but just try to keep
an open mind.
Look...
The B-67 TV Tower.
It's only a six-hour drive
from here.
I was planning on
climbing it this weekend
and I wanted to see
if you'd climb it with me.
It would be an adventure,
like old times.
And you could scatter
Dan's ashes on top.
I just...
I haven't climbed since...
I get it.
But if you don't
confront your fears,
you are always
going to be afraid.
What is it that
Dan used to say?
Don't die if you wanna live
or keep living
even if you're dying.
Shit, I feel like
I'm messing this pitch up.
No, I'm sorry.
Hunter, I just... I can't.
It's like I know I
can't do it, I'm sorry.
Hey, you're gonna be okay.
I can't.  Hey, hey, it's okay.
It's okay.
Morning, princess.
What's wrong?
"If you're scared of dying,
don't be afraid to live."
That's what Dan used to say.
Let's do it.
Let's climb your stupid tower.
Oh, my God, Becky,
baby, I'm so excited!
I've never
actually seen this video.
Shit, I was really ripped.
Yeah! You're awesome.
That is the Becky
that we need for this trip.
Aw!
Holy shit!
Look at your beaming face.
Now, who's this
in the photo with you?
I don't know. It's an oldie.
Who is it?  Nobody.
Just give it back.
Hunter has a boyfriend.
It's nothing.
Just some guy.
Oh, that some guy sure knew
how to tickle your whistle.
Yo, what's up, guys?
Danger D,
and I'm back stateside, yo,
hashtag, super badass.
Okay, in my defense,
I may act like
a total dick on camera,
but it's worth it.
I get paid for this shit.
It's enough to keep me
traveling and you know me,
I have to be doing dangerous
shit to keep my blood pumping,
so I might as well
monetize that.
I'm just saying if
you're gonna be a YouTuber,
why not be yourself?
You are awesome.
Natural born click-bait.  No.
What we're doing here,
this is clickbait.
Excuse me?
Do you have somewhere
I could charge my phone?
Power ain't free, ma'am.
Oh, and do you know
where the B-67 TV Tower is?
We can't find it on the map.
You don't need a map.
You see that light
way up there?
That's your tower.
That's insanely high.
What's with the light?
I thought you said
it was out of commission.
So aircraft can see it.
You know, this was once the
tallest structure in the U.S.
Now it's just this old relic.
They're due to tear it down
next winter.
Becky?
What?  Give me
your phone charger.
What are you doing?
A very cool life hack.
Now I'm just gonna
line up the prongs
with the elements in the lamp.
And...
How's that
for a dumb YouTuber?
Hey, honey.
Mm-hmm.  Did you sleep well?
I love you.
You're not gonna say it back?
I am saying it.
One...
Four...
Three...
I love you.
- Hey, come on, Becks.
- Sun's up.
What up, El Capitan?
I don't know, but something's
up, Sports Illustrated.
Tits for clicks.
Are you live streaming?
No, dude.
Shoot now, post later.
Oh, good.
I don't wanna be in it.
Hey, guys. Danger D here
and I have somebody
very special for you to meet.
Say hello, Becky C.  Hi.
And we have something
totally batshit crazy
for you guys today.
The B-67 TV Tower.
This bad boy is
over 2,000 feet tall.
And your homegirls
are gonna be climbing
to the tippy, tippy top.
But don't worry, Becky C,
because you're safe with...
Watch out!
Holy shit!
Eight more lives, baby!
Shit.
Looks like
we're walking from here.
How far?  I don't know.
Like a mile?
Maybe two-ish?
Damn, it's hot.
You'll cool down
once we get some air time.
We've got enough water,
you think?
Water's check.
Harnesses check.
Super badass
4K drone check.
Selfie stick,
all the essentials.
Food?
Nah, we'll be back in time
before lunch...
Oh, Jesus.
Holy shit, they're big.
It's still alive.
Get off of him!
Hey! Hey!  Go away!
Just go. Go!
Poor thing.
Pricks.
Survival of the fittest, right?
You'd do the same
if you were starving out here.
"Feeling peckish."  Hunter.
What?
That's funny.
Holy shit, 300 likes.
Oh, wow.
350.
I wonder how many of your
followers are serial killers.
Holy shit.
Looks a lot bigger
up close, right?
This is sick.
This is awful.
Hey, guys!
Danger D here.
And we are at the foot of
this stomach-churningly massive
fourth-highest structure
in the U.S.
We're gonna begin
our grueling journey
with an 1,800-foot
ladder climb
inside a steel cage.
And then after the cage...
...we have a 200-foot,
vertigo-inspiring mast
with an external ladder.
Your girl's gonna be wide open
to the elements.
And then beyond that,
we have the precipice.
The ledge.
The top of the world, Ma.
Hunter?
I'm sorry. I can't do it.
Babe, of course you can.
No, um, I really can't.
I'm, like...
I'm petrified.
I'm, like, shaking.
I'm here.
Take a breath.
After Dan died, I was
afraid of my own shadow.
But I pushed through.
I overcame the fear.
I took control.
Do not let this fear
consume you.
Come at it head on
and kick its ass.
If you can beat it,
you can beat anything.
And I'm right here
beside you the whole time.
You are so much stronger
than you think you are.
So shut your shit.
And let's do this.
God, Hunter.
You know,
that's the kind of shit
you should be posting
on Instagram.
Come on.
Dude, this is so cool.
Holy shit.
Look at this.
Damn it, Hunter.
You are such an asshole.
What are you getting us into?
Don't worry.
We've got 50 feet of rope
between us.
We're clipped in
and we're all good.
Okay.
One rung at a time,
and let me know
if you have to rest.
Okay, okay.
See?
It's easy.
Sure.
You're doing great.
Come on.
You okay?
No.
You're doing great.
Come on.
Hunter?
Hunter?  Yeah?
Can we rest a moment?
I need a drink.
Of course.
Those guy lines means
we're halfway up.
Perfect spot.
Wanna know something crazy?
What?
Halfway up.
That means we've
climbed about 1,000 feet.
So we've climbed the height
of the Eiffel Tower.
Please don't say
shit like that, Hunter.
Whoa!
There's the motel.
And the diner.
No way. Looks like
a little toy town.
Let's just get this
over with.
Yeah.
Come on.
Catch up.
That's it.
Becky, you're doing amazing.
Come on!
Come on, Becky!
Okay.
This is the end
of the internal ladder.
One step at a time, okay.
You got this.
The next 200 feet
is external.
I'm not gonna lie.
It's gonna get
a little bit crazy
when we're out of the cage
in the open.
But don't panic.
Hunter.
Hunter!
Hunter! Hunter!
Becky! You gotta come up.
It's so sick!
Okay.
Hunter?
I'm here.
It's just like 200 feet more,
that's all.
I can't!
Yes, you can!
Just look up and only up.
You're doing great.
You got this.
Okay.
Yeah! You're killing it!
You're okay.
Remember, only look up.
What the hell are we doing?
Hey!
Stop overthinking.
How?  I don't know.
Concentrate on
something else, like...
Sing a, a nursery rhyme
or some shit.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Down!
I wouldn't have
picked that one.
Wow.
Okay. Okay, Becks,
this is gonna look a
little bit worse than it is.
Ah, what the hell, Hunter?
Let's just go back down!
Becky, if I let you
go back now,
fear wins.
And I'm not going
to let that happen.
It's okay, Becks.
It's okay.
I've got your weight.
Thanks. Okay.
Reach up.
Okay.  Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Smooth as sailing
to the top now.
You got this.
I actually really
do hate you, Hunter.
Hey, does this ladder
feel loose to you?
Stop, you dick, Hunter!
Sorry.
What was that?
Come on,
we're almost there.
Come on.  Okay.
Wow.
Becky, you're not gonna
believe this.
You gotta come up
here.  I'm coming.
Okay.  Whoo!
Okay.
Hunter.
Hey, trust me.
Okay, okay.
Fuck, Becky!
Oh, I'm here.
Oh, my God.
We did it, Becks!
I knew you could.
Here we go!
On top
of the goddamn world!
Do you wanna try?
Shit! Hunter, stop!
Just focus on
getting a good shot.
I didn't wear this
stupid bra for nothing.
No.
No, Hunter.  Whoo!
Swoop it around!
Seize your day!
Okay. Oh, my God.
How'd it look?
Insane! Insane. Crazy.
Let's get this bad boy back.
Holy shit, so sick, dude.
Okay. Now the ultimate, Becks.
Your turn.
What? No.
Do you want to kick fear
in the dick or not?
No. No, Hunter.
The old Becky
would have done it.
Just saying...  Dude.
Here. I'll hold your hand.
Okay.  Yeah?
Okay.
Shit.
Come on, come on!
You can do this.
You can do it.
Okay, okay, okay.
I got you.  Okay.
Okay. Whoa!
You can trust me.  Whoa, okay.
I've got you,
Becks.  Oh, my God.
Careful over the ledge.
Take it easy.
Okay, I've got you.
I've got you.
Open your eyes.
Whoo-hoo!
Okay, just one more.
You're coming up right now.
My God, you did it.
You did it!
You did it, you idiot.
Yes! Look.
Look how amazing
these are.  Oh, my God.
Whoa!
Next time you are
ever afraid of anything,
I want you to look at these
and know that you have
nothing to be afraid of.
Thank you.  Yeah.
I'm really proud of you.
Dan would be, too.
Yeah.
Okay.
Okay, it's time.
You and I were one, Dan.
And whenever
I needed a laugh,
you told me
one of your shit jokes.
And whenever I needed
a shoulder to cry on,
it was yours.
And now you're gone
and I'm...
I don't feel whole anymore.
I miss you, um,
just so much and I'm...
I love you.
Goodbye, Dan.
Hey.  I'm sorry.
I just didn't expect it
to hit me like that.
Yeah.
I've just been
so far away for so long.
It just didn't really
feel real until then.
Come on.
Let's get back down
on earth, okay?
I don't know about you,
but I really need to pee.
I've needed to pee since
we passed the Eiffel Tower.
Okay?
Okay, home time.
Home time.
Harnesses?  Harnesses.
Think of the ice-cold
beers waiting for us.
Oh, stop.
I've got you.  Okay, slowly.
Okay.
Uh, I'm just getting
a stitch here.
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Hunter!
No!
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, holy shit.
Don't let go.  Yeah, I got you.
Hunter!
Oh, God,
please don't drop me.
Don't drop me.
Becks?
I've got you, Becks.
I can see the ladder.
I've got you.
I just died almost.
Oh, my God.
Did that really just happen?
Oh, my...  Jesus Christ!
I wish we'd filmed that.
Oh, you're here.
Let's get back on the ground
before I actually pee myself.
Yeah.
Okay, take two.
Oh, no.
The ladder.
It's gone.
Hunter, how do we get down?
Shit!
Please tell me there's
a way to go down.
There's nothing on the pole
I can get a good foothold on.
No.  Oh, no.
No, no, no.
Um, there must be something.
No. Shit.
I don't have a signal.
I don't get it, either.
I'm sure there's something,
I'm sure it's just
really spotty up here.
No, we're too freaking high.
There's no signal up here.
We're gonna be okay.
Freaking out is not gonna
help anything right now.
So just take a breath.
We're stuck on
a pizza-sized platform
in the middle of nowhere,
Hunter.
Becky, freaking out
is not gonna help anything.
It's not gonna help, okay.
It's okay.
I'm sure we can...  Wait,
Hunter. Hunter, Hunter.
Look at this.
Oh, my God.
Binoculars. Amazing.  Okay.
We have a flare.
Okay.
This is great news.  Okay.
Oh, shit,
our bag is down there.
Oh, man,
our water's in there.
Shit, we're gonna
die of thirst.
No. No.  We don't have water.
No, think about it...
The noise!
That is how you die
when you're stranded.
The noise that this thing made
when it crashed,
there is no way
nobody heard that.
Okay? I'm...
I'm sure that there
are like multiple calls to 911
as we speak.
Do you really think so?
Yeah.
Yeah, the cavalry
is coming, okay?
We just...
We just have to wait.
Okay. Okay.
Holy...
What? What?  Becky, your leg.
My God.
What the hell?
I didn't even notice this.
Whoa!
Um, whoa!  Come here.
Let's compress it.
Are you okay? I know.
Ow! It really hurts.
Can you just like...
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Can you warn me?  Okay.
Count of three?  Yeah. One...
Two... Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I know.  Oh, man.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I know I'm like,
I'm okay. It's like...
I really have to pee.
Just go.  No.
Just pee.  No, it's
fine. I can hold it.
I just need
to get comfortable.
Can you go any farther?
It's, like, spraying.
Okay, careful over
the ledge.  I'm trying.
Stop looking at me.
Oh, God. That's a relief.
I'm just grateful
you didn't need to shit.
Okay, well, we should find
a way to get comfortable,
'cause I think we're gonna
be up here for a while.
All right.
All right!
Do you really think
someone's coming?
One million percent.
Hey, Danger D,
what's happening, guys?
I'll tell you what's happenin',
Becky C.
We are stuck at the top of a
2,000-foot tower with no way down.
And I shot some of the best
goddamn footage of my life.
And no way to upload it.
That's what worrying you
about the situation?
It's quite ironic.
Well, don't worry, you'll
still be famous if you fall,
as the girl who died
taking a selfie.
Now, that is ironic.
I would like to be remembered
for my life, not my death.
Thank you very much.
Hashtag, life over death.
Hashtag,
Becky's a dick hole.
Hashtag, Hunter says
she's doing this YouTube
thing for the money,
but really I think
she's just like a "like" whore.
It's not like that.
Okay, what is it like then?
Come on, show us who you are.
Show us Shiloh Hunter.
Tell us why you vlog.
Okay, firstly,
you're an asshole.
Hmm.  Yeah.
Secondly,
um...
And this is
gonna sound stupid,
but I do this because of Dan.
What happened...
It just made me realize
that life is fleeting.
And I want to spread that
message, that life is short,
too short.
So, you gotta use every moment.
You have to do something
that makes you feel alive.
That was amazing.
Wow, I mean, I told you,
you should just be yourself.
That was really great.
Should I kill Danger D?
I'll help you
bury the body.
Oh, shit.
There's like
an old RV thing down there.
Can I see?
Just past the gate,
a little over.
Yeah.
That looks abandoned.
It's been five hours.
If anyone called 911,
they'd be here by now.
Oh, my God.
Holy shit.
Hold on, Becky,
we don't get service up here,
but we definitely
did down there.
Remember,
I got all those likes?
Shit.
Okay.
Okay, so we don't know at
what point we lost service.
Maybe it was just up here
because of some
like interference with the...
The broadcast antenna.  Yeah.
I think you're definitely
onto something, Hunter.
Okay, we have
50 feet of rope.
We can try to fish
for coverage.
I just need something
to secure this with.
My hair tie.  Yeah, perfect.
Okay.
Can you message
emergency services?
I don't think so.
But I have
over 60,000 followers.
Okay.
"Help us. Stuck on
B-67 Tower. Call 911."
It's ready to post.
We should hear it
when it sends.
Come on, come on.
Okay.
Let's see
if I can get lower.
Just be careful.
Got it, okay. Come on.
That's the end.
I didn't hear anything.
I didn't, either.
I don't think it posted.
Okay, maybe I can get lower.
What? What do you mean?
Just...
I've got it.
I've got an idea.
Careful, Hunter.  Feels solid.
Are you okay?  Yeah, I'm okay.
Okay.
Oh, my God.  Shit.
Careful.  Shit.
Oh, my God, Hunter.
Are you okay?  Yeah.
Oh, my God.  Yeah.
Careful. Shit.
I don't hear anything.
Nothing.
Okay, you need
to come back up.
Shit.
I got it.
Did it post?
No.
What do we do
now?  I don't know.
Wait, hold on.
We know there's a signal
at the base for sure.
Yeah.
What if we just drop the phone?
Okay, but what if my phone just
shatters into a million pieces?
Not if we reinforce it somehow,
so it doesn't like
the egg drop challenge.
Yeah. Okay, shit.
Um, we just need something
to... To put it in.
Yeah.  This.
It's welded on.
My shoe's too flimsy.
Your shoe?  Yeah, perfect.
Okay, got it.
We need some padding.
Can we use your sock?
Yeah. Okay.
Okay.
We still need something
more substantial.
Oh, Hunter.
Your push-up bra.
That is more substantial.  Yeah.
Dying to get
this thing off, anyway.
Thank you, VS.
Okay.
Hope it's strong enough.
Shove it real good.
Okay.
Here goes nothing.
Did it work?
I don't know.
I can't tell.
Do you see anything?
No, nothing.
Don't worry.
They're coming.
Holy shit!
There's a freaking guy!
What?  Oh, my God. Yes.
And a dog, too.
Hey! Up here!  Hey, help us!
Look, I sent you the
check, man. Come on.
I need that...
Hey!  Hey, boy! Big boy!
Parker.
Come! Come on, boy.
No, no, no, no, no.
Shit!
Hey!
Let's go.
God damn it,
they're getting away.
Parker.
He got the shoe.
Hey! Up here!  Look
up here. Please!
Hey!  Hey!
He's walking!  Hey!
No, no, no, turn
around!  Turn around!
Right here!
Hey!
Shit! Shit!  Hey!
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no.
Do not fire the flare,
he's not looking.
This might be
our only chance.
No, no, no,
he's not looking.
Wait.
Hold on.
There's somebody by the RV.
He's setting up
a grill or some shit.
Okay.
And we'll fire the flare
when the sun goes down
in like...
In like an hour.
We've only got
one shot at this.
Oh, damn.
What?
They're making ribs.  Oh, no.
And they have
really cold beer.
Don't.
These guys
are definitely a couple.
Dirty weekend away.
I'm jealous.
Hey, hey, hey.
They're finishing up.
It's now or never,
fire the flare.
Is it dark enough?  Uh-huh.
Okay.
Shit.  Shit. What the hell?
Why isn't it
firing?  I fired it.
I cocked it, maybe there's
a safety or something?
Shit. Okay, they're
going in, they're going in.
You have to do the
flare now.  I'm trying.
Get it to go.  It's stuck.
Okay, I got it. I got it.
Hey, Randy,
come check this shit out.
Okay, give me your phone.  Okay.
Hey, sons of bitches,
up here!
Holy shit! Check this out.
Up here! Hey!
Wait, wait, wait,
they're looking at us.
What?  They can see us.
Oh, my God!
Holy shit! Oh, my God,
let me see, let me see,
let me see.
Oh, my God,
they're coming.
Hey!
Holy shit,
they found the car.
They found our car,
they found our car.
They have a... A crowbar.
They're probably
gonna open the gate.
Okay.  Okay.
Wait, what the hell?
Wait, what's going on?
They stopped.  What?
Quit chatting,
go open the freakin' gate.
No. No, no, no.
What the hell?
They're stealing
my freakin' car!
What?
No, you sons of bitches!  Hey!
You asshole!
What the hell?
No! I need to see it!
Oh, my God. No, no!  Die,
you freakin' assholes!
Okay. New rule.
If somebody
falls off the tower,
they bring the cell phone
with them.
And call for help
on the way down.
And maybe post that video.
Kidding, ish.
Yeah, my leg.
I could eat aspirin
like Skittles right now.
Yeah.
It's looking a little funky.
Could use
some washing, here.
I'm sorry.
We'll just
keep it wrapped up.
What's wrong?
Dan could never say
the words, "I love you."
1-4-3.
Becky, I...  How long?
Four months.
It was a huge mistake.
I'm sorry,
I am so, so sorry.
For sleeping with my husband
or me finding out about it?
For falling in love
with the same guy.
Who made the move?
Both super drunk.  Who?
He did.
But it was a huge,
huge mistake, Becks.
No.
A mistake is a kiss.
A one-night stand.
You said you loved him, so...
It got out of hand.
I tried so hard not to,
but I fell for him. I mean...
He listened to me,
he was...
He was just different
than every other douchebag
that I'd ever dated and...
And I'd never
felt that way before.
And then you asked me
to be your maid of honor
and it all hit me
like a ton of bricks,
how messed up
this all was.
I loved him,
but I love you more,
so I ended it.
It was just so hard
seeing you guys together.
And after Dan died, I...
I just didn't
have the strength
to be there for you.
To be strong enough
for you, so...
So, I ran away.
And now you hate me
and I don't blame you,
and now we're stuck on
this stupid, freaking tower
in the middle
of freaking nowhere.
And it's all my fault.
I am so, so sorry.
What's that?
I set it when we dropped
the phone down yesterday.
It's been 24 hours.
I think it's time to accept
that either your 60,000
followers don't give a shit
or your phone's down there
in a million pieces.
Okay.
Well, we've got one
more shot. Your phone.
Yeah, no padding
this time, though.
Even less of a chance.
And if this fails we
really don't have any hope.
How long till
we die of thirst?
It's just killing me
that our water
is just right down there
in that bag.
Yeah, with the drone.
We could've used that
to get help.
We could have flown it back to our
motel with a good old fashioned note.
Wait, maybe I can get it.
What do you mean?
You said it was too smooth.
No footholds.
Yeah, but when I hung
my cell down yesterday,
I think the rope was
long enough to reach it.
Are you serious?  Yeah.
Yeah, I seriously think
I can get it.
Hunter, I don't think
this is a good idea.
Becky, I don't think
we have a choice.
Every hour that passes,
the weaker we get.
Besides...
Maybe you'll get lucky
and I'll fall.
Hunter.
Be careful.
I'm sorry, Becks.
I love you.
Okay.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, all good.
Okay.
Hunter, careful.
Shit.
I can't quite reach it.
Just come back up.
We'll attach it lower.  Come on.
Shit.
I think I can
drop myself lower.
What?
What the hell
are you doing, Hunter?
Hunter!
Shit.
I think I can swing
to it.  Hunter, no!
Hunter! Come back up!
Hunter, no!
Hunter!
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Is there a way down?
No. The ladder ripped
all the way off.
Water.
Oh, my God.  Wait, Hunter.
How are you gonna
get back on the rope?
Shit.
Can... Can you reach it?
Oh, my God.
Shit.
You okay?  Yeah.
I have an idea.
Okay.
I'm gonna try
to hook it on with this,
and then we're gonna
work together to pull me up.
Okay?  That's amazing.
That's some good
MacGyver shit right there.
Oh, come on. Please.
Come on.
You did it!  Okay.
Okay. I'm gonna
jump onto this.
I'm gonna need
your help to pull me up.
Okay.  Get ready, Becks.
Okay.  Okay.
Okay.
Okay, come on, come on.
Come on, you can do it.
Shit.
Hunter, are you okay?
You okay?
Okay. I'm okay.
Let's do this
fast and quick, Becky.
Work together to pull me up.
Okay.  I climb, you pull.
Okay? Okay, now!
I can almost
reach the ladder.
Almost there, Becks.
Okay.
Becky! I landed on the bag!
Oh, my God...
Are you okay?
I hurt my hands, real bad.
I don't think I can climb.
You're gonna
have to pull me up, okay?
Okay. Okay.
I got you.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no. Are you okay?
Shit. I thought
you died there.
I'm not going anywhere, Becks.
Yeah, that was scary.
We should ration it.  Okay.
You're right.
Is there any food in there?
No, it's just
your cherry lip balm.
I don't think
you can eat that.
Okay. It's getting dark.
I think it's now or never
on that drone.
I guess we need to...
We need to write a note.
Okay, the receipt
from the diner.
A pen... Do you have a
pen?  Eye liner in here.
Aren't you glad
I brought up makeup now?
"Help.
"Stuck on top of B-67 Tower.
Call 911."
Yeah, perfect.
Okay. See that?
That's the road
where we almost got wiped out.
It leads to the motel.
Let's do this while
we still have light.
Okay.
Okay, just keep it straight
and follow the line of the road.
Let it drift down
as it goes.  Okay.
Okay.
Okay, we're almost
past the gate.
Oh, my God.
No, no, no. The battery.  What?
It's running out
of juice.  Oh, shit.
Hit retrieve.
Or has it gone too far?
Is it gonna make it?
There's no chance!
Are you sure?  It's
not even at the gate.
Shit. It's dropping.
Hit retrieve, hit
retrieve...  Hunter.
...hit retrieve.  Okay.
It's coming back.  Fly it up.
Give it the best shot
to get back to us.
Come on, just get it
higher, higher, higher.
Just get it higher!  I'm trying.
We'll grab it
when it gets close.
Okay.
We've got this.
Get it, Becks, get it.
Nice! Good job.
We have a charger,
but we don't have any power.
Maybe just turn it off
and once it's rested,
it will have more juice.
It's never gonna
be enough. Hunter.
What are we gonna do?
Hey, we're not
gonna panic.
We're gonna stay calm.
We're gonna
figure it out, okay?
There's gotta be a way.
Are we gonna die?
No.
No, we're gonna be okay.
Hunter. Hunter...
Where are you? Hunter...
Hunter...
Hunter, where are you?
Hunter. Hunter!
Becky, it's okay.
You just had a bad dream.
You're nice and safe,
2,000 feet up
in the middle of nowhere.
I have an idea.
How to charge the drone.
Your dumb life hack.
Becky, you freakin' genius.
I think it's light
enough now. Let's do it.
Okay, it's a standard
bulb fitting,
but it's gonna be hot.
It's 30 feet but it's
gonna feel like 1,000.
Is your leg okay?  Yeah.
It smells,
but it doesn't hurt anymore.
It's fine.
Okay.
You can do this.
Yeah!  Yeah.
Keep going, Becky.
You got this, Becky.
I can't.
It's okay, it's okay.
You can do it, Becky.
You got it.
It's okay.
It's just like pole dancing.
Um... Okay, Cherry Pie.
Yes!
You did it,
my little cherry pie.
Good job!
Okay.  Yeah!
You did it,
cherry pie!
All right. All right.
Okay. Okay.  Remember, it's hot.
Be careful.
Okay, just think back
to the diner.
You're gonna want to line
the prongs of the charger
with the elements
of the bulb socket.
I don't think
it's long enough.
I think the back prong
doesn't reach.
Okay, you're gonna need
something small and metal to
carry the current, like a...
Like a screw or something
that you can jam in there.
There isn't
anything.  Jesus. Um...
It's working!
It's freaking working!
Holy shit, my hero!
Okay, we're gonna need
a full charge.
I don't know.
It just has four lights.
Okay, we have to
charge it all the way.
Give ourselves the best shot.
You gonna be okay?
Yeah.
I got this.
You okay?
Yeah.
Hang in there, Becks.
Past halfway.
Get off of me!
It's okay, it's okay,
Becky. You've got it.
Three lights.
Come on, Becky,
you're so close.
Get the hell away
from me!
You did it!
Jesus, I'm so proud of you.
Why didn't you
catch the bag?  Uh...
Babe, you okay?
We need to fly that thing
when the motel is the busiest.
Checkout, 10:00 a.m.
Just a couple of hours.
You know,
he was right about Dan.
He was just
trying to help me.
And I was
so horrible to him.
If there was anyone I
could text, it would be him.
Just to say...
I'm so sorry.
I love him.
I'm tapping out here.
Stay with me.
Try to keep
your mind occupied.
Tell me something,
something that...
That you and your dad
used to do together.
We would watch wrestling.
WWE.  Yeah.
I forgot you guys
were into that.
Yeah.
It was our thing,
you know.
He was always said
I'd be world champion
with my fighting spirit.
I always felt so close to him
when we would watch it.
Name some of
your favorite wrestlers.
Uh, "Stone Cold"
Steve Austin.
The Rock.
What was Cactus Jack's name
when he was wearing the mask?
Mankind.
Wait, I thought you said
you didn't watch it.
I didn't.
Keep going,
you need to stay awake.
Batista.
Okay. It's checkout time.
Okay, here it goes.
Just keep
that shit straight.
Follow the line
of the road.
Come on,
you son of a...
I'm past the point
of no return,
so how's the battery?
Should I retrieve?
No, keep going.
Come on, come on,
just follow the road.
Oh, shit.
It's gonna work.
Oh, God.
No.
Screw your truck.
Get the drone!
Get it!
No, no, no, no!
Go back! Go back.
No, no, no. Go back!
Go back!
Fuck, no!
Is that a storm?
It's kind of beautiful
from up here.
I can't survive
another night.
Becky, don't talk like that.
I just...
I just wanna sleep.
You can't sleep.
The vultures,
they can smell your leg.
They're waiting for you to
give up so they can attack.
Survival of the fittest.
You need energy.
We should eat something.
What?
We're 2,000 feet up in
the middle of the desert.
There's no food up here.
There's always something.
It's hopeless.
Let's send
another message.
We can pad the cell
better this time.
With what?  Give me your shoe.
I can't.  Why?
It's not up here, is it?  What?
It's down there.
It's on your foot.
Yes.
But I'm down there,
remember?
I fell.
You can't have the shoe,
because I didn't
catch the bag.
I bled out.
You didn't really think your
scrawny ass could pull me up, did you?
You pulled the bag up.
I guess you were
just too afraid
to realize that
you were up here,
all alone.
Hi, Dad.
I wanted you to know
that I...
I found my fight again.
Please leave your message...
I wanna live.
I wanna go home,
but I'm not gonna
make it.
You were right
about everything and I...
I'm sorry, Dad.
By the time you see this...
I'll be gone.
I love you.
That's it! Fuck!
You need energy.
You should eat something.
Survival of the fittest.
I can pad the cell
better this time.
Give me your shoe.
Hunter.
God, I love you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry,
but I really have to make
sure this gets through.
God, God, I'm sorry.
You can't park here.
Becky! Becky!
No.
Dad?
Dad!
I thought that was you.
Dad, I love you.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
I just...
I just want you to be okay.
I am, you know.
I'm gonna be okay.
Really.
Let's go home.
Life is fleeting.
Life is short.
Too short.
So, you gotta use
every moment.
You have to do something
that makes you feel alive.
And that shit?
That would spread that
message far and wide.