1
00:00:49,368 --> 00:00:53,841
Connection is a strange thing!
Don't ask how it works.

2
00:00:59,894 --> 00:01:02,557
Our friendship goes back years.

3
00:01:03,320 --> 00:01:05,606
Our connection is stronger than
Wi-Fi, Bluetooth.

4
00:01:06,231 --> 00:01:08,403
The best actor award goes to
Aryan Khanna.

5
00:01:08,679 --> 00:01:12,289
First time I'm getting an award,
a major award in the film industry.

6
00:01:12,809 --> 00:01:14,074
This one's for you, Ma.

7
00:01:14,892 --> 00:01:15,702
Thank you very much.

8
00:01:16,384 --> 00:01:19,360
Before I could walk, I learned
how to jump like Aryan

9
00:01:22,345 --> 00:01:23,813
Aryan? The moron!

10
00:01:25,094 --> 00:01:27,518
Anyone insults him.

11
00:01:27,987 --> 00:01:28,851
I fight.

12
00:01:32,837 --> 00:01:35,049
If I copy his style...

13
00:01:36,189 --> 00:01:37,520
I get whacked.

14
00:01:37,972 --> 00:01:40,102
I don't think I've done enough work.
It's just been 5 years

15
00:01:40,310 --> 00:01:42,683
I still have a long way to go
as an actor and star

16
00:01:44,365 --> 00:01:47,155
I'll work hard and prove
I'm a genuine superstar.

17
00:01:49,467 --> 00:01:50,389
I never compare.

18
00:01:50,828 --> 00:01:53,463
What is better is to say you are the
best, not bother about others.

19
00:01:53,703 --> 00:01:56,284
You're the greatest.
But I'm better.

20
00:01:56,950 --> 00:01:59,951
Never met him. But I spend
all day with him.

21
00:02:01,413 --> 00:02:03,162
That's real connection.

22
00:02:04,328 --> 00:02:08,240
Whatever he does, I cut, copy,
paste, and ditto.

23
00:02:09,073 --> 00:02:10,280
Tiny difference.

24
00:02:10,779 --> 00:02:12,028
He became a star.

25
00:02:12,444 --> 00:02:14,525
And I became his fan.

26
00:02:18,861 --> 00:02:20,062
And something else.

27
00:02:20,644 --> 00:02:22,031
We live together.

28
00:02:23,248 --> 00:02:26,097
In one cinema or the other.

29
00:02:31,733 --> 00:02:33,802
The real drama will start now!

30
00:02:45,369 --> 00:02:48,366
None of my achievements
are my own.

31
00:02:48,819 --> 00:02:51,824
I am who I am today,
I am where I am today.

32
00:02:52,113 --> 00:02:53,361
It's all thanks to my fans.

33
00:02:54,319 --> 00:02:57,198
Without my fans, I'm nothing.

34
00:02:57,972 --> 00:03:00,147
Can't you even get 40% marks?

35
00:03:01,207 --> 00:03:03,193
It's always Aryan, Aryan.

36
00:03:10,886 --> 00:03:13,217
My parents don't get it.

37
00:03:13,558 --> 00:03:16,362
He's not just a star,
he's my world.

38
00:03:17,468 --> 00:03:19,994
But God bowled a great googly.

39
00:03:20,493 --> 00:03:22,441
When God was making Aryan,
some clay was left behind...

40
00:03:22,657 --> 00:03:24,108
God made me with that.

41
00:03:26,646 --> 00:03:29,710
He and I are different.
Poles apart.

42
00:03:30,919 --> 00:03:31,868
But we are one.

43
00:03:33,020 --> 00:03:37,151
He is Aryan and me, Junior Aryan.

44
00:04:03,675 --> 00:04:06,422
I topped up your phone.
200 rupees.

45
00:04:06,922 --> 00:04:08,420
Send the money tomorrow.

46
00:04:08,670 --> 00:04:09,767
Don't worry.

47
00:04:10,044 --> 00:04:11,292
Tomorrow is fine.

48
00:04:11,625 --> 00:04:13,208
The shop is closing now.

49
00:04:14,040 --> 00:04:15,538
Check your phone.

50
00:04:15,996 --> 00:04:18,036
You're a gem. Bye, aunty

51
00:04:19,409 --> 00:04:22,448
Batman, Superman!
Enough slaughter.

52
00:04:22,783 --> 00:04:24,697
Shut down now. Kill the bad guys
tomorrow.

53
00:04:25,031 --> 00:04:27,533
- Gaurav, what's this?
- It's only 5.30, bro.

54
00:04:28,073 --> 00:04:31,538
Don't act smart. I told you.
You're out by 5.30.

55
00:04:32,356 --> 00:04:33,855
Go home, kids.

56
00:04:34,646 --> 00:04:35,889
Don't mess with me.

57
00:04:44,012 --> 00:04:44,802
All well?

58
00:04:45,797 --> 00:04:49,048
Miss Call Center, where were you?
I'm closing.

59
00:04:49,214 --> 00:04:50,006
So early?

60
00:04:50,463 --> 00:04:52,273
- I have a show.
- 5 minutes. Please.

61
00:04:52,694 --> 00:04:54,792
No. I'll be late.

62
00:04:55,208 --> 00:04:56,499
Only 5 minutes.

63
00:04:57,028 --> 00:04:58,330
It's urgent.

64
00:04:58,936 --> 00:05:00,828
I need a recommendation letter
for my US visa

65
00:05:01,085 --> 00:05:03,200
I have a costume trial.

66
00:05:03,521 --> 00:05:05,411
Can you do it later? Ok then.

67
00:05:05,573 --> 00:05:06,479
Thanks

68
00:05:07,062 --> 00:05:08,267
5 minutes.

69
00:05:08,789 --> 00:05:11,192
You don't let us stay and for her...

70
00:05:11,467 --> 00:05:14,091
Her work is urgent. You just
shoot partridges.

71
00:05:14,727 --> 00:05:16,937
I get what's urgent.

72
00:05:18,466 --> 00:05:20,272
Come back tomorrow.

73
00:05:20,963 --> 00:05:22,099
Get lost!

74
00:05:25,558 --> 00:05:26,509
You losers.

75
00:05:40,112 --> 00:05:43,358
Sitting here dreaming of America
won't help you.

76
00:05:44,108 --> 00:05:46,777
But staring at Aryan's photo
will help you?

77
00:05:49,019 --> 00:05:51,142
- Two minutes to go.
- All done.

78
00:05:53,639 --> 00:05:54,597
Thank you.

79
00:05:56,553 --> 00:05:58,248
How much?

80
00:06:00,092 --> 00:06:03,588
Forget it. Can't charge you
for 5 minutes.

81
00:06:05,419 --> 00:06:06,835
- Thanks.
- Enjoy!

82
00:06:12,537 --> 00:06:14,160
Brothers, the shop is closed.

83
00:06:14,910 --> 00:06:16,408
So the action just left?

84
00:06:17,098 --> 00:06:18,448
What's 30 minutes?

85
00:06:18,801 --> 00:06:20,779
I put this notice up a week ago.

86
00:06:21,071 --> 00:06:22,819
Due to the grand Dussehra show.

87
00:06:23,027 --> 00:06:26,762
Organised by the Resident Welfare
Assoc. Inder Vihar, DDA Colony.

88
00:06:27,025 --> 00:06:29,297
AK Cyber Chat closes
at 5:30 sharp.

89
00:06:29,770 --> 00:06:32,928
By order Gaurav Chandna,
proprietor AK Cyber Chat.

90
00:06:33,581 --> 00:06:34,563
See you again.

91
00:06:34,890 --> 00:06:38,734
If I knew English well, I'd be
a computer myself.

92
00:06:40,121 --> 00:06:43,279
The shop won't stay open,
even for the Prime Minister

93
00:06:43,527 --> 00:06:45,504
I said it's closed. You'll get
extra time tomorrow.

94
00:06:45,671 --> 00:06:46,503
You photocopy!

95
00:06:46,628 --> 00:06:48,334
Don't be cruel like Ravan.

96
00:06:48,945 --> 00:06:51,682
This boy needs to watch porn.
He's upset.

97
00:06:53,867 --> 00:06:56,368
I don't heal upset minds
at Cyber Chat.

98
00:06:56,755 --> 00:07:00,531
No porn films allowed here anyway.
Out, you guys!

99
00:07:00,864 --> 00:07:05,094
You better outgrow Aryan Khanna.
Sid Kapoor is the man now.

100
00:07:05,943 --> 00:07:08,301
Get smart, photocopy.

101
00:07:08,733 --> 00:07:11,145
The shop in Sector 28 is open.

102
00:07:11,356 --> 00:07:13,925
- Go there.
- Don't you dare touch me!

103
00:07:15,664 --> 00:07:18,138
- Don't touch.
- Here, I'm touching.

104
00:07:24,594 --> 00:07:25,747
Get out of here.

105
00:07:54,716 --> 00:07:56,507
Let go! They need a lesson.

106
00:07:57,005 --> 00:07:58,753
Want to see porn? Huh...

107
00:07:59,544 --> 00:08:00,864
What are you doing?

108
00:08:01,704 --> 00:08:05,288
Nothing. I let you chat.
So they made trouble

109
00:08:05,663 --> 00:08:06,787
I'm fine.

110
00:08:07,036 --> 00:08:08,577
You can all go. Thank you!

111
00:08:08,785 --> 00:08:10,357
The jobless morons.

112
00:08:12,400 --> 00:08:15,653
They came to watch blue films.
I whacked them.

113
00:08:16,269 --> 00:08:19,924
Why play the hero?
Why didn't you call for help?

114
00:08:20,315 --> 00:08:21,971
But I did call you.

115
00:08:24,852 --> 00:08:26,015
My heart did.

116
00:08:27,433 --> 00:08:28,890
So you came back.

117
00:08:29,123 --> 00:08:33,132
Please, Gaurav. Stop talking
like Aryan.

118
00:08:33,427 --> 00:08:35,883
Drop it. Coming to the show tonight?

119
00:08:36,217 --> 00:08:38,660
Too much to do. I don't
have time like you.

120
00:08:38,930 --> 00:08:41,044
Today's a birthday special.

121
00:08:41,691 --> 00:08:43,000
No, thank you.

122
00:08:43,329 --> 00:08:44,157
Welcome.

123
00:08:52,325 --> 00:08:54,256
How did you get hurt?

124
00:08:55,447 --> 00:08:58,277
Who hit you? I'll complain to
the association.

125
00:08:58,525 --> 00:09:00,803
It's fine. Don't ruin my concentration.

126
00:09:01,308 --> 00:09:05,187
Concentration? You can't move.
How will you go on stage?

127
00:09:05,854 --> 00:09:09,225
The prize is 20,000. Cash!

128
00:09:10,963 --> 00:09:13,512
You won't give me 20,000
to go and meet Aryan.

129
00:09:13,846 --> 00:09:16,218
My only chance to fulfill my dream.

130
00:09:16,843 --> 00:09:19,997
I don't have money to burn
on your silly dreams.

131
00:09:20,464 --> 00:09:23,377
What about your Tuesday trips
to the Hanuman temple?

132
00:09:23,669 --> 00:09:26,355
Doesn't your 101-rupee donation
go up in smoke?

133
00:09:26,708 --> 00:09:29,496
Hanumanji is a God.
And your Aryan...

134
00:09:29,788 --> 00:09:31,987
He's important to me.

135
00:09:33,034 --> 00:09:35,615
Every fool has met him,
only I haven't.

136
00:09:35,989 --> 00:09:37,322
Spray some scent on me.

137
00:09:41,234 --> 00:09:43,566
- Careful.
- If you can't do it, never mind.

138
00:09:43,857 --> 00:09:46,165
My fans are waiting. Get ready.

139
00:09:46,438 --> 00:09:48,604
Listen to your mother.
Stop your drama.

140
00:09:50,509 --> 00:09:52,392
The real drama starts now.

141
00:09:53,276 --> 00:09:54,717
Hold on to your hearts.

142
00:09:55,324 --> 00:09:58,217
You're about to see a performance...

143
00:09:59,337 --> 00:10:01,761
that the Western Union,
moving money for better...

144
00:10:02,008 --> 00:10:05,419
Super Star competition
can never do without.

145
00:10:06,528 --> 00:10:08,471
You guessed right.

146
00:10:08,918 --> 00:10:12,453
Here he comes.
The two-year winner:

147
00:10:12,836 --> 00:10:15,988
Our Aryan Khanna Junior.

148
00:10:53,387 --> 00:10:54,578
Jindal aunty!

149
00:10:56,083 --> 00:10:57,914
Your pressure cooker on the stove?

150
00:10:58,125 --> 00:11:00,446
The only whistle you'll hear
today is right here.

151
00:11:02,420 --> 00:11:03,481
My hattrick year.

152
00:11:03,933 --> 00:11:06,740
Today I'll share something personal.

153
00:11:06,999 --> 00:11:08,729
About me and Aryan.

154
00:11:09,274 --> 00:11:10,840
I hide nothing from you

155
00:11:11,193 --> 00:11:14,398
I'm no ace at romancing.

156
00:11:15,106 --> 00:11:18,935
But when I see her, my emotions
go haywire.

157
00:11:19,518 --> 00:11:21,299
Words escape me.

158
00:11:24,313 --> 00:11:27,884
Senior is an expert heart-stealer.
So I asked him...

159
00:11:29,175 --> 00:11:31,340
to help his Junior.

160
00:11:38,291 --> 00:11:42,495
It's delicate. I must tread carefully.

161
00:11:43,078 --> 00:11:44,535
Don't forget.

162
00:11:45,144 --> 00:11:47,407
The heart's job is to beat.

163
00:11:48,282 --> 00:11:50,585
When you count the night stars...

164
00:11:50,915 --> 00:11:53,900
and yearn to etch my name
on every star.

165
00:11:54,569 --> 00:11:56,814
You know you're in love.

166
00:11:57,730 --> 00:12:00,186
When you want to turn back
as you walk ahead.

167
00:12:00,848 --> 00:12:04,591
When you look for me
in a crowd.

168
00:12:05,146 --> 00:12:07,595
You know you're in love.

169
00:12:08,885 --> 00:12:10,322
If you don't believe me.

170
00:12:11,065 --> 00:12:12,964
Then hold my hand.

171
00:12:13,960 --> 00:12:16,877
If your heart stops, then you know...

172
00:12:17,781 --> 00:12:19,184
you're in love.

173
00:12:22,702 --> 00:12:25,036
I don't have your style, Senior.

174
00:12:25,744 --> 00:12:28,426
But if anyone insults you...

175
00:12:28,689 --> 00:12:30,114
I want to break their teeth.

176
00:12:30,624 --> 00:12:33,144
Mummy says, Calm down

177
00:12:33,580 --> 00:12:35,689
Aryan is India's sweetheart.

178
00:12:35,973 --> 00:12:37,957
But he's a Delhi boy after all.

179
00:12:38,532 --> 00:12:42,893
Come, Senior. Let's show them
some Delhi muscle.

180
00:13:21,437 --> 00:13:25,727
Ma used to say: Don't weigh
the food you're eating.

181
00:13:26,817 --> 00:13:31,951
Don't count the guys you whack.

182
00:13:39,431 --> 00:13:40,528
Here.

183
00:13:41,663 --> 00:13:42,638
Use this.

184
00:13:45,610 --> 00:13:49,079
I feel like just staring
at the screen.

185
00:13:50,057 --> 00:13:51,031
I have this dream.

186
00:13:51,336 --> 00:13:53,697
Keep doing your thing
with your heroines

187
00:13:54,718 --> 00:13:56,426
I've been your fan forever.

188
00:13:57,008 --> 00:13:58,964
I think you owe me a dance.

189
00:13:59,506 --> 00:14:00,714
We'll have a blast.

190
00:14:00,895 --> 00:14:04,001
No one will tell who is Senior,
who is Junior. Hit it!

191
00:15:20,345 --> 00:15:22,717
One last thing before I go.

192
00:15:24,132 --> 00:15:26,713
I am what I am today.

193
00:15:28,045 --> 00:15:29,710
I am where I am today.

194
00:15:30,709 --> 00:15:33,383
It's all thanks to my fans.

195
00:15:34,705 --> 00:15:36,287
Without my fans

196
00:15:38,077 --> 00:15:39,326
I'm nothing.

197
00:15:43,530 --> 00:15:44,695
Brothers and sisters!

198
00:15:44,986 --> 00:15:47,627
The Virat act did not impress us.

199
00:15:47,900 --> 00:15:50,351
The Katrina act did not impress.

200
00:15:51,018 --> 00:15:53,353
This year like every other year.

201
00:15:53,894 --> 00:15:56,487
The Western Union, moving money
for better...

202
00:15:56,724 --> 00:16:00,419
Super Star competition's trophy
goes to our very own...

203
00:16:01,507 --> 00:16:02,963
Gaurav Chandna.

204
00:16:08,844 --> 00:16:10,367
Give him a big hand!

205
00:16:25,011 --> 00:16:27,153
I want to thank my Mummy.

206
00:16:28,192 --> 00:16:29,442
My Papa.

207
00:16:31,523 --> 00:16:32,563
My God.

208
00:16:33,279 --> 00:16:36,197
The greatest actor in the world.

209
00:16:37,405 --> 00:16:38,957
The Aryan Khanna.

210
00:16:56,878 --> 00:16:57,712
Ok, go.

211
00:16:58,618 --> 00:17:01,405
But why travel without a ticket?

212
00:17:02,002 --> 00:17:03,819
- Go later.
- Later?

213
00:17:04,217 --> 00:17:09,231
Aryan's birthday is in 2 days.
And I must wait to book a ticket?

214
00:17:09,646 --> 00:17:12,499
The ticket collector will catch you
and belt you.

215
00:17:13,237 --> 00:17:14,392
Remind her...

216
00:17:14,725 --> 00:17:16,981
how Aryan travelled to Mumbai
for the first time.

217
00:17:17,888 --> 00:17:19,597
- WT.
- Without ticket!

218
00:17:20,220 --> 00:17:23,392
You want to give him the trophy?
Courier it. Post it.

219
00:17:23,740 --> 00:17:25,804
Papa, count the cash again.

220
00:17:26,303 --> 00:17:28,669
Phony fans cheer him from afar.

221
00:17:29,122 --> 00:17:33,550
But I'll hug him and hand him
the trophy myself.

222
00:17:34,039 --> 00:17:36,245
- Like this.
- Have you gone mad?

223
00:17:36,661 --> 00:17:38,118
Control the boy.

224
00:17:38,784 --> 00:17:40,325
Here. 20,000.

225
00:17:40,949 --> 00:17:42,341
Is your spit on the notes?

226
00:17:43,427 --> 00:17:46,876
Socks, in the outside pocket.
Underwear, inside the bag.

227
00:17:47,109 --> 00:17:49,587
Any extra underwear? I'll have
no time to wash them.

228
00:17:50,065 --> 00:17:53,375
Here. Give this to him from
your Papa and me.

229
00:17:53,624 --> 00:17:54,661
Sohan halwa.

230
00:17:54,909 --> 00:17:58,607
Tell him your father got it
especially for him.

231
00:17:58,893 --> 00:18:02,029
- From Chandni Chowk.
- Why tell him? I'll show him

232
00:18:02,307 --> 00:18:06,260
I'll show Aryan a family selfie.
Come, we'll get the background.

233
00:18:06,634 --> 00:18:09,507
Mummy, hold the box.
I'll hold the trophy.

234
00:18:10,213 --> 00:18:11,570
Papa, hide those undies.

235
00:18:12,190 --> 00:18:14,478
- Cheese.
- Cheese!

236
00:18:15,185 --> 00:18:17,724
- Shall I drop you at the station?
- No, you go to the shop.

237
00:18:17,932 --> 00:18:19,680
- Can you manage?
- Sure.

238
00:18:19,805 --> 00:18:21,137
Don't overstay at Aryan's

239
00:18:21,428 --> 00:18:23,551
I've only four days leave.
Can't extend.

240
00:18:23,801 --> 00:18:25,591
Don't worry, Papa. By mummy.

241
00:18:26,007 --> 00:18:27,256
Be careful, son.

242
00:18:30,212 --> 00:18:31,044
Where to?

243
00:18:31,377 --> 00:18:32,168
Hi!

244
00:18:33,666 --> 00:18:35,314
Your parents throw you out?

245
00:18:36,424 --> 00:18:38,786
Keep dreaming about moving
to America

246
00:18:39,161 --> 00:18:41,367
I'm off to meet Aryan,
face-to-face.

247
00:18:41,699 --> 00:18:43,074
Told Aryan you're coming?

248
00:18:44,046 --> 00:18:47,160
He's my Aryan, not America.
No visa needed

249
00:18:47,569 --> 00:18:51,565
I'm going to America to make a new
life. You'll get zero meeting Aryan.

250
00:18:54,010 --> 00:18:56,269
Forget it, you won't understand.

251
00:19:48,175 --> 00:19:48,799
Hello, uncle.

252
00:19:49,133 --> 00:19:50,090
Hello, aunty.

253
00:19:55,979 --> 00:19:57,125
Your ice cream.

254
00:19:58,165 --> 00:20:01,530
One vegetarian meal.

255
00:20:01,935 --> 00:20:02,910
Seat number?

256
00:20:11,530 --> 00:20:12,739
I'll get it.

257
00:20:16,183 --> 00:20:19,056
If you want to stretch your legs
or your back, tell me.

258
00:20:19,423 --> 00:20:21,411
It's only one night. We'll adjust.

259
00:20:29,051 --> 00:20:29,722
Allow me.

260
00:20:30,271 --> 00:20:31,840
Now it's ok.

261
00:20:36,527 --> 00:20:39,902
Let me put uncle's plate down.
Don't worry.

262
00:20:59,094 --> 00:21:00,024
We're coming.

263
00:21:05,165 --> 00:21:06,118
Without ticket?

264
00:21:06,830 --> 00:21:09,161
Uncle, it's a long story.

265
00:21:10,367 --> 00:21:11,700
Let me explain

266
00:21:11,950 --> 00:21:16,035
I'll do the explaining. Call
Ratlam police station.

267
00:21:16,354 --> 00:21:19,233
Let him spend two days inside.
No more WT travelling.

268
00:21:19,400 --> 00:21:21,940
Uncle, you don't get it. I could've
bought the ticket

269
00:21:22,148 --> 00:21:25,342
- I want to travel without one.
- Come along

270
00:21:26,393 --> 00:21:28,152
I'm not a thief or a criminal.

271
00:21:28,696 --> 00:21:31,014
You see tomorrow is
Aryan Khanna's birthday.

272
00:21:31,221 --> 00:21:32,637
No point if I get there late

273
00:21:32,970 --> 00:21:33,511
Aryan Khanna?

274
00:21:33,729 --> 00:21:36,062
Right! He went to Mumbai WT.

275
00:21:36,362 --> 00:21:38,090
Stayed at Hotel Delite.
Room number 205

276
00:21:38,298 --> 00:21:40,909
I'll be staying there too.
Get the picture?

277
00:21:41,471 --> 00:21:43,959
Let me get to Mumbai.
You won't lose anything.

278
00:21:44,292 --> 00:21:47,061
Here's the ticket money. Keep it.

279
00:21:47,338 --> 00:21:48,746
- But I'll travel WT.
- Shut up!

280
00:21:48,981 --> 00:21:50,286
You need a tight slap.

281
00:21:52,102 --> 00:21:53,741
Take him. He won't listen.

282
00:21:54,033 --> 00:21:55,364
Damn you!

283
00:21:56,333 --> 00:21:58,109
Take me to Mumbai. Or I'll jump.

284
00:22:01,253 --> 00:22:04,397
You'll be answering the cops
all night.

285
00:22:04,630 --> 00:22:06,436
Want to die? Get back inside.

286
00:22:06,843 --> 00:22:09,326
If I can't see Aryan Khanna
on his birthday...

287
00:22:09,844 --> 00:22:11,057
no point living.

288
00:22:11,397 --> 00:22:13,723
Don't lose your head over
these film stars.

289
00:22:14,159 --> 00:22:16,676
He may be a film star to you.
But he's special to me.

290
00:22:16,897 --> 00:22:18,549
Give me your hand or you'll die.

291
00:22:18,997 --> 00:22:21,338
- Take me to Mumbai.
- OK! Give me your hand.

292
00:22:21,735 --> 00:22:25,028
- One veg meal?
- Done. Give me your hand.

293
00:22:25,816 --> 00:22:26,611
Ok, hold me.

294
00:22:36,675 --> 00:22:39,113
Is he a relative? Do you
really know him?

295
00:22:39,696 --> 00:22:42,473
Is he family? What are you
to Aryan Khanna?

296
00:22:45,457 --> 00:22:46,434
A fan.

297
00:23:11,749 --> 00:23:13,497
Room 205 is occupied.

298
00:23:14,163 --> 00:23:16,119
Why? I've booked it.

299
00:23:16,328 --> 00:23:18,035
No bookings here.

300
00:23:18,384 --> 00:23:20,575
First come, first serve.
Pay cash, take the key

301
00:23:26,609 --> 00:23:27,733
I'll pay double.

302
00:23:28,264 --> 00:23:29,623
But only room 205.

303
00:23:31,153 --> 00:23:33,488
If you don't give it to me,
just see what I'll do.

304
00:23:38,625 --> 00:23:42,177
Hey boy! Move the stuff from 205
to 209.

305
00:23:43,253 --> 00:23:46,000
Here, brother. Room 205 for you.

306
00:24:17,933 --> 00:24:19,072
Happy birthday, Senior.

307
00:25:00,101 --> 00:25:02,984
Let me pass, brother. I'm late.
Move it!

308
00:25:10,786 --> 00:25:12,613
What a crowd! By God.

309
00:25:13,336 --> 00:25:14,777
Brother, move aside.

310
00:25:22,669 --> 00:25:23,907
The press over there.

311
00:25:27,237 --> 00:25:28,588
Let them come in.

312
00:25:30,516 --> 00:25:32,594
A selfie! Smile.

313
00:25:35,032 --> 00:25:36,090
Thank you.

314
00:25:39,417 --> 00:25:40,692
These two-faced fans.

315
00:25:41,930 --> 00:25:43,629
They moan about his films.

316
00:25:44,052 --> 00:25:47,557
And come here to pose with him.

317
00:25:48,723 --> 00:25:50,490
You can't go there

318
00:25:51,563 --> 00:25:54,608
I'm not one of them. Those FB types.
Phony fans

319
00:25:55,215 --> 00:25:57,082
I'm Gaurav Chandna

320
00:25:57,483 --> 00:26:00,730
I've come from Delhi. WT.
Rajdhani Express.

321
00:26:01,771 --> 00:26:03,062
Guess where I'm staying?

322
00:26:04,809 --> 00:26:05,676
Guess!

323
00:26:08,718 --> 00:26:11,302
Hotel Delite. Room number 205.

324
00:26:11,802 --> 00:26:13,092
Don't you get it?

325
00:26:14,341 --> 00:26:15,798
I'll show you magic.

326
00:26:16,214 --> 00:26:17,796
You'll enjoy it. Look!

327
00:26:22,708 --> 00:26:24,748
When you count the night stars...

328
00:26:25,330 --> 00:26:27,495
and yearn to etch her name
on every star.

329
00:26:28,035 --> 00:26:30,533
You know you're in love.

330
00:26:31,948 --> 00:26:33,527
When her breath is carried
by the breeze...

331
00:26:33,684 --> 00:26:35,320
Lets go press.

332
00:26:35,778 --> 00:26:37,486
You know you're in love.

333
00:26:38,554 --> 00:26:40,226
When you turn back as you walk ahead.

334
00:26:40,391 --> 00:26:41,509
Check the press IDs.

335
00:26:42,063 --> 00:26:43,483
Go inside.

336
00:26:45,102 --> 00:26:47,391
Not you! Don't you get it?

337
00:26:47,730 --> 00:26:50,347
I want to show him my trophy.

338
00:26:50,763 --> 00:26:53,374
I just want him to see it.
Then I'll be gone.

339
00:26:57,546 --> 00:26:58,429
Moron!

340
00:26:59,064 --> 00:27:00,961
If Aryan ever hears that
you hit me...

341
00:27:01,669 --> 00:27:03,042
he'll thrash you.

342
00:27:05,390 --> 00:27:06,747
It's ok. It's nothing.

343
00:28:16,899 --> 00:28:19,508
Mummy sent you special halwa.

344
00:28:21,084 --> 00:28:25,263
And this trophy... your birthday.
Mummy sent special halwa.

345
00:29:24,894 --> 00:29:25,632
Yes, Mummy?

346
00:29:26,689 --> 00:29:27,721
I'm fine

347
00:29:29,155 --> 00:29:30,619
Aryan is fine, too.

348
00:29:31,718 --> 00:29:34,477
I haven't met him yet. You're talking
like a child, Mummy.

349
00:29:34,758 --> 00:29:37,170
He's a superstar. How can
I just meet him?

350
00:29:37,770 --> 00:29:40,084
There are thousands of people
here to meet him.

351
00:29:40,454 --> 00:29:42,800
They've built a 50 ft wall
in front of him.

352
00:29:43,904 --> 00:29:45,869
The poor guy is stuck alone behind it.

353
00:29:46,725 --> 00:29:50,365
Scream as hard as you want,
he can't hear

354
00:29:53,817 --> 00:29:56,440
I'm hanging up. I'll call later.

355
00:30:08,252 --> 00:30:12,290
They say common sense deserts
a man in bad times.

356
00:30:12,457 --> 00:30:14,995
Seems that's Aryan Khanna's
fate now.

357
00:30:15,432 --> 00:30:18,897
In his twilight years, his films
are bombing.

358
00:30:19,213 --> 00:30:22,393
No surprise that he's on edge
and snappy.

359
00:30:22,700 --> 00:30:26,406
On his 48th birthday, he showed
his irritation...

360
00:30:26,909 --> 00:30:28,986
through his gift to Sid Kapoor.

361
00:30:29,430 --> 00:30:31,561
No star has matched Aryan till now.

362
00:30:32,221 --> 00:30:33,728
But Sid Kapoor...

363
00:30:34,075 --> 00:30:37,555
has pulled the rug
from under his feet.

364
00:30:38,124 --> 00:30:40,946
The party guests said...

365
00:30:41,389 --> 00:30:43,170
Sid Kapoor just hinted that...

366
00:30:43,580 --> 00:30:46,044
Aryan Khanna's days were over.

367
00:30:46,578 --> 00:30:48,719
What did Kapoor tell Aryan Khanna...

368
00:30:49,122 --> 00:30:52,130
that made him hit Sid Kapoor?

369
00:30:52,680 --> 00:30:54,398
I went to wish him happy birthday.

370
00:30:54,848 --> 00:30:58,175
Look what he did to me!
Totally out of order.

371
00:30:58,580 --> 00:31:01,338
He's an elder. I respect him a lot.

372
00:31:01,816 --> 00:31:06,004
I always say I've learned how
to act by watching his films.

373
00:31:06,590 --> 00:31:09,290
I don't know why I make him
insecure.

374
00:31:09,620 --> 00:31:11,914
What will you do?
Take legal action?

375
00:31:12,425 --> 00:31:13,330
I should

376
00:31:14,153 --> 00:31:15,690
I'll talk to my legal team.

377
00:31:16,103 --> 00:31:19,491
Let's see what they say.
It's my duty to do something.

378
00:31:19,987 --> 00:31:24,111
So no newcomer is mistreated
by a senior star.

379
00:31:26,042 --> 00:31:27,536
That's all I want to say.

380
00:31:27,938 --> 00:31:31,161
We'll talk after I've consulted
my legal team.

381
00:31:42,569 --> 00:31:44,107
Liar! Cheat.

382
00:31:44,948 --> 00:31:48,251
Playing the good boy on TV.
Anyone can see through you.

383
00:31:50,094 --> 00:31:51,572
You think he's insecure?

384
00:31:51,954 --> 00:31:54,781
He's seen off dozens like you.

385
00:31:55,112 --> 00:31:57,259
No one has touched Aryan Khanna
for 25 years.

386
00:31:57,723 --> 00:32:00,259
Do your worst, sonny!

387
00:32:01,692 --> 00:32:03,516
No one can touch him.

388
00:32:04,168 --> 00:32:05,181
Just you wait.

389
00:32:19,792 --> 00:32:20,448
Cut it!

390
00:32:29,355 --> 00:32:30,146
Great shot.

391
00:32:30,766 --> 00:32:31,644
Superb!

392
00:32:31,877 --> 00:32:33,351
- Liked it?
- Fantastic.

393
00:32:44,937 --> 00:32:47,696
Sid Kapoor! You swallowed
Aryan Khanna whole.

394
00:32:51,613 --> 00:32:53,264
What dialogue delivery!

395
00:32:56,102 --> 00:32:59,684
You've destroyed Aryan Khanna.
Blew him away.

396
00:33:00,680 --> 00:33:02,928
I am your biggest fan, sir.

397
00:33:03,515 --> 00:33:05,218
At the contest back home...

398
00:33:05,967 --> 00:33:08,340
It's my bad luck I look like Aryan,
but I always impersonate you

399
00:33:08,589 --> 00:33:09,588
I win, sir

400
00:33:10,088 --> 00:33:12,336
I've even won a trophy.
I love you, sir.

401
00:33:13,085 --> 00:33:15,707
Let me show you my trophy, sir.
Please...

402
00:33:16,248 --> 00:33:18,704
- You let the girls through.
- Let him come.

403
00:33:19,079 --> 00:33:20,411
Sir says yes.

404
00:33:20,868 --> 00:33:22,616
Sorry. Give me space

405
00:33:25,392 --> 00:33:26,546
I'll show you my act?

406
00:33:26,779 --> 00:33:27,570
Ok.

407
00:33:34,693 --> 00:33:38,504
The mind always outsmarts
the face, Mr. Singhania.

408
00:33:39,059 --> 00:33:41,098
You can ape someone.

409
00:33:41,646 --> 00:33:44,153
But you can't ape his mind.

410
00:33:46,628 --> 00:33:48,674
When all doors are shut.

411
00:33:49,631 --> 00:33:51,361
There's a knock at mind's door.

412
00:33:51,743 --> 00:33:55,060
And when that door opens,
you see a new road.

413
00:33:56,186 --> 00:33:58,580
I have walked that road to you,
Singhania.

414
00:34:00,828 --> 00:34:05,116
And through that very door
you shall walk to your peril.

415
00:34:07,063 --> 00:34:08,654
You're too good, fan.

416
00:34:09,514 --> 00:34:11,360
Well done, man.

417
00:34:13,575 --> 00:34:15,151
Relax man, calm down.

418
00:34:17,679 --> 00:34:19,802
I have the same jacket you're wearing.

419
00:34:20,875 --> 00:34:22,515
That's good. Very nice.

420
00:34:23,014 --> 00:34:25,595
- Sir's lunch break now.
- One chance, sir.

421
00:34:27,717 --> 00:34:30,258
Santosh, bring me the salad
in half an hour.

422
00:34:30,636 --> 00:34:33,029
And this fan, come on!

423
00:34:33,660 --> 00:34:34,669
Hear that?

424
00:34:37,208 --> 00:34:39,456
- Sit down.
- No, thank you.

425
00:34:42,995 --> 00:34:44,951
Sir, a small suggestion from a fan.

426
00:34:46,362 --> 00:34:47,801
Why fight with Aryan Khanna?

427
00:34:48,995 --> 00:34:51,908
Why bother with the police
and police reports?

428
00:34:52,268 --> 00:34:53,360
That's nothing, bro

429
00:34:54,132 --> 00:34:55,898
I'll drag him to court.

430
00:34:57,147 --> 00:34:57,915
Allow me.

431
00:34:58,947 --> 00:35:00,672
Time's up for Aryan Khanna.

432
00:35:03,958 --> 00:35:05,348
- I'll wring your neck.
- Santosh!

433
00:35:08,497 --> 00:35:09,843
To hell with Santosh.

434
00:35:11,008 --> 00:35:12,673
Shut up! No one is coming.

435
00:35:14,873 --> 00:35:16,268
Close your mouth.

436
00:35:18,983 --> 00:35:20,595
Now listen... sit quietly...

437
00:35:22,677 --> 00:35:25,582
Don't open your mouth again
to insult Aryan. One peep and...

438
00:35:26,386 --> 00:35:28,943
I'll crush your chocolate face
with the wrapper.

439
00:35:32,292 --> 00:35:34,432
No fan will look at you again.

440
00:35:36,893 --> 00:35:40,930
Spouting pearls of wisdom on TV.
Look at my camera.

441
00:35:42,107 --> 00:35:44,624
Read! Here's the script.
Learn the lines.

442
00:35:44,975 --> 00:35:46,747
Do your rubbish acting.

443
00:35:52,405 --> 00:35:54,074
Your damn phone never
stops ringing.

444
00:35:58,834 --> 00:36:00,151
Now I'll see.

445
00:36:01,485 --> 00:36:02,398
Read it!

446
00:36:06,077 --> 00:36:06,881
Start.

447
00:36:11,400 --> 00:36:12,390
It's in Hindi, dude.

448
00:36:16,010 --> 00:36:18,757
You're a Hindi film hero
and you can't read Hindi?

449
00:36:19,090 --> 00:36:21,379
Where do they find you guys?

450
00:36:23,626 --> 00:36:25,500
What do you film people say?

451
00:36:26,945 --> 00:36:27,706
Action!

452
00:36:28,073 --> 00:36:29,129
Dear Aryan sir

453
00:36:29,723 --> 00:36:31,411
I'm really very sorry.

454
00:36:31,716 --> 00:36:34,159
My statement to the press
was all lies

455
00:36:34,482 --> 00:36:36,198
I wanted to spoil your name.

456
00:36:37,988 --> 00:36:40,278
No one can take your place.
You're the best.

457
00:36:40,652 --> 00:36:43,982
The greatest, the most evergreen
super-duper star.

458
00:36:45,746 --> 00:36:47,146
I apologise again.

459
00:36:48,477 --> 00:36:50,891
Think of me as your kid brother
and forgive me.

460
00:36:51,526 --> 00:36:54,180
Why won't he play with you?
Shall I tell him to?

461
00:36:54,522 --> 00:36:56,137
Dad, he bullies me.

462
00:36:57,756 --> 00:36:59,748
He bullies you because
he's scared of you.

463
00:36:59,952 --> 00:37:02,485
He thinks you'll win. We'll cheat!

464
00:37:02,977 --> 00:37:04,873
- Dhruv, let's play.
- Dad, come on.

465
00:37:05,048 --> 00:37:06,542
Play with Isha. I've trained her.

466
00:37:11,288 --> 00:37:13,906
- I am so sorry.
- Dad, you made me lose a point.

467
00:37:14,740 --> 00:37:16,902
Now she's ahead of you.
Try and win from her

468
00:37:19,792 --> 00:37:23,396
I'm glad Sid realised his mistake.
He's a great guy. Young and new.

469
00:37:23,781 --> 00:37:25,516
Glad it got sorted.

470
00:37:28,097 --> 00:37:30,371
Ladies and gentlemen,
last point, next point.

471
00:37:31,283 --> 00:37:33,726
Nothing is sorted, it's a game.

472
00:37:35,011 --> 00:37:38,042
Apology, say sorry - it's all a game.

473
00:37:38,467 --> 00:37:41,344
You should've controlled yourself

474
00:37:41,569 --> 00:37:42,878
I tried very hard

475
00:37:43,093 --> 00:37:45,008
I gave him one slap. More a pat.

476
00:37:46,694 --> 00:37:48,667
See the scandal it's created.

477
00:37:49,593 --> 00:37:52,347
If someone comes to my house,
drinks my expensive wine.

478
00:37:52,660 --> 00:37:55,410
Flirts with my wife. Must I just
stand by and watch?

479
00:37:56,560 --> 00:37:58,055
You have no time.

480
00:37:58,553 --> 00:38:00,245
Let someone else flirt with me.

481
00:38:01,138 --> 00:38:02,970
Actually you're right.

482
00:38:04,926 --> 00:38:06,632
But not this moron.

483
00:38:08,486 --> 00:38:11,351
The video has gone viral.
Social media is abuzz.

484
00:38:12,162 --> 00:38:15,540
Join us for the stock market news
after this short break

485
00:38:38,184 --> 00:38:39,821
Aryan, wake up!

486
00:38:40,932 --> 00:38:42,158
What happened?

487
00:38:42,394 --> 00:38:43,940
Did you sleep here all night?

488
00:38:44,787 --> 00:38:47,966
I was reading a script. It was
so good that I dozed off

489
00:38:49,813 --> 00:38:52,336
Sunaina is here. She has something
to wake you up with.

490
00:38:52,628 --> 00:38:53,669
Good morning, Aryan.

491
00:38:53,919 --> 00:38:55,043
It's too early, Sunaina

492
00:38:55,244 --> 00:38:58,275
I know. I'm really sorry.
I have to tell you something.

493
00:38:58,525 --> 00:39:00,465
- Are you pregnant?
- Shut up, Aryan.

494
00:39:02,077 --> 00:39:02,785
See this.

495
00:39:03,211 --> 00:39:06,204
Come on. Look here and say
your lines. Hurry.

496
00:39:07,232 --> 00:39:08,066
Dear Aryan sir.

497
00:39:08,306 --> 00:39:10,210
Look here. Look at the camera.

498
00:39:12,102 --> 00:39:13,864
Ok. I'll do it.

499
00:39:15,883 --> 00:39:17,728
- Come on.
- Did Aryan send you?

500
00:39:18,066 --> 00:39:21,538
Aryan has nothing to do with it.
Do as you're told. The camera.

501
00:39:22,514 --> 00:39:25,627
If you want cash, take it.
Just let me go.

502
00:39:26,827 --> 00:39:28,935
Cash? I'll give you cash.

503
00:39:29,325 --> 00:39:31,081
Stop! I'll do it.

504
00:39:31,921 --> 00:39:33,837
What will you do? Scum!

505
00:39:53,366 --> 00:39:54,135
A fan.

506
00:39:55,253 --> 00:39:57,168
Calls himself Junior Aryan Khanna.

507
00:39:57,918 --> 00:39:59,249
He sent a message.

508
00:39:59,708 --> 00:40:02,955
A small birthday gift to the love
of my life, Senior Aryan Khanna.

509
00:40:04,099 --> 00:40:07,704
Call me once to thank me.
My life will be set.

510
00:40:18,023 --> 00:40:18,647
Hello.

511
00:40:21,186 --> 00:40:23,517
Junior Aryan Khanna?

512
00:40:24,308 --> 00:40:25,848
You calling from Aryan's house?

513
00:40:26,764 --> 00:40:27,388
Yes.

514
00:40:28,929 --> 00:40:32,591
Where is Senior? Aryan Khanna?

515
00:40:33,214 --> 00:40:36,629
He's busy right now. He asked me
to call you.

516
00:40:37,004 --> 00:40:40,292
How come he's so busy?
No time to talk to his Junior?

517
00:40:40,833 --> 00:40:42,206
I did so much for him.

518
00:40:42,676 --> 00:40:45,038
I came to the house on his birthday,
The crowd...

519
00:40:45,323 --> 00:40:46,702
Yeah, yeah, hello

520
00:40:50,440 --> 00:40:51,197
Aryan...

521
00:40:54,183 --> 00:40:55,376
Aryan Khanna?

522
00:40:56,171 --> 00:40:58,940
Gaurav this side.
Your fan, your Junior.

523
00:41:00,147 --> 00:41:01,062
Where are you?

524
00:41:02,961 --> 00:41:03,894
Just guess.

525
00:41:08,436 --> 00:41:10,637
Delite hotel, in your room.

526
00:41:12,404 --> 00:41:14,799
Room no. 205. Charni Road.
Remember?

527
00:41:16,244 --> 00:41:19,539
But if you're calling to say
thank you, it won't do.

528
00:41:20,004 --> 00:41:22,083
I deserve a hug from my brother.

529
00:41:24,190 --> 00:41:25,668
- You want to see me?
- Sure

530
00:41:25,908 --> 00:41:27,995
I made a big scandal just to meet you.

531
00:41:28,706 --> 00:41:32,343
Wait there. I'll send a car to
pick you up.

532
00:41:34,849 --> 00:41:35,653
Done, Senior.

533
00:41:36,545 --> 00:41:37,798
Thank you!

534
00:41:44,706 --> 00:41:46,184
Mind blasting.

535
00:41:47,805 --> 00:41:48,640
Really?

536
00:41:49,275 --> 00:41:51,286
Go by taxi.

537
00:41:51,767 --> 00:41:55,150
You're going to Aryan Khanna's.
Don't go by auto-rickshaw.

538
00:41:55,383 --> 00:41:58,188
He's sending me his personal car.

539
00:41:58,421 --> 00:41:59,869
He's invited me home.

540
00:42:00,566 --> 00:42:02,187
Don't forget to take pictures.

541
00:42:02,576 --> 00:42:06,539
If he offers you any food, no
pouncing on it like a pauper.

542
00:42:06,935 --> 00:42:11,232
Food? I'm not going for the food.
I'm going there to hug him.

543
00:42:11,495 --> 00:42:15,764
Tell him to wear the clothes I had
made for him at Diwali.

544
00:42:16,349 --> 00:42:20,136
- Make sure he takes the trophy.
- As though he wouldn't.

545
00:42:22,208 --> 00:42:25,179
- Say hello from me.
- And me, too.

546
00:42:25,524 --> 00:42:26,327
Ok. I'll tell him.

547
00:42:26,532 --> 00:42:29,011
Phone me once you've met him.

548
00:42:29,289 --> 00:42:31,863
The car's here. Call you later.

549
00:42:33,475 --> 00:42:34,578
The car is there.

550
00:42:39,693 --> 00:42:40,557
Hello.

551
00:42:47,428 --> 00:42:48,380
Are you the driver?

552
00:42:49,233 --> 00:42:50,503
Junior Aryan Khanna?

553
00:42:51,300 --> 00:42:53,905
- Did you act smart with Sid Kapoor?
- No.

554
00:42:55,885 --> 00:42:57,111
You're mistaken.

555
00:42:58,645 --> 00:42:59,859
Did Sid Kapoor send you?

556
00:43:00,241 --> 00:43:01,957
I'll tell you later. Come

557
00:43:02,407 --> 00:43:05,310
I'm meeting Aryan.
I won't go anywhere.

558
00:43:05,581 --> 00:43:08,600
- Like hell you won't.
- I won't come.

559
00:43:10,432 --> 00:43:11,824
Don't touch me.

560
00:43:14,008 --> 00:43:14,789
No touching.

561
00:43:22,499 --> 00:43:23,419
Let me go!

562
00:45:38,418 --> 00:45:39,262
Stop!

563
00:46:00,919 --> 00:46:02,006
Try catching me!

564
00:46:03,843 --> 00:46:07,421
- Stop! You rascal.
- Please don't hit me.

565
00:46:11,813 --> 00:46:13,445
Don't hit hard. We have orders.

566
00:46:21,907 --> 00:46:22,903
Let's go.

567
00:46:24,024 --> 00:46:26,314
Let me call Aryan Khanna.

568
00:46:27,021 --> 00:46:28,074
Where are you taking me?

569
00:46:34,888 --> 00:46:36,886
Sid Kapoor is evil. Don't get
mixed up with him.

570
00:46:37,178 --> 00:46:38,107
Shut up!

571
00:46:38,370 --> 00:46:41,964
I did it for Aryan Khanna.
His problem is my problem.

572
00:46:46,002 --> 00:46:48,874
If Aryan hears about this...

573
00:46:49,166 --> 00:46:50,852
he'll skin you alive.

574
00:46:51,996 --> 00:46:53,412
Stop!

575
00:46:55,326 --> 00:46:59,031
Think carefully. We'll be back.
Let's go.

576
00:47:26,836 --> 00:47:28,418
Good evening, sir. Come in.

577
00:47:43,545 --> 00:47:46,025
We asked him why he made the video.

578
00:47:46,882 --> 00:47:48,689
He says he'll talk only to you.

579
00:47:49,156 --> 00:47:51,917
You told us to go easy on him.

580
00:47:52,600 --> 00:47:54,601
- Hardly touched him.
- Thank you.

581
00:47:55,345 --> 00:47:57,056
- Usman.
- Yes, sir?

582
00:47:59,005 --> 00:48:00,774
This is for his expenses.

583
00:48:01,195 --> 00:48:02,530
Keep him here for 2 days.

584
00:48:02,792 --> 00:48:05,080
Get him a ticket to Delhi.
Take him to the station.

585
00:48:05,336 --> 00:48:08,045
As I said, don't beat him up
too badly.

586
00:48:08,786 --> 00:48:09,821
Just enough to scare him.

587
00:48:10,467 --> 00:48:12,333
No one must hear about this.

588
00:48:13,205 --> 00:48:16,901
No police record, no video statement.
Please.

589
00:48:17,234 --> 00:48:18,410
Sure, sir.

590
00:48:18,959 --> 00:48:20,491
Where is he?

591
00:48:22,373 --> 00:48:24,067
I want to meet him alone.

592
00:48:25,478 --> 00:48:26,903
- You stay here.
- Yeah.

593
00:48:40,212 --> 00:48:41,052
Gaurav.

594
00:49:03,390 --> 00:49:04,310
Senior.

595
00:49:04,782 --> 00:49:05,870
You're here.

596
00:49:07,536 --> 00:49:09,384
I knew you'd come.

597
00:49:10,216 --> 00:49:12,672
They hit me and hit me.

598
00:49:13,088 --> 00:49:15,170
They broke my bones.

599
00:49:18,369 --> 00:49:19,996
I protected my face.

600
00:49:20,747 --> 00:49:23,661
It's Aryan Khanna's face.
Nothing must happen to it.

601
00:49:30,612 --> 00:49:33,316
See? Same to same.

602
00:49:35,607 --> 00:49:38,438
Everyone calls me Junior
Aryan Khanna. But I say...

603
00:49:38,922 --> 00:49:40,075
there's only one Aryan Khanna.

604
00:49:42,769 --> 00:49:43,790
Relax.

605
00:49:46,097 --> 00:49:46,846
It's ok.

606
00:49:52,785 --> 00:49:55,438
I impersonate you at the yearly
Super Star competition.

607
00:49:57,274 --> 00:49:58,330
Always win first prize.

608
00:50:01,770 --> 00:50:04,165
The bastards took my bag.
My trophy was in it.

609
00:50:04,819 --> 00:50:06,067
I brought it to show you.

610
00:50:10,697 --> 00:50:12,279
I could show you my act

611
00:50:23,731 --> 00:50:25,807
I'm nervous in front of you.

612
00:50:26,761 --> 00:50:28,316
It's all right. Sit.

613
00:50:28,892 --> 00:50:33,133
No audience here. Their screaming
and cheering helps.

614
00:50:33,507 --> 00:50:35,215
- Are you from Delhi?
- West Delhi.

615
00:50:35,674 --> 00:50:37,379
You're from Rajender Nagar,
I'm from Inder Vihar.

616
00:50:37,589 --> 00:50:39,821
Two traffic lights from the TV tower.
Near DAV Park.

617
00:50:40,452 --> 00:50:41,874
Listen carefully.

618
00:50:42,906 --> 00:50:45,474
You did something nasty.

619
00:50:47,023 --> 00:50:48,007
It's a crime.

620
00:50:49,256 --> 00:50:52,881
A crime in the eyes of the law.
Love in your eyes, no?

621
00:50:53,266 --> 00:50:55,682
Not love, it's stupidity.

622
00:50:58,385 --> 00:50:59,731
Do you have family?

623
00:51:00,185 --> 00:51:02,188
There's Papa, Mummy.

624
00:51:03,054 --> 00:51:04,227
And you, too.

625
00:51:04,818 --> 00:51:06,437
Have you thought what
your parents would say?

626
00:51:06,757 --> 00:51:09,347
They'd be sad seeing you
in that sadistic video.

627
00:51:09,846 --> 00:51:12,843
Why would we show it to them?
It was for you.

628
00:51:13,495 --> 00:51:14,925
Did you like my birthday gift?

629
00:51:15,638 --> 00:51:18,587
Sid Kapoor? I beat the crap
out of him.

630
00:51:21,309 --> 00:51:25,157
I don't understand how the cops
discovered our little secret.

631
00:51:26,639 --> 00:51:27,537
Our?

632
00:51:30,799 --> 00:51:33,198
There is no our between
you and me.

633
00:51:34,004 --> 00:51:36,168
The police brought you here
on my orders.

634
00:51:37,442 --> 00:51:39,478
You made a mistake. You
had to be punished.

635
00:51:39,848 --> 00:51:42,060
So you won't mess up again.

636
00:51:45,393 --> 00:51:48,844
On your orders? I did so much for you.

637
00:51:52,522 --> 00:51:54,538
Who are you to do anything
for me?

638
00:51:57,966 --> 00:51:59,126
I'm your fan.

639
00:52:00,871 --> 00:52:03,413
- You're my star.
- Fan? So you do as you please?

640
00:52:04,113 --> 00:52:06,651
Thrash people? Murder?

641
00:52:07,950 --> 00:52:11,409
If need be, I could murder for you.

642
00:52:15,461 --> 00:52:16,722
You're not my fan.

643
00:52:18,936 --> 00:52:20,230
Don't say that.

644
00:52:21,187 --> 00:52:23,019
I risked my life to meet you.

645
00:52:23,851 --> 00:52:27,050
I hit Sid Kapoor a little, so you'd
meet me. What did I want...

646
00:52:28,014 --> 00:52:28,888
in return?

647
00:52:30,053 --> 00:52:33,342
To see you, a few photos,
an autograph. That's all.

648
00:52:35,525 --> 00:52:38,772
- Can't you spare 5 min of your life?
- It's my life.

649
00:52:40,093 --> 00:52:42,749
Why must I give you even
five seconds?

650
00:53:08,551 --> 00:53:11,776
I am who I am today,
where I am today.

651
00:53:13,587 --> 00:53:14,550
My stardom.

652
00:53:16,673 --> 00:53:19,004
It's all thanks to my fans.

653
00:53:22,132 --> 00:53:23,749
If it weren't for my fans...

654
00:53:25,082 --> 00:53:26,247
I'd be nothing.

655
00:53:39,863 --> 00:53:42,605
Gaurav makes Aryan.

656
00:53:44,770 --> 00:53:45,936
Without Gaurav...

657
00:53:47,320 --> 00:53:48,516
Aryan is nothing.

658
00:53:52,332 --> 00:53:53,928
Now you listen carefully.

659
00:53:54,560 --> 00:53:57,882
When the police let you go,
go straight to Delhi, get it?

660
00:53:58,725 --> 00:54:00,060
I'll forget all about Gaurav.

661
00:54:00,352 --> 00:54:02,957
And you forget you ever met Aryan.

662
00:54:05,064 --> 00:54:07,497
Stay in your life.
I stay in mine.

663
00:54:09,539 --> 00:54:12,273
This is your final warning. Ok.

664
00:54:26,233 --> 00:54:27,187
Forget it.

665
00:54:28,064 --> 00:54:29,444
You won't understand.

666
00:55:43,184 --> 00:55:44,101
Yes, Mummy

667
00:55:44,641 --> 00:55:45,558
I'll be home soon.

668
00:55:45,762 --> 00:55:46,289
Everything ok?

669
00:55:46,524 --> 00:55:47,388
Everything is fine.

670
00:55:47,646 --> 00:55:48,661
Why didn't you take my call?

671
00:55:48,943 --> 00:55:50,190
I was busy.

672
00:55:50,491 --> 00:55:51,788
Gaurav, we're worried about you.

673
00:55:52,072 --> 00:55:52,870
Don't worry.

674
00:55:53,090 --> 00:55:54,465
You'll come home soon?

675
00:55:54,746 --> 00:55:56,390
Tell Papa to mind the Cyber Cafe.

676
00:55:56,674 --> 00:55:57,585
Are you eating properly?

677
00:55:57,873 --> 00:55:59,626
The food is fine here.

678
00:56:02,873 --> 00:56:03,914
Thank you.

679
00:57:04,163 --> 00:57:05,836
Come, hero. Sir wants you.

680
00:57:08,995 --> 00:57:13,969
Whatever happened has happened.
Put it behind you. Right?

681
00:57:14,441 --> 00:57:17,120
Thank you, brother. I made
a mistake. Sorry.

682
00:57:48,583 --> 00:57:49,360
Gaurav!

683
00:57:52,258 --> 00:57:54,394
Did you hug Aryan Khanna?

684
00:58:07,648 --> 00:58:10,687
Didn't he meet you?
Didn't spare 5 minutes?

685
00:58:11,059 --> 00:58:12,768
Don't you feel bad.

686
00:58:13,092 --> 00:58:15,849
It's not my loss. It's his.

687
00:58:16,681 --> 00:58:19,803
He's happy where he is.
I'm happy where I am.

688
00:58:23,219 --> 00:58:25,214
Mummy, make me some
rice and beans tonight.

689
00:58:55,766 --> 00:58:56,672
Hello, aunty.

690
00:58:56,870 --> 00:58:58,514
You're moving out?

691
00:58:58,778 --> 00:59:01,238
Who knows what this boy wants.

692
00:59:01,486 --> 00:59:03,259
Got a good price?

693
00:59:03,807 --> 00:59:06,381
Don't worry, Papa. I'll invest wisely.

694
00:59:06,861 --> 00:59:09,086
Too much time wasted on Aryan.

695
00:59:10,504 --> 00:59:11,958
The shop is sold, Mummy.
Let's go.

696
00:59:12,407 --> 00:59:13,998
Hurry. You coming?

697
00:59:14,471 --> 00:59:15,810
- Let's go.
- Ok, come.

698
00:59:16,770 --> 00:59:18,156
All well, aunty?

699
01:00:53,851 --> 01:00:56,224
Fans chase stars.

700
01:00:57,515 --> 01:00:59,697
Now a star will chase a fan.

701
01:01:01,511 --> 01:01:04,515
Whenever Aryan Khanna's name
is taken...

702
01:01:06,131 --> 01:01:08,851
it'll be in the same breath
as Gaurav Chandna

703
01:01:35,849 --> 01:01:37,383
1 Year later.

704
01:01:37,787 --> 01:01:40,655
Welcome to Bollywood Caf.
98.1 FM.

705
01:01:41,117 --> 01:01:42,812
Do you know what's special
about the weekend?

706
01:01:43,133 --> 01:01:44,267
Guys, this weekend...

707
01:01:44,429 --> 01:01:47,047
is the Aryan Khanna reloaded
show presented by Hyundai.

708
01:01:47,691 --> 01:01:50,254
Stars have a great life

709
01:01:50,587 --> 01:01:52,602
I want a life like Aryan's.

710
01:01:52,838 --> 01:01:53,873
Full on, jet setter!

711
01:01:54,099 --> 01:01:56,288
One day in London, Dubrovnik the next.

712
01:01:56,506 --> 01:01:58,315
For the grand Bhutiani wedding.

713
01:01:58,533 --> 01:02:00,130
Then back to the London show.

714
01:02:00,321 --> 01:02:01,029
Wow!

715
01:02:01,585 --> 01:02:04,359
Do you know London is
one of his favourite places?

716
01:02:04,565 --> 01:02:07,249
In fact he considers it his
second home after Mumbai.

717
01:02:07,595 --> 01:02:12,154
We have some good news
and some bad news.

718
01:02:12,409 --> 01:02:13,853
The bad news first, obviously.

719
01:02:14,171 --> 01:02:16,824
The Hyundai Aryan Khanna reloaded
show is houseful.

720
01:02:17,118 --> 01:02:18,973
Oh no! What's the good news?

721
01:02:19,241 --> 01:02:22,160
We have 20 free tickets
for our listeners.

722
01:02:23,024 --> 01:02:26,190
Who ever is the first to answer
my question correctly...

723
01:02:26,438 --> 01:02:28,543
wins a free show ticket.

724
01:02:28,785 --> 01:02:33,073
My question follows straight after
this beautiful song.

725
01:02:44,785 --> 01:02:46,491
Here's your tickets. Enjoy your visit.

726
01:02:48,830 --> 01:02:50,775
- How can I help you?
- One ticket please.

727
01:02:53,769 --> 01:02:54,707
Enjoy your visit.

728
01:03:44,632 --> 01:03:46,713
The real drama starts now

729
01:03:50,815 --> 01:03:51,833
Aryan Khanna!

730
01:04:03,728 --> 01:04:06,233
Mr. Khanna, Tim Baker,
the Manager

731
01:04:06,855 --> 01:04:08,108
Aryan Khanna, the actor.

732
01:04:10,023 --> 01:04:11,355
I hope it's not a bother.

733
01:04:11,991 --> 01:04:13,520
Fans never bother.

734
01:04:18,889 --> 01:04:20,804
Sir, a photo with your wax figure.

735
01:04:22,339 --> 01:04:24,883
Let me say this. It's amazing.

736
01:04:25,244 --> 01:04:27,298
You've come all the way to London...

737
01:04:27,713 --> 01:04:29,379
to take a photo with
my wax figure.

738
01:04:29,978 --> 01:04:33,004
Really, that's very sweet.
Is this better?

739
01:04:34,966 --> 01:04:35,664
Better now?

740
01:04:37,757 --> 01:04:39,384
Let me warn you.

741
01:04:39,846 --> 01:04:40,974
I was much younger then.

742
01:04:42,186 --> 01:04:43,464
You like it?

743
01:04:43,668 --> 01:04:44,406
Honestly...

744
01:04:45,157 --> 01:04:46,070
it's very scary.

745
01:04:47,839 --> 01:04:49,604
So, does he look like me?

746
01:04:49,868 --> 01:04:52,503
- You look great in real life.
- Exactly, darling

747
01:04:52,808 --> 01:04:55,894
I agree. What a fat nose he has.

748
01:04:56,584 --> 01:04:58,475
My nose is tiny.

749
01:04:59,794 --> 01:05:01,347
A phony face.

750
01:05:01,894 --> 01:05:03,113
A fake smile.

751
01:05:03,413 --> 01:05:04,577
All phony.

752
01:05:05,399 --> 01:05:06,929
I don't smile like this.

753
01:05:08,148 --> 01:05:10,587
Actually no one smiles like this.

754
01:05:12,295 --> 01:05:15,208
His hair smells bad.
Feels bad, looks bad.

755
01:05:18,349 --> 01:05:21,097
In fact, I don't look like him at all.

756
01:05:21,883 --> 01:05:23,389
This is a fake

757
01:05:24,302 --> 01:05:26,361
Aryan Khanna is a fake.

758
01:05:26,798 --> 01:05:30,318
I want a refund. Aryan Khanna
is a fake.

759
01:05:32,779 --> 01:05:35,063
This isn't right. You can't do this
to our property.

760
01:05:35,985 --> 01:05:38,368
The white man claims
my face is his property.

761
01:05:39,382 --> 01:05:41,872
Mr. Property Agent. This is me.

762
01:05:42,341 --> 01:05:43,888
My face, my property.

763
01:05:44,435 --> 01:05:47,113
- Stop now and leave, sir.
- I won't leave.

764
01:05:51,456 --> 01:05:53,253
It's a joke. You guys can't
take a joke.

765
01:05:59,701 --> 01:06:00,709
Come here. Come.

766
01:06:00,895 --> 01:06:01,934
Who can stop me?

767
01:06:03,405 --> 01:06:04,760
I'll shoot you all.

768
01:06:06,746 --> 01:06:08,090
I don't understand what
you're talking about.

769
01:06:08,612 --> 01:06:09,746
You are gonna be in a lot
of trouble over this.

770
01:06:10,017 --> 01:06:10,431
Really?

771
01:06:13,623 --> 01:06:15,065
You are in trouble too.

772
01:06:16,799 --> 01:06:18,676
Stay out of my way! I'll shoot.

773
01:06:26,592 --> 01:06:27,720
You alright?

774
01:07:15,682 --> 01:07:16,835
Aryan...

775
01:07:20,410 --> 01:07:20,980
What?

776
01:07:21,419 --> 01:07:22,090
Come out.

777
01:07:22,546 --> 01:07:23,519
What are you saying?

778
01:07:28,104 --> 01:07:29,433
Arrest warrant for you.

779
01:07:31,704 --> 01:07:32,870
What the hell is this?

780
01:07:33,203 --> 01:07:35,001
I didn't go to Madame Tussauds.

781
01:07:35,700 --> 01:07:38,728
- The Indian Ambassador on line.
- I'm not talking to any Ambassador

782
01:07:39,364 --> 01:07:40,439
I'm here to arrest him.

783
01:07:41,028 --> 01:07:42,901
Sir, Mr. Khanna did not go to
Madame Tussauds...

784
01:07:43,110 --> 01:07:44,941
Are you Mr. Khanna?

785
01:07:45,316 --> 01:07:47,189
Then just shut up and let me
do my job.

786
01:07:47,397 --> 01:07:50,461
Excuse me. So you are doing
your job and we are faffing?

787
01:07:51,143 --> 01:07:54,182
Must say you have a very polite way
of talking to women, Mr. Duncan.

788
01:07:54,783 --> 01:07:55,431
Guess what?

789
01:07:55,638 --> 01:07:57,678
It's my turn to be polite now.

790
01:07:58,419 --> 01:08:00,190
This, sir, is nonsense.

791
01:08:02,279 --> 01:08:04,836
Where were you between
10 and 10.30 this morning?

792
01:08:05,070 --> 01:08:06,563
- I was at home.
- And who were you with?

793
01:08:07,710 --> 01:08:08,417
I was alone.

794
01:08:08,709 --> 01:08:10,628
Did anyone see you at home?

795
01:08:11,789 --> 01:08:13,038
I just told you I was alone

796
01:08:13,288 --> 01:08:14,589
Aryan, I'll call our lawyer.

797
01:08:15,213 --> 01:08:17,997
Can you talk in a language
we all can understand?

798
01:08:18,519 --> 01:08:20,806
Let me translate it in a language
you understand.

799
01:08:21,862 --> 01:08:22,509
Lawyer.

800
01:08:23,278 --> 01:08:24,401
Two options.

801
01:08:24,976 --> 01:08:28,145
Handcuffs if you are nasty,
without handcuffs if you are nice.

802
01:08:35,395 --> 01:08:36,122
Nasty.

803
01:09:12,348 --> 01:09:13,877
Just five minutes.

804
01:09:14,112 --> 01:09:15,059
You stay here.

805
01:09:15,347 --> 01:09:16,641
Just five minutes sir, please.

806
01:09:18,198 --> 01:09:19,589
Let's call Akhtar.

807
01:09:40,702 --> 01:09:41,221
What happened?

808
01:09:42,452 --> 01:09:43,416
Lost your funny bone?

809
01:09:45,614 --> 01:09:46,297
That's not me.

810
01:09:48,049 --> 01:09:49,109
Behaves like you.

811
01:09:50,442 --> 01:09:51,615
Looks like you.

812
01:09:52,940 --> 01:09:55,480
Everybody calls this person
by your name.

813
01:09:58,746 --> 01:10:00,235
I said that's not me.

814
01:10:01,320 --> 01:10:02,257
You have any proof?

815
01:10:05,485 --> 01:10:07,749
Say something, Mr. Superstar.

816
01:10:10,090 --> 01:10:11,921
Not to you, Mr. Small-Time cop.

817
01:10:12,628 --> 01:10:14,117
Not a word without my lawyer.

818
01:10:15,210 --> 01:10:16,062
Suit yourself

819
01:10:16,999 --> 01:10:19,325
24 hrs remand for Mr. Khanna.

820
01:10:19,705 --> 01:10:21,390
Till he comes out with the truth.

821
01:10:22,262 --> 01:10:24,650
- You can't do that.
- Sure, I can.

822
01:10:32,841 --> 01:10:34,900
Sir, one photograph please?

823
01:10:41,657 --> 01:10:43,911
- You have a safe trip, sir.
- Yeah, I will be.

824
01:11:52,160 --> 01:11:53,402
It's time. Lets go.

825
01:12:05,959 --> 01:12:08,758
DUBROVNIK

826
01:12:15,788 --> 01:12:17,746
In Croatian, we say - How are you?

827
01:12:19,892 --> 01:12:20,838
I'm fine.

828
01:12:21,738 --> 01:12:22,873
My name is Gaurav.

829
01:12:27,864 --> 01:12:29,333
Thank you.

830
01:12:35,810 --> 01:12:37,047
Vegetable sandwich... one.

831
01:12:37,370 --> 01:12:38,469
Which one do you want?

832
01:12:39,130 --> 01:12:39,730
This one?

833
01:12:40,036 --> 01:12:41,488
Ok. Here we go.

834
01:12:45,959 --> 01:12:48,166
No, no, more. Six more.

835
01:12:50,093 --> 01:12:51,767
It's ok. Here.

836
01:12:54,371 --> 01:12:55,332
Thank you.

837
01:12:58,314 --> 01:12:59,148
Thanks.

838
01:13:29,889 --> 01:13:30,766
It's only bail.

839
01:13:32,214 --> 01:13:33,527
We know you're lying.

840
01:13:33,925 --> 01:13:35,800
Why would I waste my lies on you?

841
01:13:36,828 --> 01:13:39,672
That was no imposter.
You twisted psycho.

842
01:13:40,145 --> 01:13:41,686
We'll have you back
in jail in no time.

843
01:13:41,874 --> 01:13:43,267
Please do that.

844
01:13:43,601 --> 01:13:46,042
Maybe I'll earn some money suing you
and the entire British police

845
01:13:46,484 --> 01:13:49,222
Aryan, control your temper.

846
01:13:49,830 --> 01:13:51,759
It's their city, their country.

847
01:13:53,003 --> 01:13:55,589
Don't make matters worse
for yourself.

848
01:13:56,039 --> 01:13:58,640
So we're done with all
the formalities?

849
01:13:59,418 --> 01:14:00,250
Thanks a lot.

850
01:14:01,583 --> 01:14:02,790
Pathetic fool

851
01:14:03,747 --> 01:14:07,238
I'm coming with you to Dubrovnik
in case of any immigration problem.

852
01:14:07,786 --> 01:14:09,283
Hey! Not that way.

853
01:14:10,320 --> 01:14:11,656
The press is outside

854
01:14:14,718 --> 01:14:16,878
Aryan, this is Deputy High
Commissioner, Mr. Murthy.

855
01:14:17,233 --> 01:14:18,816
Pleased to meet you.

856
01:14:19,148 --> 01:14:20,980
Sorry you had to go through
all this but...

857
01:14:21,191 --> 01:14:23,036
We can't interfere very much.

858
01:14:23,299 --> 01:14:24,726
This is a foreign country after all

859
01:14:25,114 --> 01:14:27,890
I know. Rules in every country
are made to get the innocent.

860
01:14:28,662 --> 01:14:31,012
Sir, we're diplomats, not detectives.

861
01:14:31,520 --> 01:14:34,883
Before the case is solved, we have
permission for you to travel.

862
01:14:35,215 --> 01:14:36,929
Now we can only do that much.

863
01:14:37,124 --> 01:14:39,495
It's a serious matter.
A diplomatic issue.

864
01:14:39,736 --> 01:14:43,082
So you must prove it wasn't you
at Madame Tussauds.

865
01:14:43,487 --> 01:14:46,372
Must I prove it? Ok, I'll play cop.

866
01:14:47,177 --> 01:14:49,368
I really appreciate your help.

867
01:14:50,034 --> 01:14:50,808
Thank you.

868
01:14:51,400 --> 01:14:52,823
Thank you, sir.

869
01:14:55,533 --> 01:14:57,536
In jail or dancing at a wedding...

870
01:14:57,737 --> 01:14:59,840
these stars are so arrogant.

871
01:15:02,480 --> 01:15:05,652
Your home CCTV footage has saved us.
It's with the police.

872
01:15:05,869 --> 01:15:09,848
It proves an impostor was at Madame
Tussauds and you were at home.

873
01:15:10,686 --> 01:15:13,161
Who is he? What's his motive.

874
01:15:13,431 --> 01:15:14,668
Forget the London cops.

875
01:15:14,871 --> 01:15:16,674
Find out. We need to get this guy.

876
01:15:17,924 --> 01:15:20,075
We'll know more back in London.

877
01:15:20,691 --> 01:15:22,095
So you know you can
really relax now.

878
01:15:22,305 --> 01:15:23,956
Wine? Champagne? Anything?

879
01:15:24,616 --> 01:15:25,103
Everything.

880
01:15:25,283 --> 01:15:26,951
Come on, Aryan. It's over now.

881
01:15:27,324 --> 01:15:29,139
Sir, a call.

882
01:15:29,387 --> 01:15:32,515
He says he knows the imposter
at Madame Tussauds.

883
01:15:33,189 --> 01:15:35,864
- Give me the phone. I'll talk.
- He'll only talk to sir.

884
01:15:36,129 --> 01:15:37,403
He won't give me his name.

885
01:15:38,726 --> 01:15:39,709
Give it to me.

886
01:15:45,672 --> 01:15:46,482
Hello.

887
01:15:54,029 --> 01:15:54,803
Senior.

888
01:16:00,610 --> 01:16:01,359
Chandna?

889
01:16:02,525 --> 01:16:04,398
I won't let you forget my name.

890
01:16:04,924 --> 01:16:06,854
It'll be taken in the same breath
as your name.

891
01:16:07,853 --> 01:16:08,644
What do you want?

892
01:16:08,909 --> 01:16:10,184
The stage is set.

893
01:16:10,684 --> 01:16:13,806
Tell everyone - admit what you did
was wrong.

894
01:16:14,640 --> 01:16:17,448
You'll never break a fan's heart
again. Say sorry.

895
01:16:17,821 --> 01:16:20,465
Stop this nonsense! I'm not
apologising to anyone.

896
01:16:21,361 --> 01:16:23,517
I tried to make you see sense.

897
01:16:23,787 --> 01:16:26,326
If you had agreed to give me
5 minutes.

898
01:16:27,106 --> 01:16:28,832
I would have my life.
You would have yours.

899
01:16:29,302 --> 01:16:31,746
But you had to prove you had
star power.

900
01:16:32,075 --> 01:16:33,352
Now you'll see a fan's power

901
01:16:33,576 --> 01:16:34,493
I'm a star.

902
01:16:35,263 --> 01:16:38,197
I took your pranks as childishness.
Threw you inside for only 2 days.

903
01:16:39,242 --> 01:16:41,569
If I knew the real you,
you'd still be inside.

904
01:16:41,906 --> 01:16:45,122
In 48 hours you snatched away
my devotion of 25 years.

905
01:16:46,215 --> 01:16:47,896
If you don't say sorry...

906
01:16:48,448 --> 01:16:50,458
in the next 48 hours,
your stardom is over.

907
01:16:51,407 --> 01:16:52,558
Do what you want

908
01:16:53,880 --> 01:16:55,800
I've seen off dozens like you.

909
01:16:56,214 --> 01:16:59,385
The higher you fly, the harder
I'll make you fall.

910
01:17:01,432 --> 01:17:04,379
But you must fly as high as me,
Gaurav Chandna.

911
01:17:04,602 --> 01:17:06,360
Impossible for you.

912
01:17:07,848 --> 01:17:11,551
We'll see how far you get
impersonating me.

913
01:17:12,133 --> 01:17:14,431
I don't need to go far.

914
01:17:15,114 --> 01:17:17,851
You're getting closer to me.
In Dubrovnik.

915
01:17:21,977 --> 01:17:24,213
Idiot. He's in Dubrovnik.

916
01:17:28,769 --> 01:17:30,810
Unknown caller, unknown location.

917
01:17:31,319 --> 01:17:34,808
Obviously, Sunaina. He won't
call from a traceable number.

918
01:17:38,257 --> 01:17:40,427
Say sorry. It's no big deal.

919
01:17:43,610 --> 01:17:44,708
He's mad.

920
01:17:44,935 --> 01:17:47,595
Is that so? And what am I?

921
01:17:52,172 --> 01:17:53,244
Is the make-up team in place?

922
01:17:53,463 --> 01:17:55,171
They are on there way.

923
01:17:55,389 --> 01:17:58,480
Oh great. The props, fireworks,
confetti all that.

924
01:17:58,832 --> 01:18:00,911
We've done a couple of rehearsals.
Everything's perfect.

925
01:18:01,106 --> 01:18:02,284
Ok. Thank you

926
01:18:03,328 --> 01:18:05,474
Aryan asked for a background
check of all the staff members.

927
01:18:05,714 --> 01:18:07,341
- Is it done yet?
- It's going on right now.

928
01:18:07,559 --> 01:18:08,527
Ok. Thank you.

929
01:18:12,533 --> 01:18:13,808
Nicksi Jelopera.

930
01:18:27,429 --> 01:18:28,854
- Medium?
- Medium size.

931
01:19:14,399 --> 01:19:17,332
You're so late, Aryan Khanna.
It's just not done

932
01:19:17,657 --> 01:19:20,074
I apologise. I'm extremely sorry,
Mr. Bhutiani

933
01:19:20,273 --> 01:19:21,671
I had a crisis, I'm sorry.

934
01:19:21,905 --> 01:19:24,796
You celebrities always have
some crisis.

935
01:19:25,271 --> 01:19:27,294
But my daughter doesn't
get married everyday

936
01:19:27,486 --> 01:19:29,431
- I know. I'm sorry.
- You've no idea.

937
01:19:29,696 --> 01:19:33,548
That stunt you pulled in London has
caused me great loss of face.

938
01:19:33,802 --> 01:19:34,934
No, Mr. Bhutiani.

939
01:19:35,390 --> 01:19:37,418
What happened at Madame Tussauds...

940
01:19:38,770 --> 01:19:40,649
You know what? I'll make
it up to you

941
01:19:40,888 --> 01:19:44,366
I swear. Your guests will always think
of the grand Bhutiani wedding.

942
01:19:44,600 --> 01:19:45,837
They better do.

943
01:19:46,252 --> 01:19:47,955
After all I'm spending
a bomb on you.

944
01:19:51,254 --> 01:19:53,523
Only you can. I'll get ready

945
01:19:55,224 --> 01:19:57,659
Sunaina, find out where
the CCTV cameras are.

946
01:19:57,918 --> 01:20:01,224
Usman, watch the guest areas,
the bars, the toilets, the corridors.

947
01:20:01,672 --> 01:20:03,721
- Keep an eye on everyone.
- Excuse me, sir

948
01:20:04,125 --> 01:20:06,488
I'm really sorry to interrupt but
we just have 2 minutes.

949
01:20:07,150 --> 01:20:09,335
I don't need two, darling.
Let's go, I'm ready.

950
01:20:10,184 --> 01:20:11,111
Good luck.

951
01:20:11,888 --> 01:20:12,989
Payal, tell me the names.

952
01:20:13,219 --> 01:20:15,519
Is Bhutiani's son-in-law called
Amul Mirchandani?

953
01:20:15,696 --> 01:20:17,001
It's Anmol Mirchandani.

954
01:20:17,174 --> 01:20:19,095
Guys, all the best. Break
a leg and do well.

955
01:20:19,286 --> 01:20:21,364
And sisters Anushka, Deepshika?

956
01:20:21,649 --> 01:20:23,886
That's for later, it's all here.

957
01:20:25,106 --> 01:20:27,012
Second entry dance 5,6,7,8.
You're giving it to me.

958
01:20:27,223 --> 01:20:28,865
- Sir, your shades.
- Thank you, Payal.

959
01:20:29,047 --> 01:20:30,987
Ok guys. You have 30 seconds
to go.

960
01:20:31,220 --> 01:20:32,757
All the best, just kill it.

961
01:21:17,809 --> 01:21:19,356
Check all entries and exits.

962
01:21:20,037 --> 01:21:20,815
Ok, Sunaina.

963
01:21:33,737 --> 01:21:34,672
Find anything?

964
01:21:34,849 --> 01:21:38,645
Not yet, sir. I've spoken to the team,
no one enters without an invite.

965
01:21:38,843 --> 01:21:40,380
Sir, your cue cards

966
01:21:40,667 --> 01:21:41,976
15 secs to go.

967
01:21:43,414 --> 01:21:44,114
Can you go to cam 4.

968
01:21:48,470 --> 01:21:50,675
When you count the night stars...

969
01:21:50,967 --> 01:21:53,025
and yearn to etch her name
on every star.

970
01:21:53,581 --> 01:21:55,046
You know you're in love.

971
01:21:55,338 --> 01:21:57,518
When you want to turn back
as you walk ahead.

972
01:21:57,912 --> 01:22:01,794
When you look for her in a crowd,
you know you're in love.

973
01:22:04,764 --> 01:22:06,259
Say sorry.

974
01:22:09,374 --> 01:22:10,713
Check the crew's photos.

975
01:22:11,165 --> 01:22:13,603
He's not a guest. He's crew.
Quick.

976
01:22:13,901 --> 01:22:14,578
Got it.

977
01:22:18,814 --> 01:22:19,604
Sorry.

978
01:22:32,993 --> 01:22:33,632
There. Zoom in.

979
01:22:34,806 --> 01:22:37,148
Check the crew backstage.

980
01:22:37,805 --> 01:22:38,233
Copy.

981
01:22:38,573 --> 01:22:41,874
Payal, we need the crew ids.
Photographs and bio-datas.

982
01:22:42,348 --> 01:22:44,964
- Anything serious, sir?
- Aryan wants to know.

983
01:22:58,303 --> 01:22:59,129
Sorry.

984
01:22:59,377 --> 01:23:00,037
It's fine.

985
01:23:03,410 --> 01:23:05,063
The crew is local.

986
01:23:05,330 --> 01:23:08,199
Except one guy. Half Indian,
half Croatian.

987
01:23:10,675 --> 01:23:12,903
Akhtar is sending you a photo
of him.

988
01:23:13,408 --> 01:23:14,526
Keep a close eye.

989
01:23:20,093 --> 01:23:20,918
Round up all the crew.

990
01:23:51,207 --> 01:23:53,203
- Any sign of him?
- Sir, nothing.

991
01:23:53,494 --> 01:23:54,951
He's not responding

992
01:23:55,451 --> 01:23:55,992
Sunaina.

993
01:23:56,283 --> 01:23:57,781
Can't see him on any camera.

994
01:23:58,198 --> 01:23:59,730
- But I'm at it.
- What are you at it?

995
01:24:06,148 --> 01:24:08,123
Where is there no CCTV camera?

996
01:24:09,077 --> 01:24:10,276
Your make-up room.

997
01:24:19,385 --> 01:24:20,261
Careful, sir.

998
01:24:38,907 --> 01:24:41,280
Gaurav makes Aryan.

999
01:24:52,481 --> 01:24:54,974
You're very stubborn.
You don't listen to me.

1000
01:24:55,642 --> 01:24:58,595
Why are you hiding?
Talk face-to-face.

1001
01:24:59,352 --> 01:25:01,472
I stand face-to-face, Aryan Khanna.

1002
01:25:02,435 --> 01:25:04,299
But you never see me.

1003
01:25:05,017 --> 01:25:08,794
Now when I'm not there, you're
longing to see me.

1004
01:25:10,447 --> 01:25:12,374
I know the feeling.

1005
01:25:12,909 --> 01:25:15,129
I felt it among the crowd
in front of your house.

1006
01:25:21,060 --> 01:25:24,569
Sir, the Bhutianis are waiting.
The audience interaction...

1007
01:25:25,422 --> 01:25:28,094
Yeah. I'm coming.

1008
01:25:29,126 --> 01:25:30,772
- I'll take care of it.
- Thank you

1009
01:25:33,392 --> 01:25:35,487
I'll come back and see you.
Hi sweetheart.

1010
01:25:35,913 --> 01:25:37,141
Hope you enjoyed the show.

1011
01:25:37,539 --> 01:25:39,556
- Aryan, it was marvelous.
- Thank you.

1012
01:25:39,988 --> 01:25:41,117
That's my daughter.

1013
01:25:41,353 --> 01:25:44,549
She's been practicing a step to
dance with you for two months.

1014
01:25:45,015 --> 01:25:46,782
Actually we were both practicing.

1015
01:25:47,013 --> 01:25:48,386
How pretty is she.

1016
01:25:48,594 --> 01:25:50,401
You know what? Let me start
with the young one

1017
01:25:50,634 --> 01:25:52,370
and I'll come back
for the experience.

1018
01:26:16,649 --> 01:26:17,926
We've found Chandna.

1019
01:26:18,232 --> 01:26:21,353
In the corridor, across from where
you're dancing

1020
01:26:22,059 --> 01:26:23,227
I'm not dancing.

1021
01:26:24,207 --> 01:26:25,482
Chandna is on the dance floor.

1022
01:27:15,496 --> 01:27:17,089
What the hell is wrong with him?

1023
01:27:17,621 --> 01:27:21,085
I was dancing. He started touching me
here, there, everywhere.

1024
01:27:21,769 --> 01:27:23,291
I don't know. You'll have
to do something.

1025
01:27:23,557 --> 01:27:25,519
- Get him out.
- I don't care.

1026
01:27:36,861 --> 01:27:38,027
What the hell are you doing?

1027
01:27:38,276 --> 01:27:39,067
Mr. Bhutiani?

1028
01:27:39,348 --> 01:27:41,388
- Where do you think you are?
- Calm down, Mr. Bhutiani.

1029
01:27:41,564 --> 01:27:43,784
- What happened?
- That girl is like my daughter.

1030
01:27:45,606 --> 01:27:47,350
Is this how you film stars behave?

1031
01:27:47,677 --> 01:27:49,915
I'm really sorry, ladies.
I'm sorry

1032
01:27:50,114 --> 01:27:52,928
I'll explain. The guy who was
here wasn't me.

1033
01:27:53,480 --> 01:27:55,155
- Nonsense.
- It was somebody else

1034
01:27:55,334 --> 01:27:56,591
I'm Aryan Khanna.

1035
01:27:57,314 --> 01:27:58,756
- I'm Aryan Khanna.
- What nonsense!

1036
01:27:58,922 --> 01:28:00,430
You known me for years

1037
01:28:00,603 --> 01:28:03,404
I love you guys. I'd never
harm you people.

1038
01:28:03,677 --> 01:28:05,486
That person wasn't me.

1039
01:28:07,248 --> 01:28:08,871
I suggest you leave.

1040
01:28:22,607 --> 01:28:23,861
Keep back!

1041
01:28:34,803 --> 01:28:35,520
Stop the car!

1042
01:33:57,010 --> 01:33:59,303
No one has given me the
interaction script

1043
01:34:00,503 --> 01:34:03,636
15 minutes to show time.
Is there a delay?

1044
01:34:08,168 --> 01:34:09,026
What?

1045
01:34:15,855 --> 01:34:17,351
The show's cancelled.

1046
01:34:18,622 --> 01:34:22,613
They've boycotted the show.

1047
01:34:24,113 --> 01:34:26,564
Sponsors have also pulled out.

1048
01:34:29,093 --> 01:34:31,698
Nobody came, not a soul.

1049
01:35:42,969 --> 01:35:43,951
Whats wrong with you?

1050
01:35:44,143 --> 01:35:44,757
You wimp.

1051
01:35:44,906 --> 01:35:46,115
Watch where you're going?

1052
01:35:59,205 --> 01:36:00,998
Media playing up the story.

1053
01:36:01,599 --> 01:36:02,934
The wedding video has gone viral.

1054
01:36:19,738 --> 01:36:23,436
Given Khanna's status, he must
take responsibility for his actions.

1055
01:36:23,910 --> 01:36:25,278
Is he attention-seeking?

1056
01:36:25,507 --> 01:36:27,901
Movie stars forget that one day
they'll be has-beens.

1057
01:36:28,111 --> 01:36:30,913
Stars must go through traumas.
Look at what his done.

1058
01:36:31,206 --> 01:36:33,224
It's a crime if an ordinary man
misbehaves...

1059
01:36:33,452 --> 01:36:36,213
if it's a star - it's a stunt.
Why these double standards...

1060
01:36:36,471 --> 01:36:39,093
for stars? A criminal is
a criminal.

1061
01:36:48,668 --> 01:36:49,237
Hello.

1062
01:36:49,807 --> 01:36:52,269
Hello, sir. It's me, Aryan.
I'm calling from London.

1063
01:36:53,042 --> 01:36:55,491
I know you are in London,
but what's going on?

1064
01:36:57,226 --> 01:37:00,143
A Delhi boy is impersonating me,
committing crimes.

1065
01:37:00,600 --> 01:37:01,783
We have to arrest him.

1066
01:37:02,051 --> 01:37:05,183
But the crimes are committed
outside of India.

1067
01:37:05,759 --> 01:37:08,675
We can't arrest him. It's not
in our jurisdiction.

1068
01:37:09,018 --> 01:37:11,418
Must we wait till he commits
a crime in India?

1069
01:37:12,475 --> 01:37:13,795
His name is Gaurav Chandna.

1070
01:37:14,035 --> 01:37:16,556
Find me his Delhi address.
It will help.

1071
01:37:17,510 --> 01:37:19,285
You don't teach me my job.

1072
01:37:19,844 --> 01:37:23,048
But who shall we arrest?
You're the accused, Aryan.

1073
01:37:23,865 --> 01:37:25,444
I just...

1074
01:37:25,881 --> 01:37:27,723
Come back to India.

1075
01:37:28,354 --> 01:37:31,370
Then we'll look into the matter with
the proper procedure. OK?

1076
01:37:33,839 --> 01:37:34,685
Hello.

1077
01:37:38,196 --> 01:37:39,228
What did he say?

1078
01:37:42,373 --> 01:37:44,348
Organise a press conference
first thing tomorrow.

1079
01:37:44,768 --> 01:37:47,488
- In Mumbai?
- No, here in London.

1080
01:37:50,878 --> 01:37:56,371
You now have the video footage
and all the documents, etc.

1081
01:37:57,223 --> 01:37:58,833
You have proof...

1082
01:37:59,456 --> 01:38:03,212
that Aryan Khanna did not
commit these crimes.

1083
01:38:12,754 --> 01:38:16,319
You're angry with me, and you
have the right to be.

1084
01:38:17,509 --> 01:38:18,523
But believe me.

1085
01:38:19,333 --> 01:38:22,160
That dangerous and evil face
you see on TV is not me.

1086
01:38:22,760 --> 01:38:24,142
That person is not me.

1087
01:38:24,411 --> 01:38:25,432
So please give me time.

1088
01:38:25,701 --> 01:38:29,332
Time, so that I can prove
I've done nothing wrong

1089
01:38:31,234 --> 01:38:34,192
I'd never do anything that
would make you ashamed...

1090
01:38:34,474 --> 01:38:35,932
to call me your star.

1091
01:38:36,688 --> 01:38:38,120
Whatever I am...

1092
01:38:42,402 --> 01:38:46,203
I just want to say, I would
never do anything like this.

1093
01:38:47,209 --> 01:38:47,959
Thank you.

1094
01:38:50,210 --> 01:38:54,213
Sir, do you know this impostor?
Have you met him?

1095
01:38:54,639 --> 01:38:58,569
Sorry. We can't talk now.
The case is under trial.

1096
01:38:58,887 --> 01:39:00,238
What about the imposter's name?

1097
01:39:00,478 --> 01:39:03,342
As soon as we have proof,
you'll be the first to know.

1098
01:39:04,068 --> 01:39:06,552
Are you the real Aryan Khanna
or the imposter?

1099
01:39:10,561 --> 01:39:12,501
You find this funny? A big joke?

1100
01:39:14,253 --> 01:39:17,993
If this happened to a girl in your
family would you still be grinning?

1101
01:39:19,883 --> 01:39:23,263
A woman was molested and
you find it's funny?

1102
01:39:24,733 --> 01:39:25,892
And one more thing.

1103
01:39:26,960 --> 01:39:29,715
This press meet is not
to prove my innocence.

1104
01:39:30,579 --> 01:39:32,314
I want to warn you all.

1105
01:39:33,515 --> 01:39:36,604
The man who's impersonating me,
spoiling my name.

1106
01:39:37,121 --> 01:39:39,713
He can hurt anyone, anytime.

1107
01:39:40,506 --> 01:39:41,696
So please be careful.

1108
01:39:43,697 --> 01:39:45,192
Thank you everybody.
Thanks for coming

1109
01:39:45,438 --> 01:39:47,820
Aryan has a flight to catch, he's
going back to India.

1110
01:39:48,138 --> 01:39:49,619
So have a great day and
see you soon.

1111
01:39:50,262 --> 01:39:52,386
MUMBAI

1112
01:40:04,073 --> 01:40:06,852
Don't stop, go from behind.

1113
01:40:17,141 --> 01:40:17,939
Open up!

1114
01:40:20,138 --> 01:40:22,860
One minute, sir. Madam said we must
inform her.

1115
01:40:23,498 --> 01:40:24,733
Good. Hurry up.

1116
01:40:25,050 --> 01:40:26,864
Before the journalists outside mob me.

1117
01:40:32,530 --> 01:40:33,025
Hello.

1118
01:40:33,242 --> 01:40:35,099
Ma'am, can sir come in?

1119
01:40:38,559 --> 01:40:39,663
No, wait a second.

1120
01:40:41,766 --> 01:40:44,622
- Are you sure it's him?
- It sounds like sir.

1121
01:40:45,842 --> 01:40:47,278
Ask him to face the camera.

1122
01:40:48,824 --> 01:40:50,853
Sir, ma'am wants you to step forward.

1123
01:40:56,927 --> 01:41:00,462
Hi, I am Aryan Khanna. Height 5'10.
Black hair, black eyes.

1124
01:41:00,794 --> 01:41:01,898
A big nose.

1125
01:41:02,134 --> 01:41:03,790
School: Kendriya Vidyalaya,
New Delhi.

1126
01:41:04,640 --> 01:41:06,729
Hans Raj College, Delhi University.

1127
01:41:08,324 --> 01:41:10,058
Give me the phone, quick!

1128
01:41:11,973 --> 01:41:13,695
The press will surround me.

1129
01:41:14,931 --> 01:41:17,432
Let me in. Or I'll end up
in their arms.

1130
01:41:17,663 --> 01:41:18,931
Why is your phone off?

1131
01:41:20,352 --> 01:41:22,007
Can I tell you inside?

1132
01:41:25,052 --> 01:41:25,887
Open the door.

1133
01:41:35,980 --> 01:41:38,198
Guys. Dad's here

1134
01:42:04,775 --> 01:42:06,396
Aryan, you're back?

1135
01:42:18,870 --> 01:42:20,385
- Hi.
- Hi.

1136
01:42:20,918 --> 01:42:23,611
- You're back.
- Yes, I'm back.

1137
01:42:25,847 --> 01:42:27,025
Are the kids asleep?

1138
01:42:32,358 --> 01:42:34,760
Yes. It's way past their bedtime.

1139
01:42:35,285 --> 01:42:36,805
Of course.

1140
01:42:37,535 --> 01:42:39,089
Let them sleep.

1141
01:42:40,499 --> 01:42:44,326
Let's relax and talk quietly
in our room.

1142
01:42:48,775 --> 01:42:49,570
Yes.

1143
01:42:55,767 --> 01:42:59,983
- What an entrance exam!
- You passed with flying colours

1144
01:43:00,350 --> 01:43:02,841
I spent my life preparing
for this moment.

1145
01:43:03,216 --> 01:43:05,759
Relax. Make yourself a drink.
I'll run the shower for you.

1146
01:43:06,134 --> 01:43:07,327
Of course.

1147
01:43:22,624 --> 01:43:26,233
She was crying. Not easy getting
her to sleep again.

1148
01:43:31,020 --> 01:43:34,223
It's better for us both if Isha
stays asleep.

1149
01:43:41,208 --> 01:43:42,490
I did say...

1150
01:43:43,653 --> 01:43:45,829
we could talk calmly.

1151
01:43:47,974 --> 01:43:49,250
Why do you need that?

1152
01:43:49,864 --> 01:43:50,907
Give.

1153
01:43:51,590 --> 01:43:55,124
I have nothing against you
or your children.

1154
01:43:56,864 --> 01:43:57,951
Give me that.

1155
01:44:00,937 --> 01:44:02,475
Senior ignores me.

1156
01:44:03,913 --> 01:44:05,626
You can't let him do that.

1157
01:44:07,817 --> 01:44:11,718
Show me Aryan's study, he's
always talking about it.

1158
01:44:15,341 --> 01:44:16,443
Sound asleep.

1159
01:44:17,614 --> 01:44:18,941
Come, come.

1160
01:44:27,319 --> 01:44:30,208
Sit. He lands in 20 minutes.
I haven't much time.

1161
01:44:30,710 --> 01:44:32,277
Come on, sit down.

1162
01:44:37,334 --> 01:44:39,330
This room has so many stories.

1163
01:44:41,851 --> 01:44:44,011
Many stories behind these awards.

1164
01:44:45,233 --> 01:44:46,757
In these costumes.

1165
01:44:48,587 --> 01:44:50,935
Days that Aryan does not want
to forget.

1166
01:44:51,847 --> 01:44:55,375
Memories he wants to keep close
to his heart.

1167
01:45:01,557 --> 01:45:04,018
I treasured his memories too.

1168
01:45:04,978 --> 01:45:08,091
Kept them right here.

1169
01:45:10,596 --> 01:45:14,776
At home, on the walls of my room,
in cupboards.

1170
01:45:15,413 --> 01:45:16,989
On shelves like these

1171
01:45:26,373 --> 01:45:29,824
Aryan Khanna filled every corner
of my life.

1172
01:45:31,504 --> 01:45:33,057
But he ended it all.

1173
01:45:33,439 --> 01:45:37,063
Five minutes! I asked him for
only five minutes.

1174
01:45:37,415 --> 01:45:40,048
Know what he said?
It's my life.

1175
01:45:40,370 --> 01:45:42,448
Why must I give you even
five seconds of it?

1176
01:45:47,287 --> 01:45:50,296
- I apologise on his behalf.
- Why should you apologise?

1177
01:45:51,669 --> 01:45:53,709
I hit Sid Kapoor for his sake.

1178
01:45:54,683 --> 01:45:56,164
He was hassling Aryan.

1179
01:45:57,098 --> 01:45:59,788
What did Aryan do? Threw me in jail.
Had me beaten.

1180
01:46:01,186 --> 01:46:05,737
Said: It's a crime! A crime?

1181
01:46:07,584 --> 01:46:09,110
Crime is what I'll do now.

1182
01:46:11,356 --> 01:46:15,114
Breaking hearts of fans who are
devoted to you...

1183
01:46:15,849 --> 01:46:17,393
is a crime too.

1184
01:46:21,237 --> 01:46:22,513
You tell me.

1185
01:46:23,794 --> 01:46:25,481
Am I so wrong?

1186
01:46:26,758 --> 01:46:30,417
When he fights with you,
doesn't he say sorry?

1187
01:46:32,878 --> 01:46:35,781
So, why can't he say sorry to me?
Tell me!

1188
01:46:36,096 --> 01:46:38,218
Don't do this. I beg you.

1189
01:46:38,452 --> 01:46:40,287
What do you mean please?

1190
01:46:41,518 --> 01:46:43,867
He left nothing for me. Why must
I leave anything for him?

1191
01:46:44,211 --> 01:46:46,259
How can I? Impossible.

1192
01:46:47,437 --> 01:46:49,207
A sham. All lies.

1193
01:46:50,228 --> 01:46:52,907
Liar. He's a fake.

1194
01:46:54,407 --> 01:46:55,990
The rascal acts all the time.

1195
01:46:57,332 --> 01:46:58,855
An actor after all.

1196
01:47:07,548 --> 01:47:09,585
I wanted to give him my trophy.

1197
01:47:15,021 --> 01:47:17,300
A belated happy birthday,
Aryan Khanna.

1198
01:47:38,823 --> 01:47:39,958
Open the door!

1199
01:47:57,699 --> 01:48:00,184
I sent the children to my parents.

1200
01:48:01,149 --> 01:48:04,779
They were terrified. I didn't know
what to tell them.

1201
01:48:05,867 --> 01:48:08,981
Isha asked me repeatedly: Why did
Papa destroy the study?

1202
01:48:10,677 --> 01:48:11,373
Don't worry. It's ok.

1203
01:48:11,619 --> 01:48:15,004
- Why don't we call the police?
- The police will do nothing.

1204
01:48:15,827 --> 01:48:18,233
They'll ask for proof. They believe
I'm the criminal.

1205
01:48:19,547 --> 01:48:22,073
I came this far in life
on my own steam

1206
01:48:23,429 --> 01:48:25,146
I'll handle it myself.

1207
01:48:28,678 --> 01:48:30,810
Play rough like a street hoodlum

1208
01:48:31,626 --> 01:48:33,854
I'll rip him apart. Send him back
to where he belongs.

1209
01:48:36,054 --> 01:48:38,685
Gaurav Chandna has seen my star face.

1210
01:48:40,012 --> 01:48:42,106
Now he'll see my real face

1211
01:48:43,650 --> 01:48:45,001
I'm a Delhi man too.

1212
01:48:46,919 --> 01:48:50,282
The dangerous and evil face
on the news is not me.

1213
01:48:50,957 --> 01:48:52,621
That person is not me.
Give me time

1214
01:48:53,037 --> 01:48:55,077
I'll prove I've done nothing wrong

1215
01:48:55,317 --> 01:48:58,865
I'd never do anything to make you
ashamed calling me your star

1216
01:48:59,247 --> 01:49:02,583
Aryan Khanna's press conference
proves that he is innocent.

1217
01:49:02,893 --> 01:49:06,482
A criminal is impersonating him
and committing crimes.

1218
01:49:06,803 --> 01:49:10,266
Who is the culprit? His name?
His whereabouts?

1219
01:49:10,561 --> 01:49:14,102
No one knows the motives
behind his terrible actions.

1220
01:49:15,723 --> 01:49:20,493
The police have informed us that
they're very hopeful...

1221
01:49:20,831 --> 01:49:23,674
this criminal will not escape them.

1222
01:49:24,086 --> 01:49:26,442
When he's arrested, he'll be
severely punished.

1223
01:49:50,847 --> 01:49:52,038
Hello, Gauru.

1224
01:49:53,161 --> 01:49:53,828
Mummy.

1225
01:49:54,493 --> 01:49:57,163
What's wrong with your phone?
Where are you, Gauru?

1226
01:49:57,722 --> 01:49:58,436
Right here

1227
01:49:59,253 --> 01:50:00,012
I'm ok.

1228
01:50:01,816 --> 01:50:02,638
And you?

1229
01:50:02,979 --> 01:50:06,148
Son, come home soon.
We're in trouble.

1230
01:50:09,131 --> 01:50:12,652
You've roamed the world, now return
to your home

1231
01:50:16,998 --> 01:50:17,611
Aryan?

1232
01:50:19,561 --> 01:50:20,798
You barged into my home?

1233
01:50:21,669 --> 01:50:24,865
You can barge into mine, can't I
do the same?

1234
01:50:26,823 --> 01:50:29,337
I came here to grab your
parents by the throat.

1235
01:50:29,568 --> 01:50:31,708
To ask why they produced
a nasty son like you.

1236
01:50:32,773 --> 01:50:35,770
- But I am not a lowlife like you.
- Don't drag my parents into this.

1237
01:50:36,275 --> 01:50:37,735
They did nothing.

1238
01:50:38,684 --> 01:50:39,674
What did my kids do?

1239
01:50:40,243 --> 01:50:43,761
I went alone into your fortress.
Did you bring an army?

1240
01:50:44,024 --> 01:50:45,847
I am here alone, Gaurav Chandna.

1241
01:50:46,274 --> 01:50:49,964
No security, no secretary.
No star, no hero.

1242
01:50:50,362 --> 01:50:52,712
If you have the guts, face me.

1243
01:50:53,099 --> 01:50:54,304
Settle the score.

1244
01:50:55,955 --> 01:50:58,789
The score will only be settled
when you apologise.

1245
01:50:59,870 --> 01:51:02,867
Get on the stage at the Inder Vihar
contest and say sorry.

1246
01:51:03,109 --> 01:51:04,033
And listen...

1247
01:51:04,949 --> 01:51:07,447
If you touch my parents with
a feather even...

1248
01:51:08,055 --> 01:51:12,108
I know your mother-in-law's house,
where your children are hiding.

1249
01:51:13,348 --> 01:51:15,064
Your daughter is very cute, by God.

1250
01:51:18,964 --> 01:51:21,413
- Your son is stubborn like you.
- You rascal

1251
01:51:21,977 --> 01:51:25,649
I'll bury you in a gutter here, if you
dream of harming my kids.

1252
01:51:29,357 --> 01:51:31,089
What will my parents think?

1253
01:51:33,054 --> 01:51:34,338
Such a big star...

1254
01:51:36,477 --> 01:51:37,916
with such a foul tongue.

1255
01:51:40,785 --> 01:51:41,828
Forget it.

1256
01:51:43,210 --> 01:51:46,006
See you at the contest.

1257
01:51:48,425 --> 01:51:49,987
Your son has lost his mind.

1258
01:51:51,204 --> 01:51:54,288
- He's crossed the line.
- Our Gaurav was not like that.

1259
01:51:54,990 --> 01:51:57,022
He was a good boy.

1260
01:51:58,297 --> 01:52:00,146
He changed after meeting you.

1261
01:52:01,315 --> 01:52:03,841
What would you have lost
if you gave him 5 mins?

1262
01:52:04,154 --> 01:52:05,804
Don't blame Aryan.

1263
01:52:06,351 --> 01:52:07,401
It's our fault.

1264
01:52:09,028 --> 01:52:12,238
We let him get obsessed by
your glamorous life.

1265
01:52:13,372 --> 01:52:16,358
Not your hard slog. He would've
followed your example.

1266
01:52:17,009 --> 01:52:20,154
Worked hard and become someone.

1267
01:52:21,613 --> 01:52:25,190
Then the call center girl could've
become his girlfriend or wife.

1268
01:52:28,431 --> 01:52:29,615
He has a girlfriend?

1269
01:52:30,616 --> 01:52:33,860
A one-way romance.
Gaurav loves her but...

1270
01:52:34,132 --> 01:52:37,932
Enough. We have to accept things
the way they are.

1271
01:52:38,309 --> 01:52:42,031
- Where's the contest held?
- The other end of the colony.

1272
01:52:43,376 --> 01:52:46,473
Apologise. End this terrible situation.

1273
01:52:46,827 --> 01:52:48,243
You think I'm wrong too?

1274
01:52:48,538 --> 01:52:49,809
And I must apologise?

1275
01:52:50,343 --> 01:52:51,604
Arrest him.

1276
01:52:53,836 --> 01:52:55,691
He must be punished.

1277
01:52:57,594 --> 01:53:01,376
Imprison him for years, if you must.

1278
01:53:05,547 --> 01:53:06,921
But don't beat him.

1279
01:53:08,025 --> 01:53:08,961
Please.

1280
01:54:14,979 --> 01:54:17,517
Hey Junior. Where were you?

1281
01:54:18,142 --> 01:54:20,265
- Hello Uncle, Aunty.
- Hello.

1282
01:54:20,599 --> 01:54:23,304
Have you been watching the
news on TV about Aryan?

1283
01:54:24,277 --> 01:54:25,469
Never mind

1284
01:54:25,843 --> 01:54:28,099
I have good news for you all

1285
01:54:28,673 --> 01:54:30,071
I've got my American visa

1286
01:54:30,464 --> 01:54:31,878
I knew it.

1287
01:54:34,543 --> 01:54:37,332
Why is he standing with his back
to me? It's not like him.

1288
01:54:39,195 --> 01:54:41,868
He's going on stage soon,
he's just nervous.

1289
01:54:42,105 --> 01:54:43,492
Him? And nervous?

1290
01:54:43,741 --> 01:54:46,802
Has he done anything in life
besides copying Aryan?

1291
01:54:47,694 --> 01:54:50,352
Hey Superstar, your make-up...

1292
01:54:59,684 --> 01:55:00,263
Neha.

1293
01:55:04,033 --> 01:55:05,761
I have to talk to you.

1294
01:55:08,332 --> 01:55:10,680
Super surprise!

1295
01:55:11,700 --> 01:55:14,378
Western Union - moving money
for better.

1296
01:55:14,784 --> 01:55:17,911
Now for the last act of the
Super Star competition.

1297
01:55:18,736 --> 01:55:20,497
Our favourite winner.

1298
01:55:20,980 --> 01:55:24,049
Our Junior Aryan Khanna.

1299
01:55:28,489 --> 01:55:30,192
He's a criminal!

1300
01:55:30,957 --> 01:55:32,203
Get him off the stage.

1301
01:55:42,475 --> 01:55:43,598
Calm down.

1302
01:55:43,806 --> 01:55:45,774
It's not the real Aryan Khanna.

1303
01:55:46,051 --> 01:55:48,676
It's our very own superstar...

1304
01:55:49,218 --> 01:55:50,259
Gaurav Chandna.

1305
01:55:50,507 --> 01:55:51,548
Give him a big hand!

1306
01:56:26,448 --> 01:56:29,733
I do a show for Aryan every year.

1307
01:56:30,633 --> 01:56:32,907
I know, Aunty. You cheer the loudest.

1308
01:56:34,438 --> 01:56:35,671
But this year's show...

1309
01:56:37,101 --> 01:56:38,422
The show today is for...

1310
01:56:39,877 --> 01:56:40,702
someone else.

1311
01:56:41,865 --> 01:56:44,776
The girl over there who is...

1312
01:56:45,482 --> 01:56:47,402
smiling at me. She's my friend.

1313
01:56:48,669 --> 01:56:49,665
Neha!

1314
01:56:50,518 --> 01:56:51,791
Come, babes.

1315
01:56:58,386 --> 01:57:01,817
There's something I've kept
in my heart for days.

1316
01:57:05,445 --> 01:57:06,128
I love you, Neha.

1317
01:57:08,816 --> 01:57:10,897
- I love you too, Aryan.
- Not Aryan.

1318
01:57:11,272 --> 01:57:13,437
Gaurav loves you.

1319
01:57:16,046 --> 01:57:18,409
Gaurav loves Neha.

1320
01:57:20,431 --> 01:57:21,268
What nonsense!

1321
01:57:21,763 --> 01:57:22,470
Get lost.

1322
01:57:22,821 --> 01:57:25,174
- He's nuts.
- Thinks he's real Aryan Khanna.

1323
01:57:25,528 --> 01:57:26,175
Get him off.

1324
01:57:26,458 --> 01:57:29,639
Wait! He is talking to me.
I'll deal with it.

1325
01:57:32,052 --> 01:57:34,479
I love you!

1326
01:57:35,041 --> 01:57:37,388
Drop it. You love only Aryan.

1327
01:57:37,676 --> 01:57:39,172
He can go to hell.

1328
01:57:39,494 --> 01:57:42,370
- Is that you talking?
- It's not just talk

1329
01:57:42,862 --> 01:57:43,907
I've sent him to hell.

1330
01:57:45,016 --> 01:57:47,129
I fixed Aryan Khanna for good.

1331
01:57:47,537 --> 01:57:49,937
First in London, then in Dubrovnik.

1332
01:57:50,657 --> 01:57:53,080
I made my way into his house too.

1333
01:57:55,961 --> 01:57:58,619
Smashed everything in sight.

1334
01:57:59,868 --> 01:58:02,760
If you don't believe me, read the
papers. Watch TV or the Net.

1335
01:58:03,588 --> 01:58:06,420
Your Gaurav is famous the world over

1336
01:58:07,554 --> 01:58:09,126
I'm no less than Aryan.

1337
01:58:09,558 --> 01:58:10,698
Not at all.

1338
01:58:12,019 --> 01:58:13,550
I am a star in real life.

1339
01:58:14,504 --> 01:58:17,247
Not a star. A monster.

1340
01:58:17,708 --> 01:58:18,540
What?

1341
01:58:18,832 --> 01:58:21,173
They all think you're a star.

1342
01:58:21,497 --> 01:58:23,556
While you shamed Inder Vihar.

1343
01:58:23,934 --> 01:58:25,020
Listen to her

1344
01:58:25,375 --> 01:58:27,448
I became a monster for her

1345
01:58:27,787 --> 01:58:29,363
I don't want to know a monster.

1346
01:58:29,612 --> 01:58:31,687
A monster! Forget it.

1347
01:58:31,903 --> 01:58:34,580
Take my hand and say:
I love you too.

1348
01:58:34,899 --> 01:58:36,106
- Let go.
- I won't

1349
01:58:58,438 --> 01:58:59,561
I'm very sorry, Neha.

1350
01:59:00,107 --> 01:59:00,858
Are you ok?

1351
01:59:01,056 --> 01:59:02,059
Thank you

1352
01:59:02,568 --> 01:59:04,921
Aryan. He's a good guy.

1353
01:59:10,196 --> 01:59:10,928
Gaurav!

1354
01:59:19,708 --> 01:59:20,704
Get down!

1355
02:03:52,093 --> 02:03:53,133
Enough!

1356
02:03:55,049 --> 02:03:56,964
Enough of this game.

1357
02:03:58,046 --> 02:03:58,747
Get up!

1358
02:04:04,122 --> 02:04:05,455
I am happy in my life.

1359
02:04:06,662 --> 02:04:08,368
Can't you be happy in yours?

1360
02:04:11,824 --> 02:04:13,363
Be a good son to your parents.

1361
02:04:15,153 --> 02:04:16,944
A good friend, a good boyfriend.

1362
02:04:18,817 --> 02:04:21,272
Stop being a fan.

1363
02:04:28,432 --> 02:04:30,471
What's the difference between us?

1364
02:04:32,386 --> 02:04:34,259
I came from the same streets.

1365
02:04:35,009 --> 02:04:36,715
I had normal parents like you.

1366
02:04:37,881 --> 02:04:40,253
A regular house, regular school,
regular friends.

1367
02:04:57,457 --> 02:04:59,070
I made my way up alone.

1368
02:05:01,456 --> 02:05:02,939
Not in anyone's shadow

1369
02:05:06,144 --> 02:05:06,935
I'm human.

1370
02:05:08,838 --> 02:05:12,649
I laugh and cry, get mad like you.
I have a family. Responsibilities.

1371
02:05:13,684 --> 02:05:16,331
I don't have the time to meet
all my fans

1372
02:05:24,930 --> 02:05:26,197
I'll say it again

1373
02:05:28,297 --> 02:05:29,621
I'll forget all this.

1374
02:05:30,975 --> 02:05:32,070
You do the same.

1375
02:05:33,158 --> 02:05:33,950
Start over.

1376
02:05:35,657 --> 02:05:37,404
Not as Junior Aryan Khanna.

1377
02:05:42,129 --> 02:05:44,106
See how it feels like to be
Gaurav Chandna.

1378
02:05:48,289 --> 02:05:49,101
Come!

1379
02:05:55,326 --> 02:05:57,351
The joy of living as yourself...

1380
02:05:57,922 --> 02:06:00,239
cannot be matched by living
as another.

1381
02:06:01,650 --> 02:06:02,633
Stop now.

1382
02:06:04,861 --> 02:06:06,038
Live your life.

1383
02:06:07,239 --> 02:06:08,545
Let me live mine.

1384
02:06:17,008 --> 02:06:18,363
Where to, Senior?

1385
02:06:20,316 --> 02:06:22,911
You destroyed me and ask me
to let you live your life?

1386
02:06:27,209 --> 02:06:28,176
And my life?

1387
02:06:31,072 --> 02:06:33,398
You took everything from me.

1388
02:06:35,531 --> 02:06:37,112
My parents' love.

1389
02:06:38,028 --> 02:06:39,569
Neha's friendship.

1390
02:06:41,899 --> 02:06:43,773
My neighbours' smiles.

1391
02:06:52,556 --> 02:06:54,977
You were my lifeline, Senior.

1392
02:06:57,939 --> 02:06:59,049
You cut the connection.

1393
02:07:00,967 --> 02:07:03,545
OK. I'll do as you say

1394
02:07:06,208 --> 02:07:07,582
I'll stop this game.

1395
02:07:12,536 --> 02:07:14,598
I can separate myself from you.

1396
02:07:17,607 --> 02:07:21,229
But you can never separate
my name from yours.

1397
02:07:27,950 --> 02:07:29,185
You said everything.

1398
02:07:32,813 --> 02:07:34,381
But you never said sorry.

1399
02:07:39,566 --> 02:07:40,424
Gaurav!

1400
02:07:41,216 --> 02:07:42,256
No, Gaurav.

1401
02:07:43,395 --> 02:07:44,420
It's not over.

1402
02:07:44,907 --> 02:07:46,411
Think of your parents.

1403
02:07:48,802 --> 02:07:49,707
Stop this madness.

1404
02:08:07,416 --> 02:08:11,121
Forget it. You won't understand

1405
02:09:57,297 --> 02:10:01,293
Aryan Khanna has cleared
his name completely.

1406
02:10:01,875 --> 02:10:05,205
But Inder Vihar's Gaurav Chandna...

1407
02:10:05,664 --> 02:10:08,898
has tied his name to superstar
Aryan's name forever.

1408
02:10:09,227 --> 02:10:13,031
A wave of love greets Aryan's
on his birthday today.

1409
02:10:13,324 --> 02:10:18,192
Fans are singing his songs. They're
here in their thousands.

1410
02:10:20,143 --> 02:10:21,073
It's time.

1411
02:10:24,749 --> 02:10:26,317
Everyone is waiting

