This connection of mine
is an amazing thing.
If it happens
then it happens...
My connection is stronger
than WiFi or Bluetooth
He is not just a star...
He is my world
Only fake fans
cheer from distance.
I will hug him and
give my trophy to him
Everytime it's Aryan...
- What are you to Aryan Khanna?
Fan...
Aryan Khanna...
A small birthday gift
To the love of my life
Aryan Khanna
- Happy Birthday, Sir
He's a fan...
Calls himself "Junior Aryan Khanna"
Listen to me carefully
What you did...
...is wrong
- No, I did so much for you...
Who are you to do
anything for me?
Your fan
- You are not my fan
Don't say that. Can't I have
5 minutes of your time?
My life...
My time...
Why should I give
even 5 seconds?
Before, the fan used
to chase the star.
Now, the star will
chase the fan.
I would like to warn you
He can hurt anyone at anytime.
If Gaurav is there
then Aryan is there
If Gaurav is not there...
...then Aryan is nothing.