Fixed & Synced by bozxphd.Enjoy The Flick
Connection is a strange thing!
Don't ask how it works.
Our friendship goes back years.
Our connection is stronger than
Wi-Fi, Bluetooth.
The best actor award goes to
Aryan Khanna.
First time I'm getting an award,
a major award in the film industry.
This one's for you, Ma.
Thank you very much.
Before I could walk, I learned
how to jump like Aryan
Aryan? The moron!
Anyone insults him
I fight.
If I copy his style...
I get whacked.
I don't think I've done enough work.
It's just been 5 years
I still have a long way to go
as an actor and star
I'll work hard and prove
I'm a genuine superstar.
I never compare.
What is better is to say you are the
best, not bother about others.
You're the greatest.
But I'm better.
Never met him. But I spend
all day with him.
That's real connection.
Whatever he does, I cut, copy,
paste, and ditto.
Tiny difference.
He became a star.
And I became his fan.
And something else.
We live together.
In one cinema or the other.
The real drama will start now!
None of my achievements
are my own.
I am who I am today,
I am where I am today.
It's all thanks to my fans.
Without my fans, I'm nothing.
Can't you even get 40% marks?
It's always Aryan, Aryan.
My parents don't get it.
He's not just a star,
he's my world.
But God bowled a great googly.
When God was making Aryan,
some clay was left behind...
God made me with that.
He and I are different.
Poles apart.
But we are one.
He is Aryan and me, Junior Aryan.
I topped up your phone.
200 rupees.
Send the money tomorrow.
Don't worry.
Tomorrow is fine.
The shop is closing now.
Check your phone.
You're a gem. Bye, aunty
Batman, Superman!
Enough slaughter.
Shut down now. Kill the bad guys
tomorrow.
- Gaurav, what's this?
- It's only 5.30, bro.
Don't act smart. I told you.
You're out by 5.30.
Go home, kids.
Don't mess with me.
All well?
Miss Call Center, where were you?
I'm closing.
So early?
- I have a show.
- 5 minutes. Please.
No. I’ll be late.
Only 5 minutes.
It's urgent.
I need a recommendation letter
for my US visa
I have a costume trial.
Can you do it later? OK then.
Thanks
5 minutes.
You don't let us stay and for her...
Her work is urgent. You just
shoot partridges.
I get what's urgent.
Come back tomorrow.
Get lost!
You losers.
Sitting here dreaming of America
won't help you.
But staring at Aryan's photo
will help you?
- Two minutes to go.
- All done.
Thank you.
How much?
Forget it. Can't charge you
for 5 minutes.
- Thanks.
- Enjoy!
Brothers, the shop is closed.
So the action just left?
What's 30 minutes?
I put this notice up a week ago.
“Due to the grand Dussehra show.
“Organised by the Resident Welfare
Assoc. lnder Vihar, DDA Colony.
“AK Cyber Chat closes
at 5:30 sharp.
“By order Gaurav Chandna,
proprietor AK Cyber Chat".
See you again.
If I knew English well, I'd be
a computer myself.
The shop won't stay open,
even for the Prime Minister
I said it's closed. You'll get
extra time tomorrow.
You photocopy!
Don't be cruel like Ravan.
This boy needs to watch porn.
He's upset.
I don't heal upset minds
at Cyber Chat.
No porn films allowed here anyway.
Out, you guys!
You better outgrow Aryan Khanna.
Sid Kapoor is the man now.
Get smart, photocopy.
The shop in Sector 28 is open.
- Go there.
- Don't you dare touch me!
- Don't touch.
- Here, I'm touching.
Get out of here.
Let go! They need a lesson.
Want to see porn? Huh...
What are you doing?
Nothing. I let you chat.
So they made trouble
I'm fine.
You can all go. Thank you!
The jobless morons.
They came to watch blue films.
I whacked them.
Why play the hero?
Why didn't you call for help?
But I did call you.
My heart did.
So you came back.
Please, Gaurav. Stop talking
like Aryan.
Drop it. Coming to the show tonight?
Too much to do. I don't
have time like you.
Today's a birthday special.
No, thank you.
Welcome.
How did you get hurt?
Who hit you? I'll complain to
the association.
It's fine. Don't ruin my concentration.
Concentration? You can't move.
How will you go on stage?
The prize is 20,000. Cash!
You won't give me 20,000
to go and meet Aryan.
My only chance to fulfill my dream.
I don't have money to burn
on your silly dreams.
What about your Tuesday trips
to the Hanuman temple?
Doesn't your 101 -rupee donation
go up in smoke?
Hanumanji is a God.
And your Aryan...
He's important to me.
Every fool has met him,
only I haven't.
Spray some scent on me.
- Careful.
- If you can't do it, never mind.
My fans are waiting. Get ready.
Listen to your mother.
Stop your drama.
The real drama starts now.
Hold on to your hearts.
You're about to see a performance...
that the Western Union,
moving money for better...
Super Star competition
can never do without.
You guessed right.
Here he comes.
The two-year winner:
Our Aryan Khanna Junior
Jindal aunty!
Your pressure cooker on the stove?
The only whistle you'll hear
today is right here.
My hattrick year.
Today I'll share something personal.
About me and Aryan.
I hide nothing from you
I'm no ace at romancing.
But when I see her, my emotions
go haywire.
Words escape me.
Senior is an expert heart-stealer.
So I asked him...
to help his Junior.
It's delicate. I must tread carefully.
Don't forget.
The heart's job is to beat.
When you count the night stars...
and yearn to etch my name
on every star.
You know you're in love.
When you want to turn back
as you walk ahead.
When you look for me
in a crowd.
You know you're in love.
If you don't believe me.
Then hold my hand.
If your heart stops, then you know...
you're in love.
I don't have your style, Senior.
But if anyone insults you...
l want to break their teeth.
Mummy says, “Calm down”
“Aryan is India's sweetheart”.
But he's a Delhi boy after all.
Come, Senior. Let's show them
some Delhi muscle.
Ma used to say: “Don't weigh
the food you're eating.
“Don't count the guys you whack”.
Here.
Use this.
I feel like just staring
at the screen.
I have this dream.
Keep doing your thing
with your heroines
I've been your fan forever.
I think you owe me a dance.
We'll have a blast.
No one will tell who is Senior,
who is Junior. Hit it!
One last thing before I go.
I am what I am today.
I am where I am today.
It's all thanks to my fans.
Without my fans
I'm nothing.
Brothers and sisters!
The Virat act did not impress us.
The Katrina act did not impress.
This year like every other year.
The Western Union, moving money
for better...
Super Star competition's trophy
goes to our very own...
Gaurav Chandna.
Give him a big hand!
I want to thank my Mummy.
My Papa.
My God.
The greatest actor in the world.
The Aryan Khanna.
OK, go.
But why travel without a ticket?
- Go later.
- Later?
Aryan's birthday is in 2 days.
And I must wait to book a ticket?
The ticket collector will catch you
and belt you.
Remind her...
how Aryan travelled to Mumbai
for the first time.
- WT.
- Without ticket!
You want to give him the trophy?
Courier it. Post it.
Papa, count the cash again.
Phony fans cheer him from afar.
But I'll hug him and hand him
the trophy myself.
- Like this.
- Have you gone mad?
Control the boy.
Here. 20,000
ls your spit on the notes?
Socks, in the outside pocket.
Underwear, inside the bag.
Any extra underwear? I'll have
no time to wash them.
Here. Give this to him from
your Papa and me
Sohan halwa.
Tell him your father got it
especially for him.
- From Chandni Chowk.
- Why tell him? I'll show him
I'll show Aryan a family selfie.
Come, we'll get the background.
Mummy, hold the box.
I'll hold the trophy.
Papa, hide those undies.
- Cheese.
- Cheese!
- Shall I drop you at the station?
- No, you go to the shop.
- Can you manage?
- Sure.
Don't overstay at Aryan's
I've only four days leave.
Can't extend.
Don't worry, Papa. By mummy.
Be careful, son.
Where to?
Hi!
Your parents throw you out?
Keep dreaming about moving
to America
I'm off to meet Aryan,
face-to-face.
Told Aryan you're coming?
He's my Aryan, not America.
No visa needed
I'm going to America to make a new
life. You'll get zero meeting Aryan.
Forget it, you won't understand.
Hello, uncle.
Hello, aunty.
Your ice cream.
One vegetarian meal.
Seat number?
I'll get it.
If you want to stretch your legs
or your back, tell me.
It's only one night. We'll adjust.
Allow me.
Now it's OK.
Let me put uncle's plate down.
Don't worry.
We're coming.
Without ticket?
Uncle, it's a long story.
Let me explain
I'll do the explaining. Call
Ratlam police station.
Let him spend two days inside.
No more WT travelling.
Uncle, you don't get it. I could've
bought the ticket
- I want to travel without one.
- Come along
I'm not a thief or a criminal.
You see tomorrow is
Aryan Khanna's birthday.
No point if I get there late
Aryan Khanna?
Right! He went to Mumbai WT.
Stayed at Hotel Delite.
Room number 205
I'll be staying there too.
Get the picture?
Let me get to Mumbai.
You won't lose anything.
Here's the ticket money. Keep it.
- But I'll travel WT.
- Shut up!
You need a tight slap.
Take him. He won't listen.
Damn you!
Take me to Mumbai. Or I'll jump.
You'll be answering the cops
all night.
Want to die? Get back inside.
If I can't see Aryan Khanna
on his birthday...
no point living.
Don't lose your head over
these film stars.
He may be a film star to you.
But he's special to me.
Give me your hand or you'll die.
- Take me to Mumbai.
- OK! Give me your hand.
- One veg meal?
- Done. Give me your hand.
OK, hold me
ls he a relative? Do you
really know him?
ls he family? What are you
to Aryan Khanna?
A fan.
Room 205 is occupied.
Why? I've booked it.
No bookings here.
First come, first serve.
Pay cash, take the key
I'll pay double.
But only room 205.
If you don't give it to me,
just see what I'll do.
Hey boy! Move the stuff from 205
to 209.
Here, brother. Room 205 for you.
Happy birthday, Senior.
Let me pass, brother. I'm late.
Move it!
What a crowd! By God.
Brother, move aside.
The press over there.
Let them come in.
A selfie! Smile.
Thank you.
These two-faced fans.
They moan about his films.
And come here to pose with him.
You can't go there
I'm not one of them. Those FB types.
Phony fans
I'm Gaurav Chandna
I've come from Delhi. WT.
Rajdhani Express.
Guess where I'm staying?
Guess!
Hotel Delite. Room number 205.
Don't you get it?
I'll show you magic.
You'll enjoy it. Look!
When you count the night stars...
and yearn to etch her name
on every star.
You know you're in love.
When her breath is carried
by the breeze...
Lets go press.
You know you're in love.
When you turn back as you walk ahead.
Check the press IDs.
Go inside.
Not you! Don't you get it?
I want to show him my trophy
l just want him to see it.
Then I'll be gone.
Moron!
If Aryan ever hears that
you hit me...
he’ll thrash you.
It's OK. It's nothing.
Mummy sent you special halwa.
And this trophy... your birthday.
Mummy sent special halwa.
Yes, Mummy?
I'm fine
Aryan is fine, too.
I haven't met him yet. You're talking
like a child, Mummy.
He's a superstar. How can
I just meet him?
There are thousands of people
here to meet him.
They've built a 50 ft wall
in front of him.
The poor guy is stuck alone behind it.
Scream as hard as you want,
he can't hear
I'm hanging up. I'll call later.
They say common sense deserts
a man in bad times.
Seems that's Aryan Khanna's
fate now.
In his twilight years, his films
are bombing.
No surprise that he's on edge
and snappy.
On his 48th birthday, he showed
his irritation...
through his gift to Sid Kapoor.
No star has matched Aryan till now.
But Sid Kapoor...
has pulled the rug
from under his feet.
The party guests said...
Sid Kapoor just hinted that...
Aryan Khanna's days were over.
What did Kapoor tell Aryan Khanna...
that made him hit Sid Kapoor?
I went to wish him happy birthday.
Look what he did to me!
Totally out of order.
He's an elder. I respect him a lot.
I always say I've learned how
to act by watching his films.
I don't know why I make him
insecure.
What will you do?
Take legal action?
I should
I'll talk to my legal team.
Let's see what they say.
It's my duty to do something.
So no newcomer is mistreated
by a senior star.
That's all I want to say.
We'll talk after I've consulted
my legal team.
Liar! Cheat.
Playing the good boy on TV.
Anyone can see through you.
You think he's insecure?
He's seen off dozens like you.
No one has touched Aryan Khanna
for 25 years.
Do your worst, sonny!
No one can touch him.
Just you wait.
Cut it!
Great shot.
Superb!
- Liked it?
- Fantastic.
Sid Kapoor! You swallowed
Aryan Khanna whole.
What dialogue delivery!
You've destroyed Aryan Khanna.
Blew him away.
I am your biggest fan, sir.
At the contest back home...
It's my bad luck I look like Aryan,
but I always impersonate you
I win, sir
I've even won a trophy.
I love you, sir.
Let me show you my trophy, sir.
Please...
- You let the girls through.
- Let him come.
Sir says yes.
Sorry. Give me space
I'll show you my act?
OK
The mind always outsmarts
the face, Mr. Singhania.
You can ape someone.
But you can't ape his mind.
When all doors are shut.
There's a knock at mind's door.
And when that door opens,
you see a new road.
I have walked that road to you,
Singhania.
And through that very door
you shall walk to your peril.
You're too good, fan.
Well done, man.
Relax man, calm down.
I have the same jacket you're wearing.
That's good. Very nice.
- Sir's lunch break now.
- One chance, sir
Santosh, bring me the salad
in half an hour.
And this fan, come on!
Hear that?
- Sit down.
- No, thank you.
Sir, a small suggestion from a fan.
Why fight with Aryan Khanna?
Why bother with the police
and police reports?
That's nothing, bro
I'll drag him to court.
Allow me.
Time's up for Aryan Khanna.
- I'll wring your neck.
- Santosh!
To hell with Santosh.
Shut up! No one is coming.
Close your mouth.
Now listen... sit quietly...
Don't open your mouth again
to insult Aryan. One peep and...
I'll crush your chocolate face
with the wrapper.
No fan will look at you again.
Spouting pearls of wisdom on TV.
Look at my camera.
Read! Here's the script.
Learn the lines.
Do your rubbish acting.
Your damn phone never
stops ringing.
Now I’ll see.
Read it!
Start.
It's in Hindi, dude.
You're a Hindi film hero
and you can't read Hindi?
Where do they find you guys?
What do you film people say?
Action!
Dear Aryan sir
I'm really very sorry.
My statement to the press
was all lies
I wanted to spoil your name.
No one can take your place.
You're the best.
The greatest, the most evergreen
super-duper star.
I apologise again.
Think of me as your kid brother
and forgive me.
Why won't he play with you?
Shall I tell him to?
Dad, he bullies me.
He bullies you because
he's scared of you.
He thinks you'll win. We'll cheat!
- Dhruv, let's play.
- Dad, come on.
Play with lsha. I've trained her.
- I am so sorry.
- Dad, you made me lose a point.
Now she's ahead of you.
Try and win from her
I'm glad Sid realised his mistake.
He's a great guy. Young and new.
Glad it got sorted.
Ladies and gentlemen,
last point, next point.
Nothing is sorted, it's a game.
Apology. Say sorry - it's all a game.
You should've controlled yourself
I tried very hard
I gave him one slap. More a pat.
See the scandal it's created.
If someone comes to my house,
drinks my expensive wine.
Flirts with my wife. Must I just
stand by and watch?
You have no time.
Let someone else flirt with me.
Actually you're right.
But not this moron.
The video has gone viral.
Social media is abuzz.
Join us for the stock market news
after this short break
Aryan, wake up!
What happened?
Did you sleep here all night?
I was reading a script. It was
so good that I dozed off
Sunaina is here. She has something
to wake you up with.
Good morning, Aryan.
It's too early, Sunaina
I know. I'm really sorry.
I have to tell you something.
- Are you pregnant?
- Shut up, Aryan.
See this.
Come on. Look here and say
your lines. Hurry.
Dear Aryan sir.
Look here. Look at the camera.
OK. I'll do it.
- Come on.
- Did Aryan send you?
Aryan has nothing to do with it.
Do as you're told. The camera.
If you want cash, take it.
Just let me go.
Cash? I'll give you cash.
Stop! I'll do it.
What will you do? Scum!
A fan.
Calls himself Junior Aryan Khanna.
He sent a message.
“A small birthday gift to the love
of my life, Senior Aryan Khanna.
Call me once to thank me.
My life will be set”.
Hello.
Junior Aryan Khanna?
You calling from Aryan's house?
YES
Where is Senior? Aryan Khanna?
He's busy right now. He asked me
to call you.
How come he's so busy?
No time to talk to his Junior?
I did so much for him.
I came to the house on his birthday,
The crowd...
Yeah, yeah, hello
Aryan...
Aryan Khanna?
Gaurav this side.
Your fan, your Junior.
Where are you?
Just guess
Delite hotel, in your room.
Room no. 205. Charni Road.
Remember?
But if you're calling to say
thank you, it won't do.
I deserve a hug from my brother.
- You want to see me?
- Sure
I made a big scandal just to meet you.
Wait there. I'll send a car to
pick you up.
Done, Senior.
Thank you!
Mind blasting.
Really?
Go by taxi.
You're going to Aryan Khanna's.
Don't go by auto-rickshaw.
He's sending me his personal car.
He's invited me home.
Don't forget to take pictures.
If he offers you any food, no
pouncing on it like a pauper.
Food? I'm not going for the food.
I'm going there to hug him.
Tell him to wear the clothes I had
made for him at Diwali.
- Make sure he takes the trophy.
- As though he wouldn't.
- Say hello from me.
- And me, too.
OK. I'll tell him.
Phone me once you've met him.
The car's here. Call you later.
The car is there.
Hello.
Are you the driver?
Junior Aryan Khanna?
- Did you act smart with Sid Kapoor?
- No.
You're mistaken.
Did Sid Kapoor send you?
I'll tell you later. Come
I'm meeting Aryan.
I won't go anywhere.
- Like hell you won't.
- I won't come.
Don't touch me.
No touching.
Let me go!
Stop!
Try catching me!
- Stop! You rascal.
- Please don't hit me.
Don't hit hard. We have orders.
Let's go.
Let me call Aryan Khanna.
Where are you taking me?
Sid Kapoor is evil. Don't get
mixed up with him.
Shut up!
I did it for Aryan Khanna.
His problem is my problem.
If Aryan hears about this...
he’ll skin you alive.
Stop!
Think carefully. We'll be back.
Let's go.
Good evening, sir. Come in.
We asked him why he made the video.
He says he'll talk only to you.
You told us to go easy on him.
- Hardly touched him.
- Thank you.
- Usman.
- Yes, sir?
This is for his expenses.
Keep him here for 2 days.
Get him a ticket to Delhi.
Take him to the station.
As I said, don't beat him up
too badly.
Just enough to scare him.
No one must hear about this.
No police record, no video statement.
Please.
Sure, sir.
Where is he?
I want to meet him alone.
- You stay here.
- Yeah
Gaurav.
Senior.
You're here.
I knew you'd come.
They hit me and hit me.
They broke my bones.
I protected my face.
It's Aryan Khanna's face.
Nothing must happen to it.
See? Same to same.
Everyone calls me Junior
Aryan Khanna. But I say...
there’s only one Aryan Khanna.
Relax.
It's OK.
I impersonate you at the yearly
Super Star competition.
Always win first prize.
The bastards took my bag.
My trophy was in it.
I brought it to show you.
I could show you my act
I'm nervous in front of you.
It's all right. Sit.
No audience here. Their screaming
and cheering helps.
- Are you from Delhi?
- West Delhi.
You're from Rajender Nagar,
I'm from lnder Vihar.
Two traffic lights from the TV tower.
Near DAV Park.
Listen carefully.
You did something nasty.
It's a crime.
A crime in the eyes of the law.
Love in your eyes, no?
Not love, it's stupidity.
Do you have family?
There's Papa, Mummy.
And you, too.
Have you thought what
your parents would say?
They'd be sad seeing you
in that sadistic video.
Why would we show it to them?
It was for you.
Did you like my birthday gift?
Sid Kapoor? I beat the crap
out of him.
I don't understand how the cops
discovered our little secret.
Our?
There is no “our” between
you and me.
The police brought you here
on my orders.
You made a mistake. You
had to be punished.
So you won't mess up again.
On your orders? I did so much for you.
Who are you to do anything
for me?
I'm your fan.
- You're my star.
- Fan? So you do as you please?
Thrash people? Murder?
If need be, I could murder for you.
You're not my fan.
Don't say that.
I risked my life to meet you.
I hit Sid Kapoor a little, so you'd
meet me. What did I want...
in return?
To see you, a few photos,
an autograph. That's all.
- Can't you spare 5 min of your life?
- It's my life.
Why must I give you even
five seconds?
I am who I am today,
where I am today.
My stardom.
It's all thanks to my fans.
If it weren't for my fans...
I'd be nothing
Gaurav makes Aryan.
Without Gaurav...
Aryan is nothing.
Now you listen carefully.
When the police let you go,
go straight to Delhi, get it?
I'll forget all about Gaurav.
And you forget you ever met Aryan.
Stay in your life.
I stay in mine.
This is your final warning. OK.
Forget it.
You won't understand.
Yes, Mummy
I'll be home soon.
Everything OK?
Everything is fine.
Why didn't you take my call?
I was busy
Gaurav, we're worried about you.
Don't worry.
You'll come home soon?
Tell Papa to mind the Cyber Cafe.
Are you eating properly?
The food is fine here.
Thank you.
Come, hero. Sir wants you.
Whatever happened has happened.
Put it behind you. Right?
Thank you, brother. I made
a mistake. Sorry
Gaurav!
Did you hug Aryan Khanna?
Didn't he meet you?
Didn't spare 5 minutes?
Don't you feel bad.
It's not my loss. It's his.
He's happy where he is.
I'm happy where I am.
Mummy, make me some
rice and beans tonight.
Hello, aunty.
You're moving out?
Who knows what this boy wants.
Got a good price?
Don't worry, Papa. I'll invest wisely.
Too much time wasted on Aryan.
The shop is sold, Mummy.
Let's go.
Hurry. You coming?
- Let's go.
- OK, come.
All well, aunty?
Fans chase stars.
Now a star will chase a fan.
Whenever Aryan Khanna's name
is taken...
it’ll be in the same breath
as Gaurav Chandna
1 Year later.
Welcome to Bollywood Café.
98.1 FM.
Do you know what's special
about the weekend?
Guys, this weekend...
is the Aryan Khanna reloaded
show presented by Hyundai.
Stars have a great life
I want a life like Aryan's.
Full on, jet setter!
One day in London, Dubrovnik the next.
For the grand Bhutiani wedding.
Then back to the London show.
Wow!
Do you know London is
one of his favourite places?
In fact he considers it his
second home after Mumbai.
We have some good news
and some bad news.
The bad news first, obviously.
The Hyundai Aryan Khanna reloaded
show is houseful.
Oh no! What's the good news?
We have 20 free tickets
for our listeners.
Who ever is the first to answer
my question correctly...
wins a free show ticket.
My question follows straight after
this beautiful song.
Here's your tickets. Enjoy your visit.
- How can I help you?
- One ticket please.
Enjoy your visit.
The real drama starts now
Aryan Khanna!
Mr. Khanna, Tim Baker,
the Manager
Aryan Khanna, the actor.
I hope it's not a bother.
Fans never bother.
Sir, a photo with your wax figure.
Let me say this. It's amazing.
You've come all the way to London...
to take a photo with
my wax figure.
Really, that's very sweet.
ls this better?
Better now?
Let me warn you.
I was much younger then.
You like it?
Honestly...
it's very scary.
So, does he look like me?
- You look great in real life.
- Exactly, darling
I agree. What a fat nose he has.
My nose is tiny.
A phony face.
A fake smile.
All phony.
I don't smile like this.
Actually no one smiles like this.
His hair smells bad.
Feels bad, looks bad.
In fact, I don't look like him at all.
This is a fake
Aryan Khanna is a fake.
I want a refund. Aryan Khanna
is a fake.
This isn't right. You can't do this
to our property.
The white man claims
my face is his property.
Mr. Property Agent. This is me.
My face, my property.
- Stop now and leave, sir.
- I won't leave.
It's a joke. You guys can't
take a joke.
Come here. Come.
Who can stop me?
I'll shoot you all.
I don't understand what
you're talking about.
You are gonna be in a lot
of trouble over this.
Really?
You are in trouble too.
Stay out of my way! I'll shoot.
You alright?
Aryan...
What?
Come out.
What are you saying?
Arrest warrant for you.
What the hell is this?
I didn't go to Madame Tussauds.
- The Indian Ambassador on line.
- I'm not talking to any Ambassador
I'm here to arrest him.
Sir, Mr. Khanna did not go to
Madame Tussauds...
Are you Mr. Khanna?
Then just shut up and let me
do my job.
Excuse me. So you are doing
your job and we are faffing?
Must say you have a very polite way
of talking to women, Mr. Duncan.
Guess what?
It's my turn to be polite now.
This, sir, is nonsense.
Where were you between
10 and 10.30 this morning?
- I was at home.
- And who were you with?
I was alone.
Did anyone see you at home?
I just told you I was alone
Aryan, I'll call our lawyer.
Can you talk in a language
we all can understand?
Let me translate it in a language
you understand.
Lawyer.
Two options.
Handcuffs if you are nasty,
without handcuffs if you are nice.
Nasty.
Just five minutes.
You stay here.
Just five minutes sir, please.
Let's call Akhtar.
What happened?
Lost your funny bone?
That's not me.
Behaves like you.
Looks like you.
Everybody calls this person
by your name.
I said that's not me.
You have any proof?
Say something, Mr. Superstar.
Not to you, Mr. Small-Time cop.
Not a word without my lawyer.
Suit yourself
24 hrs remand for Mr. Khanna.
Till he comes out with the truth.
- You can't do that.
- Sure, I can.
Sir, one photograph please?
- You have a safe trip, sir.
- Yeah, I will be.
It's time. Lets go.
DUBROVNIK
In Croatian, we say - How are you?
I'm fine.
My name is Gaurav.
Thank you.
Vegetable sandwich... one.
Which one do you want?
This one?
OK. Here we go.
No, no, more. Six more.
It's OK. Here.
Thank you.
Thanks.
It's only bail.
We know you're lying.
Why would I waste my lies on you?
That was no imposter.
You twisted psycho.
We'll have you back
in jail in no time.
Please do that.
Maybe I'll earn some money suing you
and the entire British police
Aryan, control your temper.
It's their city, their country.
Don't make matters worse
for yourself.
So we're done with all
the formalities?
Thanks a lot.
Pathetic fool
I'm coming with you to Dubrovnik
in case of any immigration problem.
Hey! Not that way.
The press is outside
Aryan, this is Deputy High
Commissioner, Mr. Murthy.
Pleased to meet you.
Sorry you had to go through
all this but...
We can't interfere very much.
This is a foreign country after all
I know. Rules in every country
are made to get the innocent.
Sir, we're diplomats, not detectives.
Before the case is solved, we have
permission for you to travel.
Now we can only do that much.
It's a serious matter.
A diplomatic issue.
So you must prove it wasn't you
at Madame Tussauds.
Must I prove it? OK, I'll play cop.
I really appreciate your help.
Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
In jail or dancing at a wedding...
these stars are so arrogant.
Your home CCTV footage has saved us.
It's with the police.
It proves an impostor was at Madame
Tussauds and you were at home.
Who is he? What's his motive.
Forget the London cops.
Find out. We need to get this guy.
We'll know more back in London.
So you know you can
really relax now.
Wine? Champagne? Anything?
Everything.
Come on, Aryan. It's over now.
Sir, a call.
He says he knows the imposter
at Madame Tussauds.
- Give me the phone. I'll talk.
- He'll only talk to sir.
He won't give me his name.
Give it to me.
Hello.
Senior
Chandna?
I won't let you forget my name.
It'll be taken in the same breath
as your name.
What do you want?
The stage is set.
Tell everyone - admit what you did
was wrong.
You'll never break a fan's heart
again. Say sorry.
Stop this nonsense! I'm not
apologizing to anyone.
I tried to make you see sense.
If you had agreed to give me
5 minutes.
I would have my life.
You would have yours.
But you had to prove you had
star power.
Now you'll see a fan's power
I'm a star.
I took your pranks as childishness.
Threw you inside for only 2 days.
If l knew the real you,
you'd still be inside.
In 48 hours you snatched away
my devotion of 25 years.
If you don't say sorry...
in the next 48 hours,
your stardom is over.
Do what you want
I've seen off dozens like you.
The higher you fly, the harder
I'll make you fall.
But you must fly as high as me,
Gaurav Chandna.
Impossible for you.
We'll see how far you get
impersonating me.
I don't need to go far.
You're getting closer to me.
In Dubrovnik.
Idiot. He's in Dubrovnik.
Unknown caller, unknown location.
Obviously, Sunaina. He won't
call from a traceable number.
Say sorry. It's no big deal.
He's mad
ls that so? And what am I?
ls the make-up team in place?
They are on there way.
Oh great. The props, fireworks,
confetti all that.
We've done a couple of rehearsals.
Everything's perfect.
OK. Thank you
Aryan asked for a background
check of all the staff members
- ls it done yet?
- It's going on right now.
OK. Thank you
Nicksi Jelopera.
- Medium?
- Medium size.
You're so late, Aryan Khanna.
It's just not done
I apologise. I'm extremely sorry,
Mr. Bhutiani
I had a crisis, I'm sorry.
You celebrities always have
some crisis.
But my daughter doesn't
get married everyday
- I know. I'm sorry.
- You've no idea.
That stunt you pulled in London has
caused me great loss of face.
No, Mr. Bhutiani.
What happened at Madame Tussauds...
You know what? I'll make
it up to you
I swear. Your guests will always think
of the grand Bhutiani wedding.
They better do.
After all I'm spending
a bomb on you.
Only you can. I'll get ready
Sunaina, find out where
the CCTV cameras are
Usman, watch the guest areas,
the bars, the toilets, the corridors.
- Keep an eye on everyone.
- Excuse me, sir
I'm really sorry to interrupt but
we just have 2 minutes.
I don't need two, darling.
Let's go, I'm ready.
Good luck.
Payal, tell me the names
ls Bhutiani's son-in-law called
Amul Mirchandani?
It's Anmol Mirchandani.
Guys, all the best. Break
a leg and do well.
And sisters Anushka, Deepshika?
That's for later, it's all here.
Second entry dance 5,6,7,8.
You're giving it to me.
- Sir, your shades.
- Thank you, Payal.
OK guys. You have 30 seconds
to go.
All the best, just kill it.
Check all entries and exits.
OK, Sunaina.
Find anything?
Not yet, sir. I've spoken to the team,
no one enters without an invite.
Sir, your cue cards
15 secs to go.
Can you go to cam 4.
When you count the night stars...
and yearn to etch her name
on every star.
You know you're in love.
When you want to turn back
as you walk ahead.
When you look for her in a crowd,
you know you're in love.
“Say sorry".
Check the crew's photos.
He's not a guest. He's crew.
Quick.
Got it.
Sorry.
There. Zoom in.
Check the crew backstage.
COPY
Payal, we need the crew ids.
Photographs and bio-datas.
- Anything serious, sir?
- Aryan wants to know.
Sorry.
It's fine.
The crew is local.
Except one guy. Half Indian,
half Croatian
Akhtar is sending you a photo
of him.
Keep a close eye.
Round up all the crew.
- Any sign of him?
- Sir, nothing.
He's not responding
Sunaina.
Can't see him on any camera.
- But I'm at it.
- What are you at it?
Where is there no CCTV camera?
Your make-up room.
Careful, sir.
“Gaurav makes Aryan".
You're very stubborn.
You don't listen to me.
Why are you hiding?
Talk face-to-face.
I stand face-to-face, Aryan Khanna.
But you never see me.
Now when I'm not there, you're
longing to see me.
I know the feeling.
I felt it among the crowd
in front of your house.
Sir, the Bhutianis are waiting.
The audience interaction...
Yeah. I'm coming.
- I'll take care of it.
- Thank you
I'll come back and see you.
Hi sweetheart.
Hope you enjoyed the show.
- Aryan, it was marvelous.
- Thank you.
That's my daughter.
She's been practicing a step to
dance with you for two months.
Actually we were both practicing.
How pretty is she.
You know what? Let me start
with the young one
and I'll come back
for the experience.
We've found Chandna.
In the corridor, across from where
you're dancing
I'm not dancing
Chandna is on the dance floor.
What the hell is wrong with him?
I was dancing. He started touching me
here, there, everywhere.
I don't know. You'll have
to do something.
- Get him out.
- I don't care.
What the hell are you doing?
Mr. Bhutiani?
- Where do you think you are?
- Calm down, Mr. Bhutiani.
- What happened?
- That girl is like my daughter
ls this how you film stars behave?
I'm really sorry, ladies.
I'm sorry
I'll explain. The guy who was
here wasn't me.
- Nonsense.
- It was somebody else
I'm Aryan Khanna.
- I'm Aryan Khanna.
- What nonsense!
You known me for years
I love you guys. I'd never
harm you people.
That person wasn't me.
I suggest you leave.
Keep back!
Stop the car!
No one has given me the
interaction script
15 minutes to show time.
ls there a delay?
What?
The show's canceled.
They've boycotted the show.
Sponsors have also pulled out.
Nobody came, not a soul.
Whats wrong with you?
You wimp.
Watch where you're going?
Media playing up the story.
The wedding video has gone viral.
“Given Khanna's status, he must
take responsibility for his actions
“ls he attention-seeking?
“Movie stars forget that one day
they'll be has-beens.
“Stars must go through traumas.
Look at what his done.
“It's a crime if an ordinary man
misbehaves...
“...if it's a star - it's a stunt.
Why these double standards...
“...for stars? A criminal is
a criminal".
Hello.
Hello, sir. It's me, Aryan.
I'm calling from London.
I know you are in London,
but what's going on?
A Delhi boy is impersonating me,
committing crimes.
We have to arrest him.
But the crimes are committed
outside of India.
We can't arrest him. It's not
in our jurisdiction.
Must we wait till he commits
a crime in India?
His name is Gaurav Chandna.
Find me his Delhi address.
It will help.
You don't teach me my job.
But who shall we arrest?
You're the accused, Aryan.
I just...
Come back to India.
Then we'll look into the matter with
the proper procedure. OK?
Hello.
What did he say?
Organise a press conference
first thing tomorrow.
- In Mumbai?
- No, here in London.
You now have the video footage
and all the documents, etc.
You have proof...
that Aryan Khanna did not
commit these crimes.
You're angry with me, and you
have the right to be.
But believe me.
That dangerous and evil face
you see on TV is not me.
That person is not me.
So please give me time.
Time, so that I can prove
I've done nothing wrong
I'd never do anything that
would make you ashamed...
to call me your star.
Whatever I am...
I just want to say, I would
never do anything like this.
Thank you.
Sir, do you know this impostor?
Have you met him?
Sorry. We can't talk now.
The case is under trial.
What about the imposter's name?
As soon as we have proof,
you'll be the first to know.
Are you the real Aryan Khanna
or the imposter?
You find this funny? A big joke?
If this happened to a girl in your
family would you still be grinning?
A woman was molested and
you find it's funny?
And one more thing.
This press meet is not
to prove my innocence.
I want to warn you all.
The man who's impersonating me,
spoiling my name.
He can hurt anyone, anytime.
So please be careful.
Thank you everybody.
Thanks for coming
Aryan has a flight to catch, he's
going back to India.
So have a great day and
see you soon.
MUMBAI
Don't stop, go from behind.
Open up!
One minute, sir. Madam said we must
inform her.
Good. Hurry up.
Before the journalists outside mob me.
Hello.
Ma'am, can sir come in?
No, wait a second.
- Are you sure it's him?
- It sounds like sir.
Ask him to face the camera.
Sir, ma'am wants you to step forward.
Hi, I am Aryan Khanna. Height 5'10.
Black hair, black eyes.
A big nose.
School: Kendriya Vidyalaya,
New Delhi.
Hans Raj College, Delhi University.
Give me the phone, quick!
The press will surround me.
Let me in. Or I'll end up
in their arms.
Why is your phone off?
Can I tell you inside?
Open the door.
Guys. Dad's here
Aryan, you're back?
- Hi.
- You're back.
- Yes, I'm back.
Are the kids asleep?
Yes. It's way past their bedtime.
Of course.
Let them sleep.
Let's relax and talk quietly
in our room.
YES
- What an entrance exam!
- You passed with flying colours
I spent my life preparing
for this moment.
Relax. Make yourself a drink.
I'll run the shower for you.
Of course.
She was crying. Not easy getting
her to sleep again.
It's better for us both if lsha
stays asleep.
I did say...
we could talk calmly.
Why do you need that?
Give.
I have nothing against you
or your children.
Give me that.
Senior ignores me.
You can't let him do that.
Show me Aryan's study, he's
always talking about it.
Sound asleep.
Come, come.
Sit. He lands in 20 minutes.
I haven't much time.
Come on, sit down.
This room has so many stories.
Many stories behind these awards.
In these costumes.
Days that Aryan does not want
to forget.
Memories he wants to keep close
to his heart.
I treasured his memories too.
Kept them right here.
At home, on the walls of my room,
in cupboards.
On shelves like these
Aryan Khanna filled every corner
of my life.
But he ended it all.
Five minutes! I asked him for
only five minutes.
Know what he said?
“It's my life.
Why must I give you even
five seconds of it?”
- I apologise on his behalf.
- Why should you apologise?
I hit Sid Kapoor for his sake.
He was hassling Aryan.
What did Aryan do? Threw me in jail.
Had me beaten.
Said: “It's a crime!” A crime?
Crime is what I'll do now.
Breaking hearts of fans who are
devoted to you...
is a crime too.
You tell me.
Am I so wrong?
When he fights with you,
doesn't he say sorry?
So, why can't he say sorry to me?
Tell me!
Don't do this. I beg you.
What do you mean “please”?
He left nothing for me. Why must
I leave anything for him?
How can l? Impossible.
A sham. All lies.
Liar. He's a fake.
The rascal acts all the time.
An actor after all.
I wanted to give him my trophy.
A belated happy birthday,
Aryan Khanna.
Open the door!
I sent the children to my parents.
They were terrified. I didn't know
what to tell them
lsha asked me repeatedly: “Why did
Papa destroy the study?
Don't worry. It's OK.
- Why don't we call the police?
- The police will do nothing.
They'll ask for proof. They believe
I'm the criminal.
I came this far in life
on my own steam
I'll handle it myself.
Play rough like a street hoodlum
I'll rip him apart. Send him back
to where he belongs
Gaurav Chandna has seen my star face.
Now he'll see my real face
I'm a Delhi man too.
The dangerous and evil face
on the news is not me.
That person is not me.
Give me time
I'll prove I've done nothing wrong
I'd never do anything to make you
ashamed calling me your star
Aryan Khanna's press conference
proves that he is innocent.
A criminal is impersonating him
and committing crimes.
Who is the culprit? His name?
His whereabouts?
No one knows the motives
behind his terrible actions.
The police have informed us that
they're very hopeful...
this criminal will not escape them.
When he's arrested, he'll be
severely punished.
Hello, Gauru.
Mummy.
What's wrong with your phone?
Where are you, Gauru?
Right here
I'm OK.
And you?
Son, come home soon.
We're in trouble.
You've roamed the world, now return
to your home
Aryan?
You barged into my home?
You can barge into mine, can't I
do the same?
I came here to grab your
parents by the throat.
To ask why they produced
a nasty son like you.
- But I am not a lowlife like you.
- Don't drag my parents into this.
They did nothing.
What did my kids do?
I went alone into your fortress.
Did you bring an army?
I am here alone, Gaurav Chandna.
No security, no secretary.
No star, no hero.
If you have the guts, face me.
Settle the score.
The score will only be settled
when you apologise.
Get on the stage at the lnder Vihar
contest and say sorry.
And listen...
If you touch my parents with
a feather even...
I know your mother-in-law's house,
where your children are hiding.
Your daughter is very cute, by God.
- Your son is stubborn like you.
- You rascal
I'll bury you in a gutter here, if you
dream of harming my kids.
What will my parents think?
Such a big star...
with such a foul tongue.
Forget it.
See you at the contest.
Your son has lost his mind.
- He's crossed the line.
- Our Gaurav was not like that.
He was a good boy.
He changed after meeting you.
What would you have lost
if you gave him 5 mins?
Don't blame Aryan.
It's our fault.
We let him get obsessed by
your glamorous life.
Not your hard slog. He would've
followed your example.
Worked hard and become someone.
Then the call center girl could've
become his girlfriend or wife.
He has a girlfriend?
A one-way romance.
Gaurav loves her but...
Enough. We have to accept things
the way they are.
- Where's the contest held?
- The other end of the colony.
Apologise. End this terrible situation.
You think I'm wrong too?
And I must apologise?
Arrest him.
He must be punished
lmprison him for years, if you must.
But don't beat him.
Please.
Hey Junior. Where were you?
- Hello Uncle, Aunty.
- Hello.
Have you been watching the
news on TV about Aryan?
Never mind
I have good news for you all
I've got my American visa
I knew it.
Why is he standing with his back
to me? It's not like him.
He's going on stage soon,
he's just nervous.
Him? And nervous?
Has he done anything in life
besides copying Aryan?
Hey Superstar, your make-up...
Neha.
I have to talk to you.
Super surprise!
Western Union - moving money
for better.
Now for the last act of the
Super Star competition.
Our favourite winner.
Our Junior Aryan Khanna.
He's a criminal!
Get him off the stage.
Calm down.
It's not the real Aryan Khanna.
It's our very own superstar...
Gaurav Chandna.
Give him a big hand!
I do a show for Aryan every year.
I know, Aunty. You cheer the loudest.
But this year's show...
The show today is for...
someone else.
The girl over there who is...
smiling at me. She's my friend
Neha!
Come, babes.
There's something I've kept
in my heart for days.
I love you, Neha.
- I love you too, Aryan.
- Not Aryan
Gaurav loves you
Gaurav loves Neha.
What nonsense!
Get lost.
- He's nuts.
- Thinks he's real Aryan Khanna.
Get him off.
Wait! He is talking to me.
I'll deal with it.
I love you!
Drop it. You love only Aryan.
He can go to hell
- ls that you talking?
- It's not just talk
I've sent him to hell.
I fixed Aryan Khanna for good.
First in London, then in Dubrovnik.
I made my way into his house too.
Smashed everything in sight.
If you don't believe me, read the
papers. Watch TV or the Net.
Your Gaurav is famous the world over
I'm no less than Aryan.
Not at all.
I am a star in real life.
Not a star. A monster.
What?
They all think you're a star.
While you shamed lnder Vihar.
Listen to her
I became a monster for her
I don't want to know a monster.
A monster! Forget it.
Take my hand and say:
“| love you too”.
- Let go.
- I won't
I'm very sorry, Neha.
Are you OK?
Thank you
Aryan. He's a good guy
Gaurav!
Get down!
Enough!
Enough of this game.
Get up!
I am happy in my life.
Can't you be happy in yours?
Be a good son to your parents.
A good friend, a good boyfriend.
Stop being a fan.
What's the difference between us?
I came from the same streets.
I had normal parents like you.
A regular house, regular school,
regular friends.
I made my way up alone.
Not in anyone's shadow
I'm human.
I laugh and cry, get mad like you.
I have a family. Responsibilities.
I don't have the time to meet
all my fans
I'll say it again
I'll forget all this.
You do the same.
Start over.
Not as Junior Aryan Khanna.
See how it feels like to be
Gaurav Chandna.
Come!
The joy of living as yourself...
cannot be matched by living
as another.
Stop now.
Live your life.
Let me live mine.
Where to, Senior?
You destroyed me and ask me
to let you live your life?
And my life?
You took everything from me.
My parent's love.
Neha's friendship.
My neighbours' smiles.
You were my lifeline, Senior.
You cut the connection.
OK. I'll do as you say
I'll stop this game.
I can separate myself from you.
But you can never separate
my name from yours.
You said everything.
But you never said sorry
Gaurav!
No, Gaurav.
It's not over.
Think of your parents.
Stop this madness.
Forget it. You won't understand
Aryan Khanna has cleared
his name completely.
But lnder Vihar's Gaurav Chandna...
has tied his name to superstar
Aryan's name forever.
A wave of love greets Aryan's
on his birthday today.
Fans are singing his songs. They're
here in their thousands.
It's time.
Everyone is waiting