Easy, friends.
She's with me.
Time for bed little one.
Can I bring him?
Of course.
Good night.
Excuse me, sorry.
Does he know?
I'm taking the GT40.
This car suits me better.
It's okay...
we're all going to the same place.
We'll get the car there.
Go after the girl!
Hurry up!
The American fugitives killed three
DEA agents during a train robbery...
...Police warn they are armed
and extremely dangerous.
Anyone with information should contact
law enforcement immediately...
I apologize for
the interruption.
Senior Reyes,
may I speak with you?
We've found them.
Go that way!
The other two
went over the wall!
I told you the skinny
chick had balls.
Looks like she started
the party without us.
What's this guy saying?
Ugly is still ugly in
Spanish or in English.
Nobody move!
Explain.
They invaded
the Leblon house.
Who invaded?
The men from the train.
How much did they take?
They didn't
take anything.
They burned it!
They burned my money?
Yes. And said
there's more coming.
Okay...
Then this...
...is what
we're going to do.
Clean the houses.
I want that money
under lock and key...
...within an hour.
Understand?
Understood.
Looks like this is going to be a
shorter trip than I thought...
Everything okay?
Everything is okay.
Who is this Hobbs?
This Federal Agent running around town?
Some American cowboy.
He's handled.
He killed sixteen
of our men.
Handle him better.
Look... He requested a rookie
patrol officer as his assistant.
They won't be a problem.
It's all here?
Yes.
What about Toretto and O'Conner?
Where are they?
Nothing yet.
But I have all our
officers searching.
Not good enough.
Put a price
on their heads.
High enough...
...to get every pair of eyes in
the city searching for them.
Two to one says
you blow the wrong pipe.
I ain't negative.
I'm just positive
you're going to mess it up.
Next time if there's no
elevator, I'm not coming.
You need to learn
to relax, loco.
You better hurry up,
we got less than a minute.
Why do you always set
the timer so short?
I hope you know
where you're going.
...a police station.
You used too much
explosive! Again.
Too much, too little...
it's all the same.
That's some Buddha shit you learned from
a book in the prison library, isn't it?
And what you're doing
there on the wall...
You got that from
the same book, huh?
Dominic Toretto's
ride in my garage.
Now that...
will be a nice trophy.
I know she's here!
Find her!
Go! Go! Go!
Yo, you burned it!
Yeah, but your mom is the
worst cook in the world.
Yo, don't you be talking
about my momma.
See?
I called in every cop
on our payroll.
We're covered.
We've got every entrance
covered with weapons teams.
God Himself couldn't get at
your money if He wanted to.
God isn't my worry.
What's happening?
They're taking the vault!
What?
The vault!
Follow me! Quickly!
Let me through!
Don't move!
Stay down.
Zizi, stay on them.
They can't outrun us
on the bridge.
They have no way out.
Hey, what is he doing?
We've got him!
Close down the bridge!
Do something, asshole!
Kill him, dammit!
Kill him now!
”For Rosa and Nico.
See you soon, -Uncle Dom”
MONACO
You sure about this?
You know I am.
You don't need to do this.
Just leave me alone.
Bro, I'm not trying to
be negative, but casinos
are the kinds of places designed to
take money from guys like you and me.
When I win here I'm buying you a
lifetime supply of antidepressants.
You don't put
ten million on red!
Enough already.
You put it on black.
No more bets.
DIPLOMATIC SECURITY SERVICE HEADQUARTERS
- WASHINGTON, D.C.