We swap in parts from Ford
Plymouths and Cadillac.
My grandfather bought it in 1957.
When he died he passed it to my father.
Then my brother and now to me.
Look at this,
this is an engine from a boat.
Whatever it takes to keep it running!
Your spirit, keep it up.
Never ever lose that.
It's your cousin..
He's in trouble, come quickly!
Come on, come on.
Please don't do this, understand my problem.
You should show your people some respect.
I am really scared.
Are you ready for this, family?
This is Havana!
Be fast!
Be safe!
But don't be last.
Racers ready...?
Go...!
Stop.
Can I help you with that?
Look out...!
We land back in Moscow by nine.
Here's the latest defense report,
All the items in yesterday's meet.
What is going on?
Drive fast!
Drive! Drive!
There's more cars ahead of us.
Shoot their engines.
Oh God!
Faster, faster!
- Who the hell is that?
- What is he doing?
What the hell are you waiting for?
Shoot him!
Come on, come on!
I'm out.
Shit.
Don't worry sir.
This car is bulletproof.
You'll be safe in here.
Give him the case.
These are nuclear launch codes.
We cannot give it to him.
What is he doing now?
He just cut a hole in our gas tank.
See you later...
We have a possible threat incoming.
Raise the barricade, As soon as possible.
We've lost power, get to your positions now.
Engaging target.
He's beneath the Sub.
I'm losing control, mayday, mayday.
I'm going down.
You're driving.
I said it from the beginning.
No way, I'm not driving.