Allright, we're good to go
You got this?
You bet your ass, bubba.
let's make some money!
Everyone in position?
I thought that we would be robbing banks by now
not some gas truck
in the middle of nowhere.
Down here, gas is gold, bubba.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
I wouldn’t piss them off guys
Ok guys we got to hit this hard fast
we got 14 left before they drive to bridge
Locked and loaded
This is all you, Han
Liquid gold
ha, ha
Were clear
Okay, T, you're up.
Let's see if you can get it under
6 tries this time, huh, T?
More like three come on Tego
keep it real
Just one K left. We're running
out of road. Get in there, brother.
I got it, I got it
Oh shit
Tear cut loose, un-Hitch... un-Hitch
Spray that hitch!
I don't have a hammer!
Just do it
Hold on, hold on
Oh shit
Hold on to something tight
give me your hand, I can't reach
you gotta jump
Jump
Letty, jump!
I've got you!
Dom
Credits to original uploader
Fixed by "StRiKer" ! Enjoy!
Cops just raided our garage in Baracoa.
They were real interested in you.
Heat's on and we just sent up a flare
that's gonna lead them right to us.
I say we move out first thing
in the morning.
Nah, it's me they want.
And if they catch me,
they're throwing big numbers
at anybody with me.
Han, we had a good run.
Time for you to go
do your own thing.
Heard they're doing
some crazy shit in Tokyo.
Have you seen Letty?
There she is.
I hear Rio is nice this time of year.
The cops are getting hungrier.
Then I guess we're doing our job.
I'm a walking target.
I don't want you around
when they catch up to me.
"Ride or die," remember?
Dom, how long have we
been doing this?
And now all of a sudden, out of
nowhere, it's too dangerous?
Come on
We'll figure it out. We always do.
Move
Move out of my way
I got a gun.
I don't know shit!
Give me a name!
David Park! David Park's
the guy you want!
Please
Oh thank god.
Listen, he's in a mood
because yesterday was his cheat day,
and then today, some genius
brought in donuts.
Oh great
BRIAN: Sorry I'm late.
Complaints keep rolling in after your
little downtown Olympics, O'Conner.
Tell me that reinstating you
wasn't a mistake.
I got a name
David park
That's it?
Is that all you got
David park?
I could throw a fortune cookie out this window
and hit 50 David Parks right now.
It's Korean, not Chinese.
Whatever.
Park is a scout that recruits street racers
to be mules for the Braga cartel.
We find park,
and we bust the bad guys
Whats up
Mia, I told you not to call me here.
Dom its letty
She's been murdered
PRIEST: We have gathered here
to pay our final respects to...
Facial recognition software
matched Toretto
about 10 minutes after
he crossed the border.
I don't get it
I thought he'd show.
I told you not to come, they are staking the place out
what if they find you?
They won't
Come on
Look at you
Letty wouldn't let them junk it.
Even though it is a goddamn curse.
When she came back,
she was always in here
Working on it, day and night.
It was weird
It was like she knew you were coming back
I want to see the crash site
PENNING: I just got off the phone
with Deputy Director Lawson.
If we don't make serious inroads into
the Braga case in the next 72 hours,
There are going to shut us down
I know I'm a newbie here,
but why the clock now?
Because it’s been two years
And the last three agents We sent in for infiltrate
this organization have come back in body bags
He's moved more heroin across the border
than Escobar did in 10 years.
This guy is becoming one of our biggest national threats
and we don’t even have a picture of him
We don’t have prints, not even a god damn DOB
What's the status on David Park?
Isn't he our ticket into
the Braga organization?
Well, we are running the name through city
and county databases sorting the possibilities
We have got over 500 already
Parks is an insignificant,
sounds like another jerk off to me.
He's not, without Park, Braga would't
have drivers to move the shipment
Cross check traffic
Illegal modifications, Street racing.
This guy will definitely
have a record. We'll find him.
We better
Your boy Toretto's red Chevelle has
been spotted in his old neighborhood.
I'm going to bring his ass in.
Not in your car you're not.
Straight ahead
You found something back there
There were burn marks on the ground.
The kind that could only be
caused by nitrometh.
There's only one guy in all of L.A.
that sells that.
Nothing you can do is
gonna bring her back, Dom
If I were Letty, I would ask you..
No, I would beg you, please let this go
Before it’s too late
It’s already too late
I love you
Miss Toretto
I am Michel Stasiak, FBl
Let's you and I have a little chat.
Hi. This is Forsythe in Evidence.
I need Stasiak down here right away
to sign some greenies.
Thanks
I narrowed it down to 50 or so David Parks
What I'd like you to do is run the make
and model on each one of them.
Hey, Tyler, we got a transfer.
You want to come with me?
What?
- Toreto, when did you get back in town?
I'm looking for a car
you did an engine mod on.
Nitromethane tank. Ford full-size.
Continental tires.
What.. What you doing? Coming here like this
This ain't your scene anymore boss
Don’t you put your hands on me again.. Okay?
Say hi to your sister for me
A Korean kid brought it in.
David park
It's a green Ford Torino.
Shit, Don’t drop this on me
Almost done
Why don't you tell me why
you dragged me here, Brian?
You know they're going to capture Dom.
Maybe worse
I don't want you get tangled up in this
stay away from him
That's what you have to say to me after 5 years
All of the sudden you care what happens to me
What I did to you was wrong
I am sorry
it was, it was hardest thing I ever had to do
I’m sorry too Brian
I’m so sorry that you had to come
into my home and pretend to love me
I’m so sorry that you ripped my family apart
I’m very sorry that was hard for you
I lied to you
I lied to Dom, I lied to every body
That’s what I do best, that’s why the feds recruited me.
Maybe you're lying to yourself
If You’re not the good guy pretending to be a bad guy
Maybe you’re the bad guy pretending to be the good guy
You ever think about that
Every day
How I always wondered
Why did you let my brother go that day?
I don't know
Oh shit..
BRIAN
Brian, I got a crosschecks on
David park pack, I have a list of possibles
What do you got?
A 45 year old male, with three reckless driving tickets
No
One cherry taco, no
2 Mini Coopers, a '06 and a '07,
a Toyota hybrid, no
No
A '98 Saturn,
a '95 Sebring. A '98 Nissan 240 with an illegal mod.
Wait. That's it.
The 240 with the illegal mod.
- How do u know?
'Cause that's something I'd drive.
Green Torino, running nitro, whose car?
I'm just the middleman. I swear!
I'm just the middleman!
Wait... wait, I don’t know shit man, I swear
I just run cars for Braga alright, all I
do is get you in the race that's all I can do
What race?
Come on man, I don't know shit, just let me up
Bring him up, Dom
Bring him up
Are you here to take me in, O'conner
Oh.. Shit
Shut up
Letty was my friend, too.
You weren't anyone's friend.
Yo, can you guys talk about this later?
Now pull my ass up!
She was running for this guy Braga and the things went bad
Please
I’m goanna get these guys, Dom
Now let me do my job, and bring him up
I'm going to kill this Braga.
And anyone else that gets in my way
Don’t let go
Conner
O'Conner! If you ever release
a witness of mine again...
That's enough!
STASIAK: Don't touch me.
I'm fine
PENNING: That's enough.
- You are through conner
- I said that’s enough
Stasiak, go and get yourself cleaned up
What? He hit me first
This isn't the Cub Scouts!
Now, go on!
You're bleeding on my floor.
O'Conner, do you know the difference
between a cop and a criminal?
- What?
- One bad judgment call
Keep your shit on line son
Have a good time
Take a seat
Good news. We have intel that
Braga's number 2, Ramon Campos,
will hold a street race
in Koreatown tomorrow night
They've already chosen
3 drivers from previous races.
Our newest informant,
Mr. David Park,
has been kind enough to get us into the race
O'Conner
You’re up
Let me guess, winner gets the slot
All right, so these are all the imports
the city has in impound.
- Okay nice
- Pick your poison
Alright 2206
I crashed one of those.
3418 and 2765.
Okay, so which one do you want
I want them all
Standard issue tracking device.
Boss wants to know where
you are at all times.
What are you looking at, nutsack?
I don’t know you tell me
The racer wants what Dwight's got.
See, but, ladies, Dwight's
already on the team.
You got to be fast if you want
to drive for Braga.
Is there a problem here?
No
You one of Park's guys, blondie?
- Yeah.. Yeah I am
Follow me
See you later punk
You, too, punk.
FENIX: Bull's-eye, coño, come on!
Ohm... it looks so thin.. Lama lama...
You all know why you're here
Good drivers
are a dime a dozen.
Man, every corner's got a chingadera
tuner racing for pinks.
That's not what Braga
has got me looking for.
Braga wants someone that would sell
their abuelita to be behind the wheel.
Someone that drives their 10-second cars
not in a straight line,
But to push it, and make it through
places that no one else would take it
Real drivers, you getting this
So, what are we hauling?
CAMPOS: For the money Braga's paying,
you don't need to know.
You just said you wanted real drivers
A real driver knows
exactly what's in his car.
Mira, real driver,
Nobody is forcing you to race?
You the boss?
Or am I talking to the boss?
Do I look like a boss?
My job is to find the best drivers, period
Whoever wins the race gets the info
Are we cool?
ARE WE COOL?
YEAH, we cool
Nah, we ain't cool, man
who's closing the streets?
No one, thats the point
AUTOMATED VOICE ON GPS:
Please wait while
directions are downloaded.
Proceed to the highlighted route.
You sure you want to do this?
A lot has changed.
You' re right.
GO
RIGHT, TURN AHEAD
YOU ARE NOW 5 MILES FROM YOUR DESTINATION
How's my ass look, Chia Pet?
Ghetto Smurf.
Dead man driving
Come on
Right, turn ahead
Oh.. Shit!
Yeah!
Rerouting.
Proceed straight ahead
- Rerouting.
- Just Shut Up!
You are 2.6 miles from destination
Oopse, I didn’t see you
You are now 4 and half miles from your destination
U-turn, if possible.
Are you kidding me?
You are now 4.2 mile from your destination
Sorry, car.
Your now 1 mile from your destination
Yeah, guess who's back, Dom?
Let’s go
Nice car baby
Bitch
Your now one quater mile on your destination
To early Dom
Still a buster.
Your have reached your destination.
Goodbye.
At least we know you can't beat me
straight up.
I didn't know there were any rules
Now that's what I call real driving.
No, that's bullshit, man!
Go cry to your mama, eh?
You work for Braga now
When the GPS calls, you follow
Driver's licence?
What driver's license?
Thumb
Cell phone number
The print is for Campos.
The number is for me
Yo, nutsack!
Let me tell you something, man,
muscle beats import every time.
You know what am saying
EVERY TIME!
Ladies, let's get on
back to Papa Dwight's.
DWIGHT: Papa Dwight wants you
to take off your shoes.
Dwight likes feet.
Take off your shoes.
So beautiful
Dwight likes this foot a lot.
- FBl
- Freeze
I didn't do nothing, man!
Dwight didn't do nothing!
Hey, no! Stay! Where you going?
WOMAN: Bye, Dwight!
No, what did I do?
BRIAN: You're under arrest
for distribution of meth.
Meth? Dwight's never
touched that shit, bro!
Dwight has now.
Yo, that ain't mine! No!
- Get off
You know that's never
gonna stick, right?
Yeah, it's not supposed to.
Yeah, Corona.
That's too bad about Dwight.
Having the Feds raid your house
the same night you make the team.
So unfortunate.
I wish I could say I was a surprised to see you here
What's to stop someone
from telling them you're a cop?
Probably the same thing that's keeping me
from telling them why you're really here.
What up, fellows?
Hey, how you doing?
Great. You having a good time?
Yeah, a great time.
Yeah, great time
How's your car?
It took a nasty bump
BRIAN: lt'll be ready.
I also heard you just
got out of County.
Yeah
You know a guy called Jim Garcia
No, big place, there’s lots of names, lots of faces
And you, you're wanted by
a lot of people, homes.
Well that kind of heat can't be good for business
Yeah, well that depend on how you look at things
I go down, I do time
I do REAL time
I don't know about your other drivers,
but when I see flashing lights in my mirror,
I don’t stop
Do you know each other?
He used to date my sister
I see
- You're lucky man
- How's that?
- You're still breathing
To the ladies we've loved
and the ladies we've lost.
Salute
So, what's Braga "about"?
You know, he's just one of us
Came up from the streets.
Down for el barrio.
Now, he's shot caller
Boss of bosses
See all these cats in here?
Anyone of them will die for Braga
Including you?
Especially me
Enjoy the party fellas
The clubs is yours, what ever you want
Braga's mine
I’m taking the whole house down
Good luck
Something interest you about this car?
Just admiring the body work
Are you one of those boys who prefers cars to women?
I'm one of those boys who'd appreciates
The fine body  regardless of the make.
Your car?
It's Fenix's car
You'll meet him at the rendezvous.
He'll be leading you.
So now
That I know your taste in cars
Tell me, what about your women
It all starts with the eyes.
She has gotta have those kind of eyes that
can look right through the bullshit
to the good in someone.
20% angel, 80% devil
Down to earth
Ain't afraid to get a little engine
grease under her fingernails.
That doesn't sound anything like me.
It ain't
- Hey - I got a gift
for you - Alright
A dirty shot glass, just what I always wanted
I got these from the club last night
There's 2 sets of prints here.
Run them both.
I know one of these is Campos'.
I think the other might be Braga's.
And you're gonna have
to go beyond lnterpol.
So, that means I have to contact
individual agencies,
and that could take weeks
Ok
DOWNLOADING DATA COORDINATES
Yeah
That’s your third traffic violation in less than three blocks
Slow it down, O'Conner
Sure thing, Dad.
He stopped
We lost him
- He killed the tracker
- We don’t know that
- I’m telling you he killed the tracker
- We don’t know that yet
Get the bird overhead
PILOT ON RADIO : Right now,
I'm moving north, 33', 56'...
All clear
PILOT ON RADIO :
Base, flag nine, I'm at Angels 5.
I don 't have a tally on the target.
Repeat, I don't have a tally on the target.
They' re gone, there's no one
down there.
- Damn it
TASH: This ain't right, bro. Nobody said
nothing about being locked in no truck.
Tell me about it
Yo!
Where do you think they're taking us?
Don’t matter
We're all just along for the ride now
Welcome to Mexico, boys
There're helicopters and surveillance cameras
that scans for heat signature at the border
But there're blind spots that I
can guide you through via satellites
There can be no margin of error
So you must follow my every direction
Any questions?
I thought Fenix was gonna be here
He will meet you out there
Allright everybody, sync up
Good luck gentlemen
GISELE ON RADIO :
Satellite linkup engaged.
Keep proceeding northbound
at current speed.
Stay close to Fenix
He'll lead you across
I got a heat signature northbound
along Legardo Ravine.
Thermal imaging window on the Mexico
side's gonna be down for about 45 seconds.
Get the camera on it.
MAN: Manual override.
Rerouting camera
to designated coordinates.
GISELE: Hurry it up.
You guys have been tagged.
SHIT..
Toretto, get back in formation.
Reimaging commencing.
I don't see anything
They're gone
Get the helicopters to cover it
PILOT ON RADIO : Base, we're 40 seconds
out from Legardo Ravine.
GISELE: They're sending a helicopter.
You have 30 seconds
PILOT: North 32' 33', west 116' 49'.
GISELE: The window is closing fast.
You need to get out of there before
they send ground support.
15 seconds
PILOT: Base, target is at 2 miles.
GISELE: You're running out of time.
You need to get out, NOW
PILOT: Base, we're at north 32' 33',
west 116' 49'
We have no visual contact.
Roll ground units for confirmation.
Sloppy!
Very sloppy!
What are you doing man?
Come on
Get out.
Come on, today, man.
Come on, let's go.
MALIK: Hey, don't touch me.
Hey, don't touch me, man!
Hey, I said don't touch me, man!
Hey, look, dawg, don't put
your hands on me.
TASH: Hey, Malik, chill, bro.
Yo, man, what's up
with your boy?
DOM: Hey, boss man!
What did you say?
I said only pussies run nitrometh.
You looked under my hood?
I’m talking to you
You got something in your mind?
'70 Plymouth.
Her name was Letty
Yo
Where’s my money?
DOM: And somebody
wrecked her car.
I wrecked her car.
You remember her face?
Because I don’t
Last time I saw her
it was burning
Now what?
I'm going to enjoy
what happens next.
Come on, get in
GET IN
Come on, get in fucking car, let's go
hurry up
HURRY UP
PENNING: What have you got, Trinh?
We contacted agencies in multiple countries
Unfortunately most of them have to
manually scan their print for us to upload
O'Conner is online 5
Sir you should see this
Thank you
Talk to me, O'Conner
- Where the hell have you been?
- I got the shipment? or we got the shipment?
What are you talking about?
Traffic cams in the area picked up
pictures of you and Toretto together.
Listen to me O'Conner
Bring in the shipment and bring in Toretto
But I thought the point was to get Braga.
We got an opportunity here.
Brian, the clock stopped ticking
Bring him in, are we clear?
O'Conner?
So this is what $60 million looks like.
Yeah, we got to get you to a doctor.
We have to find a place to hide this
I got a spot
502, wet reckless.
I need a 48-hour hold.
Out back. Any spot you can find.
Are you sure about this?
Yeah. The last place they'll check,
their own impound yard.
Trust me.
You know, I've been thinking,
when you blew up your car back
there, you blew up mine, too.
Yeah?
Yeah
So, now you owe me a 10 second car
Is that right?
Yeah
How are you?
Is this your way of keeping me
away from him?
You're the only one I could call.
He's my brother, of course.
The bullet's not in there.
I'm gonna clean it and stitch it up.
It's going to hurt.
I bet your are gonna enjoy this
A little
MIA: Want some of this?
DOM: Yeah.
MIA: It's spicy.
I like it hot.
Dom, what are you doing?
You reached first,
you have to say grace.
Thank you lord
For blessing this table
With food and family
And friendship
You asked me why I let Dom go?
I think it's because at that moment,
I respected him more than I did myself.
One thing I learned from Dom is that
nothing really matters unless you have a code.
And what’s your code, Brian?
I’m working on it
Oh, Shit
Hey Dom,
When were you gonna tell me?
- Dom what you doing
- When were you gonna tell me that you were running Letty?
- Let me explain this - When were you gonna......
Stop, Stop
You don't understand.
I don't understand?
Stop!
Stop, Stop it, please Stop!
She did it for...
She did it for you, Dom!
She did it for you!
Letty came to me to clear your name
in exchange for bringing down Braga.
She just wanted you to come home
I’m sorry Dom, I'm sorry
You better have one hell of an explanation
You disobeyed a direct order.
- Where’s the shipment?
- Its safe
It’s safe
Look, we could use the shipment
to parade in front of the media,
get a few hundred pounds
of heroin off the street,
but Braga's just gonna send another shipment
next week and the week after that.
And a week after that
Let's use the shipment to lure Braga out
and lop the head off
a multi-billion dollar cartel.
And how do you suggest we do that?
A hand-to-hand exchange with Braga.
He'll never show up
He can't afford not to
You got a plan?
There’s a price
We bag Braga, you let Toretto walk.
- Yes
- Hey star
I was just thinking about you
You know when I gave you my number
l was hoping that you'll call
But not under these circumstances
What circumstances?
Me, being alive!
Don’t take it personally
...it’s just business
I got some business of my own
Get Campos
It's them.
Was that how Braga inspires loyalty?
Killing his drivers?
One can always find more drivers
Its just good for business
I want to trade
Braga doesn't negotiate.
Fine
You explain to him how all of a sudden
$60 million worth of product disappears.
I know that can't be good for business
What do you want?
6 million cash, delivered by Braga himself
I don’t like being shot at
I ain't gonna put my neck out again
unless he's got something to lose, too.
He'll never go for it
Either I deal with Braga or you do
When and where?
Sir, players are onsite.
Holding positions at the perimeter.
All right. Listen up.
Everybody stay frosty.
We don't move a muscle until
O'Conner gives the signal.
When he gets the money,
you know what to do.
Well, the good news is,
when we get this guy,
You walk out here a free man
- Is that what they told you?
- Yeah that’s the deal
You still put milk and cookies out for Santa Claus?
Yeah
In case things go shitty.
- Just like old times
- Yeah
Oy, you dropped something
That's what you wanted, right?
Dom...
He's harmless don’t worry about him
And he's really sorry about, Letty
Where’s our stuff?
You mean the stuff that used to be in here right?
Well, you'll see it when we see Braga.
That was the deal.
No worries
Braga keeps his word
2 million
You get the rest when I get my property
Stasiak.
TRINH: We got a match.
The fingerprint's Braga's 100%.
Just waiting a facial confirmation via fax
BRIAN: I got a question for you.
I got a question for you.
You wearing pink when you were
clawing your way out of el barrio?
Order all agents to move in.
We got confirmation.
Primary suspect wearing gray suit.
Let's move
- Sir, O'Conner hasn't given us the signal yet
What part of that didn't you understand?
We just got confirmation. Do it!
FBI AGENT: Secure primary suspect
in gray suit. Repeat!
Secure primary suspect in gray suit.
You're thinking what I'm thinking, right?
He ain’t Braga
Oh shit
SWAT AGENT 1: Drop your weapons!
SWAT AGENT 2: FBI!
Look out
Get out of here
Get out of here, Dom
Run him down
Campos is Braga
Come on
SWAT LEADER:
Approaching primary target.
SWAT AGENT ON RADIO :
Primary suspect is secure.
Let’s go
Get up
INVESTIGATOR: He was under your nose
the whole time.
Now Braga's escaped.
Toretto's heading south, probably
long across the border by now.
Do you have any idea the kind
of trouble you're in, O'Conner?
I was doing my job
He ain't the first bad guy you
helped escape the law's grasp.
As of now, you're being taken off active duty,
until this house can
mount a formal inquiry.
- What about Braga?
- That's no longer your concern
- We now know where Braga is, right?
Customs tracked him via satellite
to his home base in Tecali, Mexico.
- Mexico is out of our jurisdiction
...the fact is
The press will be so busy
holding press conferences over the seizure
we'll skate under the radar.
I thought we signed on
to do the right thing.
- Everyone's looking for you
I’m right here
It's nice to see you've gone
with the times
and switched to electronic fuel injection.
- It looks good
Buster became a gearhead.
I’m going with you
I don't plan on bringing anyone back
I know
Hit that throttle.
How do you say goodbye
to your only brother?
You don’t.
I thought you were't gonna show up.
You saved my life
I’m willing to return the favour
This will help get you to Braga.
Dom
Going in there is suicide
I have no choice
You must have loved her very much
So this's where my jurisdiction ends?
This, is where mine begins
Amen
You ain't forgiven
You boys want to arrest me?
No, we're beyond that.
You can't buy your way out of this one
You and me
You and me, we are not so different
You're no hero
You're right
And that's why you're going back across the border
But Fenix's mine
You got it
Oh.. Shit
You'll make it a couple of miles out,
if you're lucky.
You know where you’re going?
You want to borrow my GPS?
Where are your boys at?
Are they going to show up or what?
Be careful what you ask for
Just stop, just stop the car
Right behind you
Dom, head to the tunnel
let's use the tunnel
Get out of here, Brian
You sure you know where the tunnels are?
Yeah, hold on
This might hurt
You're in my world now, baby!
That’s it baby, end of the road
Now what?
- Ah game over
- No No No
Come on
Hey, get me out of here
PUSSY
Let me see that
Hey, just keep the pressure there
You'll be alright
You have to get out of here
I ain't running anymore
- Can I ask you something
- Yeah
You know I would of won that race if you didn’t cheat, right?
You did hit your head hard
Don’t make me laugh
All rise
Please be seated
Please rise, mr Toretto
I've listened to the Testimony
...and taking in to special consideration
Agent O'Conner's
appeal of clemency
on behalf of Mr. Toretto.
That his actions directly resulted
in the apprehension
of known drug trafficker
Arturo Braga
However
This Judiciary finds that
One right does not make up for
a lifetime worth of wrongs
...and as such
I find that I'm forced to
level the maximum sentence under California law
Dominic Toretto
You are here by sentenced to serve 25 years to life
at the Lompoc maximum
security prison system
without the possibility of early parole.
This court is adjourned.