All right,
we're good to go.
You got this? You bet your ass, bubba.
Let's make some money!
Everyone in position.
I thought we'd be
robbing banks by now...
...not some gas truck
in the middle of nowhere.
Down here, gas is gold, bubba.
Kill the chatter!
Game time.
I wouldn't piss him off, guys.
Okay, guys, we're gonna have
to hit this hard and fast.
We got four K left
before the downgrade.
Locked and loaded!
This is all you, Han.
Liquid gold.
We're clear.
Okay, T, you're up.
Let's see if you can get it
under six tries this time, huh, T?
It's more like three. Come
on, Tego, keep it real.
Just one K left. We're running
out of road. Get in there, brother.
I got it, I got it.
Shit!
T, cut loose!
Unhitch, unhitch!
Spray that hitch!
I don't have a hammer!
Just do it!
Hold on! Hold on!
No shit!
Hold onto
something tight!
Letty!
Give me your hand!
I can't reach!
You got to jump!
Jump!
Letty, jump!
I've got you!
Dom...
Dom?
Dom!
How you doing?
Money, money!
Good.
Yo, why your stack
is bigger than mine always?
I'm supersized,
baby.
Cops just raided
our garage in Baracoa.
They were real
interested in you.
Heat's on and we just sent up a flare
that's gonna lead them right to us.
I say we move out first
thing in the morning.
Nah, it's me they want.
And if they catch me...
...they're throwing big
numbers at anybody with me.
Han, we had a good run.
Time for you to go
do your own thing.
Heard they're doing
some crazy shit in Tokyo.
Have you seen Letty?
There she is.
I hear Rio is nice
this time of year.
The cops are
getting hungrier.
Then I guess we're doing our job.
I'm a walking target.
I don't want you around
when they catch up to me.
"Ride or die,"
remember?
Dom, how long have we been doing this?
And now all of a sudden, out
of nowhere, it's too dangerous?
Come on.
We'll figure it out.
We always do.
I don't know shit!
Give me a name!
I don't know shit, man!
David Park! David
Park's the guy you want!
Please!
Thank God. Listen, he's in a mood
because yesterday was his cheat day...
...and then today, some
genius brought in donuts.
Great.
Sorry I'm late.
Complaints keep rolling in after your
little downtown Olympics, O'Conner.
Tell me that reinstating
you wasn't a mistake.
I got a name. David Park. That's it?
That's all you got?
David Park?
I could throw a fortune cookie out this
window and hit 50 David Parks right now.
It's Korean, not Chinese. Whatever.
Park is a scout that recruits street
racers to be mules for the Braga cartel.
We find Park, and we bust the bad guys.
Dom.
Mia, I told you
not to call me here.
Dom, it's Letty.
She's been murdered.
We have gathered here to
pay our final respects to...
Let us reflect
on her journey...
"The Lord is my shepherd, I shall
not want. He makes me lie down... "
Facial recognition software
matched Toretto...
...about 10 minutes after
he crossed the border.
I don't get it.
I thought he'd show.
I told you not to come.
They're staking the place out.
If they find you...
They won't.
Come on.
Look at you.
Letty wouldn't
let them junk it.
Even though it is
a goddamn curse.
When she came back,
she was always in here...
...working on it
day and night.
It was weird.
It was like she knew
you were coming back.
I want to see
the crash site.
I just got off the phone
with Deputy Director Lawson.
If we don't make serious inroads into
the Braga case in the next 72 hours...
...they're gonna
shut us down.
I know I'm a newbie here,
but why the clock now?
Because it's been
two years...
...and the last three agents we sent
to infiltrate his organization...
...came back in body bags.
He's moved more heroin across the
border than Escobar did in 10 years.
This guy is becoming one of
our biggest national threats...
...and we don't even
have a picture of him.
We don't have prints!
Not even a goddamn DOB!
What's the status
on David Park?
Isn't he our ticket into
the Braga organization?
We're running the name through city and
county databases, sorting the possibilities.
We've got
over 500 already.
Park's insignificant. Sounds
like another jerk-off to me.
It's not. Without Park, Braga wouldn't
have drivers to move his shipments.
Cross-check traffic.
Illegal modifications.
Street racing. This guy will definitely
have a record. We'll find him.
We better.
What do you know?
Your boy Toretto's red Chevelle has
been spotted in his old neighborhood.
I'm going to
bring his ass in.
Not in your car
you're not.
It's straight ahead.
You found something
back there.
There were burn marks
on the ground.
The kind that could only
be caused by nitrometh.
There's only one guy in
all of L.A. That sells that.
Nothing you can do is
gonna bring her back, Dom.
If I were Letty,
I would ask you...
No, I would beg you,
please, let this go.
Before it's too late.
It's already too late.
I love you.
Miss Toretto.
I'm Michael Stasiak, FBI.
Let's you and I
have a little chat.
Hi. This is Forsythe
in Evidence.
I need Stasiak down here right
away to sign some greenies.
Thanks.
Hi.
Hey.
Okay, I narrowed it down
to 50 or so David Parks.
What I'd like you to do is run the
make and model on each one of them.
All right?
Okay. All right.
Thank you.
Hey, Tyler,
we got a transfer.
You want to
come with me?
Toretto.
When'd you get
back in town?
I'm looking for a car
you did an engine mod on.
Nitromethane tank. Ford
full-size. Continental tires.
Look, what are you doing,
coming in here like this, huh?
This ain't your scene
anymore, boss.
Don't ever put your hands
on me again, okay?
Say hi to your
sister for me.
A Korean kid brought it in. David Park.
It's a green Ford Torino.
Please don't
drop this on me!
I'm almost done.
Why don't you tell me why
you dragged me here, Brian?
You know they're going to
capture Dom. Maybe worse.
I don't want you getting tangled
up in this. So stay away from him.
That's what you have to
say to me after five years?
All of a sudden, you
care what happens to me.
What I did to you
was wrong.
I'm sorry. It was... It was the
hardest thing I've ever had to do.
I'm sorry, too, Brian.
I'm so sorry that you had to come
into my home and pretend to love me.
I'm so sorry that you
ripped my family apart.
I'm very sorry that
that was hard for you.
I lied to you.
I lied to Dom.
I lied to everybody.
That's what I do best. It's
why the Feds recruited me.
Maybe you're lying
to yourself.
Maybe you're not the good guy
pretending to be a bad guy.
Maybe you're the bad guy
pretending to be the good guy.
You ever think about that?
Every day.
I always wondered...
...why did you let
my brother go that day?
I don't know.
Shit.
Brian!
I got the cross-checks on David Park
back and have a list of possibles.
What do you got? All right. A
45-year-old male in a '06 Scion...
...with three reckless driving tickets. No.
An '01 Chevy Tahoe.
No.
Two Mini Coopers, a '06
and a '07, a Toyota hybrid.
Hell no. A '98 Saturn, a '95 Sebring.
A '98 Nissan 240
with an illegal mod.
Wait. That's it.
What? The 240 with the illegal mod.
How do you know? 'Cause
that's something I'd drive.
Don't! Don't! Don't!
Green Torino,
running nitro.
Whose car?
I don't know, man.
I'm just the middleman. I
swear! I'm just the middleman!
Wait, wait, wait.
I don't know shit, man. I swear. I
just run cars for Braga, all right?
All I can do is get you in
the race! That's all I can do!
What race?
Help! Come on,
hold on!
Let me up, man!
Come on!
Come on, man, I don't
know shit! Just let me up!
I told you, you got to talk to Braga!
Bring him up, Dom.
God! Don't drop me!
That's all I know!
Bring him up.
You here to take
me in, O'Conner?
Shit! Shit!
Shut up!
Letty was my friend, too.
You weren't
anyone's friend.
Yo, can you guys talk about
this later? Now pull my ass up!
She was running for this guy,
Braga, and things went bad.
Please!
I'm going to
get these guys, Dom.
Now let me do my job
and bring him up.
I'm going to
kill this Braga.
God!
And anyone else
who gets in my way.
Hey!
Don't let go.
O'Conner!
O'Conner! If you ever release
a witness of mine again...
That's enough!
Don't touch me.
I'm fine!
That's enough.
You're through, O'Conner!
I said that's enough!
Stasiak, go get
yourself cleaned up.
What?
He hit me first! You...
This isn't
the Cub Scouts!
Now, go on! You're bleeding on my floor.
O'Conner, do you know the difference
between a cop and a criminal?
What?
One bad judgment call.
Keep your shit in line,
son.
Have a good time.
Take a seat.
Good news. We have intel that
Braga's number two, Ramon Campos...
...will hold a street race
in Koreatown tomorrow night...
...to fill a slot
on his team.
They've already chosen three
drivers from previous races.
Our newest informant,
Mr. David Park...
...has been kind enough
to get us into the race.
O'Conner, you're up.
Let me guess,
winner gets the slot.
All right, so these are all the
imports the city has in impound.
Okay, nice.
Pick your poison.
All right, 2206.
I crashed one of those.
3418 and 2765.
Okay, so which one
do you want?
I want them all.
Standard issue
tracking device.
Boss wants to know where
you are at all times.
You want to
play with it?
Hey!
What are you
looking at, nutsack?
I don't know.
You tell me.
The racer wants
what Dwight's got.
See, but, ladies, Dwight's
already on the team.
You got to be fast if you
want to drive for Braga.
Is there a problem here? No.
You one of
Park's guys, blondie?
Yeah. Yeah, I am.
Follow me.
See you later, punk.
You, too, punk.
Bull's-eye, coño,
come on!
We can do this all day.
You all know
why you're here.
Good drivers...
...are a dime a dozen.
Man, every corner's got a
chingadera tuner racing for pinks.
That's not what Braga
has got me looking for.
Braga wants someone that would sell
their abuelita to be behind the wheel.
Someone that drives their 10-second
cars not in a straight line...
...but to push it and make it through
places no one else would take it.
Real drivers.
So, what are we hauling?
For the money Braga's paying,
you don't need to know.
You just said you wanted real drivers.
A real driver knows
exactly what's in his car.
Mira, real driver...
...nobody's forcing you
to race.
You the boss?
Or am I talking
to the boss?
Do I look like a boss?
My job is to find the
best drivers, period.
Whoever wins the race
gets the info. We cool?
Are we cool?
Yeah, we're cool.
No,
we ain't cool, man.
Who's closing these streets?
No one.
That's the point.
Please wait while
directions are downloaded.
Proceed to
the highlighted route.
Ten...
...nine...
...eight...
...seven...
...six...
You sure you want to do
this? A lot has changed.
...four...
You're right.
...three...
...two...
...one...
...go!
Right turn ahead.
You are now five miles
from your destination.
How's my ass look,
Chia Pet?
Ghetto Smurf.
Dead man driving.
Come on!
Right turn ahead.
Shit!
Damn.
Rerouting.
Proceed straight ahead.
Shit.
Rerouting.
Just shut up!
You are 2.6 miles
from destination.
Oops, I didn't see you.
You are now four and one-half
miles from your destination.
U- Turn, if possible.
Are you kidding me?
You are now 4.2 miles
from your destination.
Sorry, car.
You are now one mile
from your destination.
Yeah,
guess who's back, Dom?
Let's go!
Nice car, baby!
Bitch!
You are now one-quarter
mile from your destination.
Too early, Dom.
No!
Still a buster.
You have reached your
destination. Goodbye.
At least we know you
can't beat me straight up.
I didn't know
there were any rules.
Now that's what I call
real driving.
No, that's bullshit, man!
Go cry to your mama, eh?
You work for Braga now.
When the GPS calls,
you follow.
Driver's license.
What driver's license?
Thumb.
Cell phone number.
The print is for Campos.
The number is for me.
Yo, nutsack!
Let me tell you something, man,
muscle beats import every time.
You know what I'm saying? Every time!
Ladies, let's get on
back to Papa Dwight's.
Papa Dwight wants you
to take off your shoes.
Dwight likes feet.
Take off your shoes.
So beautiful.
Dwight likes this foot a lot.
Yes, baby!
Daddy Dwight loves...
FBI!
Hey! Yo,
what are you doing?
I didn't do nothing, man!
Dwight didn't do nothing!
Hey, no! Stay, stay! Where
you going? Bye, Dwight!
No, what did I do?
You're under arrest
for distribution of meth.
Meth? Dwight's never
touched that shit, bro!
Dwight has now.
Yo, that ain't mine! No!
You know that's never
gonna stick, right?
Yeah, it's not
supposed to.
Live it up!
Yeah, Corona.
That's too bad
about Dwight.
Having the Feds raid your house
the same night you make the team.
So unfortunate.
I wish I could say I was
surprised to see you here.
What's to stop someone from
telling them you're a cop?
Probably the same thing that's keeping me
from telling them why you're really here.
What up, fellows?
Hey, how you doing?
Great. You having a good
time? Yeah, a great time.
Come on, let's have a better time.
How's your car?
It took a nasty bump.
It'll be ready.
I also heard you just
got out of County.
Yeah.
Mmm-hmm.
You know a guy
named Jim Garcia?
Nah. Big place. Lots
of names, lots of faces.
And you, you're wanted by
a lot of people, homes.
Yeah, that kind of heat
can't be good for business.
Yeah, well, that depends
on how you look at things.
I go down, I do time.
I do real time.
I don't know about your other drivers, but
when I see flashing lights in my mirror...
I don't stop.
Do you know each other?