1
00:00:57,140 --> 00:00:59,391
All right,
we're good to go.

2
00:00:59,517 --> 00:01:02,311
You got this?
You bet your ass,
bubba.

3
00:01:02,854 --> 00:01:04,813
Let's make some money!

4
00:01:10,904 --> 00:01:12,196
Everyone in position.

5
00:01:14,491 --> 00:01:16,867
I thought we'd be
robbing banks by now,

6
00:01:16,951 --> 00:01:19,328
not some gas truck
in the middle of nowhere.

7
00:01:19,412 --> 00:01:22,081
Down here,
gas is gold,
bubba.

8
00:01:22,207 --> 00:01:24,041
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

9
00:01:25,251 --> 00:01:26,251
(LAUGHS)

10
00:01:26,336 --> 00:01:28,045
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

11
00:01:29,714 --> 00:01:30,714
(RADIO SQUEALS)

12
00:01:30,799 --> 00:01:32,841
DOM ON RADIO:
Kill the chatter!
Game time.

13
00:01:32,926 --> 00:01:35,260
I wouldn't
piss him off, guys.

14
00:01:49,526 --> 00:01:50,609
(IGUANA GROWLS)

15
00:01:50,693 --> 00:01:52,402
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

16
00:01:56,241 --> 00:01:58,158
DOM: Okay, guys,
we're gonna have to hit
this hard and fast.

17
00:01:58,243 --> 00:02:01,078
We got four K left
before the downgrade.

18
00:02:05,291 --> 00:02:06,792
(TIRES SQUEAL)

19
00:02:22,225 --> 00:02:24,017
Locked and loaded !

20
00:02:32,443 --> 00:02:34,153
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

21
00:02:35,738 --> 00:02:37,239
(TRUCK HONKING)

22
00:02:38,158 --> 00:02:39,533
(SPRAYING)

23
00:02:42,370 --> 00:02:44,413
(TRUCK CONTINUES HONKING)

24
00:02:48,251 --> 00:02:49,751
(GRUNTS)

25
00:02:49,836 --> 00:02:51,920
This is all you, Han.

26
00:02:57,343 --> 00:02:59,011
Liquid gold.

27
00:02:59,262 --> 00:03:00,637
(CHUCKLES)

28
00:03:06,311 --> 00:03:07,352
We're clear.

29
00:03:07,437 --> 00:03:08,604
Okay, T, you're up.

30
00:03:12,650 --> 00:03:15,694
Let's see if you can
get it under six tries
this time, huh, T?

31
00:03:15,778 --> 00:03:18,822
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

32
00:03:18,907 --> 00:03:22,034
It's more like three.
Come on, Tego,
keep it real.

33
00:03:22,118 --> 00:03:23,827
(TIRES SQUEALING)

34
00:03:32,545 --> 00:03:34,129
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

35
00:03:38,676 --> 00:03:42,221
Just one K left.
We're running out of road.
Get in there, brother.

36
00:03:42,305 --> 00:03:44,139
I got it, I got it.

37
00:03:48,228 --> 00:03:49,269
(YELLS)

38
00:03:49,437 --> 00:03:51,146
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

39
00:03:53,441 --> 00:03:54,608
Shit!

40
00:03:55,526 --> 00:03:56,902
(GRUNTS)

41
00:04:00,073 --> 00:04:02,699
T, cut loose!
Unhitch, unhitch !

42
00:04:05,328 --> 00:04:06,328
(SCREAMS)

43
00:04:07,664 --> 00:04:08,997
(GUNSHOTS)

44
00:04:23,304 --> 00:04:27,349
(BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH)

45
00:04:32,897 --> 00:04:34,606
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

46
00:04:40,905 --> 00:04:42,531
(ENGINE REVVING)

47
00:04:49,038 --> 00:04:51,957
Spray that hitch !
I don't have a hammer!

48
00:04:52,041 --> 00:04:53,542
Just do it!

49
00:05:03,386 --> 00:05:04,386
(SCREAMS)

50
00:05:08,224 --> 00:05:09,558
Hold on ! Hold on !

51
00:05:09,642 --> 00:05:11,143
No shit!

52
00:05:13,396 --> 00:05:15,522
Hold onto
something tight!

53
00:05:28,202 --> 00:05:29,411
(METAL CLANKS)

54
00:05:39,297 --> 00:05:40,672
DOM: Letty!

55
00:05:40,757 --> 00:05:43,008
Give me your hand !
I can't reach !

56
00:05:43,092 --> 00:05:44,760
You got to jump!

57
00:05:54,604 --> 00:05:56,396
(BRAKES SCREECHING)

58
00:05:59,692 --> 00:06:01,443
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

59
00:06:10,995 --> 00:06:12,162
Jump!

60
00:06:13,664 --> 00:06:15,165
Letty, jump!

61
00:06:19,796 --> 00:06:21,296
I've got you !

62
00:06:28,346 --> 00:06:29,346
(GROANS)

63
00:06:54,455 --> 00:06:55,705
Dom. . .

64
00:06:58,126 --> 00:06:59,251
Dom?

65
00:07:03,339 --> 00:07:04,506
Dom !

66
00:07:32,827 --> 00:07:35,203
(CLUB MUSIC PLAYING)

67
00:07:46,924 --> 00:07:48,550
(CARS REVVING)

68
00:07:48,634 --> 00:07:49,885
(EXCLAIMS)

69
00:08:05,359 --> 00:08:15,202
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

70
00:08:15,286 --> 00:08:16,870
HAN: How you doing?

71
00:08:18,581 --> 00:08:20,123
OMAR: Money, money!

72
00:08:21,459 --> 00:08:22,626
Good.

73
00:08:25,254 --> 00:08:27,172
OMAR: Yo, why your stack
is bigger than mine always?

74
00:08:27,256 --> 00:08:29,090
TEGO: I'm supersized,
baby.

75
00:08:29,926 --> 00:08:32,260
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

76
00:08:38,935 --> 00:08:41,728
Cops just raided
our garage in Baracoa.

77
00:08:42,522 --> 00:08:45,065
They were real
interested in you.

78
00:08:45,650 --> 00:08:50,403
Heat's on and we just
sent up a flare that's gonna
lead them right to us.

79
00:08:50,488 --> 00:08:53,573
I say we move out
first thing in the morning.

80
00:08:54,951 --> 00:08:56,993
Nah, it's me they want.

81
00:08:57,620 --> 00:08:59,579
And if they catch me,

82
00:08:59,664 --> 00:09:02,666
they're throwing
big numbers
at anybody with me.

83
00:09:05,836 --> 00:09:07,796
Han, we had a good run.

84
00:09:09,799 --> 00:09:12,551
Time for you to go
do your own thing.

85
00:09:16,472 --> 00:09:19,474
Heard they're doing
some crazy shit in Tokyo.

86
00:09:25,773 --> 00:09:27,691
Have you seen Letty?

87
00:09:40,246 --> 00:09:42,080
There she is.

88
00:09:45,209 --> 00:09:46,376
(SIGHS)

89
00:09:48,087 --> 00:09:50,797
I hear Rio is nice
this time of year.

90
00:09:54,427 --> 00:09:56,720
The cops are
getting hungrier.

91
00:09:56,804 --> 00:09:59,222
Then I guess
we're doing
our job.

92
00:10:03,978 --> 00:10:05,937
I'm a walking target.

93
00:10:06,522 --> 00:10:09,816
I don't want you
around when they
catch up to me.

94
00:10:11,569 --> 00:10:14,404
"Ride or die,"
remember?

95
00:10:15,698 --> 00:10:18,533
Dom, how long
have we been doing this?

96
00:10:20,578 --> 00:10:24,372
And now all of a sudden,
out of nowhere,
it's too dangerous?

97
00:10:25,041 --> 00:10:26,541
Come on.

98
00:10:31,547 --> 00:10:34,633
We'll figure it out.
We always do.

99
00:11:46,455 --> 00:11:48,289
(FOOTSTEPS)

100
00:11:50,209 --> 00:11:51,543
(MAN PANTING)

101
00:11:53,379 --> 00:11:54,629
(CAR HONKING)

102
00:11:55,631 --> 00:11:56,923
(GRUNTS)

103
00:12:42,386 --> 00:12:43,803
(WOMAN SCREAMS)

104
00:12:43,888 --> 00:12:45,430
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)

105
00:12:48,893 --> 00:12:50,351
(GRUNTING)

106
00:12:51,353 --> 00:12:53,104
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)

107
00:13:03,282 --> 00:13:04,783
(GUNSHOTS)

108
00:13:04,867 --> 00:13:06,201
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)

109
00:13:13,834 --> 00:13:15,293
(BABY CRYING)

110
00:13:21,884 --> 00:13:23,343
(WOMAN SCREAMING)

111
00:13:30,601 --> 00:13:31,893
(PANTING)

112
00:13:56,877 --> 00:13:58,253
(GUNSHOTS)

113
00:14:00,297 --> 00:14:01,631
(GROANING)

114
00:14:01,715 --> 00:14:02,841
I don't know shit!
Give me a name!

115
00:14:02,925 --> 00:14:05,009
I don't know shit, man !
Give me a name!

116
00:14:05,094 --> 00:14:08,096
David Park!
David Park's
the guy you want!

117
00:14:08,681 --> 00:14:09,806
Please!

118
00:14:17,481 --> 00:14:20,817
Thank God. Listen,
he's in a mood because
yesterday was his cheat day,

119
00:14:20,901 --> 00:14:22,861
and then today,
some genius
brought in donuts.

120
00:14:22,945 --> 00:14:24,153
Great.

121
00:14:25,447 --> 00:14:27,073
BRIAN: Sorry I'm late.

122
00:14:27,157 --> 00:14:28,324
(SCOFFS)

123
00:14:28,409 --> 00:14:32,704
Complaints keep rolling in
after your little
downtown Olympics, O'Conner.

124
00:14:32,788 --> 00:14:35,957
Tell me that
reinstating you
wasn't a mistake.

125
00:14:36,041 --> 00:14:39,210
I got a name.
David Park.
That's it?

126
00:14:39,295 --> 00:14:41,754
That's all you got?
David Park?

127
00:14:41,839 --> 00:14:44,716
I could throw a fortune cookie
out this window and hit
50 David Parks right now.

128
00:14:44,800 --> 00:14:47,468
It's Korean,
not Chinese.
Whatever.

129
00:14:48,137 --> 00:14:52,724
Park is a scout that recruits
street racers to be mules
for the Braga cartel.

130
00:14:52,808 --> 00:14:55,393
We find Park,
and we bust
the bad guys.

131
00:15:05,029 --> 00:15:07,155
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

132
00:15:08,824 --> 00:15:11,034
(BOY SPEAKING SPANISH)

133
00:15:19,084 --> 00:15:20,293
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

134
00:15:20,377 --> 00:15:21,711
MIA: Dom.

135
00:15:21,795 --> 00:15:24,464
Mia, I told you
not to call me here.

136
00:15:24,965 --> 00:15:26,674
Dom, it's Letty.

137
00:15:27,635 --> 00:15:29,469
She's been murdered.

138
00:15:45,152 --> 00:15:49,614
PRIEST: We have
gathered here to pay
our final respects to. . .

139
00:15:49,698 --> 00:15:52,867
Let us reflect
on her journey. . .

140
00:15:56,622 --> 00:16:01,334
"The Lord is my shepherd,
I shall not want.
He makes me lie down. . ."

141
00:16:03,504 --> 00:16:05,004
(SOBBING)

142
00:16:21,158 --> 00:16:23,952
Facial recognition software
matched Toretto

143
00:16:24,036 --> 00:16:25,870
about 10 minutes after
he crossed the border.

144
00:16:28,832 --> 00:16:30,458
I don't get it.

145
00:16:30,668 --> 00:16:32,543
I thought he'd show.

146
00:17:27,266 --> 00:17:30,059
I told you not to come.
They're staking the place out.

147
00:17:30,144 --> 00:17:32,603
If they find you. . .
They won't.

148
00:17:35,441 --> 00:17:38,609
Come on.
Look at you.

149
00:18:04,887 --> 00:18:07,346
Letty wouldn't
let them junk it.

150
00:18:09,016 --> 00:18:11,517
Even though it is
a goddamn curse.

151
00:18:14,313 --> 00:18:17,273
When she came back,
she was always in here,

152
00:18:18,317 --> 00:18:20,818
working on it
day and night.

153
00:18:26,450 --> 00:18:28,076
It was weird.

154
00:18:29,703 --> 00:18:32,663
It was like she knew
you were coming back.

155
00:18:34,708 --> 00:18:37,043
I want to see
the crash site.

156
00:18:42,674 --> 00:18:46,135
PENNING: I just
got off the phone with
Deputy Director Lawson.

157
00:18:46,645 --> 00:18:50,264
If we don't make serious
inroads into the Braga case
in the next 72 hours,

158
00:18:50,349 --> 00:18:52,600
they're gonna
shut us down.

159
00:18:53,769 --> 00:18:56,312
I know I'm a newbie here,
but why the clock now?

160
00:18:56,396 --> 00:18:58,189
Because it's been
two years,

161
00:18:58,199 --> 00:19:00,775
and the last three agents
we sent to infiltrate
his organization

162
00:19:00,859 --> 00:19:03,236
came back in body bags.

163
00:19:03,320 --> 00:19:07,907
He's moved more heroin
across the border
than Escobar did in 1 0 years.

164
00:19:07,991 --> 00:19:10,785
This guy is becoming
one of our biggest
national threats,

165
00:19:10,869 --> 00:19:12,954
and we don't even
have a picture of him.

166
00:19:13,038 --> 00:19:16,541
We don't have prints!
Not even a goddamn DOB!

167
00:19:19,586 --> 00:19:21,796
What's the status
on David Park?

168
00:19:21,880 --> 00:19:24,090
Isn't he our ticket into
the Braga organization?

169
00:19:24,174 --> 00:19:27,969
We're running the name through
city and county databases,
sorting the possibilities.

170
00:19:28,053 --> 00:19:29,971
We've got
over 500 already.

171
00:19:30,055 --> 00:19:33,099
Park's insignificant.
Sounds like another
jerk-off to me.

172
00:19:33,183 --> 00:19:37,145
BRIAN: It's not. Without Park,
Braga wouldn't have drivers
to move his shipments.

173
00:19:37,229 --> 00:19:39,981
Cross-check traffic.
Illegal modifications.

174
00:19:40,065 --> 00:19:44,402
Street racing.
This guy will definitely
have a record. We'll find him.

175
00:19:45,237 --> 00:19:46,501
We better.

176
00:19:46,511 --> 00:19:49,031
(CHUCKLES)
What do you know?

177
00:19:49,116 --> 00:19:52,785
Your boy Toretto's
red Chevelle has been spotted
in his old neighborhood.

178
00:19:52,870 --> 00:19:54,662
I'm going to
bring his ass in.

179
00:19:54,746 --> 00:19:56,998
Not in your car
you're not.

180
00:20:05,757 --> 00:20:07,633
It's straight ahead.

181
00:20:30,866 --> 00:20:31,866
(TIRES SQUEALING)

182
00:21:03,398 --> 00:21:04,815
(TIRES SQUEALING)

183
00:21:06,526 --> 00:21:08,361
(CAR ENGINES REVVING)

184
00:21:35,180 --> 00:21:36,514
(GROANING)

185
00:21:44,690 --> 00:21:46,190
(GUN COCKING)

186
00:21:54,616 --> 00:21:55,658
(GUNSHOT)

187
00:22:13,385 --> 00:22:15,720
You found something
back there.

188
00:22:20,642 --> 00:22:23,227
There were burn marks
on the ground.

189
00:22:26,356 --> 00:22:29,567
The kind that could
only be caused
by nitrometh.

190
00:22:33,238 --> 00:22:36,574
There's only one guy
in all of L.A.
that sells that.

191
00:22:40,579 --> 00:22:43,789
Nothing you can do
is gonna bring
her back, Dom.

192
00:22:45,876 --> 00:22:48,169
lf I were Letty,
I would ask you. . .

193
00:22:48,253 --> 00:22:51,839
No, I would beg you,
please, let this go.

194
00:22:53,050 --> 00:22:55,092
Before it's too late.

195
00:22:59,598 --> 00:23:01,515
It's already too late.

196
00:23:07,105 --> 00:23:08,481
I love you.

197
00:23:22,037 --> 00:23:23,371
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)

198
00:24:13,588 --> 00:24:15,381
(CAR DOOR OPENING)

199
00:24:15,465 --> 00:24:16,966
STASIAK:
Miss Toretto.

200
00:24:17,884 --> 00:24:20,219
I'm Michael Stasiak, FBI.

201
00:24:20,762 --> 00:24:23,347
Let's you and I
have a little chat.

202
00:24:29,020 --> 00:24:30,563
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)

203
00:24:44,870 --> 00:24:47,705
Hi. This is Forsythe
in Evidence.

204
00:24:47,789 --> 00:24:51,417
I need Stasiak
down here right away
to sign some greenies.

205
00:24:51,501 --> 00:24:53,002
Thanks.

206
00:24:53,086 --> 00:24:54,628
Hi.
Hey.

207
00:24:54,713 --> 00:24:57,298
Okay, I narrowed it down
to 50 or so David Parks.

208
00:24:57,382 --> 00:24:59,758
What I'd like you to do
is run the make and model
on each one of them.

209
00:24:59,843 --> 00:25:00,801
All right?
Okay. All right.

210
00:25:00,886 --> 00:25:02,136
Thank you.

211
00:25:10,312 --> 00:25:11,562
(DOOR BUZZES)

212
00:25:12,772 --> 00:25:15,065
Hey, Tyler,
we got a transfer.

213
00:25:17,235 --> 00:25:19,278
You want to
come with me?

214
00:25:21,823 --> 00:25:23,282
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)

215
00:25:40,717 --> 00:25:41,967
Toretto.

216
00:25:43,303 --> 00:25:44,845
When'd you get
back in town?

217
00:25:44,930 --> 00:25:47,806
I'm looking for a car
you did an engine mod on.

218
00:25:47,891 --> 00:25:52,394
Nitromethane tank.
Ford full-size.
Continental tires.

219
00:25:54,314 --> 00:25:57,650
Look, what are you doing,
coming in here like this, huh?

220
00:25:58,193 --> 00:26:00,861
This ain't your scene
anymore, boss.

221
00:26:00,946 --> 00:26:03,656
Don't ever put your hands
on me again, okay?

222
00:26:03,740 --> 00:26:06,075
Say hi to your
sister for me.

223
00:26:09,621 --> 00:26:11,121
(GRUNTING)

224
00:26:15,794 --> 00:26:17,044
(GROANING)

225
00:26:17,629 --> 00:26:20,965
A Korean kid
brought it in.
David Park.

226
00:26:21,800 --> 00:26:24,134
It's a green Ford Torino.

227
00:26:25,136 --> 00:26:27,471
Please don't
drop this on me!

228
00:26:32,352 --> 00:26:34,061
I'm almost done.

229
00:26:36,356 --> 00:26:39,817
Why don't you tell me
why you dragged me here,
Brian?

230
00:26:45,949 --> 00:26:49,827
You know they're going
to capture Dom.
Maybe worse.

231
00:26:51,538 --> 00:26:55,833
I don't want you
getting tangled up in this.
So stay away from him.

232
00:26:56,751 --> 00:27:00,129
That's what you have
to say to me
after five years?

233
00:27:01,506 --> 00:27:04,341
All of a sudden,
you care
what happens to me.

234
00:27:07,679 --> 00:27:10,097
What I did to you
was wrong.

235
00:27:10,181 --> 00:27:14,476
I'm sorry. It was. . .
It was the hardest thing
I've ever had to do.

236
00:27:15,937 --> 00:27:17,855
I'm sorry, too, Brian.

237
00:27:18,481 --> 00:27:23,235
I'm so sorry that you had
to come into my home
and pretend to love me.

238
00:27:23,320 --> 00:27:25,696
I'm so sorry
that you ripped
my family apart.

239
00:27:25,780 --> 00:27:28,699
I'm very sorry
that that was
hard for you.

240
00:27:32,412 --> 00:27:34,038
I lied to you.

241
00:27:35,498 --> 00:27:38,042
I lied to Dom.
I lied to everybody.

242
00:27:38,543 --> 00:27:41,795
That's what I do best.
It's why the Feds
recruited me.

243
00:27:43,465 --> 00:27:45,841
Maybe you're lying
to yourself.

244
00:27:47,093 --> 00:27:50,804
Maybe you're not the good guy
pretending to be a bad guy.

245
00:27:51,264 --> 00:27:54,642
Maybe you're the bad guy
pretending to be the good guy.

246
00:27:54,726 --> 00:27:56,894
You ever think about that?

247
00:27:58,521 --> 00:28:00,022
Every day.

248
00:28:12,410 --> 00:28:14,244
I always wondered,

249
00:28:16,456 --> 00:28:19,249
why did you let
my brother go that day?

250
00:28:20,752 --> 00:28:22,252
I don't know.

251
00:28:32,180 --> 00:28:33,597
Shit.

252
00:28:36,726 --> 00:28:37,726
Brian !

253
00:28:37,811 --> 00:28:40,813
I got the cross-checks
on David Park back and
have a list of possibles.

254
00:28:40,939 --> 00:28:43,357
What do you got?
All right. A 45-year-old
male in a '06 Scion

255
00:28:43,441 --> 00:28:45,526
with three reckless
driving tickets.
No.

256
00:28:45,610 --> 00:28:47,986
An '01 Chevy Tahoe.
No.

257
00:28:48,071 --> 00:28:51,907
Two Mini Coopers,
a '06 and a '07,
a Toyota hybrid.

258
00:28:51,991 --> 00:28:54,660
Hell no.
A '98 Saturn,
a '95 Sebring.

259
00:28:54,744 --> 00:28:56,870
A '98 Nissan 240
with an illegal mod.

260
00:28:56,955 --> 00:28:58,956
Wait. That's it.

261
00:28:59,040 --> 00:29:01,542
What?
The 240 with
the illegal mod.

262
00:29:01,668 --> 00:29:04,920
How do you know?
'Cause that's something
I'd drive.

263
00:29:29,362 --> 00:29:30,821
Don't! Don't! Don't!

264
00:29:42,459 --> 00:29:45,169
Green Torino,
running nitro.

265
00:29:46,129 --> 00:29:47,796
Whose car?
I don't know, man.

266
00:29:47,881 --> 00:29:50,883
I'm just the middleman. I swear!
I'm just the middleman !

267
00:29:51,509 --> 00:29:52,760
(GROANS)

268
00:29:55,722 --> 00:29:57,431
(PANTING)
Wait, wait, wait.

269
00:29:58,016 --> 00:30:01,810
I don't know shit, man. I swear.
I just run cars for Braga, all right?

270
00:30:01,895 --> 00:30:04,688
All l can do is
get you in the race!
That's all l can do!

271
00:30:04,773 --> 00:30:06,148
What race?

272
00:30:08,401 --> 00:30:09,735
(SCREAMING)

273
00:30:11,613 --> 00:30:13,363
Help! Come on,
hold on !

274
00:30:13,448 --> 00:30:15,824
Let me up, man !
Come on !

275
00:30:27,003 --> 00:30:29,838
Come on, man,I don't know shit!
Just let me up!

276
00:30:29,923 --> 00:30:32,090
O told you, you got to
talk to Braga!

277
00:30:32,175 --> 00:30:33,133
Bring him up, Dom.

278
00:30:33,218 --> 00:30:35,928
God ! Don't drop me!
That's all I know!

279
00:30:37,013 --> 00:30:38,514
Bring him up.

280
00:30:38,598 --> 00:30:41,099
You here to take
me in, O'Conner?

281
00:30:41,559 --> 00:30:44,102
Shit! Shit!
Shut up!

282
00:30:46,981 --> 00:30:48,690
Letty was my friend, too.

283
00:30:48,775 --> 00:30:50,400
You weren't
anyone's friend.

284
00:30:50,485 --> 00:30:53,612
Yo, can you guys
talk about this later?
Now pull my ass up!

285
00:30:53,696 --> 00:30:55,989
She was running
for this guy, Braga,
and things went bad.

286
00:30:56,074 --> 00:30:57,115
Please!

287
00:30:57,200 --> 00:30:59,827
I'm going to
get these guys, Dom.

288
00:30:59,911 --> 00:31:02,120
Now let me do my job
and bring him up.

289
00:31:02,205 --> 00:31:04,665
I'm going to
kill this Braga.

290
00:31:06,584 --> 00:31:07,793
God !

291
00:31:08,211 --> 00:31:10,963
And anyone else
who gets in my way.

292
00:31:15,218 --> 00:31:16,426
Hey!

293
00:31:17,095 --> 00:31:18,637
Don't let go.

294
00:31:27,522 --> 00:31:28,814
O'Conner!

295
00:31:30,567 --> 00:31:34,236
O'Conner!
If you ever release
a witness of mine again. . .

296
00:31:35,154 --> 00:31:36,154
(GROANS)

297
00:31:38,616 --> 00:31:40,534
That's enough !
STASIAK:
Don't touch me.

298
00:31:40,618 --> 00:31:42,035
I'm fine!
PENNlNG: That's enough.

299
00:31:42,120 --> 00:31:45,330
You're through, O'Conner!
I said that's enough !

300
00:31:46,833 --> 00:31:48,375
Stasiak, go get
yourself cleaned up.

301
00:31:48,459 --> 00:31:50,711
What?
He hit me first! You. . .

302
00:31:50,795 --> 00:31:52,796
This isn't
the Cub Scouts!

303
00:31:52,881 --> 00:31:56,133
Now, go on !
You're bleeding
on my floor.

304
00:32:05,727 --> 00:32:08,562
O'Conner, do you know
the difference between
a cop and a criminal?

305
00:32:08,646 --> 00:32:11,064
What?
One bad judgment call.

306
00:32:12,567 --> 00:32:14,735
Keep your shit in line,
son.

307
00:32:18,698 --> 00:32:20,449
Have a good time.

308
00:32:23,453 --> 00:32:25,120
Take a seat.

309
00:32:29,042 --> 00:32:33,670
Good news.
We have intel that Braga's
number two, Ramon Campos,

310
00:32:33,755 --> 00:32:35,923
will hold a street race
in Koreatown tomorrow night

311
00:32:36,007 --> 00:32:38,175
to fill a slot
on his team.

312
00:32:38,718 --> 00:32:41,386
They've already chosen three drivers
from previous races.

313
00:32:42,889 --> 00:32:45,015
Our newest informant,
Mr. David Park,

314
00:32:45,099 --> 00:32:47,851
has been kind enough
to get us into the race.

315
00:32:50,355 --> 00:32:52,564
O'Conner, you're up.

316
00:32:53,399 --> 00:32:55,984
Let me guess,
winner gets the slot.

317
00:32:59,989 --> 00:33:01,031
(CHUCKLES)

318
00:33:01,532 --> 00:33:04,284
All right, so these are all the imports
the city has in impound.

319
00:33:04,369 --> 00:33:06,495
Okay, nice.
Pick your poison.

320
00:33:06,579 --> 00:33:09,790
All right, 2206.
I crashed one of those.

321
00:33:09,874 --> 00:33:14,544
3418 and 2765.

322
00:33:15,880 --> 00:33:17,839
Okay, so which one
do you want?

323
00:33:17,924 --> 00:33:19,633
I want them all.

324
00:33:49,622 --> 00:33:51,415
Standard issue
tracking device.

325
00:33:51,499 --> 00:33:53,417
Boss wants to know
where you are at all times.

326
00:33:54,210 --> 00:33:55,210
(WHIRRING)

327
00:34:21,487 --> 00:34:24,156
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING
ON SPEAKERS)

328
00:34:38,588 --> 00:34:40,088
(CAMPOS SPEAKING SPANISH)

329
00:34:45,928 --> 00:34:47,137
You want to
play with it?

330
00:34:48,139 --> 00:34:49,264
DWIGHT: Hey!

331
00:34:49,640 --> 00:34:52,059
(SNICKERS)
What are you
looking at, nutsack?

332
00:34:52,143 --> 00:34:53,894
I don't know.
You tell me.

333
00:34:53,978 --> 00:34:56,229
The racer wants
what Dwight's got.

334
00:34:56,314 --> 00:34:59,274
See, but, ladies,
Dwight's already
on the team.

335
00:34:59,358 --> 00:35:01,318
You got to be fast
if you want
to drive for Braga.

336
00:35:01,402 --> 00:35:04,237
Is there a problem here?
No.

337
00:35:06,741 --> 00:35:08,742
You one of
Park's guys, blondie?

338
00:35:08,826 --> 00:35:10,327
Yeah. Yeah, I am.

339
00:35:11,079 --> 00:35:12,537
Follow me.

340
00:35:15,875 --> 00:35:17,667
(SOFTLY)
See you later, punk.

341
00:35:18,461 --> 00:35:19,669
You, too, punk.

342
00:35:32,016 --> 00:35:34,184
FENIX: Bull's-eye, coño,
come on !

343
00:35:39,190 --> 00:35:40,148
(CAMPOS EXCLAIMS)

344
00:35:40,233 --> 00:35:41,441
FENIX: We can do this all day.

345
00:35:41,526 --> 00:35:42,984
(CAMPOS SPEAKING SPANISH)

346
00:35:46,656 --> 00:35:48,990
You all know
why you're here.

347
00:35:49,659 --> 00:35:51,159
Good drivers

348
00:35:52,829 --> 00:35:54,621
are a dime a dozen.

349
00:35:55,039 --> 00:35:59,334
Man, every corner's
got a chingadera tuner
racing for pinks.

350
00:36:00,169 --> 00:36:03,171
That's not what Braga
has got me looking for.

351
00:36:03,756 --> 00:36:08,426
Braga wants someone that
would sell their abuelita
to be behind the wheel.

352
00:36:10,012 --> 00:36:14,099
Someone that drives
their 10-second cars
not in a straight line,

353
00:36:14,183 --> 00:36:18,395
but to push it and
make it through places
no one else would take it.

354
00:36:19,105 --> 00:36:20,689
Real drivers.

355
00:36:22,817 --> 00:36:24,901
So, what are we hauling?

356
00:36:25,903 --> 00:36:29,322
CAMPOS: For the money
Braga's paying,
you don't need to know.

357
00:36:29,407 --> 00:36:32,075
You just said
you wanted real drivers.

358
00:36:33,995 --> 00:36:37,247
A real driver knows
exactly what's in his car.

359
00:36:39,167 --> 00:36:40,584
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

360
00:36:42,295 --> 00:36:44,087
Mira, real driver,

361
00:36:45,965 --> 00:36:48,175
nobody's forcing you
to race.

362
00:36:48,259 --> 00:36:50,010
You the boss?

363
00:36:51,762 --> 00:36:54,055
Or am I talking
to the boss?

364
00:36:57,018 --> 00:36:58,935
Do I look like a boss?

365
00:37:01,147 --> 00:37:04,691
My job is to find
the best drivers,
period.

366
00:37:04,775 --> 00:37:08,445
Whoever wins the race
gets the info. We cool?

367
00:37:13,367 --> 00:37:14,910
Are we cool?

368
00:37:17,121 --> 00:37:18,788
Yeah, we're cool.

369
00:37:19,290 --> 00:37:21,291
RACER: No,
we ain't cool, man.

370
00:37:22,001 --> 00:37:24,169
Who's closing these streets?

371
00:37:24,712 --> 00:37:26,379
(CHUCKLING)

372
00:37:26,464 --> 00:37:28,548
No one.
That's the point.

373
00:37:30,760 --> 00:37:33,553
(CAR ENGINES REVVING)

374
00:37:40,478 --> 00:37:43,688
AUTOMATED VOICE ON GPS:
PIease wait whiIe
directions are downIoaded.

375
00:37:49,445 --> 00:37:51,905
Proceed to
the highlighted route.

376
00:37:52,657 --> 00:37:53,782
Ten,

377
00:37:55,493 --> 00:37:56,701
nine,

378
00:37:58,287 --> 00:37:59,537
eight,

379
00:38:01,207 --> 00:38:02,457
seven,

380
00:38:03,834 --> 00:38:05,001
six...

381
00:38:05,044 --> 00:38:08,338
You sure
you want to do this?
A lot has changed.

382
00:38:09,298 --> 00:38:11,132
...four...
You're right.

383
00:38:11,968 --> 00:38:13,176
...three,

384
00:38:14,720 --> 00:38:15,887
two,

385
00:38:17,390 --> 00:38:18,556
one,

386
00:38:19,976 --> 00:38:21,101
go!

387
00:38:21,185 --> 00:38:22,852
(TIRES SQUEALING)

388
00:38:29,485 --> 00:38:31,194
Right turn ahead.

389
00:38:34,532 --> 00:38:37,701
You are now five miIes
from your destination.

390
00:38:48,170 --> 00:38:49,379
(HONKING)

391
00:39:03,728 --> 00:39:05,562
How's my ass look,
Chia Pet?

392
00:39:06,397 --> 00:39:07,939
Ghetto Smurf.

393
00:39:11,444 --> 00:39:13,111
(TIRES SQUEALING)

394
00:39:16,407 --> 00:39:17,907
(CARS HONKING)

395
00:39:21,412 --> 00:39:22,412
(TRUCK HONKS)

396
00:39:33,049 --> 00:39:34,758
Dead man driving.

397
00:39:38,387 --> 00:39:39,679
Come on !

398
00:39:40,973 --> 00:39:42,766
Right turn ahead.

399
00:39:58,115 --> 00:39:59,115
(SCREAMS)

400
00:40:01,744 --> 00:40:02,911
Shit!

401
00:40:08,209 --> 00:40:09,501
Damn.

402
00:40:09,585 --> 00:40:19,427
Rerouting.

403
00:40:28,062 --> 00:40:30,230
Proceed straight ahead.

404
00:40:34,527 --> 00:40:35,902
Rerouting.

405
00:40:38,739 --> 00:40:39,739
(HONKING)

406
00:40:40,199 --> 00:40:41,491
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)

407
00:40:45,704 --> 00:40:46,913
Shit.

408
00:40:48,374 --> 00:40:50,583
Rerouting.
Just shut up!

409
00:40:54,380 --> 00:40:57,799
You are 2.6 miIes
from destination.

410
00:41:00,678 --> 00:41:02,387
Oops, I didn't see you.

411
00:41:04,849 --> 00:41:08,852
You are now four
and one-haIf miIes
from your destination.

412
00:41:14,525 --> 00:41:15,817
(CAR HONKING)

413
00:41:41,552 --> 00:41:44,429
U-turn, if possible.
Are you kidding me?

414
00:41:44,513 --> 00:41:48,558
You are now 4.2 miIes
from your destination.

415
00:41:50,394 --> 00:41:51,811
Sorry, car.

416
00:41:59,111 --> 00:42:01,613
You are now one miIe
from your destination.

417
00:42:01,697 --> 00:42:03,907
Yeah,
guess who's back, Dom?

418
00:42:06,827 --> 00:42:08,161
Let's go!

419
00:42:12,625 --> 00:42:14,250
Nice car, baby!

420
00:42:32,353 --> 00:42:33,895
(TIRES SQUEALING)

421
00:42:40,319 --> 00:42:41,319
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)

422
00:42:58,921 --> 00:43:00,129
Bitch !

423
00:43:01,465 --> 00:43:04,551
You are now
one-quarter mile
from your destination.

424
00:43:18,440 --> 00:43:19,816
(ENGINE REVVING)

425
00:43:23,195 --> 00:43:24,821
Too early, Dom.

426
00:43:27,866 --> 00:43:28,866
(TIRES SQUEAL)

427
00:43:44,049 --> 00:43:45,091
No!

428
00:43:45,676 --> 00:43:47,468
Still a buster.

429
00:43:49,555 --> 00:43:50,805
(PEOPLE CHEERING)

430
00:43:50,889 --> 00:43:54,017
You have reached
your destination.
Goodbye.

431
00:44:06,196 --> 00:44:09,073
At least we know
you can't beat me
straight up.

432
00:44:09,158 --> 00:44:10,950
I didn't know
there were any rules.

433
00:44:11,035 --> 00:44:12,827
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

434
00:44:12,911 --> 00:44:14,621
Now that's what I call
real driving.

435
00:44:14,705 --> 00:44:16,080
No, that's bullshit, man !

436
00:44:16,165 --> 00:44:18,124
Go cry to your mama, eh?

437
00:44:20,544 --> 00:44:22,545
You work for Braga now.

438
00:44:22,963 --> 00:44:25,757
When the GPS calls,
you follow.

439
00:44:30,763 --> 00:44:32,555
Driver's license.

440
00:44:32,640 --> 00:44:35,224
What driver's license?

441
00:44:35,768 --> 00:44:37,310
Thumb.

442
00:44:41,982 --> 00:44:43,775
Cell phone number.

443
00:44:48,864 --> 00:44:51,074
The print is for Campos.

444
00:44:51,742 --> 00:44:53,618
The number is for me.

445
00:44:57,081 --> 00:44:58,456
Yo, nutsack!

446
00:44:58,540 --> 00:45:02,126
Let me tell you
something, man, muscle
beats import every time.

447
00:45:02,211 --> 00:45:05,004
You know what I'm saying?
Every time!

448
00:45:05,881 --> 00:45:08,925
Ladies, let's get on
back to Papa Dwight's.

449
00:45:15,557 --> 00:45:18,601
DWIGHT: Papa Dwight wants you
to take off your shoes.

450
00:45:19,269 --> 00:45:22,230
Dwight likes feet.
Take off your shoes.

451
00:45:23,148 --> 00:45:24,691
So beautiful.

452
00:45:24,775 --> 00:45:26,025
(CHUCKLES)

453
00:45:26,819 --> 00:45:28,820
Dwight likes this foot a lot.

454
00:45:37,121 --> 00:45:38,538
Yes, baby!

455
00:45:39,707 --> 00:45:41,916
Daddy Dwight loves. . .
BRIAN: FBI !

456
00:45:43,794 --> 00:45:46,838
I didn't do nothing, man !
Dwight didn't do nothing !

457
00:45:46,964 --> 00:45:49,424
Hey, no! Stay, stay!
Where you going?
WOMAN: Bye, Dwight!

458
00:45:49,508 --> 00:45:50,717
No, what did I do?

459
00:45:50,801 --> 00:45:51,843
(EXCLAIMS IN PAIN)

460
00:45:51,927 --> 00:45:54,011
BRIAN: You're under arrest
for distribution of meth.

461
00:45:54,096 --> 00:45:57,432
Meth? Dwight's never
touched that shit, bro!

462
00:45:57,516 --> 00:45:58,558
Dwight has now.

463
00:45:58,642 --> 00:46:01,018
Yo, that ain't mine! No!

464
00:46:01,103 --> 00:46:03,229
You know that's never
gonna stick, right?

465
00:46:03,313 --> 00:46:05,565
Yeah, it's not
supposed to.

466
00:46:07,234 --> 00:46:08,234
(TIRES SQUEALING)

467
00:46:08,318 --> 00:46:10,236
Live it up!
Live it up!

468
00:46:10,320 --> 00:46:45,688
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)

469
00:47:05,709 --> 00:47:07,210
Yeah, Corona.

470
00:47:10,214 --> 00:47:11,589
That's too bad
about Dwight.

471
00:47:11,673 --> 00:47:15,134
Having the Feds raid
your house the same night
you make the team.

472
00:47:15,219 --> 00:47:17,220
So unfortunate.

473
00:47:17,304 --> 00:47:20,723
I wish I could say I was surprised
to see you here.

474
00:47:22,309 --> 00:47:25,561
What's to stop someone
from telling them
you're a cop?

475
00:47:25,646 --> 00:47:29,398
Probably the same thing
that's keeping me from telling
them why you're really here.

476
00:47:29,483 --> 00:47:31,692
What up, fellows?
Hey, how you doing?

477
00:47:31,777 --> 00:47:34,445
Great. You having
a good time?
Yeah, a great time.

478
00:47:34,530 --> 00:47:37,073
Come on,
let's have
a better time.

479
00:47:37,616 --> 00:47:41,160
How's your car?
It took a nasty bump.

480
00:47:41,245 --> 00:47:42,787
BRIAN: It'll be ready.

481
00:47:42,871 --> 00:47:46,207
I also heard you just
got out of County.

482
00:47:46,291 --> 00:47:47,875
Yeah.
Mmm-hmm.

483
00:47:48,210 --> 00:47:49,961
You know a guy
named Jim Garcia?

484
00:47:50,045 --> 00:47:54,090
Nah. Big place.
Lots of names,
lots of faces.

485
00:47:55,592 --> 00:47:58,636
And you, you're wanted by
a lot of people, homes.

486
00:47:58,720 --> 00:48:01,305
Yeah, that kind of heat
can't be good for business.

487
00:48:01,390 --> 00:48:04,308
Yeah, well, that depends
on how you look at things.

488
00:48:04,393 --> 00:48:06,769
I go down, I do time.

489
00:48:07,813 --> 00:48:09,480
I do real time.

490
00:48:10,524 --> 00:48:15,069
I don't know about your
other drivers, but when I see
flashing lights in my mirror,

491
00:48:15,153 --> 00:48:16,654
I don't stop.

492
00:48:22,035 --> 00:48:24,036
Do you know each other?

493
00:48:28,125 --> 00:48:30,293
He used to date
my sister.

494
00:48:31,378 --> 00:48:32,712
I see.

495
00:48:35,132 --> 00:48:37,675
You're a lucky man.
How's that?

496
00:48:38,719 --> 00:48:40,720
You're still breathing.

497
00:48:42,472 --> 00:48:43,806
(CHUCKLES)

498
00:48:46,768 --> 00:48:50,813
To the ladies we've loved
and the ladies we've lost.

499
00:48:50,981 --> 00:48:53,149
(CAMPOS TOASTING IN SPANISH)

500
00:48:59,531 --> 00:49:01,574
So, what's Braga about?

501
00:49:03,493 --> 00:49:05,369
You know,
he's just one of us.

502
00:49:05,454 --> 00:49:08,915
Came up from the streets.
Down for el barrio.

503
00:49:08,999 --> 00:49:11,208
Now he's a shot caller.

504
00:49:12,044 --> 00:49:13,920
The boss of bosses.

505
00:49:14,546 --> 00:49:16,839
See all these
cats in here?

506
00:49:17,424 --> 00:49:20,092
Any one of them
would die for Braga.

507
00:49:20,177 --> 00:49:21,802
Including you?

508
00:49:23,931 --> 00:49:25,556
Especially me.

509
00:49:28,477 --> 00:49:30,102
(WHISPERING)

510
00:49:35,359 --> 00:49:37,109
Enjoy the party, fellows.
Club's yours.

511
00:49:37,194 --> 00:49:40,446
Whatever you want,
booze, broads,
it's all good.

512
00:49:43,867 --> 00:49:45,409
Braga's mine.

513
00:49:48,997 --> 00:49:51,374
I'm taking the
whole house down.

514
00:49:52,167 --> 00:49:53,542
Good luck.

515
00:49:56,004 --> 00:49:57,797
(CLUB MUSIC PLAYING)

516
00:50:41,925 --> 00:50:43,759
(ELEVATOR BELL RINGS)

517
00:51:05,949 --> 00:51:07,616
(MEN CHATTERING)

518
00:52:01,338 --> 00:52:04,048
Something interests you
about this car?

519
00:52:04,674 --> 00:52:06,926
Just admiring
the body work.

520
00:52:08,512 --> 00:52:12,515
Are you one of those boys
who prefers cars to women?

521
00:52:15,977 --> 00:52:20,689
I'm one of those boys
that appreciates a fine body,
regardless of the make.

522
00:52:24,361 --> 00:52:25,820
Your car?

523
00:52:29,866 --> 00:52:31,534
It's Fenix's car.

524
00:52:32,744 --> 00:52:36,831
You'll meet him
at the rendezvous.
He'll be leading you.

525
00:52:38,333 --> 00:52:39,708
So now

526
00:52:41,128 --> 00:52:43,504
that I know
your taste in cars,

527
00:52:43,588 --> 00:52:46,132
tell me,
what about your women?

528
00:52:48,135 --> 00:52:50,302
It all starts
with the eyes.

529
00:52:52,806 --> 00:52:57,977
She's got to have those
kind of eyes that can look
right through the bullshit

530
00:52:58,061 --> 00:53:00,187
to the good in someone.

531
00:53:04,818 --> 00:53:07,987
20% angel,
80% devil.

532
00:53:09,656 --> 00:53:11,490
Down to earth.

533
00:53:13,326 --> 00:53:17,496
Ain't afraid to get
a little engine grease
under her fingernails.

534
00:53:24,462 --> 00:53:27,089
That doesn't sound
anything like me.

535
00:53:29,759 --> 00:53:31,093
It ain't.

536
00:53:39,186 --> 00:53:40,186
Hi.
Hi.

537
00:53:40,270 --> 00:53:43,355
I got a gift for you.
All right.

538
00:53:43,440 --> 00:53:45,983
A dirty shot glass,
just what I always wanted.

539
00:53:46,067 --> 00:53:47,651
I got these
from the club last night.

540
00:53:47,736 --> 00:53:49,695
There's two sets
of prints here.
Run them both.

541
00:53:49,779 --> 00:53:53,282
I know one of these
is Campos'. I think
the other might be Braga's.

542
00:53:53,366 --> 00:53:55,910
And you're gonna have
to go beyond Interpol.

543
00:53:55,994 --> 00:53:58,370
So, that means
I have to contact
individual agencies,

544
00:53:58,455 --> 00:54:00,998
and that could
take weeks. Okay.

545
00:54:01,082 --> 00:54:03,125
(GPS VIBRATING)

546
00:54:09,049 --> 00:54:10,633
(CARS HONKING)

547
00:54:13,136 --> 00:54:14,637
(CELL PHONE RINGING)

548
00:54:16,097 --> 00:54:17,056
Yeah.

549
00:54:17,140 --> 00:54:20,309
That's your third
traffic violation in
less than three blocks.

550
00:54:20,393 --> 00:54:22,394
Slow it down,
O'Conner.

551
00:54:23,063 --> 00:54:24,772
Sure thing, Dad.

552
00:54:53,843 --> 00:54:54,927
He stopped.

553
00:55:07,274 --> 00:55:08,774
(BUG DETECTOR BUZZING)

554
00:55:08,858 --> 00:55:09,858
(BEEPING)

555
00:55:44,102 --> 00:55:46,395
(BUG DETECTOR BUZZING)

556
00:55:49,566 --> 00:55:50,983
We lost him.

557
00:55:51,067 --> 00:55:52,568
He killed the tracker.
We don't know that.

558
00:55:52,694 --> 00:55:54,903
I'm telling you,
he killed the tracker.
We don't know that yet!

559
00:55:54,988 --> 00:55:56,905
Get the bird overhead.

560
00:55:58,033 --> 00:56:01,076
PILOT ON RADIO: Right now,
I'm moving north,
33', 56'...

561
00:56:05,081 --> 00:56:06,457
All clear.

562
00:56:29,397 --> 00:56:31,690
PILOT ON RADIO:
Base, fIag nine,
I'm at AngeIs 5.

563
00:56:31,775 --> 00:56:35,402
I don't have a tally on
the target. Repeat, I don't
have a tally on the target.

564
00:56:35,487 --> 00:56:37,196
They're gone,
there's no one
down there.

565
00:56:37,280 --> 00:56:38,614
Damn it!

566
00:56:49,667 --> 00:56:54,463
TASH: This ain't right, bro.
Nobody said nothing about
being locked in no truck.

567
00:56:54,547 --> 00:56:56,298
Tell me about it.

568
00:56:59,052 --> 00:57:00,803
Hey. Hey!

569
00:57:02,514 --> 00:57:05,557
Yo!
Where do you think
they're taking us?

570
00:57:05,642 --> 00:57:07,226
Don't matter.

571
00:57:10,146 --> 00:57:12,981
We're all just along
for the ride now.

572
00:57:24,077 --> 00:57:26,078
Welcome to Mexico, boys.

573
00:57:31,835 --> 00:57:34,211
There are helicopters
and surveillance cameras

574
00:57:34,295 --> 00:57:36,755
that scan for heat
signatures at the border.

575
00:57:36,840 --> 00:57:40,801
But there are blind spots
that I can guide you
through via satellite.

576
00:57:40,885 --> 00:57:45,389
There can be no margin
of error, so you must
follow my every direction.

577
00:57:46,099 --> 00:57:47,474
Any questions?

578
00:57:49,519 --> 00:57:52,062
I thought Fenix
was gonna be here.

579
00:57:55,233 --> 00:57:57,317
He'll meet you
out there.

580
00:58:02,198 --> 00:58:04,533
All right,
everybody,
sync up.

581
00:58:07,328 --> 00:58:09,204
Good luck, gentlemen.

582
00:58:10,665 --> 00:58:12,374
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

583
00:58:22,635 --> 00:58:24,219
GISELE ON RADIO:
Satellite Iinkup engaged.

584
00:58:25,555 --> 00:58:28,599
Keep proceeding northbound
at current speed.

585
00:58:32,562 --> 00:58:34,438
Stay cIose to Fenix.

586
00:58:35,607 --> 00:58:37,065
He'll Iead you across.

587
00:58:43,740 --> 00:58:45,073
(BEEPING)

588
00:58:49,746 --> 00:58:51,163
(MONITOR BEEPING)

589
00:58:51,247 --> 00:58:54,791
I got a heat signature
northbound
along Legardo Ravine.

590
00:58:57,253 --> 00:59:01,798
Thermal imaging window
on the Mexico side's gonna be
down for about 45 seconds.

591
00:59:01,883 --> 00:59:03,759
Get the camera on it.

592
00:59:03,843 --> 00:59:07,679
MAN: Manual override.
Rerouting camera to
designated coordinates.

593
00:59:10,850 --> 00:59:13,644
GISELE: Hurry it up.
You guys have been tagged.

594
00:59:19,275 --> 00:59:21,068
(CAR ENGINES REVVING)

595
00:59:23,446 --> 00:59:24,780
Shit.

596
00:59:25,949 --> 00:59:28,367
Toretto,
get back in formation.

597
00:59:31,538 --> 00:59:32,621
Reimaging commencing.

598
00:59:41,422 --> 00:59:43,340
I don't see anything.

599
00:59:43,424 --> 00:59:44,633
They're gone.

600
00:59:46,678 --> 00:59:48,637
Get the helicopters
to cover it.

601
00:59:52,725 --> 00:59:55,852
PILOT ON RADIO: Base,
we're 40 seconds out
from Legardo Ravine.

602
00:59:56,729 --> 00:59:58,355
GISELE: They're sending
a heIicopter.

603
00:59:59,983 --> 01:00:01,858
You have 30 seconds.

604
01:00:10,660 --> 01:00:13,787
PILOT: North 32' 33',
west 1 1 6' 49'.

605
01:00:20,295 --> 01:00:22,087
GISELE: The window
is cIosing fast.

606
01:00:22,171 --> 01:00:25,340
You need to get out
of there before
they send ground support.

607
01:00:31,556 --> 01:00:33,223
Fifteen seconds.

608
01:00:38,688 --> 01:00:41,023
PILOT: Base,
target is at two miIes.

609
01:00:54,203 --> 01:00:56,413
GISELE: You're running
out of time.

610
01:00:59,459 --> 01:01:01,543
You need to get out now!

611
01:01:13,514 --> 01:01:17,517
PILOT: Base,
we're at north 32' 33',
west 1 1 6' 49'.

612
01:01:17,602 --> 01:01:21,480
We have no visuaI contact.
Roll ground units
for confirmation.

613
01:01:42,418 --> 01:01:43,752
Sloppy!

614
01:01:44,420 --> 01:01:45,962
Very sloppy!

615
01:01:51,594 --> 01:01:53,637
What are you doing, man?

616
01:01:54,972 --> 01:01:56,056
(GAS HISSING)

617
01:01:56,140 --> 01:01:57,474
Come on.

618
01:01:57,809 --> 01:01:59,267
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

619
01:02:00,603 --> 01:02:01,937
Get out.

620
01:02:05,400 --> 01:02:06,650
Come on, man.

621
01:02:06,734 --> 01:02:08,694
Come on, today, man.
Come on, let's go.

622
01:02:08,778 --> 01:02:10,654
MALIK: Hey, don't touch me.
Hey, don't touch me, man !

623
01:02:10,738 --> 01:02:11,947
(MAN SPEAKING SPANISH)

624
01:02:12,031 --> 01:02:13,740
Hey,
I said don't
touch me, man !

625
01:02:13,825 --> 01:02:15,367
Hey, look, dawg,
don't put
your hands on me.

626
01:02:15,451 --> 01:02:16,952
TASH: Hey,
Malik, chill, bro.

627
01:02:17,078 --> 01:02:18,286
Yo, man, what's up
with your boy?

628
01:02:18,371 --> 01:02:20,247
(GUN COCKS)
DOM: Hey, boss man !

629
01:02:23,167 --> 01:02:24,876
What did you say?

630
01:02:24,961 --> 01:02:28,714
I said only pussies
run nitrometh.

631
01:02:31,342 --> 01:02:33,427
You looked under my hood?

632
01:02:40,309 --> 01:02:42,018
I'm talking to you.

633
01:02:42,103 --> 01:02:44,312
Got something on your mind?

634
01:02:45,148 --> 01:02:46,481
'70 Plymouth.

635
01:02:49,485 --> 01:02:50,777
Her name was Letty.

636
01:02:53,906 --> 01:02:54,990
Yo.

637
01:02:56,534 --> 01:02:58,285
Where's my money?

638
01:02:59,996 --> 01:03:02,330
DOM: And somebody
wrecked her car.

639
01:03:10,131 --> 01:03:11,381
I wrecked her car.

640
01:03:11,632 --> 01:03:12,841
(TIRES SQUEALING)

641
01:03:15,970 --> 01:03:17,012
You remember her face?

642
01:03:22,769 --> 01:03:23,769
Huh?

643
01:03:24,645 --> 01:03:26,271
'Cause I don't.

644
01:03:27,648 --> 01:03:30,317
Last time I saw it,
it was burning.

645
01:03:44,123 --> 01:03:45,499
Now what?

646
01:03:47,126 --> 01:03:49,878
I'm going to enjoy
what happens next.

647
01:03:55,426 --> 01:03:57,344
(MAN SCREAMING)

648
01:04:02,558 --> 01:04:03,600
(GUNFIRE)

649
01:04:05,895 --> 01:04:07,270
(GRUNTING)

650
01:04:13,152 --> 01:04:14,361
(GUNSHOT)

651
01:04:20,660 --> 01:04:21,660
(MAN GROANS)

652
01:04:23,955 --> 01:04:25,455
Dom, get in !

653
01:04:26,749 --> 01:04:28,416
Get in ! Come on !

654
01:04:29,085 --> 01:04:30,335
(ALARM BLARING)

655
01:04:30,419 --> 01:04:34,256
Come on ! Get in
the fucking car!
Let's go! Hurry up!

656
01:04:36,259 --> 01:04:38,385
(HELICOPTERS WHIRRING
IN DISTANCE)

657
01:04:56,404 --> 01:04:57,696
(PHONE DIALING)

658
01:04:58,155 --> 01:04:59,739
(PHONE RINGING)

659
01:05:01,242 --> 01:05:02,868
PENNING: What
have you got, Trinh?

660
01:05:02,952 --> 01:05:05,537
We're contacting agencies
in multiple countries.

661
01:05:05,621 --> 01:05:10,625
Unfortunately, most of them
have to manually scan
their prints for us to upload.

662
01:05:11,460 --> 01:05:13,545
O'Conner's on line five.

663
01:05:13,629 --> 01:05:15,714
And, sir,
you should see this.

664
01:05:15,798 --> 01:05:17,299
Thank you.

665
01:05:26,601 --> 01:05:27,601
(PHONE BEEPS)

666
01:05:27,685 --> 01:05:28,810
Talk to me, O'Conner.

667
01:05:29,270 --> 01:05:31,438
Where the hell have you been?
I got the shipment.

668
01:05:31,522 --> 01:05:34,524
"I got the shipment,"
or "we got the shipment"?

669
01:05:34,609 --> 01:05:36,651
What are you
taIking about?

670
01:05:36,736 --> 01:05:41,197
Traffic cams in the area
picked up pictures of you
and Toretto together.

671
01:05:42,325 --> 01:05:47,078
Listen to me, O'Conner.
Bring in the shipment
and bring in Toretto.

672
01:05:47,496 --> 01:05:50,165
But I thought the point
was to get Braga.
We got an opportunity here.

673
01:05:50,249 --> 01:05:52,834
Brian, the clock
stopped ticking.

674
01:05:53,711 --> 01:05:56,004
Bring them in.
Are we cIear?

675
01:06:00,343 --> 01:06:01,676
O'Conner?

676
01:06:01,761 --> 01:06:03,094
(PHONE BEEPS)

677
01:06:11,687 --> 01:06:14,522
So this is what
$60 million looks like.

678
01:06:16,275 --> 01:06:18,902
Yeah, we got to
get you to a doctor.

679
01:06:18,986 --> 01:06:21,655
We got to find
a place to hide this.

680
01:06:24,241 --> 01:06:25,408
I got a spot.

681
01:06:35,503 --> 01:06:38,421
502, wet reckless.
I need a 48-hour hold.

682
01:06:40,549 --> 01:06:42,384
Out back.
Any spot you can find.

683
01:06:47,556 --> 01:06:49,432
You sure about this?

684
01:06:50,393 --> 01:06:56,564
Yeah. The last place
they'll check, their own
impound yard. Trust me.

685
01:07:03,072 --> 01:07:04,948
You know,
I've been thinking,

686
01:07:05,032 --> 01:07:07,492
when you blew up
your car back there,
you blew up mine, too.

687
01:07:07,576 --> 01:07:10,078
Yeah?
Yeah.

688
01:07:10,162 --> 01:07:12,747
So now you owe me
a 1 0-second car.

689
01:07:14,083 --> 01:07:16,334
Is that right?
Yeah.

690
01:07:27,596 --> 01:07:29,305
Now we're even.

691
01:07:42,486 --> 01:07:44,195
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)

692
01:07:44,989 --> 01:07:47,866
Is this your way
of keeping me away from him?

693
01:07:47,992 --> 01:07:51,828
You're the only one
I could call.
He's my brother, of course.

694
01:07:59,462 --> 01:08:01,546
The bullet's not in there.

695
01:08:09,096 --> 01:08:13,058
I'm gonna clean it
and stitch it up. It's going to hurt.

696
01:08:13,142 --> 01:08:15,602
I bet you're going
to enjoy this.

697
01:08:16,270 --> 01:08:17,604
A little.

698
01:08:20,566 --> 01:08:22,984
MIA: Want some of this?
DOM: Yeah.

699
01:08:23,069 --> 01:08:25,111
MIA: It's spicy.

700
01:08:26,864 --> 01:08:28,490
I like it hot.

701
01:08:29,617 --> 01:08:31,826
Dom, what are you doing?

702
01:08:31,911 --> 01:08:34,829
You reached first,
you have to say grace.

703
01:08:45,132 --> 01:08:49,010
Thank you, Lord,
for blessing this table.

704
01:08:50,471 --> 01:08:55,225
With food, family
and friendship.

705
01:09:28,968 --> 01:09:31,302
You asked me
why I let Dom go.

706
01:09:33,389 --> 01:09:36,057
I think it's because
at that moment,

707
01:09:37,768 --> 01:09:40,603
I respected him
more than I did myself.

708
01:09:44,984 --> 01:09:46,192
Yeah.

709
01:09:47,778 --> 01:09:52,907
One thing I learned from Dom
is that nothing really matters
unless you have a code.

710
01:09:56,120 --> 01:09:58,413
And what's your code,
Brian?

711
01:10:00,791 --> 01:10:02,584
I'm working on it.

712
01:10:19,810 --> 01:10:21,060
(BEEPS)

713
01:10:25,107 --> 01:10:26,191
(PHONE DIALING)

714
01:10:27,109 --> 01:10:28,943
(CELL PHONE RINGING)

715
01:10:37,453 --> 01:10:38,995
Shit. Hey, Dom.

716
01:10:39,121 --> 01:10:41,664
When were you
gonna tell me?
Dom, what are you doing?

717
01:10:41,749 --> 01:10:43,708
When were you gonna tell me
you were running Letty?

718
01:10:43,792 --> 01:10:46,127
Let me explain. . .
When were you gonna. . .

719
01:10:51,550 --> 01:10:52,842
Dom, stop!

720
01:10:52,927 --> 01:10:55,094
You don't understand.
I don't understand?

721
01:10:55,179 --> 01:10:56,387
Stop!

722
01:10:57,097 --> 01:10:59,057
(BOTH GRUNTING)

723
01:11:00,559 --> 01:11:01,768
She did it for. . .

724
01:11:02,478 --> 01:11:04,103
(GROANING)

725
01:11:04,855 --> 01:11:06,397
BRIAN: Dom, stop!

726
01:11:06,482 --> 01:11:08,608
Dom, stop it!
Please stop!

727
01:11:12,321 --> 01:11:13,863
(BRIAN GRUNTING)

728
01:11:14,573 --> 01:11:15,949
(GRUNTING)

729
01:11:18,035 --> 01:11:21,663
She did it for you, Dom !
She did it for you !

730
01:11:26,168 --> 01:11:30,505
Letty came to me to clear
your name in exchange
for bringing down Braga.

731
01:11:33,550 --> 01:11:36,052
She just wanted you
to come home!

732
01:11:52,152 --> 01:11:53,152
(YELLS)

733
01:11:53,237 --> 01:11:55,029
I'm sorry, Dom !

734
01:11:55,114 --> 01:11:56,531
I'm sorry!

735
01:12:21,390 --> 01:12:27,228
(SIGHING) You better have
one hell of an explanation.
You disobeyed a direct order.

736
01:12:28,105 --> 01:12:30,106
Where's the shipment?
It's safe.

737
01:12:30,190 --> 01:12:31,983
It's safe.

738
01:12:32,067 --> 01:12:34,944
Look, we could use
the shipment to parade
in front of the media,

739
01:12:35,029 --> 01:12:36,946
get a few hundred
pounds of heroin
off the street,

740
01:12:37,031 --> 01:12:40,742
but Braga's just gonna send
another shipment next week
and the week after that.

741
01:12:40,826 --> 01:12:42,952
Let's use the shipment
to lure Braga out

742
01:12:43,037 --> 01:12:45,079
and lop the head off
a multi-billion dollar cartel.

743
01:12:45,164 --> 01:12:47,540
And how do you
suggest we do that?

744
01:12:47,624 --> 01:12:49,584
A hand-to-hand
exchange with Braga.

745
01:12:49,668 --> 01:12:51,044
He'll never show.

746
01:12:51,128 --> 01:12:52,920
He can't afford not to.

747
01:13:03,057 --> 01:13:04,724
You got a plan?

748
01:13:06,226 --> 01:13:07,894
There's a price.

749
01:13:10,773 --> 01:13:13,566
We bag Braga,
you let Toretto walk.

750
01:13:18,238 --> 01:13:19,781
(RINGING)

751
01:13:22,368 --> 01:13:24,577
Yes?
It's Dom.

752
01:13:25,621 --> 01:13:27,914
I was just
thinking about you.

753
01:13:28,290 --> 01:13:32,210
You know, when I
gave you my number,
I was hoping you'd call.

754
01:13:32,795 --> 01:13:35,338
But not under
these circumstances.

755
01:13:35,672 --> 01:13:38,800
What circumstances?
Me being alive?

756
01:13:39,843 --> 01:13:41,803
Don't take it personally.

757
01:13:42,304 --> 01:13:44,222
It's just business.

758
01:13:44,306 --> 01:13:45,890
I got some business
of my own.

759
01:13:47,184 --> 01:13:48,643
Get Campos.

760
01:13:51,146 --> 01:13:52,563
It's them.

761
01:13:56,902 --> 01:13:57,902
Uh-huh.

762
01:13:58,153 --> 01:14:02,156
Was that how Braga
inspires loyalty?
Killing his drivers?

763
01:14:02,658 --> 01:14:04,992
One can always
find more drivers.

764
01:14:05,244 --> 01:14:07,245
It's just good business.

765
01:14:07,496 --> 01:14:08,746
I want to trade.

766
01:14:09,039 --> 01:14:11,082
Braga doesn't negotiate.

767
01:14:11,166 --> 01:14:12,166
(SCOFFS) Fine.

768
01:14:12,251 --> 01:14:17,130
You explain to him how
all of a sudden $60 million
worth of product disappears.

769
01:14:17,840 --> 01:14:20,133
I know that can't
be good for business.

770
01:14:21,218 --> 01:14:22,760
What do you want?

771
01:14:23,262 --> 01:14:27,515
Six million cash,
delivered by Braga himself.

772
01:14:27,933 --> 01:14:29,225
(LAUGHING)

773
01:14:30,185 --> 01:14:31,811
I don't Iike being shot at.

774
01:14:32,187 --> 01:14:35,440
I ain't gonna put my neck
out again unless he's got
something to lose, too.

775
01:14:35,524 --> 01:14:37,108
He'll never go for it.

776
01:14:37,192 --> 01:14:40,820
Either I deal with Braga,
or you do.

777
01:14:44,825 --> 01:14:46,367
When and where?

778
01:15:01,425 --> 01:15:05,344
Sir, players are onsite.
Holding positions
at the perimeter.

779
01:15:05,804 --> 01:15:08,389
All right. Listen up.
Everybody stay frosty.

780
01:15:08,474 --> 01:15:11,142
We don't move a muscIe untiI
O'Conner gives the signaI.

781
01:15:11,226 --> 01:15:13,936
When he gets the money,
you know what to do.

782
01:15:14,521 --> 01:15:16,981
Well, the good news is,
when we get this guy,

783
01:15:17,065 --> 01:15:19,484
you walk out of here
a free man.

784
01:15:19,860 --> 01:15:21,277
Is that what
they told you?

785
01:15:21,361 --> 01:15:22,987
Yeah, that's the deal.

786
01:15:23,071 --> 01:15:26,491
You still put milk
and cookies out
for Santa Claus?

787
01:15:27,784 --> 01:15:28,951
Yeah.

788
01:15:33,749 --> 01:15:34,832
Here.

789
01:15:34,917 --> 01:15:37,001
In case things go shitty.

790
01:15:41,965 --> 01:15:44,008
Just like old times?

791
01:15:44,092 --> 01:15:45,384
Yeah.

792
01:15:47,679 --> 01:15:48,888
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

793
01:15:48,972 --> 01:15:50,264
You dropped something.

794
01:15:50,349 --> 01:15:52,517
That's what
you wanted, right?
Dom. . .

795
01:15:52,601 --> 01:15:54,435
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

796
01:15:54,937 --> 01:15:57,772
(BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH)

797
01:16:07,616 --> 01:16:10,243
He's harmless.
Don't worry about him.

798
01:16:11,995 --> 01:16:14,497
And he's really
sorry about Letty.

799
01:16:16,625 --> 01:16:18,417
Where's our stuff?

800
01:16:21,171 --> 01:16:24,465
You mean the stuff
that used to be
in here, right?

801
01:16:25,634 --> 01:16:29,428
Well, you'll see it
when we see Braga.
That was the deal.

802
01:16:30,389 --> 01:16:31,806
No worries.

803
01:16:32,182 --> 01:16:34,183
Braga keeps his word.

804
01:17:08,885 --> 01:17:10,344
(BEEPING)

805
01:17:18,186 --> 01:17:19,687
$2 million.

806
01:17:20,772 --> 01:17:23,524
You get the rest
when I get my property.

807
01:17:27,863 --> 01:17:29,488
Stasiak.
TRINH: We got a match.

808
01:17:29,573 --> 01:17:31,616
The fingerprint's
Braga's 100%.

809
01:17:31,700 --> 01:17:34,160
Just waiting on
faciaI confirmation
via fax.

810
01:17:34,244 --> 01:17:36,203
BRIAN: I got
a question for you.

811
01:17:36,288 --> 01:17:40,041
You wearing pink
when you were clawing
your way out of el barrio?

812
01:17:41,293 --> 01:17:42,752
Order all agents
to move in.

813
01:17:42,836 --> 01:17:45,963
We got confirmation.
Primary suspect
wearing gray suit.

814
01:17:46,048 --> 01:17:47,048
Let's move.

815
01:17:47,132 --> 01:17:49,050
Sir, O'Conner hasn't
given us the signal yet.

816
01:17:49,134 --> 01:17:52,470
What part of that didn't
you understand? We just
got confirmation. Do it!

817
01:17:52,554 --> 01:17:55,890
FBI AGENT:
Secure primary suspect
in gray suit. Repeat!

818
01:17:55,974 --> 01:17:58,559
Secure primary suspect
in gray suit.

819
01:18:12,032 --> 01:18:14,742
You're thinking
what I'm thinking,
right?

820
01:18:17,537 --> 01:18:19,163
He ain't Braga.

821
01:18:23,752 --> 01:18:24,752
Oh, shit.

822
01:18:24,920 --> 01:18:27,171
SWAT AGENT 1 :
Drop your weapons!
SWAT AGENT 2: FBI !

823
01:18:27,589 --> 01:18:28,881
Get down !

824
01:18:28,965 --> 01:18:30,257
(GUNFIRE)

825
01:18:32,386 --> 01:18:34,095
Get out of here!

826
01:18:38,183 --> 01:18:40,059
Get out of here, Dom !

827
01:18:42,938 --> 01:18:44,271
(CAR ENGINE REVVING)

828
01:18:44,356 --> 01:18:45,940
Run him down.

829
01:18:46,441 --> 01:18:47,650
Go!

830
01:18:48,318 --> 01:18:49,985
Campos is Braga!

831
01:18:50,070 --> 01:18:51,779
(MEN GROANING)

832
01:18:57,452 --> 01:18:58,744
Come on.

833
01:18:58,829 --> 01:19:00,162
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)

834
01:19:06,128 --> 01:19:08,254
SWAT LEADER:
Approaching primary target.

835
01:19:08,797 --> 01:19:10,965
SWAT AGENT ON RADIO:
Primary suspect is secure.

836
01:19:13,635 --> 01:19:15,428
INVESTIGATOR:
He was under your nose
the whoIe time.

837
01:19:15,971 --> 01:19:17,722
Now Braga's escaped.

838
01:19:17,806 --> 01:19:20,766
Toretto's heading south,
probably long across
the border by now.

839
01:19:20,851 --> 01:19:23,060
Do you have any idea
the kind of trouble
you're in, O'Conner?

840
01:19:23,145 --> 01:19:25,104
I was doing my job.

841
01:19:25,188 --> 01:19:27,732
He ain't the first bad guy
you helped escape
the law's grasp.

842
01:19:27,816 --> 01:19:29,775
As of now,
you're being taken
off active duty,

843
01:19:29,860 --> 01:19:32,820
until this house can
mount a formal inquiry.

844
01:19:34,990 --> 01:19:36,741
What about Braga?

845
01:19:37,826 --> 01:19:40,161
That's no longer
your concern.

846
01:19:50,547 --> 01:19:52,047
We now know
where Braga is,
right?

847
01:19:52,132 --> 01:19:55,593
Customs tracked him
via satellite to his home
base in Tecali, Mexico.

848
01:19:55,677 --> 01:19:58,095
Mexico is out
of our jurisdiction.

849
01:20:00,891 --> 01:20:02,475
The fact is

850
01:20:02,559 --> 01:20:06,645
the brass will be so busy
holding press conferences
over the seizure,

851
01:20:06,730 --> 01:20:08,856
we'll skate
under the radar.

852
01:20:09,316 --> 01:20:12,359
I thought we signed on
to do the right thing.

853
01:20:50,732 --> 01:20:52,858
Everyone's looking for you.

854
01:20:53,235 --> 01:20:54,860
I'm right here.

855
01:20:56,154 --> 01:20:57,488
It's nice to see
you've gone with the times

856
01:20:57,572 --> 01:21:01,158
and switched to
electronic fuel injection.
Looks good.

857
01:21:02,285 --> 01:21:04,370
Buster became a gearhead.

858
01:21:08,458 --> 01:21:10,251
I'm going with you.

859
01:21:14,172 --> 01:21:16,841
I don't plan on
bringing anyone back.

860
01:21:18,802 --> 01:21:20,135
I know.

861
01:21:28,895 --> 01:21:30,563
Hit that throttle.

862
01:21:46,997 --> 01:21:48,330
(SIGHING)

863
01:21:56,840 --> 01:21:57,965
Hey.

864
01:22:13,982 --> 01:22:15,482
(BOTTLES CLATTERING)

865
01:22:39,758 --> 01:22:42,760
How do you say goodbye
to your only brother?

866
01:22:44,930 --> 01:22:46,347
You don't.

867
01:23:00,070 --> 01:23:01,737
(ENGINE REVVING)

868
01:23:55,250 --> 01:23:57,626
I thought you weren't
gonna show up.

869
01:23:57,711 --> 01:23:59,336
You saved my life.

870
01:24:00,213 --> 01:24:02,673
I'm willing to
return the favor.

871
01:24:06,553 --> 01:24:09,054
This will help
get you to Braga.

872
01:24:13,268 --> 01:24:14,351
Dom.

873
01:24:15,353 --> 01:24:17,980
Going in there
is suicide.

874
01:24:26,531 --> 01:24:28,282
I have no choice.

875
01:24:31,870 --> 01:24:34,329
You must have
loved her very much.

876
01:24:43,298 --> 01:24:44,882
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

877
01:24:52,390 --> 01:24:55,100
So this is where
my jurisdiction ends.

878
01:25:00,899 --> 01:25:03,067
And this is where
mine begins.

879
01:25:05,612 --> 01:25:06,987
(ALL SHOUTING)

880
01:25:42,649 --> 01:25:44,358
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

881
01:25:51,199 --> 01:25:52,533
(DOOR OPENING)

882
01:25:56,329 --> 01:25:57,746
(DOOR CLOSING)

883
01:25:58,998 --> 01:26:06,046
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

884
01:26:19,227 --> 01:26:21,562
(BOTH SPEAKING SPANISH)

885
01:26:26,401 --> 01:26:30,946
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

886
01:27:02,395 --> 01:27:04,021
(RECITING PRAYER)

887
01:27:13,448 --> 01:27:15,324
You ain't forgiven.

888
01:27:18,786 --> 01:27:20,954
You boys want
to arrest me?

889
01:27:21,039 --> 01:27:23,916
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

890
01:27:24,000 --> 01:27:26,043
No, we're beyond that.

891
01:27:27,128 --> 01:27:29,922
You can't buy
your way
out of this one.

892
01:27:31,299 --> 01:27:32,966
You and me. . .

893
01:27:34,177 --> 01:27:37,012
You and me,
we're not so different.

894
01:27:38,765 --> 01:27:40,349
You're no hero.

895
01:27:50,985 --> 01:27:52,653
You're right.

896
01:27:55,782 --> 01:27:59,117
And that's why
you're going back
across the border.

897
01:28:03,665 --> 01:28:05,040
(HANDCUFFS CLICKING)

898
01:28:05,124 --> 01:28:06,833
But Fenix is mine.

899
01:28:07,835 --> 01:28:08,919
You got it.

900
01:28:17,178 --> 01:28:18,345
(DOOR OPENING)

901
01:28:23,059 --> 01:28:24,893
(DOOR CLOSING)

902
01:28:31,192 --> 01:28:32,317
Shit!

903
01:28:32,402 --> 01:28:34,027
(TIRES SQUEALING)

904
01:28:37,365 --> 01:28:40,909
You'll make it
a couple of miles out,
if you're lucky.

905
01:28:41,619 --> 01:28:43,161
(CARS HONKING)

906
01:28:43,288 --> 01:28:45,789
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)

907
01:28:50,878 --> 01:28:53,005
(MAN SHOUTING IN SPANISH
ON RADIO)

908
01:28:53,089 --> 01:28:54,631
(ALL SHOUTING)

909
01:29:09,564 --> 01:29:11,231
(PEOPLE CHEERING)

910
01:29:16,612 --> 01:29:17,612
(EXCLAIMS)

911
01:29:17,697 --> 01:29:19,323
(WHISPERING)

912
01:29:29,917 --> 01:29:30,917
(CHUCKLES)

913
01:29:33,463 --> 01:29:35,714
You know where
you're going?

914
01:29:36,758 --> 01:29:38,925
You want to borrow my GPS?

915
01:29:41,512 --> 01:29:42,554
(LAUGHING)

916
01:29:42,638 --> 01:29:44,348
Where are your boys at?

917
01:29:44,432 --> 01:29:45,974
Are they going
to show up or what?

918
01:29:46,059 --> 01:29:47,351
(GUNFIRE)

919
01:29:49,437 --> 01:29:51,480
Careful what you ask for.

920
01:30:07,789 --> 01:30:09,998
Just stop.
Just stop the car.

921
01:30:13,086 --> 01:30:14,378
(SCREAMING)

922
01:30:14,462 --> 01:30:15,754
(SHOUTING IN SPANISH)

923
01:30:22,553 --> 01:30:24,805
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

924
01:30:30,186 --> 01:30:31,895
Right behind you.

925
01:30:46,744 --> 01:30:49,830
Dom, head to the tunnel.
Let's use the tunnel.

926
01:31:09,475 --> 01:31:10,642
(GUNSHOT)

927
01:31:17,066 --> 01:31:19,025
Get out of here, Brian.

928
01:31:24,282 --> 01:31:25,782
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

929
01:31:26,784 --> 01:31:30,287
You sure you know
where the tunnels are?
You sure?

930
01:31:30,830 --> 01:31:32,581
Yeah. I'd hold on.

931
01:31:35,668 --> 01:31:37,335
This might hurt.

932
01:31:50,725 --> 01:31:52,893
You're in
my world now, baby!

933
01:32:07,867 --> 01:32:08,867
(YELLS)

934
01:32:13,247 --> 01:32:14,539
(BANGING)

935
01:32:21,506 --> 01:32:24,049
That's it, baby!
End of the road.

936
01:32:24,133 --> 01:32:25,592
Now what?

937
01:32:26,385 --> 01:32:27,469
Game over.

938
01:32:27,553 --> 01:32:29,095
No, no, no.

939
01:32:31,599 --> 01:32:32,599
(YELLS)

940
01:32:43,361 --> 01:32:44,653
(GUNFIRE)

941
01:32:50,660 --> 01:32:51,993
(MAN SCREAMS)

942
01:32:58,709 --> 01:33:00,126
Come on !

943
01:33:03,506 --> 01:33:04,506
(LAUGHING)

944
01:33:06,300 --> 01:33:07,300
(GROANS)

945
01:33:07,385 --> 01:33:08,635
(BRAKES SCREECHING)

946
01:33:18,646 --> 01:33:19,854
(PILLAR CRACKING)

947
01:33:23,985 --> 01:33:24,985
(YELLS)

948
01:33:30,950 --> 01:33:31,950
(BANGING)

949
01:34:14,452 --> 01:34:15,452
(GRUNTS)

950
01:34:19,332 --> 01:34:20,415
CAMPOS: Hey!

951
01:34:21,542 --> 01:34:23,376
Get me out of here!

952
01:34:46,400 --> 01:34:47,400
(GROANS)

953
01:35:07,129 --> 01:35:08,505
(GRUNTING)

954
01:35:11,008 --> 01:35:12,008
(SIGHS)

955
01:35:12,093 --> 01:35:13,635
(SPEAKING SPANISH)

956
01:35:13,719 --> 01:35:15,011
(GRUNTS)

957
01:35:19,892 --> 01:35:21,101
(COCKS GUN)

958
01:35:22,103 --> 01:35:23,353
(GRUNTS)

959
01:35:53,509 --> 01:35:54,926
Pussy.

960
01:36:04,937 --> 01:36:06,354
(GROANING)

961
01:36:12,319 --> 01:36:13,945
Let me see that.

962
01:36:16,490 --> 01:36:18,867
Yeah.
Just keep pressure there.

963
01:36:19,535 --> 01:36:21,536
(POLICE SIRENS WAILING)
You'll be all right.

964
01:36:21,620 --> 01:36:23,496
(HELICOPTERS WHIRRING)

965
01:36:27,418 --> 01:36:29,502
You gotta get
out of here.

966
01:36:32,131 --> 01:36:34,132
I ain't running anymore.

967
01:36:39,764 --> 01:36:41,848
I gotta ask you
something.

968
01:36:42,516 --> 01:36:43,641
Yeah?

969
01:36:44,393 --> 01:36:48,438
You know I would have
won that race
if you didn't cheat, right?

970
01:36:51,525 --> 01:36:53,443
You hit your head hard.

971
01:36:53,527 --> 01:36:54,736
(LAUGHS)

972
01:36:58,324 --> 01:37:00,200
Don't make me laugh.

973
01:37:09,293 --> 01:37:10,543
(GAVEL BANGING)

974
01:37:10,878 --> 01:37:12,253
All rise.

975
01:37:17,551 --> 01:37:19,260
Please be seated.

976
01:37:23,516 --> 01:37:25,558
Please rise,
Mr. Toretto.

977
01:37:27,937 --> 01:37:30,230
I've listened
to the testimony

978
01:37:30,731 --> 01:37:32,857
and taken into
special consideration

979
01:37:32,942 --> 01:37:36,945
Agent O'Conner's
appeal of clemency on
behalf of Mr. Toretto.

980
01:37:37,905 --> 01:37:40,573
That his actions
directly resulted
in the apprehension

981
01:37:40,658 --> 01:37:43,493
of known drug
trafficker Arturo Braga.

982
01:37:45,037 --> 01:37:46,412
However,

983
01:37:47,706 --> 01:37:49,666
this judiciary
finds that

984
01:37:49,750 --> 01:37:54,587
one right does not
make up for a lifetime
worth of wrongs.

985
01:37:55,256 --> 01:37:57,006
And as such,

986
01:37:57,091 --> 01:38:02,095
I find that I am forced
to level the maximum
sentence under California law.

987
01:38:04,515 --> 01:38:06,182
Dominic Toretto,

988
01:38:07,017 --> 01:38:11,020
you are hereby
sentenced to serve
25 years to life

989
01:38:11,105 --> 01:38:14,190
at the Lompoc
maximum security
prison system

990
01:38:14,942 --> 01:38:17,735
without the possibiIity
of earIy paroIe.

991
01:38:18,320 --> 01:38:20,154
This court is adjourned.

992
01:38:20,239 --> 01:38:21,573
(GAVEL BANGS)

993
01:38:44,972 --> 01:38:46,806
(CAR ENGINES REVVING)

994
01:39:00,321 --> 01:39:02,322
(BOTH ARGUING IN SPANISH)

