Nice ride.
It does the job.
What job, delivering pizzas?
Well, it's not the ride,
it's the rider.
What the hell was that?
What?
Hey! You talking to my girl?
Oh, shit. Here we go. Yeah.
She was just admiring my ride.
"My ride."
My grandma's Buick could smoke ...
that piece of shit, trailer trash.
Well, what about your daddy's Viper?
This beast's got 500 horsepower ...
and a Borla exhaust system.
It does 0 to 60
in like 4.3 seconds ...
That's about right.
That's about right. Yeah.
Wow. You can read the brochure.
What a pitch, baby.
What a pitch. I like that.
What's he gonna do?
- Let's make it happen.
- Bring it.
I got your ...
I got your back.
Why don't you nice boys
let your cars do the talking?
I only race for pink slips.
This car goes for 80 grand.
What would I do with a broken-ass
piece of shit like that?
How about me?
Winner gets me.
Cut it, let's cut it.
Let's go, go, go, go!
Blast-off, baby!
First one out the other side ...
It's time. Let's go!
Ready, boys?
Make it interesting, Clay.
Shit!
Yeah!
I thought you loved me.
Oh, well.
What the hell?
Guess I got a new date for prom.
Clay, stop the car! Shut up!
Clay, stop the car!
Shut up!
Stop it!
Clay, please stop! Please stop!
Can I get a copy of that?
You think this is a joke, huh?
You see Ken and Barbie over there?
They're gonna walk out of here
without even a slap on the wrist.
Mommy and Daddy are too hooked up.
But I like screw-ups like you.
You know why?
'Cause you're 100%
guaranteed conviction.
- Where's my car?
- I crushed it.
You did what?
- Sit down! You're done.
- Easy, easy.
You're done.
You understand me? You're done.
And all before your eighteenth
birthday. Now sit down.
Sean.
What the hell were
you thinkin', huh?
Mrs. Boswell? Please.
It's, uh, it's Miss.
Officer, is it, um,
illegal to smoke in here?
It's a tough state.
And it's a pretty clear-cut case.
He'll be lucky if they don't
try him as an adult.
This is our third town
in two years.
Your son's got two priors
for reckless driving,
wilful destruction of property.
This makes it strike three.
They're definitely gonna want
to get him off the streets.
Well, there's
just got to be another way.
So, where are we moving this time?
We are not moving anywhere.
Sean.
I thought you were
gonna be here on the 7th.
Today is the 7th.
Well, look,
just hold on one second.
Come on in.
This is it.
You know, Sean, I was,
I was gonna be there.
But your mom,
she said the 7th, see,
and we're a day
ahead of you in Japan.
Well, you're here now,
and that's good.
So, how is your mom?
Where do I sleep?
Now, Sean, you know
she had no other choice.
I mean, it was
either this or juvie hall,
I mean, you just
can't keep moving away ...
every time you get into trouble.
Worked for you.
Look, neither of us asked for this.
But I promised your mom
I'd take care of you.
So you just go by the
rules her and I agreed to,
and I'm sure
you'll manage just fine.
Rules?
Yeah, rules. Real simple.
You go to school,
you come back here right after.
And I don't want to see or hear
about you anywhere near a car.
Here, the bedroom is yours.
Make yourself comfortable.
Lights out in 10.
You got to be kiddin'.
Wrong train.
I'm new here.
Boswell, yes, ma'am.
Japanese food is like the Army.
Don't ask, don't tell.
Name's Twinkie.
Hey, I noticed
you ain't have a laptop.
Yeah?
I'll hook you up. Half price.
No, I'm cool.
60% off. Hmm?
Since we're both army
brats and everything.
I ain't got no cash, man.
And I ain't an army brat.
All right, all right.
Well, what about
a cell phone, huh?
Everybody needs a cell phone.
No offense,
but I'm probably
not gonna be here ...
long enough to remember your name.
Then you gonna need some new
shoes to book town with, man.
You like Michael Jordan?
I love Michael Jordan.
Check this out.
Brand new Jordans.
Not even out yet.
LeBron James couldn't even
get his hands on those.
You selling that
Sparco steering wheel?
Hell, no.
That's mine right there.
Man, I even paid
retail for it.
What you drive?
- My ride?
- Yeah.
My ride's one of a kind.
Show me.
Thought you
weren't stickin' around.
All right.
Slamming, huh? Look at that car.
At least let me drive.
Y'all better have some
real cars around here.
Okay, I see
somebody got jokes, huh?
Well, all right.
I don't know if you're
ready for them, though.
You look a little nervous.
What up, Tosh?
For when you
blow your wad, man.
Hear that?
It's still not right
for the way I drive.
I don't need a computer to tell
me about my throttle response.
Okay. Then we're done here.
You wouldn't have
that problem with a V8.
Boys.
All they care about is
who's got the biggest engine.
I'm a guy. It's in my DNA.
So y'all race with these things,
huh?
Cute little toys.
You know, I almost didn't recognize
you without your slippers on.
Don't you mean Uwabaki?
Neela, right?
You're a quick learner.
So, where you from, anyway?
Here.
No, I mean, not where you live.
Where'd you come from?
Does it really matter
where I'm from?
Who's the tourist?
What's with you
and the schoolgirls, D?
You're moving up in the world.
You gotta elevate your company.
Wednesday, Wednesday,
meet Thursday.
God. Girl.
Ladies, hold that thought, all right?
All right, beautiful. Hold up.
Hey!
He was just leaving.
I'm sorry.
I don't speak Japanese.
Understand that? Gaijin?
Takashi.
We were just talking.
This isn't your scene.
That word you called me,
gaijin or something or other,
what does that mean exactly?
Means, turn around,
keep walking.
That's exactly what we gonna do.
Come on, man, let's roll.
Yo, look, man, he's Yakuza.
Now, see, that's funny,
'cause I thought this
was, like, a free country
where a girl could talk
to whoever she wants.
You know who I am, boy?
Yeah. You're like the Justin
Timberlake of Japan, right?
Leave.
Damn, man.
You know Yakuza? The Mafia?
Look, sorry, DK - san.
Monkey didn't have
his banana today.
Hey, D, let's go.
It's time to race.
Hey, good luck, Timberlake.
You're the one that's lucky,
'cause I'm about to race.
Then let's race.
With what, huh? Your skateboard?
Easy to sound cocky
when you got no ride.
Take mine.
Let's race.
What? I wanna see
what the kid's got.
Can he drive?
You know what DK stands for?
Donkey Kong?
Drift King.
Drift?
What do you mean, drift?
Still need a dictionary?
You know that
real famous painting?
The one of the woman
who's smiling all the time?
The Mona Lisa.
Right, right, right.
Mona Lisa.
Well, look, man,
this car right here's ...
like the Mona Lisa
of the drift world.
Han rebuilt this bad boy
from ground up.
We talking forged pistons,
bigger turbo,
new rods, new crankshaft.
Hey, man, Han's labor
ain't cheap, man, you feel me?
Well, if I needed a 30-second
lesson on how to drift ...
All right, look, man, there's lots
of ways you can do this, all right?
Hand braking is the easiest,
so the first thing
I want you to do,
I want you to rip that e-brake.
All right,
after you rip the e-brake,
then I want you to power over.
You know what?
Just don't mess up Mona,
all right?
All right.
Ready.
Set.
Go!
I told you.
Damn it!
Don't leave town.
Do you know what time it is?
I thought it was around 7:00.
You know,
US is a few hours behind.
Looks like the party
was better here, anyway.
Have you been racing, Sean?
You're out of here.
Go ahead.
You don't get it, do you?
You have nowhere else to go.
If it doesn't work out here,
you're going to jail.
Do you get that?
This isn't a game.
And I'm gonna tell you
one more time,
if you're gonna
live under my roof,
you're gonna go by
my rules or get out.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
Get in.
I'll get you your money.
Why you talking
like you have a choice?
There's a guy in there
with a paw ...
that owes me some money.
A paw?
Go get me my money.
Okay.
Han said,
okane.
Han said, okane.
Let's go.
You're in the pickup
and delivery business now.
I might call you once a week
or once an hour.
I don't care
if you're sick as a dog ...
or in bed with Beyoncé.
I call, you show.
Only if you teach me
how to drift.
This ain't a negotiation.
I wasn't negotiating.
What's he doing here?
He's paying me back for
that crumpled beer can ...
sitting in my garage.
Hope he's not driving.
Gaijin.
When is your next race?
I'd really like to be there.
Why not be in it?
You heard me.
Ready to lose another car, Han?
I'm ready to take that
'86 Corolla off your hands.
All right.
Put up the '72 Skyline.
Done.
What do you think,
Morimoto, huh?
Get him out of here.
We have business to discuss.
Your shipment's late.
Since when are you
so worried about the details?
When is
the shipment arriving, Han?
Just sit pretty
and let me handle it.
Hey, Dad, it's me.
Uh, I had to stay after school ...
for some extracurricular activities.
So I'll be home a little later.
Sir.
You really need to stop
following me around.
What are you doing here?
I thought I'd stop by
and ask your boyfriend ...
for some drifting lessons.
Trust me.
You don't wanna be
a part of this world.
It's good enough for you.
You don't know anything about me.
Well, why don't you think I know?
'Cause I'm a gaijin? An outsider?
Let me guess.
You're an army brat
who moved around a lot.
Your mama and daddy
was never home.
So you walked around
pissed off all the time.
And now you found your family
with these drift nuts.
Zero for one, cowboy.
Why can't you go find
a nice Japanese girl
like the rest of
the white guys around here?
Is everything okay back there?
I can handle DK.
I thought he's Yakuza.
His uncle's Yakuza.
He's just playing gangster
in his little storage room.
But I need him.
He keeps Uncle Kamata
from poking around too much.
What do you mean?
Well, his uncle gets
a piece of the action ...
from everyone on his turf.
We're on his turf.
50% of something is better than
100% of nothing.
So have you raced DK?
Why not? Is he that good?
What's the point of a race?
To see if I'm better
than the other guy.
Just proves you're faster,
that's all.
If I were to race,
it would have to be ...
for something important.
Or why else do it at all?
Why are you letting me race?
'Cause you're DK's kryptonite.
And you owe me a car.
Oh, shit.
What the ...
Police cars here are
only factory-tuned.
You can do better than 180k,
they can't catch you,
so they don't even try.
You know what?
I'm beginning to like
this country already.
Danny!
You're looking good.
Disco.
We gotta catch up.
Get you a drink on me, huh?
Let's go.
Aha. Easy now, ladies.
Come on.
What's up? How you doing?
Hey, baby.
Keep your hands off the kid, girls.
He's underage.
Ladies, ladies, ladies.
Disneyland for grownups, huh?
All these girls, man,
they look like ...
What, models?
Check it out.
See,
Tokyo is the fashion capital ...
on this side of the planet,
all right?
Now, imagine
you been posing all day.
I mean,
that's a lot of hard work.
Not only do you get tired,
but, on top of that,
you wanna have a little fun,
but you can't ...
'cause you don't even know
nobody in town.
And most of
the guys around here are ...
too chicken shit
to even try picking up one.
So what do you do?
Man, you talk to the little
dude who makes you laugh.
Yeah.
Look, man, I don't just think
outside the box.
I tear it up.
That's my thing.
Yo.
Sean!
The red Evo's yours.
What do you mean?
You're representing me now.
What you think, I'm gonna
let you roll in a Hyundai?
Oh, man.
Damn it.
My mother,
she's blind in one eye ...
and she can drift
better than that.
Han, where did you find this guy?
Will someone please teach
this guy how to drift?
Is that yours?
Sure is.
What happened?
I don't know. I found
it this way at the base.
It's got potential.
Yeah, maybe. We'll see.
You know, Sean,
the Japanese have a saying.
"The nail that sticks out
gets hammered."
You're gonna be late.
Sean!
Come on, man, you broke it.
Hey, whoa, whoa.
There must be a misunderstanding.
Out of my way, or you're next.
Take it easy.
Look, man, I don't
do refunds, all right?
Okay, let's go, then!
Let's go!
Touch me again ...
Here.
Try not to break this one.
Say, man!
What the hell is
wrong with you, huh?
Now everybody's gonna want
exchanges around here.
Damn!
Not easy saving the day, is it?
Maybe you could give me
some pointers sometime.
You're doing all right.
Thanks.
Hey.
Yeah?
Sorry about the other night.
Your life isn't any of my business.
It's okay.
Foul!
- Ain't no damn foul.
- That was a foul.
- Yo, you in my face.
Hey, Han, sort this wanker out.
A wanker?
What do I look like, a zebra?
So, how did you end up
over here, anyway?
Well, you know
those old Westerns ...
where the cowboys
make a run for the border?
This is my Mexico.
Why'd you let me
race with your car?
You knew I was gonna wreck it.
Why not?
'Cause it's a lot of money.
I have money.
It's trust and character
I need around me.
You know, who you
choose to be around you ...
lets you know who you are.
And one car in exchange
for knowing ...
what a man's made of,
that's a price I can live with.
Look at all those
people down there.
They follow the rules, for what?
They're letting fear lead them.
What happens if they don't?
Life's simple.
You make choices
and you don't look back.
So, if you don't drift to win,
what do you drift for?
You really want to know?
Yeah.
Okay. Let's go.
There's no "wax on,
wax off" with drifting.
Learn by doin' it.
The first drifters
invented drifting ...
out here in the mountains
by feeling it.
So feel it.
Again!
What's in this bag?
You'll see.
How much you got?
Keep going, keep going.
I'm so good, man, I could
sell rubbers to a monk.
Again.
Watch it. Watch it.
Not too early, now.
Go, go, go, go!
Don't lose it! Don't lose it!
Hey, Twink.
Get this man a bunk.
Pleasure doing business.
Yeah, baby. I told you.
I told you, didn't I?
It's actually not bad.
I didn't even have
to put ketchup on it.
See, I'm not a total gaijin.
I hate that word.
It's what they used
to call me when I was a kid.
I thought you were born here.
Well, "outsider" can mean
many different things.
My mom died when I was 10.
She came out here
from Australia ...
when she finished high school.
And all I know
about her is that ...
she went to work in a hostess bar.
DK's grandmother took me in.
Well, my parents
split up when I was three.
Me and Mom moved around a lot.
Mostly 'cause of me.
Well, it was all 'cause of me.
Kind of made myself
an outsider, you know,
without even thinking about it.
But I realize now,
outsider or insider,
it doesn't really matter.
All that matters is knowing
what you really want
and going after it.
We used to come up here
when we were kids.
Even before we could drive
we'd cut class, sneak out,
come up here, and watch
the older kids drift.
Things were different back then.
Once I got my license,
I practically lived up here.
Back then, kids just drove
whatever they had.
You know, we just made do.
No one bothered us.
The day I got my license ...
is the day I got
my first speeding ticket.
The day after that,
I won my first race.
I beat this rich kid
by three lengths.
I gotta admit, it felt good.
It felt like ...
Like everything else
just disappears.
No past and no future.
No problems.
Just the moment.
Boy needs to chill.
Hey, Twink,
I'm gonna grab another set.
Whoa! Whoa,
whoa, whoa! Another set?
No. Look, that was
your third set today.
I mean, them tires ain't cheap.
DK, grab a chair.
We're about to
roast some marshmallows.
Yo, come on, man, look ...
Stay away from her,
or the only thing you'll
be driving is a wheelchair.
Find yourself a new driver.
I'm all right.
What'd you expect?
You didn't just play with fire,
you soaked
the matches in gasoline.
It's over.
All this over a gaijin?
I am a gaijin.
You've changed, DK.
You say I've changed.
But we're not so different,
you and I.
We're both products
of fuckups, aren't we?
They say your mom
was the best trick ...
in all of Kabukicho
back in the day.
Leave my mother out of this.
If we hadn't taken you in,
you'd be just like her,
doing anything for a buck.
Think anyone would take
a second look at you ...
if it wasn't for your uncle?
We're the same, Neela.
Difference is I know who I am
and where I belong.
Do you know who you are?
Do you know where you belong?
Hey.
Come on.
Hey, brother.
I vouched for you!
Put my reputation
on the line for you!
We were partners!
You think you can keep
your side deals from me?
Come on.
We ain't in the Boy Scouts.
This is what we do.
Takashi!
What about now? Hmm?
Is this what we do?
Man, you need me.
You'd still be
shaking down teahouses ...
for chump change
if it wasn't for me.
Get in!
Go! Go! Go!
Come on.
Sean. Sean!
Takashi.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
Okay.
I'll go with you.
Neela.
See you when Daddy's not around.
I'm putting you on a plane tonight.
Dad ...
Sean, don't argue with me.
I did this. I can't run away.
I can't.
Sean, I'm your father.
I'm responsible
for your well-being.
And I'm responsible
for my mess.
I gotta do this.
Can you understand that?
At least you're not
redoing my mistakes.
You all right, man?
We're leaving town.
Look, I know some people ...
I can't do it, Twink.
Look, DK wants your head.
All right?
And the trouble you
just made for Kamata?
You're done here, bro.
Maybe I should talk to Kamata.
What?
DK answers to him.
I know I just didn't hear that.
I gotta end this.
I'm gonna go talk to him.
What, are you crazy, huh?
Han is dead, all right!
Plus, you can't just walk
into Kamata's place, man!
It's all I got.
Something I think Han
would've wanted you to have.
What's this?
You're gonna need it
if you're gonna make it ...
out of Kamata's place alive.
Don't you need it?
No, it's cool.
Look, I'll figure it out.
Sean.
You need to leave.
You came to the wrong place.
I didn't come here to see you.
Takashi.
You think ...
you can walk in here,
dump some cash and walk out?
I know I'm only returning
what belonged to you ...
in the first place, sir.
But that's not why I really came.
I came here to apologize.
I know your nephew and I have
embarrassed ourselves badly.
Sir, I'm here to offer you
a peaceful solution.
How do you plan
to accomplish that?
A race.
DK and I have caused
nothing but problems for you,
for us.
And I'm asking you
to allow us to settle this,
once and for all.
We race ...
and the loser leaves town
for good.
I've already beat
this piece of shit once!
Good.
Then it should be easy.
The cops took all the cars.
Hey!
That's why she's spitting.
We almost there, Twink.
Couple more tweaks.
It's not the car
I'm worried about, man.
DK picked this road
for a reason.
This is his mountain.
He's the only one to ever
make it to the bottom.
Yeah!
Yes!
Come on.
Yeah! Come on!
Come on, Sean.
Let's go! Let's go!
Sean, you the boss. Let's go.
Damn! Come on, man!
That ain't right.
Yeah, baby!
That's what
I'm talking about, man.
I told you!
Hey, yo, Sean! Yo, Sean!
Hey, check this out, man.
This dude over here
wanna race the new DK.
Heard he's been beating
everybody around Asia, too.
Not tonight, Twinkie.
Said he knew Han.
Said Han was family.
All right.
Let's race.
Nice ride.
I won it from my friend Han,
a few years ago.
I didn't know he was
into American muscle.
He was when
he was rolling with me.
You know this ain't
no 10-second race.
I got nothing but time.
You ready, kid?
Come on, Sean! Come on!
Ready!
Set!
Go!