Synced And Corrected By pSYcH0
@Subscene
LONDON, ENGLAND
They say if you want a glimpse of the future...
Just look behind you.
I used to think that was bollocks.
Now I realize...
you can't outrun the past.
When we were kids...
You'd start fights with the toughest bastards in the yard.
But I was the one...
who were to step in and finish them.
Rest now, little brother.
While I settle your one last score.
Take care of my brother.
Anything happens to him...
I'll come back looking for you.
Here.
Hold this.
FAST & FURIOUS 7
Come on, Dom, so where are you taking me?
They say an open road helps you think...
about where you've been...
where you're going.
So you don't remember any of this yet?
It's not fair.
You know I don't.
So what is it exactly that you're trying to show me?
That.
Race Wars.
We used to come here?
"Come here"?
We invented it.
RACE WARS
Keep it under 9000 rpms.
Kid's gonna fire his pistons after the first 200.
You know that's not my style, I got to ride or die, right?
How about you just ride on this one.
Are you ready?
I know you're ready!
Go!
Nice job!
Hey!
That's the girl I heard so much about.
Where you been at, ghost girl?
That's the girl...
Ghost girl...
Letty, what the hell?
Damn, Dom! Your girl's still got that swing, homie.
You never could take a punch.
Right, right.
Hey, man, I'm glad you're back, man. It's good to see you.
Good to see you, Hektor.
Alright. We made it, Jack.
- Yeah, we made it! - Yeah, we made it.
I just gotta, find that door button.
Buddy where's the door button at? Do you know?
- Hey. - Hey.
Yeah, of course.
I'm new to this.
Yeah, you don't seem like the minivan type.
No, not exactly.
Hey buddy you didn't give me a high-five? Wait, wait, wait.
High-five! All right! Yeah, buddy.
Appreciate it, thank you.
Don't worry, you'll get used to this in no time.
Yeah, that's what I'm afraid of.
First time I saw this...
I thought it was kind of funny.
I guess now, the joke's on me.
What are you doing?
What I should've done a long time ago.
Stop!
Look at it.
It's the truth.
That's the date that I lost my memory.
That's the date that Letty died.
And I was born.
No.
You never died.
Do you know how hard it is for me when you look at me?
And you see me through 15 years of memories?
Every beautiful moment we've ever had.
I see it in your eyes.
I can't give that to you.
I got nothing.
You got me.
And you've got only a piece of me.
I have to find myself.
For me.
Goodbye, Dom.
DIPLOMATIC SECURITY SERVICE LOS ANGELES DIVISION
You're disappointed, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
The last arrest.
It was too easy. Target didn't even run.
Ah, it's okay.
Gives me a chance to hit the iron.
Also, lets me work on my stamping skills.
You're a terrible liar.
See you tomorrow, boss.
- I'll see you then. - Don't stay too late.
I'll stay as long as I want, woman.
I knew you'd say that.
Elena?
What's this?
It's the letter of recommendation you asked for.
Just know I meant every word in there.
Thanks, Hobbs.
Thanks for everything.
Come on, way too sentimental right now.
Get home. Good night.
Okay. Bye.
Just one sec.
You sure as hell ain't the IT guy so you better start talking...
before I break that finger six different ways...
and stick it straight right where the sun doesn't shine.
Agent Hobbs, right?
That's right.
I'm also the last man on Earth whose computer you wanna be hacking into.
You just earned yourself a dance with the devil, boy.
You're under arrest.
Like I said, I'm here for the team that crippled my brother.
There ain't no goddamn team.
It was just one man, and he's standing right in front of you.
The lady was right.
You are a terrible liar.
Goddamn IT guys.
Hobbs!
On me!
Elena!
Hobbs?
Hobbs!
Alright buddy, we gotta go or we'll be late.
Come on.
Okay, uhh.
What do you think?
Parking brake slide right up to the school?
Where's mommy?
I don't know. She's up there. She's coming.
Oh.
Watch your head.
Dom, you have a package out here.
From Tokyo.
Tokyo?
What's Han trying, to convert me over to a turbo charger?
You ready?
There we go.
Hey buddy, cars don't fly.
Hey, cars don't fly.
This one did, huh?
Brian in a minivan.
Things have changed.
He's struggling, Dom.
He doesn't want me to see it...
but the white picket fence is like an anchor for him. I can tell.
I tried to talk to him the other night. Do you know what he said?
He doesn't miss the girls. He doesn't miss the cars.
He misses the bullets.
Let him settle in. Give him time.
How does nine months sound?
I'm having another baby.
And you didn't tell him, did you?
You gotta tell him.
I don't want him to be disappointed with this life.
With me.
He will never be disappointed with you.
You're the best thing that's ever happened to him.
Thank you.
Yeah?
Dominic Toretto.
You don't know me.
You're about to.
Private number Tokyo, Japan
Get down!
Jack!
Shattered his collarbone, fractured his leg in two places.
He only regained consciousness this morning.
First thing he said was, "Get me Dom".
He's in there.
You okay?
I'm fine.
He's waiting. Let's go.
Got something for you.
Your files.
Thank you.
You risk life and limb to save the free world...
and what do they give you?
Jell-O and a bad 70's TV show.
Y'know, it's got its perks.
Sponge baths ain't that bad.
Dad!
I'm sorry, baby.
"Dad"?
Honey, I want to introduce you to somebody.
He's a, uhh...
He's an old friend.
Go on and say hello.
Dominic Toretto, right?
My dad said, he kicked your ass once.
Who did this?
You remember Owen Shaw?
The one we tore half of London down trying to get.
Well...
This is his big, bad brother.
Take a look at this.
"Deckard Shaw"
British Special Forces assassin.
The kind of unique asset...
that no government would ever admit to employing.
Black Ops boys.
Worse. They created a monster.
They felt Shaw was a necessary evil until eventually...
they decided he was unnecessary.
The powers that be, felt that he knew just a little bit too much.
The asset became a liability.
So they sent in 20 elite operatives to retire him.
And they missed.
That was 6 years ago and Shaw's been a ghost ever since.
Until now.
How do I find him?
The official answer is: you don't.
He killed Han.
Almost killed my family.
He also tried to put me in a body bag, too.
Which is why when I get out, I'm gonna put a hurt on him so bad...
he's gonna wish his mother had kept her legs closed.
But until then, my official answer to you...
is stand down.
Now you know I can't do that.
I do know you, Dom.
Which is why now I give you a brother to brother answer.
You do whatever it is you gotta do.
When you find that sumbitch...
Just do me one favor.
What's that?
Don't miss.
MONTECRISTO, DOMINICAN REPUBLIC
Thank you so much for letting us stay, Mando.
I hope it's not a problem.
Listen, Dom needed a safe delivered to Rio in two days.
That was a problem.
Hosting his family in the Dominican Republic,
that is vacation.
Anyone messes with you here...
they're messing with the entire country.
You'll be safe.
Yeah, they're here. I picked them up myself at the airport.
Hold on. Your brother.
Dom.
Yeah, Mia, it's me.
How's it going there?
We're at Mando's. This place is like a fortress.
You should see Brian. He's in full FBI mode.
He built a surveillance hub in Mando's garage and everything.
What about you? Did you find out who's after us?
Looks like the sins of London have followed us home.
How did Buster take the news?
I can't tell him.
If he knew about the baby, he'd stay here with us.
And with all that's going on, you're gonna need him by your side.
Just watch out for him. Keep him safe.
And come home together.
Tell Brian I'll see him in LA in two days.
Where are you going?
Tokyo.
I'm bringing Han home.
Authorities are still trying to determine...
the motive behind this daring attack here at the office...
of the US Diplomatic Security Service in downtown Los 羘geles...
less than 36 hours ago.
Facts are still coming in...
but what is known is the suspect entered the building's 4th floor...
Hey.
- You okay? - Yeah.
This guy's just, relentless.
That's why Dom needs you.
You two need to find this guy and you need to stop him...
before he does any more damage to our family.
I just...
I've screwed up so many things.
I couldn't live with myself if I screwed this up, too.
You won't.
I believe in you.
I believe in us. That's all that matters.
I love you, Brian.
Love you, baby.
Just promise me. After this, we're done.
No more jobs, no more enemies.
Come back to us.
I won't let you down, Mia.
I know.
TOKYO, JAPAN
Hey yo, Sean!
Hey, check this out, man.
This dude over here wanna race the new DK.
Not tonight, Twinkie.
He said he knew Han.
Han said you was fast, but not that damn fast.
Who said American muscle can't drift?
Han mentioned he left his enemies in his rear view.
He never talked about it much.
Always playing it close to the vest.
We found a couple of things by the crash.
Wasn't much left.
Gisele.
Yeah.
There's one more thing.
I found this.
Must've meant something to him.
When you find the guy that killed Han...
What are you going to do?
Words ain't even been invented yet.
They say to live in the hearts of those we leave behind...
is not to die.
But he put you in his grave.
So now I'll do the same to him.
I can't do no more funerals.
First, Han...
Now Hobbs is laid out, of all people.
We're being hunted.
You know he's out there somewhere watching, right?
I hope so.
That means he's close.
Just promise me, Brian.
No more funerals.
Just one more.
His.
You never should've messed with a man's family.
I told your brother the same thing.
Reinforced your chassis.
Just like going into the ring with weighted gloves.
Your mistake. I'm not here to play games.
See, you and me...
We're from different worlds.
Trust me, I've seen a lot meaner streets than the ones you're used to.
Stick around.
It's gonna get a lot meaner.
You think this was gonna be a street fight?
On the ground!
Now!
Drop him or I will drop you!
Woah, woah!
Easy, guys. We're on the same team here.
Mr. Toretto...
I'm here on the recommendation...
of a, mutual friend of ours.
- Mr. Hobbs? - Who the hell are you?
Me? I'm just a guy.
I'm, Mr. Nobody.
That's a big entrance for a nobody.
And the guy who put our mutual friend in the hospital...
you just let him get away.
I think I might've just saved your ass there, Dom.
Listen, you think you can let go of my guy there?
He's beginning to turn a little blue.
I appreciate that.
Here they come.
Listen, Dom.
There's a war going on between shadows and ghosts like me.
You and your team unwittingly walked into the middle of it in London...
and it appears it's now followed you home.
It's up to you.
I'm gonna have a beer.
You're welcome to join me.
By the way, I can get you Deckard Shaw.
BASE OF OPERATIONS EL SEGUNDO, CALIFORNIA
Belgian ale.
Man, those monks got it right.
I don't know about the whole celibacy thing, but when it comes to beer...
Would you like one?
I'm more of a Corona man myself.
Your files, not only detailed...
It's, extremely entertaining.
Look, Shaw's power is that he's a shadow.
He's really good at getting in and out of places...
without being seen and leaving nothing but a body count in his wake.
He's a legitimate English badass.
But to be honest with you Dom, I don't give two shits about Deckard Shaw.
It's you I want.
Because you and I can help each other get what we both need.
I'm listening.
Just recently, a private military company...
led by a wanted terrorist named Mose Jakande...
kidnapped a hacker known only by the name "Ramsey".
Lady Liberty's got her panties in a bunch over this but rightfully so...
because this Ramsey has created something interesting.
- Bring it up. - Yes, sir.
Say hello...
To God's Eye.
Now this little bastard hacks into anything that's on a digital network.
That means every cellphone, satellite, ATM machine, and computer,
simultaneously.
If it's got a microphone or a lens, God's Eye can use it to find you.
So you invited me here to show me a tracking device.
On steroids. Lots of them.
Let me put it to you this way.
It took us nearly a decade to find Osama bin Laden.
With this, we could locate him anywhere on the planet
in a couple of hours.
Now that's a serious piece of machinery...
that could be catastrophic in the wrong hands.
But for some very nauseating, political reasons...
any rescue plans involving any US government forces or entity...
has been strictly ruled out.
And that's why I need you.
But why do I need you?
I mean I could go back outside, enjoy the rest of the Coronas...
let Shaw come to me.
You could do that. How's that working out for you so far?
You got one friend in the ground, another one in the hospital...
and then of course there's that little issue of the bomb...
that destroyed your home.
Shaw lives in a world that doesn't play by your rules.
Like it or not...
you live in that world now, too.
You wanna know how to kill a shadow?
You just shine a little light on it.
If you get the God's Eye for me...
I've already got authorization for you to use it until you get Shaw.
You go from the hunted, to the hunter.
And there's no place on Earth Shaw can hide from you.
More importantly,
you and your family...
don't go to any more funerals.
You get Ramsey, you get the God's Eye...
You get Shaw.
Well that's the windup and the pitch.
Now that I've given you this incredibly sensitive and highly classified information...
What do you think, Toretto?
I think you already know what I'm gonna do.
Good.
But, it'll be my way.
And my crew.
I assumed you might say that.
Which is why I've taken the liberty of gathering your team.
This is crazy.
What the hell is going on in here?
Our intelligence suggests that Ramsey will be transported...
by an armed motorcade through the Caucasus mountain range.
If they clear this range and reach their destination...
Ramsey's as good as gone.
So let me get this straight.
There's only one road that leads in or out...?
Sheer drops on every side...
A motorcade from hell protected by a small army...
from one mile on either direction?
Yeah, that's about it.
- You done? - No, I'm not done.
So you all wanted me to break into a police station, fine.
Then you asked me to stop a tank.
I wasn't happy about it, but I did it.
Then you came up with this brillant idea...
to shoot down one of the largest airplanes, ever.
I shot that shit outta the sky...
It's nothing.
But this right here, my friend...
happens to be the stupidest idea I've ever heard of in my life.
I forgot that, you were the only one to bring that plane down.
No, only thing I've ever seen him take down was "No knees" Denise.
Remember? At prom?
Really, Brian? You're gonna do that right here?
See, y'all try'na get me off my point.
All I'm saying is, I'm tired of everybody around me...
making all the decisions.
This time, I lead.
Seriously. If I don't start making decisions, I'm out.
All right, Roman.
What do you got?
I mean, I wouldn't try to get into the whole leadership thing, like, now.
You know what I'm saying? I'm just kind of...
Talking about like, at some point.
Like, you know, when we...
Whatever. I mean, I think...
Let's hit it from here.
- I don't think that that's... - No, don't think.
That's my job.
Okay.
It is impossible to hit it there.
That is literally the most secure spot on the mountain.
Why? Because you cannot physically access it.
Now see, that's what makes it so sweet.
Because it's the place that they least expect us to hit them from.
As much as I hate to admit it, he's on to something there.
What do you think, Dom?
Here?
Yeah.
I think we got a plan.
Completely wrong thinking.
And I like it.
- You see? - I'm good at this.
Good?
Okay.
How are you planning on getting on that road?
Well, Tej?
I think I may actually have a plan for that.
What? I delegated.
That's what good leaders do.
Leader!
You know, when I was reading your files...
I was impressed with what you've accomplished with your team.
But, meeting them now I gotta say, Dom...
you truly have a gift.
Consider my workshop your new playhouse.
I think you'll find our cars...
extremely appealing.
And your team...
is now complete.
I went to the house.
I was looking for you everywhere.
You scared the shit outta me.
You will never be alone...
Where did you find that?
Found it in Han's car.
It was left as a message.
A message I plan on returning.
Can you ride?
Yeah, of course I can.
Han was my family, too.
Brian!
We're gonna need long travel suspension...
limited slip differentials in all of them.
How you doing.
Tej!
I want the demon lovechild between that...
and that.
That's a lot of armor.
Just gonna add more weight, slow you down.
This time it ain't just about being fast.
Yeah, I'm good.
From the streets, you know what I'm sayin'?
It's nothing.
Hey, Roman, you're freaking out, ain't you?
- No. - Yeah, you are.
I said, no.
Listen man, it takes a grown man to embrace his feelings.
If you need to cry, just go ahead and cry.
As your friend, you know I'm concerned about your well-being.
Which is why I took the precaution...
of putting some adult diapers in your glove compartment.
Can you just chill out, man?
I have seen some crazy shit, Dom, but this really could make some waves.
So let's just try to keep it as low key as possible, huh?
Don't I always?
I tell you what: you knock it down a couple of notches this time...
and I'll swap out my Belgian for a keg of Corona.
You'd be doing yourself a favor there.
Can somebody just walk me through what we're supposed to be doing here?
Come on, Rom. This was your plan, you gotta embrace it.
No, this was not my plan.
Yeah, here we go. Gametime.
Roman, you need some fresh air?
'Cause you about to get a whole lot of it.
Okay, here we go!
Just when you didn't think it can get any better, huh?
Oh, shit!
Now we're moving.
Everybody good? Everybody make it out?
You should tell 'em, that this is not for you!
This is not your mission!
Rom, what's up man! Talk to me, come on!
- I can't do it. - The hell, you can't!
Come on man! You throw that thing in reverse and get your ass out here now!
Look I can't do it, okay? Listen to what I'm saying.
Now isn't the time!
I'mma stay up here with the pilot.
We're gonna circle around and make sure we're holding them down from up here!
We're running out of time!
The chute is guided by GPS!
You don't have to do anything!
- Tej! - I'm already on it.
Listen, man. Listen
I'm sorry to let y'all down, okay? I'mma go ahead and stay up here.
No, brother.
- I'm sorry to let you down. - What?
Is that...?
Tej! What are you doing?
No!
Tej!
I hate you, Tej!
Get ready!
Ground's coming fast!
C'mon, baby.
Come on.
Touchdown, baby!
Car check. Call it in.
- Check. - Check.
I'm good, let's do this.
Hello? Please man!
Get me outta here, somebody!
No! The trees!
Shit.
Sit tight, Roman. We'll come back for you.
This is not the plan!
CAUCASUS MOUNTAINS, AZERBAIJAN
All right.
You got one chance to hit them here, Dom.
You miss, they'll make it to their black site...
they'll squeeze whatever information they need out of Ramsey.
The device and your chance of ever getting Shaw will be gone for good.
That ain't gonna happen.
I'll see you at the pickup.
Ramsey, will be in the bus.
Then let's do this.
Captain we have company. Four cars inbound.
What, no!
- Tej, shoot it! - I'm on the way!
All right, formation!
Bulletproof, baby.
Punch it!
Strike!
Guns, free.
Yes, sir.
No!
Shit!
Get out of the way!
Those aren't guns, those are goddamn cannons!
Armor piercing rounds!
Hook 'em up.
Brian, Tej, blow it!
Lock it up.
Brian, you're up!
Little closer, Tej!
Ramsey?
Stay away from me! Stay back!
Don't you touch me!
My name's Brian, and I'm gonna get you out of here...
but I'm gonna need you to settle down, all right?
I'm gonna cut those things off of you.
Sir?
Sir, we have an unidentified vehicle approaching.
Come on! Closer!
You have to jump!
We're out of time. Come on.
We gotta get out of here!
Come on!
Look at me!
If you don't jump, we're gonna die! Okay?
You're jumping. Come on!
One.
Two!
Well, well, well.
Take my hand!
Welcome to the party, Mr. Shaw.
Letty, stay with Brian.
Oh shit!
What are you doing? This is crazy!
Keeping you alive!
There's a cliff.
Cliff! cliff!
No!
Too slow!
Yeah!
I'm back, bitches!
You good?
Thank you.
Roman! Get back to the others.
What about you?
Don't worry about me.
I have to say, I am impressed.
I would very much like to know the name...
of the man who is causing me so much trouble.
There is no way out of there.
What is he doing?
He's frozen like a damn deer on headlights.
Toretto ain't no deer.
Come on, Dominic.
Give us the girl, and I'll let you live.
What are you going to do?
You might wanna put on your helmet for this one.
Target the driver!
Dammit! What is he thinking?
You're insane!
You're pointing the wrong way!
Am I now?
Fire on my mark.
Interesting.
Three!
Two!
Hold on.
One!
Fire!
Looks like our demon lovechild worked.
That's one way down a mountain.
Where's Ramsey?
Hello Kitty's awake.
She don't look like a hacker to me.
Oh yeah? And what do hackers look like?
They don't suppose to look...
like that.
I'm just saying, like, how they normally wear them li'l weird glasses...
that's all crooked, with pimples all over they face from drinking soda.
I mean trust me, with a body like that...
I ain't gonna park it behind a computer.
How you feeling?
Did you hit your head?
Feeling nauseous? Ears ringing?
No?
Where's my shoe?
It flew off when you crashed.
When you start experiencing any of those things, let me know. Okay?
I don't know whether to thank you for rescuing me...
or to kick your ass for throwing me off a cliff.
Thank us or kick our ass, huh?
How about you tell us where that device is?
I mailed it to a friend.
In Abu Dhabi.
That was pretty easy.
That other team would've tortured you for that information.
I didn't trust them.
I trust you.
Now why would you trust us? You barely know us.
I know enough.
Ex-cop. Military, something like that.
The way you took out those guys, serious training.
Tech guy. Offended by the hacker remark, naturally.
Alpha.
Mrs. Alpha.
Joker.
Wrong.
Double Alpha.
Man-candy. Y'know what I'm saying?
Man, sit your candy-ass down.
The disrespect is real around here.
Life is binary. Zeroes and ones.
Only two things keep a group like this together.
Fear or loyalty.
And I don't see a drop of fear among you guys.
Very impressive. Just one thing.
They're not married.
She's so off as crack, you're just gonna roll with it?
You're telling me there can't be a double alpha in one group?
You work for the US government?
We got similar interests.
Tej, call it in.
We're going to the Middle East!
Hey, Dom, it was pretty wild in that mountain, huh?
That was too close.
But we got the job done.
Know what the crazy thing is? It's...
You missed the bullets.
That's messed up, huh?
Brian, I've seen you jump from trains, dive from planes.
Hell, I saw your courage the day I met you.
Right.
You wanna know the bravest thing I've ever saw you do?
Be a good man to M韆.
Being a great father to my nephew, Jack.
Everyone's looking for their thrill...
but what's real,
is family.
Your family.
Hold on to that, Brian.
UNITED ARAB EMIRATES
This was hotter than I thought it would be.
Yeah, well, we are in the desert so, it would be hot.
No, I ain't talking about the weather.
My, my, my.
Now that, is a woman that's worth falling out a plane for.
Get outta there, man. I got dibs on that. You see me looking at that.
Did you just say "dibs"?
What are you, in the fourth grade?
Man, can you just get outta there?
It's a free market.
What are you talking about?
- Get outta that. - Free.
Rock, paper, scissors for it.
Are you guys for real right now?
Look at you.
You both look whooped already. You got stalker eyes.
I tried to call dibs on Ramsey. Two years ago.
Her knee, my balls.
Trust me, you don't wanna do that.
Hey! Ramsey!
Hello, Zafar.
So you made some new friends.
Yeah, some short- tempered new friends.
I need the speed drive I sent you. Where is it?
Oh good, you will be pleased to know. I sold it.
You sold it?
You hear that?
I asked you to take care of it.
Why on Earth would you sell it?
We're gonna need it back.
Impossible.
Zafar, I stashed something inside it. It's important.
Okay.
Good news: It is safe.
And the bad news?
It is very safe.
Sold it to a Jordanian prince living up there.
Trust fund billionaire.
Said he wanted it in his supercar.
Now see, this...
This I like. Billionaire, supercar.
What makes it so, "s鷓er"?
242 mile per hour, top speed.
And, it's bulletproof.
Am I the only one around right now?
It's like, y'know what I'm sayin?
.....
Whatever.
Where does he keep it?
In his penthouse.
Tower number one.
Now why in the hell would he keep his car in his penthouse?
He's a billionaire, my friend.
He can do whatever he wants.
Now, tomorrow happens to be the longest day of the year.
Prince wants to celebrate it, host a party, tomorrow afternoon.
So you can get us up there, right?
Sure.
But not dressed like that.
What?
Something wrong?
There's a billion things wrong.
But not in this moment.
You look handsome.
I feel awkward.
You and me both.
Seeing you dressed like this...
Just reminds me of something.
Of what?
Old times.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine .
Showtime.
No, listen, man.
They're telling me they party like this everyday,
on this level, they party everyday.
This is crazy. I might have to move out here.
I think I'mma start a new culture. It's called "Blarab".
You know, like Black Arab?
How are we looking, Tej?
We're almost in position.
Okay, so this is how we work this.
We gotta move in sync if we're gonna pull this off so let's...
go over it to make sure everyone clearly understands their role.
Roman, that means you.
You know what? You're being real unprofessional right now, Tej.
The God's Eye chip is hidden in a speed drive installed in the prince's car...
which he keeps in a safe room vault.
Now I make 8 to 10 playing closed security.
Not to mention the prince...
and his personal bodyguards.
Security cameras are clustered by the north wall
that's where the vault is.
Now to get in that vault, we gotta tap into the security system...
which can be accessed in the prince's bedroom.
Alright, guys. I'm going in.
Excuse me.
I was just looking for...
- The party is that way. - What?
This room is off...
Now once we're tapped in
Ramsey and I can hack into the network and pop the door
so you can get in and get that chip.
Wait, wait. You missed a step.
What about my steps? What am I supposed to be doing?
No, we didn't miss anything.
You're special team, so when we need you...
do what you do best.
And that is?
Shine brightly, like only Roman Pearce can do.
Now we're talking.
Alright, Tej. I'm in.
Find a phone jack. The tap always runs behind that.
It's gonna be a 350 mega Hertz CAT5 D cable.
They probably got a couple dozen back there.
But this'll be the bonded pair with a plenum coat.
English, Tej.
It'll be the orange wire.
Alright, ladies and gentlemen, we are in the pilot's seat.
Alright, Roman.
Do whatever it is you do.
It's your birthday, right?
Are you Jasmine?
God, no. Not the birthday routine.
Happy birthday to you. This way.
Excuse me, so sorry. I'm coming through, sorry.
Right this way.
Listen, excuse me one second.
Man, you ain't...
Sir, thank you so much.
Listen, people. Please everybody, gather around.
Understand something right now.
Listen to what I'm telling y'all.
We are here to celebrate Jasmine's 18th birthday.
Happy birthday, my dear.
Happy birthday to you.
To you.
I wish I didn't see that.
Ramsey, open it up for us.
Copy that.
You're in.
You realize what this is?
Lykan HyperSport.
$3.4 million. 0 to 60 in less than 30 seconds.
There's 7 of these things in the world and this guy keeps it locked up in a vault.
Nothing's sadder than locking a beast in a cage.
Right now I really wanna punch him in the face.
Okay.
Let's get to work.
You got this, right?
Go.
All right.
Would you believe I knocked him out with my charm?
You ain't that charming, bitch.
Intruders.
Lock it down.
No!
Tej, our magic trick is failing. We're losing systems.
I know.
I see it.
Tej, talk to me.
I'm trying but their security system is locking us out.
Listen, ladies and gentlemen...
Oh, there he is. These your dancers?
This is a party, baby!
Some of ya'll probably went to the bathroom
and noticed that all the hairspray was missing.
Yep. She did it.
Thank you.
And we're so happy for you to be here.
You look like you got some missiles underneath that dress.
He did not just...
Did you just say that?
Shit! Not the gate!
Brian, faster!
We're playing all the defense we can up here.
But we're gonna lose, you gotta hurry up.
Thank god, you showed up.
These parties bore me to death.
Guys get out of there right now.
You've got an army headed your way.
Brian, get up! Forget it!
Tej, we're taking the car.
This is what I do. Y'know what I'm sayin'?
Letty, Letty, talk to me.
Are you okay?
Guys I can't hold it. I'm losing the final gate.
You gotta get out of there.
Tear off the dash!
Go through it.
Wait, just hold on man.
Time to unleash the beast.
Go!
Stay with me, I got you.
Let's get the hell outta here.
Dom. Cars don't fly!
Cars don't fly!
Shit!
No brakes!
What?
- No brakes! - Shit!
No!
- Got it! - Get out!
TORRES ETHIHAD Abu Dhabi
Still miss the bullets, Brian?
There they are, disaster.
I'm sorry.
I get you an invite to the most exclusive party in Abu Dhabi.
Zafar.
No, no, you steal the host's car.
And you jump it between two buildings.
Actually, it was three buildings.
Oh! Two, insult. Three, honor. My bad
Wow, wow, wow.
I have to say...
You've got an interesting interpretation there of low key, Mr. Toretto.
I thought we had an understanding.
Sometimes you have to play the hand you're dealt.
That's why I prefer to be the dealer.
Good night.
Kicked out of my own garage.
This is great.
May I?
Brian.
Give it to him.
All that trouble for this little.... thing.
With all due respect, Dom...
You really did great work back there. All of you.
All of my men are now standing by...
and are fully at your disposal.
Your call.
Ramsey.
Fire it up, and find me Shaw.
Damn, this is crazy.
Thank you.
Give me a second.
What is it doing now?
It's hunting.
Hacking into the security cameras at Ethihad Towers.
That's the last place we saw Shaw so that's where we start.
That's him, right there.
Wait. What are these numbers out here for?
It's biomapping Shaw's face.
It will run that against every camera...
Every audio device in this hemisphere.
Bingo. Looks like he's holed up here.
That's perfect.
Automated factory, no people. Lots of places to hide.
You just changed the face of manhunts forever.
Congratulations.
Can I check my e-mail real quick?
Dawn's up in two hours.
We're gonna go take down Shaw then.
Go get changed.
We should go now.
Just you, your team and me.
I thought you said at dawn?
My guys are racers.
Best drivers in the world.
But they ain't killers.
Told you he'd say that.
I know you too well, Dom, and I'm going with you.
Looks like we got a nice little hunting party.
Let's go bag a shadow.
Ten clicks out, boys. Get ready to rock and roll.
Here we go. Weapons hot.
You ready for this?
Yeah.
I hope you're enjoying your last meal.
This is it?
This is all you want?
A dozen men?
I think you'll find it's more than enough.
I'm ready to meet my maker.
Are you?
What were you expecting, Toretto? Catch me off guard?
Me standing here, waving a white flag?
Have you ever heard the saying:
"The enemy of my enemy...
is my friend"?
I don't have friends.
I got family.
Well, I got a lot of friends.
Keep your formation! Sheppard, clear one!
Brian, leave it!
Get down!
I got you.
The God's Eye.
You didn't really think I was gonna walk in there naked, did you?
You got hit bad.
Look. Toretto.
I know you won't listen to me.
You're not gonna wanna hear what I have to say.
But the truth is...
you really ought to...
try that Belgian ale, man.
It's something special.
Belgian ale, huh?
We gotta get you to a hospital.
No, you're not.
I carry my own health insurance.
SOCOM Medics on standby. They're already inbound.
Pull over, kid.
Dom, you got to protect Ramsey.
As long as she's alive,
she can lock them out of God's Eye and they know that.
That means, they're not gonna stop coming until they've got her.
And this time when they come...
They're gonna come with everything they've got.
I'm not leaving you.
You're not.
I'm leaving you.
Go now, Dom.
A war is coming to us whether we like it or not.
But if a war's coming...
We're gonna face them on the streets we know best.
I'm all for winging it, but this is crazy, man.
We got mercenaries with some real heat on us.
I mean I ain't scared of nothing but...
..I don't even have a gun.
Gun?
We got a whole city.
And we may have more than that.
If they use God's Eye...
it will tap the cameras around to find our location.
Which means we could plant a virus.
And then break in when they access it.
So you're talking about hacking my hacking device.
That's brilliant.
Yeah, but there's one problem.
The signal strength.
We can't start a hack on them until they're within a two mile range.
- That's really close. - Close?
These guys are military.
If they're within two miles of us, we already dead.
I don't know about y'all, but I didn't really plan on dying today.
Only one way to stay alive.
We play keepaway with Ramsey.
What?
They can't hit us if we keep moving.
And I'll take Shaw.
So basically we're just gearing up for a big game of hot potato, huh?
Why does it feel like I'm not gonna see you again?
I'll come back for that.
Promise?
Promise.
Brian, are you okay?
M韆, listen to me.
Something's about to go down.
If you don't hear from me in 24 hours...
I need you to take Jack and move on.
You understand?
You understand what I'm saying?
No I can't do that, Brian.
No, I can't.
We're gonna have another baby.
It's a little girl.
And she's going to need her father.
So you have to finish what you're doing...
and you have to come home to her.
You have to come home to us.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you before.
I was scared you'd be disappointed with domestic life.
You know the best decision I ever made was stepping into that store...
buying that first sandwich.
It was such a bad s醤dwich.
I know.
But I ate a lot of 'em.
I love you, M韆.
Don't do that.
What?
The way you said it. It's like goodbye.
Say something else.
Okay. Kiss Jack for me.
I will.
I love you, Brian.
I love you, M韆.
One last ride.
Boot up God's Eye, and find them.
I'm getting something.
I got a positive ID. It's Toretto.
God's Eye is placing him at Hill and Seventh.
Should we follow him?
No. Let Shaw take care of him.
Find Ramsey.
Yes, sir.
I don't know why we gotta keep driving around like this.
Why can't we just pull over somewhere...
park, gather our thoughts in like a bunker somewhere?
Because it does not work like that.
We gotta stick close enough to the bad guys...
in order to get in range for Ramsey to hack 'em...
but we gotta be mobile enough not to get shot like fish in a barrel.
So do me a favor, focus on the mission, keep us from getting killed.
Got them. Target acquired.
She's riding shotgun in a blue GT-R.
Guys, they're here.
How many cars?
None.
And that's kind of the problem.
Let's give them a tour.
Break on my mark.
Three, two, one.
Go!
Splitting up won't work.
You can't hide from God's Eye.
In range.
Ramsey, start the hack.
Initiating.
Now.
Sir, I think someone's trying to hack the system.
It's Ramsey.
Send in the predator!
Take her out!
Releasing predator.
I think we lost the chopper.
I think we got bigger problems than that!
Oh, my God.
What are you doing?
Going old school!
PUBLIC PARKING
It's coming back around!
The predator's back on 'em.
Ready missiles!
Roger that.
Fire!
Shit!
I need a lateral.
Rom, where are you?
Running back! Charging in.
Meet me on Third and Spring.
You got it!
I'm halfway there.
Grab your computer and get in the window!
- Why? - Do it, now!
You gotta go! Right now!
Fire!
No!
He made it!
Can't believe we pullled that off!
Wait, we're still being hacked.
What?
God's Eye is still tracking Ramsey.
Keep the drone in pursuit of her.
The signal has to be coming from somewhere.
Breaking news out of Los 羘geles tonight.
In what can only be described as vehicular warfare,
police are engaged in a high speed pursuit...
I got it. The piggyback in the hack off that satellite tower right there.
Take it out!
Toretto.
Wait, what happened? We were almost there.
They've cut the signal. I can't finish the hack.
What do you mean?
Brian, they took out the tower!
Dad, what's going on?
Daddy's gotta go to work.
Alright, baby girl.
Elena's gonna be here in a little bit.
You know our drill.
Give me three for the road.
You thought this was gonna be a street fight?
You're goddamn right it is.
There has to be another way.
Wait. I'm seeing half a dozen cell towers between Sixth and State.
Brian, if you can get to the top of any one of those buildings around there...
we can reroute the signal manually and finish the job.
I'm on it.
Sir, did you hear that?
O碈onner is on foot heading for a repeater.
He's gonna try to reinitiate the hack.
Keep the drone on the girl.
Kiet.
O碈onner's on foot somewhere between Sixth and State.
Don't let him make it there.
Boys is on us!
And them boys ain't ready for this!
Shit!
First a tank, then a plane...
Now we got a spaceship?
That's not a spaceship, that's a drone!
Oh it's a drone?
Now you gonna break it down and be articulate...
like you already know what the hell is going on?
Shut your ass up and drive the car!
Letty, the football's on fire!
We need help!
Hang on! I'm coming!
Ramsey, get ready to go again.
Drone has missile lock.
Fire!
Target destroyed.
Wait! God's Eye still has her.
How can that be?
Get up. Come on.
Let's go! Let's go.
They switched her under the bridge.
What?
You gotta get outta here, it's on your trail and it's coming fast.
Got it.
So if this car goes south, who's coming to save us?
Save us, honey? We're it.
Where are they now?
Six blocks east, hauling ass.
Where we heading, Tej?
There's a service elevator past the maintenance center.
It will take you directly up to the repeater.
Brian, you gotta hurry!
Too slow!
It's coming back.
We'll lose them in the tunnel.
Got it!
Fire!
I can't shake this thing!
The predator has missile lock.
Take it out!
No way.
Wait! What happened?
Sir, someone just double tapped our drone.
What?
Hey, did you bring the cavalry?
Woman, I am the cavalry.
Who is that?
That's Hobbs!
I'm at the repeater.
The access cable's in the base.
Just plug it into your phone and Ramsey will be back online.
Ramsey, go!
Brian did it. We're back in.
We've got God's Eye back.
- We lost the God's Eye! - What?
Shit!
Military's inbound. Three minutes and closing.
We need to get the hell outta here.
Tej, Roman, I'm on my way.
Alright, homie. I'll see you there.
I have eyes on Toretto.
Shaw's in the way.
Then it seems our friendship is at an end.
Do it.
The thing about street fights?
The street always wins.
Goodbye, Toretto.
Take him out!
Son of a...
I need some help out here!
We're getting killed.
I need some backup!
No! Son of a bitch.
He's getting away!
No, stop them.
Don't miss.
Dom!
Come on.
C'mon, buddy.
Is he breathing?
Here's what I need you to do. Keep his head tilted up.
All right. Keep it back like this.
Clinch his nose, keep his head tilted. Breathe in him now. Go.
That's good.
Come on, Dom.
Come on, goddammit!
You come on, you breathe!
Go, go, breathe!
C'mon, dammit. Let's go. Come on, Dom! I need you to breathe.
Come on, Dom. Come back, c'mon.
Come on, buddy. Dom, come on!
Back off!
Will you stop? Breathe into him.
You breathe into him.
- You breathe into him. - Back off!
Please, please, Dom.
Dom, baby.
I know you're hurting right now.
But I want you to listen.
Stay awake and focus on me.
I remember everything.
It came to me like a flood.
That night, in the Dominican Republic.
The night we got married.
Who has the ring?
Will this do?
With this silver necklace, love...
We have eternity in this moment.
You will never be alone again.
I vow, wherever you go, I go.
You ride, I ride.
You fight, I fight.
And if you ever die on me, Dominic Toretto...
I'm gonna die with you.
I love you, Letty.
I will always love you.
If you die, I die.
And I'm not ready to leave this place yet.
This moment, still ours.
I remember everything.
I remember it all.
It's about time.
Oh, God.
Why didn't you tell me we were married?
Because you can't tell someone they love you.
Holy shit.
BLACK SITE --- CIA
You sure you brought enough backup with you, Hobbs?
Oh, they ain't mine.
They're here to protect you.
From me killing your ass.
You do know, none of this will keep me, right?
Well I want you to dig through 38 feet of concrete and steel...
and my fist and a bodybag will be waiting for you on the other side.
So I suggest you get to digging, boy.
- Daddy, come play. - Yeah.
Look at him, look at him.
Yeah, buddy.
- Duty calls. - It does.
- Come on... - Let's get momma...
Y'know we gotta tan because...
the sun is out, you know...
medium rare, but I can get like...
well done, like really dark.
- What you nudging me for? - Close your mouth for two seconds.
Just open your eyes, man.
Beautiful.
That's where he belongs.
Home.
Where he's always belonged.
Things are gonna be different now.
You got it. What...
One more time.
You aren't going to say goodbye?
Yeah! Good job!
My man.
It's never goodbye.
Music: See You Again by: Wiz Khalifa
It's been a long day without you, my friend
And I'll tell you all about it when I see you again
We've come a long way from where we began
Oh, I'll tell you all about it when I see you again
When I see you again
First you both go out your way
And the vibe is feeling strong
And what's small turn to a friendship
A friendship turn into a bond
And that bond will never be broken
And the love will never get lost
And when brotherhood come first
Then the line will never be crossed
Established it on our own
When that line had to be drawn
And that line is what we reach
So remember me when I'm gone
It's been a long day
Without you, my friend
And I'll tell you all about it when I see you again
When I see you again
Hey, thought you could leave without saying goodbye?
I used to say I lived my life a quarter mile at a time.
And I think that's why we were brothers.
Because you did, too.
- This is your car. - My car?
You're all free.
Home, sweet home.
- What's happening, boy? - Thanks for the invite.
Wanna go for a drive?
No matter where you are,
whether it's a quarter mile away,
or halfway across the world...
The most important thing in life will
always be the people in this room.
Right here, right now.
Salud, mi familia.
You'll always be with me.
And you'll always be my brother.
FOR PAUL