He used to date
my sister.
I see.
You're a lucky man.
How's that?
You're still breathing.
To the ladies we've loved
and the ladies we've lost.
So, what's Braga about?
You know,
he's just one of us.
Came up from the streets.
Down for el barrio.
Now he's a shot caller.
The boss of bosses.
See all these
cats in here?
Any one of them
would die for Braga.
Including you?
Especially me.
Enjoy the party, fellows.
Club's yours.
Whatever you want, booze,
broads, it's all good.
Braga's mine.
I'm taking the
whole house down.
Good luck.
Something interests you
about this car?
Just admiring
the body work.
Are you one of those boys
who prefers cars to women?
I'm one of those boys that appreciates
a fine body, regardless of the make.
Your car?
It's Fenix's car.
You'll meet him at the
rendezvous. He'll be leading you.
So now...
...that I know
your taste in cars...
...tell me, what about your women?
It all starts
with the eyes.
She's got to have those kind of eyes
that can look right through the bullshit...
...to the good in someone.
20% angel,
80% devil.
Down to earth.
Ain't afraid to get a little
engine grease under her fingernails.
That doesn't sound
anything like me.
It ain't.
Hi.
I got a gift for you.
All right.
A dirty shot glass,
just what I always wanted.
I got these from the club last night.
There's two sets of
prints here. Run them both.
I know one of these is Campos'. I
think the other might be Braga's.
And you're gonna have
to go beyond Interpol.
So, that means I have to
contact individual agencies...
...and that could
take weeks. Okay.
Yeah.
That's your third traffic
violation in less than three blocks.
Slow it down,
O'Conner.
Sure thing, Dad.
He stopped.
We lost him.
He killed the tracker.
We don't know that.
I'm telling you, he killed the
tracker. We don't know that yet!
Get the bird overhead.
Right now, I'm moving north, 33', 56'...
All clear.
Base, flag nine,
I'm at Angels 5.
I don't have a tally on the target.
Repeat, I don't have a tally on the target.
They're gone, there's no one down there.
Damn it!
This ain't right, bro. Nobody said
nothing about being locked in no truck.
Tell me about it.
Hey. Hey!
Yo! Where do you think
they're taking us?
Don't matter.
We're all just along
for the ride now.
Welcome to Mexico, boys.
There are helicopters
and surveillance cameras...
...that scan for heat
signatures at the border.
But there are blind spots that I
can guide you through via satellite.
There can be no margin of error, so
you must follow my every direction.
Any questions?
I thought Fenix
was gonna be here.
He'll meet you
out there.
All right, everybody, sync up.
Good luck, gentlemen.
Satellite linkup engaged.
Keep proceeding northbound
at current speed.
Stay close to Fenix.
He'll lead you across.
I got a heat signature
northbound along Legardo Ravine.
Thermal imaging window on the Mexico
side's gonna be down for about 45 seconds.
Get the camera on it.
Manual override. Rerouting
camera to designated coordinates.
Hurry it up.
You guys have been tagged.
Shit.
Toretto,
get back in formation.
Reimaging commencing.
I don't see anything.
They're gone.
Get the helicopters
to cover it.
Base, we're 40 seconds
out from Legardo Ravine.
They're sending
a helicopter.
You have 30 seconds.
North 32' 33',
west 116' 49'.
The window
is closing fast.
You need to get out of there
before they send ground support.
Fifteen seconds.
Base,
target is at two miles.
You're running
out of time.
You need to get out now!
Base, we're at north
32' 33', west 116' 49'.
We have no visual contact. Roll
ground units for confirmation.
Sloppy!
Very sloppy!
What are you doing, man?
Come on.
Get out.
Come on, man.
Come on, today, man.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, don't touch me.
Hey, don't touch me, man!
Hey, I said don't touch me, man!
Hey, look, dawg, don't
put your hands on me.
Hey,
Malik, chill, bro.
Yo, man, what's up
with your boy?
Hey, boss man!
What did you say?
I said only pussies
run nitrometh.
You looked under my hood?
I'm talking to you.
Got something on your mind?
'70 Plymouth.
Her name was Letty.
Yo.
Where's my money?
And somebody
wrecked her car.
I wrecked her car.
You remember her face?
Huh?
'Cause I don't.
Last time I saw it,
it was burning.
Now what?
I'm going to enjoy
what happens next.
Dom, get in!
Get in! Come on!
Come on! Get in the fucking
car! Let's go! Hurry up!
What
have you got, Trinh?
We're contacting agencies
in multiple countries.
Unfortunately, most of them have to
manually scan their prints for us to upload.
O'Conner's on line five.
And, sir,
you should see this.
Thank you.
Talk to me, O'Conner.
Where the hell have you
been? I got the shipment.
"I got the shipment,"
or "we got the shipment"?
What are you
talking about?
Traffic cams in the area picked up
pictures of you and Toretto together.
Listen to me, O'Conner. Bring in
the shipment and bring in Toretto.
But I thought the point was to get
Braga. We got an opportunity here.
Brian, the clock
stopped ticking.
Bring them in.
Are we clear?
O'Conner?
So this is what
$60 million looks like.
Yeah, we got to
get you to a doctor.
We got to find
a place to hide this.
I got a spot.
502, wet reckless.
I need a 48-hour hold.
Out back.
Any spot you can find.
You sure about this?
Yeah. The last place they'll check,
their own impound yard. Trust me.
You know,
I've been thinking...
...when you blew up your car back
there, you blew up mine, too.
Yeah?
Yeah.
So now you owe me
a 10-second car.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Now we're even.
Is this your way of
keeping me away from him?
You're the only one I could
call. He's my brother, of course.
The bullet's not in there.
I'm gonna clean it and stitch
it up. It's going to hurt.
I bet you're going
to enjoy this.
A little.
Want some of this?
Yeah.
It's spicy.
I like it hot.
Dom, what are you doing?
You reached first,
you have to say grace.
Thank you, Lord,
for blessing this table.
With food, family
and friendship.
You asked me
why I let Dom go.
I think it's because
at that moment...
I respected him
more than I did myself.
Yeah.
One thing I learned from Dom is that nothing
really matters unless you have a code.
And what's your code,
Brian?
I'm working on it.
Shit. Hey, Dom.
When were you gonna tell
me? Dom, what are you doing?
When were you gonna tell me
you were running Letty?
Let me explain...
When were you gonna...
Dom, stop!
You don't understand.
I don't understand?
Stop!
She did it for...
Dom, stop!
Dom, stop it!
Please stop!
She did it for you, Dom!
She did it for you!
Letty came to me to clear your name
in exchange for bringing down Braga.
She just wanted you
to come home!
I'm sorry, Dom!
I'm sorry!
You better have one hell of an
explanation. You disobeyed a direct order.
Where's the shipment?
It's safe.
Look, we could use the shipment
to parade in front of the media...
...get a few hundred pounds
of heroin off the street...
...but Braga's just gonna send another
shipment next week and the week after that.
Let's use the shipment
to lure Braga out...
...and lop the head off
a multi-billion dollar cartel.
And how do you
suggest we do that?
A hand-to-hand
exchange with Braga.
He'll never show.
He can't afford not to.
You got a plan?
There's a price.
We bag Braga,
you let Toretto walk.
Yes?
It's Dom.
I was just
thinking about you.
You know, when I gave you my
number, I was hoping you'd call.
But not under
these circumstances.
What circumstances?
Me being alive?
Don't take it personally.
It's just business.
I got some business
of my own.
Get Campos.
It's them.
Uh-huh.
Was that how Braga inspires
loyalty? Killing his drivers?
One can always
find more drivers.
It's just good business.
I want to trade.
Braga doesn't negotiate.
Fine.
You explain to him how all of a sudden
$60 million worth of product disappears.
I know that can't
be good for business.
What do you want?
Six million cash,
delivered by Braga himself.
I don't like being shot at.
I ain't gonna put my neck out again
unless he's got something to lose, too.
He'll never go for it.
Either I deal with Braga,
or you do.
When and where?
Sir, players are onsite. Holding
positions at the perimeter.
All right. Listen up.
Everybody stay frosty.
We don't move a muscle until
O'Conner gives the signal.
When he gets the money,
you know what to do.
Well, the good news is,
when we get this guy...
...you walk out of here
a free man.
Is that what
they told you?
Yeah, that's the deal.
You still put milk and
cookies out for Santa Claus?
Yeah.
Here.
In case things go shitty.
Just like old times?
Yeah.
You dropped something.
That's what you wanted, right? Dom...
He's harmless.
Don't worry about him.
And he's really
sorry about Letty.
Where's our stuff?
You mean the stuff that
used to be in here, right?
Well, you'll see it when we
see Braga. That was the deal.
No worries.
Braga keeps his word.
$2 million.
You get the rest
when I get my property.
Stasiak.
We got a match.
The fingerprint's
Braga's 100%.
Just waiting on facial
confirmation via fax.
I got
a question for you.
You wearing pink when you were
clawing your way out of el barrio?
Order all agents
to move in.
We got confirmation. Primary
suspect wearing gray suit.
Let's move.
Sir, O'Conner hasn't
given us the signal yet.
What part of that didn't you understand?
We just got confirmation. Do it!
Secure primary suspect
in gray suit. Repeat!
in gray suit.
You're thinking what
I'm thinking, right?
He ain't Braga.
Oh, shit.
Drop your weapons!
FBI!
Get down!
Get out of here!
Get out of here, Dom!
Run him down.
Go!
Campos is Braga!
Come on.
Approaching primary target.
Primary suspect is secure.
He was under your nose
the whole time.
Now Braga's escaped.
Toretto's heading south, probably
long across the border by now.
Do you have any idea the kind
of trouble you're in, O'Conner?
I was doing my job.
He ain't the first bad guy you
helped escape the law's grasp.
As of now, you're being
taken off active duty...
...until this house can
mount a formal inquiry.
What about Braga?
That's no longer
your concern.
We now know where Braga is, right?
Customs tracked him via satellite
to his home base in Tecali, Mexico.
Mexico is out
of our jurisdiction.
The fact is...
...the brass will be so busy holding
press conferences over the seizure...
...we'll skate
under the radar.
I thought we signed on
to do the right thing.
Everyone's looking for you.
I'm right here.
It's nice to see you've
gone with the times...
...and switched to electronic
fuel injection. Looks good.
Buster became a gearhead.
I'm going with you.
I don't plan on
bringing anyone back.
I know.
Hit that throttle.
Hey.
How do you say goodbye
to your only brother?
You don't.
I thought you weren't
gonna show up.
You saved my life.
I'm willing to
return the favor.
This will help
get you to Braga.
Dom.
Going in there
is suicide.
I have no choice.
You must have
loved her very much.
So this is where
my jurisdiction ends.
And this is where
mine begins.
You ain't forgiven.
You boys want
to arrest me?
No, we're beyond that.
You can't buy your way out of this one.
You and me...
You and me,
we're not so different.
You're no hero.
You're right.
And that's why you're going
back across the border.
But Fenix is mine.
You got it.
Shit!
You'll make it a couple of
miles out, if you're lucky.
You know where
you're going?
You want to borrow my GPS?
Where are your boys at?
Are they going
to show up or what?
Careful what you ask for.
Just stop.
Just stop the car.
Right behind you.
Dom, head to the tunnel.
Let's use the tunnel.
Get out of here, Brian.
You sure you know where
the tunnels are? You sure?
Yeah. I'd hold on.
This might hurt.
You're in
my world now, baby!
That's it, baby!
End of the road.
Now what?
Game over.
No, no, no.
Come on!
Hey!
Get me out of here!
Pussy.
Let me see that.
Yeah.
Just keep pressure there.
You'll be all right.
You gotta get
out of here.
I ain't running anymore.
I gotta ask you
something.
Yeah?
You know I would have won that
race if you didn't cheat, right?
You hit your head hard.
Don't make me laugh.
All rise.
Please be seated.
Please rise,
Mr. Toretto.
I've listened
to the testimony...
...and taken into
special consideration...
Agent O'Conner's appeal of
clemency on behalf of Mr. Toretto.
That his actions directly
resulted in the apprehension...
...of known drug
trafficker Arturo Braga.
However...
...this judiciary
finds that...
...one right does not make up
for a lifetime worth of wrongs.
And as such...
I find that I am forced to level the
maximum sentence under California law.
Dominic Toretto...
...you are hereby sentenced
to serve 25 years to life...
...at the Lompoc maximum
security prison system...
...without the possibility
of early parole.
This court is adjourned.