1
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000
Timing could be further improved, self improved

1
00:04:25,891 --> 00:04:27,308
Easy, friends.

2
00:04:27,892 --> 00:04:28,768
She's with me.

3
00:05:19,152 --> 00:05:20,820
Time for bed little one.

4
00:05:20,904 --> 00:05:22,488
Can l bring him?

5
00:05:22,572 --> 00:05:24,200
Of course.

6
00:05:46,930 --> 00:05:48,023
Excuse me, sorry.

7
00:06:31,933 --> 00:06:33,017
Does he know?

8
00:11:00,910 --> 00:11:02,711
l'm taking the GT40.

9
00:11:50,335 --> 00:11:52,669
This car suits me better.

10
00:12:08,645 --> 00:12:10,896
lt's okay. We're all going to 
the same place.

11
00:12:10,896 --> 00:12:12,272
We'll get the car there.

12
00:12:58,486 --> 00:12:59,653
Go after the girl!

13
00:13:00,613 --> 00:13:01,613
Hurry up!

14
00:19:16,614 --> 00:19:23,370
The American fugitives killed three
DEA agents during a train robbery...

15
00:19:23,454 --> 00:19:26,414
Police warn they are armed and
extremely dangerous.

16
00:19:26,499 --> 00:19:30,418
Anyone with information should contact law 
enforcement immediately...

17
00:24:36,725 --> 00:24:38,685
l apologize for the interruption.

18
00:24:39,145 --> 00:24:41,538
Señor Reyes, may l speak with you?

19
00:24:42,022 --> 00:24:43,399
We've found them.

20
00:31:11,662 --> 00:31:12,662
Go that way!

21
00:31:12,746 --> 00:31:14,539
The other two went over the wall!

22
00:43:02,664 --> 00:43:05,707
l told you the skinny chick had balls.

23
00:43:05,792 --> 00:43:08,210
Looks like she started the party without us.

24
00:43:11,965 --> 00:43:14,341
What's this guy saying?

25
00:43:15,009 --> 00:43:16,927
Ugly is still ugly in Spanish or in English.

26
00:46:11,310 --> 00:46:12,719
Nobody move!

27
00:48:54,974 --> 00:48:55,974
Explain.

28
00:48:56,475 --> 00:48:58,310
They invaded the Leblon house.

29
00:48:58,686 --> 00:48:59,978
Who invaded?

30
00:49:00,062 --> 00:49:01,300
The men from the train.

31
00:49:10,781 --> 00:49:12,649
How much did they take?

32
00:49:13,034 --> 00:49:15,076
They didn't take anything.

33
00:49:15,161 --> 00:49:16,705
They burned it.

34
00:49:18,956 --> 00:49:20,624
They burned my money?

35
00:49:20,708 --> 00:49:22,793
Yes. And said there's more coming.

36
00:49:31,886 --> 00:49:32,927
Okay...

37
00:49:41,562 --> 00:49:43,563
Then this...

38
00:49:45,399 --> 00:49:46,900
...is what we're going to do.

39
00:49:53,449 --> 00:49:55,075
Clean the houses.

40
00:49:55,159 --> 00:49:59,371
l want that money under lock and key...

41
00:50:00,998 --> 00:50:03,517
...within an hour, understand?

43
00:50:06,587 --> 00:50:08,254
Understood.

44
00:52:25,017 --> 00:52:26,910
Looks like this is going to be
a shorter trip than l thought...

45
00:54:05,284 --> 00:54:06,242
Everything okay?

46
00:54:06,327 --> 00:54:07,327
Everything is okay.

47
00:54:07,411 --> 00:54:10,497
Who is this Hobbs?
This Federal Agent running around town?

48
00:54:10,497 --> 00:54:11,497
Some American cowboy.

49
00:54:12,082 --> 00:54:13,082
He's handled.

50
00:54:13,334 --> 00:54:14,918
He killed sixteen of our men.

51
00:54:15,669 --> 00:54:16,878
Handle him better.

52
00:54:17,171 --> 00:54:21,767
Look, he requested a rookie 
patrol officer as his assistant.

53
00:54:25,179 --> 00:54:26,179
They won't be a problem.

54
00:54:55,084 --> 00:54:57,001
- lt's all here?
- Yes.

55
00:54:58,504 --> 00:55:00,514
What about Toretto and O'Conner?
Where are they?

56
00:55:00,714 --> 00:55:01,714
Nothing yet.

57
00:55:02,716 --> 00:55:04,550
But l have all our officers searching.

58
00:55:05,427 --> 00:55:06,552
Not good enough.

59
00:55:07,388 --> 00:55:10,390
Put a price on their heads, 
high enough to get...

61
00:55:10,849 --> 00:55:13,101
...every pair of eyes in 
the city searching for them.

62
00:59:47,834 --> 00:59:50,962
Two to one says you blow the wrong pipe.

63
00:59:53,006 --> 00:59:54,507
l ain't negative.

64
00:59:55,509 --> 00:59:58,594
l'm just positive you're going to mess it up.

65
01:00:06,853 --> 01:00:09,523
You need to learn to relax, <i>loco</i>.

66
01:00:10,691 --> 01:00:13,859
You need to learn to relax, <i>loco</i>.

67
01:00:34,339 --> 01:00:37,258
You better hurry up,
we got less than a minute.

68
01:00:37,843 --> 01:00:39,923
Why do you always set the timer so short?

69
01:01:06,413 --> 01:01:08,207
l hope you know where you're going.

70
01:01:24,222 --> 01:01:26,017
A police station.

71
01:01:39,613 --> 01:01:41,365
You used too much explosive again.

72
01:01:43,450 --> 01:01:45,201
Too much, too little...

73
01:01:45,660 --> 01:01:46,702
lt's all the same.

74
01:01:47,329 --> 01:01:52,166
That's some Buddha shit you learned
from a book in the prison library, isn't it?

75
01:01:53,752 --> 01:01:55,086
And what you're doing there on the wall...

76
01:01:55,170 --> 01:01:57,963
You got that from the same book, huh?

77
01:04:20,440 --> 01:04:21,950
Damn, bro...

78
01:04:52,972 --> 01:04:55,806
Dominic Toretto's ride in my garage.

79
01:04:55,767 --> 01:04:59,437
Now that... will be a nice trophy.

80
01:23:02,519 --> 01:23:03,895
l know she's here!

81
01:23:06,607 --> 01:23:07,899
Find her!

82
01:23:07,983 --> 01:23:09,400
Go! Go! Go!

83
01:23:57,866 --> 01:23:59,411
Yo, you burned it!

84
01:24:02,621 --> 01:24:05,125
Yeah, but your mom is 
the worst cook in the world.

85
01:39:29,213 --> 01:39:30,255
See?

86
01:39:31,924 --> 01:39:34,509
l called in every cop on our payroll.

87
01:39:36,054 --> 01:39:37,846
We're covered.

88
01:39:39,557 --> 01:39:41,016
We've got every entrance covered
with weapons teams.

89
01:39:41,100 --> 01:39:43,852
God Himself couldn't get at your 
money if He wanted to.

90
01:39:44,103 --> 01:39:47,023
God isn't my worry.

91
01:41:00,805 --> 01:41:02,264
What's happening?

92
01:41:02,348 --> 01:41:03,724
They're taking the vault!

93
01:41:03,808 --> 01:41:05,517
- What?
- The vault!

94
01:41:15,069 --> 01:41:16,321
Follow me! Quickly!

95
01:41:22,618 --> 01:41:23,661
Let me through!

96
01:41:34,297 --> 01:41:35,297
Don't move!

97
01:41:36,382 --> 01:41:37,758
Stay down.

98
01:47:54,969 --> 01:47:57,220
Zizi, stay on them.

99
01:48:23,789 --> 01:48:25,665
They can't outrun us on the bridge.

100
01:48:35,759 --> 01:48:36,968
They have no way out.

101
01:49:24,133 --> 01:49:25,391
What is he doing?

102
01:49:29,813 --> 01:49:30,980
We've got him!

103
01:49:47,831 --> 01:49:49,082
Close down the bridge!

104
01:50:23,367 --> 01:50:24,701
Do something, asshole!

105
01:50:36,839 --> 01:50:37,922
Kill him, dammit!

106
01:50:49,310 --> 01:50:50,768
Kill him now!

107
01:56:23,477 --> 01:56:26,937
For Rosa and Nico. See you soon,
Uncle Dom

108
01:56:33,779 --> 01:56:37,239


109
01:56:39,201 --> 01:56:40,826
You sure about this?

110
01:56:42,829 --> 01:56:44,330
You know l am.

111
01:56:46,249 --> 01:56:47,833
You don't need to do this.

112
01:56:48,752 --> 01:56:51,087
Just leave me alone.

113
01:56:51,171 --> 01:56:53,339
Bro, l'm not trying to be negative,
but casinos...

114
01:56:53,423 --> 01:56:56,133
are the kinds of places designed to take
money from guys like you and me.

115
01:56:56,343 --> 01:56:59,929
When l win here l'm buying you
a lifetime supply of antidepressants.

116
01:57:00,222 --> 01:57:03,140
You don't put ten million on red!

117
01:57:03,225 --> 01:57:04,183
Enough already.

118
01:57:04,267 --> 01:57:05,643
You put it on black.

119
01:57:07,604 --> 01:57:08,604
No more bets.

120
02:03:25,982 --> 02:03:30,527
