jmg subs
All right,
we're good to go.
You got this? You bet your ass, bubba.
Let's make some money!
Everyone in position.
I thought we'd be
robbing banks by now,
not some gas truck
in the middle of nowhere.
Down here, gas is gold, bubba.
Kill the chatter!
Game time.
I wouldn't piss him off, guys.
Okay, guys, we're gonna have
to hit this hard and fast.
We got four K left
before the downgrade.
Locked and loaded!
This is all you, Han.
Liquid gold.
We're clear.
Okay, T, you're up.
Let's see if you can get it
under six tries this time, huh, T?
It's more like three. Come
on, Tego, keep it real.
Just one K left. We're running
out of road. Get in there, brother.
I got it, I got it.
Shit!
T, cut loose!
Unhitch, unhitch!
Spray that hitch!
I don't have a hammer!
Just do it!
Hold on! Hold on!
No shit!
Hold onto
something tight!
Letty!
Give me your hand!
I can't reach!
You got to jump!
Jump!
Letty, jump!
I've got you!
Dom...
Dom?
Dom!
How you doing?
Money, money!
Good.
Yo, why your stack
is bigger than mine always?
I'm supersized,
baby.
Cops just raided
our garage in Baracoa.
They were real
interested in you.
Heat's on and we just sent up a flare
that's gonna lead them right to us.
I say we move out first
thing in the morning.
Nah, it's me they want.
And if they catch me,
they're throwing big
numbers at anybody with me.
Han, we had a good run.
Time for you to go
do your own thing.
Heard they're doing
some crazy shit in Tokyo.
Have you seen Letty?
There she is.
I hear Rio is nice
this time of year.
The cops are
getting hungrier.
Then I guess we're doing our job.
I'm a walking target.
I don't want you around
when they catch up to me.
"Ride or die,"
remember?
Dom, how long have we been doing this?
And now all of a sudden, out
of nowhere, it's too dangerous?
Come on.
We'll figure it out.
We always do.
I don't know shit!
Give me a name!
I don't know shit, man!
David Park! David
Park's the guy you want!
Please!
Thank God. Listen, he's in a mood
because yesterday was his cheat day,
and then today, some
genius brought in donuts.
Great.
Sorry I'm late.
Complaints keep rolling in after your
little downtown Olympics, O'Conner.
Tell me that reinstating
you wasn't a mistake.
I got a name. David Park. That's it?
That's all you got?
David Park?
I could throw a fortune cookie out this
window and hit 50 David Parks right now.
It's Korean, not Chinese. Whatever.
Park is a scout that recruits street
racers to be mules for the Braga cartel.
We find Park, and we bust the bad guys.
Dom.
Mia, I told you
not to call me here.
Dom, it's Letty.
She's been murdered.
We have gathered here
to pay our final respects to...
Let us reflect
on her journey...
"The Lord is my shepherd, I shall
not want. He makes me lie down... "
Facial recognition software
matched Toretto
about 10 minutes after
he crossed the border.
I don't get it.
I thought he'd show.
I told you not to come.
They're staking the place out.
If they find you...
They won't.
Come on.
Look at you.
Letty wouldn't
let them junk it.
Even though it is
a goddamn curse.
When she came back,
she was always in here,
working on it
day and night.
It was weird.
It was like she knew
you were coming back.
I want to see
the crash site.
I just got off the
phone with Deputy Director Lawson.
If we don't make serious inroads into
the Braga case in the next 72 hours,
they're gonna
shut us down.
I know I'm a newbie here,
but why the clock now?
Because it's been
two years,
and the last three agents we sent
to infiltrate his organization
came back in body bags.
He's moved more heroin across the
border than Escobar did in 10 years.
This guy is becoming one of
our biggest national threats,
and we don't even
have a picture of him.
We don't have prints!
Not even a goddamn DOB!
What's the status
on David Park?
Isn't he our ticket into
the Braga organization?
We're running the name through city and
county databases, sorting the possibilities.
We've got
over 500 already.
Park's insignificant. Sounds
like another jerk-off to me.
It's not. Without Park, Braga
wouldn't have drivers to move his shipments.
Cross-check traffic.
lllegal modifications.
Street racing. This guy will definitely
have a record. We'll find him.
We better.
What do you know?
Your boy Toretto's red Chevelle has
been spotted in his old neighborhood.
I'm going to
bring his ass in.
Not in your car
you're not.
It's straight ahead.
You found something
back there.
There were burn marks
on the ground.
The kind that could only
be caused by nitrometh.
There's only one guy in
all of L.A. that sells that.
Nothing you can do is
gonna bring her back, Dom.
If I were Letty,
I would ask you...
No, I would beg you,
please, let this go.
Before it's too late.
It's already too late.
I love you.
Miss Toretto.
I'm Michael Stasiak, FBl.
Let's you and I
have a little chat.
Hi. This is Forsythe
in Evidence.
I need Stasiak down here right
away to sign some greenies.
Thanks.
Hi.
Hey.
Okay, I narrowed it down
to 50 or so David Parks.
What I'd like you to do is run the
make and model on each one of them.
All right?
Okay. All right.
Thank you.
Hey, Tyler,
we got a transfer.
You want to
come with me?
Toretto.
When'd you get
back in town?
I'm looking for a car
you did an engine mod on.
Nitromethane tank. Ford
full-size. Continental tires.
Look, what are you doing,
coming in here like this, huh?
This ain't your scene
anymore, boss.
Don't ever put your hands
on me again, okay?
Say hi to your
sister for me.
A Korean kid brought it in. David Park.
It's a green Ford Torino.
Please don't
drop this on me!
I'm almost done.
Why don't you tell me why
you dragged me here, Brian?
You know they're going to
capture Dom. Maybe worse.
I don't want you getting tangled
up in this. So stay away from him.
That's what you have to
say to me after five years?
All of a sudden, you
care what happens to me.
What I did to you
was wrong.
I'm sorry. It was... It was the
hardest thing I've ever had to do.
I'm sorry, too, Brian.
I'm so sorry that you had to come
into my home and pretend to love me.
I'm so sorry that you
ripped my family apart.
I'm very sorry that
that was hard for you.
I lied to you.
I lied to Dom.
I lied to everybody.
That's what I do best. It's
why the Feds recruited me.
Maybe you're lying
to yourself.
Maybe you're not the good guy
pretending to be a bad guy.
Maybe you're the bad guy
pretending to be the good guy.
You ever think about that?
Every day.
I always wondered,
why did you let
my brother go that day?
I don't know.
Shit.
Brian!
I got the cross-checks on David Park
back and have a list of possibles.
What do you got? All right. A
45-year-old male in a '06 Scion
with three reckless driving tickets. No.
An '01 Chevy Tahoe.
No.
Two Mini Coopers, a '06
and a '07, a Toyota hybrid.
Hell no. A '98 Saturn, a '95 Sebring.
A '98 Nissan 240
with an illegal mod.
Wait. That's it.
What? The 240 with the illegal mod.
How do you know? 'Cause
that's something I'd drive.
Don't! Don't! Don't!
Green Torino,
running nitro.
Whose car?
I don't know, man.
I'm just the middleman. I
swear! I'm just the middleman!
Wait, wait, wait.
I don't know shit, man. I swear. I
just run cars for Braga, all right?
All I can do is get you in
the race! That's all I can do!
What race?
Help! Come on,
hold on!
Let me up, man!
Come on!
Come on, man, I don't
know shit! Just let me up!
I told you, you got to talk to Braga!
Bring him up, Dom.
God! Don't drop me!
That's all I know!
Bring him up.
You here to take
me in, O'Conner?
Shit! Shit!
Shut up!
Letty was my friend, too.
You weren't
anyone's friend.
Yo, can you guys talk about
this later? Now pull my ass up!
She was running for this guy,
Braga, and things went bad.
Please!
I'm going to
get these guys, Dom.
Now let me do my job
and bring him up.
I'm going to
kill this Braga.
God!
And anyone else
who gets in my way.
Hey!
Don't let go.
O'Conner!
O'Conner! If you ever release
a witness of mine again...
That's enough! STASIAK: Don't touch me.
I'm fine! PENNING: That's enough.
You're through, O'Conner!
I said that's enough!
Stasiak, go get
yourself cleaned up.
What?
He hit me first! You...
This isn't
the Cub Scouts!
Now, go on! You're bleeding on my floor.
O'Conner, do you know the difference
between a cop and a criminal?
What?
One bad judgment call.
Keep your shit in line,
son.
Have a good time.
Take a seat.
Good news. We have intel that
Braga's number two, Ramon Campos,
will hold a street race
in Koreatown tomorrow night
to fill a slot
on his team.
They've already chosen three
drivers from previous races.
Our newest informant,
Mr. David Park,
has been kind enough
to get us into the race.
O'Conner, you're up.
Let me guess,
winner gets the slot.
All right, so these are all the
imports the city has in impound.
Okay, nice.
Pick your poison.
All right, 2206.
I crashed one of those.
3418 and 2765.
Okay, so which one
do you want?
I want them all.
Standard issue
tracking device.
Boss wants to know where
you are at all times.
You want to
play with it?
Hey!
What are you
looking at, nutsack?
I don't know.
You tell me.
The racer wants
what Dwight's got.
See, but, ladies, Dwight's
already on the team.
You got to be fast if you
want to drive for Braga.
Is there a problem here? No.
You one of
Park's guys, blondie?
Yeah. Yeah, I am.
Follow me.
See you later, punk.
You, too, punk.
Bull's-eye, coño,
come on!
We can do this all day.
You all know
why you're here.
Good drivers
are a dime a dozen.
Man, every corner's got a
chingadera tuner racing for pinks.
That's not what Braga
has got me looking for.
Braga wants someone that would sell
their abuelita to be behind the wheel.
Someone that drives their 10-second
cars not in a straight line,
but to push it and make it through
places no one else would take it.
Real drivers.
So, what are we hauling?
For the money Braga's paying,
you don't need to know.
You just said you wanted real drivers.
A real driver knows
exactly what's in his car.
Mira, real driver,
nobody's forcing you
to race.
You the boss?
Or am I talking
to the boss?
Do I look like a boss?
My job is to find the
best drivers, period.
Whoever wins the race
gets the info. We cool?
Are we cool?
Yeah, we're cool.
No,
we ain't cool, man.
Who's closing these streets?
No one.
That's the point.
Please wait while
directions are downloaded.
Proceed to
the highlighted route.
Ten,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six...
You sure you want to do
this? A lot has changed.
...four...
You're right.
...three,
two,
one,
go!
Right turn ahead.
You are now five miles
from your destination.
How's my ass look,
Chia Pet?
Ghetto Smurf.
Dead man driving.
Come on!
Right turn ahead.
Shit!
Damn.
Rerouting.
Proceed straight ahead.
Shit.
Rerouting.
Just shut up!
You are 2.6 miles
from destination.
Oops, I didn't see you.
You are now four and one-half
miles from your destination.
U- turn, if possible.
Are you kidding me?
You are now 4.2 miles
from your destination.
Sorry, car.
You are now one mile
from your destination.
Yeah,
guess who's back, Dom?
Let's go!
Nice car, baby!
Bitch!
You are now one-quarter
mile from your destination.
Too early, Dom.
No!
Still a buster.
You have reached your
destination. Goodbye.
At least we know you
can't beat me straight up.
I didn't know
there were any rules.
Now that's what I call
real driving.
No, that's bullshit, man!
Go cry to your mama, eh?
You work for Braga now.
When the GPS calls,
you follow.
Driver's license.
What driver's license?
Thumb.
Cell phone number.
The print is for Campos.
The number is for me.
Yo, nutsack!
Let me tell you something, man,
muscle beats import every time.
You know what I'm saying? Every time!
Ladies, let's get on
back to Papa Dwight's.
Papa Dwight wants you
to take off your shoes.
Dwight likes feet.
Take off your shoes.
So beautiful.
Dwight likes this foot a lot.
Yes, baby!
Daddy Dwight loves...
FBl!
I didn't do nothing, man!
Dwight didn't do nothing!
Hey, no! Stay, stay! Where
you going? Bye, Dwight!
No, what did I do?
You're under arrest
for distribution of meth.
Meth? Dwight's never
touched that shit, bro!
Dwight has now.
Yo, that ain't mine! No!
You know that's never
gonna stick, right?
Yeah, it's not
supposed to.
Live it up!
Yeah, Corona.
That's too bad
about Dwight.
Having the Feds raid your house
the same night you make the team.
So unfortunate.
I wish I could say I was
surprised to see you here.
What's to stop someone from
telling them you're a cop?
Probably the same thing that's keeping me
from telling them why you're really here.
What up, fellows?
Hey, how you doing?
Great. You having a good
time? Yeah, a great time.
Come on, let's have a better time.
How's your car?
It took a nasty bump.
It'll be ready.
I also heard you just
got out of County.
Yeah.
Mmm-hmm.
You know a guy
named Jim Garcia?
Nah. Big place. Lots
of names, lots of faces.
And you, you're wanted by
a lot of people, homes.
Yeah, that kind of heat
can't be good for business.
Yeah, well, that depends
on how you look at things.
I go down, I do time.
I do real time.
I don't know about your other drivers, but
when I see flashing lights in my mirror,
I don't stop.
Do you know each other?
He used to date
my sister.
I see.
You're a lucky man.
How's that?
You're still breathing.
To the ladies we've loved
and the ladies we've lost.
So, what's Braga about?
You know,
he's just one of us.
Came up from the streets.
Down for el barrio.
Now he's a shot caller.
The boss of bosses.
See all these
cats in here?
Any one of them
would die for Braga.
Including you?
Especially me.
Enjoy the party, fellows.
Club's yours.
Whatever you want, booze,
broads, it's all good.
Braga's mine.
I'm taking the
whole house down.
Good luck.
Something interests you
about this car?
Just admiring
the body work.
Are you one of those boys
who prefers cars to women?
I'm one of those boys that appreciates
a fine body, regardless of the make.
Your car?
It's Fenix's car.
You'll meet him at the
rendezvous. He'll be leading you.
So now
that I know
your taste in cars,
tell me, what about your women?
It all starts
with the eyes.
She's got to have those kind of eyes
that can look right through the bullshit
to the good in someone.
20% angel,
80% devil.
Down to earth.
Ain't afraid to get a little
engine grease under her fingernails.
That doesn't sound
anything like me.
It ain't.
Hi.
I got a gift for you.
All right.
A dirty shot glass,
just what I always wanted.
I got these from the club last night.
There's two sets of
prints here. Run them both.
I know one of these is Campos'. I
think the other might be Braga's.
And you're gonna have
to go beyond Interpol.
So, that means I have to
contact individual agencies,
and that could
take weeks. Okay.
Yeah.
That's your third traffic
violation in less than three blocks.
Slow it down,
O'Conner.
Sure thing, Dad.
He stopped.
We lost him.
He killed the tracker.
We don't know that.
I'm telling you, he killed the
tracker. We don't know that yet!
Get the bird overhead.
Right now, I'm moving north, 33', 56'...
All clear.
Base, flag nine,
I'm at Angels 5.
I don't have a tally on the target.
Repeat, I don't have a tally on the target.
They're gone, there's no one down there.
Damn it!
This ain't right, bro. Nobody said
nothing about being locked in no truck.
Tell me about it.
Hey. Hey!
Yo! Where do you think
they're taking us?
Don't matter.
We're all just along
for the ride now.
Welcome to Mexico, boys.
There are helicopters
and surveillance cameras
that scan for heat
signatures at the border.
But there are blind spots that I
can guide you through via satellite.
There can be no margin of error, so
you must follow my every direction.
Any questions?
I thought Fenix
was gonna be here.
He'll meet you
out there.
All right, everybody, sync up.
Good luck, gentlemen.
Satellite linkup engaged.
Keep proceeding northbound
at current speed.
Stay close to Fenix.
He'll lead you across.
I got a heat signature
northbound along Legardo Ravine.
Thermal imaging window on the Mexico
side's gonna be down for about 45 seconds.
Get the camera on it.
Manual override. Rerouting
camera to designated coordinates.
Hurry it up.
You guys have been tagged.
Shit.
Toretto,
get back in formation.
Reimaging commencing.
I don't see anything.
They're gone.
Get the helicopters
to cover it.
Base, we're 40 seconds
out from Legardo Ravine.
They're sending
a helicopter.
You have 30 seconds.
North 32' 33',
west 116' 49'.
The window
is closing fast.
You need to get out of there
before they send ground support.
Fifteen seconds.
Base,
target is at two miles.
You're running
out of time.
You need to get out now!
Base, we're at north
32' 33', west 116' 49'.
We have no visuaI contact. Roll
ground units for confirmation.
Sloppy!
Very sloppy!
What are you doing, man?
Come on.
Get out.
Come on, man.
Come on, today, man.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, don't touch me.
Hey, don't touch me, man!
Hey, I said don't touch me, man!
Hey, look, dawg, don't
put your hands on me.
Hey,
Malik, chill, bro.
Yo, man, what's up
with your boy?
Hey, boss man!
What did you say?
I said only pussies
run nitrometh.
You looked under my hood?
I'm talking to you.
Got something on your mind?
'70 Plymouth.
Her name was Letty.
Yo.
Where's my money?
And somebody
wrecked her car.
I wrecked her car.
You remember her face?
Huh?
'Cause I don't.
Last time I saw it,
it was burning.
Now what?
I'm going to enjoy
what happens next.
Dom, get in!
Get in! Come on!
Come on! Get in the fucking
car! Let's go! Hurry up!
What
have you got, Trinh?
We're contacting agencies
in multiple countries.
Unfortunately, most of them have to
manually scan their prints for us to upload.
O'Conner's on line five.
And, sir,
you should see this.
Thank you.
Talk to me, O'Conner.
Where the hell have you
been? I got the shipment.
"I got the shipment,"
or "we got the shipment"?
What are you
talking about?
Traffic cams in the area picked up
pictures of you and Toretto together.
Listen to me, O'Conner. Bring in
the shipment and bring in Toretto.
But I thought the point was to get
Braga. We got an opportunity here.
Brian, the clock
stopped ticking.
Bring them in.
Are we clear?
O'Conner?
So this is what
$60 million looks like.
Yeah, we got to
get you to a doctor.
We got to find
a place to hide this.
I got a spot.
502, wet reckless.
I need a 48-hour hold.
Out back.
Any spot you can find.
You sure about this?
Yeah. The last place they'll check,
their own impound yard. Trust me.
You know,
I've been thinking,
when you blew up your car back
there, you blew up mine, too.
Yeah?
Yeah.
So now you owe me
a 10-second car.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Now we're even.
Is this your way of
keeping me away from him?
You're the only one I could
call. He's my brother, of course.
The bullet's not in there.
I'm gonna clean it and stitch
it up. It's going to hurt.
I bet you're going
to enjoy this.
A little.
Want some of this?
Yeah.
It's spicy.
I like it hot.
Dom, what are you doing?
You reached first,
you have to say grace.
Thank you, Lord,
for blessing this table.
With food, family
and friendship.
You asked me
why I let Dom go.
I think it's because
at that moment,
I respected him
more than I did myself.
Yeah.
One thing I learned from Dom is that nothing
really matters unless you have a code.
And what's your code,
Brian?
I'm working on it.
Shit. Hey, Dom.
When were you gonna tell
me? Dom, what are you doing?
When were you gonna tell me
you were running Letty?
Let me explain...
When were you gonna...
Dom, stop!
You don't understand.
I don't understand?
Stop!
She did it for...
Dom, stop!
Dom, stop it!
Please stop!
She did it for you, Dom!
She did it for you!
Letty came to me to clear your name
in exchange for bringing down Braga.
She just wanted you
to come home!
I'm sorry, Dom!
I'm sorry!
You better have one hell of an
explanation. You disobeyed a direct order.
Where's the shipment?
It's safe.
Look, we could use the shipment
to parade in front of the media,
get a few hundred pounds
of heroin off the street,
but Braga's just gonna send another
shipment next week and the week after that.
Let's use the shipment
to lure Braga out
and lop the head off
a multi-billion dollar cartel.
And how do you
suggest we do that?
A hand-to-hand
exchange with Braga.
He'll never show.
He can't afford not to.
You got a plan?
There's a price.
We bag Braga,
you let Toretto walk.
Yes?
It's Dom.
I was just
thinking about you.
You know, when I gave you my
number, I was hoping you'd call.
But not under
these circumstances.
What circumstances?
Me being alive?
Don't take it personally.
It's just business.
I got some business
of my own.
Get Campos.
It's them.
Uh-huh.
Was that how Braga inspires
loyalty? Killing his drivers?
One can always
find more drivers.
It's just good business.
I want to trade.
Braga doesn't negotiate.
Fine.
You explain to him how all of a sudden
$60 million worth of product disappears.
I know that can't
be good for business.
What do you want?
Six million cash,
delivered by Braga himself.
I don't like being shot at.
I ain't gonna put my neck out again
unless he's got something to lose, too.
He'll never go for it.
Either I deal with Braga,
or you do.
When and where?
Sir, players are onsite. Holding
positions at the perimeter.
All right. Listen up.
Everybody stay frosty.
We don't move a muscle untiI
O'Conner gives the signaI.
When he gets the money,
you know what to do.
Well, the good news is,
when we get this guy,
you walk out of here
a free man.
Is that what
they told you?
Yeah, that's the deal.
You still put milk and
cookies out for Santa Claus?
Yeah.
Here.
In case things go shitty.
Just like old times?
Yeah.
You dropped something.
That's what you wanted, right? Dom...
He's harmless.
Don't worry about him.
And he's really
sorry about Letty.
Where's our stuff?
You mean the stuff that
used to be in here, right?
Well, you'll see it when we
see Braga. That was the deal.
No worries.
Braga keeps his word.
$2 million.
You get the rest
when I get my property.
Stasiak.
We got a match.
The fingerprint's
Braga's 100%.
Just waiting on faciaI
confirmation via fax.
I got
a question for you.
You wearing pink when you were
clawing your way out of el barrio?
Order all agents
to move in.
We got confirmation. Primary
suspect wearing gray suit.
Let's move.
Sir, O'Conner hasn't
given us the signal yet.
What part of that didn't you understand?
We just got confirmation. Do it!
FBl AGENT: Secure primary
suspect in gray suit. Repeat!
Secure primary suspect
in gray suit.
You're thinking what
I'm thinking, right?
He ain't Braga.
Oh, shit.
Drop your weapons!
FBl!
Get down!
Get out of here!
Get out of here, Dom!
Run him down.
Go!
Campos is Braga!
Come on.
Approaching primary target.
Primary suspect is secure.
He was under your nose
the whole time.
Now Braga's escaped.
Toretto's heading south, probably
long across the border by now.
Do you have any idea the kind
of trouble you're in, O'Conner?
I was doing my job.
He ain't the first bad guy you
helped escape the law's grasp.
As of now, you're being
taken off active duty,
until this house can
mount a formal inquiry.
What about Braga?
That's no longer
your concern.
We now know where Braga is, right?
Customs tracked him via satellite
to his home base in Tecali, Mexico.
Mexico is out
of our jurisdiction.
The fact is
the brass will be so busy holding
press conferences over the seizure,
we'll skate
under the radar.
I thought we signed on
to do the right thing.
Everyone's looking for you.
I'm right here.
It's nice to see you've
gone with the times
and switched to electronic
fuel injection. Looks good.
Buster became a gearhead.
I'm going with you.
I don't plan on
bringing anyone back.
I know.
Hit that throttle.
Hey.
How do you say goodbye
to your only brother?
You don't.
I thought you weren't
gonna show up.
You saved my life.
I'm willing to
return the favor.
This will help
get you to Braga.
Dom.
Going in there
is suicide.
I have no choice.
You must have
loved her very much.
So this is where
my jurisdiction ends.
And this is where
mine begins.
You ain't forgiven.
You boys want
to arrest me?
No, we're beyond that.
You can't buy your way out of this one.
You and me...
You and me,
we're not so different.
You're no hero.
You're right.
And that's why you're going
back across the border.
But Fenix is mine.
You got it.
Shit!
You'll make it a couple of
miles out, if you're lucky.
You know where
you're going?
You want to borrow my GPS?
Where are your boys at?
Are they going
to show up or what?
Careful what you ask for.
Just stop.
Just stop the car.
Right behind you.
Dom, head to the tunnel.
Let's use the tunnel.
Get out of here, Brian.
You sure you know where
the tunnels are? You sure?
Yeah. I'd hold on.
This might hurt.
You're in
my world now, baby!
That's it, baby!
End of the road.
Now what?
Game over.
No, no, no.
Come on!
Hey!
Get me out of here!
Pussy.
Let me see that.
Yeah.
Just keep pressure there.
You'll be all right.
You gotta get
out of here.
I ain't running anymore.
I gotta ask you
something.
Yeah?
You know I would have won that
race if you didn't cheat, right?
You hit your head hard.
Don't make me laugh.
All rise.
Please be seated.
Please rise,
Mr. Toretto.
I've listened
to the testimony
and taken into
special consideration
Agent O'Conner's appeal of
clemency on behalf of Mr. Toretto.
That his actions directly
resulted in the apprehension
of known drug
trafficker Arturo Braga.
However,
this judiciary
finds that
one right does not make up
for a lifetime worth of wrongs.
And as such,
I find that I am forced to level the
maximum sentence under California law.
Dominic Toretto,
you are hereby sentenced
to serve 25 years to life
at the Lompoc maximum
security prison system
without the possibility
of early parole.
This court is adjourned.