Nice ride.
It does the job.
What job,
delivering pizzas?
Well, it's not the ride,
it's the rider.
What the hell
was that?
What?
Hey!
You talking to my girl?
Oh, shit. Here we go.
Yeah.
She was just
admiring my ride.
"My ride. "
My grandma's Buick
could smoke
that piece of shit,
trailer trash.
Well, what about
your daddy's Viper?
This beast's
got 500 horsepower
and a Borla exhaust system.
It does 0 to 60
in like 4.3 seconds...
That's about right.
That's about right. Yeah.
Wow.
You can read the brochure.
What a pitch, baby.
What a pitch. I like that.
What's he gonna do?
Let's make it happen.
Bring it.
I got your...
I got your back.
Why don't you nice boys
let your cars do the talking?
I only race
for pink slips.
This car goes for 80 grand.
What would I do with a broken-ass
piece of shit like that?
How about me?
Winner gets me.
Cut it, let's cut it.
Let's go, go, go, go!
Blast-off, baby!
First one out
the other side...
It's time.
Let's go!
Ready, boys? Make it interesting, Clay.
Shit!
Yeah!
I thought
you loved me.
Oh, well.
What the hell?
Guess I got
a new date for prom.
Clay, stop the car!
Shut up!
Stop it!
Clay, please stop!
Please stop!
Can I get
a copy of that?
You think
this is a joke, huh?
You see Ken and Barbie
over there?
They're gonna walk out of here
without even a slap on the wrist.
Mommy and Daddy
are too hooked up.
But I like
screw-ups like you.
You know why?
'Cause you're 100%
guaranteed conviction.
Where's my car?
I crushed it.
You did what?
Sit down! You're done.
Easy, easy.
You're done. You
understand me? You're done.
And all before your eighteenth
birthday. Now sit down.
Sean.
What the hell were
you thinkin', huh?
Mrs. Boswell? Please.
It's, uh, it's Miss.
Officer, is it, um,
illegal to smoke in here?
It's a tough state.
And it's
a pretty clear-cut case.
He'll be lucky if they don't
try him as an adult.
This is our third town
in two years.
Your son's got two priors
for reckless driving,
willful destruction
of property.
This makes it
strike three.
They're definitely gonna want
to get him off the streets.
Well, there's
just got to be another way.
So, where are we
moving this time?
We are not
moving anywhere.
Sean.
I thought you were
gonna be here on the 7th.
Today is the 7th.
Well, look,
just hold on one second.
Come on in.
This is it.
You know, Sean, I was,
I was gonna be there.
But your mom,
she said the 7th, see,
and we're a day
ahead of you in Japan.
Well, you're here now,
and that's good.
So, how is your mom?
Where do I sleep?
Now, Sean, you know
she had no other choice.
I mean, it was
either this or juvie hall,
I mean, you just
can't keep moving away
every time
you get into trouble.
Worked for you.
Look, neither of us
asked for this.
But I promised your mom
I'd take care of you.
So you just go by the
rules her and I agreed to,
and I'm sure
you'll manage just fine.
Rules?
Yeah, rules. Real simple.
You go to school,
you come back here
right after.
And I don't
want to see or hear
about you
anywhere near a car.
Here,
the bedroom is yours.
Make yourself comfortable.
Lights out in 10.
You got to be kiddin'.
Wrong train.
I'm new here.
Boswell, yes, ma'am.
Japanese food
is like the Army.
Don't ask, don't tell.
Name's Twinkie.
Hey, I noticed
you ain't have a laptop.
Yeah?
I'll hook you up.
Half price.
No, I'm cool.
60% off. Hmm?
Since we're both army
brats and everything.
I ain't got no cash,
man.
And I ain't
an army brat.
All right, all right.
Well, what about
a cell phone, huh?
Everybody needs
a cell phone.
No offense,
but I'm probably
not gonna be here
long enough
to remember your name.
Then you gonna need some new
shoes to book town with, man.
You like Michael Jordan?
I love Michael Jordan.
Check this out.
Brand new Jordans.
Not even out yet.
LeBron James couldn't even
get his hands on those.
You selling that
Sparco steering wheel?
Hell, no.
That's mine right there.
Man, I even paid
retail for it.
What you drive?
My ride?
Yeah.
My ride's one of a kind.
Show me.
Thought you
weren't stickin' around.
All right.
My life be like
Ooh Aah, Ooh Ooh
It's times like these
that make me say
Lord if you see me
please come my way
Leavin' bread crumbs
for when I stray
Rely on sacrifice
and the price you paid
Feel me like a fingertip
Slamming, huh?
Look at that car.
Tryin' not to quench your
fire with the things I do
At least let me drive.
Y'all better have some
real cars around here.
Okay, I see
somebody got jokes, huh?
Well, all right.
I don't know if you're
ready for them, though.
You look a little nervous.
What up, Tosh?
I wonder if you know
How they live in Tokyo
If you see me then you mean
it Then you know you have to go
Tick, Tick, Tick
I wonder if you know
How they live in Tokyo
If you see me then you mean
it Then you know you have to go
For when you
blow your wad, man.
Tick, Tick, Tick
Hear that?
It's still not right
for the way I drive.
I don't need a computer to tell
me about my throttle response.
Okay.
Then we're done here.
You wouldn't have
that problem with a V8.
Boys.
All they care about is
who's got the biggest engine.
I'm a guy.
It's in my DNA.
So y'all race
with these things, huh?
Cute little toys.
You know, I almost didn't recognize
you without your slippers on.
Don't you mean uwabaki?
Neela, right?
You're a quick learner.
So, where you from,
anyway?
Here.
No, I mean,
not where you live.
Where'd you come from?
Does it really matter
where I'm from?
Who's the tourist?
What's with you
and the schoolgirls, D?
You're moving up
in the world.
You gotta
elevate your company.
Wednesday, Wednesday,
meet Thursday.
God. Girl.
Ladies, hold that thought, all right?
All right, beautiful.
Hold up.
Hey!
He was just leaving.
I'm sorry.
I don't speak Japanese.
Understand that?
Gaijin?
Takashi.
We were just talking.
This isn't your scene.
That word you called me,
gaijin or something or other,
what does that mean
exactly?
Means, turn around,
keep walking.
That's exactly
what we gonna do.
Come on, man,
let's roll.
Yo, look, man,
he's yakuza.
Now, see, that's funny,
'cause I thought this
was, like, a free country
where a girl could talk
to whoever she wants.
You know who I am,
boy?
Yeah. You're like the Justin
Timberlake of Japan, right?
Leave.
Damn, man.
You know yakuza? The Mafia?
Look, sorry, DK- san.
Monkey didn't have
his banana today.
Hey, D, let's go.
It's time to race.
Hey, good luck, Timberlake.
You're the one that's lucky,
'cause I'm about to race.
Then let's race.
With what, huh?
Your skateboard?
Easy to sound cocky
when you got no ride.
Take mine.
Let's race.
What? I wanna see
what the kid's got.
Can he drive?
You know what DK
stands for?
Donkey Kong?
Drift King.
Drift?
What do you mean,
drift?
Still need
a dictionary?
You know that
real famous painting?
The one of the woman
who's smiling all the time?
The Mona Lisa.
Right, right, right.
Mona Lisa.
Well, look, man,
this car right here's
like the Mona Lisa
of the drift world.
Han rebuilt this bad boy
from ground up.
We talking forged pistons,
bigger turbo,
new rods, new crankshaft.
Hey, man, Han's labor
ain't cheap, man, you feel me?
Well, if I needed a 30-second
lesson on how to drift...
All right, look, man, there's lots
of ways you can do this, all right?
Hand braking
is the easiest,
so the first thing
I want you to do,
I want you
to rip that e-brake.
All right,
after you rip the e-brake,
then I want you
to power over.
You know what?
Just don't mess up Mona,
all right?
All right.
Ready.
Set.
Go!
I told you.
Damn it!
Don't leave town.
Do you know
what time it is?
I thought
it was around 7:00.
You know,
US is a few hours behind.
Looks like the party
was better here, anyway.
Have you been racing, Sean?
You're out of here.
Go ahead.
You don't get it,
do you?
You have
nowhere else to go.
If it doesn't
work out here,
you're going to jail.
Do you get that?
This isn't a game.
And I'm gonna tell you
one more time,
if you're gonna
live under my roof,
you're gonna go by
my rules or get out.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
Get in.
I'll get you your money.
Why you talking
like you have a choice?
There's a guy in there
with a paw
that owes me some money.
A paw?
Go get me my money.
Okay.
Han said,
okane.
Han said, okane.
Let's go.
You're in the pickup
and delivery business now.
I might call you once a week
or once an hour.
I don't care
if you're sick as a dog
or in bed with Beyoncé.
I call, you show.
Only if you teach me
how to drift.
This ain't a negotiation.
I wasn't negotiating.
What's he doing here?
He's paying me back for
that crumpled beer can
sitting in my garage.
Hope
he's not driving.
Gaijin.
When is your next race?
I'd really like to be there.
Why not be in it?
You heard me.
Ready to lose
another car, Han?
I'm ready to take that
'86 Corolla off your hands.
All right.
Put up the '72 Skyline.
Done.
What do you think,
Morimoto, huh?
Get him out of here.
We have business
to discuss.
Your shipment's late.
Since when are you
so worried about the details?
When is
the shipment arriving, Han?
Just sit pretty
and let me handle it.
Hey, Dad, it's me.
Uh, I had to
stay after school
for some
extracurricular activities.
So I'll be home
a little later.
Sir.
You really need to stop
following me around.
What are you
doing here?
I thought I'd stop by
and ask your boyfriend
for some drifting lessons.
Trust me.
You don't wanna be
a part of this world.
It's good enough for you.
You don't know
anything about me.
Well, why don't you
think I know?
'Cause I'm a gaijin?
An outsider?
Let me guess.
You're an army brat
who moved around a lot.
Your mama and daddy
was never home.
So you walked around
pissed off all the time.
And now you found your family
with these drift nuts.
Zero for one, cowboy.
Why can't you go find
a nice Japanese girl
like the rest of
the white guys around here?
Mamacita, oh my God,
I think your on fire
Do you want me
to get you water
Is everything okay
back there?
I can handle DK.
I thought he's yakuza.
His uncle's yakuza.
He's just playing gangster
in his little storage room.
But I need him.
He keeps Uncle Kamata
from poking around too much.
What do you mean?
Well, his uncle gets
a piece of the action
from everyone
on his turf.
We're on his turf.
50% of something
is better than
100% of nothing.
So have you raced DK?
Why not? Is he that good?
What's the point
of a race?
To see if I'm better
than the other guy.
Just proves you're faster,
that's all.
If I were to race,
it would have to be
for something important.
Or why else do it at all?
Why are you
letting me race?
'Cause you're
DK's kryptonite.
And you owe me a car.
She wanna break it down, break it
down, break it down, break it down
She want some reggaeton,
reggaeton, reggaeton, reggaeton
She wanna break it down, break it
down, break it down, break it down
She want some reggaeton,
reggaeton, reggaeton, reggaeton
Oh, shit.
I make ya smile right
What the...
Police cars here are
only factory-tuned.
You can do
better than 180 k,
they can't catch you,
so they don't even try.
'Cause its just nice you lookin
different sayin' to yourself
You know what?
I'm beginning to like
this country already.
When my chain keep linkin'
like Christmas lights
Mamacita, oh my God
I think your on fire
Do you want me
to get you water
Danny!
You're looking good.
Disco.
We gotta catch up.
Get you a drink on me, huh?
Let's go.
Aha. Easy now, ladies.
Come on.
Hey Mami, you sexy,
hey Mami, you sexy
What's up?
How you doing?
Hey, baby.
Hey Mami, you sexy,
hey Mami, you sexy
Hey Mami, you sexy
Can I get that number
Big hot pockets,
feya, ugly
Corny, busted,
chopped, straight fugly
British guys playing rugby
Brooklyn boys
who wanna thug me
Skanky, cranky,
foogly, oogly
Slammin dudes
that wanna do me
G'Doonk G'Doonk,
skoonky, flavors
Keep your hands
off the kid, girls.
He's underage.
Country boys and them boys
in the city
Ladies, ladies, ladies.
Disneyland
for grownups, huh?
All these girls, man,
they look like...
What, models?
Check it out.
See,
Tokyo is the fashion capital
on this side of the planet,
all right?
Now, imagine
you been posing all day.
I mean,
that's a lot of hard work.
Not only do you get tired,
but, on top of that,
you wanna have a little fun,
but you can't
'cause you don't even know
nobody in town.
And most of
the guys around here are
too chicken shit
to even try picking up one.
So what do you do?
Man, you talk to the little
dude who makes you laugh.
Yeah.
Look, man, I don't just think
outside the box.
I tear it up.
That's my thing.
Yo.
You should
slow it down papi
You sound like
a carbon copy
Sean!
But you're
just plain sloppy
Hey Mami, you sexy
It's dipset Bitch
There it go
Baby don't stop now
There you go
Damn shorty look good
And I'm thinkin' about
gettin' at her
Okay,
time to whistle at her
Ay girl,
you make my whistle blow
There it go
Bring it here baby
Top down
and I'm at it again
It's hot now
and I'm at it to win
You heard me
Who want it with me
Nobody wanna it with me
Oh, I'm so fly
Oh, Mami, Back up
Move it till you feel
something hard on your back
The red Evo's yours.
If u want it come and get it
I ain't kiddin' I'm with it
Here it go, go
So, girl,
let me see you get low
There it go
Yeah, just like that
What do you mean?
You're representing
me now.
What you think, I'm gonna
let you roll in a Hyundai?
So, girl,
let me see you get low
Oh, man.
Damn it.
My mother,
she's blind in one eye
and she can drift
better than that.
Han,
where did you find this guy?
Will someone please teach
this guy how to drift?
Is that yours?
Sure is.
What happened?
I don't know. I found
it this way at the base.
It's got potential.
Yeah, maybe. We'll see.
You know, Sean,
the Japanese have a saying.
"The nail that sticks out
gets hammered. "
You're gonna be late.
Sean!
Come on, man, you broke it.
Hey, whoa, whoa.
There must be
a misunderstanding.
Out of my way,
or you're next.
Take it easy.
Look, man, I don't
do refunds, all right?
Okay, let's go, then!
Let's go!
Touch me again...
Here.
Try not to break
this one.
Say, man!
What the hell is
wrong with you, huh?
Now everybody's gonna want
exchanges around here.
Damn!
Not easy saving the day,
is it?
Maybe you could give me
some pointers sometime.
You're doing
all right.
Thanks.
Hey.
Yeah?
Sorry about the other night.
Your life isn't
any of my business.
It's okay.
Foul!
Ain't no damn foul.
That was a foul.
Yo, you in my face.
Hey, Han,
sort this wanker out.
A wanker?
What do I look like,
a zebra?
So, how did you end up
over here, anyway?
Well, you know
those old Westerns
where the cowboys
make a run for the border?
This is my Mexico.
Why'd you let me
race with your car?
You knew
I was gonna wreck it.
Why not?
'Cause it's a lot of money.
I have money.
It's trust and character
I need around me.
You know, who you
choose to be around you
lets you know
who you are.
And one car in exchange
for knowing
what a man's made of,
that's a price
I can live with.
Look at all those
people down there.
They follow the rules,
for what?
They're letting
fear lead them.
What happens if they don't?
Life's simple.
You make choices
and you don't look back.
So,
if you don't drift to win,
what do you drift for?
You really
want to know?
Yeah.
Okay. Let's go.
There's no "wax on,
wax off" with drifting.
Learn by doin' it.
The first drifters
invented drifting
out here in the mountains
by feeling it.
So feel it.
Again!
What's in this bag?
You'll see.
How much you got?
Keep going, keep going.
I'm so good, man, I could
sell rubbers to a monk.
Again.
Watch it. Watch it.
Not too early, now.
Go, go, go, go!
Don't lose it! Don't lose it!
Hey, Han.
Hey, Twink.
Get this man a bunk.
Pleasure doing business.
Yeah, baby. I told you.
I told you, didn't I?
It's actually not bad.
I didn't even have
to put ketchup on it.
See,
I'm not a total gaijin.
I hate that word.
It's what they used
to call me when I was a kid.
I thought
you were born here.
Well, "outsider" can mean
many different things.
My mom died when I was 10.
She came out here
from Australia
when she
finished high school.
And all I know
about her is that
she went to work
in a hostess bar.
DK's grandmother took me in.
Well, my parents
split up when I was three.
Me and Mom
moved around a lot.
Mostly 'cause of me.
Well,
it was all 'cause of me.
Kind of made myself
an outsider, you know,
without even
thinking about it.
But I realize now,
outsider or insider,
it doesn't really matter.
All that matters is knowing
what you really want
and going after it.
We used to come up here
when we were kids.
Even before we could drive
we'd cut class, sneak out,
come up here, and watch
the older kids drift.
Things were different
back then.
Once I got my license,
I practically lived up here.
Back then, kids just drove
whatever they had.
You know, we just made do.
No one bothered us.
The day I got my license
is the day I got
my first speeding ticket.
The day after that,
I won my first race.
I beat this rich kid
by three lengths.
I gotta admit, it felt good.
It felt like...
Like everything else
just disappears.
No past and no future.
No problems.
Just the moment.
Boy needs to chill.
Hey, Twink,
I'm gonna grab another set.
Whoa! Whoa,
whoa, whoa! Another set?
No. Look, that was
your third set today.
I mean,
them tires ain't cheap.
DK, grab a chair.
We're about to
roast some marshmallows.
Yo, come on, man, look...
Stay away from her,
or the only thing you'll
be driving is a wheelchair.
Find yourself a new driver.
I'm all right.
What'd you expect?
You didn't just
play with fire,
you soaked
the matches in gasoline.
It's over.
All this over a gaijin?
I am a gaijin.
You've changed, DK.
You say I've changed.
But we're not so different,
you and I.
We're both products
of fuckups, aren't we?
They say your mom
was the best trick
in all of Kabukicho
back in the day.
Leave my mother
out of this.
If we hadn't taken you in,
you'd be just like her,
doing anything
for a buck.
Think anyone would take
a second look at you
if it wasn't
for your uncle?
We're the same, Neela.
Difference is I know who I am
and where I belong.
Do you know
who you are?
where you belong?
Hey.
Come on.
Hey, brother.
I vouched for you!
Put my reputation
on the line for you!
We were partners!
You think you can keep
your side deals from me?
Come on.
We ain't in the Boy Scouts.
This is what we do.
Takashi!
What about now? Hmm?
Is this what we do?
Man, you need me.
You'd still be
shaking down teahouses
for chump change
if it wasn't for me.
Get in!
Go! Go! Go!
Come on.
Sean. Sean!
Takashi.
I wouldn't do that
if I were you.
Okay.
I'll go with you.
Neela.
See you when
Daddy's not around.
I'm putting you
on a plane tonight.
Dad...
Sean, don't argue with me.
I did this.
I can't run away.
I can't.
Sean,
I'm your father.
I'm responsible
for your well-being.
And I'm responsible
for my mess.
I gotta do this.
Can you understand that?
At least you're not
redoing my mistakes.
You all right, man?
We're leaving town.
Look, I know some people...
I can't do it, Twink.
Look, DK wants your head.
All right?
And the trouble you
just made for Kamata?
You're done here, bro.
Maybe I should
talk to Kamata.
What?
DK answers to him.
I know I just
didn't hear that.
I gotta end this.
I'm gonna go talk to him.
What, are you crazy, huh?
Han is dead, all right!
Plus, you can't just walk
into Kamata's place, man!
It's all I got.
Something I think Han
would've wanted you to have.
What's this?
You're gonna need it
if you're gonna make it
out of Kamata's place
alive.
Don't you need it?
No, it's cool.
Look, I'll figure it out.
Sean.
You need to leave.
You came to the wrong place.
I didn't come here
to see you.
Takashi.
You think
you can walk in here,
dump some cash and walk out?
I know I'm only returning
what belonged to you
in the first place, sir.
But that's not
why I really came.
I came here
to apologize.
I know your nephew and I have
embarrassed ourselves badly.
Sir, I'm here to offer you
a peaceful solution.
How do you plan
to accomplish that?
A race.
DK and I have caused
nothing but problems for you,
for us.
And I'm asking you
to allow us to settle this,
once and for all.
We race
and the loser leaves town
for good.
I've already beat
this piece of shit once!
Good.
Then it should be easy.
The cops
took all the cars.
Hey!
That's why she's spitting.
We almost there, Twink.
Couple more tweaks.
It's not the car
I'm worried about, man.
DK picked this road
for a reason.
This is his mountain.
He's the only one to ever
make it to the bottom.
Yeah!
Yes!
Come on.
Yeah! Come on!
Come on, Sean.
Let's go! Let's go!
Sean, you the boss. Let's go.
Damn! Come on, man!
That ain't right.
Yeah, baby!
That's what
I'm talking about, man.
I told you!
I wonder if you know
How they live in Tokyo
If you see me then you mean
it Then you know you have to go
Fast and furious
Tick, Tick, Tick
Hey, yo, Sean!
Yo, Sean!
Hey, check this out, man.
This dude over here
wanna race the new DK.
Heard he's been beating
everybody around Asia, too.
Not tonight, Twinkie.
Said he knew Han.
Said Han was family.
All right.
Let's race.
Nice ride.
I won it from my friend Han,
a few years ago.
I didn't know he was
into American muscle.
He was when
he was rolling with me.
You know this ain't
no 10-second race.
I got nothing but time.
You ready, kid?
Come on, Sean! Come on!
Ready!
Set!
Go!