Ana, take my car.
I gave you the recorder, right?
Oh, yes.
And you have all the questions?
Yes.
And you know where you're going?
Yes, I do have a GPS.
And a 4.0 GPA.
I can figure it out.
Are you wearing that?
Okay, maybe a little
less talking,
more eating.
How about that?
Wow.
Miss Kavanagh?
May I take your coat?
Oh. Yeah. Um...
She's...
Okay, so...
Mr. Grey will see you now.
Okay.
This way, please.
Okay. Mr. Grey has a
conference call at 11:15.
Right this way.
Miss Kavanagh.
Are you all right?
Christian Grey.
I'm Anastasia Steele.
Um, Miss Kavanagh has the flu,
so she asked me to fill in.
I see.
So, you're studying
journalism as well.
No, English Lit.
Um...
Kate's my roommate.
As I said,
I only have 10 minutes.
Please, have a seat,
Miss Steele.
Okay.
Thank you.
Ready?
Whenever you are.
Okay. Um...
So, this is for the special
graduation issue
of the student newspaper.
Yes, I'm giving the commencement
address at this year's ceremony.
You are?
I mean, um...
I know.
Uh..."You are very young to
have amassed such an empire.
"To what do you owe your..."
To what do I owe my success?
Yep.
Seriously?
Yes.
Business is about people.
And I've always
been good at people.
What motivates them,
what incentivizes them,
what inspires them.
Um, maybe you're just lucky.
I've always found
that the harder I work,
the more luck I seem to have.
The key to my success has been in
identifying talented individuals
and harnessing their efforts.
So, you're a control freak?
Oh, I exercise control in
all things, Miss Steele.
Okay. Um...
"Your company is
involved primarily
"in the telecommunications
sector,
"yet you also invest in
numerous agricultural projects,
"including several in Africa.
"Is that something that you
feel passionate about?
"Feeding the world's poor?"
It's smart business.
You don't agree?
I don't know enough about it.
I just wonder if
perhaps your heart might be a bit
bigger than you want to let on?
There are some people who say
that I don't have a heart at all.
Why would they say that?
Because they know me well.
Go on.
Um..."Do you have any
interests outside of work?"
I enjoy various
physical pursuits.
You're unmarried.
Oh.
You were adopted at age four.
That's a matter
of public record.
I'm sorry, I didn't...
Do you have an actual
question, Miss Steele?
Yeah, sorry.
"Are you gay?"
It's written here, I'm just...
No, Anastasia.
I'm not gay.
I apologize, Mr. Grey.
Kate can be a little...
Intrusive?
Curious.
What about you?
Why don't you ask me something
that you want to know?
Earlier, you said that there are
some people who know you well.
Why do I get the feeling
that, that is not true?
Mr. Grey, your next meeting
is in the conference room.
Cancel, please.
We're not finished here.
Yes, sir.
No... I'm...
I can go. It's fine.
I would like to
know more about you.
There's really not much
to know about me.
You said you're
an English major?
Tell me,
was it Charlotte Brontë,
Jane Austen, or Thomas Hardy
who first made you fall
in love with literature?
Hardy.
I would have guessed
Jane Austen.
What are your plans
after you graduate?
I'm just trying to
get through finals right now.
And then?
And then I was planning
on moving here, to Seattle,
with Kate.
We offer an excellent
internship program.
I don't think I'd fit in here.
Look at me.
I am.
I hope you got
everything you needed.
I... I think you only
answered four questions.
Anastasia.
Christian.
Holy cow.
Um...
Before you say anything...
You're a goddess.
This is perfect.
What?
I just got his e-mail.
He answered every question.
So, what was he like?
Um...
He was fine.
"Fine"?
Just fine?
Um, he was really polite,
and he was courteous,
and very formal,
and clean.
"Clean"?
I mean, he was very smart.
And intense.
It was kind of intimidating.
I can understand
the fascination.
Uh-huh.
Why are you
looking at me like that?
Like what?
Okay.
I'm gonna make a sandwich.
Do you want one?
No, thanks.
You have to admit,
he's ridiculously hot.
I'm sure if you
are attracted to that
sort of human, then...
The hot type of human?
I asked him if he was gay.
That was in your questions.
Why would you do that to me?
Because whenever he's
in the society pages,
he's never been photographed with a woman.
So, naturally...
Well, maybe he just wants to keep
his private life private, Kate.
And now you're defending him.
I'm terminating
this conversation.
Too bad we don't have
some original stills
of your hot, clean
27-year-old billionaire.
The camera loves him
almost as much as you do.
Okay, I wasn't hungry,
but now I am.
Thank you.
I love you.
"I declared I could not change,
"yet you tell me to my face
"I shall change soon.
"And what a distortion
in your judgment,
"what a perversity
in your ideas..."
Ana. I've been looking for you.
What's up?
Guess what.
What?
Portland Place is going to exhibit
my photographs next month.
Oh, my God.
Congratulations!
That's so good!
Solo show, corazón.
Can we celebrate later? Because
I'm really late for work.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You got it.
But, um...
Hold on.
Thank you.
You're my hero.
I'll see you later.
Okay.
Mom, I'm at work.
Can I call you back?
Oh, no, wait.
I called for a reason.
Bob broke his foot playing
golf, of all things.
God. Is he okay?
Is he in a lot of pain?
Who can tell with the man?
He calls the paramedics
for a blister.
It means, though, we won't be
able to fly in for graduation.
Really?
You don't wanna just come alone?
You don't have to bring Bob.
Ah. And leave Tiger Woods
to fend for himself?
You do understand.
Don't you, darling?
Yeah. Yeah, it's fine.
Um, I really have to go, okay?
I love you, Ana.
I know. I love you, too.
Oh, God.
Ana.
Could you give me
a hand out back?
Uh, yeah.
I'll be right there.
I thought it was you.
What the...
What a pleasant surprise,
Miss Steele.
Just "Ana."
You're in here.
I was in the area on business.
I needed to pick
up a few things.
Are you free?
Yeah.
What can I help you with?
Do you stock cable ties?
Cable ties, yes. We do.
I can show you, if you want.
Please lead the way,
Miss Steele.
Just "Ana."
Is that it?
Masking tape.
Are you redecorating?
No.
Um, we have two-inch
and one-inch.
But the truly
self-respecting handyman
will have both in his toolbox.
Of course he will.
Mmm-hmm.
It's rare to find
a connoisseur these days.
Do you want anything else?
Yes.
Rope.
That's impressive.
Are you a Girl Scout?
Um, no.
Organized group activities
aren't really my thing.
So what is your "thing"?
Um...
I don't know. Books?
Okay.
Rope, tape, cable ties.
You're the complete
serial killer.
Not today.
Anything else?
What would you recommend?
For a do-it-yourselfer?
Um...
Maybe coveralls,
so you protect your clothes.
I could just take
all my clothes off.
Okay.
No clothes.
I mean, no coveralls.
I can't think of anything else.
Well, I guess that's it, then.
Cool.
Thank you for answering
Kate's questions, by the way.
She was thrilled.
I hope she's feeling better.
She is, yeah, much.
She's just having a hard time
clearing a photo of you, I think.
If she'd like an original,
I'm around tomorrow.
You'd be willing to do that?
Yeah.
Want me to bag for you, Ana?
Oh. Uh, no, I'm good.
Thanks, though, Paul.
Okay.
I'm staying
locally at the Heathman.
Call me before 10:00.
About the photos.
Oh.
Yeah, I will.
Enjoy your...
Thanks again
for doing this, Mr. Grey.
I'm happy to help.
Uh, how about we try
a few with a smile?
Or not.
You do realize that he hasn't
stopped looking at you.
He asked me
to go for coffee afterwards.
What?
Kate, shh.
So, is he your boyfriend?
Who?
The photographer.
José?
No.
I saw the way
he was smiling at you.
No, José is more like family.
He's not my boyfriend.
And the guy at the store?
Paul?
No.
Thank you.
You seem nervous.
I find you intimidating.
You should.
Eat.
Not to mention high-handed.
I'm used to getting my own way.
That must get very boring.
Tell me about your family.
My family? Um...
Okay.
My dad died when I was a baby.
So, I was raised by
my stepfather, Ray.
He's amazing.
And your mother?
Um, my mother is on
husband number four.
She's an incurable romantic.
Are you?
Am I a romantic?
Well, I study English Lit.
So, I kind of have to be.
I thought the photo
shoot went well. Right?
Kate seems to be really...
I'm sorry, I can't...
What?
I'll walk you out.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Is that it?
I don't do the girlfriend thing.
What does that even...
Watch it!
I'm not the man for you.
You should steer clear of me.
I have to let you go.
Goodbye, Mr. Grey.
All right, pencils down.
Please take your final exams
to the back of the classroom.
Final grades will be
posted in two weeks.
Hey. You all good?
Yeah. Why wouldn't I be?
We are so partying tonight.
Oh, my God.
This is way too much.
No, this is exactly
the right amount.
You're getting it
all over my face.
That's the idea.
Wow. No, Kate.
Cab's early. Let's go.
Ana, it's a package for you.
"Why didn't you tell
me there was danger?
"Why didn't you warn me?
"Ladies know what
to guard against
"because they read novels that
tell them of these tricks."
That's a quote from
Tess of the D'Urbervilles.
Oh, my God.
These must be from Christian.
Do you... I mean...
These are incredible.
Wow, Grey.
Kate, these are first editions.
I can't.
This is too much.
- I can't accept these.
- I have to send them back.
That's the cab.
Okay, are you ready?
Are you ready to go?
Yes. Yes, very.
Let's get out of here.
- Shots first...
- Shots, shots, shots!
Hold on.
Nobody hold back, either.
Did you do it all?
All right.
With my eyes closed
and left-handed,
I can get this in.
- What?
- Ready?
I gotta pee.
Okay.
Where you going?
I gotta go.
I gotta pee.
Anastasia?
Yeah, this is me.
I'm sending back
your expensive books,
because I already
have copies of those.
Thanks, though,
for the kind gesture.
You're welcome. Where are you?
I'm in line, because I
have to pee really bad.
Anastasia,
have you been drinking?
Yeah.
I have, Mr. Fancy Pants.
You hit the hail on the nead.
I mean,
the head right on the nail.
Listen to me. I want you
to go home right now.
You're so bossy.
"Ana, let's go for coffee."
"No, stay away from me, Ana.
"I don't want you.
Get away."
"Come here, come here."
"Go away."
That's it.
Tell me where you are.
I'm a long way from Seattle.
A long way from you.
Which bar?
What's it called?
I don't know.
I gotta go, though.
Which bar, Ana?
I told him. Right?
I'm sorry, I didn't...
Stay where you are.
I'm coming to get you.
What?
Hello?
Hey.
Oh, thanks.
You okay?
Yeah. I'm just a little
bit more drunk than...
Come here, stay warm.
Oh, it's cool.
I'm good, José. I got it.
I don't know when I'll have
the courage to do this.
Do what?
Ana. I like you.
No.
You do?
Very much.
Oh, my God.
Please.
One kiss.
No, no, no.
José, I don't...
I'm sorry, no.
Dude, she said no!
Christian?
- Don't look at me. Ugh.
- Here.
Nice touch.
I will launder this item.
Let's get you home.
I'm with Kate.
I'll have Elliot tell her.
Who's Elliot?
He's my brother. He's inside,
talking to her right now.
How... I don't...
He was at my hotel with me.
You're still at the Heathman?
Yeah.
Come.
That's your brother?
Not by choice. Let's go.
Wait, what did Kate say?
She warned me to be
on my best behavior.
More like threatened me.
She threatened you?
You're spinning.
I think I'm gonna faint.
What? Now?
Good morning, Anastasia.
How are you feeling?
Better than I deserve.
Did you put me to bed?
Mmm-hmm.
You undressed me?
I didn't have much choice.
Where did you sleep?
Oh, my God.
Did we? We didn't...
Necrophilia is not my thing.
So we just slept, then?
It was a novelty for me, too.
You need to eat.
I had Taylor pick
you up some clothes.
Who's Taylor?
My driver.
Thank you, but you
didn't have to do that.
Yes, I did.
Yours were covered in vomit.
You shouldn't get
drunk like that.
I'm all for testing the limits,
but you put yourself
at risk last night.
I know.
If you were mine, you wouldn't
be able to sit down for a week.
What?
I gotta go take a shower.
Why am I here, Christian?
You're here because I'm
incapable of leaving you alone.
Then don't.
Why did you send me those books?
I thought I owed you an apology.
For what?
For letting you
believe that I...
Listen to me.
I don't do romance.
My tastes are very
singular.
You wouldn't understand.
Enlighten me, then.
You look beautiful.
Taylor has good taste.
What are you doing later?
I'm working at the
hardware store until 7:00.
I'll have Taylor
pick you up then.
I would like to bite that lip.
I think I'd like that, too.
I'm not gonna touch you.
Not until I have
your written consent.
What?
I'll explain later.
Come, I'll take you home.
Fuck the paperwork.
As I was saying...
What is it about elevators?
Hey.
Hi. You must be Ana.
You must be Elliot.
And we must be going.
Elliot...
So awesome to meet you.
Kate's told me a lot about you.
Elliot, find your shoes. Some
of us have work to attend to.
What you're doing with
Mr. Warmth here,
I have no idea.
Laters, baby.
I'll see you tonight.
E-mail me
if something changes.
My computer's broken.
Call, then.
I know you have my number.
Laters, baby.
Elliot seems
like a really nice guy.
Uh-uh. No, no.
We're starting with you.
If you're seeing
him again tonight,
that means that
something happened.
Ana.
Mmm-hmm.
Ana, you have to
tell me what happened.
I have to get ready for work.
We just kissed.
Once.
Only once? That's odd.
Mmm.
"Odd" doesn't even cover it.
Uh-huh.
And a new jacket.
Hmm.
Bye.
Hi. It's Taylor, right?
Good evening, Miss Steele. Mr.
Grey will be joining us there.
Good evening, Anastasia.
Wait. You're flying this?
No escaping now.
November 1-2-2-4. Charlie
Tango, ready to depart.
Roger that, Charlie Tango.
Your flight plan from Portland
to Seattle is cleared.
Seattle?
That's where we're going?
Would you like a drink?
Yes, please.
Wow.
Do you play?
Yes.
Of course you do.
What's this?
It's a non-disclosure
agreement.
It means that you cannot discuss
anything about us with anyone.
I'm afraid my lawyer
insists on it.
I'd never talk to
anyone about us, anyway.
Are you gonna
make love to me now?
Two things.
First, I don't make love.
I fuck.
Hard.
And the second thing?
Come.
It's just beyond this door.
What is?
My play room.
Like your Xbox and stuff?
It's important that you know
you can leave at any time.
Why? What's in there?
I meant what I said.
The helicopter's on standby to
take you whenever you wanna go.
Christian, just open the door.
Oh, my God.
It's called a flogger.
Say something, please.
Do women do this to you?
Or do you...
No, I do this to women.
With women.
Women who want me to.
You're a sadist?
I'm a dominant.
What does that mean?
It means I want you to willingly
surrender yourself to me.
Why would I do that?
To please me.
To please you?
How?
I have rules.
If you follow them,
I'll reward you.
If you don't, I'll punish you.
You'll punish me...
Like, you'd use
this stuff on me?
Yes.
What would I get out of this?
Me.
If we were to do this,
this would be your room.
You can decorate it
however you like.
You want me to move in?
Not full time.
Just Friday through to Sunday.
We can negotiate
the particulars.
So, uh...
So, I'd sleep in here with you?
No. I'd be downstairs.
I told you,
I don't sleep with anyone.
What if I don't want
anything to do with that?
I would understand completely.
But then we wouldn't have any
sort of relationship at all?
This is the only sort
of relationship I have.
Why?
It's the way I am.
When you said "negotiate,"
what did you mean?
I already have a contract prepared.
It's fairly detailed.
You would review it,
and we would negotiate what you
are and are not willing to try.
How could I know what
I'd be willing to try?
Well, when you've had sex
was there anything that
you didn't like doing?
We have to be honest with each
other for this to work, okay?
I wouldn't know.
What do you mean?
Because I haven't...
You're still a virgin?
I have just shown you...
I know. I just...
You've done other things, right?
No.
Where have you been?
Waiting.
Men must throw
themselves at you.
Never one I've wanted.
You're biting your lip.
What are you doing?
Rectifying the situation.
I'm a situation?
Mmm.
You're energetic this morning.
You hungry?
Very.
Because I'm making pancakes.
Let's get you cleaned up.
Do you trust me?
Stay here.
Hold out your wrists.
Hold them there.
You understand?
Tell me you understand.
I won't move my arms.
Good girl.
Stay still.
Okay.
Say "yes."
To what?
To being mine.
No need
to announce me. Christian!
Shit.
What?
It's my mother.
I'm naked.
Get dressed.
And there's no need
to show me around.
And there's no need to hover.
He's still sleeping,
Dr. Grey.
He's still sleeping?
But he never sleeps in.
Certainly not at this hour.
Unless, of course,
he's ill. Is he... Ah.
Sorry, Mr. Grey.
It's fine.
I know how she can be.
"She"?
Well, if you're
trying to avoid me,
the very least you can do
is call me by my correct
name, which would be "Mum."
Hi.
Oh. Dear God.
Mother, Anastasia Steele.
Ana, meet my mother,
Dr. Grace Trevelyan Grey.
You have no idea how
delighted I am to meet you.
It's nice to meet you,
too, Dr. Grey.
"Grace."
She's very pretty.
You're very pretty.
Thank you.
Mmm-hmm.
So, what happened to
calling before dropping by?
And have your henchmen
give me the runaround?
No, thank you.
I'll take my chances.
Anyway, I was in
the neighborhood,
and I thought perhaps
we could have lunch.
I can't today.
I have to drive Ana home.
It's okay. Take it.
I was just showing Mother out.
Excuse me.
Anastasia...
Kate, hold on.
It was a joy to meet you.
And I'm having the whole family
for dinner next week
at my house.
Christian's sister,
Mia, is back from Paris.
You must come.
We'll see, Mother.
Nice to meet you.
You, too.
Thank you.
I can't talk about
it right now, Kate.
I gotta go.
I'll call you back, okay?
Everything okay
with the phone call?
Yeah. Nothing important.
I liked your mom.
She's excited. She's never
seen me with a woman before.
It was a first.
What is it, Ana?
Um...
I just...
How many women
have stayed in here?
Fifteen.
That's a lot of women.
I told you before,
if you want out...
I don't want out. I just...
I'm not exactly jumping
at the opportunity
to get whipped and tortured
in your red room of pain.
That room is much more
about pleasure.
Promise you.
Would we still go out
to dinner and movies?
That's not really my thing.
Try to keep an open mind.
If you agree to be
my submissive,
I will be devoted to you.
This is what I want.
And I want it with you.
Why do I have to sleep in here?
We slept in the same bed
last night.
Like normal people.
Try not to get hung up on
the sleeping arrangements.
If you agree to do this,
you're gonna want your own room.
Why, because I'll
be your sex slave?
I don't wanna do this here.
Let's talk downstairs.
No. You know what?
I think I'll hold
on to my free will
a little while longer,
thank you.
Actually, you know what? I would
like to go home. Can I go home?
Which one's yours?
All of them.
Let's go for a walk.
How did you start doing this?
One of my mother's friends.
I was 15.
She seduced you?
I was her submissive
for six years.
Seriously?
Does your mother know that?
Of course not.
No one in my family knows
about this part of me.
So, she introduced you
to all this?
Mrs. Robinson?
"Mrs. Robinson."
I'll tell her you said that.
She'll love it.
You still talk to her?
On occasion.
We're friends.
Ana.
I know how intimidating this is.
I felt the same at first.
Well, what changed your mind?
By giving up control,
I felt free.
From responsibility,
from making decisions.
I felt safe.
You will, too, you'll see.
I've never taken anyone
in the helicopter.
I've never had sex
in my own bed.
I've never slept next to anyone.
Ever.
Only you.
This is the contract.
Read it carefully.
E-mail me if you
have any questions.
I told you, my computer's down.
Just consider it, okay?
I really hope you say yes.
Thanks for the ride.
Laters, baby.
Um...
Okay, you're all set.
Your roommate let me in.
I just figured that you forgot to
tell me about it. Do I look okay?
- Tell you about what?
- Just sign here.
Hold on. Do you have
the right apartment?
Anastasia Steele?
Enjoy.
Another gift, huh?
Whatever happened
to flowers and chocolates?
I'm dying to hear everything.
But I have to run right now, because
Elliot and I are having dinner
and then we're going to
see a show at The Gorge.
José called for you.
Twice, by the way.
Did the mail already come?
Oh. Um, no, this is...
These are my thesis notes.
I left them at school.
Oh. All right. Well,
there's yesterday's mail.
What?
I don't know.
You look different.
I feel different.
Of course you do.
Okay.
Bye!
The fundamental
purpose of this contract
is to allow
the Submissive to explore
her sensuality and
her limits safely.
The Dominant and Submissive
agree and acknowledge
that all that occurs under
the terms of this contract
will be consensual,
confidential,
and subject to the agreed limits
and safety procedures
set out in this contract.
The Submissive will agree
to any sexual activity deemed fit
and pleasurable by the Dominant,
excepting those activities
outlined in Hard Limits.
...so much.
Thank you.
The Submissive will not drink to excess,
smoke, or take recreational drugs,
or put her person into
any unnecessary risk.
The Submissive will not
enter into sexual relations
with anyone other than
the Dominant.
The Submissive agrees to
procure oral contraception
from a physician
of the Dominant's choosing.
The Submissive
will eat regularly
to maintain her
health and well-being
from a prescribed
list of foods. Appendix Four.
The Submissive will obey any
instruction given by the Dominant.
She will do so eagerly
and without hesitation.
The Submissive may not
touch the Dominant
without his expressed
permission to do so.
The Submissive shall
always conduct herself
in a respectful manner
to the Dominant,
and she'll address him only
as "Sir," "Mr. Grey..."
...or such other title
as the Dominant may direct.
The Dominant may flog, spank, whip,
or corporally punish the Submissive
as he sees fit,
for purposes of discipline
or for his personal enjoyment.
The safeword "Yellow"
will be used
to bring to the attention
of the Dominant
that the Submissive
is close to her limit.
When the safeword
"Red" is spoken,
the Dominant's action will cease
completely and immediately.
Does the Submissive consent to being
restrained with hands bound in front?
Does the Submissive consent
to being blindfolded?
to being gagged?
How much pain is the Submissive
willing to experience?
Christian.
It's been "nice"
knowing me, has it?
Let me remind you
how "nice" it was.
Is this what you want?
Don't make a sound.
Was this "nice"?
That was really nice.
What are you doing to me?
What about here?
Why not?
Is it breaking the rules?
Speaking of which...
I haven't made up my mind yet.
You're not staying?
I told you,
I don't sleep with anyone.
Well, can we negotiate?
Now, that's a hell of a sack,
Miss Steele.
Business meeting.
Impressive.
I've done this before.
Business meetings, I mean.
Oh.
Miss Steele.
Hmm?
Your meeting.
Page one.
Strike out my old address and
replace with the new one.
An oversight. Duly noted.
Page three, section 1520.
"The Submissive
shall submit to any
"sexual activity
demanded by the Dominant
"and shall do so without
hesitation or argument."
Uh, turn to page five.
Appendix Three,
"Soft Limits."
With you.
Find "anal fisting."
I'm all ears.
Strike it out.
Strike out
"vaginal fisting," too.
Are you sure?
Yep.
Same page, "Is the use of sex toys
acceptable to the Submissive?"
Vibrators, okay.
Dildos, fine.
Genital clamps?
Absolutely not.
Consider them gone.
What are butt plugs?
You must go through quite a few
non-disclosure agreements.
My staff know only what
I choose to tell them.
Please resume, Miss Steele.
Also on page five, there are some
terms which need clarification.
"Suspension"?
Hanging on ropes
from the ceiling.
For what possible reason?
For your pleasure.
Really?
And mine.
Something to consider.
No. Hard limit.
I'm good with rope,
leather cuffs, handcuffs.
Please lose "tape."
And what's "Other"?
Cable ties.
Can I just say
how impressed I am
with your commitment
to this meeting?
And in that spirit, I'm
gonna throw in a sweetener.
How about once a week,
on a night of your choosing,
we go on a date?
Just like a regular couple.
Dinner, movie,
ice skating.
Whatever you want.
Accepted.
You're very kind.
I'll suggest it
in Appendix Five.
I would like to fuck you into
the middle of next week.
You're not fighting fair.
I never have.
I'll review all these changes and
try to arrive at a decision.
You wanna leave?
Yes.
But your body tells me
something different.
Your legs, for instance.
The way you're pressing your
thighs together under the table.
And the change
in your breathing.
And in your complexion.
My complexion?
You're flushed.
That could just be the wine.
It's the adrenaline.
Say I did stay.
What would happen?
First,
I would help you out of
that little dress of yours.
Yes.
And I'd be pleased to discover
that you're naked underneath.
Really?
Then I would bend you over.
Right here?
Yes.
On this table?
Thank you for the meeting,
Mr. Grey.
This is me.
Didn't know I was a collector
of classic cars, huh?
You sure I can't
persuade you to stay?
Good night, Christian.
When will you know?
Soon, maybe.
Why do I think
you're telling me goodbye?
Because I'm leaving.
You got your
valedictory speech ready?
Oh, more or less.
Annie!
Dad!
Hi!
Sorry I'm late. I had
a hell of a time parking.
That's okay. You're here,
that's all that matters.
You kidding me? I wouldn't
miss this for the world.
I saved you a seat
next to Kate's parents.
Anywhere you
want me, sweetheart.
Okay. I'll see you after. Yeah.
Good luck up there.
And he's also a major
benefactor to our university.
Please join me in welcoming
Mr. Christian Grey.
Thank you.
I am deeply moved by the great
compliment accorded to me today.
He is so hot.
Oh, God. He so is.
I heard he's gay.
The goal?
To help eradicate hunger and
poverty across the globe.
I myself
have known what it's like
to be profoundly hungry.
So this is a very
personal mission for me.
Megan Soliah.
Anastasia Steele.
Nancy Hines.
Congratulations.
You should be very proud.
I am.
Nice tie, by the way.
It's recently
become my favorite.
Do you have your answer yet?
I'm still thinking.
Anastasia, just try it
my way. Please.
Okay.
What?
Congratulations.
Thank you.
We did it, we did it, we did it!
Dad! Hi.
I am so proud of you, Annie.
Thank you.
And, Kate, best
valedictorian speech ever.
Oh, thank you.
It was awesome.
Yeah...
Ana. Hi.
Hi.
Ray, have you met Christian
Grey, Ana's boyfriend?
Hi. Great pleasure
to meet you.
Likewise. I really
enjoyed your speech.
Thank you, sir.
Sounds like you have accomplished
some pretty impressive things.
- I'll say.
- Thank you.
Well, I'm gonna go
find my family
who've been patiently
waiting to embarrass me.
Bye. Come see us
in Seattle, okay?
Yeah, as soon as I
get an invitation.
So, how long have you two
known each other?
Um... Mmm-hmm.
A few weeks, now.
We actually met when Anastasia
interviewed me for
the student newspaper.
Uh, picture, please,
Mr. Grey?
Excuse us a moment.
Big smile, now.
To celebrate your graduation,
among other things.
Roll your eyes at me again
and I will take you
across my knee.
Oh.
So it begins.
Mmm. Come on. I have
something to show you.
What?
That's cute.
Doesn't really seem
like your style, though.
It's not.
Happy graduation, Anastasia.
Oh, my God.
Christian, that's a car.
You don't miss much, do you?
Thank you, but I can't...
Do you like it?
Of course I like it.
It's beautiful.
But I have a car.
Where's my car?
I told Taylor to
fetch a decent price.
Oh, Christian,
this is way too much.
Did you just roll
your eyes at me?
Oh!
Do you know why I'm doing this?
Because I rolled my eyes.
And is that polite?
No.
Excuse me?
No, sir.
Do you want more?
Welcome to my world.
What are you doing?
I have a few things at the office
that require my attention.
You okay?
I just thought that...
I enjoyed tonight.
I'll see you
at my place tomorrow.
Hi, Momma.
Anastasia, what's going on?
I have left you two
messages this week.
I know. I'm sorry.
I just got a little distracted.
Sorry I missed your graduation, honey.
I heard it was lovely.
And your new beau?
Ray told me all about him. He
sounds like quite the young man.
Of course,
I would have preferred
to have heard
about him from you.
Ana?
What's the matter?
Nothing. I'm fine.
Is he not making you happy?
He is, yeah.
Most of the time, yeah.
It's complicated.
Listen, honey,
if you need a break,
you just come
right on down here.
Even if it's for a day or two.
I have air miles, and we could
talk and have girl time.
Promise me
you'll think about it.
Yeah, I promise.
I promise.
I love you, Momma.
I love you, too, darling.
I gotta go.
Bye.
Looks like you and Grey did
some celebrating last night.
Is he still asleep?
Uh... No, he couldn't stay.
Whose car keys are those, then?
Those are my keys.
Wow, Ana.
What?
Nothing. I just...
Make sure you're taking it
at your own pace, okay?
I am, I am. I gotta go.
Where are you going?
Look at this.
I've seen it.
It's not a bad picture.
"Christian Grey
with friend."
It says we're friends.
Well, it must be true
if it's in the paper.
Mmm.
So, how'd it go
with Dr. Greene?
It was fine.
But she said that I
have to abstain from
all sexual activity
for at least four weeks.
You know,
after I start the pill.
What?
Just kidding.
I wanna take you
to my play room.
But I haven't signed
the contract.
I'm well aware.
Call it due diligence.
Okay.
You ready?
Eyes down.
Take off your shoes.
Arms above your head.
You have a beautiful
body, Anastasia.
I want you unashamed of your nakedness.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
You're biting your lip.
You know what that does
to me. Turn around.
When I tell you to
come into this room,
this is how you'll be.
You'll wait for me,
kneeling by the door.
Do it now.
Hands flat on your thighs.
Good.
Hold out your hand.
Did that hurt?
No.
You see?
Most of your fear
is in your head.
Come.
How does it feel?
Good, sir.
Mmm.
Quiet.
Where are we going?
Remember my mother
mentioned dinner?
My sister Mia's in town.
Yeah.
You got everything you need?
Dance with me.
Good evening, Mr. Grey.
They're here.
You're here.
Welcome, welcome.
Ana, Mother, you've met.
Hi. Good to see you. Come on in.
And this is my father, Carrick.
Hi, pleasure to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Is she here? You are the
subject of some speculation.
Oh, my God, you exist!
It's a great apartment, and
the rent's not ridiculous.
Elliot and José
helped us move in.
José is Ana's friend.
Although, I think that
Elliot's trying to poach him.
They've sparked
quite the bromance.
He's a cool guy.
Ana, where is your family from?
My stepfather lives in Montesano,
and my mom's in Georgia.
Georgia? Which part?
Savannah.
How nice.
Although, I do hear it gets rather
humid in Georgia this time of year.
Oh, my God, it does.
It's stifling sometimes.
Actually, I'm going
to visit her tomorrow.
Oh, how nice.
Mmm-hmm.
You hear that, Christian?
Some children do visit their
parents now and again.
Hey, Dad, you catch
the Mariners game?
Uh, I heard it went
to extra innings.
Ugh. Seattle baseball...
This is news to me.
When were you gonna tell me?
Who wants coffee?
Actually, I promised Ana
a tour of the grounds.
Excuse us.
Christian, I cannot walk
that fast in these shoes.
Oh.
When were you gonna
tell me about Georgia?
What? You have
no right to be mad.
Yeah, but I am mad.
Palm-twitchingly mad.
Ow!
You're mine.
All mine, you understand?
Christian, you are so confusing.
Ana.
What do you want?
I want you.
I'm trying, Christian.
I know you are.
Why can't we sleep
in the same bed?
Why won't you let me touch you?
Why does it have
to be like this?
If you would just
sign the contract,
you wouldn't have
to think about...
Why do you care so much about
the contract, Christian?
Don't you like me the way I am?
Of course I do.
Then why are you
trying to change me?
I'm not.
It's...
I need more. I want more.
Hearts and flowers?
That's not something I know.
Ana, please.
It's you that's changing me.
Let me touch you.
Let me.
Are they burns?
I had a rough start in life.
That's all you need to know.
Okay.
The woman that gave birth to me
was a crack addict
and a prostitute.
She died when I was four.
I remember certain things.
Terrible things.
But I don't remember her.
But sometimes,
I think I see her in my dreams.
Mmm.
Do you really have
to go to Georgia?
Yeah, I really do.
Good morning. 12-H is
down to your right.
Good morning. 2-B, oh
it's just right here.
Oh! No, I'm supposed
to be in coach.
Oh, you must have been upgraded.
Good morning. 12-A
just down to your right.
Good morning.
Oh.
Gazpacho is very healthy, Bob.
You'll get fat with all this
sitting around. You tell him, Ana.
I'm not gonna tell him that.
Yes, thank you, Ana.
I'm just saying that gazpacho is
basically eating a bowl of salsa.
You should hand me some chips
with my bowl of salsa here.
You can have a carrot.
What are you
getting at with this?
You are damn lucky that I just
happen to love you very much.
I know that.
Do you?
Mmm, I do.
Oh, darling, I think
we should pace ourselves.
Or at least order
something to eat.
You go ahead.
I'm not very hungry.
Oh. I'll just have
the fruit salad.
He can wait.
Mom...
Holy fuck.
What? What is it?
It's Christian. He's here.
Um, in Georgia.
Oh.
"Here" here.
Mrs. Adams.
Delighted to meet you.
Something to drink, sir?
Gin and tonic.
Hendrick's, if you have it.
Otherwise, Bombay Sapphire.
Cucumber with the Hendrick's,
lime with the Bombay.
I like him already.
What are you doing here,
Christian?
I came to see you.
I'm gonna step
outside for a bit.
I broke rule seven, clause five.
Here.
We'll let it go.
Let's not talk about
the contract right now.
How was your dinner?
She's a friend.
That's all.
She's a child abuser.
I confide in her.
She knows me.
What did she advise you to do?
Well, I'm here.
And now what?
I've got a room in this hotel.
Well, I hope you'll
be comfortable in it.
What are you doing
for breakfast tomorrow?
Where are we going?
It's a surprise.
I think I've reached
my quota of surprises.
We're almost there.
Mr. Grey. Hey.
I'll be your tow pilot.
How do you do? This is my
girlfriend, Anastasia Steele.
We're at 3,000 feet.
Y'all ready?
Well?
Yeah, do it.
Release.
Hold on tight.
Is this more?
Oh, my God. So much more!
Oh, my God. That was
incredible, Christian.
Thank you.
We aim to please, Miss Steele.
And you said you
didn't do romance.
I don't.
Ana.
Mmm. What?
What?
Why are you fighting this?
What are you afraid of?
Grey.
What?
When?
Tell Stephan to
have the plane ready.
I'll be on the tarmac
in 30 minutes.
What happened?
I have to go back to Seattle.
Come, I'll take you home.
Oh, sweetheart.
I wish Christian
could have stayed.
Bob was really looking
forward to meeting him.
I know.
He had to get back
to Seattle, though.
There was some
situation at work.
I wish I could tell you that
things get easier, but they don't.
You just get to
know yourself better.
Thank you for everything, Momma.
Take care
of yourself, sweetheart.
I will.
Did you think I wouldn't
recognize you, Taylor?
How does he seem today, Taylor?
Preoccupied, I'm afraid.
Really?
Yes, ma'am.
Well, that's not gonna work.
When?
Well, then, tell them that
they don't have 24 hours.
That is unacceptable.
I need to know.
Just keep me informed.
Is everything okay?
Nothing that concerns you.
I can leave.
Do you want me to go?
No.
No, that's the last thing
I want.
I want you to be
in the play room in 15 minutes.
What are your safewords?
"Red" and "Yellow."
Remember those.
Mmm.
It sounds so sad.
Everything you play is so sad.
You said you were six
when you learned.
Was it because you wanted
to please your new family?
I just wanna talk.
Why won't you let me in?
We should be talking.
Like normal people?
Yeah.
Is that so wrong?
Is this because of the contract,
because I still
haven't signed it?
Fuck the contract.
I think it's a little
redundant, don't you?
So, then, the rules
are redundant, too?
No. The rules stand.
And what if I break them?
Then there'll be consequences.
Punishment.
Yes.
Why do you want to punish me?
Ana...
Why do you wanna hurt me?
I would never do anything to
you that you couldn't handle.
But why do you even wanna do
anything to me at all, Christian?
If I told you, you would never
look at me the same way again.
So, there is a reason.
Tell me.
Do you wanna punish me
right now?
Yes. I wanna punish you
right now.
What if I told you that I feel the
same way about being punished
as you do about me touching you?
Would you still
want to punish me then?
No.
But that doesn't mean
I wouldn't need to.
Why?
Ana, stop.
Why do you need to?
Because it's the way I am!
Because I am fifty shades
of fucked up.
Show me, then.
I need you to show me
what you want to do to me.
Punish me.
Show me how bad it can be. I
want you to show me the worst.
It's the only way
I can understand.
Are you sure about this?
Yes.
Bend over.
I'm gonna hit you six times.
And you're gonna count with me.
Count, Anastasia.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
No! Don't fucking touch me.
This is what you want?
You want to see me like this?
Ana...
Don't come near me.
Does this give you pleasure?
Don't.
Don't you dare come near me.
Please don't hate me.
You'll never
do that to me again.
I'm not what you want.
No, you're everything
that I want.
I've fallen in love with you.
No.
No, Ana, you can't love me.
I need you to leave.
Please.
I'd like my car back.
Taylor already sold it.
Then I'd like the money
he got for it, please.
I'll send you a check.
Okay.
Taylor will take you home.
Stop.
No!
Ana...
Christian.