♪♪ [ Piano ]
[ Woman ]
♪ I put a spell on you ♪
♪ Because you’re mine ♪
♪ You better
stop the things
you do ♪
♪ I tell you
I ain’t lyin’ ♪
♪ I ain’t lyin’ ♪
♪ You know I can’t stand it ♪
♪ Your running around ♪
♪ You know better, Daddy ♪
♪ I can’t stand it
’cause you put me down ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ I put a spell on you ♪
♪ Because you’re mine ♪
♪ You know I love you ♪
♪ I love you, I love you ♪
♪ I love you anyhow ♪
♪ And I don’t care
if you don’t want me ♪
♪ I’m yours right now ♪
♪ I put a spell on you ♪
♪ Because you’re mine ♪
[ Woman ]
Ana, take my car.
I gave you
the recorder, right?
Oh. Yes.
And you have
all the questions?
Yes.
And you know
where you’re going?
Yes, I do have a GPS.
And a 4.0 GPA.
I can figure it out.
Are you wearing that?
Okay, maybe
a little less talking.
More eating.
[ Laughs ]
How about that?
♪ You know
I can’t stand it ♪
♪ Your running around ♪
♪ You know better, Daddy ♪
♪ I can’t stand it
’cause you put me down ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
Wow.
♪ I put a spell on you ♪
♪ Because you’re mine ♪
[ Elevator Bell Dings ]
♪ Because you’re mine ♪♪
Is Mr. Grey’s
5:00 confirmed?
Miss Kavanagh?
[ Receptionist On Phone ]
Yes. Uh-huh.
May I take your coat?
Oh. Yes.
Um, sh– Uh, she’s–
Okay, so–
Mr. Grey
will see you now.
Okay.
This way,
please.
Okay.
[ Receptionist ]
Mr. Grey has
a conference call at 11:15.
Right this way.
-[ Gasps ]
-[ Pen Rolls On Floor ]
Miss Kavanagh.
Are you all right?
Christian Grey.
I’m Anastasia Steele.
Miss Kavanagh has the flu,
so she asked me to fill in.
I see.
So you’re studying
journalism as well.
No. English Lit.
Um, Kate’s my roommate.
As I said,
I only have 10 minutes.
Please, have a seat,
Miss Steele.
[ Recorder Beeps ]
Thank you.
[ Clears Throat ]
Ready?
Whenever you are.
I– Okay.
Um, so, this is for
the special graduation issue
of the student newspaper.
Yes. I’m giving
the commencement address
at this year’s ceremony.
You are?
I mean, um...
I know.
[ Clears Throat ]
[ Reading ]
Uh, you are very young
to have amassed such an empire.
-To what do you owe your s–
-To what do I owe my success?
Yep.
Seriously?
Yes.
Business
is about people.
And I’ve always
been good at people.
What motivates them,
what incentivizes them,
what inspires them.
Well, maybe
you’re just lucky.
I’ve always found
that the harder I work,
the more luck I seem to have.
The key to my success
has been in identifying
talented individuals...
and harnessing
their efforts.
So you’re a control freak?
Oh, I exercise control
in all things, Miss Steele.
Okay, um–
Uh, your company is involved...
primarily in
the telecommunications sector,
yet you also invest in
numerous agricultural projects,
including several in Africa.
Is that something that
you feel passionate about,
feeding the world’s poor?
It’s smart business.
You don’t agree?
I don’t know
enough about it.
I just wonder if...
perhaps your heart
might be a bit bigger
than you want to let on.
There are some people
who say that I don’t
have a heart at all.
Why would they say that?
Because they know me well.
Go on.
[ Clears Throat ]
Um, do you have any interests
outside of work?
I enjoy various
physical pursuits.
You’re unmarried– Oh.
-You were adopted at age four.
-That’s a matter
of public record.
I’m sorry.
I didn’t–
Do you have
an actual question,
Miss Steele?
Yeah. Sorry.
Are you gay?
[ Laughs ]
It’s written here.
I’m just–
No, Anastasia,
I’m not gay.
I apologize, Mr. Grey.
Kate can be a little–
Intrusive?
Curious.
What about you?
Why don’t you
ask me something
that you want to know.
Earlier, you said
that there are some people
who know you well.
Why do I get the feeling
that that is not true?
Mr. Grey, your next meeting
is in the conference room.
Cancel, please.
We’re not finished here.
Yes, sir.
No. Uh, I’m– I–
We– I can go. It’s fine.
I’d like to know
more about you.
There’s really
not much to know about me.
You said
you’re an English major?
Tell me,
was it Charlotte Brontë,
Jane Austen
or Thomas Hardy...
who first made you
fall in love
with literature?
Hardy.
I would have guessed
Jane Austen.
What are your plans
after you graduate?
I’m just trying to
get through finals right now.
And then?
And then I was
planning on moving here,
to Seattle, with Kate.
We offer an excellent
internship program.
I don’t think
I’d fit in here.
Look at me.
I am.
[ Phone Ringing ]
[ Receptionist ]
Mr. Grey’s office.
I hope you got
everything you needed.
I-I think you only answered
four questions.
[ Elevator Bell Dings ]
Anastasia.
Christian.
[ Rain Falling ]
Holy cow.
[ Chuckles ]
Um, before you
say anything, I can–
-You’re a goddess.
This is perfect.
-What?
I just got his e-mail.
He answered every question.
So, what was he like?
Um–
He was fine.
"Fine"?
Just fine?
Um, he was
really polite,
and he was courteous,
and very formal,
and– and clean.
"Clean"?
I mean, he was very,
you know, smart.
And intense.
It was
kind of intimidating.
I can understand
the fascination.
Uh-huh.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
Like what?
Okay.
I’m gonna make a sandwich.
Do you want one?
No, thanks.
You have to admit,
he’s ridiculously hot.
I’m sure if you...
are attracted
to that sort...
of human, then–
The hot type of human?
[ Laughs ]
I asked him if he was gay.
That was in your questions.
Why would you
do that to me?
Because whenever he’s in
the society pages, he’s never
been photographed with a woman.
So, naturally–
Maybe he just wants to
keep his private life
private, Kate.
And now
you’re defending him.
I’m terminating
this conversation.
Too bad we don’t have
some original stills...
of your hot, clean,
27-year-old billionaire.
The camera loves him
almost as much as you do.
Okay, I wasn’t hungry,
but now I am.
Thank you.
I love you.
"I declared
I could not change,
yet you tell me to my face
I shall change soon.
And what a distortion
in your judgment.
What a perversity
in your ideas.
Is it better to
drive a fellow creature
to despair...
than transgress
a mere human law?"
Ana. I’ve been
looking for you.
What’s up?
Guess what.
What?
Portland Place is going
to exhibit my photographs
next month.
Oh, my God.
[ Laughing ]
Congratulations!
Yeah!
That’s so good!
Solo show, corazón.
Can we celebrate later?
’Cause I’m really
late for work.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You got it, you got it.
But, um–
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Thank you.
You’re my hero.
I’ll see you later.
Okay.
[ Engine Starts ]
[ Phone Ringing ]
Mom, I’m at work.
Can I call you back?
No, wait, wait, wait.
I called for a reason.
Bob broke his foot
playing golf,
of all things.
God. Is he okay?
Is he in a lot of pain?
Who can tell with the man?
He calls the paramedics
for a blister.
It means, though,
we won’t be able to
fly in for graduation.
Really?
You don’t wanna just come alone?
You don’t have to bring Bob.
And leave Tiger Woods
to fend for himself?
You do understand,
don’t you, darling?
Yeah. I–
Yeah, it’s fine.
Um, I really have to go.
Okay?
I love you, Ana.
I know.
I love you too.
[ Beeps ]
God.
Ana?
-Could you give me
a hand out back?
-Uh, yeah. I’ll be right there.
[ Gasps ]
-I thought it was you.
-What the f–
What a pleasant surprise,
Miss Steele.
Just Ana.
[ Clears Throat ]
You’re in here.
I was in the area on business.
Needed to pick up a few things.
Are you free?
Yeah.
What can I
help you with?
Do you stock cable ties?
Cable ties.
Yes, we do.
I can show you,
if you want.
Please lead the way,
Miss Steele.
Just Ana.
Is that it?
Masking tape.
Are you redecorating?
No.
Um, we have two-inch
and one-inch.
But the truly
self-respecting handyman...
will have both
in his toolbox.
Of course he will.
It’s rare to find
a connoisseur these days.
Do you want
anything else?
Yes.
Rope.
That’s impressive.
You a Girl Scout?
[ Chuckles ]
Um, no.
Organized group activities
aren’t really my thing.
So what is
your "thing"?
Um, I don’t know.
Books? [ Laughs ]
Okay.
Rope, tape, cable ties.
You’re the complete
serial killer.
Not today.
Anything else?
What would you
recommend?
For a do-it-yourself-er?
Um, maybe coveralls,
so you protect your clothes.
Could just take
all my clothes off.
Okay, no clothes.
I mean, no coveralls.
You–
I can’t think
of anything else.
Well, I guess
that’s it then.
Cool.
Thank you for answering
Kate’s questions,
by the way.
She was thrilled.
I hope
she’s feeling better.
She is, yeah. Much.
She’s just having
a hard time clearing
a photo of you.
If she’d like an original,
I’m around tomorrow.
You’d be willing
to do that?
Yeah.
Want me to bag
for you, Ana?
Oh. Uh, no, no, I’m good.
Thanks though, Paul.
Okay.
I’m staying locally
at the Heathman.
Call me before 10:00.
-About the photos.
-Oh.
Yeah, I will.
Enjoy your s–
[ Shutter Clicking ]
-Thanks again for
doing this, Mr. Grey.
-I’m happy to help.
Uh, how about we try
a few with a smile?
Or– Or not.
You do realize
that he hasn’t stopped
looking at you.
[ Clears Throat ]
He asked me to go
for coffee afterwards.
What?
[ Giggles ]
Kate, shh.
So, is he
your boyfriend?
Who?
The photographer.
[ Laughs ]
José?
No.
I saw the way
he was smiling at you.
No, José is more like family.
He’s not my boyfriend.
And the guy
at the store?
Paul? No.
Thank you.
You seem nervous.
I find you
intimidating.
You should.
Eat.
Not to mention
high-handed.
I’m used to
getting my own way.
That must get
very boring.
Tell me
about your family.
My family?
Um, okay.
My dad died
when I was a baby.
So I was raised
by my stepfather, Ray.
He’s amazing.
And your mother?
Um, my mother is on
husband number four.
She’s an incurable
romantic.
-Are you?
-Am I a romantic?
Well,
I study English Lit.
So I kind of have to be.
Thought
the photo shoot
went well. Right?
Kate seems to be
really happ–
I’m sorry. I can’t, uh–
What?
I’ll walk you out.
Do you have a girlfriend?
Is that it?
I don’t do
the girlfriend thing.
What does that even m–
Watch it!
I’m not
the man for you.
You should
steer clear of me.
I have to let you go.
Good-bye, Mr. Grey.
All right, pencils down.
[ Exhales ]
Please take your final exams
to the back of the classroom.
Final grades will be
posted in two weeks.
Hey.
You all good?
Yeah.
Why wouldn’t I be?
We are so partying tonight.
Oh, my God.
This is
way too much.
No–
You’re getting it–
No, this is exactly
the right amount.
All over my face.
That’s the idea.
Wow.
No, Kate.
Cab’s early.
Let’s go.
[ Exhales ]
Ana, it’s a package
for you!
"Why didn’t you tell me
there was danger?
Why didn’t you
warn me?
Ladies know
what to guard against–"
[ Together ]
"Because they read novels that
tell them of these tricks."
That’s a quote from
Tess of the d’Urbervilles.
Oh, my God.
These must be from Christian.
Do you– I mean, wh–
These are incredible.
Wow, Grey.
Kate, these are
first editions.
I can’t.
This is too much.
I can’t accept these.
I have to send them back.
[ Horn Honking ]
That’s the cab.
Okay, are you ready?
Are you ready to go?
Yes. Yes, very.
Let’s get out
of here.
♪♪ [ Hip-hop: Man Rapping ]
[ José ]
All right, shots first.
Shots! Shots! Shots! Shots!
Nobody hold back either!
[ Screams ]
Did you do it all?
With my eyes closed
and left-handed,
I can get this in.
What?
I gotta pee.
Okay.
[ Laughs ]
Where you going?
I’m gonna go–
I gotta pee.
[ Chattering ]
Yeah.
Yeah, right?
[ Chuckles ]
[ Dialing,
Line Ringing ]
[ Phone Buzzing ]
Anastasia?
Yeah.
This is me.
I’m sending back
your expensive books...
’cause I already have
copies of those.
Thanks, though,
for the kind gesture.
You’re welcome.
Where are you?
[ Sighs ]
Oh.
I’m in line because
I have to pee really bad.
Anastasia,
have you been drinking?
[ Giggles ]
Yeah.
I have,
Mr. Fancy Pants.
You hit the hail–
hail on the nead.
[ Giggles ]
I mean, the head
right on the nail.
Listen to me.
I want you to
go home right now.
You’re so bossy.
"Ana, let’s go for coffee."
[ Gruff, Low Voice ]
"No, stay away from me, Ana.
I don’t want you. Get away."
"Come here." "Go away."
That’s it.
Tell me where you are.
I’m a long way from Seattle.
A long way from you.
Which bar?
What’s it called?
I don’t know.
I gotta go though.
Which bar, An–
[ Dial Tone ]
I told him. Right?
[ Giggles ]
[ Chattering
Continues ]
Okay. I don’t know.
Yeah.
[ Laughs ]
Of course.
[ Ringing ]
[ Beeps ]
I’m sorry. I didn’t–
Stay where you are.
I’m coming to get you.
What?
[ Dial Tone ]
Hello?
[ Beeps ]
[ Sighs ]
Hey.
Oh, thanks.
You okay?
[ Sighs ]
Yeah. I just–
I’m a little bit more...
drunk than–
[ Laughs ]
Come here. Stay warm.
Oh, it’s cool.
I’m good, José.
I got it.
I don’t know when I’ll
have the courage to do this.
Do what?
Ana.
No.
I like you.
You do?
Very much.
Oh, my God.
Mmm.
Please.
One kiss.
No. No, no, no.
José, I don’t–
I’m sorry, no.
Dude, she said no!
Christian?
[ Coughs, Vomits ]
[ Coughing, Groaning ]
Don’t look at me.
Here.
Nice touch.
I will launder
this item.
Let’s get you home.
I’m with Kate.
I’ll have Elliot tell her.
Who’s Elliot?
He’s my brother.
He’s inside,
talking to her right now.
H– I don’t–
He was at my hotel
with me.
You’re still
at the Heathman?
Yeah.
Come.
♪♪ [ Dance Pop ]
[ No Audible Dialogue ]
That’s your brother?
Not by choice.
Let’s go.
Wait.
What did Kate say?
She warned me to be
on my best behavior.
[ Laughs ]
More like
threatened me.
She threatened you?
[ Laughs ]
You’re spinning.
I think I’m gonna faint.
What, now?
[ Door Opens ]
Good morning, Anastasia.
How are you feeling?
Better than I deserve.
Did you put me to bed?
Mm-hmm.
You undressed me?
I didn’t have much choice.
Where did you sleep?
Oh, my God.
Did we– We didn’t–
Necrophilia
is not my thing.
So we just slept then?
It was a novelty for me too.
You need to eat.
I had Taylor
pick you up some clothes.
Who’s Taylor?
My driver.
Thank you, but you didn’t
have to do that.
Yes, I did.
Yours were covered
in vomit.
You shouldn’t get drunk
like that.
I’m all for testing limits,
but you put yourself
at risk last night.
I know.
If you were mine,
you wouldn’t be able to
sit down for a week.
What?
I gotta go
take a shower.
Why am I here, Christian?
You’re here because
I’m incapable of
leaving you alone.
Then don’t.
Why’d you send me
those books?
I thought I owed you
an apology.
For what?
For letting you
believe that I–
Listen to me.
I don’t do romance.
My tastes
are very...
singular.
You wouldn’t understand.
Enlighten me then.
[ Door Closes ]
[ Door Opens ]
You look beautiful.
Taylor has good taste.
What are you doing
later?
I’m working
at the hardware store
till 7:00.
I’ll have Taylor
pick you up then.
[ Sighs ]
I would like to
bite that lip.
I think I’d like that too.
I’m not gonna touch you.
Not until I have
your written consent.
What?
I’ll explain later.
Come. I’ll take you home.
[ Bell Dings ]
Fuck the paperwork.
[ Chattering Stops ]
[ Men Clearing Throats ]
As I was saying–
[ Chattering Resumes ]
What is it
about elevators?
-Hey.
-[ Kate, Ana Laughing ]
Hi.
You must be Ana.
You must be Elliot.
And we must be
going.
-Elliot.
-[ Elliot ]
So awesome to meet you.
Kate’s told me
a lot about you.
Elliot, find your shoes.
Some of us have work
to attend to.
What you’re doing
with Mr. Warmth here,
I have no idea.
Laters, baby.
[ Giggling ]
I’ll see you tonight.
E-mail me if something changes.
My computer’s broken.
Well, call then.
I know you have my number.
Laters, baby.
[ Exhales, Giggles ]
Elliot seems like
a really nice guy.
No, no.
We’re starting with you.
If you’re seeing him
again tonight, that means
that something happened.
[ Sighs ]
Ana.
Mm-hmm.
Ana, you have to
tell me what happened.
I have to get ready for work.
We just kissed.
Once.
Only once?
That’s odd.
Mmm.
"Odd" doesn’t
even cover it.
Uh-huh.
And a new jacket.
Hmm.
Bye.
Hi.
It’s Taylor, right?
Good evening,
Miss Steele.
Mr. Grey will be
joining us there.
Good evening, Anastasia.
[ Woman ]
♪ Fading in, fading out ♪
♪♪ [ Continues ]
Wait.
You’re flying this?
♪ What are we waiting for? ♪
♪♪ [ Continues ]
[ Gasps ]
No escaping now.
November 1-2-2-4.
Charlie Tango,
ready to depart.
[ Radio: Man ]
Roger that, Charlie Tango.
Your flight plan
from Portland to Seattle
is cleared.
Seattle?
That’s where we’re going?
[ Laughs ]
♪ I’ll let you set the pace ♪
♪ ’Cause I’m not
thinking straight ♪
♪ My head’s spinning around ♪
♪ I can’t see clear no more ♪
♪ What are you waiting for? ♪
♪ Hold me like you do ♪
♪ H-Hold me
like you do ♪
♪ Like you do ♪
♪ Touch me like you do ♪
♪ T-T-Touch me like you do ♪
♪ Yeah-eah ♪
♪ Kiss me like you do ♪
♪ K-K-Kiss me
like you do ♪
♪ What are we waiting for? ♪
♪ Hold me like you do ♪
♪ H-H-Hold me
like you do ♪
♪ Whoa-ohh-ohh ♪
♪ Kiss me like you do ♪
♪ K-K-Kiss me
like you do ♪
♪ Ah-ah ♪
♪ What are we waiting for? ♪♪
Would you like
a drink?
Yes, please.
♪♪ [ Speakers: Opera,
Soprano Singing ]
Wow.
Do you play?
Yes.
[ Chuckles ]
Of course you do.
What’s this?
It’s a nondisclosure
agreement.
It means that you cannot
discuss anything about us
with anyone.
I’m afraid my lawyer
insists on it.
I’d never talk to anyone
about us anyway.
[ Pen Scratching On Paper ]
[ Sighs ]
Are you gonna make love
to me now?
Two things.
First, I don’t make love.
I fuck. Hard.
And the second thing?
Come.
It’s just beyond
this door.
What is?
My playroom.
Like your Xbox and stuff?
It’s important that you know
you can leave at any time.
Why?
What’s in there?
I meant what I said.
The helicopter’s on standby
to take you
whenever you wanna go.
Christian,
just open the door.
Oh, my God.
It’s called a flogger.
Say something, please.
Do women do this to you,
or do you–
No, I do this to women.
With women.
Women
who want me to.
You’re a sadist?
I’m a dominant.
What does that mean?
It means I want you
to willingly
surrender yourself to me.
Why would I do that?
To please me.
To please you?
How?
I have rules.
If you follow them,
I’ll reward you.
If you don’t,
I’ll punish you.
You’d punish me–
Like, you’d use
this stuff on me?
Yes.
What would I
get out of this?
Me.
If we were
to do this,
this would be
your room.
You can decorate it
however you like.
You want me
to m-move in?
Not full time.
Just Friday
through to Sunday.
We can negotiate
the particulars.
So– So, I’d sleep
in here with you?
No.
I’d be downstairs.
I told you,
I don’t sleep with anyone.
What if I don’t want
anything to do with that?
I would understand
completely.
But then we wouldn’t have
any sort of relationship at all?
This is the only sort
of relationship I have.
Why?
It’s the way I am.
When you said "negotiate,"
what did you mean?
I already have
a contract prepared.
It’s fairly detailed.
You would review it,
and we would negotiate
what you are and are not
willing to try.
How could I know
what I’d be willing to try?
Well, when you’ve had sex,
was there anything
that you didn’t like doing?
We have to be honest
with each other
for this to work, okay?
I don’t– I–
I wouldn’t know.
What do you mean?
Because I have–
I haven’t–
You’re still a virgin?
I have
just shown you–
I know. I just–
You’ve done
other things, right?
No.
[ Exhales ]
Where have you been?
Waiting.
Men must
throw themselves at you.
Never one I’ve wanted.
You’re biting your lip.
What are you doing?
Rectifying
the situation.
I’m a situation?
[ Woman ]
♪ Lonely float ♪
♪ Got in the way ♪
♪ You are the feel ♪
♪ And I knew it anyway ♪
♪ Take a chance ♪
♪ It wasn’t what you know ♪
♪ Take my hand ♪
♪ And don’t let go ♪
[ Sighs ]
♪♪ [ Vocalizing ]
♪ You can do it ♪
♪ You’re safe ♪
♪ Turn her on ♪
♪ With how you feel ♪
♪ Give her everything ♪
♪ She needs to hear ♪
♪ Give your heart ♪
♪ And say, "Come take it" ♪
♪ And she will see ♪
♪ That you’re a good ♪
♪ Man ♪
♪♪ [ Vocalizing ]
♪ You can do it ♪
♪ Don’t break ♪
♪ Yes, you can do it ♪
♪ Yeah, you’ll pull
through it ♪
♪ You’re safe ♪♪
♪♪ [ Piano ]
♪♪ [ Piano Continues ]
♪♪ [ Rock ]
[ Man ]
♪ I’ll never be
your beast of burden ♪
♪ My back is broad ♪
♪ But it’s a-hurtin’ ♪
♪ All I want is for you
to make love to me ♪
♪ Am I hard enough? ♪
♪ Am I rough enough? ♪
♪ Am I rich enough? ♪
♪ I’m not too blind ♪
♪ To see ♪♪
♪♪ [ Continues ]
[ Gasps ]
You’re energetic
this morning.
You hungry?
Very.
[ Sighs ]
’Cause I’m making pancakes.
Mmm.
Let’s get you
cleaned up.
Do you trust me?
Stay here.
Hold out
your wrists.
Hold them there.
You understand?
Tell me
you understand.
I won’t move my arms.
Good girl.
[ Moaning ]
-Stay still.
-Okay.
[ Moaning Continues ]
-Say "yes."
-To what?
To being mine.
[ Woman ]
Christian!
Shit.
What?
It’s my mother.
[ Laughing ]
-I’m naked.
-Get dressed.
And there’s no need
to show me around.
And there’s
no need to hover.
He’s still sleeping,
Dr. Grey.
He’s still sleeping?
But he never sleeps in.
Certainly not at this hour.
Unless, of course,
he’s ill. Is he– Ah.
Sorry, Mr. Grey.
It’s fine.
I know how she can be.
[ Chuckles ]
"She"?
Well, if you’re
trying to avoid me,
the very least
you can do is call me
by my correct name,
which would be "Mum."
Hi.
Ah!
Dear God.
Mother,
Anastasia Steele.
Ana, meet my mother,
Dr. Grace Trevelyan Grey.
You have no idea
how delighted I am
to meet you.
It’s nice to meet you too,
Dr. Grey.
Grace.
She’s very pretty–
You’re very pretty.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
[ Christian ]
What happened to calling
before dropping by?
And have your henchmen
give me the runaround?
No, thank you.
I’ll take my chances.
Anyway, I was in the
neighborhood, and I thought
perhaps we could have lunch.
I can’t today.
I have to
drive Ana home.
[ Phone Ringing ]
It’s okay. Take it.
I was just showing Mother out.
Excuse me.
[ Ringing Continues ]
[ Chuckles ]
Anastasia.
Kate, hold on.
It was a joy
to meet you.
I’m having
the whole family for dinner
next week at my house.
Christian’s sister, Mia,
is back from Paris.
You must come.
We’ll see, Mother.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
Kate?
Thank you.
I can’t talk about it
right now, Kate.
I– I gotta go.
I’ll call you back. Okay?
Everything okay
with the phone call?
Yeah.
Nothing important.
I liked your mom.
[ Scoffs ]
She’s excited.
She’s never seen me
with a woman before.
That was a first.
[ Sighs ]
What is it, Ana?
Um, I just–
How many women
have stayed in here?
Fifteen.
That’s a lot of women.
I told you before,
if you want out–
I don’t want out.
I just–
I’m not exactly jumping
at the opportunity...
to get whipped and tortured
in your red room of pain.
That room is much more
about pleasure.
Promise you.
Would we still go out to dinner
and– and movies, and–
That’s not really my thing.
Try to keep an open mind.
If you agree
to be my submissive,
I will be devoted to you.
This is what I want.
And I want it with you.
Why do I have to sleep
in here?
We slept in the same bed
last night, like normal people.
Try not to get hung up on
the sleeping arrangements.
If you agree to do this,
you’re gonna want
your own room.
Why? ’Cause I’ll be
your sex slave?
I don’t wanna do this here.
Let’s talk downstairs.
No. I think I’ll hold on
to my free will a little
while longer, thank you.
Actually, you know what?
I would like to go home.
Can I go home?
Which one’s yours?
All of them.
[ Man ]
♪ You make it look like
it’s magic ♪
♪ I see nobody ♪
♪ Nobody but you, you, you ♪
♪ I’m never confused ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ I’m so used to being used ♪
♪ So I love when you call ♪
♪ Unexpected ♪
♪ ’Cause I hate ♪
♪ When the moment’s expected ♪
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
♪ So I’m-a care for you ♪
♪ You, you ♪
♪ I’m-a care for you,
you, you, you ♪
♪ Yeah ♪♪
Let’s go for a walk.
How did you start
doing this?
One of my
mother’s friends.
I was 15.
She seduced you?
I was her submissive
for six years.
Seriously?
Does your mother
know that?
Of course not.
No one in my family
knows about
this... part of me.
So she introduced you
to all this?
Mrs. Robinson?
[ Christian ]
"Mrs. Robinson."
I’ll tell her
you said that.
She’ll love it.
You still
talk to her?
On occasion.
We’re friends.
Ana.
I know how intimidating
this is.
I felt the same at first.
Well...
what made you
change your mind?
By giving up control,
I felt free...
from responsibility,
from making decisions.
I felt safe.
You will too.
You’ll see.
I never took anyone
in the helicopter.
Never had sex
in my own bed.
Never slept
next to anyone.
Ever.
Only you.
This is the contract.
Read it carefully.
E-mail me if you have
any questions.
I told you,
my computer’s down.
Just consider it, okay?
I really hope
you say yes.
Thanks for the ride.
Laters, baby.
-Um–
-Okay, you’re all set.
-Your roommate let me in.
-I just figured that you
forgot to tell me about it.
Do I look okay?
Tell you about what?
Just sign here.
Hold on. Do you have
the right apartment?
Anastasia Steele?
Enjoy.
[ Kate ]
Another gift, huh?
Whatever happened to
flowers and chocolates?
[ Door Closes ]
I’m dying to hear everything.
But I have to run right now
because Elliot and I
are having dinner,
and then we’re going to
see a show at the Gorge.
José called for you.
Twice, by the way.
-The mail already come?
-The–
Oh. Uh, no. This is–
These are my thesis notes.
I left them at school.
Oh. All right.
Well, there’s yesterday’s mail.
What?
I don’t know.
You look... different.
I feel different.
Of course you do.
[ Chuckles ]
-Okay.
-Bye.
-[ Door Closes ]
[ Exhales ]
[ Chimes ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Christian’s Voice ]
The following are the terms
of a binding contract...
between the dominant
and the submissive.
The fundamental purpose
of this contract...
is to allow the submissive
to explore her sensuality
and her limits safely.
The dominant and submissive
agree and acknowledge...
that all that occurs
under the terms
of this contract...
will be consensual,
confidential...
and subject to the agreed limits
and safety procedures...
set out in this contract.
The submissive will agree
to any sexual activity...
deemed fit and pleasurable
by the dominant,
excepting those activities
outlined in Hard Limits.
The submissive agrees to
procure oral contraception...
from a physician
of the dominant’s choosing.
The submissive will not enter
into sexual relations...
with anyone
other than the dominant.
The submissive
will eat regularly,
to maintain
her health and well-being,
from a prescribed
list of foods.
[ Men Chattering ]
The submissive will not
drink to excess, smoke
or take recreational drugs.
The submissive shall
always conduct herself...
in a respectful manner
to the dominant,
and she’ll address him
only as "Sir," "Mr. Grey,"
or such other title
as the dominant may direct.
The submissive may not
touch the dominant...
without his express
permission to do so.
The safeword "yellow"
will be used...
to bring to the attention
of the dominant...
that the submissive
is close to her limit.
When the safeword "red"
is spoken,
the dominant’s action
will cease completely
and immediately.
Does the submissive consent
to being restrained,
with hands bound in front?
Does the submissive consent
to being blindfolded?
to being gagged?
How much pain is the submissive
willing to experience?
[ Chimes ]
It was nice
knowing you.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Whooshing Sound ]
[ Phone Chimes ]
♪♪ [ Earbuds: Rock ]
♪♪ [ Humming ]
[ Gasps ]
Christian.
It’s been nice knowing me,
has it?
[ Nervous Chuckle ]
[ Gasps ]
Let me remind you
how nice it was.
Is this what you want?
[ Woman ]
♪ It’s what you do ♪
♪ It’s what you see ♪
♪ I know if I’m haunting you ♪
♪ You must be hauntin’ me ♪
[ Laughs ]
Wait.
♪ It’s where we go ♪
♪ It’s where we’ll be ♪
♪ I know if I’m on to you ♪
♪ I’m on to you ♪
Don’t make a sound.
♪ On to you ♪
♪ You must be on to me ♪
♪ My haunted lungs ♪
♪ Ghost in the sheets ♪
♪ I know if I’m haunting you ♪
♪ You must be hauntin’ me ♪
♪ My wicked tongue ♪
♪ Where will it be? ♪
♪ I know if I’m on to you ♪
♪ I’m on to you, on to you ♪
♪ I’m on to you ♪
♪ On to you
You must be on to me ♪
[ Gasps ]
♪ My haunted lungs ♪
♪ Ghost in the sheets ♪
♪ I know if I’m haunting you ♪
♪ You must be haunting me ♪
♪ My wicked tongue ♪
♪ Where will it be? ♪
♪ I know if I’m on to you ♪
♪ You must be on to me ♪
[ Moans ]
Was this nice?
♪ I know if I’m on to you ♪
♪ I’m on to you ♪
♪ On to you
I’m on to you ♪
You must be on to me ♪
[ Moaning ] Yes.
♪ You must be on to me ♪♪
That was really nice.
[ Sighs ]
What are you doing to me?
Come on.
What about here?
Why not?
Is it breaking the rules?
Speaking of which–
I haven’t
made up my mind yet.
You’re not staying?
I told you,
I don’t sleep with anyone.
Well, can we negotiate?
[ Chuckles ]
[ Chimes ]
[ Typing ]
[ Bell Dings ]
Now, that’s a hell
of a sack, Miss Steele.
Business meeting.
[ Sighs ]
Impressive.
I’ve done this before.
Business meetings,
I mean.
Oh. Uh–
Miss Steele.
-Hmm?
-Your meeting.
Page one, strike out
my old address...
and replace
with the new one.
An oversight.
Duly noted.
Page three, section 15-20.
"The submissive shall submit
to any sexual activity...
demanded by the dominant...
and shall do so without
hesitation or argument."
[ Laughing ]
Uh, turn to page five.
Appendix three,
"Soft limits."
With you.
-Find "anal fisting."
-I’m all ears.
Strike it out.
Strike out
"vaginal fisting" too.
-Are you sure?
-Yep.
Same page, "Is the use
of sex toys acceptable
to the submissive?"
Vibrators, okay.
Dildos, fine.
Genital clamps?
Absolutely not.
Consider them gone.
What are butt plugs?
You must go through
quite a few nondisclosure
agreements.
My staff know
only what I choose
to tell them.
Please resume,
Miss Steele.
[ Clears Throat ]
Also on page five,
there are some terms
which need clarification.
"Suspension"?
Hanging on ropes
from the ceiling.
For what possible reason?
For your pleasure.
-Really?
-And mine.
Something to consider.
No. Hard limit.
"Is bondage acceptable
to the submissive?"
I’m good with rope,
leather cuffs, handcuffs.
Please lose "tape."
And, uh, what’s "Other"?
Cable ties.
Can I just say
how impressed I am...
with your commitment
to this meeting?
And in that spirit,
I’m gonna throw in
a sweetener.
How about once a week,
on a night
of your choosing,
we go on a date?
Just like
a regular couple.
Dinner, movie...
ice skating.
Whatever you want.
Accepted.
You’re very kind.
I’ll suggest it
in appendix five.
I would like to fuck you
into the middle of next week.
[ Chuckles ]
You’re not fighting fair.
I never have.
I’ll review all these changes
and try to arrive at a decision.
-You want to leave?
-Yes.
But your body tells me
something different.
Your legs, for instance.
The way you’re pressing
your thighs together
under the table.
And the change
in your breathing.
-And in your complexion.
-My complexion?
You’re flushed.
That could just be the wine.
It’s the adrenaline.
Let’s say I did stay.
What would happen?
First,
I would help you out of
that little dress of yours.
Yes.
And I’d be pleased to discover
that you’re naked underneath.
Really?
Then I would
bend you over.
-Right here?
-Yes.
On this table?
Yes.
Thank you for the meeting,
Mr. Grey.
This is me.
Didn’t know
I was a collector
of classic cars, huh?
You sure I can’t
persuade you to stay?
Good night, Christian.
When will you know?
Soon, maybe.
Why do I think you’re
telling me good-bye?
Because I’m leaving.
[ Engine Starts ]
[ Door Closes ]
You got your valedictory
speech ready?
Oh, more or less.
Annie!
Dad!
[ Laughing ]
Hi.
Sorry I’m late.
I had a hell of a time
parking.
That’s okay. You’re here.
That’s all that matters.
You kidding me?
I wouldn’t miss this
for the world.
I saved you a seat
next to Kate’s parents, okay?
Anywhere you want me,
sweetheart.
Okay. I’ll see you after.
Yeah.
Good luck up there.
And he’s also a major benefactor
to our university.
Please join me in welcoming...
Mr. Christian Grey.
[ Applause ]
Thank you.
I am deeply moved
by the great compliment
accorded to me today.
He is so hot.
Oh, gosh. He so is.
[ Christian Continues ]
[ Clears Throat ]
I heard he’s gay.
The goal?
To help eradicate
hunger and poverty
across the globe.
I, myself,
have known what it’s like
to be profoundly hungry.
So this is a very personal
mission for me.
[ Applause ]
[ Woman ]
Megan Soliah.
Anastasia Steele.
[ Applause ]
You’ve done really well.
Very proud of you.
Thank you.
Nancy Steinz.
Congratulations.
You should be very proud.
I am.
Nice tie, by the way.
It’s recently
become my favorite.
Do you have your answer yet?
I’m still thinking.
Anastasia,
just try it my way. Please.
Okay.
What?
[ Chuckles ]
Congratulations.
Thank you.
We did it.
I know.
Dad! Hi!
I am so proud of you,
Annie.
Thank you.
Ah!
And, Kate,
best valedictorian
speech ever.
Oh, thank you.
It was awesome.
Yeah–
Hi.
Ray, have you met
Christian Grey,
Ana’s boyfriend?
Ah. Great pleasure
to meet you.
-Likewise. I really
enjoyed your speech.
-Thank you, sir.
Sounds like you’ve
accomplished some pretty
impressive things.
I’ll say.
Thank you.
I’m gonna go find my family,
who’ve been patiently waiting
to embarrass me.
Bye. Come see us
in Seattle, okay?
Yeah, as soon as I
get an invitation.
[ Chuckling ]
So, how long you two
known each other?
Um–
A few weeks now.
We actually met
when Anastasia interviewed me
for the student newspaper.
-Uh, picture, please, Mr. Grey?
-Uh, excuse us a moment.
Yeah, it’s fine.
Big smile now.
[ Pops ]
[ Man On Stereo: R & B ]
♪ The most delicate creature ♪
♪ She will be the queen
of the streets ♪
♪ Precious love and attention ♪
To celebrate your graduation,
among other things.
[ Clicks Tongue ]
Roll your eyes at me again,
and I will take you
across my knee.
Oh.
So it begins.
[ Buzzing ]
Come on. I have
something to show you.
What?
That’s cute.
Doesn’t really seem
like your style though.
It’s not.
Happy graduation,
Anastasia.
Oh, my God.
Christian, that’s a car.
You don’t miss much,
do you?
Thank you, but I can’t–
That– This is, uh–
Do you like it?
Of course I like it.
It’s beautiful.
But I have a car.
I have–
Where’s my car?
I told Taylor
to fetch a decent price.
Oh! Christian,
this is way too much.
Did you just
roll your eyes at me?
[ Squeals ]
-Do you know why
I’m doing this?
-Because I rolled my eyes.
-And is that polite?
-[ Chuckles ]
-No.
-Excuse me?
No, sir.
[ Breathing Heavily ]
[ Gasping ]
[ Gasps, Panting ]
Do you want more?
[ Spanks ]
[ Whimpers ]
Welcome to my world.
What are you doing?
I have a few things
at the office that
require my attention.
You okay?
I just thought that–
I enjoyed tonight.
I’ll see you
at my place tomorrow.
[ Door Opens, Closes ]
[ Phone Ringing,
Buzzing ]
Hi, Mama.
Anastasia,
what’s going on?
I have left you
two messages this week.
I know.
I’m sorry. I–
There, uh–
I just got
a little distracted.
Sorry I missed
your graduation, honey.
I heard it was lovely.
And your new beau?
Ray told me all about him.
He sounds like quite
the young man.
Of course, I would have
preferred to have heard
about him from you.
[ Sighs ]
Ana?
What’s the matter?
[ Sniffles ]
Nothing. I’m fine.
Is he not
making you happy?
He is, yeah.
Uh, most of the time,
yeah.
It’s complicated.
Listen, honey, if–
if you need a break,
you just come
right on down here.
Even if it’s
for a day or two.
I have air miles,
and we could talk
and have girl time.
[ Sniffles ]
Promise me you’ll
think about it.
Yeah, I promise.
I promise.
I love you, Mama.
I love you too,
darling.
I gotta go.
[ Sighs ]
Bye.
Looks like you and Grey
did some celebrating
last night.
[ Chuckling ]
Is he still asleep?
Uh, no,
he couldn’t stay.
Whose car keys
are those then?
Those are my keys.
Wow, Ana.
What?
Nothing. I just–
Make sure you’re taking it
at your own pace, okay?
I am, I am.
I gotta go.
Where are you going?
Look at this.
I’ve seen it.
That’s not a bad picture.
"Christian Grey
with friend."
It says we’re friends.
Well, it must be true
if it’s in the paper.
Mmm.
So how’d it go
with Dr. Greene?
It was fine.
But she said that I have to
abstain from all sexual activity
for at least four weeks.
You know,
after I start the pill.
What?
I’m just kidding.
[ Man On Stereo ]
♪ Oh, I’m on fire ♪
I wanna take you
to my playroom.
But I haven’t signed
the contract.
I’m well aware.
Call it due diligence.
Okay.
You ready?
Eyes down.
Take off your shoes.
Arms above your head.
You have a beautiful body,
Anastasia.
I want you unashamed
of your nakedness.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
You’re biting your lip.
You know what
that does to me.
Turn around.
When I tell you
to come into this room,
this is how you’ll be.
You’ll wait for me,
kneeling by the door.
Do it now.
Hands flat on your thighs.
Good.
[ Gasps ]
Hold out your hand.
[ Breathing Shakily ]
[ Gasps ]
Did that hurt?
No.
You see?
Most of your fear
is in your head.
Come.
[ Clicking, Rattling ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Inhales ]
[ Gasps ]
[ Woman ]
♪ I look and stare
so deep in your eyes ♪
How does it feel?
♪ I touch on you
more and more every time ♪
Good, sir.
♪ When you leave,
I’m begging you not to go ♪
♪ Call your name
two, three times in a row ♪
♪ Such a funny thing
for me to try to explain ♪
[ Gasps ]
♪ How I’m feeling
and my pride is the one
to blame ♪
[ Slaps ]
[ Gasps ]
♪ I still don’t understand ♪
Mmm.
Quiet.
♪ Just how your love could do
what no one else can ♪
♪ Got me looking so crazy
right now ♪
♪ Your love’s got me looking
so crazy right now ♪
♪ Got me looking
♪ Your touch got me looking
so crazy right now ♪
♪ Your love ♪
♪ Hoping you’ll save me
right now ♪
♪ Your kiss got me hoping
you’ll save me right now ♪
[ Gasps ]
♪ Looking so crazy in love ♪
♪ Got me hoping
you’ll save me right now ♪
♪ Your kiss got me hoping
♪ Got me so crazy in love ♪♪
[ Panting ]
♪♪ [ Man Singing On Stereo,
Faint ]
♪ And I’ve got
no defense for it ♪
♪ The heat
is too intense for it ♪
Where are we going?
♪ What good would common sense
for it do? ♪
Remember my mother
mentioned dinner?
-My sister Mia’s in town.
-Yeah.
♪ Wicked witchcraft ♪
You got
everything you need?
Yeah.
♪ And although I know
it’s strictly taboo ♪
Dance with me.
♪ When you arouse
the need in me ♪
♪ My heart says "Yes, indeed"
in me ♪
♪ Proceed with what
you’re leading me to ♪
♪ It’s such an ancient pitch ♪
♪ But one that
I’d never switch ♪
♪ ’Cause there’s
no nicer witch than you ♪♪
[ Giggles ]
♪♪ [ Ends ]
-Good evening, Mr. Grey.
-They’re here.
You’re here.
Welcome, welcome.
-Ana, Mother, you’ve met.
-Hi. Good to see you.
And this is my father,
Carrick.
Hi. Pleasure to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Is she here?
You are the subject
of some speculation.
Oh, my God! You exist!
It’s a great apartment,
and the rent’s not ridiculous.
Elliot and José
helped us move in.
José is Ana’s friend,
although I think that Elliot’s
trying to poach him.
They’ve sparked
quite the bromance.
He’s a cool guy.
Ana, where is
your family from?
My stepfather
lives in Montesano,
and my mom’s in Georgia.
[ Gasps ]
Georgia? Which part?
-Savannah.
-How nice.
Although I do hear it gets
rather humid in Georgia
at this time of year.
Oh, my God, it does.
It’s stifling sometimes.
Actually, I’m going
to visit her tomorrow.
Oh! How nice.
Mm-hmm.
You hear that, Christian?
Some children
do visit their parents
now and again.
Hey, Dad, you catch
the Mariners game?
-Uh, heard it went
to extra innings.
-Ugh!
Seattle baseball.
[ Speaking French ]
-This is news to me.
-I don’t know what
she just said.
But it didn’t sound
like "Go, M’s."
When were you gonna tell me?
[ Grace ]
Who wants coffee?
Actually, I promised Ana
a tour of the grounds.
Excuse us.
Christian,
I cannot walk that fast
in these shoes.
Ah!
When were you gonna
tell me about Georgia?
What?
You have no right
to be mad.
Yeah, but I am mad.
Palm-twitchingly mad.
Ow!
You’re mine. All mine.
You understand?
Christian,
you are so confusing.
Ana.
What do you want?
I want you.
I’m trying, Christian.
I know you are.
Why can’t we sleep
in the same bed?
Why won’t you
let me touch you?
Why does it have
to be like this?
If you would just sign
the contract, you wouldn’t
have to think about any–
Why do you care so much
about the contract, Christian?
Don’t you like me
the way I am?
Of course I do.
Then why are you trying
to change me?
I’m not.
It’s–
I need more.
I want more.
Hearts and flowers?
That’s not
something I know.
Ana, please.
It’s you
that’s changing me.
Let me touch you.
Let me.
Are they burns?
I had a rough start
in life.
That’s all
you need to know.
Okay.
The woman
that gave birth to me...
was a crack addict...
and a prostitute.
She died
when I was four.
I remember certain things.
Terrible things.
But I don’t remember her.
But sometimes,
I think I see her
in my dreams.
Mmm.
Do you really have to
go to Georgia?
Yeah, I really do.
Oh!
Gazpacho
is very healthy, Bob.
Yeah.
You’ll get fat with
all this sitting around.
You tell him, Ana.
I’m not gonna
tell him that.
Yes, thank you, Ana.
I’m just saying that,
you know, gazpacho is basically
eating a bowl of salsa.
You know, you should
hand me some chips with
my bowl of salsa here.
You can have a carrot.
What are you
getting at with this?
[ Chuckling ]
You are damn lucky
that I just happen to
love you very much.
I know that.
Do you?
Mmm, I do.
[ Laughing, Chattering ]
[ Mother ]
Bob!
[ Chuckles ]
[ Phone Chimes ]
[ Chimes ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Line Ringing ]
[ Buzzing ]
[ Sighs ]
[ Mother ]
Ooh! Darling, I think
we should pace ourselves.
Or at least order
something to eat.
You go ahead.
I’m not very hungry.
Oh. I’ll just have
the fruit salad.
-[ Chuckles ]
-[ Chimes, Buzzes ]
He can wait.
Mom.
Holy fuck.
What?
What is it?
It’s Christian.
He’s here, um,
in Georgia.
Oh, uh, here here.
Mrs. Adams.
Delighted to meet you.
Something to drink, sir?
Gin and tonic.
Hendrick’s, if you have it.
Otherwise, Bombay Sapphire.
Cucumber with the Hendrick’s,
lime with the Bombay.
I like him already.
What are you doing here,
Christian?
I came to see you.
I’m gonna step outside
for a bit.
I broke rule seven,
clause five.
Here.
We’ll let it go.
Let’s not talk about
the contract right now.
How was your dinner?
She’s a friend.
That’s all.
She’s a child abuser.
I confide in her.
She knows me.
Well, what did she
advise you to do?
Well, I’m here.
And now what?
I’ve got a room
in this hotel.
Well, I hope you’ll
be comfortable in it.
What are you doing
for breakfast tomorrow?
Where are we going?
It’s a surprise.
[ Sighs ]
I think I’ve reached
my quota of surprises.
We’re almost there.
[ Woman ]
♪ Why does he want to
bring me where he goes? ♪
Mr. Grey. Hey.
I’ll be your tow pilot.
How do you do?
This is my girlfriend,
Anastasia Steele.
♪ It’s enough to make you
wanna try for one last night ♪
♪ Ghosts and silhouettes ♪
♪ They took a piece of me
They want it all ♪
♪ Oh, but to wait
in an empty room ♪
We’re at 3,000 feet.
Y’all ready?
Well?
[ Giggles ]
Yeah, do it.
[ Christian ]
Release.
-♪ I had a dream I was dying ♪
-[ Squealing ]
♪ But I found nobody there ♪
♪ And if one last night
is all that we’ve been given ♪
♪ Let’s live it like we care ♪
♪ For one last night ♪
[ Christian ]
Hold on tight.
♪ For one last night ♪
[ Anastasia Squeals,
Laughs ]
-Is this more?
-Oh, my God.
So much more!
[ Laughing ]
♪ Broken upon the rocks ♪
♪ It’s enough to make you
wanna try for ♪
♪ One last night ♪♪
[ Anastasia Laughing ]
Oh, my God.
That was incredible,
Christian.
Thank you.
Well, we aim to please,
Miss Steele.
And you said you
didn’t do romance.
I don’t.
Mmm.
Ana.
What?
What? Why are you
fighting this?
What are you afraid of?
[ Phone Ringing ]
Grey.
What? When?
Tell Stephan
to have the plane ready.
I’ll be on the tarmac
in 30 minutes.
What happened?
I have to go back
to Seattle.
Come.
I’ll take you home.
Oh, sweetheart.
I wish Christian
could have stayed.
Bob was really
looking forward
to meeting him.
I know. He had to
get back to Seattle though.
There was some situation
at work.
I wish I could tell you
that things get easier,
but they don’t.
You just get to
know yourself better.
Thank you
for everything, Mama.
Take care of yourself,
sweetheart.
I will.
Did you think I wouldn’t
recognize you, Taylor?
Miss Steele.
How does he seem today,
Taylor?
Preoccupied, I’m afraid.
-Really?
-Yes, ma’am.
[ Christian ]
That’s not gonna work.
When?
Well, then tell them that
they don’t have 24 hours.
That is unacceptable.
I need to know.
Just keep me informed.
Is everything okay?
Nothing that concerns you.
I can leave.
Do you want me to go?
No.
No, that’s
the last thing I want.
I want you...
to be in the playroom
in 15 minutes.
What are your safe words?
"Red" and "yellow."
Remember those.
[ Inhales Deeply ]
Mmm.
[ Gasps ]
♪♪ [ Piano: Classical ]
It sounds so sad.
Everything you play
is so sad.
You said you were six
when you learned.
Was it because you wanted
to please your new family?
♪♪ [ Notes ]
I just wanna talk.
Why won’t you
let me in?
We should be talking.
Like normal people?
Yeah.
Is that so wrong?
Is this because
of the contract, because
I still haven’t signed it?
Fuck the contract.
I think
it’s a little redundant,
don’t you?
So, then the rules
are redundant too?
No. The rules stand.
And what if I break them?
Then there’ll
be consequences.
Punishment.
Yes.
Why do you want
to punish me?
Ana.
Why do you want to hurt me?
I would never
do anything to you
that you couldn’t handle.
But why do you even
want to do anything to me
at all, Christian?
If I told you,
you’d never look at me
the same way again.
[ Inhales ]
So there is a reason.
Tell me.
Do you want to
punish me right now?
Yes.
I want to punish you
right now.
What if I told you
that I feel the same way
about being punished...
as you do
about me touching you?
Would you still
want to punish me then?
No.
But that doesn’t mean
I wouldn’t need to.
Why?
Ana, stop.
Why do you need to?
Because it’s the way I am!
’Cause I am 50 shades
of fucked up.
Show me then.
I need you to show me...
what you want to do to me.
Punish me.
Show me how bad
it can be.
I want you
to show me the worst.
It’s the only way
I can understand.
Are you sure about this?
Yes.
Bend over.
I’m gonna hit you
six times.
And you’re gonna
count with me.
[ Gasps ]
Count, Anastasia.
One.
[ Grunts ]
[ Whispers ]
Two.
[ Sighs ]
[ Crying ]
Three.
[ Gasps ]
Four.
[ Belt Slaps ]
Five.
[ Sighs ]
Six.
No! Don’t fucking
touch me.
This is what you want?
You wanna see–
You wanna see me like this?
-Ana.
-Don’t come near me.
Does this
give you pleasure?
Don’t.
Don’t you dare come near me.
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
[ Rain Falling ]
[ Crying ]
Please don’t hate me.
You’ll never
do that to me again.
I’m not what you want.
No, y-you’re everything
that I want.
I’ve fallen in love
with you.
No.
No, Ana,
you can’t love me.
[ Sobs ]
I need you to leave.
Please.
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
I’d like my car back.
Taylor already sold it.
Then I’d like the money
he got for it, please.
I’ll send you a check.
Okay.
Taylor will take you home.
Stop.
No!
-Ana.
-Christian.
[ Man ]
♪ I’m-a care for you ♪
♪ I’m-a care for you,
you, you, you ♪
♪ You make it look
like it’s magic ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ ’Cause I see nobody,
nobody but you, you, you ♪
♪ I’m never confused ♪
♪ Hey, hey ♪
♪ I’m so used to being used ♪
♪ So I love
when you call unexpected ♪
♪ ’Cause I hate
when the moment’s expected ♪
♪ So I’m-a care for you,
you, you ♪
♪ I’m-a care for you,
you, you, you ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ ’Cause, girl, you’re perfect ♪
♪ Girl, you’re perfect ♪
♪ You’re always worth it ♪
♪ Always worth it ♪
♪ And you deserve it ♪
♪ You deserve it ♪
♪ The way you work it ♪
♪ ’Cause, girl, you earned it ♪
♪ Earned it ♪
♪ Goddamn ♪
♪ Yeah, on that lonely night ♪
♪ Lonely night ♪
♪ We said
it wouldn’t be love ♪
♪ But we felt the rush ♪
♪ It made us believe ♪
♪ It was only us ♪
♪ Was only us ♪
♪ Convinced we were broken
inside ♪
♪ ’Cause, girl, you earned it ♪
♪ You did, yeah ♪
♪ Earned it ♪
♪♪ [ Vocalizing ]
♪♪ [ Fades ]
[ Woman ]
♪ I believe, I believe
there’s love in you ♪
♪ Gridlocked
on the dusty avenues ♪
♪ Inside your heart,
just afraid to go ♪
♪ Don’t complicate it ♪
♪ Don’t let the past dictate ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I have been patient ♪
♪ But slowly
I’m losing faith ♪
♪ So, please ♪
♪ I know you, baby ♪
♪ I believe, I believe
you could love me ♪
♪ But you’re lost
on the road to misery ♪
♪ And what I gave to you ♪
♪ I can never get back ♪
♪ Say what you will ♪
♪ But I know
that you want to stay ♪
♪ So, please ♪
♪ I know you, baby ♪
♪ The shadows of your heart ♪
♪ Are hanging
in the sweet, sweet air ♪
♪ I know you, baby ♪
♪ The secrets that you hide
control us ♪
♪ And it’s just not fair ♪
♪ I know you, baby ♪♪
[ Man ]
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, yeah, oh, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ I feel the blood rushing
throughout your body ♪
♪ You see the scars
painted over my skin ♪
♪♪ [ Vocalizing ]
♪ I’m always numb
to the topic of loving ♪
♪ I fell in love
with the subject of sin ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I don’t have to remind you ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ It’s my need to confine you ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ I see your face every time
I’m with somebody else ♪
♪ Can’t you see
that I want you? ♪
♪ Put your feelings
behind you ♪
♪ I don’t have to remind you ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Where you belong ♪
♪ Where you belong, long, long ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪♪