Alex.
Tod and George's dad just called.
He's picking you up at 3:30 tomorrow.
And the bus leaves the high school
for the airport around 5.
How's my suitcase working out for you?
Mom, Mom, Mom,
you gotta leave that on.
Yeah, it's like you know,
The tag made the last flight without
the plane crashing or anything.
So I figure,
it's gotta be on the bag
or at least with the bag.
For luck.
Where would you get
a nutball idea like that?
I'm still here.
So...
17, on the loose.
Senior trip with your friends...
in Paris. Ten days in the springtime.
Live it up, Alex.
You got your whole life ahead of you.
Alex.
The white zone is for immediate loading
and unloading of passengers only.
No parking.
Hey, Hitchcock.
What?
Let me give you a hand with this, man.
No...
There you go.
Carter, you dick.
Schmuck.
Good one.
You left this on the bus.
Thanks, come on,
let's get your stuff together.
Hey, Christa.
Hi, Blake.
What are you doing?
He's the man. The man.
Alright, you guys got everything?
Yeah, yeah Dad, we're all set.
Students,
Let's go to France.
Does that mean...
go?
Don't know.
Look, this is for both of you,
alright?
Have a great time.
Thanks, Dad.
Yeah.
Both of us.
Let's go.
Alex.
Yes?
You take care of them.
I will.
I... I didn't think anything
could look worse than my yearbook photo.
How do you think I feel having
to look at you all the time?
Hey children, listen!
Excuse me, listen!
What is the call?
What the fuck does he want?
Airport is not responsible
for their activities
Thank you.
The airport does not endorse solicitors.
Good Clear, is correct
So...
Follow me.
We are going to France.
Death is not the end.
It will be for you
if you harass my students.
Hare Rama.
Fuck off.
I have to ask you a few questions
this evening.
Did you pack your bags yourself?
Have your belongings remained
in your possession the entire time?
Mr. Browning?
Yeah.
Have you received any packages
from persons unknown to you?
Same as your birthday.
What?
September 25,
9:25.
Your birthday's the same
as your departure time.
Because I looked at him.
Are you sure?
Lisa, wait up.
No, it's ok.
Fuck, that was good.
Dick.
Hey.
Hey, George, Dad said both.
Both of us, alright, man?
Come on, just give me some cash.
Hey, hey, knock it off.
Excuse me.
Catch.
You asshole.
Thanks.
You're welcome.
Alex,
let's go take a shit.
Why don't you go by yourself?
No, no, no, dude. Listen, ok?
Listen, take some knowledge.
We're about to board a seven-hour flight.
The toilets in coach are...
barely ventilated closets,
alright if that.
Now let's say halfway
through the flight right,
your body wants that food out.
You gotta go torque a wicked cable.
And then right after you...
like directly after you walks in...
Christa or Blake.
Did you want them to associate you
with that watery sting in their eye?
That reflexive gag
at the back of their throat?
John Denver.
Died in a plane crash.
Ladies and gentlemen,
thank you for your patience.
At this time, we would like
to begin preboarding
of Volée Air Flight,
180 to Paris,
through Gate 46.
Anyone seen Billy Hitchcock?
How did we lose him?
21.22.23.
Come sir.
Go. Go.
25.
26.
Go.
That hurt.
My little baby.
That's a good sign.
The younger, the better.
It'd be a fucked-up God
to take down this plane.
Hi.
A really fucked-up God.
Hey, Tod.
Hello. How you doing?
I'm gonna sit here.
Can you switch seats with Christa?
God.
You know, I would,
but I got a bladder thing.
It's a urinary tract infection.
Let's go ask Alex.
Alex,
could you trade seats with Blake
so she and I could sit together?
She asked Tod, but he said
he had some sort of medical thing.
Please?
Yeah.
You're so sweet.
Thanks Alex.
Thank you, Alex.
You're welcome, you're welcome.
Fag.
Did you...
really think we're gonna
titty fuck them over Greenland?
You know,
because of you, I gotta sit here
and watch
fucking Stuart Little.
Thank you.
Thanks man.
That's great.
Sorry I'm late.
Your number?
This way please.
That's my seat right there.
Hello?
I'm going that way.
May I have your attention?
To properly fasten your seat belts,
slide the flat portion into the buckle.
Equipped with six emergency exits.
Two in front, two over the wing, two in the rear.
All exits are clearly marked.
Follow the red exit signs
and public lighting in the aisle way.
Flight attendants, prepare for departure.
Atention!
Our journey begins!
Alright!
Yeah.
Whatever.
It's ok.
I wanna go.
It's fine.
It's ok, honey, I...
What the fuck...
Oh my God!
Everybody!
Quick. Quick. Quick.
No! No!
Christa! No!
Alex,
could you trade seats with Blake
so she and I could sit together?
She asked Tod, but he said
he had some medical thing.
Please?
What's up, dude?
Is there a problem, sir?
What's your problem?
Alex, what happen?
The fucking plane's gonna explode.
Shut up Browning.
You're so not funny.
If this is your joke
It's not a joke. It's not a joke.
Alex take it easy.
That's it sit down, Browning.
It's going down.
We will remove you fro this airplane.
I'll remove him.
I'll remove myself.
Excuse me.
Get off him.
That's my seat right there.
This plane is going down.
Everybody in the aisle, off the plane.
Get off the plane.
Stay where you are.
Just sit tight.
The fucking plane is going down.
Go check him out.
See how he's doing.
Ok.
I got my ticket here.
Get off me.
Jerk.
Hey.
You got this?
No one gets back on board.
That's my call.
Wait, please.
I've got 40 students
going to Paris, please.
Please.
Look, you must understand my position.
I do, I understand and I apologize for Alex.
But one of us needs to be on that plane.
I cannot let students
go to Paris for ten days
Carter no!
Sit the fuck down, Carter.
Sit.
One of you can go on the flight
and that's it.
Larry.
Look, the airline's not taking this very well.
But they'll let one of us back on, it's fine.
The rest of us can take an 11:10 flight. It
gets in three hours later, it's alright.
I'll stay.
No, no, you know the whole French thing.
Get on the plane,
it's fine.
Hi, Mr. Murnau. See, I was in the bathroom.
And the lock, it was stuck and...
Wait, I didn't fight with anyone.
Damn.
Thanks.
I just, I called your parents.
They're on their way.
We should be going.
Alex, talk to me.
Tell me what happened.
I saw it.
Like, I don't know. I saw it.
I saw it...
on the runway. I saw it take off.
I saw out my window, I saw...
the ground and, and...
Carter.
The cabin, it starts to shake, right.
And...
the left side blows up.
And then the whole plane just explodes.
And it was so real.
Just like how everything happens,
you know?
You been on planes that blew up?
You must have fallen asleep.
We get thrown off the plane.
We blow what, a half a day in Paris
all because Browning
has a bad fucking dream?
But wait, the plane,
it's gonna blow up.
It's gonna blow up.
Hey, hey.
Fuck you, Horton.
Tod.
The only trip you're taking
is to the fucking hospital.
Get off him.
Hey, hey!
Alex!
Stop it!
Come on, now.
There they go,
here we stay.
You're paying for my trip, Browning.
I wish you were on that plane.
You fucking prick.
Shit!
Call it in. Security
You're looking at me as if I caused this.
I didn't cause this.
Are there any survivors?
How should I know?
What, you think I'm some sort of?
He's not a witch.
Hello, I'm Howard Seigel,
National Transportation Safety Board.
We've contacted all your families.
They are on the way.
Is there anyone here who...
feels they might need
a little medical attention
or spiritual counseling at this time?
What's going on?
Are there any survivors?
Well, the cause for the explosion
is still undetermined.
The Nassau County authorities
are on the scene.
Naval Search and Rescue en route.
We...
Excuse me.
I'm agent Weine, this is agent Schreck.
We're with the FBI.
I understand how you all
must be feeling right now.
I know it's gonna be difficult for you.
We're gonna ask you couple of questions
regarding today's events,
while they're still fresh in your mind.
This will prove invaluable
to our rescue attempts
and any potential criminal investigation.
You said, listen to me.
This plane will explode on takeoff.
How did you know that?
I got this feeling.
This weird feeling.
Did you take any sedatives
before boarding the plane,
or on board did you take any sleeping,
pills, any narcotics, hallucinogens?
Alex, do you take any drugs?
No.
I saw it.
I saw it happen.
I saw the plane explode.
Did the real feelings have anything
to do with your saying that
you wished that Carter
Horton was on the plane
just before it exploded?
No.
Then why'd you say it?
Because I really didn't think
it was gonna happen.
If that's the case Alex,
then why did you really
get off the plane?
My brother George,
he told me to go,
and keep an eye on Alex.
And...
so...
he stayed and...
He told me to get off the plane.
Larry Murnau said...
I should get back on but I...
I told him that he should go.
I sent him back on the plane.
Alright.
Nobody forced you off the plane.
You said you weren't friends
with those that were.
So Clear, why did you get off the plane?
Because I saw and I heard Alex.
And I believed him.
Honey.
God.
There he is.
Over here.
Thank you for the ride.
You're looking
at the first piece of debris
to wash ashore
from Volée Air Flight 180.
Which erupted shortly
after a 9:25 p.m. take off
from John F. Kennedy Airport
in New York.
There are no known survivors.
However, Coast Guard
and Naval Search and Rescue efforts
are continuing at this moment,
even as jet fuel burns
on the ocean's surface.
Authorities are pessimistic
about the possibility
of finding anyone alive
from the ill-fated flight.
All 287 passengers are feared dead.
Amongst the travelers,
a class of 40 students and four teachers
from Mount Abraham High School
in southeast New York
en route to Paris on a field trip.
There are reports that several students
were removed from the aircraft
moments before departure.
However investigators remain guarded
about the specifics of this incident.
Authorities from the National
Transportation and Safety Board
and the Federal Bureau of Investigation
have arrived at JFK
to begin the initial investigation.
Eyewitnesses at the airport,
as well as on Long Island
report seeing the plane explode.
No other aircraft
were visibly near Flight 180.
At JFK, air traffic controllers
are corroborating
these eyewitness accounts.
After the explosion,
debris apparently rained into the
Atlantic Ocean for several miles.
However, investigators are cautious
about verifying these accounts
believing they'll learn more from the
found debris when daylight arrives.
Thirty-nine days have passed
since we lost our 39 loved ones,
friends and teachers.
As each day passes,
without a determining cause
for the accident
we ask ourselves.
Why?
Ecclesiastes tells us:
Man,
no more knows his own time,
than fish taken in the fatal net
or birds trapped in the snare.
Like these,
the children of men caught,
when the time falls
suddenly upon them.
And so before we can heal,
before we can escape
the presence of death,
and time,
we must mourn and celebrate theirs,
with this...
memorial.
I hope you don't think
because my name ain't up on this wall
that I owe you anything.
I don't.
Because all I owe are these people.
To live my life to the fullest.
Why don't you stay off the J.D.,
then, Carter?
Listen. Don't you ever fucking tell me
what to do, alright?
I control my life, not you.
Carter.
I'm never gonna die.
Hey, Alex.
Hey.
I took my driver's test last week
at the DMV.
Got a 70.
It's the lowest score
you can get, but I passed.
The thing is when I was done with the test
You know the guy that drives
with you during the test?
Right.
Yeah well, he goes...
Young man,
you're gonna die at a very young age.
Yeah. Yeah.
Is that true?
Not now,
not here, not ever, Billy.
If I ask out Cynthia Paster,
will she say no?
Fuck.
Ok.
Yeah.
Miss Lewton.
Don't talk to me.
You scare the hell out of me.
I'm gonna go up.
Hey.
I don't want you to take this
the wrong way, man right.
I miss you,
you know?
Yeah.
Yeah, I miss you too.
But my father, you know,
he doesn't understand.
Yeah.
Hey look, when he gets over this thing,
you and me,
little road trip to the city, you know?
Catch the Yanks.
Yeah.
Yeah, alright, we'll do that.
Cool.
Look, I'd better go.
Yeah.
This thing Miss Lewton showed me in class,
they're gonna let me read it.
It says what I'm feeling.
Take care, man.
Because of you, I'm still alive.
Thank you.
We say, that the hour of
death cannot be forecast.
But...
when we say this,
we imagine that the hour
is placed in an obscure...
and distant future.
It never occurs to us
that it has...
any connection,
with the day already begun.
Or that death could arrive
this same afternoon.
This afternoon, which is so certain
and which has every hour,
filled in advance.
What happened?
Where's Tod?
Alex.
Get out of here.
Didn't you see it?
What happened?
You caused Tod so much guilt over
George staying on the plane,
he took his own life.
No.
Time to go.
Look,
he wouldn't do that.
Ok? He said to me we'd be friends
again after you got better.
Why would he make plans with me
if he was thinking about killing himself?
Mr. Waggner.
Here we go.
Easy.
Alright.
Here we go.
Let's go.
Almost autumn.
It's only the end of June.
Yeah, but everything's
always in transition.
If you focus, even now,
just one week into summer,
you can almost feel autumn coming.
Kind of like being able to see the future.
Why were you at Tod's house last night?
I've seen enough TV to know that
the FBI doesn't investigate teen suicides.
They were there last night.
That means one,
they still don't have a clue
what caused the crash.
They haven't ruled out anything.
The fact that seven people got off
the plane is probably weird enough.
Not to mention that one of those people
had a vision,
or whatever
of the plane exploding minutes before
it did explode, is highly suspicious.
And it doesn't help that the visionary's
friend just committed suicide.
Why were you there last night?
Do you know what this is?
This is a...
Who's the spring-head guy?
It's you.
Not a likeness.
It's how you make me feel, Alex.
I'm sorry.
You know, like you, the sculpture
doesn't even know what or why it is.
It's reluctant to take form.
And yet, creating an absolute...
but incomprehensible attraction.
In four years of high school,
we haven't said one word to each other.
At that moment on the plane,
I felt...
what you felt.
I didn't even know where those emotions were
coming from until you started freaking out.
I didn't see what you saw,
but I felt it.
You can still feel it, can't you?
Something from that day is still with you.
I know because I can still feel you.
That's why I was there last night.
You know, I've never dealt
with death before.
This could all be in our head.
It just feels like it's all around us.
It?
What if Tod was just the first?
Of us?
Is that something that you're feeling?
I don't know, you know.
I just wish I could see him again.
One last time.
So maybe I would know.
Then let's go see him.
Easy.
Gives me a rush.
This place?
Doing something I'm not supposed to.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Is that him?
I think.
Why did they make him up
like Michael Jackson?
Yeah, that's him.
But whatever it was that made him Tod
is definitely gone.
Christ.
Please.
You'll wake the dead.
Why did his hand do that?
Chemicals,
in the vascular flush create...
cadaveric spasms.
Look...
I'm his friend and...
I know who you are.
What are all those tiny marks?
Cuticle lacerations
from pulling at the wire.
Pulling at the wire?
If he was pulling at the wire,
he wasn't trying to kill himself.
It was an accident.
In death,
there are no accidents.
No coincidences.
No mishaps.
And no escapes.
What you have to realize
is that we're all just a...
mouse that a cat has by the tail.
Every single move we make,
from the mundane
to the monumental,
the red light that we stop at or run
the people we have sex with
or won't with us
the airplanes that we ride
or walk out of
it's all part of death's sadistic design,
leading to the grave.
Design?
Does that mean if...
you figure out the design,
you could cheat death?
Alex.
You've already done that
by walking off the plane.
Your friend's departure...
shows that death has a new design,
for all of you.
Now, you have to figure out how...
and when...
it's coming back at you.
Play your hunch, Alex.
If you think you can get away with it.
But remember...
the risk...
of cheating the plan
of disrespecting the design,
could incite a fury
that could terrorize
even the Grim Reaper.
And you don't even wanna fuck
with that Mack Daddy.
Ok, then, well...
Yeah, I'm sorry we broke in and...
No harm.
No foul.
I'll see you soon.
The mortician said
that death has a design.
Ok.
I'm talking about omens.
How do we know,
that just by sitting here,
by sipping this coffee
or breathing the air,
or crossing the intersection
that we haven't started...
in motion,
the events that will lead to our death
40 years from now,
10 years from now, tomorrow?
We don't,
unless we open ourselves up
to the signs it's willing to show us.
I don't understand.
Did you see Tod die?
Did it happen again,
like on the plane?
No.
No it didn't, but I mean
it might as well have.
This is a message of something, Clear.
Or someone,
hinting at a design.
Total bullshit.
I mean, you can find
death omens anywhere you want to.
Coffee.
Starts with a C and ends with an E.
So does the word choke.
So, what we're gonna choke to death?
I wanna hear you.
We'll go nuts if you start with this shit.
The mortician said
that death has a design,
right?
Now what if...
you, me, Tod, Carter,
Terry, Billy, Miss Lewton,
messed up that design
for whatever reason? I...
saw death's plan,
then we cheated it.
But what if it was our time?
What if we were not meant
to get off that plane?
What if it still is our time?
If it is,
then it's not finished.
And we will die...
now, not later.
Unless.
Unless we find the patterns
and cheat it again.
After hearing you, I do believe
that Tod killed himself.
Yeah, I'm fine. Whatever.
You alright man?
Hey baby, come on, not now.
Carter.
It looks like we have
a bit of a reunion here.
Let it go.
When are you moving?
A couple weeks.
That's too bad.
You dick.
We're losing our favorite teacher.
Baby, come on.
Look, guys.
There's something
I need to tell you, ok?
Alex.
And you lived here your whole life?
Yeah.
And now she's gotta move...
Hey Carter, please listen...
all because of Browning.
We're all in danger!
Enough!
Both of you.
They died and we lived.
Get over it.
I will not let this plane crash
be the most important thing in my life.
I'm moving on,
Carter.
And if you wanna waste your life,
beating the shit out of Alex
every time you see him.
Then you can just drop fucking dead.
Ok.
You look like a smart shopper.
Well, thank you.
Let's just say, you were to see this
knife set in a department store.
What do you think you'd have to pay?
That's a huge knife set, but how many?
Hello?
Is Alex there?
Hi, Clear. Yeah, just a minute.
It's Clear, again.
You wanna talk to her?
Clear, he's in the shower.
Can I get him to call you back?
Sure, bye.
She's concerned about you.
I'm concerned about you.
Why won't you talk to her?
Or me?
Dad, you and Mom
have both been a big help.
But there's something I need
to understand before I can talk,
to anyone.
The National Transportation Safety Board
has a new theory tonight
on the possible cause of the explosion
of Volée Air Flight 180.
Officials believe
deterioration of silicon insulation
on an electrical connector
to the scavenger pump
may have leaked combustible fluids.
A spark in the fuel,
beneath the coach cabin in the fuselage,
That's Tod's seat.
May have ignited the fuel line
and proceeded to the fuel pump
which would have set off
the catastrophic explosion.
The path of the explosion.
Ok, the first was Tod.
Then it was Terry.
They're dying in the order
they would have died.
That's death's design.
Miss Lewton's next.
And whenever I can fall asleep, I just...
I see Terry Chaney.
And in the day,
out of nowhere I hear the
sound of my own voice in my head
saying to Larry Murnau.
No.
You know the whole French thing.
Get on the plane.
Everything reminds me of that day.
Right.
Yeah.
I'm hoping a change will help.
It's just that...
I've lived...
I've lived here my whole life,
you know and everywhere I looked
were great memories.
And now all I see is...
Larry and those...
those kids,
you know?
Just...
just looking out my own front yard
makes me feel nothing but fear.
Laura, I'm gonna have to call you back.
Right.
Hi, this is Valerie Lewton.
I need agent Schreck.
What are you doing here?
I was just...
I was checking the air in the tire
to make sure it's safe.
Get in the car.
Put on your seat belt.
I believe that...
Miss Lewton is next.
Next?
Yes.
Yeah, next, because...
there's this pattern...
that's occurring.
Right, a pattern, yeah.
You noticed that too?
Mom's favorite.
So, what about this pattern, Alex?
Did you see it
in another one of your visions?
Did you catch it in some TV static?
You know, I never asked for...
for what happened on the plane.
You guys are gonna sit on your
little chairs and make fun of me.
Whatever, it's fine.
But I saved six lives on that plane.
Six lives, and everybody in my
entire school thinks I'm a freak.
And I'm...
I'm not suffering from...
posttraumatic stress.
I don't have a narcissistic deity complex.
I'm not going Dahmer,
on you guys.
This just is.
There is a pattern,
for us all.
There's a pattern for you,
There's a pattern,
there's a design for everyone.
I don't know how yet.
But I'm gonna break this one.
Alex,
you came to our attention at first
because you were under suspicion
in this plane explosion.
Now,
I know you didn't blow up the plane.
And we were ready to move on,
but then the other survivors started to die.
First, your friend Tod.
Then Terry Chaney,
while you were there at the scene.
And now tonight we pick you
up at Val Lewton's house.
Alex, nobody has control
over life and death.
Unless they are taking lives,
and causing death.
Now, can you promise me
that no one else is going to die?
No, I can't.
As long as I'm in here,
it's out of my control, I'm sorry.
Ok.
Go ahead.
Get out of here.
Thank you.
That kid gives me the creeps.
What are we gonna do?
We got nothing to hold him.
That's not what I'm talking about.
There were a couple of moments there...
where I almost believed him.
Can I tell you something?
Don't take this the wrong way.
But sometimes,
you give me the creeps.
You've gotta stop this.
Stop this, it's a stupid mug.
You're out of here.
Pretty soon, you'll be gone.
You'll be gone.
Miss Lewton.
Ok.
Alright, ok. I...
Ok. Ok. Ok. Just stay still, ok?
God. God. Miss Lewton.
Hey, Alex.
Dude.
I don't know where he is.
He's not talking to me.
Why?
Because I didn't believe him.
If he does contact you
I think it would be in the best
interest of your safety if you called us.
Now,
here's my card.
Toll-free number.
Interesting work.
Carter, you dick.
What are you doing?
Terry's name should be on this wall.
Shit.
Why'd you want us
to meet you here anyway?
Because they're watching me,
see if I go to Alex.
That's why you're taking me.
Why would I wanna see him?
Because he knows
which one of us is next.
So, drive the speed limit, ok?
And...
don't pass on the right.
Billy, wait a minute here.
I'm getting a vision.
You're the next one, man.
Hey, man, why'd you say that?
Because if you say another word,
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
He could be anywhere from here
to a mile down on the road.
So you guys drive down there,
start that way we'll meet around the middle.
It'll take half the time.
Do you think they're still up there?
Somehow,
Flight 180, are they still in flight?
Somewhere,
are they safe?
When I was a kid,
like 6 or 7
I used to worry so much
about my parents dying.
Lying awake at night just worrying.
Yeah, well, most kids do, I guess.
Most kids never have it happen.
When I was 10,
my dad went into a 7-Eleven
for cigarettes.
I guess that he heard someone say,
Don't turn around.
So...
on reflex or thinking
it was a friend joking, he did.
And the guy blew his head off.
Life became shit after that.
My mom just couldn't deal anymore.
She married this asshole
who my mom with my real dad would
have crossed the street to avoid this guy.
He really didn't want a kid.
So my mom didn't either anymore.
If that was the design,
for my father and my family
then fuck death.
God, I have thought a lot,
about that somewhere, Alex.
It exists that place.
Where my dad is still safe.
Where he had a full pack of cigarettes
that night and just kept driving.
Where me and my mom
and my dad are still together
and have no idea about this life here.
Where our friends are still in the sky.
Where everyone gets a second chance.
Alex,
we can't give up.
Look, I can't go home.
Alright? Because after Miss Lewton,
they're gonna be looking for me.
No, we're taking you
to my dad's cabin woods.
It's only a couple miles from my house.
Alright, Browning, you fucking warlock.
Did you know about Miss Lewton or what?
Why do you think I was hiding?
Billy told the FBI he saw you
running from her house.
I was running because
they blame me for everything.
They blame me for Tod,
they blame me for her,
They blame me
for the fucking plane crash Billy.
The fire like caramelized her blood Alex.
Your shoe prints were in it.
Your fingerprints were on the knives.
I told you Billy,
I told you they were not...
I'm not talking about whether
you did alright or not you did it.
Or even if you knew she was dead.
Did you know she was gonna be next...
before she was?
Yeah, I did.
I knew.
Alright.
Out of us,
who's next to see it?
Please,
tell me I'm gonna get to see
the Jets win a Super Bowl.
It's me, right?
That's why you're not saying.
Alright I knew I should have felt up
Tammy in the pool that time.
What are you whining about?
He say I'm next.
He didn't say anything.
Just drive.
Shit,
you have a responsibility to tell me.
Do you think it's gonna make it
easier to know, Carter?
It's not, it's gonna make it fucking harder.
Yeah you know,
you get off having control over me.
You let me decide how to deal with it.
It doesn't matter who's next.
Because we're all on the same list.
All of us.
Fuck.
Really?
Alright, then why bother?
What's the fucking point, right?
Me and Terry, we'll be back together
on the other side,
so why wait any longer?
Carter, what are you doing?
Carter, slow down.
Slow down, Carter!
Fuck you.
Knock it off.
May as well go out
on my own free will, right?
Not with us in the fucking car.
Jesus, Carter, no.
Stop it.
Carter, stop the car.
Hey, what's the fucking worry
if it ain't your time?
I can get nailed
running this next red light.
And you all wouldn't give a shit, right?
It's only me.
It doesn't work that way, Carter.
And I fucking hated French class.
Get control yourself.
That's what I'm doing.
I know what you're doing.
And it's alright to be scared, Carter.
I'm not afraid.
Alright, I decide when it's time.
I control my life, I can...
I control my death.
You don't have to prove to us
how big your balls are. Not now.
Carter, stop driving like such an asshole.
What are you doing?
Fuck it Carter, Jesus Christ.
Carter, put your hands back on the wheel.
Carter stop.
Hands on the wheel Carter.
Shit.
Ok, Carter, easy.
I am so close to puking
right now, you don't even wanna know.
We're afraid too, Carter,
but we're not going to quit.
Stop what you're doing
and stop this fucking car.
Damn it Carter.
I want you to stop this car right now.
Billy.
Move it.
Hey, open the door Billy.
Move the fucking car!
Hey, open the fucking door.
Move the car.
Open it.
Open the door.
Easy, easy, open the fucking door.
Billy, open the fucking door!
Billy, open it!
Open the door!
Carter, listen to me. Don't do this.
Goddamn it!
Get out of the fucking car.
Carter listen to me.
Hey, listen to me.
This isn't the way.
It's not the way. Get out of the car.
Come on!
It's coming, it's coming!
Carter!
It ain't my time.
Shit.
Carter, listen to me.
This isn't the way.
Get out of the car, Carter.
Carter, get out of the car.
Come on, get out!
I can't get out!
Alex!
No!
Man, he really is next.
Get out!
Come on!
Fuck!
God.
I saw it. I saw the belt.
Scared now?
It broke.
Bullshit.
He saved your life again.
That's right.
You're next, Carter.
I'm staying the fuck away from you.
Shut up Billy.
We don't need this shit right now.
I don't need it ever.
What are you doing?
Get away from him, he's next.
Hey fuck you Billy I'm not dead.
You will be.
You're dead, you're dead.
And you ain't taking me with you!
Shit. Shit.
Jesus fucking Christ!
You should've been next.
You should've been next after Lewton.
That's the plan. That's the design.
You should be fucking dead.
You're the fucking devil.
I saw the seat belt. I knew it would rip.
That's how I saved him.
Just like the plane.
Just like the explosion, I saw it.
The police are coming.
Fuck, I saved him.
Because I saved him
it skipped Carter, went to the next
in the path of the explosion, Billy.
I have to see it.
And if I see it, then I intervene.
And if I intervene, I cheat the design.
What intervene?
What are you God now?
Gods aren't afraid to die.
Gods don't die. We do.
You know?
Baby, you're losing it, ok?
The police will be here.
We have to get you to my cabin.
You can hide,
and get your head together.
Ok, after Billy, I'm next.
I'm next.
And then me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, listen.
I'm not gonna let it happen, ok?
Listen to me,
alright?
Hey, hey, hey.
Why don't you two
just get the fuck out of here?
Rusted.
Tetanus.
Nice one.
I overlooked it.
You tried to capitalize.
But I caught you.
You fuck.
I can beat you.
Yeah, I mean not forever,
but I got this cabin rigged
to beat you now!
She was there a minute ago.
What are you talking about?
I'm not turning him in.
It's too dangerous for him
out there alone.
I go with you.
You can't.
Clear, you just tell us where he is.
Wait at home, I give you my word
that we will bring him in safely
in protective custody.
I never moved.
Christa asked me to change seats
but I never moved.
I would've been up next to Tod.
Fuck, why didn't I remember that?
I never moved.
Clear's seat was in front of mine.
She's next.
Alex!
Come on, get in the car.
We're going around. Get in the car.
Come on!
Go!
Move!
There!
Come on, let's go!
Over here.
Alex!
Alex, we're trying to help you.
Fritz,
get away from it.
Come on.
Alex!
Run!
We lost him.
From the direction,
there's only one place he's heading.
No shit.
Clear!
No.
Oh my God.
Don't move. Stay there.
Don't move, don't move.
Don't touch anything.
You're grounded by the tires, ok?
The car's gonna explode.
I can only hold on for so long,
you know what to do.
Don't!
When I do this, it'll skip you,
and it'll be over.
It's the only way
we can cheat death again.
No, don't!
Clear, I am not gonna let it beat us both.
You know what to do.
I'll always be with you.
No!
Alex!
Alex, get away from there.
No!
Alex.
Damn it,
you can't do this to me.
Come on, baby.
Come on.
Alex, Alex?
Shit, he's not breathing.
Hold on, Alex.
Come on, stay with me.
Welcome to France.
Goodbye.
Hi. Welcome to France.
Well, we made it.
Paris, I can't believe it.
You know what, I just can't believe
we got on a plane again.
You know what I'm saying?
Voila.
Thanks.
It's weird being here?
We finally completed a puzzle.
It's just, there's something missing,
you know?
To Terry.
Yeah.
To Tod.
To all of our friends that can't be here.
Cheers.
What?
If you would have told me
six months ago
that the three of us would be
sitting here having a drink.
Yeah.
I don't know I mean,
sometimes it just feels
like the two of you
are the only ones
who can really understand.
You were right, Browning.
It did skip us. There was a design.
We beat it. You know, we won.
I think the only thing we won, Carter,
is a chance at a full life.
A chance that I won't ever waste.
Yeah,
there's just something,
You know, something I can't figure out.
What?
About the design.
Alex, just let it go.
Alright?
I swear just...
Just hear me out, alright?
Oh my God.
It's just Listen.
Now, the path of the explosion,
determined the order of our deaths, right?
When I intervened and saved Carter
it skipped him and went to the next
person in the path. It went to Billy.
Alright, and then it was Clear.
But I intervened and saved her,
so it went to me, but in my case...
no one intervened, right?
I was thrown from that power...
line by the explosion.
So.
So why did it skip you, right?
How do we know that this isn't exactly
what was meant to happen?
That out of everyone on Flight 180
you, me and Carter were meant to live.
Maybe that was the design all along.
Or you could still be next.
Shut up, Carter.
What?
I didn't make up the rules.
Somebody's gotta intervene
before death can skip them.
Alex proved that three times.
In the plane, with me, you.
For all I know, it could circle back
and get us all again.
But I am the safest fucker in the world,
because you're still next.
Can we just stop talking about this?
Let's figure out
what we're gonna do tomorrow.
I'm gonna meet you back at the hotel, ok.
Just wait, I'll go with you.
No, no. Just...
Just stay here, ok?
Clear just stay here.
Alright?
See, it's true.
I told you you were next, man.
Stop it Carter.
Alex wait.
No Clear, stay there.
Ok?
Stay away.
Alex!
I told you, you were next.
Then it just skipped me.
So who's next?
By LESAIGNEUR
Sync & corrections January 2022