Alex.
Tod and George's dad just called.
He's picking you up at
3:30 tomorrow.
And the bus leaves the high school for the airport around 5:00
How's my suitcase working out for you?
Whoa, Mom, Mom, Mom,
you gotta leave that on.
Yeah, it's like the tag made the last flight without the plane crashing or anything.
So I figure it's gotta be on the bag, or at least, with the bag.
For luck.
Where would you get
a nutball idea like that?
I'm still here.
So 17, on the loose.
Senior trip with your friends in Paris.
Ten days in the springtime.
Live it up, Alex.
You got your whole life ahead of you.
Alex.
The white zone....
....is for immediate loading and unloading of passengers only.
No parking.
Yeah, I've been sitting here
for over an hour.
Where are you?
~ Hey, Hitchcock.
~ What?
Let me give you a hand with this, man. There you go.
Carter, you dick.
~ Schmuck.
~ Good one.
~ You left this on the bus.
~ Oh, thanks.
Come on, let's get your stuff together.
Hey, Christa. Hi, Blake.
~ What are you doing?
~ He's the man. The man.
All right, you guys got everything?
Yeah, yeah. Dad, we're all set.
Does that mean go?
Don't know.
Look, this is for both of you, all right? Have a great time.
~ Thanks, Dad.
~ Yeah.
~ Both of us.
~ Let's go.
~ Alex.
~ Yes?
~ You take care of them.
~ I will.
You know, I didn't think anything could look worse than my yearbook photo.
How do you think I feel
having to look at you all the time?
~ What the fuck does he want?
~ Shh.
"The airport does not
endorse solicitors."
Death is not the end.
It will be for you
if you harass my students.
~ Hare Rama.
~ Fuck off.
I have to ask you a few questions this evening.
Did you pack your bags yourself?
Have your belongings remained
in your possession the entire time?
Mr. Browning?
Oh, yeah.
Have you received any packages
from persons unknown to you?
~ Same as your birthday.
~ What?
September 25, 9:25.
Your birthday's the same
as your departure time.
~ Because I looked at him.
~ Are you sure?
Lisa, wait up.
No, it's okay.
Fuck, that was good.
Dick.
~ Hey.
~ Hey, George, Dad said both.
Both of us, all right, man?
Just give me some cash.
Hey, hey, knock it off.
~ Excuse me.
~ Catch.
You asshole.
~ Thanks.
~ You're welcome.
Alex, let's go take a shit.
~ Why don't you go by yourself?
~ No, dude. Listen, okay?
Listen, take some knowledge.
We're about to board
a seven-hour flight.
The toilets in coach are barely
ventilated closets, all right, if that.
Now, let's say halfway through the flight, your body wants that food out.
You gotta go torque a wicked cable.
And then right after you, like, directly after you walks in Christa or Blake.
You want them to associate you
with that watery sting in their eye?
That reflexive gag
at the back of their throat?
John Denver.
Died in a plane crash.
Ladies and
gentlemen, thank you for your patience.
At this time,
we would like to begin preboarding....
....of Volée Air Flight 180 to Paris through Gate 46.
Anyone seen Billy Hitchcock?
How did we lose him?
Go. Go.
Go. Ow.
Ow. That hurt.
Oh, my little baby.
That's a good sign.
The younger, the better.
It'd be a fucked-up God
to take down this plane.
Hi.
A really fucked-up God.
Yeah.
~ Hi.
~ Hey, Tod.
Hello. How you doing?
I'm gonna sit here.
~ Can you switch seats with Christa?
~ Oh, God.
You know, I would,
but I got a bladder thing.
It's a urinary tract infection.
Let's go ask Alex.
Alex, could you trade seats with Blake so she and I could sit together?
She asked Tod, but he said
he had some sort of medical thing.
Please?
Yeah.
You're so sweet.
~ Thanks, Alex.
~ Thank you, Alex.
You're welcome, you're welcome,
you're welcome.
Fag.
Did you really think we're gonna titty fuck them over Greenland?
You know, because of you, I gotta sit here and watch fucking Stuart Little.
Thank you.
Thanks, man. That's great.
Sorry I'm late.
That's my seat right there.
~ Hello?
~ I'm going that way.
May I have your attention?
To properly fasten your seat belts, slide the flat portion into the buckle.
~ Equipped with six emergency exits: Two in front, two over the wing, two in the rear.
All exits are clearly marked.
Follow the red exit signs
and public lighting in the aisle way.
Flight
attendants, prepare for departure.
~ All right.
~ All right, all right.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Huh?
It's okay.
~ I wanna go.
~ It's fine.
It's okay, honey, I....
What the....?
Oh, my God!
Everybody....
No! No!
Christa! No!
Alex, could you trade seats with Blake so she and I could sit together?
She asked Tod, but he said
he had some medical thing.
Please?
What's up, dude?
~ Is there a problem, sir?
~ What's your problem?
Alex, qu'est-ce que c'est?
~ The fucking plane's gonna explode.
~ Shut up, Browning.
~ You're so not funny.
~ If this is your joke....
It's not a joke. It's not a joke.
~ Alex, take it easy.
~ That's it, sit down, Browning.
~ It's going down.
~ We will remove you.
~ I'll remove him.
~ I'll remove myself.
~ Excuse me.
~ Get off him.
~ That's my seat right there.
~ This plane is going down.
Everybody in the aisle, off the plane.
~ Get off the plane.
~ Stay where you are.
~ Just sit tight.
~ The fucking plane is going down.
Go check him out.
See how he's doing.
Okay.
~ I got my ticket here.
~ Get off me.
Jerk.
~ Hey.
~ You got this?
No one gets back onboard.
~ That's my call.
~ Wait, please.
I've got 40 students going to Paris. Please, please?
~ Look, you must understand my position.
~ I understand, and I apologize for Alex.
But one of us needs to be on that plane.
I cannot let students
go to Paris for ten days....
Carter, no.
~ Sit the fuck down, Carter.
~ Sit down.
Sit.
One of you can go on
the flight. That's it.
Larry.
Airline's not taking this well.
They'll let one of us back on.
The rest can take an 11:10 flight. It gets in three....
I'll stay.
No, no, you know the whole French thing. Get on the plane, it's fine.
Hi, Mr. Murnau.
See, I was in the bathroom.
And the lock, it was stuck, and....
Oh, wait, I didn't fight with anyone.
Damn.
Thanks.
I just.... I called your parents. They're on their way.
We should be going.
Alex, talk to me. Tell me what happened.
I saw it.
Like, I don't know. I saw it.
I saw it on the runway.
I saw it take off.
I saw out my window.
~ I saw the ground, and....
~ Carter.
The cabin, it starts to shake, right? And the left side blows up.
And then the whole plane just explodes.
And it was so real. Just like
how everything happens, you know?
You been on planes that blew up?
You must have fallen asleep.
Whoa, we get thrown off the plane.
We blow, what, a half a day in Paris....
....all because Browning
has a bad fucking dream?
But wait, "The plane, it's gonna blow up, it's gonna blow up."
~ Hey, hey, fuck you, Horton.
~ Tod.
The only trip you're taking
is to the fucking hospital.
~ Get off him.
~ Hey, hey.
~ Alex, stop it.
~ Come on, now.
There they go, here we stay.
~ You're paying for my trip.
~ I wish you were on that plane.
~ You fucking prick.
~ Oh, shit!
~ Call it in.
~ Security....
You're looking at me
as if I caused this.
I didn't cause this.
Are there any survivors?
How should I know?
~ What, you think I'm some sort of....?
~ He's not a witch.
Hello, I'm Howard Seigel,
National Transportation Safety Board.
We've contacted all your families. They are on the way.
Is there anyone here who feels they might need a little medical attention....
....or spiritual counseling at this time?
What's going on?
Are there any survivors?
Well, the cause for the explosion is still undetermined.
The Nassau County authorities
are on the scene.
Naval Search and Rescue en route. We....
Excuse me.
I'm Agent Weine. This is Agent Schreck.
We're with the FBI.
I understand how you all
must be feeling right now.
I know it's gonna be difficult.
We're gonna ask you questions
regarding today's events....
....while they're still
fresh in your mind.
This will prove invaluable to our rescue attempts and any criminal investigation.
You said, "Listen to me.
This plane will explode on takeoff."
How did you know that?
I got this feeling.
This weird feeling.
Did you take any sedatives
before boarding the plane?
Did you take any sleeping pills, any narcotics, hallucinogens?
~ Alex, do you take any drugs?
~ No.
I saw it.
I saw it happen.
I saw the plane explode.
Did the feelings
have anything to do with your saying....
....that you wished that Carter Horton was on the plane just before it exploded?
~ No.
~ Then why'd you say it?
Because I really didn't think
it was gonna happen.
If that's the case, Alex, then why did you really get off the plane?
My brother, George, he told me
to go and keep an eye on Alex.
And so he stayed, and....
He told me to get off the plane.
Larry Murnau said I should get back on, but I told him that he should go.
I sent him back on the plane.
All right.
Nobody forced you off the plane.
You said you weren't friends
with those that were.
So, Clear,
why did you get off the plane?
Because I saw and I heard Alex.
And I believed him.
Honey.
Oh, God.
There he is.
Over here.
Thank you for the ride.
You're looking
at the first piece of debris....
....to wash ashore
from Volée Air Flight 180....
....which erupted shortly
after a 9:25 p.m. Takeoff....
....from John F. Kennedy Airport in New York.
There are no known survivors.
However, Coast Guard
and Naval Search and Rescue efforts....
....are continuing at this moment even as jet fuel burns on the ocean's surface.
Authorities are pessimistic
about the possibility....
....of finding anyone alive
from the ill-fated flight.
All 287 passengers are feared dead.
Amongst the travelers, a class of 40 students and four teachers....
....from Mount Abraham High School in southeast New York....
....en route to Paris on a field trip.
There are reports that several students were removed from the aircraft....
....moments before departure.
However, investigators remain guarded about the specifics of this incident.
Authorities from the National
Transportation and Safety Board....
....and the Federal Bureau of
Investigation have arrived at JFK....
....to begin the initial investigation.
Eyewitnesses at the airport,
as well as on Long Island....
....report seeing the plane explode.
No other aircraft
were visibly near Flight 180.
At JFK, air traffic controllers
are corroborating....
....these eyewitness accounts.
After the explosion, debris apparently rained into the Atlantic Ocean for several miles.
However, investigators are cautious about verifying these accounts....
....believing they'll learn more from the found debris when daylight arrives.
Thirty-nine days have passed....
....since we lost our 39 loved ones, friends and teachers.
As each day passes without
a determining cause for the accident....
....we ask ourselves, "Why?"
Ecclesiastes tells us:
"Man no more knows his own time
than fish taken in the fatal net....
....or birds trapped in the snare.
Like these, the children of men caught when the time falls suddenly upon them."
And so, before we can heal....
....before we can escape
the presence of death and time....
....we must mourn and celebrate theirs with this memorial.
I hope you don't think
because my name ain't up on this wall....
....that I owe you anything.
I don't.
Because all I owe are these people.
To live my life to the fullest.
Why don't you stay off
the J.D., then, huh, Carter?
Listen. Don't you ever fucking tell me what to do, all right?
I control my life, not you.
Carter.
I'm never gonna die.
Hey, Alex.
~ Hey.
I took my driver's test last week at the DMV.
Got a 70. It's the lowest score
you can get, but I passed.
When I was done with the test....
You know the guy that drives with you?
~ Right.
~ Yeah, well, anyways.
He goes, "Young man, you're gonna die at a very young age."
Yeah. Yeah.
Is that true?
Not now, not here, not ever, Billy.
If I ask out Cynthia Paster,
will she say no?
Fuck.
~ Okay.
~ Yeah.
Yeah.
~ Miss Lewton....
~ Don't talk to me.
You scare the hell out of me.
I'm gonna go up.
Hey.
I don't want you
to take this the wrong way.
But I miss you, you know?
Yeah.
Yeah, I miss you too.
But my father, you know,
he doesn't understand.
Yeah.
Hey, look, when he gets
over this thing....
....you and me,
little road trip to the city, you know?
Catch the Yanks.
Yeah. Yeah, all right, we'll do that.
Cool.
~ Look, I'd better go.
~ Yeah.
This thing Miss Lewton showed me in class, they're gonna let me read it.
It says what I'm feeling.
Take care, man.
Because of you, I'm still alive.
Thank you.
"We say that the hour of death
cannot be forecast.
But when we say this,
we imagine that the hour is placed....
....in an obscure and distant future.
It never occurs to us
that it has any connection....
....with the day already begun.
Or that death could arrive
this same afternoon.
This afternoon, which is so certain....
....and which has every hour
filled in advance."
What happened?
Where's Tod?
Alex.
Get out of here.
~ Didn't you see it?
~ What happened?
You caused Tod so much guilt over George staying on the plane, he took his own life.
~ No.
~ Time to go.
Look, he wouldn't do that.
Okay? He said to me we'd be friends again after you got better.
Why would he make plans with me if he was thinking about killing himself?
Mr. Waggner.
~ Mr. Waggner.
~ Here we go.
Easy.
All right.
Here we go.
Let's go.
Almost autumn.
It's only the end of June.
Yeah, but everything's
always in transition.
If you focus, one week into summer....
....you can feel almost feel
autumn coming.
Kind of like being able
to see the future.
Why were you at Tod's house last night?
I've seen enough TV to know that the FBI doesn't investigate teen suicides.
They were there last night.
They don't have a clue....
....what caused the crash.
They haven't ruled out anything.
The fact that seven people got off the plane is probably weird enough.
Not to mention that one of those people had a vision, or whatever....
....of the plane exploding minutes before it did explode, is highly suspicious.
And it doesn't help that the visionary's friend just committed suicide.
Why were you there last night?
Do you know what this is?
This is a....
Who's the spring-head guy?
It's you.
Not a likeness.
It's how you make me feel, Alex.
I'm sorry.
You know, like you, the sculpture doesn't even know what, or why, it is.
It's reluctant to take form.
And yet, creating an absolute
but incomprehensible attraction.
In four years of high school,
we haven't said one word to each other.
At that moment on the plane,
I felt what you felt.
I didn't know
where those emotions were from....
....until you started freaking out.
I didn't see what you saw,
but I felt it.
You can still feel it, can't you?
Something from that day
is still with you.
I know because I can still feel you.
That's why I was there last night.
You know,
I've never dealt with death before.
This could all be in our head.
It just feels like it's all around us.
It?
What if Tod was just the first?
Of us?
Is that something that you're feeling?
I don't know, you know.
I just wish I could see him again.
One last time.
So maybe I would know.
Then let's go see him.
Easy.
Gives me a rush.
This place?
Doing something I'm not supposed to.
Come on.
Hurry up.
~ Is that him?
~ I think.
Why did they make him up
like Michael Jackson?
Yeah, that's him.
But whatever it was that made him Tod is definitely gone.
Christ.
Shh.
Please.
You'll wake the dead.
Why did his hand do that?
Chemicals in the vascular flush
create cadaveric spasms.
Look, um....
~ I'm his friend and....
~ I know who you are.
What are all those tiny marks?
Cuticle lacerations
from pulling at the wire.
Pulling at the wire?
If he was pulling at the wire,
he wasn't trying to kill himself.
~ It was an accident.
~ In death, there are no accidents.
No coincidences. No mishaps.
And no escapes.
What you have to realize is that we're all just a mouse that a cat has by the tail.
Every single move we make,
from the mundane to the monumental....
....the red light that
we stop at or run....
....the people we have sex with, or won't with us....
....the airplanes that we ride,
or walk out of....
....it's all part of death's sadistic design leading to the grave.
Design?
Does that mean if you figure out the design, you could cheat death?
Alex.
You've already done that
by walking off the plane.
Your friend's departure shows....
....that death has a new design
for all of you.
Now, you have to figure out how
and when it's coming back at you.
Play your hunch, Alex.
If you think you can get away with it.
But remember the risk
of cheating the plan....
....of disrespecting the design
could incite a fury....
....that could terrorize
even the Grim Reaper.
And you don't even wanna fuck
with that Mack Daddy.
Okay, then, well....
Yeah, I'm sorry we broke in and....
No harm. No foul.
I'll see you soon.
The mortician said
that death has a design.
Okay.
I'm talking about omens.
How do we know that just by sitting here, by sipping this coffee....
....or breathing the air
or crossing the intersection....
....that we haven't started in motion the events that will lead to our death....
....40 years from now,
10 years from now, tomorrow?
We don't unless we open ourselves up....
....to the signs it's willing to show us.
I don't understand.
Did you see Tod die?
Did it happen again, like on the plane?
No, no, it didn't, but I mean,
it might as well have.
This is a message of something, Clear.
Or someone, hinting at a design.
Total bullshit. I mean, you can find death omens anywhere you want to.
Coffee.
Starts with a C and ends with an E.
So does the word choke.
So, what, we're gonna choke to death?
I wanna hear you.
We'll go nuts if you
start with this shit.
The mortician said
that death has a design, right?
Now, what if you, me, Tod, Carter,
Terry, Billy, Miss Lewton....
....messed up that design
for whatever reason?
I saw death's plan, then we cheated it.
But what if it was our time?
What if we were not meant
to get off that plane?
What if it still is our time?
If it is, then it's not finished.
And we will die now, not later.
Unless....
Unless we find the patterns
and cheat it again.
After hearing you, I do believe....
....that Tod killed himself.
Yeah, I'm fine. Whatever.
~ You all right, man?
~ Hey, baby, come on, not now.
~ Carter.
~ Oh.
It looks like
we have a bit of a reunion here.
~ Let it go.
~ When are you moving?
A couple weeks.
~ That's too bad.
~ You dick.
~ We're losing our favorite teacher.
~ Baby, come on.
Look, guys. There's something
I need to tell you, okay?
Alex.
And you lived here
your whole life? Yeah.
And now she's gotta move
all because of Browning.
Enough, both of you.
They died and we lived.
Get over it.
I will not let this plane crash
be the most important thing in my life.
I'm moving on, Carter.
And if you wanna waste your life....
....beating the shit out of Alex every time you see him....
....then you can just drop fucking dead.
~ Okay.
~ You look like a smart shopper.
Well, thank you.
Let's just say you were to see
this knife set in a department store.
What do you think you'd have
to pay?
Wow, that's a huge knife set,
but how many....?
~ Hello?
~ Is Alex there?
Oh, hi, Clear. Yeah, just a minute.
It's Clear again. You wanna talk to her?
The economy kept trading
volume below average today, and stocks....
Clear, he's in the shower.
~ Can I get him to call you back?
~ Sure, bye.
She's concerned about you.
I'm concerned about you.
Why won't you talk to her?
Or me?
~ Which could put a cloud
over both stocks and bonds.
Dad, you and Mom
have both been a big help.
But there's something I need to understand before I can talk to anyone.
~ The Dow down 75.
The National Transportation Safety Board has a new theory tonight....
....on the possible cause of the explosion of Volée Air Flight 180.
Officials believe
deterioration of silicon insulation....
....on an electrical connector
to the scavenger pump....
....may have leaked combustible fluids.
~ A spark in the fuel switch....
~ That's Tod's seat.
....in the fuselage may have ignited the fuel line and proceeded to the fuel pump....
....which would have set off
the catastrophic explosion.
The path of the explosion.
Okay, the first was Tod.
Then it was Terry.
They're dying in the order
they would have died.
That's death's design.
Miss Lewton's next.
And whenever I can
fall asleep, I just....
I see Terry Chaney.
And in the day, out of nowhere....
....I hear the sound of my own voice in my head....
....saying to Larry Murnau:
"No, you know the whole French thing. Get on the plane."
Everything reminds me of that day.
Right, yeah.
I'm hoping a change will help.
It's just that I've lived here
my whole life, you know?
And everywhere I looked
were great memories.
And now all I see is Larry....
....and those kids, you know?
Just looking out my own front yard makes me feel nothing but fear.
Laura, I'm gonna have to call you back.
Right.
Hi, this is Valerie Lewton.
I need Agent Schreck.
What are you doing here?
I was just....
I was checking the air in the tire to make sure it's safe.
Get in the car.
Put on your seat belt.
I believe that Miss Lewton is next.
~ Next?
~ Yes.
Yeah, next, because there's this pattern that's occurring.
Oh, right, a pattern, yeah.
You noticed that too, huh?
Mom's favorite.
So, what about this pattern, Alex?
Did you see it
in another one of your visions?
Did you catch it in some TV static?
You know, I never asked
for what happened on the plane.
You guys are gonna sit on your little chairs and make fun of me. Whatever, it's fine.
But I saved six lives on that plane.
Six lives, and everybody in my
entire school thinks I'm a freak.
And I'm not.... I'm not suffering from posttraumatic stress.
I don't have a narcissistic
deity complex.
I'm not going Dahmer on you guys.
This just is.
There is a pattern for us all.
There's a pattern for you,
there is a pattern for you.
There's a design for everyone.
I don't know how yet.
But I'm gonna break this one.
Alex, you came to our
attention at first....
....because you were under suspicion in this plane explosion.
Now, I know
you didn't blow up the plane.
And we were ready to move on, but then the other survivors started to die.
First, your friend Tod.
Then Terry Chaney,
while you were there at the scene.
And now tonight we pick you
up at Val Lewton's house.
Alex, nobody has control
over life and death.
Unless they are taking lives
and causing death.
Now, can you promise me
that no one else is going to die?
No, I can't.
As long as I'm in here,
it's out of my control, I'm sorry.
Okay, go ahead. Get out of here.
Thank you.
That kid gives me the creeps.
What are we gonna do?
We got nothing to hold him.
That's not what I'm talking about.
There were a couple of moments there....
....where I almost believed him.
Can I tell you something?
Don't take this the wrong way.
But sometimes, you give me the creeps.
You've gotta stop this.
Stop this, it's a stupid mug.
You're out of here.
Pretty soon, you'll be gone.
You'll be gone.
Miss Lewton.
Okay, all right, okay.
Just stay still, okay?
Oh, God. Oh, God. Miss Lewton.
Hey, Alex.
Dude.
I don't know where he is.
~ He's not talking to me.
~ Why?
Because I didn't believe him.
If he does contact you....
....I think it would be in the best interest of your safety if you called us.
Now, here's my card.
Toll-free number.
Interesting work.
Carter, you dick.
What are you doing?
Terry's name should be on this wall.
Shit.
Why'd you want us
to meet you here anyway, huh?
Because they're watching me,
see if I go to Alex.
That's why you're taking me.
Why would I wanna see him?
Because he knows
which one of us is next.
So drive the speed limit, okay?
Oh, and don't pass on the right.
Billy, wait a minute here.
I'm getting a vision.
You're the next one, man.
Hey, man, why'd you say that?
Because if you say another word, I'm gonna fucking kill you.
He could be anywhere from here
to a mile down.
So you guys drive down there,
we'll meet around the middle.
It'll take half the time.
Do you think they're still up there?
Somehow, Flight 180,
are they still in flight?
Somewhere, are they safe?
When I was a kid, like 6 or 7....
....I used to worry so much
about my parents dying.
Lying awake at night just worrying.
Yeah, well, most kids do, I guess.
Most kids never have it happen.
When I was 10, my dad went into
a 7-Eleven for cigarettes.
I guess that he heard someone say, "Don't turn around."
So on reflex, or thinking
it was a friend joking, he did.
And the guy blew his head off.
Life became shit after that.
My mom just couldn't deal anymore.
She married this asshole....
....who my mom with my real dad would have crossed the street to avoid this guy.
He really didn't want a kid.
So my mom didn't either anymore.
If that was the design
for my father and my family....
....then fuck death.
God, I have thought a lot
about that somewhere, Alex.
It exists, that place.
Where my dad is still safe.
Where he had a full pack of cigarettes that night and just kept driving.
Where me and my mom
and my dad are still together....
....and have no idea
about this life here.
Where our friends are still in the sky.
Where everyone gets a second chance.
Alex, we can't give up.
Look, I can't go home.
All right? After Miss Lewton,
they're gonna be looking for me.
No, we're taking you to my dad's cabin.
It's only a couple miles from my house.
All right, Browning,
you fucking warlock.
~ Did you know about Miss Lewton, or what?
~ Why do you think I was hiding?
Billy told the FBI
he saw you running from her house.
I was running because they blame me.
They blame me for Tod, they blame me for her, for the plane crash.
The fire, like, caramelized her blood, Alex. Your shoe prints were in it.
~ Your fingerprints were on the knives.
~ I told you they were not....
I'm not talking about whether or not you did it. Or even if you knew she was dead.
Did you know she was gonna be next before she was?
Yeah, I did.
~ I knew.
~ All right.
Out of us, who's next to see it?
Please, tell me I'm gonna get to see the Jets win a Super Bowl.
It's me, right?
That's why you're not saying.
I knew I should have felt up Tammy in the pool that time.
~ What are you whining about? I'm next.
~ He didn't say anything. Just drive.
You have a responsibility to tell me.
Do you think it's gonna make it
easier to know, Carter?
Huh? It's not,
it's gonna make it fucking harder.
You know, you get off
having control over me.
~ You let me decide how to deal with it.
~ It doesn't matter who's next.
Because we're all
on the same list. All of us.
Oh, fuck. Really?
All right, then why bother?
What's the fucking point, right?
Me and Terry, we'll be back together on the other side, so why wait any longer?
Carter, what are you doing?
Carter, slow down.
~ Slow down, Carter!
~ Fuck you.
~ Knock it off.
~ May as well go out on my own free will.
Not with us in the fucking car.
~ Jesus, Carter, no.
~ Stop it.
Carter, stop the car.
Hey, what's the worry
if it ain't your time?
I could get nailed
and you all wouldn't give a shit, right?
~ It's only me.
~ It doesn't work that way, Carter.
And I fucking hated French class.
~ Control yourself.
~ That's what I'm doing.
I know what you're doing.
And it's all right to be scared.
I'm not afraid, all right?
I decide when it's time.
I control my life, I control my death.
You don't have to prove to us
how big your balls are. Not now.
~ Carter, stop driving like such an asshole.
~ What are you doing?
Fuck it, Carter, Jesus Christ.
Carter, put your hands back on the wheel.
~ Carter, stop.
~ Hands on the wheel, Carter.
Oh, shit.
Okay, Carter, easy.
I am so close to puking
right now, you don't even wanna know.
We're afraid too, Carter,
but we're not going to quit.
Stop what you're doing
and stop this fucking car.
Damn it, Carter.
I want you to stop this car right now.
~ Billy.
~ Move it.
~ Hey, open the door, Billy.
~ Move the fucking car!
~ Hey, open the fucking door.
~ Move the car.
Open it.
~ Open the door.
~ Easy, easy, open the door.
~ Billy, open the fucking door!
~ Billy, open it!
~ Open the door!
Open the door!
Carter, listen to me. Don't do this.
Goddamn it! Get out of the fucking car.
Carter, listen to me. Hey, listen to me.
This isn't the way.
It's not the way. Get out of the car.
~ Come on!
~ It's coming, it's coming!
~ Carter.
~ It ain't my time.
Oh, shit.
Carter, listen to me. This isn't the way. Get out of the car, Carter.
Carter, get out of the car.
Come on, get out!
I can't get out!
Alex! No!
Man, he really is next.
~ Get out!
~ Come on!
~ Fuck!
Oh, God.
I saw it. I saw the belt.
~ Scared now?
~ It broke.
Bullshit. He saved your life again.
That's right.
You're next, Carter.
I'm staying the fuck away from you.
~ Shut up.
~ We don't need this shit right now.
I don't need it ever. What are you doing? Get away from him, he's next.
Hey, fuck you, Billy. I'm not dead.
Oh, you will be.
You're dead, you're dead.
And you ain't taking me with you!
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Jesus fucking Christ!
You should've been next.
You should've been next after Lewton.
That's the plan. That's the design.
~ You should be dead.
~ You're the fucking devil.
I saw the seat belt.
I knew it would rip.
That's how I saved him.
Just like the plane.
Just like the explosion, I saw it.
~ The police are coming.
~ Fuck, I saved him.
Because I saved him....
....it skipped Carter, went to the next in the path of the explosion, Billy.
I have to see it.
And if I see it, then I intervene. And if I intervene, I cheat the design.
What, intervene?
What are you, God now?
Gods aren't afraid to die.
Gods don't die. We do.
~ You know?
~ Baby, you're losing it, okay?
The police will be here.
We have to get you to my cabin.
You can hide,
and get your head together.
Okay, after Billy, I'm next. I'm next.
~ And then me.
~ Hey, hey, hey, listen.
I'm not gonna let it happen, okay?
~ Listen to me, all right?
~ Hey, hey, hey.
Why don't you two
just get the fuck out of here?
Rusted.
Tetanus.
Nice one.
I overlooked it.
You tried to capitalize.
But I caught you, you fuck.
I can beat you.
Yeah, I mean, not forever, but I got this cabin rigged to beat you now!
~ She was there a minute ago.
~ What are you talking about?
I'm not turning him in.
It's too dangerous for him
out there alone.
~ I go with you.
~ You can't.
Clear, you just tell us where he is.
Wait at home, I give you my word....
....that we will bring him in safely in protective custody.
I never moved.
Christa asked me to change seats but I never moved.
I would've been up next to Tod.
Fuck, why didn't I remember that?
I never moved.
Clear's seat was in front of mine.
She's next.
Alex!
Come on, get in the car.
We're going around. Get in the car.
Come on!
~ Go!
~ Move!
Oh, shit.
~ There!
~ Come on, let's go, over here.
Alex!
Alex, we're trying to help you.
Fritz, get away from it.
Come on.
Alex!
Run!
We lost him.
From the direction,
there's only one place he's heading.
No shit.
Clear!
No.
Oh, my God.
Don't move. Stay there.
Don't move, don't move.
Don't touch anything.
You're grounded by the tires, okay?
The car's gonna explode.
I can only hold on for so long,
you know what to do.
Don't!
When I do this, it'll skip you,
and it'll be over.
~ It's the only way we can cheat death again.
~ No, don't!
Clear, I am not gonna let it beat us both. You know what to do.
I'll always be with you.
No!
Alex! Alex, get away from there.
Alex. Alex.
Damn it, you can't do this to me.
Come on, baby. Come on.
Alex, Alex?
Oh, shit, he's not breathing.
Hold on, Alex. Come on, stay with me.
~ Well, we made it.
~ Paris, I can't believe it.
I just can't believe
we got on a plane again.
You know what I'm saying?
Wow.
It's weird being here, huh?
We finally completed a puzzle.
It's just there's something missing, you know?
~ To Terry.
~ Yeah.
~ To Tod.
~ To all of our friends that can't be here.
~ Cheers.
What?
If you would have told me
six months ago....
....that the three of us
would be sitting here having a drink....
~ Yeah.
~ I don't know.
I mean, sometimes it just feels
like the two of you....
....are the only ones
who can really understand.
You were right, Browning.
It did skip us. There was a design.
We beat it. You know, we won.
I think the only thing we won, Carter, is a chance at a full life.
A chance that I won't ever waste.
Yeah, there's just something....
You know, something I can't figure out.
~ What?
~ About the design.
Alex, just let it go. All right?
I swear.... Just hear me out, all right?
~ Oh, my God.
~ It's just.... Listen.
Now, the path of the explosion determined the order of our deaths, right?
When I intervened and saved Carter....
....it skipped him and went to the next person in the path. It went to Billy.
All right, and then it was Clear.
But I intervened and saved her,
so it went to me, but in my case....
....no one intervened, right?
I was thrown from that power line by the explosion.
~ So....
~ So why did it skip you, right?
How do we know that this isn't exactly what was meant to happen?
That out of everyone on Flight 180, you, me and Carter were meant to live.
Maybe that was the design all along.
~ Or you could still be next.
~ Shut up, Carter.
What? I didn't make up the rules.
Somebody's gotta intervene
before death can skip them.
Alex proved that three times.
In the plane, with me, you.
For all I know, it could circle back and get us all again.
But I am the safest fucker in the world because you're still next.
Can we just stop talking about this?
Let's figure out
what we're gonna do tomorrow.
I'm gonna meet you back at the hotel.
~ Just wait, I'll go with you.
~ No, just stay here.
Okay, Clear? Just stay here.
All right?
See, it's true.
I told you you were next, man.
Stop it, Carter.
~ Alex, wait.
~ No, Clear, stay there.
Okay? Stay away.
Alex!
I told you, you were next.
~ Then it just skipped me.
~ So who's next?