Promo Bonus 300%. Bonus Langsung setiap hari
Gabung sekarang di mantulbanget.net
Situs dengan Winrate terbesar di Indonesia
Tomorrow marksthe one year anniversary
since Velez Air Flight 180exploded and crashed
shortly after takeofffrom JFK airport.
It's a disasterthat's affected many.
None more so thanMt. Abraham High School,
which lost 40 students and fourfaculty members in the crash.
But it was the eventsafter the crash
that has turnedthis tragic story
into something evenstranger.
The survivors who managed to getoff the plane before it crashed
died soon thereafterin a series
of mysteriousand bizarre accidents.
Now, to some, these deathsare just tragic coincidences,
but to others,they're an indication
that there are moresinister events taking place.
That's the contentionof tonight's guest.
Thank you for joining usthis evening.
Thank you for having me.
And I appreciate you usingthe word sinister.
Most people say supernaturalbecause they think I'm talking
about ghosts and witchesand stuff like that.
Here's your chanceto set the record straight.
Great. Okay.
I believe that there'sa sort of force,
an unseen malevolentpresence...
That's all around usevery day.
And it determineswhen we live and die.
And some people callthis force the devil,
but I think thatwhole religious thing is--
so I prefer to call itdeath itself.
So I'm surrounded by death?
Absolutely. Absolutely.
Every day, everywhere,all the time.
And that's what I want peopleto understand--
that deathhas this grand design
that we all fit into.
So when Alex Browninggot off that plane
and took the othersurvivors with him,
he basically screwed updeath's plan.
And that's what I'm tryingto warn people about.
And the fact that allof the survivors have died
is your evidence of this?
Well, it's not so muchthat the survivors died,
but it's the waythat they died.
I mean, there wereso many weird,
seemingly random thingsabout the way they died.
It just didn'tmake sense.
And that's the proofthere's something out there--
Wait, that's not proof.That is your interpretation
of events that can't be provenin order to support your ideas.
Kimberly.
You should be moreopen-minded about--
What happened afterthat was just coincidence.
May I finish?
Mere coincidence would haveone or two of these kids die.
But not all of themincluding their teachers.
Yes, butpeople die all the time,
so why should this beany different?
It forced peopleto question
these so-calledeveryday coincidences.
What if theywere something more?
What if you could dosomething about it?
Please, are you listeningto yourself? This is crazy.
You're saying we should be on guardevery morning when we leave the house?
That's exactlywhat I'm saying.
Exactly it.
And in order to survive--
the only way to survive
is to look beneaththe visible world.
Because in the end no onecan escape death.
And today may be your dayto die.
Okay, I'll call you.
Kimberly, are you sureyou've got everything?
Credit card,cell phone, triple-a card?
Dad, it's Daytona,not Somalia.
All right. Fix-a-flat, roadflares, sunblock, mace?
Condoms, whips, chains.
Just kidding, Mr. Corman.
Don't worry,I'll keep an eye on her.
That makes me feela lot better, thanks.
- Okay.- All righty.
Can we go get the guys?I'm getting horny.
Go on.
Okay, I'll call you.
Whips and chains.That's nice.
Whatever,your dad's cool.
Buckle up!
Watch it!
- Oh, easy, Kimmy. First year of driving?- Sorry.
- Oh my God.- Fucking freak.
Yo, Dano,shouldn't we help your mom?
Good one, man.You're hilarious.
You're not getting any of my weed.Nothing.
Whatever.
What are we goingto do in Daytona?
We're going to seelots of honeys there.
We're gonna get drunk, we're gonnasmoke this big "El gagerero,"
we're gonna have thisawesome party...
Pileup! Pileup!
A candlelight vigilto mark the one year anniversary
of the crash of flight 180 willbe held at 8:00 P.M. tonight
at the Mt. AbrahamHigh School auditorium.
♪ Highway to hell...
Oh my God.
- Hello?- Hey, Kimberly, it's dad.
Hey, what's up?
Listen, your car's leakingtransmission fluid.
So I want you to getit checked right away.
Okay, yeah.
I'll do that.
I mean it. Take care of it.
- Is that someone coughing?- Yeah, okay.
I'll take care of it.I'll talk to you later.
- I love you.- Bye, honey.
- What did you do?- Look at those titties!
- Shut up.- You missed that?!
That's too bad.That's too bad.
Oh, shit!
Fuck man, there's afucking cop behind us!
Pull in the right Lane now!
Shit.
Seriously, put it out.
- Put that thing out.- All right.
Wait, wait, wait!
- Get rid of it.- Shit.
Hey, it's Kat.
Listen--what the hell?!
Just wait. Not you.
I think we better pull overand check the car, because--
Kimberly, the caris going to be fine.
Your dad's going to be fine,you're going to be fine.
Okay?
Look at that guy.
He's drinking a beer.
Oh, yeah,that's real responsible.
You ever hearof the ozone layer, asshole?!
♪ When it comes to this drugshit I was made to play ♪
♪ don't come around if you ain'tgot no cocaine to bring... ♪
what? I'm wearingmy seatbelt.
You're gonna bust me,bitch?!
Aaah!
Son of a...
Bitch.
Fuck!
- Oh my God!- Watch out!
- Stop!- Oh my God!
Watch out!Aaah!
Shaina?
I can't get out of here!
Help me!
Oh, easy, Kimmy.First year of driving?
Yo, Dano,shouldn't we help your mom?
Good one, man.You're hilarious.
Pileup! Pileup!
- Oh my God.- What?
There's going to bea huge accident.
We're all gonna die!I just saw it.
That's it.My turn to drive.
- No, I'm serious.- Kim, what's wrong?
- What are you doing?- Oh my God.
...Of flight 180 willbe held at 8:00 P.M. tonight
at the Mt. AbrahamHigh School auditorium.
"Highway to hell.""Highway to hell..."
"Highway to hell"?
♪ I'm on a highwayto hell... ♪
okay, Kimberly,you're scaring me.
- Green means go, Kimmy.- Yeah.
Are you out of your mind?What the hell are you doing?
What the fuck, Kimberly?
What's this?
Kimberly, you just gotto breathe.
Oh, shit, shit.Five-o is coming.
- Let's fucking roll.- What?
Oh my God.
Do you know how muchfucking weed I have on me?
- Huh?- Dano, just shut up!
Just stay cool.
Oh, fuck. I'm going to jail.I'm fucking going to jail.
What's going on here?
I think there's goingto be a huge pileup.
I saw it.
There were bodieseverywhere.
There were logs--I saw it.
It just happened.
All right, miss, I'd like you toplease step out of the vehicle.
Just pull over!
I know,mommy's hungry, too.
Come on.
Come on!
Oh, fuck this.
I'm going to get thisand we're going to go.
Fuck.
What the hellis going on up there?
Excuse me!
Is there any waythat we could drive around?
- I have a delivery--
- You need to get backinto your vehicles.
- Just move it--- now!
That's it!
That's the truck that'sgoing to kill everybody.
You need to stopthat truck!
I told you again,you have to calm down!
- Why won't you listen to me?!
- Fuck!- Oh my God.
This is unit 13 requestingmedical assistance
and backup for a majortraffic accident...
Kimberly, what's going on?
No!
Listen, sir, this girlis really freaked out.
In fact, all of them arescared as you can imagine.
Scared?!
These people are the luckiestsons of bitches on the planet.
Get this guy,Evan Lewis--
yesterday the kid winsthe lotto.
Today, some loony bitchblocks traffic
and he avoids the worstpileup in years.
I should beso damn "unlucky."
Go babysit the restof them.
I'll be done with Lewisin a minute.
Hey, excuse me--
We're trying to dothe best we can.
We're going to get you outof here as soon as possible.
I just think it'sa bunch of bullshit.
Listen, I knowyou've gone over all this
with detective Suby...
But would you mindtelling me what happened?
It was likeI was there.
I knew something bad was goingto happen even before it did.
I just felt wrong,just like...
Just like what?
Look, I knowthis sounds crazy but...
You guys all heardabout flight 180, right?
The kid who got offthe plane?
Well, it happeneda year ago, today.
My premonitionwas just like his.
- What are you talking about?- Come on.
You must have readabout the kid
who had a dreamabout a plane blowing up,
so he got all his buddiesoff the plane
and then the thing blew upjust like in his dream?
- Yeah.- But did you hear what happened after?
So a month goes by,right?
Everything seems cool.
But then all the survivorsstart to die one-by-one.
'Cause when your number's up,your number's up, right?
You know, some people even say thatdeath itself was stalking them,
hunting each one down
until they were all...Dead.
Please.
There was one survivor.
Clear Rivers is ina padded room
at the StonybrookInstitution.
Well, that's encouraging.
Okay, you want meto believe this is true,
that this is happeningall over again?
I don't knowwhy we're even here.
What do you want from me?
But if I was never meantto pull over,
we all should have diedin that pileup.
Which means deathcould be coming for us.
Yeah, like...
What if we're all getting that"different strokes" curse or something?
I think you're allare certifiable.
I can't believe I've beenlistening to this crap.
Let's go.Let's go, Tim.
Mrs. Carpenter,please.
Kimberly!
Oh baby!
- Are you okay?- I'm so sorry.
Shh, shh.
You can all go now.Thank you for your patience.
Could I ask you something?
Anything.
Did mom ever have any...
I don't know, weirdfeelings about anything?
What do you mean?
Like visionsor premonitions.
Sweetie, are you sureyou're okay?
Dad, I knowthis sounds crazy,
but I'm really scaredfor the others.
I don't know, I havethis really bad feeling.
What?
It's not over yet.
Jesus Christ!
Shit!
Hey, Evan, it's Tawny.
Sorry I haven't called.
Hey, listen, I heardabout your lottery win.
Let's hook up.Call me.
Yeah.
Hi, Evan, it's Nikki.
We met at Tucker's partylast year?
I know it's been awhile, butI've been thinking about you.
I just wanted to say congratulations.
- So give me a call.
555-0123. Bye.
You little bastard.
Shit.
Come on.Come on.
Fuck. Fuck.
Come on!
Come on.
Fuck!
Jesus!
Oh!
Hey, this is Evan.Leave a message.
If you're looking for Rick,I don't know where he is,
and I don't knowwhen he's coming back. Thanks.
Evan, call me when youget in, you lucky fuck!
Come on! Come on!Come on!
Aah!
Jesus!
Come on.
Aah!
Shit, I'm lucky.
Jesus Christ!
No, mother,
just turn on any station.
Well, I don't know how youmissed it, it's been on all day.
Yes, mother,channel 4 is fine.
Okay-- here it is!I got to go, okay?
I got to go!
To recap our top story,
route 23 was backed upfor almost nine hours today.
A record-breaking pileupkilled an estimated 18 people.
Emergency crews spent hourssifting through the wreckage
hoping to recover any survivorsfrom this tragic collision.
So far police are refusing torelease the names of the victims
until the familiesare notified.
The cameraof a highway patrol car
managed to catchthis shocking footage.
- A semi comes...- Oh my God.
And smashesinto a red SUV.
- The driver of the SUV...- No, um...
Leave it.
...may havesaved her life.
He pulled her backat the last second
just as the semi plowedinto the vehicle.
The passengers insidethe SUV...
Oh, oh, oh! You guys see that?!Shit, I was there, baby!
In other news, a freak accidenttook the life of a lotto winner.
- Friends say Evan Lewis...- Hey, shh.
Was on top of the world afterrecently winning $250,000.
But in tragic turn of events,Lewis died today
while trying to escape a firein his apartment.
He managed to make it outof the building,
but somehow the ladderon the fire escape
slipped and impaled him.
Investigators believe Lewisdied instantly.
Come in.
Hey, buddy.
I want you to take thisso you can get some sleep.
And then tomorrow it's off to thedentist, which I know you love.
Now, get some rest.
- Mom.- Yeah?
You think those guyswere bsing us today?
Yeah.
Some people just needsome rewiring, that's all.
Lights out.
At the requestof the patient,
you'll relinquishany sharp objects
such as: Nail files,pencils, pens,
safety pins, bobby pins,your necklace,
matches, lighters,belts, belt buckles,
earrings, hair clips,glasses, shoelaces,
paper clips, watches, moneyclip, pocket knives,
food, drinks, keys,cell phone--
you have a cell phoneon you?
--poisons, pills,medications.
Great. And let me seeyour nails.
Good. Then I thinkwe're all done.
Wait.
Is she dangerousor something?
No, honey,she expects you are.
Get him off me.Get him off me!
How long are they gonna keepher locked up like this?
Depends on her, I guess.She's voluntary.
- Clear Rivers?- Don't come any closer.
They told meyou had something to do
with the crash on route 23.
Look, I don't know howto explain it,
but I saw the pileupbefore it happened.
And I saved some people.
And now you think deathis after you.
Nice work.
Maybe if you're real lucky,you'll wind up in here with me.
Anything else?
One of the people diedin a freak accident last night.
What if the other peopleare in danger, too?
If you put them on the list,they're already dead.
List? What list?
Death's list.
The survivors of flight 180
died in the exact order
they were originally meantto die in the plane crash.
That was death'soriginal design.
The list.
I was supposed to diein that crash with my friends.
So you're telling methat I'm next?
You said someone else diedlast night.
That means someone musthave intervened.
Officer Burke pulled me away fromthe crash that killed my friends.
Congratulations.
You'll be the last to go.
But don't worry,once the others are dead,
it'll come back for you.
It always does.
This doesn't make sense.
You said that you die in the orderyou're originally meant to.
But my friends died lastin my premonition, not first.
Wait.
Dead last?
Backwards.
Are you sure?
In my premonition
that Nora womanand her kid died.
Then Evan,then me and my friends.
Why is this evenhappening to me?
That's what Alex usedto ask himself.
So, what am Isupposed to do?
Clear.
Watch out for the signs.
What?
Have you ever seen anythingcreepy or ominous?
An in-your-face ironykind of thing?
The songs on the radio.
Yeah, the guy in the beer truck,everything on the road.
Well, don't ignore it.
Recognizing those signsusually means
the difference betweenlife and death.
You got to help me.
I don't haveto do anything.
But you beat it.
Take a look around.
What did I beat, Kimberly?
If you were smart,you'd save yourself
and just forgetabout the others.
How can you say that?You have a responsibility.
My friends are dead.
That's how I can say that.
This is what happened to Alexwhen I was responsible for him.
Get out.
Before you hurt meor yourself.
- All right, you know what?- What?
I think you're a coward.
You hide out in herebecause you're
too damn bitter and selfishto help any other person.
In my opinion,you're already dead.
I tried callingyou last night,
but your father saidyou were sleeping.
- Evan Lewis is dead.- Yeah.
I've been getting calls all morningfrom everyone who was on the on-ramp.
We're meeting tonightat my apartment.
Wait, so... You believeall this death stuff?
Well, at first,no, I didn't.
Until last yearwhen I was dispatched
to clean up one of theflight 180 survivors.
Clean up, I don't--
- did you see that?- See what?
- Pigeons.- Pigeons?
- It's a sign.- A sign of what?
If Clear's right aboutthe order,
then Nora and Tim are goingto be attacked by pigeons.
I'm not following you.
They're nexton death's list.
If we don't find them,they're going to die.
The doctor's readyfor you, now.
If he gives me the gas
and I wake upwith my pants unbuttoned...
- We ain't paying.- Tim.
There you are.
What happenedto you yesterday, Tim?
We missed you in here.
We got hung up by thataccident on route 23.
Good lord.How lucky that you're okay.
Your mom says you've beenhaving some pain lately.
Not really.
I'm a bitdisappointed, Tim.
Does your mom knowyou've been smoking?
Uh-huh.
Ow.
Yeah, that one's goingto have to be filled.
Damn those pigeons.
How many times am I going to haveto replace those goddamn windows?
We can'tdo it, boss, we can't do it!
This will only stingfor a moment.
Open big.
Little bit wider.
Wider.
Okay.
Oh God.
How do theyexpect me to...
Would you rather just havethe laughing gas?
- Yeah.- Okay.
Jean, I'm goingto need you in here.
You're have to speak up,there's too much noise.
What?! I can't hear you!
Excuse me, what?!
Yes, the sixth at 2:00 P.M.
Jean! Let meget this started.
Tim, you'll be awakeand a little groggy,
but you're not goingto be able to move much.
Okay, great, thanks.All right, turn around.
The cleaning lady said they're at theEllis Medical Complex off of 14th.
Goddamn it anyway.
- Okay, I got it.- I can't find a box!
Not again. Careful.
There we go.
Jean, how isTim doing in there?
What did he sayabout your tooth?
- Did he say--- I can't remember.
- Nora!- The pigeons!
What? Pigeons?
Hey, whoa, whoa!Kid, kid!
- No-oo!- Tim!
Look out!
- Stay back, stay back!- No! Please, no!
Nora's not coming.She won't leave her son.
- No, but she's next--- Right now I don't think she cares.
This is really happeningagain, isn't it?
I hoped we'd get there
and they'd be fine,
and Clear Riverswas just full of shit,
and Evan Lewis' deathwas just some freak accident.
But we're all goingto die, aren't we?
I'm so scared.
I know you didn't askfor any of this...
But I don't think you have itin you to quit either.
A second one just died.
A 15-year-old kid.
I hope you're readyfor this.
It's this way.
How is this guygoing to help us anyway?
He seemed to knowa hell of a lot more
about deaththan he ever told us.
Shouldn't we knock first?
He probably already knowswe're coming.
Hello, Clear.
I've been expecting you.
Oh my God.
- That's Evan Lewis.- Come to pick my brain?
Just a simple question and we'll leaveyou alone with your new friend.
Dead...
Yet still fresh.
Look, we drovea long way to get here,
so if you happen to knowhow to stop death,
it would be really greatif you told us.
You can't cheat death.
- There are no escapes.- Bullshit.
You told me deathhas a distinct design.
But Alexand I cheated death,
not once but dozensof times.
The design is flawed,it can be beaten.
Such fire in you now.
People are alwaysmost alive
just before they die.
Don't you think?
Look, please...
If you know of anythingthat could help us,
what harm could it do?
Only new lifecan defeat death.
What the helldoes that mean?
Some people say there's abalance to everything.
For every lifethere's a death,
and for every deaththere is a life.
But the introduction of lifethat was not meant to be,
that caninvalidate the list,
force deathto start anew.
You have to followthe signs...
Kimberly.
How do you know my name?
- Whoa!- Wait a second.
"New life defeats death"?"Follow the signs"?
Where did youfind that guy?
I thought he wassupposed to help us,
not freak us out.
What the fuckare you thinking?!
I'm thinking suckon my junk, bee-atch.
Little punk.
What is it?
- What did you see?
You have to tell us,what did you see?
Kimberly, look at me!You have to tell us.
What did you see?!
I was driving a white van.
I don't know,I must have lost control,
because I crashedinto a lake.
- And I drowned.- You were there?
I can practically tastethe water in my mouth.
Wait, remember, the on-ramp?
There was a pregnant womanin a white delivery van.
He said only new lifecan defeat death.
If she gives birthto a baby
that would've diedin that car crash--
a brand new soul that was neverpart of death's design--
it throws the whole listout of whack
and we start overwith a clean slate.
It seems like a bit of areach, don't you think?
What else could it mean?
We have to findthe pregnant lady's number.
I don't have it.She never came to the station.
We have to find her and warn her about thelake so she can stay alive to have the baby.
- That'll be an easy conversation to have.- How are we gonna find her?
- There could be thousands ofwhite vans in the state. - Hey!
I'm a cop, remember?
Wait, that's it.
Got it.
With the plate numberI can put out an apb.
Here we go.
The vehicleis a delivery van
registered to Marcusand Isabella Hudson.
We should pick them uppretty quickly.
Come on, let's getto the meeting.
Hey, hold the door!
Hey, let go of my shoe!
Give me my shoe!
I wrote to management two weeksago about these friggin' bumpers.
Is that dogshit, dude?
Eww.
Oh, you got somethingon your...
It's still there, bro'.Here, I can get it for you.
No, it's all right.
I'll do itif you want me to do it.
Just let-- I'll--let me do it.
What?
Hey, man,how you doing?
Listen, any wordon that white van yet?
Okay, keep checking.
Does anybody have a valium?
Oh, yeah.
Here.
You're just going to wantto take half of that.
Keep 'em coming.
If what you're sayingis true,
that means I'm next.
This is crazy, people,come on.
First deathis stalking us,
and now premonitions?What?
You're not next, Nora.
Nobody has to be next.That's the point.
We need to help each otherin order to get through this.
This cannot be happening.
See, because my careeris at a peak
and I finally meta quality guy.
I just bought a house.
Maybe if you shut thefuck up, you'll live.
Like I'm goingto take advice from you.
Okay, look,if you know what to look for,
you have a fighting chance.
If I call and say,I don't know-- subway--
get to a high-rise fast.
A place where no subwaycould ever possibly go.
Get it?
Okay, you guys, listen--
just because Kimberlyhas these visions,
it doesn't meanwe're not all capable
of seeing signsto some extent.
Okay, okay, look.
I gotta call bullshit.
I mean, I've sat hereand listened
to all your theoriesand all your stories,
and I think it's justall bullshit.
Call it what you want!
- It'll keep your ass alive.- Darlin', my ass is alive!
Has been all day.
There is nobody after usbut you,
trying to make us all crazy.
I should have seenthat coming.
Yeah.
If death is outto get you,
why don't you getthe hell away from us?
She's the only one that'sdealt with this before.
We need to look outfor each other from now on.
Sleep in shifts.
We need to safe-proofthis deathtrap.
Get you to step outof the van, miss?
Are you kidding me?
- What did I do?- This vehicle's been reported stolen.
Ohh!
Screw this.I'm going for a smoke.
No, no, no,it's not safe out there.
So, Nora's got to bite itbefore me anyhow, huh?
Oh, you people haveno sense of humor.
Nora, you okay?
Four years agomy husband died.
Now Tim.There's nothing left for me.
Don't say that,okay?
If it is my time to goand be in heaven...
With my family,I can accept that.
You got to trust me.We can fight this.
If we just sticktogether long enough
for herto have her baby--
if you'll excuse me,I have a funeral to plan.
Nora.
What do you thinkyou're doing?
- I'm finished. I'm out.- Don't leave, Eugene.
Look, look.
I control my life,all right?
Not some crazy listdeath has put together.
I'll be sure to carvethat into your tombstone.
Whatever. You may beable to scare these people,
- but I'm not buying that shit.- Be careful, man.
- Hey.- What?
Even if you don't believe,give this to Nora.
I'm just goingto put this in the...
Closet.
Sorry.
Whoa.
Man with hooks?
Man with hooks.
Hey, I think I seea man with hooks.
Is that...
- A sign?- Oh my God.
- Do you guys see that?- He's right.
- The phone.- Shit.
- Hello?- Nora!
- Who is this?- Can you hear me?!
Officer Burke,I can't--
I can't hear you!What?!
What does he--what?!
A man with hooksis going to kill you.
- What, what?- Oh...
What is it, Nora?
No!
- Wait, wait!- Let go!
Wait, wait, Nora!
- Get me out of here!- Will you stop it?!
Let me help!
Let me go!
Let go of me!
Kat!
Help me!
- Wait!- I don't want to die!
Aah!
I got it, thanks.They found the van.
Isabella's being held at theGreenwood Lake Sheriff's station.
I'm in control of my life!
- Kiss my ass!- Eugene, what is it?
- I control my life!- What happened, Eugene?
- You hear me, you reaper cocksucker?!- Calm down.
- What happened? Where's Nora?- Back the fuck up!
- Whoa, whoa, okay!- Back the fuck up!
Eugene, what's wrong?Just tell us what happened.
All right, giveme the gun, Eugene.
- Give me the gun.- No! Fuck no!
Eugene, you just gotto relax, bro', okay?
You just gotto calm down, man.
Give me the gun.Give me the gun, Eugene!
- No, no, no, no!- Don't do it! Don't do it!
- I ain't going out like that.- Hey, Eugene, no!
- On my terms!- Oh my God!
You hear me!
- God!
Oh!
You don't keep it loaded?
- Maybe they're all duds.- Six in a row?
Never.That's impossible.
It wasn't his turn to die.
Can we find the pregnantwoman, now, please?
Is this safe, guys?
I mean, someone in this caris about to get whacked.
Do the rest of us really feellike sitting next to him?
Or her?
Hopefully her.
Okay, guys,let's not panic.
- Isabella's safe.- How do you know?
You said she was goingto drive into a lake.
How can she if she'sin protective custody?
Look at me.
Come on.
Does it look likeI'm in the condition
to commit grand theft auto?This is insane.
Look, hopefullythe district judge
will have it all sorted outby Monday morning, okay?
Marcus.
Marcus, Marcus.
When I get out of here,I am going to sue his--
- Oh my God.- What, what now?
My water just broke.
- What?- My water, it just broke.
- I'm gonna have my baby.- No, not here.
- No, you can't do this to me.- Don't just stand there!
- Get me to a hospital!- Give me a second to think!
I am not going to have my babyin a jail cell!
Get me to the hospital!
Okay, okay!
Sheriff Perry, this isDeputy Adams, come back.
God, I need the car!Sheriff Perry, I need the car!
My van! My van!Take my van!
Okay. Okay.
Yeah, we'll go.We'll go.
Yeah, we'll go.
Come on,come on!
Y'all want tohear something crazy?
It's not the first timeI cheated death.
A kid came to schoolwith a knife--
killed his teacher.
Teacher would havebeen me,
but I was transferred to anotherschool two days before.
That's fucking weird, man.
You want weird?
Last year my partner and Iwere heading out
when a call came inabout a train wreck.
Frank decidedto let me handle it alone.
He died that nightin a shootout.
If that call had come injust 10 seconds later,
I'd be dead, too.
Oh my God.
I'm sorry.
It's just I got one, too.
Okay, so last mayI'm supposed to go and stay
at this cheesy little bedand breakfast in Pennsylvania.
Anyhow, there's this majorgas leak no one knows about,
and all the guests suffocatedduring the night.
- So what happened?- I don't know.
I never made it.
The bus I was on splatteredsome girl over the road.
Was that in Mt. Abraham?
Yes. How did you know?
That bus you were on killedTerry chaney.
She was supposed to dieon flight 180.
Hey, do you guys rememberthat theater in Paris
that collapsed last yearand killed everybody inside?
Well, I had tickets to go.
But one night I'm in Paris
and I'm justtripping on acid
and sipping lattesand such.
And then all of a sudden
this dude out of nowhere
just gets whackedby this falling sign.
- Carter.- Wait, wait, wait.
The teacher I replaced,her name was Val Lewton.
She was from Mt. Abraham.She died in an explosion.
Shit. The call aboutthe train wreck
that saved my life...
That was the nightI scraped up Billy Hitchcock.
Wait a minute.Who are these people?
The people who got offof flight 180.
They were my friends.
Kimberly, tell uswhat happened.
About a year ago my mom and Iwere at the mall.
I was supposedto meet her outside,
but I got caught up watchingthis news report
about some kidthat committed suicide.
I kept thinking,
"how can you strangle yourselfin the bathtub?
That's stupid."
It felt wrong.
And yet...
I heard some gunshotsand I ran outside.
Some kids were tryingto steal my mom's car.
She tried to fight them off,she was a fighter,
and they killed her.
After the funeralI kept thinking
that it shouldhave been me.
I guess everyone mustthink that.
But I guess I was right.
Get there.
Could you drivea little faster maybe?!
- I'm going as fast as I can.- God!
When we gotoff flight 180,
it didn't just changeour lives.
It affected everyoneand everything
we've comeinto contact with since.
I'm not sureI'm understanding you.
Being alive afterwe were supposed to die,
it caused an outward ripple.
A rift in death's design.
So if you had nevergotten off the plane...
We wouldn't be alivein the first place.
Yes, that's why deathis working backwards!
It's tying upall the loose ends,
sealing the rift onceand for all.
Oh, shit!
Jesus Christ!
Hang on! Hang on!
- Is everybody all right?- Oh God.
God, Eugene!
- He can't breathe.- Oh, my legs!
No, please.
- It's not going to wait.- I got to go help those people.
Do you want to deliverthis baby?
Those people can help.Let's go.
Officer Adams reportinga vehicle collision
off 9-aat the 180 mile-marker.
Send all emergency vehiclesto the scene.
- We have to go. Go!- Okay, okay, okay!
Just-- okay, okay!We're going! We're going!
- Easy, easy.- Here, here, here.
I think he hasa collapsed lung.
- Everyone okay?- Call an ambulance!
Stay with us.
Hey, hey you!
Hey! Come on.Help me out.
You got to get me out of here beforethis thing explodes or something, okay?
I think it's okay.
I don't smell any gasand nothing's dripping.
All right, get this thing off me.Just pull. Hurry.
Okay. Be careful.Ready?
Oh God, Jethro!Jesus Christ!
I got to be able to usemy legs when I'm done.
I'm so-- dad!
Eugene, everything'sgoing to be okay.
If he doesn't get a respirator,he's not going to make it!
We're going to get you to the hospital.Be careful with that!
Check the gaugeson the regulator,
and watch outfor overdoses!
- And look out for potholes and puddles.- You can't come in, miss.
And watch outfor power lines!
Watch it!
You trying to get yourselfkilled, little boy?
You got to useyour head, man.
Thanks.
Okay, let's go.
How is she doing?
I think she's goingto be okay.
- Can I ask you a question?- Yeah.
When I die...
Is it going to hurt?
I don't know.
You're going to die after me,right?
Yeah, I guess so.
Would you take these?
And if I die...
Will you throw outall my drugs
and my paraphernaliaand my porno?
You know...
Anything that's goingto break my mom's heart.
Please?
Thank you.
This is Cheyenne Jacobson
reporting livefrom the Gibbons Farm.
Sheriff Perry,officer Burke here.
I'm trying to get someinformation on Isabella--
she did?
Okay. Thanks.Great. Kimberly!
Isabella's at Lakeview Hospital.They're prepping her for delivery.
- We got to go now.- What about Kat?
I'll go talk to her.
Hi.
Just find Isabella and getthis thing over with, okay?
Go on, I'll be fine.
- Where's Rory?- I don't know.
Could you be a little quieterwith that thing, please?
Yeah, sure. I'll justput it on quiet mode.
That would be good.
Rory.
Oh my God!
Somebody get out there!
- We have to get to the hospital now!- Well, take my truck!
The keys are in it.
Kimberly!
- Kimberly.- What do you see?
- What are we looking for?- It's not here.
This one was different.
It was like the van crashinginto the lake.
I was in a hospital,there was screaming
and a nurse was tryingto choke me.
I couldn't see her, but Icould see her name tag.
It was right in my face.Kalarjian.
I think a nurse named Kalarjian isgoing to try and kill Isabella.
Listen to me, Isabella!I need you to stop pushing!
What's wrong?Is my baby all right?
The cord's around the neck.This baby's in trouble.
A bizarre accidenthas left two people dead,
one of them killed by a safetydevice meant to protect us.
Ironically, the womanwas impaled through the head
after her emergencyairbag deployed.
She was trapped in her vehicle after itcrashed into a field near greenwood lake.
Suddenly the airbagwent off...
Isabella Hudson!What room is she in?
We may need to doa stat caesarean!
Get Dr. Kalarjianup here now!
Dr. Kalarjian, code blue.Delivery room six.
I'm just goingto wait outside,
'cause I'm just reallyin the way here.
- Don't you dare leave me!- Okay, okay.
You guys, get to Isabella!
I'm going to find Eugene!
Dr. Kalarjian, code blue.Delivery room six.
Dr. Kalarjian, delivery room six.Code blue.
Dr. Kalarjian,in here, hurry!
That's her.
Wait, wait, wait!
Contractions have stopped.
Arrest in descent halfwaythrough the birth canal.
Bad tracing,it's losing oxygen.
The cord's compressed!
- Down to 40.- Oh God! What's happening?!
Where's Kalarjian?!
Dr. Kalarjian!
- Dr. Kalarjian!- Not now, I'm busy.
- Ow! Hey! Hey!- Police business.
Just push a little more.
Oh, no.
Isabella, is the baby okay?
I'm sorry.You can't be here.
- I'm going to have to ask you to leave.- I need to know--
I need to know if the baby's all right!
It's a boy.
Thank you.Congratulations!
Who the hell are they?
Oh my God!
- Clear.- I can't find Eugene.
- No, don't worry. She had the baby!- It's okay.
It's over.It's okay.
- Kimberly.- What did you see?
I don't think Isabella was eversupposed to die in that pileup.
Then what's the premonitionof the lake supposed to be?
Try to remember.
Bloody hands.Someone with bloody hands.
Eugene.
Only new life defeats death.What is that supposed to mean?
You saw an ecg machineand what else?
Bloody hands.What else did you see, Kimberly?
Wait.
Eugene.
Oh God, no!
Bloody hands.
It's me.The premonitions are about me.
- What?- Crash cart.
Let's go! Move it!
Dr. Kalarjian.
ECG machine.
The lake.
The white van.
What are you talking about?
Kimberly:New life.
What is it?
I know what I haveto do to save us.
- I have to die.- No, that's crazy.
You can't give up now.We have to fight this thing.
Get Kalarjian.
Only new life can defeat death.
If it is my time togo and be in heaven...
With my family.I can accept that.
Flight 180...
I know what Ihave to do to save us.
There are no known survivors.
I have to die.
Ready and clear.
Nothing.
- Come on.- Ready, clear.
She's back!
Epinephrine. Two milligrams,IV push.
I want her preppedand stabilized for ICU.
Welcome back.
They lost youfor a minute there.
Hey. We did it.
Thanks to you,we cheated death.
- Would you like some wine?- I think I'll stick to our beer, thanks.
All right.
This is really great,Mrs. Gibbons.
Thank you so muchfor inviting us.
It's our pleasure.
- How are you doing, Kimberly?- Good. Yeah.
I had a fun summer.
I don't know, I guess things arepretty much getting back to normal.
Brian, I think you bettergo check that barbecue.
Hey, careful.Those things are dangerous.
Trust me. I think I'vebeen through closer calls.
Yeah, me too.
Dad, you should tell themabout the news van thing.
What's that?
Brian was almost hit by thatnews van that day in the field.
And your friend Rory, he pulledhim back at the last second.
Saved his life.
You nevertold me that, Peter.
Boy, that was lucky.
Brian!
♪ I'm right behind you
♪ here I come
♪ let me remind you
♪ you're on the run
♪ my name is death
♪ come taste mypeppermint-laced breath ♪
♪ all lights are diamonds
♪ behind dark glass
♪ she leans toward me
♪ a forward pass
♪ in the blood,come-a, come-a cow cud ♪
♪ nobody really caresabout you now, bud ♪
♪ pay the price, roll the dicerun the maze like-a mice ♪
♪ ashes ever turn to dustfor the two of us ♪
♪ my name is death
♪ come taste mypeppermint-laced breath ♪
♪ come taste, come taste
♪ come to the party
♪ the price is free
♪ you seem to persisthanging on the fount beauty ♪
♪ my name is death
♪ come taste mypeppermint-laced breath ♪
♪ come taste my
♪ peppermint-laced
♪ my name is...
♪ Death.