OCR issues corrected & timing
moved slightly ahead by Tronar
Alex.
Tod and George's
dad just called.
He's picking you up
at 3:30 tomorrow.
And the bus leaves the high
school for the airport around 5.
How's my suitcase
working out for you?
Whoa, Mom, Mom, Mom, you
gotta leave that on.
Yeah, it's like the tag made the last flight
without the plane crashing or anything.
So I figure it's gotta be on the
bag, or at least, with the bag.
For luck.
Where would you get a
nutball idea like that?
I'm still here.
So 17, on the loose.
Senior trip with your
friends in Paris.
Ten days in the springtime.
Live it up, Alex.
You got your whole
life ahead of you.
Alex.
The white zone...
is for immediate loading and
unloading of passengers only.
No parking.
Yeah, I've been sitting
here for over an hour.
Where are you?
- Hey, Hitchcock.
- What?
Let me give you a hand with this, man.
There you go.
Carter, you dick.
- Schmuck.
- Good one.
- You left this on the bus.
- Oh, thanks.
Come on, let's get
your stuff together.
Hey, Christa. Hi, Blake.
- What are you doing?
- He's the man. The man.
All right, you guys
got everything?
Yeah, yeah. Dad, we're all set.
Does that mean go?
Don't know.
Look, this is for both of you, all right?
Have a great time.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Yeah.
- Both of us.
- Let's go.
- Alex.
- Yes?
- You take care of them.
- I will.
You know, I didn't think anything could
look worse than my yearbook photo.
How do you think I feel having
to look at you all the time?
- What the fuck does he want?
- Shh.
"The airport does not
endorse solicitors."
Death is not the end.
It will be for you if
you harass my students.
- Hare Rama.
- Fuck off.
I have to ask you a few
questions this evening.
Did you pack your bags yourself?
Have your belongings remained in
your possession the entire time?
Mr. Browning?
Oh, yeah.
Have you received any packages
from persons unknown to you?
- Same as your birthday.
- What?
September 25, 9:25.
Your birthday's the same
as your departure time.
- Because I looked at him.
- Are you sure?
Lisa, wait up.
No, it's okay.
Fuck, that was good.
Dick.
- Hey.
- Hey, George, Dad said both.
Both of us, all right, man?
Just give me some cash.
Hey, hey, knock it off.
- Excuse me.
- Catch.
You asshole.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Alex, let's go take a shit.
- Why don't you go by yourself?
- No, dude. Listen, okay?
Listen, take some knowledge.
We're about to board
a seven-hour flight.
The toilets in coach are barely
ventilated closets, all right, if that.
Now, let's say halfway through the
flight, your body wants that food out.
You gotta go torque
a wicked cable.
And then right after you, like, directly
after you walks in Christa or Blake.
You want them to associate you with
that watery sting in their eye?
That reflexive gag at the
back of their throat?
John Denver.
Died in a plane crash.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank
you for your patience.
At this time, we would like
to begin preboarding...
of Volée Air Flight 180
to Paris through Gate 46.
Anyone seen Billy Hitchcock?
How did we lose him?
Go. Go.
Go.
Ow.
That hurt.
Oh, my little baby.
That's a good sign. The
younger, the better.
It'd be a fucked-up God
to take down this plane.
Hi.
A really fucked-up God.
Yeah.
- Hi.
- Hey, Tod.
Hello. How you doing?
I'm gonna sit here.
- Can you switch seats with Christa?
- Oh, God.
You know, I would, but
I got a bladder thing.
It's a urinary tract infection.
Let's go ask Alex.
Alex, could you trade seats with Blake
so she and I could sit together?
She asked Tod, but he said he
had some sort of medical thing.
Please?
Yeah.
You're so sweet.
- Thanks, Alex.
- Thank you, Alex.
You're welcome, you're
welcome, you're welcome.
Fag.
Did you really think we're gonna
titty fuck them over Greenland?
You know, because of you, I gotta sit
here and watch fucking Stuart Little.
Thank you.
Thanks, man. That's great.
Sorry I'm late. That's
my seat right there.
- Hello?
- I'm going that way.
May I have your attention?
To properly fasten your seat belts,
slide the flat portion into the buckle.
Equipped with six emergency exits: Two in
front, two over the wing, two in the rear.
All exits are clearly marked.
Follow the red exit signs and
public lighting in the aisle way.
Flight attendants,
prepare for departure.
- All right.
- All right, all right.
Yeah.
Whatever.
Huh?
It's okay.
- I wanna go.
- It's fine.
It's okay, honey, I...
What the...?
Oh, my God!
Everybody...
No! No!
Christa! No!
Alex, could you trade seats with Blake
so she and I could sit together?
She asked Tod, but he said
he had some medical thing.
Please?
What's up, dude?
- Is there a problem, sir?
- What's your problem?
Alex, qu'est-ce que c'e-st?
- The fucking plane's gonna explode.
- Shut up, Browning.
- You're so not funny.
- If this is your joke...
it's not a joke.
It's not a joke.
- Alex, take it easy.
- That's it, sit down, Browning.
- It's going down.
- We will remove you.
- I'll remove him.
- I'll remove myself.
- Excuse me.
- Get off him.
- That's my seat right there.
- This plane is going down.
Everybody in the
aisle, off the plane.
- Get off the plane.
- Stay where you are.
- Just sit tight.
- The fucking plane is going down.
Go check him out.
See how he's doing.
Okay.
- I got my ticket here.
- Get off me.
Jerk.
- Hey.
- You got this?
No one gets back on board.
- That's my call.
- Wait, please.
I've got 40 students going to Paris.
Please, please?
- Look, you must understand my position.
- I understand, and I apologize for Alex.
But one of us needs
to be on that plane.
I cannot let students go
to Paris for ten days...
Carter, no.
- Sit the fuck down, Carter.
- Sit down.
Sit.
One of you can go on the flight.
That's it.
Larry.
Airline's not taking this well.
They'll let one of us back on.
The rest can take an 11:10 flight.
It gets in three...
I'll stay.
No, no, you know the whole French thing.
Get on the plane, it's fine.
Hi, Mr. Murnau. See, I
was in the bathroom.
And the lock, it
was stuck, and...
Oh, wait, I didn't
fight with anyone.
Damn.
Thanks.
I just... I called your parents.
They're on their way.
We should be going.
Alex, talk to me. Tell
me what happened.
I saw it.
Like, I don't know. I saw it.
I saw it on the runway.
I saw it take off.
I saw out my window.
- I saw the ground, and...
- Carter.
The cabin, it starts to shake, right?
And the left side blows up.
And then the whole
plane just explodes.
And it was so real. Just like how
everything happens, you know?
You been on planes that blew up?
You must have fallen asleep.
Whoa, we get thrown
off the plane.
We blow, what, a half
a day in Paris...
all because Browning has
a bad fucking dream?
But wait, "The plane, it's gonna
blow up, it's gonna blow up."
- Hey, hey, fuck you, Horton.
- Tod.
The only trip you're taking
is to the fucking hospital.
- Get off him.
- Hey, hey.
- Alex, stop it.
- Come on, now.
There they go, here we stay.
- You're paying for my trip.
- I wish you were on that plane.
- You fucking prick.
- Oh, shit!
- Call it in.
- Security...
You're looking at me
as if I caused this.
I didn't cause this.
Are there any survivors?
How should I know?
- What, you think I'm some sort of...?
- He's not a witch.
Hello, I'm Howard Seigel, National
Transportation Safety Board.
We've contacted all your families.
They are on the way.
Is there anyone here who feels they might
need a little medical attention...
or spiritual counseling
at this time?
What's going on?
Are there any survivors?
Well, the cause for the explosion
is still undetermined.
The Nassau County authorities
are on the scene.
Naval Search and Rescue en route.
We...
Excuse me.
I'm Agent Weine. This
is Agent Schreck.
We're with the FBI.
I understand now you all
must be feeling right now.
I know it's gonna be difficult.
We're gonna ask you questions
regarding today's events...
while they're still
fresh in your mind.
This will prove invaluable to our rescue
attempts and any criminal investigation.
You said, "Listen to me. This
plane will explode on takeoff."
How did you know that?
I got this feeling.
This weird feeling.
Did you take any sedatives
before boarding the plane?
Did you take any sleeping pills,
any narcotics, hallucinogens?
- Alex, do you take any drugs?
- No.
I saw it.
I saw it happen.
I saw the plane explode.
Did the feelings have anything
to do with your saying...
that you wished that Carter Horton was
on the plane just before it exploded?
- No.
- Then why'd you say it?
Because I really didn't
think it was gonna happen.
If that's the case, Alex, then why
did you really get off the plane?
My brother, George, he told me
to go and keep an eye on Alex.
And so he stayed, and...
He told me to get off the plane.
Larry Murnau said I should get back
on, but I told him that he should go.
I sent him back on the plane.
All right.
Nobody forced you off the plane.
You said you weren't friends
with those that were.
So, Clear, why did you
get off the plane?
Because I saw and I heard Alex.
And I believed him.
Honey.
Oh, God.
There he is.
Over here.
Thank you for the ride.
You're looking at the
first piece of debris...
to wash ashore from
Volée Air Flight 180...
which erupted shortly after a 9:25 p.m.
takeoff...
From John F. Kennedy
Airport in New York.
There are no known survivors.
However, Coast Guard and Naval
Search and Rescue efforts...
are continuing at this moment even as
jet fuel burns on the ocean's surface.
Authorities are pessimistic
about the possibility...
of finding anyone alive
from the ill-fated flight.
All 287 passengers
are feared dead.
Amongst the travelers, a class of
40 students and four teachers...
from Mount Abraham High School
in southeast New York...
en route to Paris
on a field trip.
There are reports that several students
were removed from the aircraft...
moments before departure.
However, investigators remain guarded
about the specifics of this incident.
Authorities from the National
Transportation and Safety Board...
and the Federal Bureau of
Investigation have arrived at JFK...
to begin the initial
investigation.
Eyewitnesses at the airport,
as well as on Long Island...
report seeing the plane explode.
No other aircraft were
visibly near Flight 180.
At JFK, air traffic controllers
are corroborating...
these eyewitness accounts.
After the explosion, debris apparently rained
into the Atlantic Ocean for several miles.
However, investigators are cautious
about verifying these accounts...
believing they'll learn more from the
found debris when daylight arrives.
Thirty-nine days have passed...
since we lost our 39 loved
ones, friends and teachers.
As each day passes without a
determining cause for the accident...
we ask ourselves, "Why?"
Ecclesiastes tells us:
"Man no more knows his own time than
fish taken in the fatal net..."
or birds trapped in the snare.
"Like these, the children of men caught
when the time falls suddenly upon them."
And so, before we can heal...
before we can escape the
presence of death and time...
we must mourn and celebrate
theirs with this memorial.
I hope you don't think because
my name ain't up on this wall...
that I owe you anything.
I don't.
Because all I owe
are these people.
To live my life to the fullest.
Why don't you stay off the
J.D., then, huh, Carter?
Listen. Don't you ever fucking
tell me what to do, all right?
I control my life, not you.
Carter.
I'm never gonna die.
Hey, Alex.
- Hey.
I took my driver's test
last week at the DMV.
Got a 70. it's the lowest score
you can get, but I passed.
When I was done with the test...
You know the guy that
drives with you?
- Right.
- Yeah, well, anyways.
He goes, "Young man, you're
gonna die at a very young age."
Yeah. Yeah.
Is that true?
Not now, not here,
not ever, Billy.
If I ask out Cynthia
Paster, will she say no?
Fuck.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- Miss Lewton...
- Don't talk to me.
You scare the hell out of me.
I'm gonna go up.
Hey.
I don't want you to take
this the wrong way.
But I miss you, you know?
Yeah.
Yeah, I miss you too.
But my father, you know,
he doesn't understand.
Yeah.
Hey, look, when he gets
over this thing...
you and me, little road
trip to the city, you know?
Catch the Yanks.
Yeah. Yeah, all
right, we'll do that.
Cool.
- Look, I'd better go.
- Yeah.
This thing Miss Lewton showed me in
class, they're gonna let me read it.
It says what I'm feeling.
Take care, man.
Because of you, I'm still alive.
Thank you.
"We say that the hour of
death cannot be forecast."
But when we say this, we imagine
that the hour is placed...
in an obscure and
distant future.
It never occurs to us that
it has any connection...
with the day already begun.
Or that death could arrive
this same afternoon.
This afternoon, which
is so certain...
"...and which has every
hour filled in advance."
What happened?
Where's Tod?
Alex.
Get out of here.
- Didn't you see it?
- What happened?
You caused Tod so much guilt over George
staying on the plane, he took his own life.
- No.
- Time to go.
Look, he wouldn't do that.
Okay? He said to me we'd be friends
again after you got better.
Why would he make plans with me if he
was thinking about killing himself?
Mr. Waggner.
- Mr. Waggner.
- Here we go.
Easy.
All right.
Here we go.
Let's go.
Almost autumn.
It's only the end of June.
Yeah, but everything's
always in transition.
If you focus even now,
just one week into summer...
you can feel almost
feel autumn coming.
Kind of like being able
to see the future.
Why were you at Tod's
house last night?
I've seen enough TV to know that the
FBI doesn't investigate teen suicides.
They were there last night.
They don't have a clue...
what caused the crash.
They haven't ruled out anything.
The fact that seven people got off
the plane is probably weird enough.
Not to mention that one of those
people had a vision, or whatever...
of the plane exploding minutes before
it did explode, is highly suspicious.
And it doesn't help that the visionary's
friend just committed suicide.
Why were you there last night?
Do you know what this is?
This is a...
Who's the spring-head guy?
It's you.
Not a likeness.
It's how you make me feel, Alex.
I'm sorry.
You know, like you, the sculpture
doesn't even know what, or why, it is.
It's reluctant to take form.
And yet, creating an absolute but
incomprehensible attraction.
In four years of high school, we
haven't said one word to each other.
At that moment on the plane,
I felt what you felt.
I didn't know where those
emotions were from...
until you started freaking out.
I didn't see what you
saw, but I felt it.
You can still feel
it, can't you?
Something from that day
is still with you.
I know because I can
still feel you.
That's why I was
there last night.
You know, I've never
dealt with death before.
This could all be in our head.
It just feels like
it's all around us.
It?
What if Tod was just the first?
Of us?
Is that something
that you're feeling?
I don't know, you know.
I just wish I could see him again.
One last time.
So maybe I would know.
Then let's go see him.
Easy.
Gives me a rush.
This place?
Doing something I'm
not supposed to.
Come on.
Hurry up.
- Is that him?
- I think.
Why did they make him up
like Michael Jackson?
Yeah, that's him.
But whatever it was that made
him Tod is definitely gone.
Christ.
Shh.
Please.
You'll wake the dead.
Why did his hand do that?
Chemicals in the vascular flush
create cadaveric spasms.
Look, um...
- I'm his friend and...
- I know who you are.
What are all those tiny marks?
Cuticle lacerations from
pulling at the wire.
Pulling at the wire?
If he was pulling at the wire, he
wasn't trying to kill himself.
- It was an accident.
- In death, there are no accidents.
No coincidences. No mishaps.
And no escapes.
What you have to realize is that we're all
just a mouse that a cat has by the tail.
Every single move we make, from
the mundane to the monumental...
the red light that
we stop at or run...
the people we have sex
with, or won't with us...
the airplanes that we
ride, or walk out of...
it's all part of death's sadistic
design leading to the grave.
Design?
Does that mean if you figure out
the design, you could cheat death?
Alex.
You've already done that
by walking off the plane.
Your friend's departure shows...
that death has a new
design for all of you.
Now, you have to figure out how
and when it's coming back at you.
Play your hunch, Alex.
If you think you can
get away with it.
But remember the risk
of cheating the plan...
of disrespecting the design
could incite a fury...
that could terrorize
even the Grim Reaper.
And you don't even wanna
fuck with that Mack Daddy.
Okay, then, well...
Yeah, I'm sorry we
broke in and...
No harm. No foul.
I'll see you soon.
The mortician said that
death has a design.
Okay.
I'm talking about omens.
How do we know that just by sitting
here, by sipping this coffee...
or breathing the air or
crossing the intersection...
that we haven't started in motion the
events that will lead to our death...
40 years from now, 10
years from now, tomorrow?
We don't unless we
open ourselves up...
to the signs it's
willing to show us.
I don't understand.
Did you see Tod die?
Did it happen again,
like on the plane?
No, no, it didn't, but I
mean, it might as well have.
This is a message of
something, Clear.
Or someone, hinting at a design.
Total bullshit. I mean, you can find
death omens anywhere you want to.
Coffee. Starts with a
C and ends with an E.
So does the word choke. So, what,
we're gonna choke to death?
I wanna hear you.
We'll go nuts if you
start with this shit.
The mortician said that
death has a design, right?
Now, what if you, me, Tod, Carter,
Terry, Billy, Miss Lewton...
messed up that design
for whatever reason?
I saw death's plan,
then we cheated it.
But what if it was our time?
What if we were not meant
to get off that plane?
What if it still is our time?
If it is, then
it's not finished.
And we will die now, not later.
Unless...
Unless we find the patterns
and cheat it again.
After hearing you,
I do believe...
that Tod killed himself.
Yeah, I'm fine. Whatever.
- You all right, man?
- Hey, baby, come on, not now.
- Carter.
- Oh.
It looks like we have a
bit of a reunion here.
- Let it go.
- When are you moving?
A couple weeks.
- That's too bad.
- You dick.
- We're losing our favorite teacher.
- Baby, come on.
Look, guys. There's something
I need to tell you, okay?
- Alex.
- And you lived here your whole life? Yeah.
And now she's gotta move
all because of Browning.
Enough, both of you.
They died and we lived.
Get over it.
I will not let this plane crash be
the most important thing in my life.
I'm moving on, Carter.
And if you wanna
waste your life...
beating the shit out of Alex
every time you see him...
then you can just
drop fucking dead.
- Okay.
- You look like a smart shopper.
Well, thank you.
Let's just say you were to see this
knife set in e department store.
What do you think
you'd have to pay?
Wow, that's a huge knife
set, but how many...?
- Hello?
- Is Alex there?
Oh, hi, Clear. Yeah,
just a minute.
It's Clear again. You
wanna talk to her?
The economy kept trading volume
below average today, and stocks...
Clear, he's in the shower.
- Can I get him to call you back?
- Sure, bye.
She's concerned about you.
I'm concerned about you.
Why won't you talk to her?
Or me?
Which could put a cloud
over both stocks and bonds.
Dad, you and Mom have
both been a big help.
But there's something I need to
understand before I can talk to anyone.
The Dow down 75.
The National Transportation Safety
Board has a new theory tonight...
on the possible cause of the
explosion of Volée Air Flight 180.
Officials believe deterioration
of silicon insulation...
on an electrical connector
to the scavenger pump...
may have leaked
combustible fluids.
- A spark in the fuel switch...
- That's Tod's seat.
In the fuselage may have ignited the fuel
line and proceeded to the fuel pump...
which would have set off the
catastrophic explosion.
The path of the explosion.
Okay, the first was Tod.
Then it was Terry.
They're dying in the order
they would have died.
That's death's design.
Miss Lewton's next.
And whenever I can
fall asleep, I just...
I see Terry Chaney.
And in the day,
out of nowhere...
I hear the sound of my
own voice in my head...
saying to Larry Murnau:
"No, you know the whole French thing.
Get on the plane."
Everything reminds
me of that day.
Right, yeah.
I'm hoping a change will help.
It's just that I've lived
here my whole life, you know?
And everywhere I looked
were great memories.
And now all I see is Larry...
and those kids, you know?
Just looking out my own front yard
makes me feel nothing but fear.
Laura, I'm gonna have
to call you back.
Right.
Hi, this is Valerie Lewton.
I need Agent Schreck.
What are you doing here?
I was just...
I was checking the air in the
tire to make sure it's safe.
Get in the car.
Put on your seat belt.
I believe that Miss
Lewton is next.
- Next?
- Yes.
Yeah, next, because there's
this pattern that's occurring.
Oh, right, a pattern, yeah.
You noticed that too, huh?
Mom's favorite.
So, what about this
pattern, Alex?
Did you see it in another
one of your visions?
Did you catch it
in some TV static?
You know, I never asked for
what happened on the plane.
You guys are gonna sit on your little chairs
and make fun of me. Whatever, it's fine.
But I saved six lives
on that plane.
Six lives, and everybody in my
entire school thinks I'm a freak.
And I'm not... I'm not suffering
from post-traumatic stress.
I don't have a narcissistic
deity complex.
I'm not going
Dahmer on you guys.
This just is.
There is a pattern for us all.
There's a pattern for you,
there is a pattern for you.
There's a design for everyone.
I don't know how yet.
But I'm gonna break this one.
Alex, you came to our
attention at first...
because you were under suspicion
in this plane explosion.
Now, I know you didn't
blow up the plane.
And we were ready to move on, but then
the other survivors started to die.
First, your friend Tod.
Then Terry Chaney, while you
were there at the scene.
And now tonight we pick you
up at Val Lewton's house.
Alex, nobody has control
over life and death.
Unless they are taking
lives and causing death.
Now, can you promise me that
no one else is going to die?
No, I can't.
As long as I'm in here, it's
out of my control, I'm sorry.
Okay, go ahead. Get out of here.
Thank you.
That kid gives me the creeps.
What are we gonna do?
We got nothing to hold him.
That's not what I'm
talking about.
There were a couple
of moments there...
where I almost believed him.
Can I tell you something? Don't
take this the wrong way.
But sometimes, you
give me the creeps.
You've gotta stop this. Stop
this, it's a stupid mug.
You're out of here. Pretty
soon, you'll be gone.
You'll be gone.
Miss Lewton.
Okay, all right, okay.
Just stay still, okay?
Oh, God. Ch, God. Miss Lewton.
Hey, Alex.
Dude.
I don't know where he is.
- He's not talking to me.
- Why?
Because I didn't believe him.
If he does contact you...
I think it would be in the best interest
of your safety if you called us.
Now, here's my card.
Toll-free number.
Interesting work.
Carter, you dick.
What are you doing?
Terry's name should
be on this wall.
Shit.
Why'd you want us to meet
you here anyway, huh?
Because they're watching
me, see if I go to Alex.
That's why you're taking me.
Why would I wanna see him?
Because he knows which
one of us is next.
So drive the speed limit, okay?
Oh, and don't pass on the right.
Billy, wait a minute here.
I'm getting a vision.
You're the next one, man.
Hey, man, why'd you say that?
Because if you say another word,
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
He could be anywhere from
here to a mile down.
So you guys drive down there,
we'll meet around the middle.
It'll take half the time.
Do you think they're
still up there?
Somehow, Flight 180, are
they still in flight?
Somewhere, are they safe?
When I was a kid, like 6 or 7...
I used to worry so much
about my parents dying.
Lying awake at night
just worrying.
Yeah, well, most
kids do, I guess.
Most kids never have it happen.
When I was 10, my dad went into
a 7-Eleven for cigarettes.
I guess that he heard someone
say, "Don't turn around."
So on reflex, or thinking it
was a friend joking, he did.
And the guy blew his head off.
Life became shit after that.
My mom just couldn't
deal anymore.
She married this asshole...
who my mom with my real dad would have
crossed the street to avoid this guy.
He really didn't want a kid.
So my mom didn't either anymore.
If that was the design for
my father and my family...
then fuck death.
God, I have thought a lot
about that somewhere, Alex.
It exists, that place. Where
my dad is still safe.
Where he had a full pack of cigarettes
that night and just kept driving.
Where me and my mom and my
dad are still together...
and have no idea about
this life here.
Where our friends are
still in the sky.
Where everyone gets
a second chance.
Alex, we can't give up.
Look, I can't go home.
All right? After Miss Lewton,
they're gonna be looking for me.
No, we're taking you
to my dad's cabin.
It's only a couple
miles from my house.
All right, Browning,
you fucking Warlock.
- Did you know about Miss Lewton, or what?
- Why do you think I was hiding?
Billy told the FBI he saw
you running from her house.
I was running because
they blame me.
They blame me for Tod, they blame
me for her, for the plane crash.
The fire, like, caramelized her blood,
Alex. Your shoe prints were in it.
- Your fingerprints were on the knives.
- I told you they were not...
I'm not talking about whether or not you
did it. Or even if you knew she was dead.
Did you know she was gonna
be next before she was?
Yeah, I did.
- I knew.
- All right.
Out of us, who's next to see it?
Please, tell me I'm gonna get to
see the Jets win a Super Bowl.
It's me, right? That's
why you're not saying.
I knew I should have felt up
Tammy in the pool that time.
- What are you whining about? I'm next.
- He didn't say anything. Just drive.
You have a responsibility
to tell me.
Do you think it's gonna make
it easier to know, Carter?
Huh? It's not, it's gonna
make it fucking harder.
You know, you get off
having control over me.
- You let me decide how to deal with it.
- It doesn't matter who's next.
Because we're all on the same list.
All of us.
Oh, fuck. Really?
All right, then why bother?
What's the fucking point, right?
Me and Terry, we'll be back together on
the other side, so why wait any longer?
Carter, what are you doing?
Carter, slow down.
- Slow down, Carter!
- Fuck you.
- Knock it off.
- May as well go out on my own free will.
Not with us in the fucking car.
- Jesus, Carter, no.
- Stop it.
Carter, stop the car.
Hey, what's the worry
if it ain't your time?
I could get nailed and you all
wouldn't give a shit, right?
- It's only me.
- It doesn't work that way, Carter.
And I fucking hated
French class.
- Control yourself.
- That's what I'm doing.
I know what you're doing. And
it's all right to be scared.
I'm not afraid, all right?
I decide when it's time.
I control my life, I
control my death.
You don't have to prove to us how
big your balls are. Not now.
- Carter, stop driving like such an asshole.
- What are you doing?
Fuck it, Carter, Jesus Christ. Carter,
put your hands back on the wheel.
- Carter, stop.
- Hands on the wheel, Carter.
Oh, shit.
Okay, Carter, easy.
I am so close to puking right
now, you don't even wanna know.
We're afraid too, Carter, but
we're not going to quit.
Stop what you're doing and
stop this fucking car.
Damn it, Carter.
I want you to stop this car right now.
- Billy.
- Move it.
- Hey, open the door, Billy.
- Move the fucking car!
- Hey, open the fucking door.
- Move the car.
Open it.
- Open the door.
- Easy, easy, open the door.
- Billy, open the fucking door!
- Billy, open it!
- Open the door!
Open the door!
Carter, listen to me.
Don't do this.
Goddamn it! Get out
of the fucking car.
Carter, listen to me.
Hey, listen to me.
This isn't the way.
It's not the way.
Get out of the car.
- Come on!
- It's coming, it's coming!
- Carter.
- It ain't my time.
Oh, shit.
Carter, listen to me. This isn't the way.
Get out of the car, Carter.
Carter, get out of the car.
Come on, get out!
I can't get out!
Alex! No!
Man, he really is next.
- Get out!
- Come on!
- Fuck!
Oh, God.
I saw it. I saw the belt.
- Scared now?
- It broke.
Bullshit. He saved
your life again.
That's right.
You're next, Carter. I'm staying
the fuck away from you.
- Shut up.
- We don't need this shit right now.
I don't need it ever. What are you doing?
Get away from him, he's next.
Hey, fuck you, Billy.
I'm not dead.
Oh, you will be. You're
dead, you're dead.
And you ain't
taking me with you!
Oh, shit. Ch, shit.
Jesus fucking Christ!
You should've been next. You
should've been next after Lewton.
That's the plan.
That's the design.
- You should be dead.
- You're the fucking devil.
I saw the seat belt.
I knew it would rip.
That's how I saved him.
Just like the plane.
Just like the
explosion, I saw it.
- The police are coming.
- Fuck, I saved him.
Because I saved him...
it skipped Carter, went to the next
in the path of the explosion, Billy.
I have to see it.
And if I see it, then I intervene. And
if I intervene, I cheat the design.
What, intervene? What
are you, God now?
Gods aren't afraid to die.
Gods don't die. We do.
- You know?
- Baby, you're losing it, okay?
The police will be here.
We have to get you to my cabin.
You can hide, and get
your head together.
Okay, after Billy, I'm next.
I'm next.
- And then me.
- Hey, hey, hey, listen.
I'm not gonna let
it happen, okay?
- Listen to me, all right?
- Hey, hey, hey.
Why don't you two just get
the fuck out of here?
Rusted.
Tetanus.
Nice one.
I overlooked it.
You tried to capitalize. But
I caught you, you fuck.
I can beat you.
Yeah, I mean, not forever, but I got
this cabin rigged to beat you now!
- She was there a minute ago.
- What are you talking about?
I'm not turning him in.
It's too dangerous for
him out there alone.
- I go with you.
- You can't.
Clear, you just tell
us where he is.
Wait at home, I
give you my word...
that we will bring him in
safely in protective custody.
I never moved.
Christa asked me to change
seats but I never moved.
I would've been up next to Tod.
Fuck, why didn't
I remember that?
I never moved. Clear's
seat was in front of mine.
She's next.
Alex!
Come on, get in the car. We're
going around. Get in the car.
Come on!
- Go!
- Move!
Oh, shit.
- There!
- Come on, let's go, over here.
Alex!
Alex, we're trying to help you.
Fritz, get away from it.
Come on.
Alex!
Run!
We lost him.
From the direction, there's
only one place he's heading.
No shit.
Clear!
No.
Oh, my God.
Don't move. Stay there.
Don't move, don't move.
Don't touch anything.
You're grounded by
the tires, okay?
The car's gonna explode.
I can only hold on for so
long, you know what to do.
Don't!
When I do this, it'll skip
you, and it'll be over.
- It's the only way we can cheat death again.
- No, don't!
Clear, I am not gonna let it beat us both.
You know what to do.
I'll always be with you.
NO!
Alex!
Alex, get away from there.
NO!
Alex. Alex.
Damn it, you can't
do this to me.
Come on, baby. Come on.
Alex, Alex?
Alex, Alex? Oh, shit,
he's not breathing.
Hold on, Alex. Come
on, stay with me.
- Well, we made it.
- Paris, I can't believe it.
I just can't believe we
got on a plane again.
You know what I'm saying?
Wow.
It's weird being here, huh?
We finally completed a puzzle.
It's just there's something
missing, you know?
- To Terry.
- Yeah.
- To Tod.
- To all of our friends that can't be here.
- Cheers.
What?
If you would have told
me six months ago...
that the three of us would be
sitting here having a drink...
- Yeah.
- I don't know.
I mean, sometimes it just
feels like the two of you...
are the only ones who
can really understand.
You were right, Browning. It did skip us.
There was a design.
We beat it. You know, we won.
I think the only thing we won,
Carter, is a chance at a full life.
A chance that I
won't ever waste.
Yeah, there's just something...
You know, something
I can't figure out.
- What?
- About the design.
Alex, just let it go. All right?
"I swear" Just hear
me out, all right?
- Oh, my God.
- It's just... Listen.
Now, the path of the explosion determined
the order of our deaths, right?
When I intervened
and saved Carter...
it skipped him and went to the next
person in the path. It went to Billy.
All right, and
then it was Clear.
But I intervened and saved her, so
it went to me, but in my case...
no one intervened, right?
I was thrown from that power
line by the explosion.
- So...
- So why did it skip you, right?
How do we know that this isn't
exactly what was meant to happen?
That out of everyone on Flight 180,
you, me and Carter were meant to live.
Maybe that was the
design all along.
- Or you could still be next.
- Shut up, Carter.
What? I didn't
make up the rules.
Somebody's gotta intervene
before death can skip them.
Alex proved that three times.
In the plane, with me, you.
For all I know, it could circle
back and get us all again.
But I am the safest fucker in the
world because you're still next.
Can we just stop
talking about this?
Let's figure out what
we're gonna do tomorrow.
I'm gonna meet you
back at the hotel.
- Just wait, I'll go with you.
- No, just stay here.
Okay, Clear?
Just stay here.
All right?
See, it's true.
I told you you were next, man.
Stop it, Carter.
- Alex, wait.
- No, Clear, stay there.
Okay?
Stay away.
Alex!
I told you, you were next.
- Then it just skipped me.
- So who's next?