Aah!
- Whoo!
- Ha ha ha!
Aah!
Oh, man!
- Did you see that?
- Woo!
Oh, my God. Ha ha!
- Yes! Yes!
- Nice, nice, nice.
- Aw, sick!
- Worth the wait.
Oh, babe. You missed out.
Yes!
I want to get off.
Whoo! Ow!
Ha ha ha!
That was intense, man.
To feel how that would be
to just crash and burn like that.
Yeah, yeah. Maybe for you...
but our lives are
actually goin' somewhere.
Oh! OK, well, where we gotta go
is to the roller coaster.
'Cause our pass is for 9:15.
If we miss that,
we'll stand in line...
for, like, a day and a half
and that's gonna kill me.
- OK!
- All right? So let's go.
They're totally
gonna dig this, man!
OK. Come on, it won't kill us...
to get a deep-fried
Snickers and a Coke.
Before ridin' Devil's Flight?
Yeah, that might kill me.
No! What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger, man.
Ha ha ha!
- Unh!
- Ha ha!
Oh, I'll take that.
No. Come on, gimme.
It's not even mine, Kevin.
It's the yearbook's.
Just... Kevin.
Ha ha!
- Oh!
- Oh, got it.
Oh, my God,
you're such an idiot.
Hey. Hey. Gimme the...
Ha ha!
- Ow!
- Nice.
Um, could you, like, please
delete that one of Stacy?
Ha ha!
These are
for the yearbook.
And I have to
turn them in tomorrow...
to make a deadline
and, like, I doubt it...
if a shot of Stacy
Kobayashi's camel toe...
is gonna make it in there.
Whew. I'd buy 2.
Ha ha ha!
Number 38, your order's ready.
That's us.
I am so sorry.
Kevin can get so out of control.
Let me just say
he would make me crazy.
Ha! I mean, you know
I'm such a control freak...
like I couldn't handle that.
I'm breaking up with him.
Couple of weeks.
After graduation.
I've been wanting to for a while.
But don't tell anybody, OK?
Whoa. Ha ha!
Now, that shot there?
That'll sell some yearbooks.
I love it. I love it.
Oh! Oh, all right,
so I'm a total whore.
Come on, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go!
Oh, my God, Ashley,
you're winning.
You're totally winning.
Am I winning?
Yeah, come on, hurry!
OK, come on, come on,
come on, come on!
Am I winning? Look around,
I don't want to look.
You're totally winning.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on!
Don't look!
Oh, my God! Come on!
Oh, my God!
I'm winning!
Aah!
- I won!
- I knew you would.
Oh, my God!
Gimme my prize.
Good job.
That was
so awesome, Ashley.
Ashley.
Woo! Ha ha!
How ya doin', my brother?
You havin' a good time, huh?
- You like that?
- Ha ha!
Yeah! You like it.
Give it up. Give it up.
Whoo-ooh!
Damn!
Excuse me.
You're not a senior.
And what are you
gonna do about it...
Miss "Cutest Couple",
rah rah? Ha ha!
Mom know you're here?
You are a complete bitch
if you tell her.
Proof where you were.
Take a shot of this.
Ha ha ha!
Yeah! That's what
I'm talking about.
That's three.
* That is three, number three *
* Oh I'm the man, I'm the man *
Man, I am hot.
Man, gimme some right here, man.
Right here, right here.
What you doin'?
Get the fuck back. Hoo!
My God, I am good. Here we go.
Boy, I'll tell ya...
Goddamn. Whoo!
Kind sir,
step right up!
There ya go. Whaddaya want?
Here we go, baby.
3 for 3. It's all mine.
Here we go. Here we go.
Big prize. Watch out. Come on.
Unh!
Ho ho ho!
* That's what I'm talkin' 'bout *
We gonna get that one.
You want that blue one?
That's the one we gonna get.
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
You can run,
but you cannot hide.
- Yes!
- Whoo!
Here we are, baby.
- Yes!
- Whoo! There it is.
Awesome.
Here, get a pic of this. Ahhh!
This is the beginning of the end.
Ha ha ha!
Hey, guys, get in line.
Let's go on again!
What's wrong?
I'm...
I was having that feeling
like déjà vu, you know?
Except for something
that hasn't happened yet.
Hey, J.
Come on, man, let's go.
- Yeah, yeah, hold on.
- Come on.
What, are you
weirded out by the ride?
'Cause, look, I know you.
And I think that maybe...
you're nervous about
this roller coaster...
because they say the real
fear with these rides...
comes from the feeling
of having no control.
Everyone imagines weird stuff
when they get scared.
But it never turns out
to be what they imagine.
Never.
OK.
You can run,
but you cannot hide.
Oh! Where you guys
are right now...
if you raise
your hands and just...
Ha! Cup them slightly...
it'll look you're holding
the devil's balls.
And we'd wanna do that why?
When else you ever gonna
see a dick that big?
I'm lookin' at one right now.
Ha ha! Man,
you guys are smokin' hot.
Get out, Frankie.
Yeah, why are you even here?
Yeah, you graduated,
like, two years ago.
I stuck around to monitor
your development.
Yeah. Good to go.
Good to go, baby.
- Let's do it. Let's do it.
- Come on. Come on.
You may never return
from Devil's Flight.
Ha ha ha ha!
You're totally sad.
Try not to scream!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
That was totally awesome!
Yeah! Sweet!
You all right?
There's nothing to worry about.
A roller coaster is
just elemental physics.
A conversion of potential
energy to kinetic energy.
Yeah. Odds are like
one in 250 million...
of dying in a roller coaster.
Yeah, yeah, thanks
for that, McKinley.
You're more likely to die
driving to an amusement park...
than dying at one.
Whoo!
Here we go.
You like this?
Won it on the wacky ladder.
You know that ladder deal
that wobbles? Took it.
I like this. It's old school...
Frankie Cheeks
is old school, ladies.
What's that?
Oh, well, it'd be my honour.
Ew.
Oh! Let's go.
Hey... Baby.
- How many?
- Uh, 4.
- 4.
- Yeah.
Uh, gate one.
- Yeah. Front car.
- Yes!
Wait... no. No, please.
I'm sorry, I don't
wanna be a hassle...
I just... I can't sit in the front.
I cannot see the tracks.
I'll freak.
OK. Take it easy.
Uh, well, Carrie will sit...
in the back with you.
Right, babe?
Uh! Why me?
What? 'Cause we're girls?
Fuck that.
I'm going to Berkeley...
and I won't get to do
this for a while.
I'm sitting in the front.
J, just go, OK? I'll live.
You're not gonna
sit by yourself.
All right, you know what?
We'll just settle
this like real men,
How about that? Hmm? Call it.
Heads.
Shit! Damn it.
All right, fine, what the fuck.
It's the same ride, right?
Go. Go ahead. Bye, babe.
Hey, uh, just do me a favour.
Keep an eye on her, OK?
She's kinda freaked out.
- Oh. Cool.
- All right?
Yeah. Boom, buddy.
No problem.
Aaah!
Here we go. Hey!
J! Keep your hands
to yourself, man.
I'm serious. You know,
payback's a bitch, OK?
You know, she might
need some comforting...
and I'll be there for her. OK?
Hey, no! No. Get out. Get out.
Hey! Find another
cockpit, Top Gun.
No. Get...
Let's just get in the back, OK?
Ha ha ha!
Ahem.
Guess who's back?
- Ugh.
Hey!
I'll meet you at the end.
Here! All right!
Cool!
Hey. How'd you guys
get in here?
What? I'm 55 inches.
Sure. Come on out. Oh, man.
You too. Out.
- Ready?
- Ohh!
I told you we wouldn't
get away with it.
You OK?
Let's go on
the bumper cars.
Come on. Here we go.
Yeah!
What's up, man? I'm good.
Dare you to, uh, flash me
them sweet, sweet titties...
when we go through the loop.
- All right.
- Ha ha!
Yo! What, you can't read?
Oh. Well, can I just put it
in my pocket, man?
- Is that cool?
- Yeah.
Yeah? Cool.
Thanks, buddy. Sorry.
Oh!
Aw, shit!
Here you go!
Whoo! Win, baby!
Yes, baby! Win!
Come on!
Come on. Get hyped.
The first hill's so high.
Yeah.
This is what we need!
- Yeah!
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
- Let's do this!
- Just win!
Ow!
Whoo!
Aw, yeah!
Whoo! Shit!
Ha ha!
Aah!
Oh, man.
Oh, my God!
Here we go!
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Aah!
Yeah! Whoo!
Ha ha!
- Aah! Aah!
- Ha ha ha!
Whoo!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Ha ha ha! Whoo!
Aah! Aah!
Whoo!
Yeah! Show me your titties!
- Fuck off, Frankie!
- Oh!
Aah!
Unh!
Oh, shit!
- Aah!
Aah!
Oh, my God!
We're gonna fall off!
Aah!
No!
Oh! Oh!
Shit!
Unh!
Oh!
- Yow!
- Kevin!
No!
Aah!
No! Aah!
Erin, hang on!
Erin!
- Hang on!
- Don't let go!
I can't.
Aah!
No!
Oh, God!
Hang on, Wen.
Hang on! Help me rock it!
Unh!
Almost got it! Gently.
Aaaah!
No!
Unh! Aah!
Aah!
Yo. What, you can't read?
Oh, well. I'll just...
I'll put it in my pocket, OK?
Thanks, bro.
All right.
Let's do this, Wen...
- Oh!
- What're you...?
Here you go!
Yeah! Let's do it, baby! Whoo!
We have to get off of here.
No, don't push the button!
Don't! Don't push the button!
Unh! Let me off! Let me off!
Wen, Wen! It's all right.
Jesus, it's gonna be over...
No! It's gonna crash!
It's gonna crash!
Wendy?
The hydraulics will rupture!
The tracks'll collapse! Please!
- What's going on?
- Let me off!
Chick's on somethin'.
It's all right!
You'll be OK!
OK let 'em out. Just the back.
Wen. Hey! Wendy!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Relax. Now, what's the matter?
I saw it. I saw it in my head.
The tracks collapsed.
The roller coaster crashed.
No, she was just
a little upset before.
Man, please, can you
please control that bitch?
Damn. "It's gonna crash!
The hydraulics, the coaster!"
Man, she's just trying to
get some fuckin' attention.
Know what? You're a real
piece of shit, Lewis.
- Fuck you.
- Fuck moi?
- No, man, fuck you!
- Don't touch me.
Ow!
Hey, hey!
Unh!
Just relax!
Fight, man!
Hey. Hey. Let me out.
Nobody else gets off this ride!
Dude, let me off.
So high school.
Let's out.
- Calm down!
- Get off of him!
- Relax!
- Lan!
Where you ladies going?
There's a fight.
Get him out of here!
Hey! Calm down! Relax!
Dude, let me off.
I gotta make sure she's OK.
- Relax! Calm down!
- Hey! Ho!
Get outta here! Go!
Get your big ass off me, man!
* Hey, ho, let's go! *
Let me out!
* Hey, ho, let's go!
Hey, ho, let's go! *
Dude!
* Hey, ho, let's go!
Hey, ho, let's go! *
- Here we go!
- Let me off!
* Hey, ho *
Dude, that's my girlfriend!
Oh, my God!
Stop it! No! Stop it!
Stop it! Please!
Please, the tracks are broken.
Stop! Stop! Please!
Jason!
Hey, just relax, OK?
- Please!
- Ease up, man.
She's all right. OK?
Just let her
settle down.
She can settle down
at home! Now listen...
what is your
home phone number?
OK, we're gonna
call your mother, OK?
Everything will be
taken care of...
Oh, my God! Jason!
Hey, Wendy!
Hey!
Wait! Wendy!
Hey! Hey, Wen. Wait.
I need... I need to talk
to you about something.
Just here to pick up my diploma.
You're not going to graduation?
No.
Look, you're not the only one...
in a fucked up place, OK?
God, I mean,
I just thought maybe...
it'd be good for you
to be somewhere...
where other people
feel the same way.
At graduation?
No. Thanks. I've had
enough funerals.
Then do it for J and Carrie.
Do what? If you die and
then there's nothing...
then they're just dead
and they don't know.
And if they are up in heaven
with Lincoln and Gandhi...
do you think
they really care about...
our high-school graduation? No.
I am alive and I don't care.
As soon as I pull out
of that parking lot...
I am so out of McKinley.
Without J, what's here for me?
I'm here. OK?
I made a promise to J...
that I would take care of you.
On the ride. For 3 minutes.
You weren't making
the promise for a lifetime.
Kevin...
if it wasn't for
you and j being friends...
and me and Carrie
being friends...
we wouldn't have
even hung out.
We don't even like each other.
"Lan McKinley."
How pathetic
is it that my last name...
is the same
as my high school?
Julie, look who I got
to sign my yearbook.
- No way. Nice.
- Yeah.
I think we should invite her.
- You think?
- Yeah.
Wen? Um...
So we're ready for
graduation tonight...
we're going to the tanning
salon after this...
and we are so totally cool
if you wanna come with.
Totally.
And just like, talk if you want.
Here's my cell.
I already have your number.
That was so nice of us.
You're not alone.
God, I appreciate
everyone trying to help.
OK? I really do.
No, it's happened before.
OK? I went online looking
for an explanation about...
Wendy, just... just
listen to me, all right?
All right, look, I went online...
Iooking for an explanation...
about what happened,
and I found out...
about this high-school
French class...
from New York.
6 years ago they went
on a trip to Paris.
When they were boarding,
a kid had a vision...
that the plane
was gonna explode.
Just like you did.
He freaked out...
and 7 people got off the plane.
Just like us.
And on takeoff,
Flight 180 blew up.
And over the next
several months...
everyone who got off
that plane...
started dying
in weird accidents.
They died in the order
they would've...
if they'd have stayed
on the plane.
Unless someone intervened,
then it skipped them.
Fuck you, Kevin.
W-Wendy! Wendy! Hey!
Ohh, every time we come here.
I was thinking of going...
for 20 minutes in the Müller.
We did that for
all the funerals...
and it turned out amazing.
Yeah, but that was just
a couple of weeks ago, though.
I mean, we're still
pretty bronzed.
I was just thinking we could
go for, like, a tune-up.
I just wanna make sure
that we look our best.
Yeah.
You know, for all those kids
that died that night...
who will never get a graduation.
You know what?
You're totally right.
- I'm sorry.
- Mmm.
This is my...
my good guy luck bracelet...
that Grandma left me
in her will.
Ohh!
Julie?
I need...
I could use some help.
I have such...
Such guilt over Jason.
I should never have
let that ride go.
God. I'm usually
such a control freak...
but I didn't do
enough to stop it.
I should've done
everything I could...
to stop it.
And I would give anything...
to have a second chance.
But I never can.
I don't want to someday...
feel that way about you, Julie.
I mean, I can't talk
to Mom and Dad.
You're all I have left.
You think when I find a place...
maybe you could come stay
with me for a while?
You know I will.
You...
keep this now...
and I'll get it
when I come see you.
Oh. And... hey,
how 'bout on your end?
Can I use the school camera
for graduation tonight?
Yeah. As long as you bring it
back to school on Monday.
Done.
Oh. Um...
actually, the battery
is pretty low...
so why don't you go get ready
and I'll recharge it a bit.
Cool.
In a hurry, Yuri.
Sorry, sorry. Cellphone
signal is shit in here.
I think tanning beds
mess with signal.
I must go outside.
Why don't you just
use that phone?
I would, but
she talks forever...
then my boss
gives me shit.
Shit. That's her.
Ohh!
You know what?
Just go outside.
We can deal with this ourselves.
OK.
Hey. No drinks in
the room this time, OK?
Good.
What are you doing?
Nobody is walking in here
and seein' me naked.
Oh, my God.
Dude, he said no drinks.
If you spill that shit...
we're gonna have to
clean it up like last time.
Mmm!
Happy, biyatch?
Nothing to spill.
Why does Yuri keep it
so cold in here?
Maybe it's supposed
to be colder...
for the machines or whatever.
Oh, a few degrees won't hurt.
Shit! I forgot my iPod.
Sucks, bitch.
They got CDs.
Ew. Céline?
Britney?
Dude, are we like
the only cool people...
that come here or what?
Uh, yeah.
Ugh. Whatever.
Why are you
wearing underwear?
Steinmetz says he gets
off on tan lines.
All right.
* Roller coaster *
* Of love *
* Say what? *
* Roller coaster *
* Ooh ooh ooh ooh *
* Right *
* Of love *
* Roller coaster *
* Ooh ooh ooh ooh *
* Roller coaster of love *
* Roller coaster *
* Wow wow wow *
* Ooh ooh ooh ooh *
* Roller coaster of love... *
* I *
* Huh, huh *
* I'm gonna ride, girl *
* Yeah *
* Wow, yeah *
* Huh huh *
* Ow *
* Oh, oh *
Whoo.
* Roller coaster of love *
* Love roller coaster, girl *
* Roller coaster *
* Lovin' you is
a freak-out world, child *
* Roller coaster of love *
Camera charged?
Oh, um, sorry,
the battery's totally dead.
Camera's not working. Sorry.
Look, Julie,
I need a minute, OK?
Like private.
* That feels nice,
roller coaster *
* One more time *
* Roller coaster of love *
* Roller coaster *
Ugh.
It's way too warm
in here now, huh?
I fucked up.
I set it too hot in here.
Huh?
Ow! Aah!
Hello?
Hey, Ashley, it's Wendy...
Psych!
Leave a message.
Hi, Ashley, this is Wendy.
Gimme a call whenever
you guys are done...
Aah!
And thanks again for the invite.
- Someone help!
- Aah!
Sorry I was too late.
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Oh! Oh!
Oh! Aah!
Aaah! Aaah!
Hey, open the door!
Help me!
Aah!
- Aah!
We may feel that
our lives are not our own.
That death controls,
frames our lives.
Our births nothing
but death begun.
Yet, whether it is
with this tragic loss...
of young lives...
which we have
suffered much of late...
or with the soft passing
of the elderly in the night...
we are all equal
in death's eyes.
"Equal in death's eyes?"
All of us?
How can you say that?
Shut up, McKinley.
Dude, think it through.
Charlie Manson made it to 70.
- Osama? Still kickin'.
- Let's go.
Pimps, vice presidents
walking around.
Let's just go. Come on.
All the atrocities
they've committed...
they're alive and well.
These two girls, who've never
done shit to anybody...
Shh!
They don't get to make it to 18?
Where's the fucking
equality in that?
- What?
- Come on, man.
I can... Yeah. Fine.
Fine. All right.
All right.
I'm fine. All right.
That's crazy.
Those of you who would like
to pay a final remembrance...
please step forward
at this time.
I so feel this is so my fault.
How could it possibly
be your fault?
Seein' women as
nothin' but fun bags.
I mean...
If I'd've seen their...
whatever... humanity...
they wouldn't have felt
the pressure to look so good.
Impress Franklin Cheeks.
Go on diets. Deodorise.
Stretch. Tan.
Don't be down, Frankie.
Be proud of your ability
to make everything...
that happens somehow
a story about you.
God!
Yo, man. These things
really suck, man.
Fucking boring.
Hey, if you ever have
to come to my funeral...
man, bring me
a PSP or somethin'.
'Least I have
somethin' to do then.
Hello?
I'm with J.
What are you doing up
here in the nosebleeds?
You know, I could've
gotten you second row.
I didn't want to upset
anyone by being there.
And I wondered if maybe
here I could feel J's...
spirit or presence or...
whatever.
But now that I'm here...
if there's any place
that makes me feel...
like there's
no life after death...
it's a cemetery.
Yeah, I haven't felt
Carrie's spirit either.
And I've tried.
Real hard. Heh.
I thought maybe
he's been with me since...
That night... before
I got on the ride...
Jason said...
God, and it was just
to get me on the ride...
he said...
"Your fear is from a sense
of having no control."
And I've felt that fear
since the moment he said it.
Even thought it maybe somehow
caused the hallucination...
but this fear is more
than just being scared.
It's like a presence.
Like a living thing
always with me.
You think it's J?
No, I know it's not.
This presence is the opposite
of how J made me feel.
It's cold and terrifying.
That's the last photograph
Lincoln posed for.
The photographic plate
was broken...
causing a line
that can't be removed.
Exactly where he was shot.
Look.
See the shadow?
But what do these pictures
have to do with us?
Look. This occurred
one year to the day...
of the Flight 180 disaster.
Look at the road sign.
Look, I guess you came
to me with this...
because I'm responsible for
putting this in your head...
with the Flight 180 thing.
And it did happen,
and it may be occurring here...
but you can't believe
every weird thing out there...
because you're desperate
for an answer.
I took these.
That night.
These?
Are these it?
Oh, shit.
Whoa, whoa, hey.
You all right?
I'm feeling a little woozy.
When was
the last time you ate?
I don't remember.
All right,
come on. I'll drive.
OK, those kids on
Flight 180 died in accidents...
in the order
they would've died...
if they'd have
stayed on the plane.
OK? So if this is that, then...
then Frankie was behind
Ashlyn and Ashley.
When I saw Ashley
and Ashlyn's picture...
I felt this instinct.
Like there was a hint
in the picture. I even...
I even called to see if
I could keep them from going.
Well, what's Frankie's
picture look like?
It's right here.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
- Wait! Watch out!
- Oh!
Hey! Hey! Are you crazy?
Sorry!
All right,
let's just eat over there.
And go through
the drive-thru.
I don't want anyone hearing
what we're talking about.
Well, it's nice to see that
things haven't made you...
any less of a control freak.
- You got it?
- Yeah, all right.
Here's Frank's picture.
All right.
Well, this is obvious.
He's falling off a ladder.
A rope ladder, though.
Maybe he might hang.
Look, or maybe
it's not that literal.
All right, what's...
Could there be anything
in these prizes?
Oh, what, like
he's gonna get crushed...
by a giant SpongeBob?
Hey, SpongeBob
lives underwater.
It's so sad that
you know that.
All right. He won that
tacky Mudflap Girl chain...
on this game, though, so...
Aren't those usually
on those big 18-wheelers?
Yeah. Yeah.
God, I don't see it in
this picture anywhere, though.
All right! God.
All right.
Uh, can I take
your order?
Yeah. What do you want?
Wen, you OK?
Please tell me there's
a short in your wiring.
Whoa. Whoa. That guy's
way too close to my truck.
Hey, you're too fucking
close, man! Pull up!
Hey!
* There is someone *
Stop! Stop!
* Walking behind you *
Watch out! Shit!
- What the fuck?
- * Turn around *
- Oh, my God!
- * Look at me *
Get out! Get out!
What? What?
Behind us!
There's no one in that truck!
* Watching your footsteps *
Shit! Hey! Pull up, man!
Come on! Pull up!
- * Look at me *
- Unh! Shit!
- * There is someone *
- Back up!
Back up!
* Who really loves you *
* Here's my heart *
Watch your eyes!
Watch your eyes! Come here!
* In my hand *
* Turn around *
- * Look at me *
- Come on. Let's go!
Come on, come on, come on.
Unh!
- Oh!
- Unh!
We're all done here.
You need a ride?
Um, we can walk
to my house...
and then I'll give you
a ride to yours.
No, thanks, we'll be OK.
Will we?
Yeah. We'll be all right.
I mean...
how Frank...
God, it... it's
not only horrible...
but can you feel...
can you feel
how vicious it was?
Easy.
OK? Easy.
Let's just...
let's just take a step back.
All right? He was behind
Ashley and Ashlyn on the ride...
but there was no ladder here.
You know, there was no rope.
Nothing in that picture
pointed to this.
We were wrong about the photos.
I should've left town.
It's better not knowing.
No, it's never better
staying ignorant.
Wilful ignorance is
surrendering control.
What, did you read
that somewhere...
in Mrs Brooks'
English class?
No. L... You know, I'm not...
I'm not the total idiot
you think I am.
OK, that's
Lewis after Frank...
then lan and Erin.
There's a couple of
kids behind them...
but I can't make them out
because this guy's arm's in the way.
Can you?
No.
All right,
you know what?
We'll ask Lewis, lan,
and Erin if they remember.
OK?
Are there any more pictures
from the roller coaster?
I guess...
that kind of thing
is gonna happen to us...
for the rest of our lives.
Yeah.
You know, I was gonna...
I was gonna ask her
to marry me.
Right after graduation.
Heh.
Oh.
No, wait.
Look, behind Stacy.
That's Frank.
This picture shows
how he died.
All right, go back to Lewis.
OK, he's got
that hammer.
And the weight looks like
it's coming down...
on his head.
No, no, no, but check this out.
Right now Lewis
is down at State...
for football training camp.
State's team is
called the Sultans.
That's it. That's the clue.
We have to tell him.
Show him these pictures.
Wouldn't you want to know?
Wait, there's pictures
of us in there?
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
Huh. No.
No. I don't want
to see mine. No. Huh.
What about wilful ignorance?
Well, I'm full of shit, all right?
I mean, I never thought
I could see my own death...
before it happened, Wendy.
No, you know what?
We can tell Lewis, but...
Seriously, if there's any way
to beat this thing...
I gotta stay focused...
and if I look at that picture
all I'm gonna do is obsess.
So, you know what?
No, I don't want to see it.
I mean, unless we have to.
You mean until we have to.
One more thing.
Is it bad?
I mean, is it, like,
painful or embarrassing?
I mean, there's nothing, like,
up my ass or anything, right?
I'll see you tomorrow.
You on crack. Both of you.
Just listen, OK?
Ashley and Ashlyn were first.
Then Frankie Cheeks
and then you. This is the...
- Aw, come on, Kevin.
- Listen.
McKinley and Erin
were next, all right?
And there were
2 people in front of us.
- Do you remember who they were?
- Fuck no, and I don't care.
And you shouldn't
care either, man...
'cause what you're
tellin' me right now...
is straight bullshit.
Just listen, Lewis.
Kevin,
it's like those stories...
like this guy was killed by
a car he sold 10 years ago.
2 sisters, right,
were killed when they were...
driving to visit each other.
You know, shit like that, man.
Fuck the Bruins!
- Oh, yeah!
- Fuck the Bruins!
Bruin faggots!
Yeah! Fuck the Bruins!
Man, you're reading
into this shit...
like them damn urban legends.
3 people have died, Lewis.
I mean, if you think
this can be written off...
as a simple coincidence
and it ends there...
you're in serious denial.
Unh! What about you two, huh?
What?
You both lost people
real close to you...
in a fucked-up way.
And in order to feel
less guilty or whatever...
seeing signs
and patterns, man.
I don't blame you.
But it's wrong, dawg.
Unh! It's wrong.
That's denial.
Unh!
- Unh!
- You got it!
OK, what about what happened
at the roller coaster? Huh?
- Wendy saw it.
- Man, she got a hunch.
Fuckin' intense,
but she got a hunch.
Man, I'm here because
I get good hunches...
before every down.
No, you know they're
either gonna run or pass.
Hers came to her
from nowhere.
You're here and alive
because of her.
No, I'm alive because of me.
No, listen.
You don't get it, man.
Does that
make sense to you?
There's nothing to get,
Kevin! It's bullshit.
No, just...
hear me out, all right?
* Yeah *
Talk about a vision.
Man, I seen
my whole life played out...
and it sure as hell
ain't gonna end now. Unh!
It's going just as I saw it.
35 high-school games
without an injury.
USA Today All-American.
Second team.
Free ride to play
for the Sultans!
The Bruins passed on you.
Man, fuck the Bruins!
- Fuck 'em!
- You goddamn right!
What the fuck
is a Bruin anyway?
Aah!
4 years from now...
Lewis Romero goin' in
the second round to Oakland.
He's gonna romp and stomp.
15 seasons, with 4 Super Bowl
rings on his fingers.
Lewis ain't afraid of
no death. Fuck death!
Death is a fuckin' Denver fan.
Death wear blue and orange.
Real men wear black.
Lewis ain't afraid of no death.
Death is afraid of me!
Death fears me!
Kevin.
'Cause, baby, I just win.
I just win, Kevin!
That's all I know how to do!
I just win! Unh!
Fuck death!
- Fuck the Bruins!
- Yeah!
Aah!
- Look out!
- Lewis!
Man, that was close, Lewis.
Hey, did you see that?
Whoo! What I tell you,
Kevin, huh?
Fuck death! I just win!
That's all I know
how to do, Kevin.
Baby, I just win!
Aaaaah!
- Ooooh!
- God!
Did I do something...
to bring this on everybody?
Don't, Wendy.
But why me?
All those people out there...
wanting to have
a premonition...
or see a ghost or
whatever and I don't.
I just want it to stop.
Just stop.
I don't know why, Wendy...
but you didn't do anything.
All right? This is just...
I don't know. I mean,
I wish I knew why, you know?
I wish I could... I could
come up with a guess even...
to make you feel OK, but...
You know, I can't.
Yeah.
There's nothing I can do.
Can you drive?
Yeah.
You know, by the way,
that... that picture of me.
My, uh...
My head's not, like,
through the windshield...
or anything?
You know, crushed by
a steering wheel?
Impaled by a gear shift?
Right?
Zip, it's Pip.
Have you cut
those plywood orders yet?
Uh, that's a big no, Pip.
Osama Bin Supervisor...
wants me to get rid
of these pigeons first.
They keep settin' off the alarms.
Hello, babies.
Ha ha ha!
Oh, ha ha ha! Heh.
Hey. After I, uh,
restock this stuff...
that these pinhead
customers can't manage...
to return to the shelves
themselves...
we can blow
out of here, OK?
Righty-o, babe.
Aah!
Erin, it's Wendy and Kevin.
Shit!
You scared
the shit out of me!
Yeah, wait till you hear
what we have to tell you.
Zip, it's Pip.
Come over here.
You are gonna trip
when you hear this.
Well, paint me intrigued,
Pip, I'm on my way.
So let me get this straight.
I'm gonna OD on nail polish...
and lan is gonna be
embarrassed to death?
You saw what happened
to Wendy, right?
What's happened to the others?
I mean, you just saw
their pictures.
Oh, my God, guys,
what's going on?
What's going on?
That's crazy! That's crazy!
Ha ha!
We need to know who
was sitting behind you...
on the roller coaster.
OK, who was sitting behind
us on the roller coaster?
Oh! Oh, wait! Wasn't it
that one guy who got voted...
most likely to become
manager at Red Lobster?
Oh, no. You know what?
God, I remember.
There was this guy,
uh, black cloak...
I didn't see his face,
but, um...
the ride attendant
did take his sickle...
before the ride started,
if that's helpful in any way.
Do you think we care
if you laugh at us?
This is our lives, OK?
What choice do we have?
Just give into it?
Oh, God. You know what?
There is no "it."
OK, wait, are you guys saying...
that death is, like, a person?
No. It's like... like a force.
Yeah. Well, you know what?
A force is just a force.
It's nothing else.
Just transferred energy.
I mean, it has no goals,
no awareness that is a force.
But there is
awareness, McKinley.
In fact, in past cases,
if the next in line is saved...
it'd skip that person.
That's why we're here.
Oh, man,
what have you been smoking?
Ha ha!
- Top shelf.
- OK.
Kevin! Those banners.
They're in the picture.
Lan, watch those boxes!
What the fuck, man?
You said those boxes were falling!
No, I said watch the boxes.
Really? What for?
They're not doing anything.
We're not gonna apologize
for trying to save you.
You haven't seen or been
through what we have... yet.
Oh. Yet.
OK, so who's next...
in this theory you have,
me or lan?
Well, we know the order...
of how we were sitting
on the roller coaster...
but not how it works with
people who sat together.
OK, we don't know if Ashley
or Ashlyn died first.
Hmm. Death is
fucking complicated.
Ha ha!
No, you know what?
It's not complicated.
It's simple. People die.
That's just part of life.
150,000 people
a day, actually.
You know? I mean...
we're biological entities,
and death is just...
Top shelf.
- The end of
biological function.
It's as simple as that.
How can you explain what
happened to us as simple?
I mean, if Wendy never
had that premonition...
and none of us
had gotten off that ride...
we'd all be dead right now.
Does that not
make sense to you?
Oh, yeah.
Kevin, how come when a guy
dies of a plain heart attack...
no one goes, like...
"Oh, wow, he was
eating French toast...
"when Princess Diana
died in Paris...
"and then he saw her funeral
on TV, and now he's dead"?
You know why? Because
they'd sound crazy...
so guess how you two
sound right now? Crazy.
Zip, I'm done.
So finish cutting...
those orders so
we can get out of here.
OK!
Unh!
Heh heh!
Ugh!
Sick.
Let's go with what
you guys are saying.
Let's just say, you know...
that death does have
a conscious plan...
and that it's been
set into motion. Great.
So, Newton's
third law of motion...
and, well, look...
I'm just guessing that
it goes for death too...
when he's working
in our world.
Newton says
that every action...
has an equal
and opposite reaction.
So, that means that...
if death has taken action,
so can we.
And that that action
we take might have...
an opposite reaction that
thwarts death's intent.
You're being a fucker,
but go on.
OK. OK.
What if, for example...
the last in line...
were to make
the utilitarian choice...
kill themselves.
Wow! Wow! That's pretty much
gonna ruin any plan...
that death's put in motion.
And even better...
hey, it's gonna save
5 skipped lives.
Any takers?
Nah, I didn't think so.
There! Those!
Ugh!
Aah!
Ooh!
Unh! Unh!
Unh!
Aah!
I didn't say anything.
I mean, I think...
they were trying to scare us
into saying something...
but they had nothing
to keep me there.
What'd you tell 'em?
Everything.
I didn't do anything.
I told them about
the pictures in the camera...
and Flight 180
and Frankie and Lewis...
and why we went to see
lan and Erin and...
Did they believe you?
Yeah, right.
Would you believe me?
No, they looked at me
like I was crazy.
10 hours they
had us in there.
For all we know...
whoever was sitting behind
Erin is already dead.
And we're next.
Now.
Lan almost died first,
but we intervened.
So it skipped lan.
That's...
that's how we regain control.
If someone intercedes...
the life that was supposed
to be next is skipped.
All right, wait, wait, wait.
So, going by the way we sat
on the roller coaster...
well, I'm next...
and then you.
We can beat this.
We're so close.
We can't give up.
All right, my dad's here.
He's gonna give me a ride back.
But are you sure
we shouldn't stick together?
It's just for a couple of hours.
All right? A couple of hours.
Go back, look at the pictures...
see if you can find
any more clues...
and I'll ask everybody I see...
if they know if anyone else
got off the ride.
OK?
Was there something
I should know about going?
No, it's just...
I'll just be freaking out
every second...
hoping you're OK.
Why?
I mean, we don't even
like each other.
Heh.
Come here.
OK?
All right, I got my cell.
OK.
Hey, Wen?
So we're meeting some guys
at that centennial thing...
and I could really use
my good luck... bracelet.
Mmm.
Huh.
Hey, this is Julie.
Leave a message.
Call me on my cell
right away.
Hello?
Do you remember Julie being
on the roller coaster?
What, your sister? No.
No, she would've said
something by now.
The person sitting
behind lan and Erin...
was wearing the exact
same charm bracelet...
our grandmother gave her.
Amber or Perry were
probably with her...
so... they're next.
I gotta find Julie.
She went to
the tricentennial thing.
Well, l... I'm here now,
working security.
I'll start looking for her.
- I'm on my way.
- Wen, wait.
Look, after them,
we're next.
So in case somethin'
happens to 'em...
before we meet up...
remember that time
we talked about?
When to look
at our pictures?
It's now.
Great. Mine has no clue.
It's just me standing in front
of a blank background...
with Jason at
the amusement park.
Wait. McKinley.
Lan? Is he in the picture?
No, but it... it feels like a clue.
And yours is the picture
that I took...
when I flashed
the camera in your face.
It's all out of focus
and overexposed, like...
Like a firework
went off in my face?
* There is someone *
* Walking behind you *
* Look at me *
* There is someone *
* Watching your footsteps *
* Look at me *
* There is someone *
* Who really loves you *
The British are coming!
Get 'em while they're hot!
Take it to those redcoats!
Column, advance!
The kite is aloft.
Now, let us hope
for some lightning.
Fuck you, Ben Franklin.
But he kept insisting.
"Get over here," right?
This is awesome, dude!
Heh heh.
Whoa. Hey!
Ha ha! Come on!
Hey, get out of here
with those, man!
You're gonna set these off!
Hurry, dude.
Come on, man, let's go!
Hurry up!
Ladies and gentlemen...
to celebrate
McKinley's tricentennial...
the fireworks extravaganza
will begin shortly.
Oh, my God. Julie.
- What?
- Look.
There's Kahlil.
Should we?
Hey, guys. I'm sorry,
but you can't be here, OK?
The viewing site is over there.
You too, sir. Come on.
They're not gonna
make us move, are they?
I don't fucking believe them.
- OK, we gotta clear out.
- Mm-hm.
Excuse me.
- Ladies.
- Boys.
What's going on?
Hey, Julie.
You 3 need to
come with me.
What did we do?
Look, it's for
your own safety, Julie.
All right?
I'll tell you about it...
as soon as we get away
from here OK?
Let go of me!
Julie.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Julie!
Ooh!
Heh heh heh!
- Sweet.
- Ha ha!
Yeah!
- Light it! Light it!
- Go, go, go, man!
Julie!
Uh! Oh!
- Oh, shit!
- Dude, we gotta bail!
- Aah!
- Unh!
Unh! Hey!
Julie! No, wait, wait.
You're in danger, OK?
I'm trying to explain something.
Let me explain this to you.
Julie, look out!
- Aah!
- Unh!
Aah!
Julie!
Unh!
Aah! Unh!
Cut him off!
Unh!
Aah!
OK, OK!
Stay back!
He's dangerous!
I got him.
- Just let me go.
- No, Julie.
You have to tell me,
you have to listen.
Tell me who was
sitting next to you...
on the roller coaster!
Oh, my God, Julie,
are you all right?
Listen to me!
You have to tell me...
who was sitting next to you
on the roller coaster!
Who? She's next!
Aah!
Kevin.
Fire!
You saved my life.
Thanks for that, McKinley.
- Shut up, McKinley!
- No!
We have to get
out of here now.
What's the deal?
Lan McKinley.
He causes my death.
In my picture I was wearing
the McKinley grad-night shirt.
- He's the clue.
- What?
There's a first-aid tent,
there should be security.
Get the fuck
outta here, McKinley!
Hey, I'm just celebrating
our town's tricentennial.
You followed me!
Oh! You are paranoid.
But, hey, I saw what happened.
You're next, right?
You're the end of it, aren't you?
Man, I would be paranoid too.
You didn't even believe me!
Yeah, well,
seeing is believing.
Then you have to
stay away from me!
"Have to"? Wow, that's extreme.
Oh, no way.
Do I cause your death?
Just like you caused Erin's?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, what? What?
You have a vision? Was I in it?
Was I in a picture?
Just tell me how to start it off!
Let's get this over with!
You'll save me
if you just stay away!
Then it'll all be over!
What do I care? It skipped me.
For me, it is over.
I'm not dying.
I'm not dying!
Ha ha ha!
You see?
I'm not gonna die!
It's you, Wendy!
You're dead!
- * Will get ya deeper *
- Hi!
* And make you right *
Thank you.
* Bruno's drops
threaten her... *
Wait, what about
that great curry place?
Don't we get off at Booth?
Oh, you mean Gupta's.
You get off at Oswald.
Oh, that's right.
You know, if I can't be
home for Thanksgiving...
I need some semblance
of a traditional dinner.
Turkey, stuffing, pie.
If you don't have
turkey for one Thanksgiving...
is that really gonna kill you?
* There is someone *
* Walking behind you *
* Turn around *
* Look at me *
* There is someone *
* Watching your footsteps *
* Turn around *
* There is someone *
* Who really needs you *
* Here's my heart *
This is Booth Street.
Next stop is Oswald.
End of the line.
The next stop
is the end of the line.
Wendy! Next stop after this.
Let's just walk.
It's freezing out.
Yeah, but the air'll feel good.
I could use some air.
Yeah!
- Ha ha ha!
- Yeah, man!
All right, man. See ya.
Let's go, Bruins!
Bruins, yeah!
Hey, man, peace out!
- Come on.
- Excuse me.
- Watch out!
- Hey, Bruins!
You missed the beginning.
Did you see that?
This is it!
- Yo, comin' through.
- Excuse me.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe this. Here.
Come on. Let's go. Let's go.
I thought you weren't
coming till tonight.
Well, Dad's car just, like,
dies out of nowhere...
and he couldn't get it fixed
anywhere on a holiday...
so instead of sitting
around for a few hours...
I lucked out and
caught an early train.
I hope I'm not
messing you up or...
No, no, it's just, um...
I think I had a sense
that you were coming now.
I was just...
I was feeling like
I did that night.
No. No, it's over.
You, me, Kevin went over
a thousand scenarios.
Lan was gonna
cause your death...
you intervened
and it skipped us.
Look, I'm not worried.
I ran into Kevin at home.
He's not worried.
And, if I were you...
until something happens
to me and then Kevin...
you've got nothing
to worry about.
You're right.
Hey, l... I want you to meet
my roommate and my friend, OK?
Yeah.
Hey, guys.
This is Julie, my...
What are you
doing here?
Wendy! Julie!
What are the chances?
How long have you
been on this train?
Uh, since home.
I was headin' up
to check out the game.
I was gonna look you up
afterwards.
You OK?
Is something wrong?
Aah!
- Julie, stay down!
- Aah!
Julie!
Aah!
- Kevin!
- Unh!
Aaaaaah!
Oh, God!
Aah!
Aah! Unh!
No!
I was gonna look you up
afterwards, but...
You OK?
Is somethin' wrong?
The train...
Oh, shit. Not again.
We gotta get out!
It's not working.
Somebody stop the train!
THE END
Subtitles by: Reklame