- What was that?
- Nothing.
- Okay, just give me one little hint.
- No, no hints!
- Almost there.
- Okay, I'm gonna take this off.
No, no, no.
Hey, you said you like surprises.
Yeah, I do, when I know what they are.
You're gonna love it.
Promise.
Yeah, I already love the view.
Ah-ah.
Watch your step, watch your step.
I can't see.
Hey, are you ready?
Are you sure I'm dressed alright?
You look like a million bucks.
Don't steal coins from the fountain,
it's bad luck.
Smile.
- You coming?
- We'll take the next one.
Oh, come on, we can fit you in.
Thanks.
Going up.
Excuse me.
Sorry, it does that sometimes.
It's 494 ft tall and weighs over 9,000 tons.
It's made of steel and reinforced concrete
and glass.
And even more
impressive, the entire project
was completed five
months ahead of schedule.
Is that a good thing?
What a time.
Fancy.
Yes, may I help you?
We have a reservation, Campbell.
Oh, I'm sorry, but we're already over
capacity for opening night.
We cannot accommodate you, if you wouldn't
mind us stepping aside.
Thank you so much.
It's okay, I worked it out with Jake.
Is he here?
I could speak.
We let Jake go this morning.
Thank you so much.
You're tearing me
apart, but I'm sorry, I can't help you,
if you wouldn't mind.
Oh, Mr. Fuller, how nice to see you.
We have a lovely table for you.
Thank you, this way.
Let's go to the bar.
I'm natural.
Um, wait a few.
This is good, right?
No, I'm just... I've just never been this
high up before.
I'm so sorry, this night's such a
disaster.
I've been waiting for it to be perfect.
Hey, it is perfect, because I'm with you.
Ah, you okay?
Oh, I think I'll live.
Yeah.
Hey, look for champagne.
That's my favorite kind.
I'll be right back.
Excuse me, where's the ladies from?
Other side of the dance floor.
Hi, sweetie.
Is everything all right?
I'm fine, thank you.
How far along are you?
What?
Oh, no, I'm, I'm not.
Um, I don't know exactly, maybe one or two
months?
Well, that's wonderful news, isn't it?
I haven't told my boyfriend yet.
Does he love you?
Yes.
Then he won't let go.
Thank you, of course.
Bye.
Okay, it's almost over.
Oh, hey, what?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
Come on, let's get some pressure.
Don't worry, I was
gonna do this at dinner, but as soon as we
have this view...
Hey, don't throw that penny.
You could kill somebody.
Oh, I'm so sorry, of course.
Yeah.
A fat ass?
Um, these past few years, I've been
absolutely magical.
And that's, uh, that's because of you.
Iris, I want to spend the rest of my life
with you.
You mean, with us?
Sorry?
I... I'm the luckiest guy in the world.
You're not upset?
Are you kidding me?
No, this is, this is incredible.
Really?
We're gonna start a family.
Um, so, will you?
Oh, yes.
Is it too tight?
It's perfect.
Hey, let's go celebrate.
Now,
Multiplication is scary, but it's not that
scary.
All right, that's it for today.
We'll start prepping for the final next
week.
Ms. Reyes, we need to talk.
Oh,
this dream is surrounding my life.
Mine too.
Every night, Steph.
God, I'm not getting any sleep.
Shit, I'm sorry.
Um, can I tell you something?
Yeah, what's up?
So, the woman in my dream, her name is
Iris, right?
Okay.
That was my grandmother's name.
I, uh, I think I'm dreaming about her.
Are you serious?
Yeah, the thing is, I never even met her.
I don't even know if she's alive.
Okay, well, either go home and find out
about grandma and hope that stops the
dreams or stay here and die in your sleep
for real.
Because I will murder you.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Okay.
Love you.
Love you too.
Go home.
Yeah.
Quietly.
Hey, there she is.
Hey, Dad.
Welcome home, sweetie.
So glad you're here.
I love you so much.
I know.
So great to see you.
Thank you.
I hate that for you.
Hey, sorry, Charlie took
your room a while ago, and my
files are in his room, so I
made up the pullout for you.
Is that okay?
Yeah.
No, that sounds totally fine.
Uh, hey, do we still have that box of
mom's old stuff?
It had, uh, some photos, like an address
book with phone numbers in it.
Uh, why do you want that?
It's not a big deal.
I just, I thought I saw it lying around
here somewhere.
Stephanie, what's going on?
Okay.
This is going to sound
really, really weird,
but I, uh, I just need
to find mom's mom, Iris.
Uh, okay.
Yeah, that is weird.
And you know, I got rid of those boxes
years ago after your mom left.
Oh, hi, Charlie.
Hey.
Um, hi, Steph.
How are you?
It's so nice to see you.
Yeah, sure.
Uh, go to the cousins.
Whoa, now?
I thought your sister just got home.
I thought we could... Actually,
you know what?
I can, I can drive you.
I was wanting to see them anyways.
That's fine.
Hey, if you're going to see your cousins,
please don't talk about Iris.
Yeah.
Yeah, no problem.
All right.
Bye.
Love you.
Love you too.
Can you just take these out?
I'm trying to talk to you.
What's your problem?
What?
You haven't said anything this entire
time.
What?
Steph, why are you here?
I mean, only coming home for holidays.
We have to tell you something, but
you will have to promise not to tell dad.
Are you pregnant?
No, I'm not pregnant, Charlie.
I don't know.
Why would you even... That's
not... I mean, you're in college.
Can you just promise me you won't tell
dad?
Why would I tell dad?
It's serious, Charlie.
Okay.
I am on academic probation.
Stop!
If I don't get my grades up... This is
kind of a big moment for me.
This is kind of funny.
Straight A's.
You're a class president, Ms.
Valedictorian.
Charlie, it's not funny.
If I don't get my grades up, I will lose
my scholarship.
Um, I'm sorry.
What happened?
I can't sleep.
Every time I close my eyes, I have this
same recurring nightmare about Iris,
our grandmother.
I don't...
I mean, it has to mean something.
I don't know.
I'm doing weird things.
I remember the hot dog ate me last night.
Like, the hot dog was eating me.
All right.
Dude, can you just do something?
Dude, calm down.
All right, we'll find him.
I can't pause over at the online event.
Are you serious?
I have to look under this.
Can you do me a kindness?
Fuck off.
You remember what happened last night?
It's a ranked match.
What's going on?
I can't find Paco.
Dude, again?
It's Paco.
Hey, cuz.
Oh my gosh.
Hey, can you help us look and just watch
your feet while you're stepping?
Yeah, yeah, sure.
I just, I gotta talk to your dad first.
The fuck are you doing home?
Oh, dude, she's fucking out of school.
Welcome to the club.
Eric, dude, have you looked anywhere?
Oh, but look who's down here.
Hi, Julia.
Oh my gosh.
So we had to promposal with Jenny,
girl.
She said yes.
Oh my gosh.
Okay, wait, who's uh, who's Jenny?
Oh, he met her in junior lifeguards.
Junior lifeguards?
Charlie, I didn't, I didn't know you were
doing junior lifeguards.
Okay, so what are you gonna wear?
Um, I'm just gonna keep it simple,
black blazer, butt.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Stephanie!
Oh my gosh.
Hi, honey.
Hi, girlfriend.
How long are you here for?
Uh, not long.
Uh, is Uncle Howard around?
Yeah.
Yeah, he's out back.
Look at him.
Howard!
Stephanie's here!
Come in!
She's like a little tired.
Is everything okay?
Oh.
Stephanie!
Look at you!
Come here, come here.
Oh, sweetie.
Oh, so good to see you.
Hey, are you hungry?
I just want to make some lunch.
No, actually, uh, I came here because I
wanted to talk to you about your mother,
Iris.
I know you don't like to talk about her.
There's not much to tell.
Hey, kids, come on, lunch!
It's just that I've been, I've been having
this recurring nightmare.
About her.
Oh, honey, it's probably just us.
You should try melatonin.
Okay, but the weird thing is, I've been
dreaming about a real place from,
from 50 years ago.
It was like a restaurant called the
Skyview.
You know, it is.
Did, did Iris tell you about it?
Uh, what did, what did she say?
Did, did she say anything?
Um, and maybe, maybe if I
could talk to her... Talk to who?
Uh, Stephanie's dreaming about Grandma
Iris.
Psycho Granny?
I thought she was dead.
Well, she's dead to us.
Steffi, Iris Campbell is a very deeply
disturbed woman.
End of story.
Look, if I could just
talk to her, then, then
maybe, maybe I can
get these dreams to stop.
Steph, just drop it.
I don't get it.
What, what happened?
That was so... For one thing, she's the
reason that your mother's so screwed up.
What?
Look, I just don't want to talk about this
anymore, okay?
Uncle Howard, please.
I just need to know.
Look, Steffi, after our father died,
Iris just snapped.
She, she wouldn't let us go to school.
She locked us inside the house.
She obsessed about all the horrific ways
we could die.
And eventually it got so bad.
I mean, so bad.
And the state came in and it took your
mother and I away from her.
But it didn't end there.
She, she tracked us all through foster
care.
And when the kids were born, she started
sending these horrible letters that were
full of obituaries and these disturbing
pictures of dead bodies.
We had to move so she couldn't contact us
anymore.
So, uh, do you still have any of those
letters?
Steffi, listen to me.
That woman is a sick and dangerous person.
And for your well-being and your safety,
stay the hell away from her.
I found Paco.
You heard your uncle.
Just let it go.
You don't understand.
My whole life is falling apart because of
this dream.
And not only that, I feel like,
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
Please, you are the only person who can
help me.
Howard would never forgive me if I put you
in touch with Iris.
Please.
Whatever you do, do not look in the bottom
drawer of the dining room cabinet.
Hi, um, I'm, I'm here to see Iris
Campbell.
Did you not see the signs?
Uh, uh, yeah, yes, I did, but...
Hey, get the fuck out of here.
No visitors.
I'm your granddaughter.
Stephanie,
empty your pockets.
Phone, keys, everything.
Well, I'm not dangerous.
It's not you I'm afraid of.
Um, um.
Coming slowly.
Shut the door.
Quick, quick, quick.
Oh, don't move.
Oh my God.
It really is you.
I can see your mother in you.
Hi, I'm Stephanie.
Stop, stop, don't move.
Not until I tell you.
Trying to trick me, aren't you?
Getting me to let my guard down.
I'm, there you go.
Sit.
Okay, um.
That's it.
So, how is Darlene?
Your mom?
Okay.
Oh, uh, no, I, I don't, I don't know.
She, uh, she left when I was 10.
So we don't, we don't see her anymore.
But you saw my letters.
That's why you're here, right?
No, um, I'm actually here because I've
been dreaming about the sky view.
Yeah, yeah, every single night for the
past two months.
It's, it's the same dream in it.
You're, you're on a date, but
then the dance floor breaks
and, and then there's an
explosion and then you-Fall and die.
Yeah, yeah, everyone dies.
It wasn't just your dream.
It was my premonition.
Years ago, at the sky view, I got a
glimpse into the future.
And saw what death was about to do.
Oh,
I'm so sorry, of course.
These past two years have been absolutely
magical.
And that's all because of you.
No, no, no, no.
This isn't right.
Is that a no?
Everyone's going to die.
The whole building is going to come down.
Are you serious?
The penny.
Iris?
Keep up.
What the hell, lady?
You need to give it to me.
What are you doing?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Iris?
She knows you'll make me a bummer.
I saved a lot of lives that night.
Lives that were never meant to be saved.
They closed the restaurant after that.
Said it needed additional renovations.
But it never reopened.
Eventually they tore it down.
So you stopped the disaster?
Yes.
But death doesn't like it when you fuck
with his plans.
So over the years he came back and he
killed everyone who was there that night.
Including my Paul.
Wait, wait a minute.
I'm sorry, did you did you say death came
back?
He's a relentless son of a bitch.
Won't stop till he finishes the job.
But I taught myself how to see him coming.
To anticipate his every move.
Been keeping him at bay for years now.
Now he's got me.
Cancer.
Believe that shit?
Sorry.
Got the diagnosis two months ago.
Wait, that's when I started having my
dream.
See, it's a sign.
Okay, but why am I dreaming about what you
saw?
Maybe my cancer passed my premonition on
to you.
Maybe it's fate's demented sense of humor.
Who the hell knows?
What matters is that when the universe
speaks, you pay attention.
I see you, you fuck.
Um, who are you talking to?
Death.
He thinks I'm distracted because you're
here.
I have to teach you everything in this
book.
It'll take some time to learn the basics.
So you need to stay here.
Stay here?
Yes, high world is too dangerous.
I haven't stepped out there in 20 years.
In here, we can be safe.
Oh.
See that?
Yeah.
This is all my research.
My life's work.
Look, I'm sorry.
I can't stay here.
I have to get back to school.
But you know, I'll come back and I'll
visit.
No, I'm sick.
I won't be alive that long.
You can't leave.
Don't you see?
Death is coming for our family.
Oh.
You don't believe me?
No.
I think I made a mistake.
I think it was probably just a dream.
No, wait!
At least take the book!
Stephanie!
Look, I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have found you.
This book is a lifeline.
It will show you everything you need to
know to keep our family safe.
You still don't believe me?
Step back.
Why?
Seeing is believing.
Hey, Steph.
Her face really exploded right in front of
you.
Is that like-Just leave her alone.
It's my bad, Steph.
I'm just curious.
Hey.
How you holding up?
Yeah.
Sorry, Uncle Howard.
You were right about Iris.
I never should have went there.
Honey, there's no need to apologize.
I'm so sorry you had to go through that.
She said something to me before she died.
She said death was coming for our family.
That's-That's crazy, right?
Oh my god.
I can't believe it.
I emailed her.
I just didn't think she'd show up.
I- Come on.
Is that Mom?
Yeah.
Come back.
It'll be ridiculous.
Come on.
You think she'll come to the barbecue?
Steph?
Hey, if she's going to Uncle Howard's
house, then I'm not.
You can get a ride with Dad.
I think you're going to talk to her?
Come on.
You don't remember her like I do.
Just give her a chance.
Why?
Charlie, she abandoned us
and now she rolls in here after
all these years and wants
to act like nothing happened?
Because who did that, right?
Wait, what?
Nothing, really.
No.
No, what's that supposed to mean?
I tried calling you so many times and
nothing.
Same with Julia.
You used to be best friends.
You don't even talk anymore.
Okay, well, I'm sorry.
I've just been distracted the last couple
of months because of this nightmare.
What about before that?
It's been like this ever since you left.
You're mad at Mom, but you haven't been
around either.
I'm not like her, okay?
I'm not crazy.
Yeah, you're right.
You're not crazy.
You just don't care.
Now you got it.
Watch out for splinters.
Hey, there she is.
Hey, come here.
So glad you made it.
Of course, come on.
Hey, everybody, come on, come on over.
Made cookies.
That's great.
Yes, of course.
Is this some peanut butter?
Yeah.
Are you trying to kill my brother?
Oh my God, Bob is allergic.
Yeah.
I totally forgot.
I'm so sorry.
The important thing is that you're here.
So, Bobby bartender, drinks, drinks all
around.
You don't get to pick the one you get.
Just gotta love the one that you got.
Now, uh, our mother, she lived alone till
the day that she died.
And her death should be
a reminder to all of us to
enjoy life and spend the
time that we have together.
Because we're not going to get any back.
I love you guys.
Cheers.
Oh my God.
There's a bug in there.
Bob, girls ready?
Mind if I join you?
See, get the load off.
There we go.
It's great to set up you've got here.
Well, I wanted the kids to have a happy
childhood.
Unlike some people I know.
You're not talking about us, are you?
Oh, yeah.
We had a great childhood.
Mm-hmm.
I mean, look at me.
I turned out fabulous.
Yep.
Oh, Howard.
What is that?
Looks like a housekeeping.
Come on.
You know, we got the
spare room and it's got to
be better than bouncing
around trailer parks.
I don't think this is a good idea.
It's never too late for a second chance.
I'm sorry.
They're better off without me.
Pick up.
Come on.
You got me, right?
Oh, nice catch, Andy.
All right.
Here we go.
Hey, Dad.
Let's do it.
Stay away from that edge.
Stephanie.
I'm glad you decided to come.
The whole family's here.
I'm okay.
All right.
Oh, good.
It's all right.
We shall wipe away every tear from their
eyes.
What is all this stuff?
Okay.
I found these papers in Iris's book.
They are obituaries and
articles for the people who were
at the Skyview on the night
that Iris had her premonition.
Each one of these people went on to die in
some weird and messed up way.
And not only that, they all died in the
same order as Iris's premonition.
Hundreds of people were supposed to die
that night, but Iris stopped the disaster.
So death came back for them one by one.
Since there were so many survivors, it
took years for death to get to all of them.
But eventually it got to Iris.
She was the last to die in the
premonition.
It was her and a little boy.
But she was prepared.
She single-handedly held off death for
decades.
Stephanie, sweetie.
I don't think this is the appropriate time
with us.
Yeah, I mean, none of this even has
anything to do with us, right?
Why are we even here?
No, it has everything to do with us.
I mean, because death took so long to make
its way through the survivors,
these people went on to have families.
Families that they never should have had.
So death took them too.
Don't you see this?
Death is coming for us because we were
never supposed to exist.
Okay, so why everybody in this room is on
death's hit list?
Bobby, stop.
That's what she's saying.
No, no, no.
Dad and Aunt Brenda are safe because
they're not part of Iris' bloodline.
Okay, following the pattern.
Death makes its way down each branch by
age.
So because Uncle Howard was the oldest,
it'll start with his family first.
Meaning, Eric, you're next.
Go fuck yourself.
Then it'll go for Julia, then Bobby.
Then it'll come for our branch.
Starting with Darlene, then me,
then Charlie.
Charlie, Charlie.
You buying this?
I don't know.
This is so messed up.
I mean, you're turning our dad's death into
some kind of fucked up conspiracy theory.
What is wrong with you?
No, no, no, no, no.
It's not.
It's not a conspiracy theory.
That's enough.
We're all going to die.
Stop.
I can't listen to this for one more
minute.
That crazy woman's nonsense has caused
enough pain and suffering for this family.
Hang on.
Hey, Brenda, please just leave it alone.
Okay.
In Iris's book, she mentioned somebody who
cheated deaths and survived.
Eric, no, wait.
I'm worried about you.
Stop it.
Let me take care of this.
Brenda, Brenda.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
Please.
You believe me, right?
I'm sorry.
Look, I love you.
But sometimes I really hate you.
I know how convincing all of this can be,
but it's not real.
How can you say that?
I know Iris taught you all of this.
Don't let my mom's beliefs derail your
life.
Sing me they did mine.
Thank you so much for that advice,
but I really don't need a mom anymore.
All
right, open mine.
Very good.
This is gonna pinch, right?
Ready?
Five, four, three, two.
Gonna hit the club.
I need you to lock up.
And don't touch any of my liquor.
No, no.
You didn't say anything about locking up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You didn't say shit about closing,
dude.
And cry me a river.
I hope you burn in hell.
You believe that shit?
My old man just died.
I come in as a favorite of that asshole,
and now he wants me to lock up.
You know what that is?
It's inconsiderate.
Anyway, you're all done.
Thank you.
Of course.
Hey, five star review.
Like and subscribe and all the things.
And now it's only fair that I should let
you know what you should know.
Oh God Come on.
Shit!
Charlie, wake up.
Charlie, wake up!
I've been trying to call Eric all night.
He's not answering me.
I don't know where he is.
I'm worried.
I'm sure he's fine.
Well, have you heard from him?
I'm going over there.
I need to check on him.
You're coming too, Charlie!
He's got a whole voicemail.
Is that him?
My friend just said the testing part went
down last night.
What?
Steph!
Ow!
Oh, what?
You're trying to kill me?
Eric?
Oh, yeah.
No, of course it's you.
Dude!
We heard about the fire.
We thought you were dead.
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
I'm so worried about you.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I said I was lucky as fuck, but I was
wearing that leather jacket.
Bailey got burned.
Really my favorite jacket, though.
What is this?
Oh, yeah.
Check it out.
I got branded.
Sick, right?
You like it?
You said you were asleep.
You're blowing up my phone with a goddamn
stalker.
What do you want me to do?
I don't get it.
You should be dead.
Right, yeah.
Yeah.
Or, you know, maybe...
Maybe death's not actually coming for our
family.
Because that would be fucking crazy.
Jesus!
Shit!
Or maybe I'm invincible.
Eric?
Eric!
Yeah?
Eric, wait!
Stop!
Just wait, okay?
Just because death didn't kill you last
night doesn't mean that you're safe.
Stay away from that tree trimmer!
Gonna move on its own, Steph?
Is that what it's gonna do?
It could fall.
And stay away from these kids.
I'll take my chances.
Steph, how is a couple kids with a soccer
ball gonna kill him?
I mean, I don't know.
The trimmer could fall and hit the leaf
blower guy, which causes him to...
blow stuff into the kid's eyes and then
take the ball to his face.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Soccer ball to my face?
That does sound deadly.
I should be more careful.
Hey!
What's up?
What happened to you?
Charve rolled by death, apparently.
She came.
That looks really bad.
No, wait, let me see that.
Eric, just stay away from this truck.
Oh, what, this truck?
Stop!
Oh my god.
Please.
Let's stop right here.
But it's such a beautiful truck.
Eric, just wait.
Stop.
You like that?
Oh my god.
Oh!
Uh oh!
Oh, Eric's tempting death again.
What's gonna happen?
Stop doing that.
Nothing at all.
How about that?
I'm just trying to help you.
Try less.
Yeah, honestly, we're so done with your
garbage.
Can you please?
For the fifteen hundredth
time, no one gives a
shit about your stupid
little death curse, okay?
So take a hint and leave us alone,
because death's not coming for our family.
It's your dentist!
Whoa, whoa!
I'm so sorry, sweetie.
Should have believed you, Steph.
No, I am.
I screwed up the order and now Julia's
dead and it's my fault.
Guys, look.
What happened was traumatic and awful,
and it's not anybody's fault.
It's my fault.
Mom, it's not your fault.
It is my fault.
Stephanie, you were
only wrong about the order
because there was
something you didn't know.
Eric isn't Howard's biological son.
I'm sorry, what are you talking about?
And Stephanie, I didn't
believe you, so I didn't
say anything to you, and
now my little girl is dead.
Well, I don't understand why you had an
affair.
Your father and I were having such a hard
time, but it was good because I got you.
I got you out of it.
It was my real time.
It doesn't matter because Howard loved you
so, so much.
How is it?
It's my real time.
Jerry Fenbury.
Oh!
Jerry Fenbury?
Yes.
Oh, shit.
No, Jerry!
Jerry fucking Fenbury?
You don't know what we're going through.
Oh, God, what is this?
Why are you always wanting to play catch?
Oh, Rick.
Okay.
So that means that if it's going in the
right order, then I'm next, right?
You got to help me, Steph.
Oh, my God.
I don't think that I can.
I mean, I thought I did,
but I don't... No, but you can.
I mean, you predicted exactly what was
going to happen.
You just got the order wrong because you
didn't have all the information, Charlie.
What do you mean, predicted?
She saw everything.
The trimmer, the blower, the soccer ball.
It was like they were
pieces to a puzzle and she
just had to put them together,
you know what I mean?
Is that true?
Darling, please do not encourage this.
Marty, I mean, everything in Iris' book,
it's like an equation.
It's math.
Stephanie, if you can see how all of this
fits together, we might have a chance.
Just stop.
You devastated this family when you walked
out, but we've been okay without you.
I'm begging you not to traumatize our kids
anymore.
It's real this time.
I'm going for a walk.
I need some air.
I can appreciate that.
Our family is clearly going to
need some counseling in the
future, but can we focus on the
fact that we're all about to die?
Right?
I mean, I mean, Steph,
didn't you say that Iris
knew someone that
cheated death or something?
Yeah, um, it's here somewhere.
It says that, um, right here, J.B.
found someone who survived, but it doesn't
say anything about who this J.B.
was or-Wait a minute, I know that name.
My mom used to write me
letters, and she sometimes
would talk about a
friend of hers named J.B.
who worked at a hospital.
Um, um, something, uh, something river
hospital, uh, uh, Deep River, uh,
Peace River Hospital, uh, Clear River-
Hope, Hope River?
That's it!
Shit, it's like an hour away.
I'm going.
I'm gonna go find him and talk to him
myself.
While I'm coming with you.
Me too.
Okay, yeah, yeah.
Let's, let's go.
Harvey, uh-What?
You need to stay here with your mom,
it's safer.
Yeah, fuck that.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not staying here by myself.
Well, it's, it's too dangerous on the road
for you.
You can't-No, I read Gammie's death book,
okay?
Alright?
I mean, there's like a thousand
house-related deaths in that thing, man.
You could trip down the stairs,
fall down a toilet or something,
I don't, I don't know.
But I'm not, I'm not, no way, I'm not
staying here.
Hang on, hang on.
Hey.
Okay, okay.
Too fast.
We'll go slow, we'll go slow.
I'm gonna go open up the truck.
Charlie, check the back.
Got it.
Be careful, this stuff's slippery
sometimes.
Hey!
Any of you fuckers doing that check?
Excuse me?
You made cookies in that thing with peanut
butter in them just a few days ago.
This poor bastard so much
as he even touches, and
not his sword, he's
gonna close up tight and...
You understand, where's the peanut butter?
Cabin and above the sink.
Thank you.
I'm so sorry Bobby, I just...
Hey, okay.
All cleared.
Thank you.
You're a good brother, Eric.
Not checked.
What?
It was good, I get it.
Wait!
I'm coming with you, bro.
Someone's gotta protect you.
Dad's calling again.
Tell him we just went for a ride with mom.
He's not gonna believe that.
At least it'll buy us some time.
Death doesn't get us, you did,
Will.
I always keep them where I can see them.
I mean, you could've
just had the real thing,
but it's okay, not everyone
wants to be a mom.
Is that what you think?
That I didn't want to be your mom?
Look, I was raised by a woman who taught
me to see death everywhere.
I thought I could put it behind me,
but then when I had you and your brother,
all I could see were a hundred different
ways that you and Charlie could die.
I didn't want you to leave the house.
I would freak out on you guys over...
nothing.
One day I looked at your face and I saw
the same scared little girl that I was
growing up, and I knew that if I stayed,
I was gonna ruin your life.
I have no idea if I did the right thing.
But I'm here for you now.
Hey, I see you, buddy.
We're going.
The front desk is this way.
Oh, hi.
Um, we're looking for JB.
And who are you?
The front desk told us we could find him
down here.
Is that you?
That would be me.
William John Bloodworth.
But my friends call me JB.
I've been waiting for you, Stephanie.
Charlie, Darlene, Button.
So, which one of you is next?
Hi.
I was sorry to hear about Iris.
She was a special woman.
How did you know her?
She saved my life.
When?
At the Skyview.
Another brought me with her to work that
night.
JB, honey, I told you, you've got to stay
back there while I'm on stage.
I wasn't supposed to be there,
except, of course, to die.
So, all that time, she
wasn't just protecting
our family, she was
protecting you, too.
Years later, she tracked me down,
helped me see the truth.
We traded ideas.
I helped her fortify her cabin.
We became friends.
I even helped her get the best medical
care I could, considering her condition.
Iris said that you found somebody who
stopped death and survived.
Yes.
And how do we do that?
There are only two ways.
By killing or by dying.
If you take a life, you get the time that
person had left.
What?
No, I'm not going to kill someone.
Maybe we should let the guy finish.
Then, to truly break the cycle,
you have to die.
What does that mean?
A long time ago, a young
woman named Kimberly
Corman found herself on
death's list, just like you.
And when her turn finally came,
she died.
Flatlined.
But her doctor managed to bring her back.
And that broke the chain.
Alright, then we'll do that.
What are you talking about?
Why didn't Iris try that?
It's risky.
And if you fuck with death and lose,
things can get very messy.
Wait.
Hang on.
Okay, wait.
There has to be another way.
Please, you have to help us.
For years, people have been coming to me
for advice.
Well, I'm tired.
I'm done with all that.
And now I'm sick, just like Iris.
There's no running this time.
The fact is, you're all going to die.
And after that, I will too.
Now that my old friend is gone,
I'm retiring.
So what?
You're just going to leave us here?
Wait, wait, wait.
Dude, what means your help?
Where are you going?
I intend to enjoy the time I have left.
And I suggest that you do the same.
Life is precious.
Enjoy every single second.
You never know when.
That's fantastic.
No.
No, that can't be it.
There has to be something here.
There has to be another answer.
Steph, Steph, he gave us an answer.
Bobby's got to die.
Eric, you're fucking insane.
We're not killing Bobby.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Am I the only guy that just listened to
that, dude?
There's only one way.
We kill Bobby, we resuscitate him,
and then boom, you're all off death's list.
Congratulations.
Wait, there has to be something else,
right?
I mean, there has to be another solution,
right, Steph?
No.
No, there's nothing else we can do,
okay?
It's over.
Stephanie, listen to me.
You have to trust me on this one,
okay?
She's giving up on you.
I'm not going to.
Look, Iris found a way to hold death off
for decades.
So will we.
I trust that guy.
Do you trust that guy?
He was... that just went back.
He was just on a charismatic, and you know
that as well as I do.
Eric and Bobby are gone.
Shit.
Shit!
I don't think I like this, dude.
We're in a hospital.
Remember, there's doctors everywhere.
We kill you, they bring you back.
Everybody's safe.
We're heroes.
That is literally the opposite of keeping
you safe.
Hey, what's the alternative, huh?
You want to kill someone, take the time
they have left?
How?
How do you even know how many years they
have?
No.
Well, I mean, no.
Of course not.
We would do that, right?
No.
We would never.
Don't touch those babies.
Look, bottom line, flatlining is your best
option.
What do you have to lose?
Okay.
All right.
How would we even do that?
See, I got an idea.
But it's a little nuts.
Your allergy is deadly, right?
Well...
Oh, hey, dude, wait.
No, look, all right?
If I'm going out, it's not going to be on
those... what is it?
Salted bitches, all right?
Give me those.
Nice choice.
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
Come on.
Hey, all right.
You know, maybe this is a sign,
so we can just...
Ah, okay.
Hey, dude, maybe we can just bail now.
I'm not giving up.
Can you help?
It's all right.
We work here.
Maintenance.
It's fine.
Put your headphones back on.
Dude, it's going to fall.
It's going to fall.
Oh, it's falling.
Hold it.
Easy work.
Now what?
Come on, man.
Hey, hang here.
Got to get something.
Don't move.
What are you talking about?
It's cool.
I've seen it in the back.
And we're in the RV?
No.
Look, if Eric was trying to cut Bobby,
where would they be?
I don't know, but there's a million ways
to die in a hospital.
Can I help you?
Excuse me?
No, just come to see my Nana.
Lovely day today.
Got much time left?
I think so.
All the talent, belongings,
and devices that
could interact with the
MRI's powerful magnets.
Hey, dude, Charlie's trying to call our
banking event.
Hey, come on.
Sit down.
What the hell?
No, but I sit in that.
Well, I've got a great idea.
There's an ER down the hall, so as soon as
you flatline, boom, I'm going to wheel
your ass down there and bring you right
back.
Hey, where's your FVV?
It's right here.
Give it to me.
What?
What is that?
Give it.
Dude, listen.
The whole idea is that you have to die.
Remember?
This keeps you alive.
Now sit.
Dude, we need to hurry.
Come on, go.
Alright, meet up.
Hey, man.
Um,
the plan's great, but, you know, if it
doesn't work out... It's going to work, Bobby.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah, but, you know, just in case,
and I die for real...
Will you just, um... Will you look after
Paco?
Yeah, yeah, of course.
I'll look after him.
Dude, I'm just saying, I mean,
the Turtles live to be like 100 years old.
Look at me.
Brother, I'm not going to take care of
Paco because you are going to be okay.
Me and you, we are going to fix things for
everyone right now.
I promise you, I'm not going to let you
die.
Technically, I'm going to let you die,
but then I'm going to bring you back.
Dude, it's not funny.
I'm just talking with you.
I'm up.
You got this.
Oh, my God.
What?
It's really good.
It's very good, I know.
Okay, other than good, what are you
feeling?
Nothing.
You've got to be kidding me.
What, are you telling me you're not
allergic anymore?
I grew out of it.
What, grew out of it?
Fuck.
You know, I don't have a plan B exactly.
Hey, you're doing it.
Bobby, you're doing it.
Hey, I'm here with you.
Hey, hey, I can't give you that.
Bobby, Bobby, hey.
Wait.
Bobby, it's so hard to play.
Calm down.
Bobby, in the wheelchair.
Try calling them in.
This is the only way we can do this.
Yeah.
Why, why is Eric dead if he's not related
to Iris?
When you fuck with Dad, things get messy.
We have to get out of here.
It's not safe.
Then go where?
Nowhere is safe.
Except Iris' cabin.
She was able to survive there for decades.
Yeah, and then she got her face blown off.
She only died because she left the cabin.
Outside is dangerous, but inside is the
safest place that there is.
It's the only place where we have any
advantage.
So we just lock ourselves in a cabin
forever?
Not you.
Me here.
Mom, you can't leave.
We just got you back.
If anybody's gonna live in that cabin,
it's me.
And as long as I am alive, death can't
touch you.
Mom, let me do this.
He'll never let you get there on your own.
But I can see him coming.
We have to do this together.
You should drive.
Yeah.
Look at this place.
It's gonna be impossible to get through
that gate.
He's about to make a move.
I don't know what it is.
We need to get you inside now.
Wait.
Wait, what?
Shit!
What?
Don't wait for me.
Just get inside.
If you get inside, I'll be safe.
Go.
Okay.
We'll save you, sister.
I'm gonna stay alive as long as I can.
Okay.
Just breathe.
Breathe.
Tell me.
What happened?
You're okay.
You died.
And I brought you back.
Mom?
She saved us.
Let's go home.
Well, there he is.
Wow.
Okay, Charlie.
Alright, give us a spin.
Oh.
You look really good.
I'm a great stylist.
Come on.
You're gonna be late.
Where's Jenny?
You think she's still inside getting
ready?
Here, let me fix this.
I'm really happy to be here for this.
Me too.
You're okay?
Yeah.
Can I have one cookie, please?
Look, it's sharp.
Thank you.
Steph, I want you to meet Jenny's dad,
Dr. Redick.
Hey, Bart.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
We just adore Charlie.
And I understand he's quite the life
saver.
Oh, yeah, you heard about that.
He, uh, brought me back from the dead.
Yeah.
What?
Well, technically, you weren't dead.
I mean, if you were
unconscious and Charlie got
your breathing again,
then your heart didn't stop.
But regardless, way to go, Charlie.
So she wasn't dead?
Exactly.
She was lucky Charlie was there.
Yeah.
Everything happens for a reason.
Jenny!
She looks like a girl in a box.