Tomorrow marks
the one year anniversary
since Velez Sir Flight 180
exploded and crashed
shortly after takeoff from JFK airport.
It's a disaster that's affected many.
None more so than
Mt. Abraham High School,
which lost 40 students and four
faculty members in the crash.
But it was the events after the crash
that has turned this tragic story
into something even stranger.
The survivors who managed
to get off the plane before it crashed
died soon thereafter in a series
of mysterious and bizarre accidents.
Now, to some, these Deaths
are just tragic coincidences,
but to others, they're an indication
that there are more
sinister events taking place.
That's the contention
of tonight's guest.
Thank you for joining us
this evening.
Thank you for having me.
And I appreciate you using
the word sinister.
Most people say supernatural,
because they think
I'm talking about ghosts,
and witches and stuff like that.
Here's your chance
to set the record straight.
Great. ok. Well.
I believe,
that there's a sort of force,
an unseen malevolent presence
That's all around us every day.
And it determines when we live and die.
And...
some people call this force the devil,
but I think that whole religious thing is...
so I prefer to call it Death itself.
So I'm surrounded by Death?
Absolutely. Absolutely.
Every day, everywhere,
all the time.
And that's what I want people
to understand that.
Death has this grand design
that we all fit into.
So when Alex Browning
got off that plane,
and took the other survivors with him,
he basically screwed up Death's plan.
And that's what I'm trying
to warn people about.
And the fact that all
of the survivors have died,
is your evidence of this?
Well, it's not so much
that the survivors died,
but it's the way that they died.
I mean, there were so many weird,
seemingly random things
about the way they died.
It just didn't make sense.
You know, and that's the proof
there's something out there
Wait, that's not proof.
That is your interpretation
of events that can't be proven
in order to support your ideas.
Kimberly.
You should be more open minded about
What happened after
that was just coincidence.
May I finish?
Mere coincidence would have
one or two of these kids die.
But not all of them
including their teachers.
Yes, but people die all the time so,
why should this be any different?
It forced people to question
these so-called everyday coincidences.
What if they were something more?
What if you could do something about it?
Please, are you listening to yourself?
This is crazy.
You're saying we should be on guard
every morning when we leave the house?
That's exactly, what I'm saying.
Exactly it.
And in order to survive
the only way to survive
is to look beneath the visible world.
Because in the end
no one can escape Death.
And today, may be your day to die.
Ok, I'll call you.
Kimberly, are you sure you've got everything?
Credit card, cell phone, triple-a card?
Dad, it's Daytona, not Somalia.
Alright.
Fix-a-flat, road flares, sunblock, mace?
Condoms, whips, chains.
Just kidding, Mr. Corman.
Don't worry, I'll keep an eye on her.
That makes me feel a lot better, thanks.
Ok.
Alright.
Can we go get the guys?
I'm getting horny.
Go on.
Ok, I'll call you.
Whips and chains.
That's nice.
Whatever, your dad's cool.
Buckle up!
Watch it!
Easy, Kimmy. First year of driving?
Sorry.
Oh my God.
Fucking freak.
Yo Dano, shouldn't we, help your mom?
Good one, man.
You're hilarious.
You're not getting any of my weed.
Nothing.
Whatever.
What are we going to do in Daytona?
We're going to see lots of honeys there.
We're gonna get drunk,
we're gonna smoke this big El gagerero,
we're gonna have this,
awesome party.
Pileup! Pileup!
A candlelight vigil to mark
the one year anniversary
of the crash of flight 180,
will be held at 8:00 P.M. tonight
at the Mt. Abraham
High School auditorium.
Oh my God.
Hello?
Hey, Kimberly, it's dad.
Hey, what's up?
Listen, your car's leaking
transmission fluid.
So I want you to get it
checked right away.
Ok, yeah.
I'll do that.
I mean it. Take care of it ok.
Is that someone coughing?
Yeah, ok.
I'll take care of it.
I'll talk to you later. I love you.
Bye, honey.
What did you do?
Look at those titties!
Shut up.
She missed that?
You missed that?
That's too bad.
Oh, shit!
Fuck man,
there's a fucking cop behind us!
Pull in the right Lane now!
Shit.
Seriously, put it out.
Eugene.
Put that thing out.
Alright.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Get rid of it.
Shit.
Hey, it's Kat.
Listen. Oh, what the hell?
No. Just wait. Not you.
Hey, I think we better pull over
and check the car, because...
Kimberly, the car is going to be fine.
Your dad's going to be fine,
you're going to be fine.
Ok?
Look at that guy.
He's drinking a beer.
Oh, yeah, that's real responsible.
You ever hear of the ozone layer, asshole?
What?
I'm wearing my seatbelt.
You're gonna bust me, bitch?
Son of a...
Bitch.
Fuck!
Oh my God!
Watch out!
Stop!
Oh my God!
Watch out!
Shaina?
I can't get out of here!
Help me!
Easy, Kimmy.
First year of driving?
Yo, Dano, shouldn't we help your mom?
Good one, man.
You're hilarious.
Pileup! Pileup!
Oh my God.
What?
There's going to be a huge accident.
We're all gonna die!
I just saw it.
Alright, that's it.
My turn to drive.
No, I'm serious.
Kim, what's wrong?
What are you doing?
Oh my God.
Of flight 180 will be held
at 8:00 P.M. tonight
at the Mt. Abraham
High School auditorium.
Highway to hell.
Highway to hell?
Ok, Kimberly, you're scaring me.
Green means go, Kimmy.
Yeah.
Are you out of your mind?
What the hell are you doing?
What the fuck, Kimberly?
What's this?
Kimberly, you just got to breathe.
Oh, shit, shit.
Five-O is coming.
Let's fucking roll, man.
What?
Oh, my God.
Do you know how much
fucking weed I have on me?
Ok Dano, just shut up!
Just stay cool.
Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck, I'm going to jail.
I'm fucking going to jail.
What's going on here?
I think there's going to be a huge pileup.
I saw it.
There were bodies everywhere.
There were logs, I saw it.
It just happened.
Alright miss, I'd like you to please
step out of the vehicle.
Just pull over!
I know, mommy's hungry, too.
Come on.
Come on!
Oh, fuck this.
I'm going to get this
and we're going to go.
Fuck.
What the hell is going on up there?
Excuse me!
Is there any way that
we could drive around?
I have a delivery
You need to get back into your vehicles.
Just move it.
Now!
That's it!
That's the truck
that's going to kill everybody.
You need to stop that truck!
I told you again,
you have to calm down!
Why won't you listen to me?
Fuck!
Oh my God.
This is unit 13 requesting
medical assistance,
and backup for a major traffic accident
Kimberly, what's going on?
No!
Listen sir, this girl is really freaked out.
In fact, all of them are scared
as you can imagine.
Scared?
These people are the luckiest
sons of bitches on the planet.
Get this guy, Evan Lewis
yesterday the kid wins the lotto.
Today, some loony bitch blocks traffic
and he avoids the worst pileup in years.
I should be so damn unlucky.
Go babysit the rest of them.
I'll be done with Lewis in a minute.
Hey, excuse me...
We're trying to do the best we can.
We're going to get you out
of here as soon as possible.
I just think it's a bunch of bullshit.
Listen, I know you've gone over
all this with detective Suby
But would you mind telling me
what happened?
It was like I was there.
I knew something bad was going
to happen even before it did.
I just felt wrong, just like...
Just like what?
Look, I know this sounds crazy but...
You guys all heard about flight 180, right?
The kid who got off the plane?
Well, it happened a year ago, today.
My premonition was just like his.
What are you talking about?
Come on.
Sure you must have read about the kid
who had a dream
about a plane blowing up,
so he got all his buddies off the plane
and then the thing blew up
just like in his dream?
Yeah.
Yeah but did you hear
what happened after?
So a month goes by, right?
Everything seems cool.
But then all the survivors
start to die one-by-one.
Because when your number's up,
your number's up, right?
You know, some people
even say that Death itself...
was stalking them,
hunting each one down
until they were all...
dead.
Please.
There was one survivor.
Clear Rivers is in a padded room
at the Stonybrook Institution.
Well, that's encouraging.
Ok.
You want me to believe this is true,
that this is happening all over again?
I don't know why we're even here.
What do you want from me?
But if I was never meant to pull over,
we all should have died in that pileup.
Which means Death could be coming for us.
Yeah, like...
What if we're all getting that
different strokes curse or something?
I think you're all are certifiable,
I can't believe I've been
listening to this crap.
Let's go.
Let's go, Tim.
Mrs. Carpenter, please.
Kimberly!
Oh baby!
Are you ok?
I'm so sorry.
You can all go now.
Thank you for your patience.
Could I ask you something?
Anything.
Did mom ever have any...
I don't know...
weird feelings about anything?
What do you mean?
Like visions or...
premonitions.
Sweetie, are you sure you're ok?
Dad I know,
I know this sounds crazy but,
I'm really scared for the others.
I don't know I just...
I just have this really bad feeling.
What?
It's not over yet.
Jesus Christ!
Shit!
Hey, Evan, it's Tawny.
Sorry I haven't called.
Hey listen, I heard about your lottery win.
Let's hook up.
Call me.
Yeah.
Hi Evan, it's Nikki.
We met at Tucker's party last year?
I know it's been awhile,
but I've been thinking about you.
I just wanted to say congratulations.
So give me a call.
555-0123.
Bye.
You little bastard.
Shit.
Come on.
Fuck. Fuck.
Come on!
Come on.
Fuck!
Jesus!
Hey, this is Evan.
Leave a message.
If you're looking for Rick,
I don't know where he is,
and I don't know when
he's coming back. Thanks.
Evan, call me when you get in,
you lucky fuck!
Come on! Come on!
Jesus!
Come on.
Shit, I'm lucky.
Jesus Christ!
No, mother just...
just turn on any station.
Well, I don't know how you missed it,
it's been on all day.
Yes, mother, channel 4 is fine.
Ok you know. Here it is!
I got to go, ok?
I got to go!
Reach them.
To recap our top story,
route 23 was backed up
for almost nine hours today.
A record-breaking pileup killed
an estimated 18 people.
Emergency crews spent hours
sifting through the wreckage
hoping to recover any survivors
from this tragic collision.
So far police are refusing to release
the names of the victims,
until the families are notified.
The camera of a highway patrol car
managed to catch this shocking footage.
A semi comes from reading across the roadway
Oh my God.
And smashes into a red SUV.
The driver of the SUV,
standing outside the vehicule,
No.
And a quick action of the police trooper
Leave it.
May have saved her life.
He pulled her back at the last second
just as the semi plowed into the vehicle.
The passengers inside the SUV
You guys see that? Shit.
I was there, baby!
In other news a freak accident
took the life of a lotto winner.
Hey...
Friends say Evan Lewis was on top of the world
after recently winning $250,000.
But in tragic turn of events,
Lewis died today
while trying to escape
a fire in his apartment.
He managed to make it out of the building,
but somehow the ladder
on the fire escape
slipped and impaled him.
Investigators believe Lewis died instantly.
Come in.
Hey, buddy.
I want you to take this,
so you can get some sleep.
And then tomorrow it's off to the dentist,
which I know you love.
Now, get some rest.
Mom.
Yeah?
Do you think those guys
were BSing us today?
Yeah.
Some people just need
some rewiring, that's all.
Lights out.
At the request of the patient,
you'll relinquish any sharp objects
such as. Nail files, pencils, pens,
safety pins, bobby pins, your necklace,
matches, lighters, belts, belt buckles,
earrings, hair clips, glasses,
shoelaces, paper clips,
watches, money clip, pocket knives,
food, drinks, keys, cell phone
you have a cell phone on you?
Poisons, pills, medications.
Great. And let me see your nails.
Good. Then I think we're all done.
Wait...
Is she dangerous or something?
No honey, she expects you are.
Get him off me.
Get him off me!
How long are they gonna
keep her locked up like this?
Depends on her, I guess.
She's voluntary.
Clear Rivers?
Don't come any closer.
They told me you had something to do
with the crash on route 23.
Look, I don't know how to explain it,
but I saw the pileup before it happened.
And I saved some people.
And now you think Death is after you.
Nice work.
Maybe if you're real lucky one,
you'll wind up in here with me.
Anything else?
One of the people died
in a freak accident last night.
What if the other people are in danger, too?
Well, if you put them on the list,
they're already dead.
List? What list?
Death's list.
The survivors of flight 180
died in the exact order
they were originally meant
to die in the plane crash.
That was Death's original design.
The list.
I was supposed to die
in that crash with my friends.
So you're telling me that I'm next?
You said someone else died last night.
That means someone
must have intervened.
Officer Burke pulled me away
from the crash that killed my friends.
Congratulations.
You'll be the last to go.
But don't worry,
once the others are dead,
it'll come back for you.
It always does.
This doesn't make sense.
You said that you die in the order
you're originally meant to.
But my friends died last
in my premonition,
not first.
Wait.
Dead last?
Backwards.
Are you sure?
In my premonition that Nora woman
and her kid died.
Then Evan,
then me and my friends.
Why is this even happening to me?
That's what Alex used to ask himself.
So, what am I supposed to do?
Clear.
Watch out for the signs.
What?
Have you ever seen,
anything creepy or ominous?
An in your face irony kind of thing?
The songs on the radio.
Yeah, the guy in the beer truck,
everything on the road.
Well, don't ignore it.
Recognizing those signs usually means
the difference between life and death.
You got to help me.
I don't have to do anything.
But you beat it.
Take a look around.
What did I beat, Kimberly?
If you were smart, you'd save yourself
and just forget about the others.
How can you say that?
You have a responsibility.
My friends are dead.
That's how I can say that.
And this is what happened to Alex
when I was responsible for him.
Get out.
Before you hurt me or yourself.
Alright, you know what?
What?
I think you're a coward.
You hide out in here because
you're too damn
bitter and selfish
to help any other person.
In my opinion, you're already dead.
I tried calling you last night,
but your father said you were sleeping.
Evan Lewis is dead.
Yeah.
I've been getting calls all morning
from everyone who was on the on ramp.
We're meeting tonight at my apartment.
Wait, so...
you believe all this death stuff?
Well at first, no I didn't.
Until last year when I was dispatched
to clean up one of the flight 180 survivors.
Clean up, I don't...
did you see that?
See what?
Pigeons.
Pigeons?
It's a sign.
A sign of what?
If Clear's right about the order then I...
Nora and Tim,
are going to be attacked by pigeons.
I'm not following you.
They're next on Death's list.
If we don't find them,
they're going to die.
The doctor's ready for you now.
If he gives me the gas and I wake up
with my pants unbuttoned.
We ain't paying.
Tim.
Shit.
There you are.
What happened to you yesterday, Tim?
We missed you in here.
We got hung up by
that accident on route 23.
Good lord.
How lucky that you're ok.
Your mom says you've been
having some pain lately.
Not really.
I'm a bit disappointed, Tim.
Does your mom know
you've been smoking?
Yeah, that one's going
to have to be filled.
Damn those pigeons.
How many times am I going to have
to replace those goddamn windows?
We can't do it, boss,
we can't do it!
This will only sting for a moment.
Open big.
Little bit wider.
Wider.
Ok.
God.
How do they expect me to...
Would you rather
just have the laughing gas?
Yeah.
Ok.
Jean, I'm going to need you in here.
You're have to speak up,
there's too much noise.
What?
I can't hear you!
Excuse me, what?
Yes, the sixth at 2:00 P.M.
Jean!
Let me get this started.
Tim you'll be awake,
and a little groggy,
but you're not going
to be able to move much.
Ok great, thanks.
Alright, turn around.
The cleaning lady said they're at the
Ellis Medical Complex off of 14th.
Goddamn it anyway.
Ok, I got it.
I can't find a box!
Not again. Careful.
There we go.
Jean, how is Tim doing in there?
What did he say about your tooth?
Did he say...
I can't remember.
Nora!
The pigeons!
What?
Pigeons?
Kid, kid!
Come on! Hey!
No!
Tim!
Look out!
Stay back, stay back!
No!
Please, no!
Nora's not coming.
She won't leave her son.
No, but she's next...
Right now I don't think she cares.
This is really happening again, isn't it?
I hoped we'd get there and...
they'd be fine,
and Clear Rivers was just full of shit,
and Evan Lewis' death
was just some freak accident.
But we're all going to die, aren't we?
I'm so scared.
I know you didn't ask for any of this
But I don't think you have it
in you to quit either.
A second one just died.
A 15 year old kid.
I hope you're ready for this.
It's this way.
How is this guy going to help us anyway?
He seemed to know a hell
of a lot more about death,
than he ever told us.
Shouldn't we knock first?
He probably already knows we're coming.
Hello, Clear.
I've been expecting you.
Oh my God.
That's Evan Lewis.
Come to pick my brain?
Just a simple question and we'll leave
you alone with your new friend.
Dead...
yet still...
fresh.
Look.
We drove a long way to get here,
so if you happen to know how
to stop the death,
it would be really great if you told us.
You can't cheat Death.
There are no escapes.
Bullshit.
You told me Death has a distinct design.
But Alex and I cheated Death
not once but dozens of times.
The design is flawed,
it can be beaten.
Such fire in you now.
People are always most alive
just before they die.
Don't you think?
Look, please
If you know of anything
that could help us,
what harm could it do?
Only new life can defeat Death.
What the hell does that mean?
Some people say
there's a balance to everything.
For every life there's a death,
and for every death there is a life.
But the introduction of life
that was not meant to be,
that can invalidate the list,
force Death,
to start a new.
You have to follow the signs
Kimberly.
How do you know my name?
Hey, wait a second.
New life defeats Death?
Follow the signs?
Where did you find that guy?
I thought he was supposed to help us,
not freak us out.
What the fuck are you thinking?
I'm thinking suck on my junk, bee-atch.
Little punk.
What is it?
What did you see?
You have to tell us,
what did you see?
Kimberly, look at me!
You have to tell us.
What did you see?
I was driving a white van and...
Or I must have lost control,
because I crashed into a lake and...
And I drowned.
You were there?
I can practically taste
the water in my mouth.
Wait, remember, the on-ramp?
There was a pregnant woman
in a white delivery van.
He said only new life can defeat Death.
If she gives birth to a baby
that would've died in that car crash
a brand new soul that was never
part of Death's design
it throws the whole list out of whack
and we start over with a clean slate.
It seems like a bit of a reach,
don't you think?
What else could it mean?
We have to find
the pregnant lady's number.
I don't have it.
She never came to the station.
We have to find her and warn her about the
lake so she can stay alive to have the baby.
That'll be an easy conversation to have.
How are we gonna find her?
There could be thousands
of white vans in the state.
Hey!
I'm a cop, remember?
Wait, that's it.
Got it.
With the plate number
I can put out an APB.
Here we go.
The vehicle is a delivery van
registered to Marcus
and Isabella Hudson.
We should pick them up pretty quickly.
Come on, let's get to the meeting.
Hey, hold the door!
Hey, let go of my shoe!
Give me my shoe!
I wrote to management two weeks ago
about these frigging bumpers.
Is that dogshit, dude?
Oh, you got something on your...
It's still there, bro.
Here, I can get it for you.
No it's... it's alright.
I'll do it if you want me to do it.
Just let...
I'll let me do it.
What?
Hey, man, how you doing?
Listen, any word on that white van yet?
Ok, keep checking.
Does anybody have a valium?
Oh, yeah.
Here.
You're just going to want
to take half of that.
Keep them coming.
If what you're saying is true,
that means I'm next.
This is crazy people, come on.
First Death is stalking us,
and now premonitions, is what?
You're not next, Nora.
Nobody has to be next.
That's the point.
We need to help each other
in order to get through this.
This cannot be happening.
See, because my career is at a peak
and I finally met a quality guy.
I just bought a house.
Maybe if you shut the fuck up, you'll live.
Like I'm going to take advice from you.
Ok, look,
if you know what to look
for you have a fighting chance.
If, I call and say...
I don't know, subway.
Get to a high rise fast.
A place where no subway
could ever possibly go.
Get it?
Ok, you guys listen,
just because Kimberly has these visions,
it doesn't mean we're not all capable
of seeing signs to some extent.
Ok, ok, look.
I gotta call bullshit.
I mean, I've sat here and listened
to all your theories and all your stories,
and I think it's just all bullshit.
Call it what you want!
It'll keep your ass alive.
Darling, my ass is alive!
Has been all day.
There is nobody after us but you,
trying to make us all crazy.
I should have seen that coming.
Yeah.
If Death is out to get you,
why don't you get
the hell away from us?
She's the only one
that's dealt with this before.
We need to look out
for each other from now on.
Sleep in shifts.
We need to safe proof this deathtrap.
Get you to step out of the van, miss?
Are you kidding me?
What did I do?
This vehicle's been reported stolen.
Screw this.
I'm going for a smoke.
No, no, no, it's not safe out there.
So, Nora's got to bite it
before me anyhow?
Oh, you people have no sense of humor.
Nora,
you ok?
Four years ago my husband died.
Now Tim.
There's nothing left for me.
Don't say that, ok?
If it is my time to go and be in heaven
with my family, I can accept that.
You got to trust me, ok.
We can fight this.
If we just stick together long enough
for her to have her baby...
if you'll excuse me,
I have a funeral to plan.
Nora.
What do you think you're doing?
I'm finished. I'm out.
I mean don't leave, Eugene.
Look, look.
I control my life, alright?
Not some crazy list Death
has put together.
I'll be sure to carve that
into your tombstone.
Whatever, you may be able
to scare these people,
but I'm not buying that shit.
Be careful, man.
Hey?
What?
Even if you don't believe,
give this to Nora.
I'm just going to put this in the...
Closet.
Sorry.
Man with hooks?
Man with hooks.
Hey,
I think I see a man with hooks.
Is that
A sign?
Oh my God.
Do you guys see that?
He's right.
The phone.
Shit.
What the fuck?
Hello?
Nora!
Who is this?
Nora, can you hear me?
O... Officer Burke, I can't, I...
I can't hear you! What?
What does he what?
A man with hooks is going to kill you.
What, what?
What is it Nora?
No!
Wait, wait!
Let go!
Wait, wait, Nora!
Get me out of here!
Will you stop it?
Let me help!
Let me go!
Let go of me!
Kat!
Help me!
Wait!
I don't want to die!
Alright good, I got it, thanks.
They found the van.
Isabella's being held at the
Greenwood Lake Sheriff's station.
Kiss my ass!
Eugene, what is it?
I control my life!
What happened, Eugene?
You hear me, you reaper cocksucker?
Calm down.
What happened?
Where's Nora?
Back up! Back up! Back up!
Back the fuck up!
Ok!
Eugene, what's wrong man?
Just tell us what happened.
Alright, give me the gun, Eugene.
Give me the gun.
No! Fuck no!
It's your Eugene.
You just got to relax, bro, ok?
You just got to calm down, man.
Give me the gun.
Give me the gun, Eugene!
No!
No, no, no, no, no!
Don't do it! Don't do it!
I ain't going out like that.
Hey, Eugene, Eugene, no!
On my terms!
Hey!
Oh my God!
You hear me or not?
God!
You don't keep it loaded?
Maybe they're all duds.
Six in a row?
Never.
That's impossible.
It wasn't his turn to die.
Can we find the pregnant
woman now please?
Is this safe, guys?
I mean,
someone in this car
is about to get whacked, right.
Do the rest of us really feel
like sitting next to him?
Or her?
Hopefully her.
Ok, guys, let's not panic.
Isabella's safe.
How do you know?
When you said she was going
to drive into a lake.
How can she if she's in protective custody?
Look at me.
Come on.
Does it look like I'm in the condition
to commit grand theft auto,
this is insane.
Look,
hopefully the district judge will have
it all sorted out by Monday morning,
ok?
Marcus.
When I get out of here,
I am going to sue his.
Oh my God.
What,
what now?
My water just broke.
What?
My water, it just broke.
I'm gonna have my baby.
No, not here.
No, you can't do this to me.
Don't just stand there!
Get me to a hospital!
Give me a second to think!
I am not going to have
my baby in a jail cell!
Get me to the hospital!
Ok, ok!
Sheriff Perry, this is
Deputy Adams, come back.
God, I need the car!
Sheriff Perry, I need the car!
My van! My van!
Take my van!
Ok. ok.
Yeah, we'll go.
We'll go.
Come on, come on!
You all want to hear something crazy?
It's not the first time I cheated Death.
A kid came to school,
with a knife
killed his teacher.
Teacher would have been me,
but I was transferred
to another school two days before.
That's fucking weird, man.
You want weird?
Last year my partner
and I were heading out
when a call came in about a train wreck.
Frank decided to let me handle it alone.
He died that night in a shootout.
If that call had come in
just 10 seconds later,
I'd be dead, too.
Oh my God.
I'm sorry.
It's just I got one, too.
Ok, so last may I'm supposed
to go and stay
at this cheesy little bed
and breakfast in Pennsylvania right.
So anyhow, there's this major gas leak
no one knows about,
and all the guests
suffocated during the night.
So what happened?
I don't know. I never made it.
The bus I was on splattered
some girl over the road.
Was that in Mt. Abraham?
Yes.
How did you know?
That bus you were on
killed Terry Chaney.
She was supposed to die on flight 180.
Hey,
do you guys remember
that theater in Paris
that collapsed last year
and killed everybody inside?
Well, I had tickets to go.
But one night I'm in Paris and...
I'm just tripping on acid and...
sipping lattes and such and...
And then all of a sudden,
this dude...
out of nowhere just gets,
whacked by this falling sign.
Carter.
Wait, wait, wait.
The teacher I replaced,
her name was Val Lewton.
She was from Mt. Abraham.
She died in an explosion.
Shit.
The call about the train
wreck that saved my life.
That was the night
I scraped up Billy Hitchcock.
Wait a minute.
Who are these people?
The people who got off of flight 180.
They were my friends.
Kimberly,
tell us what happened.
About a year ago
my mom and I were at the mall.
I was supposed to meet her outside, but...
I got caught up
watching this news report
about some kid that committed suicide.
I kept thinking,
how can you strangle
yourself in the bathtub?
That's stupid.
Alright, it felt wrong.
And yet...
I heard...
some gunshots and I ran outside.
Some kids were trying
to steal my mom's car.
She tried to fight them off,
she was a fighter and...
they killed her.
After the funeral I...
kept thinking
that it should have been me.
I guess everyone must think that.
But I guess I was right.
Get there.
Could you drive a little faster maybe?
I'm going as fast as I can.
God!
When we got off flight 180,
it didn't just change our lives.
It affected everyone
and everything we've come
into contact with since.
I'm not sure I'm understanding you.
Being alive after we were supposed to die,
it caused an outward ripple.
A rift in Death's design.
So...
if you had never gotten off the plane.
We wouldn't be alive in the first place.
Yes, that's why Death
is working backwards!
It's tying up all the loose ends,
sealing the rift once and for all.
Oh, shit!
Jesus Christ!
Hang on! Hang on!
Is everybody alright?
Oh God.
God, Eugene!
He can't breathe.
Oh, my legs!
No, please.
It's not going to wait.
I got to go help those people.
Do you want to deliver this baby?
Those people can help.
Let's go.
Officer Adams reporting a vehicle collision
off 9-A at the 180 mile-marker.
Send all emergency vehicles to the scene.
Go! Go.
Ok, ok, ok!
Go!
Ok. We're going! We're going!
Take it easy, take it easy.
Here, here, here, here, here.
I think he has a collapsed lung.
Everyone ok?
Call an ambulance!
Stay with us.
Hey, hey you!
Hey!
Come on.
Help me out.
You got to get me out of here before
this thing explodes or something, ok?
I think it's ok.
I don't smell any gas
and nothing is dripping.
Alright, get this thing off me.
Just pull. Hurry.
Ok. Be careful.
Ready?
OK
Ok.
God, Jethro!
Jesus Christ!
I got to be able to use
my legs when I'm done.
I'm so... Dad!
Eugene, everything's going to be ok.
Just keep doing.
If he doesn't get a respirator,
is gonna to make it.
We're going to get you to the hospital.
Hey be careful with that!
Check the gauges on the regulator,
and watch out for overdoses!
And look out for potholes and puddles.
You can't come in, miss.
And watch out for power lines!
Watch it!
You trying to get yourself killed, little boy?
You got to use your head, man.
Thanks.
See right away.
Ok, let's go.
How is she doing?
I think she's going to be ok.
Can I ask you a question?
Yeah.
When I die...
Is it going to hurt?
I don't know.
You're going to die after me, right?
Yeah, I guess so.
Would you take these?
And if I die...
Will you throw out all my drugs and...
my paraphernalia and my porno?
Just... You know.
Anything that's going
to break my mom's heart.
Please?
Thank you.
This is Cheyenne Jacobson
reporting live from the Gibbons Farm.
Sheriff Perry, officer Burke here, listen.
I'm trying to get some
information on Isabella Hu...
she did?
Ok.
Thanks. Great.
Kimberly!
Isabella's at Lakeview Hospital.
They're prepping her for delivery.
We got to go now.
What about Kat?
I'll go talk to her.
Hi.
Just find Isabella
and get this thing over with, ok?
Go on, I'll be fine.
Where's Rory?
I don't know.
Could you be a little quieter
with that thing, please?
Yeah, sure.
I'll just put it on quiet mode.
That would be good.
Rory.
Oh my God!
Somebody get out there!
We have to get to the hospital now!
Well, take my truck!
The keys are in it.
Kimberly!
Kimberly.
What do you see?
What are we looking for?
It's not here.
This one was different.
It was like the van crashing into the lake.
I was in a hospital I...
there was screaming
and a nurse was trying to choke me.
I couldn't see her,
but I could see her name tag.
Right in my face.
Kalarjian.
I think a nurse named Kalarjian
is going to try and kill Isabella.
Listen to me, Isabella!
I need you to stop pushing!
What's wrong?
Is my baby alright?
The cord's around the neck.
This baby's in trouble.
A bizarre accident
has left two people dead,
one of them killed by a safety
device meant to protect us.
Ironically, the woman was impaled
through the head
after her emergency airbag deployed.
She was trapped in her vehicle
after it crashed into a field near greenwood lake.
Suddenly the airbag went off
Isabella Hudson!
What room is she in?
We may need to do a stat caesarean!
Get Dr. Kalarjian up here now!
Dr. Kalarjian, code blue.
Delivery room six.
I'm just going to wait outside,
because I'm just really in the way here.
Don't you dare leave me!
Ok, ok.
You guys, get to Isabella!
I'm going to find Eugene!
Dr. Kalarjian, code blue.
Delivery room six.
Dr. Kalarjian, delivery room six.
Code blue.
Dr. Kalarjian, in here, hurry!
That's her.
Wait, wait, wait!
Contractions have stopped.
Arrest in descent halfway
through the birth canal.
Bad tracing, it's losing oxygen.
The cord's compressed!
Down to 40.
Oh God!
What's happening?
Where's Kalarjian?
Dr. Kalarjian!
Not now, I'm busy.
Hey! Hey!
Police business.
Just push a little more.
Oh, no.
Isabella, is the baby ok?
I'm sorry.
You can't be here.
I'm going to have to ask you to leave.
I need to know
I need to know if the baby's alright!
It's a boy.
Thank you.
Congratulations!
Who the hell are they?
Oh my God!
Clear.
I can't find Eugene.
No, don't worry. She had the baby!
It's ok.
It's over.
Kimberly.
What did you see?
I don't think Isabella was ever
supposed to die in that pileup.
Then what's the premonition
of the lake supposed to be?
Try to remember.
Bloody hands.
Someone with bloody hands.
Eugene.
Only new life defeats Death.
What is that supposed to mean?
You saw an ecg machine and what else?
Bloody hands.
What else did you see, Kimberly?
Wait.
Eugene.
Oh God, no!
Bloody hands.
It's me.
The premonitions are about me.
What?
Crash cart.
Let's go! Move it!
Dr. Kalarjian.
ECG machine.
The lake.
The white van.
What are you talking about?
Kimberly.
New life.
What is it?
I know what I have to do
to save us.
I have to die.
No, no, no. That's, that's crazy.
You can't give up now.
We have to fight this thing.
Get Kalarjian.
Only new life can defeat Death.
If it is my time to go and be in heaven,
with my family.
I can accept that.
Flight 180
I know what I have to do to save us.
There are no known survivors.
I have to die.
Ready and clear.
Nothing.
Come on. Ready.
Clear.
She's back!
Epinephrine. Two milligrams, IV push.
I want her prepped
and stabilized for ICU.
Welcome back.
They lost you for a minute there.
Hey.
We did it.
Thanks to you, we cheated Death.
Would you like some wine?
I think I'll stick to our beer, thanks.
Alright.
This is really great, Mrs. Gibbons.
Thank you so much for inviting us.
It's our pleasure.
How are you doing, Kimberly?
Good.
Yeah...
I had a fun summer.
I don't know, I guess things are
pretty much getting back to normal.
Brian, I think you better
go check that barbecue.
Hey, careful.
Those things are dangerous.
Trust me.
I think I've been through closer calls.
Yeah, me too.
Dad, you should tell them
about the news van thing.
What's that?
Brian was almost hit by that,
news van that day in the field.
And your friend Rory,
he pulled him back at the last second.
Saved his life.
You never told me that Peter.
Boy, that was lucky.
Brian!
By LESAIGNEUR
Sync & corrections January 2022