Oh, man!
Did you see that?
Oh, my God.
Yes! Yes!
Nice, nice, nice.
Sick!
Worth the wait.
Oh, babe. You missed out.
Yes!
That was intense, man.
To feel how that would be
to just crash and burn like that.
Yeah, maybe for you but our lives
are actually going somewhere.
Ok, well, where we gotta go
is to the roller coaster.
Because our pass is for 9:15.
If we miss that, we'll stand in line
for like a day and a half,
and that's gonna kill me.
Ok!
Alright?
So let's go.
Ok. Come on,
it won't kill us to get
a deep fried Snickers and a Coke.
Before riding Devil's Flight?
Yeah, that might kill me.
No! What doesn't kill you,
makes you stronger, man.
I'll take that.
No. Come on, give me.
It's not even mine, Kevin.
It's the yearbook's.
Just Kevin.
Got it.
Oh, my God, you're such an idiot.
Hey. Hey. Give me the...
Nice.
Could you like,
please delete that one of Stacy?
These are for the yearbook.
And I have to turn them in tomorrow
to make a deadline
and like I doubt it
if a shot of
Stacy Kobayashi's camel toe
is gonna make it in there.
I'd buy two.
Number 38, your order's ready.
That's us.
I am so sorry.
Kevin can get so out of control.
Let me just say
he would make me crazy.
I mean, you know,
I'm such a control freak like...
I couldn't handle that.
I'm breaking up with him.
Couple of weeks.
After graduation.
I've been wanting to for a while.
But don't tell anybody, ok?
Now, that shot there?
That'll sell some yearbooks.
I love it.
Oh, alright, so I'm a total whore.
Come on, go, go, go,
go, go, go go!
Oh, my God, Ashley, you're winning.
You're totally winning.
Am I winning?
Yeah, come on, hurry!
Ok, come on, come on,
come on, come on!
Am I winning? look around,
I don't want to look.
You're totally winning.
Come on, come on, come on!
Don't look! Oh, my God! Come on!
I'm winning! I'm winning!
I won!
I knew you would.
Oh, my God!
Give me my prize.
That was so awesome, Ashley.
Good job.
Ashley.
How you doing, my brother?
You having a good time?
You like that?
Yeah! You like it.
Give it up. Give it up.
Sam!
Excuse me.
You're not a senior.
And what are you gonna do about
Miss Cutest Couple, Rah Rah?
Mom know you're here?
You are a complete bitch
if you tell her.
Proof.
Where you were.
Take a shot of this.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's three.
♪ That is three, number three ♪
♪ Oh, I'm the man, I'm the man ♪
♪ Man, I am hot. ♪
Man, give me some right here, man.
Right here! Right here!
What you doing?
Get the fuck back.
My God, I am good.
Here we go.
Boy, I'll tell ya. Goddamn.
Here we go, baby.
3 for 3. It's all mine.
Here we go. Here we go.
Big prize. Watch out.
Come on.
♪ That's what I'm talking about ♪
We gonna get that one.
You want that blue one?
That's the one we gonna get.
You can run,
but you cannot hide.
Yes!
Here we are, baby.
There it is.
Awesome.
Here, get a pic of this.
This is the beginning of the end.
Hey, guys, get in line.
What's wrong?
I'm...
I was having that feeling
like déjà vu, you know?
Except for...
something that hasn't happened yet.
Hey, J.
Come on man, let's go.
Yeah, yeah, hold on.
Come on.
What, are you weirded out by the ride?
Because look I know you.
And I think that maybe...
you're nervous about this
roller coaster because
they say the real fear with these rides
comes from the feeling
of having no control.
Everyone imagines weird stuff
when they get scared.
But it never turns out
to be what they imagine.
Never.
Ok.
You can run, but you cannot hide.
Where you guys are right now
if you raise your hands it's just...
cup them slightly...
it'll look you're holding
the devil's balls.
And we'd wanna do that why?
When else you ever gonna see
a dick that big?
I'm looking at one right now.
Man, you guys are smoking hot.
Get out, Frankie.
Yeah, why are you even here?
Yeah, you graduated, like two years ago.
I stuck around to monitor
your development.
Good to go.
Good to go, baby.
Let's do it. Let's do it.
Come on. Come on.
You may never return
from Devil's Flight.
You're totally sad.
Try not to scream!
That was totally awesome!
Yeah! Sweet!
You alright?
There's nothing to worry about.
A roller coaster is just elemental physics.
A conversion of potential energy
to kinetic energy.
Yep, odds are like one in 250 million
of dying in a roller coaster.
Yeah, thanks for that, McKinley.
You're more likely to die,
driving to an amusement park than.
Dying at one.
Here we go.
You like this?
Won it on the Wacky Ladder.
You know that ladder deal that wobbles?
Took it.
I like this.
It's old school.
Frankie Cheeks is old school, ladies.
What's that?
Well, it'd be my honor.
Let's go.
Hey... Baby.
How many?
Four.
Four?
Yeah.
Gate one.
Yeah. Front car.
Yes!
No. No, wait please.
I'm sorry, I don't wanna be a hassle.
I just, I can't sit in the front.
I cannot see the tracks. I'll freak.
Ok.
Take it easy.
Ok, we'll sit in the back
are you right babe?
Why me? Because we're girls?
Fuck that. I'm going to Berkeley
and I won't get to do this for a while.
I'm sitting in the front.
J, just go, ok? I'll live.
You're not gonna sit by yourself.
Alright, you know what?
We'll just settle this like real men.
How about that? Call it.
Heads.
Shit! Damn it.
Alright, fine, what the fuck.
It's the same ride, right?
Go. Go ahead. Bye, babe.
Hey, just do me a favor.
Keep an eye on her, ok?
She's kinda freaked out.
Oh. Cool.
Alright?
Yeah. Boom, buddy.
No problem.
Here we go.
Hey!
J! Keep your hands to yourself, man.
I'm serious.
You know, payback's a bitch, ok?
You know, she might need
some comforting...
and I'll be there for her. ok?
Hey, no! No.
Get out. Get out.
Hey! Find another cockpit,
Top Gun.
No. Get...
Let's just get in the back, ok?
Guess who's back?
Hey!
I'll meet you at the end.
Here! Alright!
Cool!
Hey.
How'd you guys get in here?
What? I'm 55 inches.
Sure. Come on out.
Oh, man.
You, too. Out.
Ready?
You ok?
Come on. Here we go.
Yeah!
What's up, man? I'm good.
Dare you to, flash me them sweet,
sweet titties when we go through the loop.
Alright.
Yo!
What, you can't read?
Can I just put it in my pocket, man?
Is that cool?
Yeah.
Yeah? Cool.
Thanks, buddy. Sorry.
Shit!
Here you go!
Win, baby! Yes, baby! Win!
Come on!
Come on. Get hyped.
The first hill's so high.
This is what we need!
Let's do this!
Just win!
Shit!
Oh, man.
Oh, my God!
Here we go!
Yeah! Show me your titties!
Fuck off, Frankie!
Oh, shit!
Oh, my God!
We're gonna fall off!
No!
Kevin!
Erin, hang on!
Erin!
Hang on!
Don't let go!
I can't.
No!
Oh, God!
Hang on, Wen.
Hang on! Help me rock it!
Almost got it!
Gently.
No!
Yo. What, you can't read?
Oh, well. I'll just...
I'll put it in my pocket, ok?
Yeah.
Thanks, bro.
Alright.
Let's do this, Wen...
What're you...
Here you go!
Yeah! Let's do it, baby!
We have to get off of here.
No, don't push the button!
Don't! Don't push the button!
Let me off! Let me off!
Wen, Wen! It's alright.
Jesus, it's gonna be over...
No! It's gonna crash!
It's gonna crash!
Wendy?
The hydraulics will rupture!
The tracks'll collapse! Please!
What's going on?
Let me off!
Chick's on something.
It's alright! You'll be ok!
Ok, let them out. Just the back.
Wen. Hey! Wendy!
Relax. Now, what's the matter?
I saw it. I saw it in my head.
The tracks collapsed.
The roller coaster crashed.
No, she was just a little upset before.
Man, please, can you please
control that bitch?
Damn.
It's gonna crash!
The hydraulics, the coaster!
Man, she's just trying to get
some fucking attention.
You know what?
You're a real piece of shit, Lewis.
Fuck you.
Fuck moi?
No, man, fuck you!
Don't touch me.
Just relax!
Fight, man!
Hey. Hey. Let me out.
Nobody else gets off this ride!
Dude, let me off.
So high school.
Let's out.
Calm down!
Get off of him!
Relax!
Ian!
Where you ladies going?
There's a fight.
Get him out of here!
Relax hey!
Calm down! Relax!
Dude, let me off.
I gotta make sure she's ok.
Relax! Calm down!
♪ Hey! Ho! ♪
Get out of here!
♪ Let's go! ♪
Come on!
♪ Hey! Ho! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
Let me out!
♪ Hey! Ho! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
Dude!
♪ Hey! Ho! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
Here we go!
♪ Hey! Ho! ♪
♪ Let's go! ♪
Dude, that's my girlfriend!
Oh, my God!
Fuck.
Stop it! No! Stop it!
Stop it! Please!
Please, the tracks are broken.
Stop!
Stop! Please!
Jason!
Hey, just relax, ok?
Please!
Ease up, man. She's alright.
Ok? Just let her settle down.
She can settle down at home!
Now listen.
What is your home phone number?
Ok, we're gonna call your mother.
Everything will be taken care of...
Oh, my God!
Jason!
Hey, Wendy!
Hey!
Wait!
Wendy!
Hey! Hey, Wen.
Wait I need, I need to talk to you
about something.
Just here to pick up my diploma.
You're not going to graduation?
No.
Look, you're not the only one
in a fucked up place.
Ok?
God I mean,
I just thought maybe,
it'd be good for you to be somewhere...
where other people feel the same way.
At graduation?
No.
Thanks. I've had enough funerals.
Then do it for J and Carrie.
Do what?
If you die, then there's nothing
then you're just dead,
and they don't know.
And if they are up in Heaven
with Lincoln and Gandhi
do you think they really care about
our high school graduation? No.
I am alive and I don't care.
As soon as I pull out of that
parking lot I am so out of McKinley.
Without J, what's here for me?
I'm here. ok?
I made a promise to J that
I would take care of you.
On the ride.
For 3 minutes.
You weren't making
the promise for a lifetime.
Kevin,
if it wasn't for you and J being friends,
and me and Carrie being friends...
we wouldn't have even hung out.
We don't even like each other.
Ian McKinley.
How pathetic is it that my last name...
is the same as my high school?
Julie, look who I got to sign my yearbook.
No way. Nice.
Yeah.
I think we should invite her.
You think?
Yeah.
Wen?
So we're ready for graduation tonight,
we're going to the tanning salon after this,
and we are so totally cool
if you wanna come with.
Totally.
And just like, talk if you want.
Here's my cell.
I already have your number.
That was so nice of us.
You're not alone.
God, I appreciate
everyone trying to help.
Ok? I really do.
No, it's happened before.
Ok? I went online looking for
an explanation about...
Wendy, just, just listen to me alright?
Alright, look, I went online
looking for an explanation
about what happened,
and I found out about this high
school French class,
from New York, six years ago...
they went on a trip to Paris.
When they were boarding...
a kid had a vision,
that the plane was gonna explode.
Just like you did.
He freaked out...
and seven people got off the plane.
Just like us.
And on takeoff,
Flight 180 blew up.
And over the next several months,
everyone who got off that plane,
started dying in weird accidents.
They died in the order they would've
if they had stayed on the plane.
Unless someone intervened,
then it skipped them.
Fuck you, Kevin.
Wendy! Wendy! Hey!
Every time we come here.
I was thinking of going
for 20 minutes in the Muller.
We did that for all the funerals
and it turned out amazing.
Yeah, but that was just
a couple of weeks ago, though.
I mean we're still pretty bronzed.
I was just thinking
we could go for like a tune-up.
I just wanna make sure
that we look our best.
Yeah.
You know, for all those kids
that died that night
who will never get a graduation.
You know what?
You're totally right.
I'm sorry.
This is my,
my good guy luck bracelet
that Grandma left me in her will.
Julie?
I need...
I could use some help.
I have such...
such guilt over Jason.
I should never have let that ride go.
God.
I'm usually such a control freak
but I didn't...
do enough to stop it,
I should've done everything I could,
to stop it.
And I would give anything,
to have a second chance.
But I never can.
I don't want to some day
feel that way about you, Julie.
I mean, I can't talk to Mom and Dad.
You're all I have left.
You think when I find a place maybe you
could come stay with me for a while?
You know I will.
You...
keep this now...
and...
I'll get it when I come see you.
And... Hey...
how about on your end?
Can I use the school camera
for graduation tonight?
Yeah.
As long as you bring it back
to school on Monday.
Done.
Actually, the battery is pretty low so...
why don't you go get ready,
and I'll recharge it a bit.
Cool.
In a hurry, Yuri.
Sorry, sorry.
Cell phone signal is shit in here.
I think tanning beds mess with signal.
I must go outside.
Why don't you just use that phone?
I would but, she talks forever,
then my boss gives me shit.
Shit. That's her.
You know what just go outside.
We can deal with this ourselves.
Ok.
Hey.
No drinks in the room this time, ok?
Good.
What are you doing?
Nobody is walking in here
and seeing me naked.
Oh, my God.
Dude, he said no drinks.
If you spill that shit we're gonna
have to clean it up like last time.
Happy, beyotch?
Nothing to spill.
Why does Yuri keep it so cold in here?
Maybe it's supposed to be colder
for the machines or whatever.
A few degrees won't hurt.
Shit! I forgot my iPod.
Sucks, bitch.
They got CDs.
Dion Celine?
Britney?
Dude, are we like the only cool people
that come here or what?
Yeah.
Whatever.
Why are you wearing underwear?
Steinmetz says he gets off on tan lines.
Alright.
Camera charged?
Sorry, the battery's totally dead.
Camera's not working. Sorry.
Look Julie, I need a minute, ok?
Like private.
It's way too warm in here now?
I fucked up.
I set it too hot in here.
Hello?
Hey, Ashley, it's Wendy...
Psych! Leave a message.
Hi Ashley, this is Wendy.
Give me a call whenever
you guys are done.
And thanks again for the invite.
Someone help!
Sorry I was too late.
Hey, open the door!
Help me!
We may feel...
that our lives are not our own.
That Death controls,
frames our lives.
Our birth's nothing but death begun.
Yet, whether it is with
this tragic loss of young lives.
Which we have suffered much of late...
or with the soft...
passing of the elderly in the night...
we are all...
equal...
in Death's eyes.
Equal...
in Death's eyes?
All of us?
How can you say that?
Shut up, McKinley.
Dude, think it through.
Charlie Manson made it to 70.
Osama? Still kicking.
Let's go.
Pimps,
vice-presidents walking around.
All the atrocities...
Let's just go. Come on.
They've committed,
They're alive and well.
These two girls,
who'd never done shit to anybody,
they don't get to make it to 18?
Where's the fucking equality in that?
What?
Come on, man.
Yeah.
Fine.
Fine. Alright. Alright.
I'm fine. Alright.
That's crazy.
Those of you who would like
to pay a final remembrance,
please step forward at this time.
I so feel this is so my fault.
How could it possibly be your fault?
Seeing women as nothing
but fun bags.
I mean,
if I'd've seen their...
whatever,
humanity...
they wouldn't have felt
the pressure to look so good.
Impress Franklin Cheeks.
Go on diets.
Deodorize.
Stretch.
Tan.
Don't be down, Frankie.
Be proud of your ability to make everything
that happens somehow a story about you.
God!
Yo, man.
These things really suck, man.
Fucking boring.
Hey, if you ever have
to come to my funeral...
man, bring me a PSP or something.
At least I have something to do then.
Hello?
I'm with J.
What are you doing up here
in the nosebleeds?
You know, I could've
gotten you second row.
I didn't want to upset
anyone by being there.
And I wondered if
maybe here I could feel J's...
spirit or presence or...
whatever.
But now that I'm here...
if there's any place that makes me feel
like there's no life after death...
it's a cemetery.
Yeah, I haven't felt Carrie's spirit either.
And I've tried.
Real hard.
I thought maybe...
he's been with me since...
that night,
before I got on the ride...
Jason said...
God and it was just to get me
on the ride he said.
Your fear...
is from a sense of having no control.
And I've felt that fear
since the moment he said it.
Even thought it maybe somehow...
caused the hallucination.
But this fear is more
than just being scared.
It's like a presence.
Like a living thing,
always with me.
You think it's J?
No, I know it's not.
This presence is the opposite,
of how J made me feel.
It's cold...
and terrifying.
That's the last photograph
Lincoln posed for.
The photographic plate was broken
causing a line,
that can't be removed.
Exactly where he was shot.
Look.
See the shadow?
But what do these pictures
have to do with us?
Look.
This occurred one year to the day
of the Flight 180 disaster.
Look at the road sign.
Look, I guess you came
to me with this,
because I'm responsible
for putting this in your head
with the Flight 180 thing.
And it did happen,
and it may be occurring here
but you can't believe,
every weird thing out there because
you're desperate for an answer.
I took these.
That night.
These?
Are these it?
Oh, shit.
Oh shit.
Hey? You alright?
I'm feeling a little woozy.
When was the last time you ate?
I don't remember.
Alright. Come on I'll drive.
Ok, those kids,
on Flight 180,
died in accidents in the order they would've
died if they'd have stayed on the plane.
Ok?
So if this is that...
then...
then Frankie was behind
Ashlyn and Ashley.
When I saw Ashley and Ashlyn's
picture I felt this instinct.
Like there was a hint in the picture.
I even...
I even called to see if
I could keep them from going.
Well, what's Frankie's picture look like?
It's right here.
You got it?
Yeah.
Wait! Watch out!
Hey! Hey! Are you crazy?
Sorry!
Alright, let's just eat over there.
And go through the drive through.
I don't want anyone hearing
what we're talking about.
Well, it's nice to see that things haven't
made you any less of a control freak.
You got it?
Yeah, alright.
Here's Frank's picture.
Alright.
Well, this is obvious.
He's falling off a ladder.
A rope ladder, though.
Maybe he might hang.
Look, or maybe it's not that literal.
Alright, what's...
Could there be anything in these prizes?
Oh what, like he's gonna get
crushed by a giant Spongebob?
Hey, Spongebob lives underwater.
It's so sad that you know that.
Alright. He won that tacky mud-flap
girl chain on this game, though, so...
aren't those usually on
those big 18 wheelers?
Yeah. Yeah.
God, I don't see it in
this picture anywhere though.
Alright! God.
Alright.
Can I take your order?
Yeah.
What do you want?
Are you ok?
Please tell me
there's a short in your wiring.
That guy's way too close to my truck.
Hey, you're too fucking close, man!
Pull up!
Hey!
Stop! Stop!
Watch out! Shit!
What the fuck?
Oh, my God!
Get out! Get out!
What? What?
Behind us!
There's no one in that truck!
Shit! Hey!
Pull up, man!
Come on! Pull up!
Back up!
Watch your eyes!
Watch your eyes! Come here!
Come on. Let's go!
Come on, come on.
We're all done here.
You need a ride?
We can walk to my house then...
I'll give you a ride to yours.
No, thanks. We'll be ok.
Will we?
Yeah. We'll be alright.
I mean...
how Frank...
God, it's not only horrible
but can you feel...
can you feel how vicious it was?
Easy.
Ok? Easy.
Let's just...
just take a step back.
Alright? He was behind
Ashley and Ashlyn on the ride
but there was no ladder here.
You know there was no rope.
Nothing in that picture pointed to this.
We were wrong about the photos.
I should've left town.
It's better not knowing.
No, it's never better staying ignorant.
Willful ignorance is surrendering control.
What did you...
What did you read that somewhere
in Mrs. Brooks' English class?
No.
I, you know, I'm not...
I'm not the total idiot you think I am.
Ok, that's Lewis after Frank...
then lan and Erin.
There's a couple of kids behind them,
but I can't make them out...
because this guy's arm's in the way.
Can you?
No.
Alright you know what?
We'll ask Lewis,
lan and Erin if they remember.
Ok?
Are there any more pictures
from the roller coaster?
I guess...
that kind of thing is gonna happen
to us for the rest of our lives.
Yeah.
You know, I was gonna...
I was gonna ask her to marry me.
Right after graduation.
No, wait.
Look, behind Stacy.
That's Frank.
This picture shows how he died.
Alright, go back to Lewis.
Ok, he's got that hammer.
And the weight looks like
it's coming down...
on his head.
No, no, no, check this out right now.
Lewis is down at State
for football training camp.
State's team is called the Sultans.
That's it. That's the clue.
We have to tell him.
Show him these pictures.
Wouldn't you want to know?
Wait, there's pictures of us in there?
Yeah.
Yeah, of course.
No. No. I don't want to see mine.
No.
What about willful ignorance?
Well, I'm full of shit, alright?
I mean, I never thought I could see my
own death before it happened, Wendy.
No, you know what?
We can tell Lewis, but...
Seriously, if there's any way
to beat this thing...
I gotta stay focused and if I look at
that picture, all I'm gonna do is obsess.
So, you know what?
No, I don't want to see it.
I mean, unless we have to.
You mean until...
we have to.
One more thing.
Is it bad?
I mean, is it like,
painful or embarrassing?
I mean there's nothing like up my ass
or anything right?
I'll see you tomorrow.
You on crack.
Both of you.
Just listen.
Ok, Ashley and Ashlyn were first.
Then Frankie Cheeks and then you.
This is the...
Come on Kevin.
Listen.
McKinley and Erin
were next, alright?
And there were two people in front of us.
Do you remember who they were?
Fuck no and I don't care.
And you shouldn't care either man,
because what you're telling me
right now is straight bullshit.
Just listen Lewis.
Kevin, it's like those stories.
Like this guy was killed
by a car he sold 10 years ago.
Two sisters right,
were killed when they were driving
to visit each other.
You know shit like that man.
Fuck the Bruins!
Oh, yeah! Fuck the Bruins!
Bruin faggots!
Fuck the Bruins!
Yeah! Fuck the Bruins!
Man, you're reading into this shit
like them damn urban legends.
Three people have died, Lewis.
You think this can be written
off as a simple coincidence
and it ends there you're in serious denial.
What about you two?
What?
You both lost people real close
to you in a fucked-up way.
And in order to feel
less guilty or whatever,
seeing signs and patterns man.
I don't blame you.
But it's wrong dawg.
It's wrong.
That's denial.
Ok, what about what happened
at the roller coaster?
Wendy saw it.
Man she got a hunch.
Fucking intense, but she got a hunch.
Man I'm here because I get
good hunches before every down.
No, you know
they're either gonna run or pass.
Hers came to her from nowhere.
You're here and alive because of her.
No I'm alive because of me.
No listen.
You don't get it man.
Does that make sense to you?
There's nothing to get Kevin!
It's bullshit.
No just hear me out alright?
Talk about a vision.
Man I seen my whole life,
played out and it sure
as hell ain't gonna end now.
It's going just as I saw it.
35 high school games without an injury.
USA Today All-American.
Second team.
Free ride to play for the Sultans!
The Bruins passed on you.
Man fuck the Bruins!
Fuck them!
You goddamn right!
What the fuck is a Bruin anyway?
Four years from now,
Lewis Romero going in
the second round to Oakland.
He's gonna romp and stomp.
15 seasons, with four Super Bowl
rings on his fingers.
Lewis ain't afraid of no death.
Fuck Death!
Death is a fucking Denver fan.
Death wear blue and orange.
Real men wear black.
Lewis ain't afraid of no Death.
Death is afraid of me!
Death fears me!
Kevin.
Because baby I just win.
I just win Kevin!
That's all I know how to do!
I just win!
Fuck Death!
Fuck the Bruins!
Look out!
Lewis!
Man, that was close, Lewis.
Hey, did you see that?
What I tell you, Kevin,
Fuck Death! I just win!
That's all I know how to do Kevin.
Baby I just win!
God!
Did I do something...
to bring this on everybody?
Don't, Wendy.
But why me?
All those people out there
wanting to have a premonition,
or see a ghost or whatever,
and I don't.
I just want it to stop.
Just stop.
I don't know why, Wendy...
but you didn't do anything.
Alright?
This is just...
I don't know.
I mean I wish I knew why.
You know, I wish I could,
I could come up with a guess even...
to make you feel ok,
but...
I can't.
There's nothing I can do.
Can you drive?
You know, by the way,
that, that picture of me.
My...
my head's not like,
through the windshield or anything?
You know, crushed by a steering wheel?
Impaled by a gear shift?
Right?
Zip, it's Pip.
Have you cut those plywood orders yet?
That's a big no, Pip.
Osama bin Supervisor wants me
to get rid of these pigeons first.
They keep setting off the alarms.
Hello, babies.
Hey.
After I restock this stuff that these
pinhead customers
can't manage to return
to the shelves themselves
we can blow out of here, ok?
Righty-o, babe.
Erin!
It's Wendy and Kevin.
Shit!
You scared the shit out of me!
Yeah, wait till you hear
what we have to tell you.
Zip, it's Pip. Come over here.
You are gonna trip when you hear this.
Well, paint me intrigued, Pip.
I'm on my way.
So let me get this straight.
I'm gonna O.D. on nail polish
and lan is gonna be
embarrassed to death?
You saw what happened to Wendy.
Right? What's happened to the others?
We just saw their pictures.
Oh, my God guys, what's going on?
What's going on?
That's crazy!
We need to know who was sitting
behind you on the roller coaster.
Ok, who was sitting behind us
on the roller coaster?
Oh, wait! Wasn't it that one guy
who got voted most likely to become
manager at Red Lobster?
Oh, no. You know what?
God, I remember.
There was this guy,
black cloak I didn't see his face but...
the ride attendant did take his sickle...
before the ride started
if that's helpful in any way.
Do you think we care if you laugh at us?
This is our lives, ok?
What choice do we have?
Just give into it?
Oh, God. You know what?
There is no it.
Ok, wait, are you guys saying
that Death is like a person?
No. It's like, like a force.
Yeah. Well, you know what?
A force...
is just a force.
It's nothing else.
Just transferred energy.
I mean,
it has no goals,
no awareness that is a force.
But there is awareness, McKinley.
In fact in past cases,
if the next in line is saved
it'd skip that person.
That's why we're here.
Oh man, what have you been smoking?
Top shelf.
Ok.
Kevin!
Those banners.
They're in the picture.
Ian, watch those boxes!
What the fuck, man?
You said those boxes were falling!
No, I said watch the boxes.
Really? What for?
They're not doing anything.
We're not gonna apologize
for trying to save you.
You haven't seen or been through
what we have...
yet.
Yet.
Ok, so who's next in this theory
you have, me or lan?
Well, we know the order of how
we were sitting on the roller coaster
but not how it works
with people who sat together.
We don't know if Ashley
or Ashlyn died first.
Death is fucking complicated.
No, you know what?
It's not complicated.
It's simple.
People die.
That's just part of life.
150,000 people a day,
actually.
You know? I mean...
we're biological entities,
and death is just...
Top shelf.
The end of biological function.
It's as simple as that.
How can you explain
what happened to us as simple?
I mean, if Wendy never had
that premonition...
and none of us had gotten off that ride,
we'd all be dead right now.
Does that not make sense to you?
Oh, yeah.
Kevin, how come when a guy dies
of a plain heart attack...
no one goes like...
He was eating French toast...,
when Princess Diana died in Paris,
and then he saw her funeral on TV,
and now he's dead?
You know why because
they'd sound crazy so
guess how you two sound right now?
Crazy
Zip, I'm done.
So finish cutting those orders...
so we can get out of here.
Ok!
Sick.
Ok.
Let's go with what you guys are saying.
Let's just say, you know...
that Death does have a conscious plan
and that it's been set into motion.
Great. So...
Newton's third law of motion,
and well look, I'm just guessing that it goes
for Death, too when he's working in our world.
Newton says,
that every action,
has an equal and opposite reaction.
So, that means that...
if Death...
has taken action,
so can we.
And that,
that action we take might have
an opposite reaction,
that thwarts Death's intent.
You're being a fucker, but go on.
Ok.
What if,
for example...
the last in line,
were to make the utilitarian choice...
Kill themselves.
That's pretty much gonna ruin
any plan Death's put in motion.
And even better...
hey, it's gonna save...
five skipped lives.
Any takers?
No, I didn't think so.
There! Those!
No!
I didn't say anything.
I mean, I think they were trying
to scare us into saying something
but they had nothing
to keep me there.
What'd you tell them?
Everything.
I didn't do anything.
I...
I told them about
the pictures in the camera
and Flight 180 and Frankie and Lewis
and why we went to see
lan and Erin and...
Did they believe you?
Yeah, right.
Would you believe me?
No they looked at me like I was crazy.
10 hours they had us in there.
For all we know,
whoever was sitting
behind Erin is already dead.
And we're next.
Now.
Ian almost died first,
but we intervened.
So it skipped lan.
That's how we regain control.
If someone intercedes the life that
was supposed to be next is skipped.
Alright, wait, wait, wait. So...
going by the way we sat
on the roller coaster...
I'm next,
and then you.
We can beat this.
We're so close.
We can't give up.
Alright, my dad's here.
He's gonna give me a ride back.
But are you sure we shouldn't,
stick together?
It's just for a couple of hours.
Alright? A couple of hours. Go back,
look at the pictures,
see if you can find any more clues,
and I'll ask everybody
I see if they know,
if anyone else got off the ride.
Ok?
Was there something
I should know about going?
No, it's just...
I'll just be freaking out every second...
hoping you're ok.
Why?
I mean, we don't even like each other.
Come here.
Ok?
Alright, I got my cell.
Hey, Wen?
So we're meeting some guys
at that centennial thing
and I could really use
my good-luck...
bracelet.
Hey, this is Julie.
Leave a message.
Call me on my cell right away.
Hello?
Do you remember Julie
being on the roller coaster?
What, your sister?
No.
No, she would've said
something by now.
The person sitting behind lan and Erin
was wearing the exact same
charm bracelet
our grandmother gave her.
Amber or Perry were probably
with her so...
they're next.
I gotta find Julie.
She went to the tricentennial thing.
Well, I... I'm here now, working security.
I'll start looking for her.
I'm on my way.
Wen, wait.
Look after them, we're next.
So in case something happens to them
before we meet up...
remember that time we talked about?
When we look at our pictures?
It's now.
Great.
Mine has no clue, it's just...
me standing in front of
a blank background with,
Jason at the amusement park.
Wait.
McKinley.
Ian?
Well, is he in the picture?
No but it,
feels like a clue.
And yours is the picture that...
I took when I flashed
the camera in your face it's all...
out of focus and overexposed, like...
Like a firework went off in my face?
The British are coming!
Get them while they're hot!
Take it to those Redcoats!
Column, advance!
The kite is aloft.
Now,
let us hope for some lightning.
Fuck you, Ben Franklin.
This is awesome, dude!
Come on!
Hey, get out of here with those, man!
You're gonna set these off!
Hurry, dude.
Come on, man, let's go!
Hurry up!
Ladies and gentlemen,
to celebrate McKinley's tricentennial
the fireworks extravaganza
will begin shortly.
Oh, my God. Julie.
What?
Look.
There's Kahlil.
Should we?
Hey guys. I'm sorry
but you can't be here, ok?
The viewing site is over there.
You too sir. Come on.
They're not gonna
make us move, are they?
I don't fucking believe them.
Ok, we gotta clear out.
Excuse me.
Ladies.
Boys.
What's going on?
Hey, Julie.
You three need to come with me.
What did we do?
Look, it's for
your own safety Julie, alright?
I'll tell you about it as soon as
we get away from here, ok?
Let go of me!
Julie.
Hey.
Julie!
Sweet.
Light it! Light it!
Go, go, go, man!
Julie!
Oh, shit!
Dude, we gotta bail!
Hey!
Julie!
No, wait, wait.
You're in danger, ok?
I'm trying to explain something.
Let me explain this to you.
Julie, look out!
Julie!
Cut him off!
Ok, ok.
Stay back! He's dangerous!
I got him.
Just let me go.
No, Julie.
You have to tell me, you have to listen.
Tell me who was sitting next to you
on the roller coaster!
Oh, my God, Julie are you alright?
Listen to me!
You have to tell me
who was sitting next to you
on the roller coaster!
Who? She's next!
Kevin.
Fire!
You saved my life.
Thanks for that, McKinley.
Shut up, McKinley!
No!
We have to get out of here now.
What's the deal?
Ian McKinley.
He causes my death.
In my picture I was wearing
the McKinley grad night shirt.
He's the clue.
What?
There's a first aid tent,
there should be security.
Get the fuck outta here, McKinley!
Hey, I'm just...
celebrating our town's tricentennial.
You followed me!
You are paranoid.
But hey, I saw what happened.
You're next, right?
You're the end of it, aren't you?
Man, I would be paranoid too.
You didn't even believe me!
Yeah, well, seeing is believing.
Then you have to stay away from me!
Have to?
That's extreme.
Oh, no way.
Do I cause your death?
Just like you caused Erin's?
Wha, wha, wha, what?
What? You have a vision?
Was I in it?
Was I in a picture?
Just tell me how to start it off!
Let's get this over with!
You'll save me if you just stay away!
Then it'll all be over!
What do I care?
It skipped me.
For me, it is over.
I'm not dying!
You see?
I'm not gonna die!
It's you, Wendy!
You're dead!
♪ Came back down from this fight ♪
Hi!
♪ Will get ya deeper ♪
♪ And make you right ♪
Thank you.
♪ Bruno's drops threaten her... ♪
Wait, what about that great curry place?
Don't we get off at Booth?
Oh, you mean Gupta's.
You get off at Oswald.
That's right.
But you know, if I can't be home
for Thanksgiving,
I need some semblance
of a traditional dinner.
Turkey, stuffing, pie.
If you don't have turkey
for one Thanksgiving
is that really gonna kill you?
♪ There is someone ♪
♪ Walking behind you ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ Look at me ♪
♪ There is someone ♪
♪ Watching your footsteps ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ There is someone ♪
♪ Who really needs you ♪
♪ Here's my heart ♪
This is Booth Street.
Next stop is Oswald.
End of the line.
The next stop
is the end of the line.
Wendy!
Next stop after this.
Let's just walk.
It's freezing out.
Yeah, but the air'll feel good.
I could use some air.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Yeah, man!
Alright, man. See ya.
Let's go, Bruins!
Bruins, yeah!
Hey man, peace out!
Come on.
Excuse me.
Watch out!
Hey, Bruins!
You missed the beginning.
Did you see that?
This is it!
Yo, coming through.
Excuse me.
Hey? Oh, my God.
I can't believe this.
Here.
Come on.
Let's go. Let's go.
I thought you weren't
coming till tonight.
Well Dad's car just like
dies out of nowhere...
and he couldn't get it fixed
anywhere on a holiday
so instead of sitting around
for a few hours
I lucked out and caught an early train.
I hope I'm not messing you up or...
No, no, it's just...
I think I had a sense...
that you were coming now.
I was just...
I was feeling like I did...
that night.
No. No, it's over.
You, me, Kevin went over
a thousand scenarios.
Ian was gonna cause your death
you intervened and it skipped us.
Look,
I'm not worried.
I ran into Kevin at home.
He's not worried.
And if I were you...
until something happens
to me and then Kevin,
you've got nothing to worry about.
You're right.
Hey, I. I want you to meet
my roommate and my friend, ok?
Yeah.
Hey, guys. This is Julie my...
What are you doing here?
Wendy! Julie!
What are the chances?
How long have you been on this train?
Since home.
I was heading up to check out the game.
I was gonna look you up afterwards.
You ok?
Is something wrong?
Julie stay down!
Julie!
Kevin!
God!
No!
I was gonna look you up afterwards but...
You ok?
Is something wrong?
The train...
shit.
Not again.
We gotta get out!
It's not working.
Somebody stop the train!
By LESAIGNEUR
Sync & corrections January 2022