Subtitle by : Harout
Timing by : 8x8 [IScrew]
Final Destination 5
Hey, Sam, when I say would you mind
putting breakfast together for the retreat,
I meant like donuts,
and some coffee ?
- This is amazing!
- Thanks man!
Just remember that when you see
my sales report for last month.
- I saw it last night.
- Shit!
- Has Dennis seen it ?
- Not yet.
Look, you just
make a decision.
You know? You gonna be chef
or you gonna be ???.
I'm telling you as a friend,
because, as your boss,
I'm ready to fire your ass.
And as a friend
I appreciate that advice.
Hold on, I'll be right back!
Molly, your tickets' cancels.
I told him that is a mistake.
I was going to tell you after
this weekend.
- To tell me what?
- That I don't...
I don't think it's such a good idea.
What? The trip?
And my brother's wedding.
- What's going on here?
- We should talk about this later...
And to pretend that I haven't seen
these for the next 2 days?
No, let's talk about this now.
It's not working out, Sam.
We're not working out.
It's Candice, right?
Okay sorry, this is not a vacation.
It's a business retreat. We'll on
business for the next 2 days.
I'm sorry.
I love you but this doesn't change
the fact that you are still an intern.
That 12:30 curfew tonight,
you shouldn't planning on breaking that.
Why ?
For the naked team belling. (???)
Hey, Olivia, don't forget these.
Oh, yeah. I've been trying to.
Why ? I like it, it's very ... Lisa Lope (???)
Oh, you know, I'll rather be very...
Olivia.
- We gonna giggle soomeday. (???)
- Yeah, I'll be there.
Good morning, Peter.
You looking good.
???
Candice, do you actually get paid for
this internship or it just increase your ... ?
You know, if you wanna me get rid of that
baby fat you should try the gym.
Like those working machines in your back.
Sweety, it's not fat.
They're called tits.
You are not looking so hot,
this morning.
???
Look, have you tried that
thing that your boyfriend made ?
And this was it is ?
That's touch your nerve ?
- Leave me in peace, Isaac.
- Listen, MO. Mo, look at me.
Look at me. If you want to talk to someone,
I'm a very good listener.
Wait, don't say anything.
???.
Hey, let's sit together on the bus?
No, I remember you.
- You know what you sould do ?
- What ?
- You should apologize.
- Why ?
It does not matter. It never matters.
Only... say
I'm sorry, cause I...
Oh, shit!
Hi Stand, how is it going?
- It Sam, sir.
- Did you just correct me ?
- No.
- Look at me. What's my name ?
- Dennis.
- Look away.
- All right, Pete?
- Yes, yes sir.
We are just waiting for Nathan.
What's the only thing that
we can not recycle, Pete ?
- Wasted time, sir.
- Exactly.
We'll be in the road in 90 seconds.
I'll go tracked them down. (???)
It's a good thing
showing initiative, Stand.
It's gonna be a good day.
You know? I'm just trying to make sense.
3 weeks ago they brought you as an assistant of manager.
- And now, they give you a day off ?
- It's not a day off.
- It's a re...
- Re... what?
- Retarded?
- Retreat.
It's a retreat.
I do not want to go, I just follow the orders,
then if you do not like, you can ...
What? Can I what?
Hey, hey, come on,
we are waiting for you!
- It's  Okay.
- No, wait. Wait.
What were you saying?
There are at least 15 years of working here.
You got what ?
4 years in a class?
- Listen, I'm tired...
- It's not a good idea, Roy.
It is not a good idea, come on.
We had it good today.
How do you get away with that ?
I had no choice.
And he's the union representative.
I fire him and suddenly I got
a room full of complaints.
But I ???, even
if it kills me.
What about you ? You've already decided what
to do with the offer of the restaurant ?
- I already did.
- That's just great!
No, you know, they... They want to send
someone at the restaurant in Paris.
But, who knows for how long ?
Could be 6 months, one year...
Just thought I'll leaving
too much behind.
- I'm not so sure.
- Well, if you go to Paris,
- Do me a favor.
- What's that?
- Take her with you.
- Oh no!
- Are you coming?
- Yeah.
What are those for?
They just help me relax.
And for luck.
Gymnasts are worse than baseball players.
She's superstitious.
Hey, how are you doing?
No, just a stupid retreat thing with
idiots from the office.
No not you sir, them.
hold on a second.
I'm going to a place with more privacy.
It's a great idea, sir.
A brilliant idea.
Hang on a second babe.
I'm just heading to my private office.
Damn it!
- Peter, have you heard that?
- What?
There's something wrong.
Mo, come on!
Candice! Candice!
No!
Come on, Peter, come on!
Come on, Mo!
What the fuck... ?
Shit!
This way!
Come on, come on!
Do not look down!
Go on, go on!
Help me, help me!
Wait! Olivia, here. Come.
Continue..
Try to follow
Molly's voice, okay?
Follow her voice.
- Come on!
- Help me!
Peter, hurry up!
Hold on!
Come on! Come on!
Hold on, Sam!
Damn it!
We all got to get off!
- What are you talking about?
- The bridge is gonna collapse!
- What?
- We all gotta die!
What the hell is going on?
We all gonna die, if we do not go
off of this bridge, now!
What?
Stan Relax!
It's just some construction.
Come on !
Please follow me!
Open the door!
That's a big problem,
deal with it.
- Yeah.
- Then, go get them.
Yeah.
- Sam, Molly!
- Peter, please, follow us!
Come on! Let's go!
- Well, calm down!
- I'm going to help.
Please.
Hey, guys! Come on!
Go back to the bus,
that we talk about it!
Molly, Sam, come on, guys!
Do not you think it's weird
they are off the bus?
It is not right.
It's like he just snaps.
- What happens?
- What the hell is going on here?
Get off!
Get off the bus!
Come on!
How did you know?
That's the big question.
It says, "I saw it collapse.
I knew it would happen. "
- It seems premeditated to me.
- No, it's not what I meant.
I ... I had a vision.
Ok, a vision.
Physic phenomenon. Ghosts. Bigfoot.
You actually believe in that stuff?
I don't know.
I'll tell you what I believe.
There's an answer for everything.
Which means that there is an
answer. You knew,
because you warned that
the bridge was about to collapse,
and minutes later, it did.
I told you, I saw
it coming.
I don't know how.
I just did.
- And no one else did.
- Like I said,
It just came out of nowhere.
Has Sam ever showed some
extremist behavior?
No.
Wait. Extremist behavior?
You mean like terrorist?
Did you see him talked to anyone that morning,
on the cellphone...?
Just his girlfriend.
His ex-girlfriend.
Mo, Molly, that was in person.
Very well, thank you.
Tell me about the break-up.
Was he upset?
On a scale of 1 to 10.
It's personal.
He must have been pissed, right?
Getting dupped like that.
What's it all about?
I'm just trying to put
all the pieces of the puzzle together,
before I make them moving around, making them fit.
Look, I just had a hunch that
something bad was going to happen.
That's it.
Excuse me.
They came back with the analysis.
And?
Strong gusts of wind have
weakened the structure of the building.
- The wind!
- That's it, let go of the boy.
You free to go.
I have a feeling that we'll see each
other again.
Call it a hunch.
Authorities are now calling
the Northbay bridge collapse
a freak act of nature,
signaling that the highway
improvement project
may have weakened
the super structure.
Among the survivors, there are 8 employees
of Pressage Paper
on a way to
to a business retreat.
The another 17 employees
were killed in the collapse.
And although they were labelled the lucky 8,
the surviving employees
now face an uncertain future.
Does anyone know when this is
suppose to start?
- When Dennis gets here.
- Hey, guys.
- ???
- No..
You heard the news, they say it was natural causes.
They are more like supernatural.
Are you holding up? I try calling.
Yeah, I know. I saw it.
I'm just tired.
So? How did you explain that?
I didn't. I couldn't.
- Sam, how do you reason?
- That's exactly what the agent keep saying.
Whatever answer you are looking for,
I don't have it.
Sam is right.
It doesn't matter how it happens.
We should put this behind us and we must be
grateful that we are still alive.
???, right?
I look at people's faces
today, and I see family members, friends,
but the people that left us on ton the bridge that day,
They were some than that..
People like Jerry Obertcon,
Liz Burton,
David Buttler.
that you work next to,
you work for them
and with all work with.
Who can forget
Winks's smile?
- Or Isaac Palmer.
- He just said my name?
- It's not funny.
- I'm sorry.
You're right, I'm sorry.
- I see dead people.
- Guys.
Death...
doesn't like to be cheatted.
Excuse me?
What's that supposed to mean?
You all, just be careful now.
Ok, thanks for the advice.
Creepy guy.
- What's the manner?
- He said that's got no flavor.
- Did he want something else?
- No, he checked.
Let me taste it.
The customer is an asshole.
It's good.
Hold on!
- Do you mind if I come in?
- Yeah, sure.
- Thanks.
- I thought you'll be working tonight.
Yeah, I worked
the first shift, but
I had to do something else.
- Can I?
- Oh, yes, sure. Go ahead.
Thank you.
Listen...
When everything was going down
on that bridge,
The only thing that I thought was about you.
Getting you to safety.
You're the only thing
I care about, Molly.
- Whatever is wrong, I can fix it.
- You haven't done anything wrong.
Then what?
What is it?
- Paris.
- We've talk about that.
I'm not going
to give up my life.
- Leave you for that job.
- But it's the only thing you've ever dreamed of.
Life is too short, Sam.
- You have to go after what you love.
- I am.
You should take the job.
Go to Paris.
Hey!
What's the matter?
I don't know, I'm not ready.
It's hard to concentrate after...
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
'Cause this is the last
practice before the championship.
- So the last practice of your college carrier. (??)
- I know, but...
I think you got this.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- You're good right there.
- Ok.
You're right.
And then the coach would kill me.
Take it.
Thank you.
Go.
- Go
- Well.
You got this.
Seriously?
This is stupid!
They have not yet
placed ventilation?
They are doing on it.
Come on, Candice, you're up.
Come on, Candice,
you got this!
Candice! Now!
That's it! Everytime, Candice.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
Nicely done, Candice.
Okay, go to the bars.
Go ahead, push!
Here we go, Candice, go loose!
Ok, it's your turn.
Stay focused.
Oh, shit!
- Do not touch her!
- Call 911.
Ah, my God!
Peter!
I came as soon as I heard.
She was doing great.
She was finishing her performance and...
Why ?
Why did it happen?
- It makes no sense.
- I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Peter.
Well, let's just go, Sam.
- How's going?
- It's weird.
Coming here...
It's just so quiet.
You know Denis says ???
I know, but it's depressing.
We have get called
to get pay? (???)
- What is he doing here?
- I think he just needs a distraction.
Yeah.
Yeah, what a bummer about
Candice.
I think everyone was seeing that coming.
What?
Have not you seen the crazy shit
those gymnasts do
I am surprised that
does not happen again more often.
Like I wrote in the e-mail.
You must disable all the keys cards
employee died.
instructions are included.
Why don't you send me
the Director of Human Resources?
The Director of Human Resources
is dead.
- Dennis, you need to find someone out there?
- No, I got it.
Oh, Debbie!
You were so naughty!
Norbert, my man!
Shit!
You shouldn't mind, buddy.
Hey man, what are you doing up here?
I had to leave the floor.
Roy is driving me crazy.
So... Who wants one?
- Where did you get these?
- I've stole it.
From Roy's truck.
It's good, right?
- I got something better.
- Oh, nice one!
Yeah, Count me in.
Are you sure you wanna share that?
If I don't I'll end up drinking alone,
which is just sad.
Well, this stage got way more fun!
No, I did call you.
Of course. I just called you
right now, didn't I?
Because I really want
to take you out again.
Yeah, we could have a nice romantic dinner.
You know, it might be a place
outside the city. Hold up!
You know what? I gotta go.
No, no, no, listen ...
Hey, who's my girl, Camber?
Amber yes.
That's what I said!
Excuse me.
Amber, I'm sorry...
Sorry about that.
My sister tends to get a little
too chatty sometimes.
So... Tell me about stress relief.
And what it this really get me?
This covers a session
for two different physical therapies.
Like massage therapy.
??? massage.
This is a family operation.
Everyone on staff is professional
That's great! I prefer a professional.
You know what? I kinda demand it!
I just trying to verify if this professional
experience ends uh... happy.
- I know exactly what you need.
- Oh, I'm sure you do!
- Follow me, please.
- I'll love to...
Oh, slow down a little bit.
Yeah, you have a lovely walk!
Aahm! Yum yum!
Wait just a second.
This is solid.
I just wanted to be sure.
In case we get a little noisy
if you know what you think.
Yo Buddha, slow down the rice cake.
Just close your eyes.
Relax,
and someone will be into serving you.
Oh, yeah !
Subtitle by : Harout
Timing by : 8x8 [IScrew]
Oh, yeah ! Feels dynamite!
No, no. You are doing it the wrong way, young lady.
What happened to the younger version of you?
Ok, I'm sorry, do you come with subtitles?
I can you help you, too
You know what, I should just go here.
Relax.
I have no idea what that means.
Your spine is all out of alignment...
That's okay. I'm all right!
What are you doing ?
- Let me help you.
You are a little aggressive there,
don't you think?
Breathe in...
- What? I do not know what to say!
- Expire out...
No, I don't want to!
- Cheers!
Shit!
I gotta go.
- Bye!
- See you later.
This is the end,
So what are we toasting to?
To find new jobs.
Because it's only a matter of time,
before they shut us down.
To... starting over.
Peter.
It just does not make sense.
She dies doing something she's done
almost everyday for the last 15 years
of her life.
He said she didn't want to do it,
she said she wasn't ready.
I should have stop her.
I should have done something, I should've ...
Peter, there wasn't anything
that you could have done.
How do you know?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Hello Agent Lock, this is Denis.
Peter just freaked out
about something, I don't know why.
Does that mean anything? You told me to call
If I see anything odd.
I don't know you but thank you Denis.
Call me if you see anything strange.
Stranger.
Should we have code names
for one another, do you think?
Over now.
All right, show me how this happened.
- I don't think I can.
- What do you mean?
I mean I can try a 100 times,
and never recreate exactly what happened here.
This is some freaky shit.
Oh, it actually felt great!
We're not done yet, fat boy.
Ah, yeah, awesome!
Oh, are those things even sterilized?
No, no, I'm not catching any disease,
unless I have earned them.
Wait a second,
you understood what I said?
You speak English!
Of course I understand you. You think I'm stupid?
I'm just pretending I don't understand.
- You know what...
Let's do this. 2 billion people
can't be wrong.
Do you get it? Sure, You're Chinese.
Oh, it's in, okay it's in!
How many of this are you going
to put in me?
Could you grab it for me?
Thanks.
No phone calls
during the treatment.
It's not very nice, you know.
Now, this needle will help you grow hair
on your head.
Now, sleep for 30 minutes
and you'll feel real good.
Don't touch my eyes.
Ok, once again. I don't have no clue
what you are saying, not even a little clue.
30 minutes. You sleep!
Sleep.
Fire!
There's a fire!
Shit!
You should come with me.
To Paris?
You even say it yourself!
You're going to have to start over.
Start over with me.
- How many drinks have you had?
- Enough.
Molly, I'm serious.
You were right.
If I don't take the job,
I'll regret it.
But I'm not willing to lose you.
Why is it have to be one or the other?
I'm better when you're with me.
Guys, you're not going to believe this!
- They said it was a freak accident.
- Raise your hand if you believe that.
Who dies during a massage?
Seriously?
First Candice and now Isaac.
It can't be a coincidence.
It's not.
Where are you going?
It's that creepy dude.
Why we are following us?
Who are you?
You were at the cemetery
then the gym, now here.
- What are you doing?
- My job.
"Coroner"
What's happening to us?
What's make you think I know that?
You warned us.
At the memorial service, you said
death doesn't like to be cheated.
- It's just that I have seen this before.
- Seen what?
A lucky few survivors dying one by one...
Death comes for them all.
You change something on that bridge.
It's an ??? reality.
And that rego (?) is you.
So what, we are doomed to die ?
Is that it? We just got our lives back
so what kind of fucked-up karma is that ?
Are you saying that we can't stop this ?
You were supposed
to die on that bridge.
You are not supposed to be here.
You should have died.
So you let death have somebody else
in your place
and you take his spot in
the realm of the living,
all the days and years he have yet to live.
And they took
your place in death.
???
Wait a minute, we killed someone,
we get their life ?
Is that what you are telling me ?
I don't make the rules.
I just clean up,
after the game is over.
Maybe that's why Candice
and Isaac are dead.
They weren't supposed to survive
and now it's coming after the rest of us.
No, not all of us.
- Molly made it, she didn't die.
- What?
When I had the vision,
or premonition,
I got you across
before the bridge collapsed.
- You survived.
- You saved her ?
Why? Because you've decided that she deserved
to live more than the rest of us ?
No, it's not what he's saying
I don't deserve to live more than anything else.
But, it seems that you deserve
to live more than Candice.
- Peter, hang on!
- Look, Guys!
You will not believe it ?
Killing people to survive, death list, really ?
I may not know what's going on,
but it's not what the guy says.
What else is it then?
Shit!
We must go to Olivia.
Come on.
It's been a long time since your last visit.
What made you come today?
A lot is going on in my life.
It's just than I don't want to miss anything.
You know, nothing important.
Same reason that I ??? myself.
Come on, let's get you started.
Yeah that's the first step.
You are not going to need those again.
Here we are. Come on in.
What are these?
Oh, it's just for some younger patients.
And, sometimes the older ones too.
- What's that?
- Relax.
It looks a lot worse than what it really is.
I'm gently going to position your head...
I want you to tell me
when this feels snug.
I can't move my head.
Perfect. Just what we want.
Here we go.
Ok, now comes the fun part.
With these drops, you will feel
a little numbness in your eye.
Which is a good thing.
Deep Breathe.
Relax.
Very good.
Good girl!
That's not so bad, is it?
Looks good!
- What was that?
- Relax, Olivia.
I'm just entering some data.
Dotty.
My assistant gave me an incomplete
file. I'll Be right back.
Hold on! You're leaving?
Is that supposed to be happening?
"Emergency Stop"
Help! Help!
- Olivia Castle, where is she?
- She may be in danger!
No, she's fine.
We do those kind of procedures all the time.
Help me!
Sam...
- Can you stay with me for the night please?
- Of course.
5 different systems had to go wrong for
that laser to fail so spectacularly, 5 !
What do you want from us?
I want to tell me what you think is going on.
Two deaths, ok, all right, that's a coincidence.
Three?
It's a pattern.
I know you two didn't do this.
But I think you know something.
What is it?
We don't know anything.
Take a guess.
We think we weren't suppose
to survive on that bridge.
What?
And now, something is trying to
set it right.
Something?
that's all you got?
Right now, yeah. But, if you come over
with a better explanation, let us now.
Thank you.
You're up early.
I don't know, I could not sleep,
I'm just thinking about the bridge.
Sam...
You can't do this to yourself.
No, I was thinking of the premonition.
We all got off the bus, but
the ground gave away and Candice fell.
And the bus flipped over
and Isaac, he never got off the bus,
he went with it.
- Where are you getting at?
- I know it sounds strange.
Look, I know that I helped you
to cross.
Then I reached back to Olivia.
But she didn't make it, she fell.
So?
The first was Candice,
Then Isaac
and then Olivia.
They are dying, in that order.
Who dies after Olivia?
"Fuck you"
Subtitle by : Harout
Timing by : 8x8 [IScrew]
You could come up, Roy please?
Oh oh Roy that's the boss, you are in trouble Roy.
Okay school boy what do want to talk me about?
- About your time card.
- Yeah, let's talk about the time card.
You have cut my hours,
which means that you have cut my pay.
I removed everyone's hours, okay ? The company has
reduced by 50 percent, the hours in total.
My domain can't be
working at 50 percent.
Roy.
I want to see
if you work at 50 percent.
- We gotta go man!
- I'm not going anywhere!
We gotta to move!
We gotta to move now!
Roy? You okay down there?
- Hey Denis.
- Hey.
- They are closing us down.
- They are shutting down the plan.
Not the plan, just us.
Just sales administration.
Can you believe it, us?
Usually, it's the factor guys
that usually get laid off.
Not us, We're supposed to be safe.
Denis, we have bigger problems.
Olivia and Isaac are dead.
- Who's Isaac?
- Isaac, textport. (???)
- Wasn't he dead already?
- No, Denis.
It's going to happen to us too if
we don't do something about it.
I understand. It's called "survivor guilt."
No, guilt doesn't kill you !
Obviously, you've never
met my in-laws.
I'm not fucking around, Denis.
Anyone could be next!
It could be you, understand?
- Nobody's safe!
- What are you talking about?
We weren't supposed to survived
when that bridge collapsed.
And so now it's kill or be killed.
You get that, Denis?
Whatever, I warned you.
Do whatever you want to do.
I will.
Agent Lock, it's Denis.
Pete just came in here
and he has just completely lost it!
He yells about "kill or be killed"!
Oh, yeah, it definitely sounds
like a threat.
- What happened ?
- I don't know. It just happened so fast !
- You're okay ?
- Are you hurt ?
I'm good.
- Did you kill him?
- What?
No, no, I just...
No, he got in the way and...
No, you did, didn't you ?
You saw it coming
and then you took his live.
- You put him in the way!
- I don't really do anything!
That's true ? Did you or didn't you?
- Peter, calm down!
- Did you or didn't you ?
Did you or didn't you ?
Yes, I think I did.
I killed him.
So if the theory works then
you traded his place so he had your dead
and you'll have his. (???)
How we know for sure?
I think there is an order for these deaths.
The same order as the deaths of the bridge.
Then who will be next?
Someone wants me to tell
what the hell is going on?
- Who's next?
- Who's what?
Denis! It was Denis!
No shit!!
Why are you fighting me on this? You're
not going seriously to work, are you?
Molly...
Isaac died on a massage table!
- Death is going to come for me, I don't think it matters where I am.
- But you have to do something!
- What? Kill someone so I can live?
- No, of course not.
- We'll just have to figure something else out.
- I've figured it out.
Something saved me on the bridge.
Maybe he doesn't want me to die.
Maybe.
We can't live our lives
in fear, Molly.
If something happens tomorrow or 15 years from now,
whatever as soon as we are together.
I'll be okay.
I want you to come by after my shift,
and I'll make a nice late dinner.
Give me this.
Samuel, go to work! Come on, come on!
Could have been ugly, huh?
Just met your girlfriend. (?)
Are you sure it's okay if I make
her a dinner or something? (?)
- Make sure you leave no traces. (?)
- I will, of course, thank you.
- Chef...
- Yes.
Your partnership, if the offer still stands
I'd like to take it.
It's yours.
OK, no more suspense.
What you've been waiting for.
You made this okay? (??)
Yeah sure, you want me to...
You don't want me to...
How's your French?
Terrible.
Good! We can be terrible together.
Why ?
- I accepted the internship.
- What?
Sam that's amazing!
I'm so proud of you!
Peter...
Are you okay? You look a little upset.
Yeah, yeah.
Just rough couple days.
Yeah, to everyone.
For some, more than others.
Do you mind if I come in?
Of course, come in.
Have a seat.
Thanks.
Hey, Peter.
Hi...
Can I get you anything to eat?
I can make some pasta.
No, I'm good, thank you.
I'm sorry, I just thought...
Peter, it's good that you are here
you shouldn't be alone right now.
I'm surprised to be here at all.
To be still alive I mean.
I'm next on the list, right?
It's me and then you, right?
I was up
last night thinking about,
if I can really do it.
- Do what?
- Take someone else's life.
I could actually kill some stranger.
And replace their life with my own.
And I thought about it and uh...
and I convinced myself that I could.
So I went on a walk.
Nowhere in particular, but every couple of minutes
an opportunity will just presented itself,
like ???.
I just grab somebody and pull him in an alley...
Or push someone
in front of a car.
What did you do?
- Did you...?
- No, I didn't.
I realized that I couldn't kill
somebody that didn't deserve to die.
I thought about Candice
and I though "wait a minute...".
Candice didn't deserve to die.
Olivia didn't, Dennis didn't.
I don't.
Do I?
No, of course you don't.
Well,
None of us deserves to die,
then why you deserve to live, Molly?
You say it yourself, you don't.
Let's go!
I heard the shotfire.
Requesting backup.
Hide. Hide where you can.
Not done yet, Sam.
Where is she?
I'm not gotta hurt her, Peter!
- You'll have to kill me first.
- This doesn't do me any good.
- Death wants you too!
- This is crazy, Peter! Don't do this!
Just think... For a minute...
All right?
You are not a killer!
I don't want to kill anybody, Sam.
But I don't want to die either!
It's not your time yet.
Don't worry, Molly.
I didn't kill him.
But I don't need to...
Molly, because...
because death is going to do that for me.
It doesn't mean I can't help.
Are you okay?
- What's going on?
- It's Peter. He has a gun!
Oh, my God!
You killed him!
It's Sam's turn.
Peter, just go.
You have your life, you're safe now.
Please.
Sorry, Molly.
You've just witnessed
murder of a federal agent.
I'm not going to spend the life that I
just earned ... in prison.
Molly, go get help!
Tell Candice,
I love her.
Peter!
He's gone. You killed him!
Does that mean I get Block's life?
Yeah.
Yes, I do.
Do you mind if I take the window seat?
Do you really want me to seat here...
I'm about twice your size!
- Come on, if you dare!
- Get off the plane!
- What's that about?
- I have no idea.
"Ladies and gentlemen, fasten
your seatbelts, please ..."
Ready to go.
Sir.
Excuse me,
those passengers who got off the plane,
what was that all about ?
He had a panic attack and wanted to board off the plane.
He said he had some kind of a vision...
No!
Oh, my God!
Sam!
I got you!
Molly, hold on!
I appreciate that you came, Nathan.
Roy wasn't the easiest guy to work with.
I still can't believe he's gone.
I think it was for the best.
What do you mean?
Company got an autopsy for insurance purposes.
Turns out that Roy had bad blood vessel in his brain,
so big, that it was about to burst
and he'll be died any day now.
Any day?
Life's a bitch!
Subtitle by : Harout
Timing by : 8x8 [IScrew]