Aah!
- Whoo!
- Ha ha ha!
Aah!
Oh, man! Heh heh.
- Did you see that?
- Woo!
Oh, my God. Ha ha!
- Yes! Yes!
- Nice, nice, nice.
- Aw, sick!
- Worth the wait.
Oh, babe. You missed out.
Yes!
I want to get off.
Whoo! Ow!
Ha ha ha!
That was intense, man.
To feel how that would be
to just crash and burn like that.
Yeah, yeah. Maybe for you,
but our lives are actually goin' somewhere.
Oh! OK, well, where we gotta go
is to the roller coaster.
'Cause our pass is for 9:15.
If we miss that,
we'll stand in line...
for, like, a day and a half,
and that's gonna kill me.
- OK!
- All right?
So let's go.
They're totally gonna dig this, man!
OK. Come on, it won't kill us to get
a deep-fried Snickers and a Coke.
Before ridin' Devil's Flight?
Yeah, that might kill me.
No! What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger, man.
Ha ha ha!
- Unh!
- Ha ha!
Oh, I'll take that.
No. Come on, gimme.
It's not even mine, Kevin.
It's the yearbook's.
Just... Kevin.
Ha ha!
- Oh!
- Oh, got it.
- Oh, my God, you're such an idiot.
- Hey. Hey. Gimme the...
Ha ha!
- Ow!
- Nice.
Um, could you, like,
please delete that one of Stacy?
Ha ha!
These are for the yearbook.
And I have to turn them in tomorrow
to make a deadline...
and, like, I doubt it if a shot of
Stacy Kobayashi's camel toe...
is gonna make it in there.
Whew. I'd buy two.
Ha ha ha!
Number 38, your order's ready.
That's us.
I am so sorry.
Kevin can get so out of control.
Let me just say
he would make me crazy.
Ha! I mean, you know
I'm such a control freak...
like I couldn't handle that.
I'm breaking up with him.
Couple of weeks.
After graduation.
I've been wanting to for a while.
But don't tell anybody, OK?
Whoa. Ha ha!
Now, that shot there?
That'll sell some yearbooks.
- I love it.
Oh! Oh, all right,
so I'm a total whore.
Come on, go, go, go,
go, go, go go!
Oh, my God, Ashley, you're winning.
You're totally winning.
- Am I winning?
- Yeah, come on, hurry!
OK, come on, come on,
come on, come on!
Am I winning? Look around,
I don't want to look.
You're totally winning.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on!
- Don't look!
- Oh, my God! Come on!
Oh, my God!
I'm winning! I'm winning!
Aah! Aah!
- I won!
- I knew you would.
Oh, my God! Gimme my prize.
- Good job.
- That was so awesome, Ashley.
Ashley.
Woo! Ha ha!
How ya doin', my brother?
You havin' a good time, huh?
- You like that?
- Ha ha!
Yeah! You like it.
Give it up. Give it up.
Whoo-ooh!
Sam!
Excuse me.
You're not a senior.
And what are
you gonna do about it...
Miss "Cutest Couple,"
Rah Rah? Ha ha!
Mom know you're here?
You are a complete bitch
if you tell her.
Proof where you were.
Take a shot of this.
Ha ha ha!
Yeah! That's what I'm talking about.
That's three.
# That is three, number three #
# Oh, I'm the man, I'm the man #
Man, I am hot.
- Man, gimme some right here, man.
- Right here! Right here!
What you doin'?
Get the fuck back. Hoo!
My God, I am good. Here we go.
Boy, I'll tell ya...
Goddamn. Whoo!
Kind sir, step right up!
There ya go. Whaddaya want?
Here we go, baby.
3 for 3. It's all mine.
Here we go. Here we go.
Big prize. Watch out.
Come on.
Unh!
Ho ho ho!
# That's what I'm talkin' 'bout #
We gonna get that one.
You want that blue one?
That's the one we gonna get.
Ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
You can run, but you cannot hide.
- Yes!
- Whoo! Here we are, baby.
- Whoo!
- There it is.
- Awesome.
Here, get a pic of this. Ahhh!
This is the beginning of the end.
Ha ha ha!
Hey, guys, get in line.
Let's go on again!
What's wrong?
I'm...
I was having that feeling
like dejá vu, you know?
Except for something
that hasn't happened yet.
Hey, J.
Come on, man, let's go.
- Yeah, yeah, hold on.
- Come on.
What, are you weirded out
by the ride?
'Cause, look, I know you.
And I think that maybe...
you're nervous about
this roller coaster...
because they say the real fear
with these rides...
comes from the feeling
of having no control.
Everyone imagines weird stuff
when they get scared.
But it never turns out
to be what they imagine.
Never.
OK.
You can run, but you cannot hide.
Oh! Where you guys are right now
if you raise your hands and just...
Ha... cup them slightly...
it'll look you're holding
the devil's balls.
And we'd wanna do that why?
When else you ever gonna see
a dick that big?
I'm lookin' at one right now.
Ha ha!
Man, you guys are smokin' hot.
- Get out, Frankie.
- Yeah, why are you even here?
Yeah, you graduated,
like, two years ago.
I stuck around to monitor
your development.
Yeah. Good to go.
Good to go, baby.
Let's do it. Let's do it.
Come on. Come on.
You may never return
from Devil's Flight.
Ha ha ha ha!
You're totally sad.
Try not to scream!
Ha ha ha!
That was totally awesome!
Yeah! Sweet!
You all right?
There's nothing to worry about.
A roller coaster
is just elemental physics.
A conversion of potential energy
to kinetic energy.
Yeah. Odds are like
one in 250 million...
of dying in a roller coaster.
Yeah, yeah,
thanks for that, McKinley.
You're more likely to die
driving to an amusement park...
than dying at one.
Whoo! Heh.
Here we go.
Whoo!
You like this?
Won it on the Wacky Ladder.
You know that ladder deal
that wobbles? Took it.
I like this. It's old school.
Frankie Cheeks
is old school, ladies.
What's that?
Oh, well, it'd be my honor.
Ew.
Oh! Let's go.
Hey... Baby.
- How many?
- Uh, 4.
- 4.
- Yeah.
Uh, gate one.
- Yeah. Front car.
- Yes!
Wait... No. No, please.
I'm sorry, I don't wanna be a hassle.
I just... I can't sit in the front.
I cannot see the tracks. I'll freak.
OK. Take it easy.
Uh, well, Carrie will sit in
the back with you. Right, babe?
Uh! Why me?
What? 'Cause we're girls?
Fuck that. I'm going to Berkeley
and I won't get to do this for a while.
I'm sitting in the front.
J, just go, OK? I'll live.
You're not gonna sit by yourself.
All right, you know what?
We'll just settle this like real men.
How about that? Hmm? Call it.
Heads.
Shit! Damn it.
All right, fine, what the fuck.
It's the same ride, right?
Go. Go ahead. Bye, babe.
Hey, uh, just do me a favor.
Keep an eye on her, OK?
She's kinda freaked out.
- Oh. Cool.
- All right?
Yeah. Boom, buddy.
No problem.
Ha ha ha!
Aaah!
Ohh!
Here we go. Hey!
J! Keep your hands
to yourself, man.
I'm serious. You know,
payback's a bitch, OK?
You know, she might need
some comforting...
and I'll be there for her. OK?
Hey, no! No.
Get out. Get out.
Hey! Find another cockpit,
Top Gun.
No. Get...
Let's just get in the back, OK?
Ha ha ha!
Ahem.
Guess who's back?
- Ugh.
Hey!
I'll meet you at the end.
Here! All right!
Cool!
Hey. How'd you guys
get in here?
What? I'm 55 inches.
- Sure. Come on out.
- Oh, man.
You, too. Out.
- Ready?
- Ohh!
I told you
we wouldn't get away with it.
You OK?
Let's go on the bumper cars.
Come on. Here we go.
Yeah!
What's up, man? I'm good.
Dare you to, uh, flash me
them sweet, sweet titties...
when we go through the loop.
All right. Ha ha!
Yo! What, you can't read?
Oh. Well, can I just put it
in my pocket, man?
- Is that cool?
- Yeah.
Yeah? Cool.
Thanks, buddy. Sorry.
Oh!
Aw, shit!
Here you go!
Whoo-ooh!
Whoo! Win, baby!
Yes, baby! Win!
Come on!
Come on. Get hyped.
The first hill's so high.
Yeah.
This is what we need!
- Yeah!
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
- Let's do this!
- Just win!
Ow!
Whoo!
Aw, yeah!
Whoo! Shit!
Aah!
Oh, man.
Oh, my God!
Here we go!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
Aah!
Yeah! Whoo!
- Aah!
Ha ha!
Aah! Aah! Ha ha ha!
Whoo!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Ha ha ha! Whoo!
- Whoo!
Aah! Aah!
Whoo!
Yeah! Show me your titties!
- Fuck off, Frankie!
- Oh!
Aah!
- Aah!
- Aah! Aah!
Aah!
Unh!
Oh, shit!
- Aah!
Aah!
Oh, my God!
We're gonna fall off!
Aah!
No!
- Aah!
- Aaah!
Aah!
Oh! Oh!
Unh!
Oh!
- Yow!
- Kevin!
No!
Aah!
Whoa!
No! Aah!
Aah!
Erin, hang on!
Erin!
- Hang on!
- Don't let go!
I can't.
Aah!
No!
Oh, God!
Hang on, Wen.
Hang on! Help me rock it!
Unh! Unh! Unh!
Unh!
Almost got it! Gently.
Aaaah!
No!
Unh! Aah!
Aah!
Yo. What, you can't read?
Oh, well. I'll just...
I'll put it in my pocket, OK?
Yeah.
Thanks, bro.
Ahh. All right.
Let's do this, Wen...
What're you..?
Here you go!
Yeah! Let's do it, baby! Whoo!
We have to get off of here.
No, don't push the button!
Don't! Don't push the button!
Unh! Let me off! Let me off!
Wen, Wen! It's all right.
Jesus, it's gonna be over...
No! It's gonna crash!
It's gonna crash!
Wendy?
The hydraulics will rupture!
The tracks'll collapse! Please!
- What's going on?
- Let me off!
Chick's on somethin'.
It's all right! You'll be OK!
OK, let 'em out. Just the back.
Wen. Hey! Wendy!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Relax. Now, what's the matter?
I saw it. I saw it in my head.
The tracks collapsed.
The roller coaster crashed.
No, she was just a little upset before.
Man, please, can you please
control that bitch?
Damn. "It's gonna crash!
The hydraulics, the coaster!"
Man, she's just trying to get
some fuckin' attention.
You know what?
You're a real piece of shit, Lewis.
- Fuck you.
- Fuck moi?
No, man, fuck you!
Don't touch me.
Ow!
Hey, hey!
Unh!
Just relax!
Fight, man!
Hey. Hey. Let me out.
Nobody else gets off this ride!
Dude, let me off.
So high school.
Let's out.
- Calm down!
- Get off of him!
- Relax!
- Lan!
Where you ladies going?
There's a fight.
Get him out of here!
Hey! Calm down! Relax!
Dude, let me off.
I gotta make sure she's OK.
- Relax! Calm down!
- # Hey! Ho! Let's go #
- Get your big ass off me, man!
- # Hey, ho, let's go! #
- Let me out!
Dude!
# Hey, ho, let's go,
hey, ho, let's go #
- Here we go!
- Let me off!
# Hey, ho #
Dude, that's my girlfriend!
Oh, my God!
Whoo!
Stop it! No! Stop it!
Stop it! Please!
Please, the tracks are broken.
Stop! Stop! Please!
Jason!
Hey, just relax, OK?
- Please!
- Ease up, man. She's all right.
OK? Just let her settle down.
She can settle down at home!
Now listen...
what is your home phone number?
OK, we're gonna call your mother.
Everything will be taken care of...
Aah!
Oh, my God! Jason!
Ohh.
Hey, Wendy!
Hey!
Wait! Wendy!
Hey! Hey, Wen. Wait.
I need... I need to talk to you
about something.
Just here to pick up my diploma.
You're not going to graduation?
No.
Look, you're not the only one
in a fucked up place, OK?
God, I mean,
I just thought maybe...
it'd be good for you to be somewhere
where other people feel the same way.
At graduation?
No. Thanks.
I've had enough funerals.
Then do it for J and Carrie.
Do what? If you die,
then there's nothing...
then you're just dead,
and they don't know.
And if they are up in Heaven
with Lincoln and Gandhi...
do you think they really care about
our high school graduation? No.
I am alive, and I don't care.
As soon as I pull out
of that parking lot...
I am so out of McKinley.
Without J, what's here for me?
I'm here. OK?
I made a promise to J
that I would take care of you.
On the ride. For 3 minutes.
You weren't making
the promise for a lifetime.
Kevin...
if it wasn't for
you and J being friends...
and me and Carrie being friends...
we wouldn't have even hung out.
We don't even like each other.
"Lan McKinley."
How pathetic is it
that my last name...
is the same as my high school?
Julie, look who
I got to sign my yearbook.
- No way. Nice.
- Yeah.
I think we should invite her.
- You think?
- Yeah.
Wen? Um...
So we're ready
for graduation tonight...
we're going to
the tanning salon after this...
and we are so totally cool
if you wanna come with.
Totally.
And just like, talk if you want.
Here's my cell.
I already have your number.
That was so nice of us.
You're not alone.
God, I appreciate
everyone trying to help.
OK? I really do.
No, it's happened before.
OK? I went online looking for
an explanation about...
Wendy, just... just listen
to me, all right?
All right, look, I went online
looking for an explanation...
about what happened,
and I found out...
about this high school
French class from New York.
Six years ago
they went on a trip to Paris.
When they were boarding...
a kid had a vision that
the plane was gonna explode.
Just like you did.
He freaked out...
and seven people
got off the plane.
Just like us.
And on takeoff,
Flight 180 blew up.
And over the next several months...
everyone who got off that plane
started dying in weird accidents.
They died in the order they would've
if they had stayed on the plane.
Unless someone intervened,
then it skipped them.
Fuck you, Kevin.
W-Wendy! Wendy! Hey!
Ohh, every time we come here.
I was thinking of going
for 20 minutes in the Muller.
We did that for all the funerals
and it turned out amazing.
Yeah, but that was just
a couple of weeks ago, though.
I mean, we're still pretty bronzed.
I was just thinking
we could go for, like, a tune-up.
I just wanna make sure
that we look our best.
Yeah.
You know, for all those kids
that died that night...
who will never get a graduation.
You know what?
You're totally right.
- I'm sorry.
- Mmm.
This is my... my good guy
luck bracelet...
that Grandma left me in her will.
Ohh!
Julie?
I need...
I could use some help.
I have such...
such guilt over Jason.
I should never have let
that ride go.
God. I'm usually such
a control freak...
but I didn't do
enough to stop it.
I should've done everything
I could to stop it.
And I would give anything...
to have a second chance.
But I never can.
I don't want to some day
feel that way about you, Julie.
I mean,
I can't talk to Mom and Dad.
You're all I have left.
You think when I find a place...
maybe you could come stay
with me for a while?
You know I will.
You...
keep this now...
and I'll get it
when I come see you.
Oh. And... hey,
how 'bout on your end?
Can I use the school camera
for graduation tonight?
Yeah. As long as you bring it back
to school on Monday.
Done.
Oh. Um...
Actually, the battery is pretty low...
so why don't you go get ready,
and I'll recharge it a bit.
Cool.
In a hurry, Yuri.
Sorry, sorry.
Cell phone signal is shit in here.
I think tanning beds
mess with signal.
I must go outside.
Why don't you just use that phone?
I would, but she talks forever,
then my boss gives me shit.
Shit. That's her.
Ohh!
You know what? Just go outside.
We can deal with this ourselves.
OK.
Hey. No drinks in the room
this time, OK?
Good.
What are you doing?
Nobody is walking in here
and seein' me naked.
Oh, my God.
Dude, he said no drinks.
If you spill that shit...
we're gonna have to clean it
up like last time.
Mmm!
Happy, beyotch?
Nothing to spill.
Why does Yuri keep it
so cold in here?
Maybe it's supposed to be colder
for the machines or whatever.
Oh, a few degrees won't hurt.
Shit! I forgot my iPod.
Sucks, bitch.
They got CDs.
Ew. Celine?
Britney?
Dude, are we like the only cool people
that come here or what?
Uh, yeah.
Ugh. Whatever.
Why are you wearing underwear?
Steinmetz says
he gets off on tan lines.
All right.
# Roller coaster #
# Of love #
# Say what? #
# Roller coaster #
# Ooh ooh ooh #
# Right #
# Of love #
# Roller coaster #
# Ooh ooh ooh #
# Roller coaster of love #
# Roller coaster #
# Wow wow wow #
# Ooh ooh ooh #
# Roller coaster of love... #
# I #
# Huh, huh #
# I'm gonna ride, girl #
# Yeah #
# Whoo-hoo-hoo #
# Wow, yeah #
# Huh huh #
# Ow #
# Oh, oh #
Whoo.
# Roller coaster of love #
# Love roller coaster, girl #
# Roller coaster #
# Lovin' you
in a freaky world, child #
# Roller coaster of love #
Camera charged?
Oh, um, sorry,
the battery's totally dead.
Camera's not working. Sorry.
Look, Julie, I need a minute, OK?
Like private.
# That feels nice,
roller coaster #
# One more time #
# Roller coaster of love #
# Roller coaster #
Ugh.
It's way too warm in here now, huh?
I fucked up.
I set it too hot in here.
Huh?
Ow! Aah!
Hello?
- Hey, Ashley, it's Wendy...
- Psych! Leave a message.
Hi, Ashley, this is Wendy.
Gimme a call whenever
you guys are done.
Aah!
And thanks again for the invite.
- Someone help!
- Aah!
Sorry I was too late.
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Oh! Oh!
Oh! Aah!
Aaah! Aaah!
Hey, open the door!
Help me!
Aah!
We may feel that our lives
are not our own.
That Death controls,
frames our lives.
Our birth's nothing
but death begun.
Yet, whether it is with
this tragic loss of young lives...
which we have
suffered much of late...
or with the soft passing
of the elderly in the night...
we are all equal in Death's eyes.
"Equal in Death's eyes?"
All of us?
How can you say that?
Shut up, McKinley.
Dude, think it through.
Charlie Manson made it to 70.
- Osama? Still kickin'.
- Let's go.
Pimps, vice-presidents
walking around.
- All the atrocities they've committed...
- Let's just go. Come on.
They're alive and well.
These two girls, who'd never
done shit to anybody...
- Shh!
- They don't get to make it to 18?
Where's the fucking
equality in that?
- What?
- Come on, man.
I can... Yeah. Fine.
Fine. All right. All right.
I'm fine. All right.
That's crazy.
Those of you who would like
to pay a final remembrance...
please step forward at this time.
I so feel this is so my fault.
How could it possibly be your fault?
Seein' women as nothin' but fun bags.
I mean... if I'd've seen their...
whatever... humanity...
they wouldn't have felt
the pressure to look so good.
Impress Franklin Cheeks.
Go on diets. Deodorize.
Stretch. Tan.
Don't be down, Frankie.
Be proud of your ability
to make everything...
that happens somehow
a story about you.
God!
Yo, man.
These things really suck, man.
Fucking boring.
Hey, if you ever have
to come to my funeral...
man, bring me a PSP or somethin'.
'Least I have somethin' to do then.
Whew.
Hello?
I'm with J.
What are you doing up here
in the nosebleeds?
You know, I could've
gotten you second row.
I didn't want to upset
anyone by being there.
And I wondered if
maybe here I could feel J's...
spirit or presence or...
whatever.
But now that I'm here...
if there's any place that makes me feel
like there's no life after death...
it's a cemetery.
Yeah, I haven't felt
Carrie's spirit either.
And I've tried.
Real hard. Heh.
I thought maybe
he's been with me since...
that night...
before I got on the ride...
Jason said...
God, and it was just
to get me on the ride...
he said...
"Your fear is from a sense
of having no control."
And I've felt that fear
since the moment he said it.
Even thought it maybe somehow
caused the hallucination...
but this fear is more
than just being scared.
It's like a presence.
Like a living thing
always with me.
You think it's J?
No, I know it's not.
This presence is the opposite
of how J made me feel.
It's cold and terrifying.
That's the last photograph
Lincoln posed for.
The photographic plate
was broken...
causing a line
that can't be removed.
Exactly where he was shot.
Look. See the shadow?
But what do these pictures
have to do with us?
Look. This occurred
one year to the day...
of the Flight 180 disaster.
Look at the road sign.
Look, I guess you came
to me with this...
because I'm responsible
for putting this in your head...
with the Flight 180 thing.
And it did happen,
and it may be occurring here...
but you can't believe
every weird thing out there...
because you're desperate
for an answer.
I took these.
That night.
These?
Are these it?
Oh, shit.
Oh... shit.
Ohh.
Whoa, whoa, hey.
You all right?
I'm feeling a little woozy.
When was the last time you ate?
I don't remember.
All right, come on. I'll drive.
OK, those kids on Flight 180
died in accidents...
in the order they would've died
if they'd have stayed on the plane.
OK?
So if this is that, then...
then Frankie was behind
Ashlyn and Ashley.
When I saw Ashley
and Ashlyn's picture...
I felt this instinct.
Like there was a hint
in the picture. I even...
I even called to see if
I could keep them from going.
Well, what's
Frankie's picture look like?
It's right here.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
- Wait! Watch out!
- Oh!
Hey! Hey! Are you crazy?
Sorry!
All right,
let's just eat over there.
And go through
the drive through.
I don't want anyone hearing
what we're talking about.
Well, it's nice to see
that things haven't made you...
any less of a control freak.
- You got it?
- Yeah, all right.
Here's Frank's picture.
All right.
Well, this is obvious.
He's falling off a ladder.
A rope ladder, though.
Maybe he might hang.
Look, or maybe it's not that literal.
All right, what's...
Could there be anything
in these prizes?
Oh, what, like he's gonna get
crushed by a giant Spongebob?
Hey, Spongebob lives underwater.
It's so sad that you know that.
All right. He won that tacky
mud-flap girl chain...
on this game, though, so...
aren't those usually
on those big 18 wheelers?
Yeah. Yeah.
God, I don't see it in
this picture anywhere though.
All right! God.
All right.
Uh, can I take your order?
Yeah. What do you want?
Are you OK?
Please tell me
there's a short in your wiring.
Whoa. Whoa. That guy's
way too close to my truck.
Hey, you're too fucking
close, man! Pull up!
Hey!
# There is someone #
Stop! Stop!
# Walking behind you #
Watch out! Shit!
- What the fuck?
- # Turn around #
- Oh, my God!
- # Look at me #
- Get out! Get out!
- What? What?
Behind us!
There's no one in that truck!
# Watching your footsteps #