(PEOPLE YELLING)
(YELLING AND CHEERING)
JASON: Oh, man.
~ Did you see that?
Whoo! That was fun.
Oh, my God. Ha-ha-ha.
~ Yes. Yes.
~ Nice, nice, nice.
~ Aw, sick.
~ Worth the wait.
~ Oh, babe, you missed out.
WOMAN: Yes.
BOY (SOBBING):
I wanna get off.
FATHER: Okay. He doesn't like it.
JASON: Whoo! Ow!
(GROUP LAUGHING)
That was intense, man. To feel how that would be to just crash and burn like that.
Maybe for you, but our lives
are actually going somewhere.
Where we gotta go is to the roller coaster, because our pass is for 9:15.
If we miss that
and stand in line for a day....
....then that's gonna kill me.
All right? Let's go.
MAN: They're totally
gonna dig this, man!
It won't kill us to get
a deep-fried Snickers and a Coke.
Before riding Devil's Flight?
That might kill me.
No. What doesn't kill you
makes you stronger, man.
(CARRIE & JASON LAUGH)
(RIDERS YELLING)
KEVIN: I'll take that.
WENDY: No. Come on, give me~~
It's not even mine, Kevin,
It's the yearbook's. Just- Kevin.
JASON: Oh!
KEVIN: Oh, got it.
~ Oh, my God. You're such an idiot.
~ Hey. Hey!
~ Give me the~~
WENDY: Ha, ha!
KEVIN:
Ow!
Um, could you, like, please
delete that one of Stacy?
(GRUNTS THEN CHUCKLES)
These are for the yearbook, and I have to turn them in tomorrow for a deadline.
And, like, I doubt it if a shot of Stacy Kobayashi's camel toe....
~ ....is gonna make it in there.
~ Whew. Shit, I'd buy two.
(JASON & KEVIN LAUGHING)
MAN (OVER PA):
Number 38, your order's ready.
JASON:
That's us.
I am so sorry.
Kevin can get so out of control.
Let me just say,
he would make me crazy.
I mean, you know, I'm such a control freak. Like, I couldn't handle that.
(WENDY SIGHS)
I'm breaking up with him.
Couple of weeks. After graduation.
I've been wanting to for a while.
But don't tell anybody, okay?
KEVIN:
Whoa. Ha-ha-ha!
Now, that shot there,
that'll sell some yearbooks.
ASHLEY:
Ha-ha-ha. I love it. I love it.
Oh! Ch, all right,
so I'm a total whore.
ASHLEY: Come on. Go, go, go!
ASHLYN: Ashley, you're winning.
~ You're totally winning.
ASHLEY: Am I winning?
ASHLYN: Yeah, hurry!
~ Okay. Come on, come on, come on!
FRANKIE:
Check out those booties.
~ Am I winning? I don't wanna look away.
~ You're winning.
ASHLEY: Come on, come on, come on!
ASHLYN: Don't look.
ASHLEY: Oh, my God! Come on!
ASHLYN: Oh, my God!
ASHLEY:
I'm winning, I'm winning.
(ASHLEY and ASHLYN SHRIEK)
(BELL RINGING)
~ I won!
~ I knew you would.
ASHLEY: Oh, my God! Give me my prize.
MAN: Here you go.
ASHLYN: That was awesome, Ashley.
MAN: Good job.
Ashley.
(DANCE MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
Whoo! Ha-ha-ha.
How you doing, my brother?
You having a good time? Huh? All right.
~ You like that?
~ Yeah.
You know you like it.
Give it up. Give it up.
Whoo-ooh!
LEWIS: Damn!
Excuse me.
You're not a senior.
And what are you gonna do about it, Miss Cutest-Couple, rah, rah?
~ Ha-ha-ha!
~ Mom know you're here?
You are a complete bitch
if you tell her.
~ Proof where you were.
~ Take a shot of this.
(WOMAN CHUCKLES)
(CALLIOPE MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE YELLING)
(BELL DINGS)
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about. That's three.
(SINGING)
That is three, number three
Oh, I'm the man, I'm the man
Man, I am hot
Give me some right here, man.
What you doing? Get the fuck back. Hoo!
My God, I am good.
Here we go.
Boy, I'll tell you. Goddamn. Whoo!
BARKER:
Kind sir, step right up!
LEWIS: Here we go, baby, 3 for 3.
it's all mine.
Here we go. Here we go. Big prize. Watch out. Come on.
(GRUNTS)
(LAUGHS)
(SINGING)
That's what I'm talkin' 'bout
We gonna get that, but do we want that blue one? That's the one we gonna get.
(DEVIL LAUGHING)
(RIDERS YELL)
DEVIL:
You can run, but you cannot hide.
MAN 1:
Yes. Here we are, baby.
WOMAN: Yes!
~ Whoo! There it is.
CARRIE: Awesome.
~ Here, get a pic of this. Ahh!
DEVIL:
This is the beginning of the end.
(RIDERS YELL)
(DEVIL LAUGHING)
MAN 2:
Hey, guys, get in line.
GIRL:
Let's go on again!
What's wrong?
Um....
I was having that feeling
like déja vu, you know?
Except for something
that hasn't happened yet.
Hey, J. Come on, man, let's go.
~ Yeah, yeah, hold on.
KEVIN: Come on.
Are you weirded out by the ride?
Because, look, I know you.
I think that maybe you're nervous about this roller coaster because they say....
....the real fear with these rides comes from the feeling of having no control.
Everyone imagines weird stuff
when they get scared.
But it never turns out to be
what they imagine. Never.
~ Okay.
DEVIL: You can run, but you cannot hide.
Oh! Where you guys are right now....
....if you raise your hands
and just, heh, cup them slightly....
....it'll look like you're holding the devil's balls.
And we'd wanna do that, why?
When else you ever gonna
see a dick that big?
I'm looking at one right now.
~ Ha-ha-ha! Man, you guys are smoking hot.
~ Get out, Frankie.
~ Yeah, why are you even here?
~ Yeah, you graduated two years ago.
I stuck around to monitor
your development.
KEVIN: Yeah. Good to go?
~ Good to go, baby.
KEVIN: Let's do it.
~ Come on.
Well, go.
DEVIL:
You may never return from Devil's Flight.
(DEVIL LAUGHING)
Try not to scream.
GIRL:
It's so fun!
(CHATTERING AND LAUGHING)
(RIDERS YELL)
(GIRL YELLS AND LAUGHS)
(RIDERS CHEERING)
(BRAKES HISS)
(GASPS)
You all right? There's nothing
to worry about.
A roller coaster is just
elemental physics.
A conversion of potential energy
to kinetic energy.
Yep. Odds are like 1 in 250 million of dying in a roller coaster.
Yeah, yeah. Thanks for that, McKinley.
You're more likely to die driving to an amusement park than dying at one.
KEVIN:
Whoo!
(SIGHS)
(RIDERS YELL)
ATTENDANT:
Here we go.
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
(MEN CHEERING)
You like this?
Won it on The Wacky Ladder.
You know that ladder deal
that wobbles? Took it.
I like this. it's old-school.
Frankie Cheeks is old-school, ladies.
What's that?
Oh, well, it'd be my honor.
Ew. Ugh. Let's go.
Hey, baby.
ATTENDANT: How many?
~ Uh, four.
~ Four. Uh, gate one.
~ Yeah.
~ Yeah. Front car.
~ Wait, no.
No, please. I don't wanna be a hassle.
I just can't sit in front.
I cannot see the tracks. I'll freak.
Okay, take it easy. Uh, well, Carrie will sit in the back with you. Right, babe?
(SCOFFS)
Why me? What, because we're girls?
Fuck that. I'm going to Berkeley
and I won't get to do this for a while.
~ I'm sitting in the front.
~ J, just go. Okay?
~ I'll live.
~ You're not sitting by yourself.
You know what? We'll settle this
like real men. How about that? Hm?
~ Call it.
JASON: Heads.
Shit. Damn it.
(KEVIN SIGHS)
Fine, what the fuck?
it's the same ride, right?
Go. Go ahead. Bye, babe.
Hey, uh, just do me a favor. Keep an eye on her, okay? She's freaked out.
~ Oh. Cool. Yeah. Go on, buddy. No problem.
~ All right? Sweet.
(CHATTERING AND LAUGHING)
(GIRL SHRIEKS)
(BRAKES HISS)
(WHIMPERS)
Here we go. Hey, J! Keep your hands to yourself, man. I'm serious.
You know, payback's a bitch, okay?
She might need some comforting
and I'm gonna be there for her.
~ Hey, no, no. Get out. Get out.
~ Hey, find another cockpit, top gun.
~ No. Get~~
~ Let's just get in the back, okay?
(ASHLYN SIGHS)
(FRANKIE LAUGHING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Guess who's back.
(IN UNISON)
Ugh.
Hey!
I'll meet you at the end.
BOY 1: Come on, back here.
BOY 2: All right. Cool.
~ Hey, how'd you guys get in here?
~ What? I'm 55 inches.
~ Sure. Come on. You two. Out.
BOY 2: Oh, man.
Ready?
BOY 3:
I told you we wouldn't get away with it.
~ You okay?
BOY 3: Let's go on the bumper cars.
Come on. Here we go.
MAN 1:
Aw, yeah!
Yeah.
What's up, man? I'm good. Unh.
(SQUEAKS)
Dare you to, uh, flash me them sweet titties when we go through the loop.
(GASPS)
~ All right. Ha-ha-ha.
~ Ha-ha-ha.
Yo! What, you can't read?
Oh, well, can I just put it
in my pocket, man? Is that cool?
~ Yeah.
~ Yeah? Cool. Thanks, buddy. Sorry.
Oh!
Aw, Shit!
Here you go!
(RIDERS CHEERING)
Whoo! Win, baby!
Yes, baby! Win!
MAN 2:
Come on!
Come on. Get hyped.
~ The first hill's so high.
~ Yeah.
MAN 3:
Let's go, baby!
WOMAN 1: Yeah!
JASON: Yeah!
MAN 4:
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
~ Let's do this.
~ Just win!
MAN 5:
Ow!
WOMAN 2:
Whoo!
WOMAN 3:
Aw, yeah!
Whoo!
Whoo! Shit!
(CHUCKLES)
(WOMAN 4 SHRIEKS)
~ Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
JASON: Here we go.
JASON: Whoo-hoo-hoo-hoo!
CARRIE: Aah!
JASON:
Yeah!
(SQUEAKS)
(ALL YELLING)
Whoo!
Ha-ha-ha! Whoo!
~ Yeah! Show me your titties!
~ Fuck off, Frankie!
Oh!
(ALL SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
Oh, Shit!
WOMAN 5: Oh, my God!
We're gonna fall off!
(SCREECHING)
(PEOPLE SCREAM)
(FRANKIE GRUNTING)
FRANKIE:
Shit!
(GROANS)
~ Unh!
~ Kevin!
No.
(SCREAMS)
No! Ian!
MAN 6:
Help!
(ALL PANTING AND WHIMPERING)
ERIN: Aah!
~ Erin, hang on!
~ Hang on!
~ Don't let go!
I can't.
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(THUDS)
~ Oh, God!
~ Hang on, Wen.
(BODIES THUDDING)
Hang on! Help me rock it!
(WENDY & KEVIN GRUNTING)
Almost got it. Gently.
(SCREAMS)
No!
(WENDY GRUNTS THEN SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
ATTENDANT: Yo. What, you can't read?
~ I'll just put it in my pocket, okay?
~ Yeah.
~ Thanks, bro.
All right. Let's do this.
~ What are you~~?
ATTENDANT: Here you go!
~ Yeah! Let's do it, baby! Whoo!
~ We have to get off of here.
No, don't push the button!
Don't push the button!
~ Unh! Let me off! Let me off!
~ Wen, Wen! it's all right.
~ Jesus, it's gonna be~~
~ No! it's gonna crash!
The hydraulics will rupture!
The tracks will collapse! Please!
~ What's going on?
~ Let me off!
Chick's on something.
~ Okay, let them out. Just the back.
KEVIN: Wen. Hey, Wendy!
(SOBBING)
COLOUITT:
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
~ Relax. Now, what's the matter?
~ I saw it. I saw it in my head.
The tracks collapsed.
The roller coaster crashed.
~ No, she was just a little upset before.
LEWIS: Man, can you control that bitch?
Damn. "it's gonna crash.
The hydraulics, the coaster."
~ She's just trying to get attention.
~ You're a real piece of shit, Lewis.
~ Fuck you.
~ Fuck moi?
~ No, man, fuck you!
~ Don't touch me.
Ow!
(ALL GRUNTING)
COLQUITT:
You relax! Hey!
~ Hey, let me out.
~ Nobody else gets off this ride!
Dude, let me off!
~ So high school.
~ Let's out.
ERIN: Get off of him. Ian.
COLQUITT: Relax!
Where you ladies going?
There's a fight.
Get him out of here!
Hey! Calm down! Relax!
Dude, let me oft.
I gotta make sure she's okay.
~ Hey, ho, let's go!
MAN: Get out of here!
RIDERS (CHANTING): Hey, ho, let's go!
~ Let me out!
~ Hey, ho, let's go! Hey, ho, let's go!
~ Dude.
~ Hey, ho, let's go!
~ Here we go!
JASON: Let me off!
RIDERS: Hey, ho, let's go!
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
~ Dude, that's my girlfriend!
~ Oh, my God.
(RIDERS APPLAUDING
AND CHEERING)
Stop it! No! Stop it!
Stop it! Please! Please,
the tracks are broken. Stop!
~ Stop! Please!
~ Hey.
WENDY:
Jason!
Hey, just relax, okay?
~ Please!
~ Ease up, man. She's all right. Okay?
~ Let her settle down.
COLQUITT: She's going home.
Now listen, what is your
home phone number?
Okay, we can call your mother.
Everything will be taken care of.
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(SOBBING)
Jason!
(RAINDROPS PATTERING)
(THUNDER CRASHING)
(WENDY SIGHS)
(SOFAS)
(WIND BLOWS)
KEVIN:
Hey, Wendy.
Hey.
Wait, Wendy. Hey!
Hey, wait. I need to talk
to you about something.
Just here to pick up my diploma.
~ You're not going to graduation?
~ No.
Look, you're not the only one
in a fucked-up place, okay?
I just thought it'd be good for you to be where other people feel the same~~
In graduation?
No, thanks, I've had enough funerals.
~ Do it for J and Carrie.
~ Do what?
If you die and there's nothing, then they're just dead and they don't know.
If they're in heaven with Lincoln and Gandhi, do they care about graduation?
No. I am alive and I don't care.
As soon as I pull out of that parking lot I am so out of McKinley.
~ Without J, what's here for me?
~ I'm here. Okay?
I made a promise to J
that I would take care of you.
On the ride for 3 minutes.
You weren't making
the promise for a lifetime.
(WENDY SIGHS)
Kevin, if it wasn't for
you and J being friends....
....and me and Carrie being friends, we wouldn't have even hung out.
We don't even like each other.
IAN:
Ian McKinley.
How pathetic is it that my last name is the same as my high school?
Julie, look who I got
to sign my yearbook.
~ No way. Nice.
~ Yeah. Heh.
I think we should invite her.
~ You think?
~ Yeah.
Wen? Um....
So we're ready for graduation tonight, we're going to the tanning salon.
And we are so totally cool
if you wanna come with.
ASHLYN: Totally.
ASHLEY: And just, like, talk if you want.
Here's my cell.
I already have your number.
That was so nice of us.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
~ You're not alone.
~ I appreciate everyone trying to help.
~ Okay? I really do.
~ No, it's happened before.
Okay? I went online looking
for an explanation about~~
Wendy, just listen to me, all right.
Okay, look, I went online looking for an explanation about what happened.
I found out about this high school class from New York.
Six years ago
they went on a trip to Paris.
When they were boarding, a kid had a vision that the plane was gonna explode.
Just like you did.
He freaked out and seven
people got off the plane.
Just like us.
On takeoff Flight 180 blew up.
Over the next several months,
everyone who got off that plane....
....started dying in weird accidents.
They died in the order
they would've on the plane.
Unless someone intervened,
then it skipped them.
Fuck you, Kevin.
Wait~~ Wendy. Wendy! Hey!
(THUNDER CRASHES)
(SLURPING DRINK)
(YURI SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN)
Uhh.... Every time we come here~~
I was thinking of going
for 20 minutes in the Muller.
It turned out amazing for the funerals.
That was just two weeks ago,
we're still pretty bronzed.
I was just thinking we'd go
for, like, a tune-up.
~ I wanna make sure we look our best.
~ Well, yeah.
For all those kids that died that night who will never get a graduation.
(SIGHS)
You know what, you're totally right. I'm sorry.
(UNZIPS BAG)
This is my good-guy-luck bracelet
that Grandma left me in her will.
Ohh!
Julie?
(SIGHS)
I need~~
I could use some help.
I have such guilt over Jason.
I should never have let that ride go.
God, I'm usually such a control freak but I didn't do enough to stop it.
I should've done everything
I could to stop it.
And I would give anything
to have a second chance.
But I never can.
I don't want to someday feel
that way about you, Julie.
I mean, I can't talk to Mom and Dad.
You're all I have left.
You think when I find a place, maybe you could come stay for a while?
You know I will.
You....
....keep this now and I'll get it
when I come see you.
Oh, and, hey,
how about on your end....
....can I use the school camera
for graduation tonight?
Yeah. As long as you bring it
back to school on Monday.
Done.
Oh, um, actually, the battery
is pretty low so....
....why don't you go get ready
and I'll recharge it a bit?
Cool.
(YURI SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN)
~ In a hurry, Yuri.
~ Sorry, cell phone signal is shit in here.
I think tanning beds mess with signal. I must go outside.
Why don't you just use that phone?
I would, but she talks forever
then my boss gives me shit.
(RING TONE PLAYING ON PHONE)
Shit. That's her.
(SIGHS)
You know what, just go outside.
~ We can deal with this ourselves.
~ Okay.
Hey, no drinks in the room
this time, okay?
Good.
(YURI SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN)
What are you doing?
Nobody's walking in here,
and seeing me naked.
(WIND BLOWING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN)
Oh, my God.
ASHLYN:
Dude, he said no drinks.
If you spill that shit we're gonna have to clean it up like last time.
Mmm!
Happy, beyotch? Nothing to spill.
Why does Yuri keep it so cold in here?
Maybe it's supposed to be
colder for the machines.
Oh, a few degrees won't hurt.
(l-HUMMING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
Shit. I forgot my iPod.
Sucks, bitch.
They got CDs.
(ASHLEY SIGHS)
Ew. "Celine"? "Britney"?
Are we the only cool
people that come here or what?
Uh, yeah.
Ugh. Whatever.
(CREAKS)
(SIGHS)
Why are you wearing underwear?
Steinmetz says he gets
off on tan lines.
Ugh. An right.
(YURI SHOUTING IN RUSSIAN)
(THE OHIO PLAYERS' "LOVE
ROLLERCOASTER" PLAYING)
(SINGING ALONG)
Roller coaster
Of love
Say what?
Roller coaster
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
(OVER SPEAKERS)
Roller coaster
~ Right
~ Of love
(SINGING)
Roller coaster
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Roller coaster of love
(OVER SPEAKERS)
Roller coaster
~ Wow, wow, wow
~ Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh
Roller coaster of love
(WIND BLOWS)
(OVER SPEAKERS)
Ride
Don 't you wanna ride, girl?
Yeah
Ah. Heh.
Whoo.
~ Roller coaster of love
~ Love roller coaster, girl
Roller coaster
Lovin' you
In a freaked-out world, child
Roller coaster of love
(CRACKLING)
JULIE:
Camera charged?
Oh, um, sorry, the battery's totally dead.
Camera's not working. Sorry.
Look, Julie, I need e minute. Okay?
Like private.
Whoo.
(OVER SPEAKERS)
One more time
Roller coaster of love
Roller coaster
(AIR BLOWING)
Roller coaster of love
Ugh.
It's way too warm in here now, huh?
I fucked up. I set it too hot in here.
(RING TONE PLAYING ON PHONE)
Huh?
Ow! Ah!
ASHLEY: Hello?
~ Hey, Ashley, it's Wendy~~
Psych. Leave a message.
(BEEPS)
Hi, Ashley, this is Wendy.
WENDY: Give me a call when you guys are done and thanks for the invite.
Someone help!
(SCREAMING)
Sorry I was too late.
YURI:
Hey, open the door!
Help me!
We may feel that
our lives are not our own.
That death controls, frames our lives.
Our births nothing but death begun.
Yet, whether it is with this
tragic loss of young lives....
....which we have
suffered much of late....
....or with the soft passing
of the elderly in the night....
....we are all equal in death's eyes.
"Equal in death's eyes"'?
~ All of us? How can you say that?
MAN: Shut up, McKinley.
Dude, think it through.
Charlie Manson made it to 70.
~ Osama? Still kicking.
~ Let's go.
Pimps, vice presidents walking around.
All the atrocities they've committed, they're alive and well.
These two girls, who've never
done shit to anybody....
~ ....they don't get to make it to 18?
~ Shh!
IAN:
Where's the fucking equality in that?
~ Come on, man.
~ What? I can~~ Fine.
Fine. All right. All right.
I'm fine. All right.
Those of you who would like
to pay a final remembrance....
....please step forward at this time.
I so feel this is so my fault.
How could it possibly be your fault?
Seeing women as nothing but fun bags.
I mean, if I had seen their,
whatever, humanity....
....they wouldn't have felt the pressure to look so good. Impress Franklin Cheeks.
Go on diets. Deodorize. Stretch.
Tan.
Don't be down, Frankie. Be proud
of your ability to make everything....
....that happens somehow
a story about you.
God.
Yo, man. These things
really suck, man.
Fucking boring.
Hey, if you ever have
to come to my funeral....
....men, bring me a PSP or something. Least I have something to do then.
(PHONE RINGING)
(SIGHS)
~ Hello?
WENDY: I'm with J.
(PHONE BEEPS)
What are you doing
up here in the nosebleeds?
You know, I could've
gotten you second row.
I didn't want to upset
anyone by being there.
And I wondered if maybe
here I could feel J's....
....spirit or presence or whatever.
(SIGHS)
But now that I'm here....
If there's anyplace that makes me feel like there's no life after death....
....it's a cemetery.
Yeah, I haven't felt
Carrie's spirit either.
And I've tried.
Real hard. Heh.
I thought maybe
he's been with me since....
That night, before I got on the ride, Jason said~~
God, and it was just to get me
on the ride, he said:
"Your fear is from a sense
of having no control."
And I've felt that fear
since the moment he said it.
Even thought it maybe somehow
caused the hallucination, but....
....this fear is more
than just being scared.
It's like a presence.
Like a living thing always with me.
~ You think it's J?
~ No, I know it's not.
This presence is the opposite
of how J made me feel.
It's cold and terrifying.
WENDY: That's the last photograph
Lincoln posed for.
The photographic plate broke,
causing a line that can't be removed....
....exactly where he was shot.
Look. See the shadow?
KEVIN: Well, what do these pictures have to do with us?
Look.
This is one year before the Flight 180 disaster. Look at the road sign!
You came to me because I'm responsible for putting Flight 180 in your head.
And it did happen,
and it may be occurring here.
But you can't believe every weird thing.
~ You're desperate for an answer.
~ I took these.
That night.
These?
Are these it?
Oh, shit.
(WENDY SIGHS)
Whoa, whoa, hey.
You all right?
I'm feeling a little woozy.
When was the last time you ate?
I don't remember.
KEVIN:
All right, come on. I'll drive.
The kids on Flight 180 died in accidents in the order they would have died....
....if they'd have stayed on the plane. Okay? So if this is that, then....
Then Frankie was behind
Ashlyn and Ashley.
When I saw Ashley and Ashlyn's
picture, I felt this instinct.
Like there was a hint in the picture.
I called to see if I could
keep them from going.
~ What's Frankie's look like?
~ Right here.
KEVIN: You got it?
WENDY: Yeah.
WENDY: Watch out!
MAN: Hey!
~ Hey! Are you crazy?
KEVIN: Sorry!
(SIGHS)
WENDY:
All right, let's just eat there.
And drive through.
I don't want anyone hearing.
Well, it's nice to see things haven't made you less of a control freak.
~ You got it?
~ Yeah, all right.
~ Here's Frank's picture.
~ All right.
This is obvious,
he's falling off a ladder.
A rope ladder, though.
Maybe he might hang.
Or maybe it's not that literal.
Could there be anything
in these prizes?
What? Like he's gonna get crushed
by a giant SpongeBob?
Hey, SpongeBob lives underwater.
It's so sad that you know that.
He won that tacky mudflap girl chain on this game, though.
Aren't those usually on
those big 18-Wheelers?
~ Yeah. Yeah.
~ I don't see it in this picture anywhere.
(CAR HORN HONKING)
All right. God.
All right.
MAN 1: Uh, can I take your order?
~ Yeah. What do you want?
(SCREEN CRACKLING)
KEVIN:
Wen, you okay?
(TRUCK BEEPING)
(STATIC WAVERING)
Please tell me
there's a short in your wiring.
Whoa. Hey, that guy's way too close to my truck.
You're too fucking close, man!
Pull up!
Hey!
(THE VOGUES' "TURN AROUND,
LOOK AT ME" PLAYING OVER RADIO)
(CRASH)
There is someone
MAN 2 (IN DISTANCE):
Stop! Aah!
Walking behind you
Watch out! Shit! What the fuck?
MAN 2:
Oh, my God!
~ Get out! Get out!
~ What? What?
Behind us!
There's no one in that truck!
Watching your footsteps
Shit! Hey, pull up, man!
Come on! Pull up!
(l-HONKING)
Look at me
KEVIN: Unh! Shit!
~ Back up! Back up!
Who really loves you
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Here's my heart
Watch your eyes!
Watch your eyes! Come here!
Turn around
Come on.
Look at me
KEVIN: Come on, let's go!
Come on, come on, come on!
(BOTH PANTING)
(WENDY WHIMPERS)
(GASPS)
(cl-CHATTERING)
(SIREN WAILING)
We're all done here. You need a ride?
Um, we can walk to my house
and then I'll give you a ride to yours.
No, thanks, we'll be okay.
Will We?
(SIGHS)
Yeah, we'll be all right.
I mean, how Frank....
God, it's not only horrible,
but can you feel....?
Can you feel how vicious it was?
Easy. Okay? Easy.
Let's just....
Let's just take a step back.
He was behind Ashley and Ashlyn,
but there was no ladder here.
You know? There was no rope.
Nothing in that picture pointed to this.
We were wrong about the photos.
I should have left town.
it's better not knowing.
No, it's never better staying ignorant.
Willful ignorance
is surrendering control.
What, did you read that somewhere
in Mrs. Brooks' English class?
No. l~~ You know, I'm not~~
I'm not the total idiot you think I am.
WENDY:
Okay, that's Lewis after Frank....
....then Ian and Erin.
There's a couple of kids behind them, but I can't make them out.
~ Can you?
~ No.
(SIGHS)
You know what? We'll ask Lewis,
Ian, and Erin if they remember, okay?
Are there any more pictures
from the roller coaster?
I guess that kind of thing is gonna happen to us the rest of our lives.
Yeah.
You know, I was gonna....
I was gonna ask her to marry me.
Right after graduation.
(MOUSE CLICKING)
Ch.
No, wait. Look, behind Stacy.
That's Frank.
This picture shows how he died.
All right, go back to Lewis.
WENDY:
Okay, he's got that hammer.
And the weight looks like
it's coming down on his head.
Check this out. Lewis is down at State for football training camp.
State's team is called the Sultans.
That's it. That's the clue.
We have to tell him.
Show him these pictures.
Wouldn't you want to know?
~ What, there's pictures of us in there?
~ Yeah. Yeah, of course.
(SIGHS)
No. No, I don't want to see mine. No.
~ What about willful ignorance?
~ Well, I'm full of shit, all right?
I mean, I never thought I could
see my own death before it happened.
No, you know what?
We can tell Lewis, but~~
Seriously, if there's any way
to beat this thing....
....l gotta stay focused.
If I look, all I'm gonna do is obsess.
So you know what?
No, I don't want to see it.
I mean, unless we have to.
You mean until we have to.
One more thing.
Is it bad?
I mean, is it, like,
painful or embarrassing?
~ There's nothing up my ass or anything?
~ I'll see you tomorrow.
~ You on crack. Both of you.
~ Just listen.
Ashley and Ashlyn were first,
then Frankie, then you.
~ This is~~
~ Aw, come on, Kevin.
McKinley and Erin were next and
there were two people in front of us.
~ Remember who?
~ No, and I don't care.
You shouldn't care either.
What you're telling me is bullshit.
~ Listen, Lewis.
LEWIS: Kevin, it's like those stories.
Like, this guy was killed
by a car he stole 10 years ago.
Two sisters were killed when
driving to go visit each other.
You know, shit like that, man.
MAN 1: Fuck the Bruins!
MAN 2: Oh, yeah!
MAN 3: Yeah!
MAN 4: Fuck the Bruins!
MAN 5: Faggots!
MAN 6: Fuck the Bruins!
You're reading into this shit
like urban legends.
Three people have died, Lewis.
If you think this can be written off as a coincidence and it ends there....
....you're in serious denial.
~ Unh. What about you two, huh?
~ What?
You both lost people real close to you in a fucked-up way.
In order to feel less guilty or whatever, seeing signs and patterns, man.
I don't blame you, but it's wrong, dog. Unh! it's wrong.
(\/vEIGl-ITS CLUNK)
That's denial.
Unh!
MAN 7: Unh!
MAN 8: You got it!
What about what happened
at the roller coaster? Huh?
~ Wendy saw it.
~ She got a hunch.
Fucking intense, but she got a hunch.
I'm here because I get hunches
before every down.
No, you know they're
gonna run or pass.
Hers came to her
from nowhere.
~ You're here and alive because of her.
~ No, I'm alive because of me.
No, listen. You don't get it, man.
~ Does that make sense?
LEWIS: Nothing to get.
~ It's bullshit.
KEVIN: No, just hear me out, all right?
(MAN 9 GRUNTING)
(OVER RADIO)
Yeah
(HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(RATTLING)
Talk about a vision.
Man, I seen my whole life played out and it sure as hell ain't gonna end now. Unh!
It's going just as I saw it.
Thirty-five high school games
without an injury.
~ USA Today All-American.
~ Second team.
~ My free ride to the Sultans!
~ Bruins passed on you.
~ Man, fuck the Bruins!
MEN: Fuck them!
~ You goddamn right!
MAN 10: What the fuck is a Bruin anyway?
(MEN GRUNTING)
Four years from now, Lewis Romero
going in the second round to Oakland.
He's gonna romp and stomp.
Fifteen seasons with four
Super Bowl rings on his fingers.
Lewis ain't afraid of no death.
Fuck death!
Death is a fucking Denver fan.
Death wear blue and orange.
Real men wear black.
Lewis ain't afraid of no death.
Death is afraid of me!
Death fears me!
WENDY: Kevin.
LEWIS: Because, baby, I just win.
I just win, Kevin.
That's all I know how to do.
I just win. Unh!
~ Fuck death!
MAN 11: Fuck the Bruins!
Yeah!
Aah!
~ Look out!
KEVIN: Lewis!
MAN 12:
Man, that was close.
MAN 13:
Did you see that?
Whoo! What did I tell you, Kevin, huh? Fuck death!
I just win. That's all I know
how to do, Kevin.
Baby, I just win!
(YELLS)
~ Aah!
~ God!
Did I do something....
....to bring this on everybody?
Don't, Wendy.
But why me?
All those people out there wanting to have a premonition or see a ghost.
I don't.
I just want it to stop. Just stop.
I don't know why, Wendy,
but you didn't do anything.
All right? This is just....
I don't know. I mean,
I wish I knew why.
I wish I could come up with a guess, even, to make you feel okay, but....
Yeah, I can't.
There's nothing I can do.
(KEYS RATTLE)
Can you drive?
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
You know, by the way,
that picture of me....
My, uh~~
My head's not, like,
through the windshield or anything?
You know, crushed by a steering wheel, impaled by a gearshift?
(DOOR CLOSES)
Right?
(SNIFFS AND BLOWS)
ERIN (OVER RADIO): Zip, it's Pip.
Have you out those plywood orders yet?
Uh, that's a big no, Pip.
IAN: Osama Bin Supervisor wants me to get rid of these pigeons first.
They keep setting off the alarms.
(PIGEONS COOING)
Hello, babies.
(LAUGHING)
Hey. After I restock this stuff....
....these pinhead customers can't manage to return to the shelves themselves....
....we can blow out of here, okay?
IAN:
Rightio, babe.
(BANGING ON DOOR)
Aah!
~ Sorry. it's Wendy and Kevin.
~ Shit!
You scared the shit out of me!
Yeah, wait until you hear
what we have to tell you.
ERIN:
Zip, it's Pip. Come over here.
You are gonna trip
when you hear this.
Well, paint me intrigued,
Pip, I'm on my way.
ERIN: So, let me get this.
I OD on nail polish....
....and Ian is gonna be
embarrassed to death?
You saw what happened
to Wendy, right?
What's happened to the others?
I mean, you just saw their pictures.
Oh, my God, guys,
what's going on?
What's going on?
That's crazy. That's crazy.
(ERIN LAUGHS)
We need to know who was
behind you on the roller coaster.
Okay, who was sitting behind
us on the roller coaster?
Oh. Wait. Wasn't it that one guy voted most likely to become manager at Red Lobster?
You know what? I remember.
There was this guy. Uh, black cloak. I didn't see his face, but, um....
....the ride attendant did
take his sickle....
....before the ride started,
if that's helpful in any way.
Do you think we care
if you laugh at us?
This is our lives, okay? What choice do we have? Just give into it?
God. You know what?
There is no "it."
Are you guys saying
that death is, like, a person?
No. it's like a force.
Yeah. Well, you know what?
A force is just a force.
It's nothing else.
Just transferred energy.
I mean, it has no goals,
no awareness that it is a force.
KEVIN:
But there is awareness, McKinley.
In past cases,
if the next in line is saved....
....it'd skip that person.
That's why we're here.
IAN: Oh, man,
what have you been smoking?
(ERIN LAUGHS)
ERIN: Top shelf.
IAN: Okay.
Kevin. Those banners.
They're in the picture.
Ian, watch those boxes!
What the fuck, man?
You said those boxes were falling.
~ No, I said watch the boxes.
~ What for? They're not doing anything.
We're not gonna apologize
for trying to save you.
You haven't seen or been
through what we have yet.
Yet.
Okay, so who's next
in this theory you have, me or Ian?
Well, we know the order
of how we were sitting....
....but not how it works with
people who sat together.
We don't know if Ashley
or Ashlyn died first.
Hmm.
Death is fucking complicated.
(CHUCKLES)
No, you know what?
it's not complicated. it's simple.
People die. That's just part of life.
A hundred and fifty thousand
people a day, actually.
You know? I mean, we're biological entities and death is just....
ERIN: Top shelf.
~ ....the end of biological function.
It's as simple as that.
How can you explain
what happened as simple?
If Wendy never had the premonition and none of us got off....
....we'd all be dead now.
Does that not make sense?
IAN:
Oh, yeah.
Kevin, how come when a guy
dies of a plain heart attack....
....no one goes, like, "On, wow,
he was eating French toast....
....when Princess Diana died in Paris....
....and then he saw her funeral
on TV, and now he's dead"?
Know why? Because they'd sound crazy. So guess how you two sound right now.
Crazy.
I'm done. Finish cutting the
orders so we can get out of here.
Okay.
(SAW WHIRRING)
(GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES)
Ugh.
Sick.
(WHIRRING AND CLICKING)
(CREAKING)
(BLOWS)
IAN:
Okay.
Let's go with what
you guys are saying.
Let's just say, you know, that death does have a conscious plan....
....and that it's been set
into motion. Great.
So Newton's third law of motion~~
And, look, I'm just guessing
that it goes for death too....
....when he's working in our world.
Newton says that every action
has an equal and opposite reaction.
So that means that if death
has taken action, so can we.
And that action we take
might have an opposite reaction....
....that thwarts death's intent.
~ You're being a fucker, but go on.
IAN: Okay.
Okay. What if, for example,
the last in line....
....were to make the utilitarian choice....
Kill themselves.
Wow! Wow! That's pretty much gonna ruin any plan death's put in motion.
And even better, hey,
it's gonna save five skipped lives.
Any takers?
No, I didn't think so.
There! Those!
(GRUNTING)
(WENDY SHRHEKS)
(YELLS)
(GROANING)
(SOFAS)
(YELLS)
I didn't say anything. They were trying to scare us into saying something....
....but they had nothing to keep me.
~ What did you tell them?
~ Everything.
I didn't do anything. I told them
about the pictures, and Flight 18O....
....and Frankie and Lewis and why
we went to see Ian and Erin....
~ Did they believe you?
~ Yeah, right.
Would you believe me?
No, they looked at me like I was crazy.
Ten hours they had us in there.
For all we know, whoever
was sitting behind Erin is already dead.
And we're next.
Now.
Ian almost died first, but we intervened.
So it skipped Ian.
That's~~ That's how we regain control.
If someone intercedes, the life
that was supposed to be next is skipped.
All right, wait, wait, wait. So going by the way we sat on the roller coaster....
....well, I'm next, and then you.
We can beat this.
We're so close. We can't give up.
All right, my dad's here.
He's gonna give me a ride back.
~ You sure we shouldn't stick together?
~ It's just for a couple of hours.
All right? Go back, look at the pictures, see if there are more clues.
And I'll ask everybody I see if they know if anyone else got off the ride. Okay?
Was there something
I should know about going?
No, it's just....
I'll just be freaking out every second hoping you're okay.
Why?
I mean, we don't even like each other.
Come here.
(BOTH SIGH)
Okay? All right, I got my cell.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Hey, Wen? We're meeting
some guys at that centennial thing....
....and I could really use
my good-luck bracelet.
(CAR HORN HONKING)
(GASPS)
(DOOR SLAMS)
(DIALS)
(LINE RINGING)
JULIE:
Hey, this is Julie. Leave a message.
(BEEPS)
Call me on my cell right away.
(DIALS)
(LINE RINGING)
KEVIN:
Hello?
Do you remember Julie
being on the coaster?
What, your sister? No. No,
she would have said something by now.
The person sitting behind Ian and Erin was wearing the bracelet....
....our grandmother gave her.
Amber or Perry were probably with her, so they're next.
I gotta find Julie.
She went to the tricentennial.
Well, I'm here now, working security.
I 'll start looking for her.
~ I'm on my way.
~ Wen, wait.
Look, after them, we're next.
So in case something happens to them before we meet up....
Remember that time we talked about when to look at our pictures?
It's now.
(SlGHS)
Great. Mine has no clue. it's just me....
....standing in front of a blank background with Jason at the amusement park.
Wait. McKinley.
Ian? Wait, is he in the picture?
No, but it feels like a clue.
And yours is the picture that I took when I flashed the camera in your face.
It's all out of focus
and overexposed, like....
Like a firework went off in my face?
(STATIC WAVERING)
(THE VOGUES' "TURN AROUND,
LOOK AT ME" PLAYING)
There is someone
Walking behind you
Turn around
Look at me
There is someone
Watching your footsteps
(TIRES SCREECH)
Look at me
There is someone
Who really loves you
The British are coming!
(ALL CHEERING)
MAN 1:
Get them while they're hot!
MAN 2:
Take it to those redcoats!
MAN 3:
Column, advance!
(BAND PLAYING MILITARY MARCH)
BEN FRANKLIN:
The kite is aloft.
Now, let us hope for some lightning.
Fuck you, Ben Franklin.
WOMAN 1: But he kept insisting.
WOMAN 2: Well, he will be here, right?
BOY 1:
This is awesome, dude!
~ Heh, heh.
~ Whoa, hey!
~ Ha, ha. Come on!
KEVIN: Hey, get out of here!
~ You're gonna set these off!
BOY 2: Security, dude.
BOY 1: Come on, come on, man,
let's go! Hurry up!
ANNOUNCER (OVER PA):
Ladies and gentlemen....
....to celebrate McKinley's
tricentennial....
....the fireworks extravaganza
will begin shortly.
(BAND PLAYING SOUSA'S
"THE STARS AND STRIPES FOREVER")
AMBER:
Oh, my God, Julie.
JULIE: What?
~ Look. There's Kahill.
JULIE: Should we?
~ I'm sorry, but you can't be here, okay?
The viewing site is over there.
You too. Come on.
WOMAN 3:
They're not gonna make us move.
~ Hey, we gotta clear out.
~ Mm-hm.
(CHATTERING)
Excuse me.
(CREAKING)
~ Ladies.
WOMEN: Boys.
What's going on?
Hey, Julie.
You three need to come with me.
~ What did we do?
~ It's for your own safety, all right?
~ I'll tell you as soon as we get away.
~ Let go!
~ Julie.
~ Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
KEVIN:
Julie!
(ALL CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
(NEIGHING)
CROWD:
Ooh!
(LAUGHING)
BOY 1: Sweet.
BOY 2: Ha, ha.
Yeah.
Yeah, that's cool.
BOY 1:
Light! Light! Go, go, go, man!
Julie!
Unh! Oh!
(NEIGHING)
BOY 2: Shit!
BOY 1: Dude, we gotta bail!
(MAN PANTS)
(GRUNTS)
(PEOPLE GRUNTING)
CROWD:
Ahh....
KEVIN:
Julie! No, wait, wait!
You're in danger.
I'm trying to explain something.
Let me explain this to you.
Julie, look out!
~ Aah!
~ Unh!
(YELLING)
Julie!
(GRUNTING)
Cut him off!
OFFICER:
Oh, the horse!
(SHRIEKING)
(SCREAMS)
(CROWD MURMURING)
(JULIE SOBBING)
CLARK:
Okay, okay.
OFFICER:
Stay back. He's dangerous.
~ I got him.
~ Just let me go!
No, you have to tell me!
You have to listen!
Tell me who was next to you
on the roller coaster!
Julie, are you all right?
(NEIGHING)
Tell me who was next to you
on the roller coaster! Who? She's next!
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
Kevin.
(BOTH YELL)
WOMAN 1: Fire!
WOMAN 2: Let's get out of here.
(KEVIN COUGHING)
KEVIN:
You saved my life.
(GIRL SOBBING)
JASON: Thanks for that, McKinley.
MAN: Shut up, McKinley!
~ No!
~ We have to get out of here now!
KEVIN: What's the deal?
WENDY: Ian McKinley, he causes my death.
In my picture I was wearing
the McKinley shirt.
~ He's the clue.
~ What?
There's a first-aid tent.
There should be security.
Get the fuck out of here, McKinley!
Hey, I'm just celebrating
our town's tricentennial.
(CREAKS)
~ You followed me!
IAN: Oh, you are paranoid.
But, hey, I saw what happened.
You're next, right?
You're the end of it, aren't you?
~ Man, I would be paranoid too.
~ You didn't even believe me!
Yeah, well, seeing is believing.
~ Then you have to stay away from me!
~ "Have to"? Wow, that's extreme.
Oh, no way.
Do I cause your death?
Just like you caused Erin's?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, what?
What? Did you have a vision?
Was I in it?
Was l~~ Was I in a picture?
Just tell me how to start it off!
Let's get this over with!
You'll save me if you just stay away! Then it'll all be over!
What do I care? It skipped me.
For me, it is over. I'm not dying.
I'm not dying!
(LAUGHS)
You see?
I'm not gonna die!
it's you, Wendy!
You're dead!
(CREAKING)
(PANTING)
(SIREN WAILING)
(SINGING) Came back down from this fight
Will get ya deeper
Hi. Thank you.
~ I don't know, let's go for anything.
WOMAN: Thank you very much.
What about that curry place?
Don't we get off at Booth?
~ You mean Gupta's. Get off at Oswald.
~ Oh, that's right.
You know, if I can't be home
for Thanksgiving....
....I need some semblance
of a traditional dinner.
Turkey, stuffing, pie.
LAURA: If you don't have turkey for one
Thanksgiving is that gonna kill you?
MUSICIAN (SINGING):
There is someone
Walking behind you
Turn around
MAN: I'm sorry....
~ It's okay.
Look at me
There is someone
Watching your footsteps
Turn around
There is someone
Who really needs you
Here's my heart
SEAN:
What's with you and Gupta's'?
(TRAIN SCREECHES)
(TRACK CLICKING)
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLES)
(GASPS)
DRIVER: This is Booth Street.
Next stop is Oswald. End of the line.
The next stop is the end of the line.
Wendy, next stop after this.
WENDY: Let's just walk.
~ It's freezing out.
Yeah, but the air will feel good.
I could use some air.
MAN 1: Yeah!
WOMAN: Ha-ha-ha.
MAN 2: Yeah, man!
MAN 3: All right, man.
~ See you.
MAN 4: Let's go, Bruins!
MAN 5:
Bruins, yeah!
(SQUEAKING)
MAN 6:
Hey, man, peace out.
~ Come on.
MAN 7: Excuse me.
MAN 8: Watch out.
MAN 9: Hey, Bruins!
MAN 10: You miss the beginning?
Did you see?
~ This is it!
MAN 11: Yo, coming through.
Excuse me.
JULIE:
Oh, my God.
I can't believe this.
Here.
LAURA:
Come on, let's go.
Let's go.
~ I thought you weren't coming till tonight.
~ Dad's car died out of nowhere.
He couldn't get it fixed on a holiday.
So instead of sitting around for hours, I caught an early train.
~ I hope I'm not messing you up or....
~ No, it's just, um....
....I think I had a sense
that you were coming now.
(CLAN K)
I was just....
I was feeling like I did that night.
No. No, it's over.
You, me, Kevin went over
a thousand scenarios.
Ian was gonna cause your death,
you intervened and it skipped us.
(SQUEAKING)
Look, I'm not worried.
I ran into Kevin at home.
He's not worried.
And if I were you, until something happens to me and then Kevin....
....you've got nothing to worry about.
You're right.
(SIGHS)
I want you to meet
my roommate and friend.
Yeah.
WENDY:
Hey, guys. This is Julie, my....
What are you doing here?
Wendy! Julie! What are the chances?
~ How long have you been on this train?
~ Uh, since home.
I was heading up to check out the game. I was gonna look you up afterwards.
You okay? Is something wrong?
(SHRIEKS)
(ALL CLAMORING)
(SCREECHING)
(ALL GRUNTING AND YELLING)
(SHRIEKS THEN GROANING)
Julie, stay down!
Julie!
(SCREAMS)
WENDY: Kevin!
~ Unh!
(SCREAMS)
WENDY:
Oh, God!
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(SOBBING)
(SCREECHING)
No!
KEVIN: I was gonna look you up
afterwards, but~~
You okay? Is something wrong?
WENDY:
The train....
Oh, shit. Not again.
WENDY:
We gotta get out! Come on.
KEVIN: It's not working.
Somebody stop the train!
(METAL GRINDING AND CRASHING)
(DEVIL LAUGHING)