What was that?
Nothing.
Okay, just give me one little hint.
No, no hints.
We're almost there.
Okay, I'm going to take this off.
No, no, no.
Hey, you said you like surprises.
Yeah, I do.
When I know what they are.
You're going to love it.
I promise.
Yeah, I already love the view.
Uh-huh.
Hello?
There's a burning train.
A burning train.
Alright, we're...
What's your stop?
I can't see.
Alright, stop.
I'm taking it off...
now.
I didn't even know this place was open yet.
Pulled some favors and got us on the list for opening night.
Oh!
Are you sure I'm dressed all right?
You look like a million bucks.
Come on.
And it burns, burns, burns.
The ring of fire.
Hey!
Don't steal points from the fountain.
It's bad luck.
Sorry, sir.
Go on.
Smile.
Here's your ticket.
Thank you.
Did you catch that, everyone?
You coming?
Take the next one.
Aw, come on.
We can fit you in.
Thanks.
Going up.
Oh, excuse me.
Sorry, it does that sometimes.
Facts about the Skagway Tower.
It's 494 feet tall and weighs over 9,000 tons.
It's made of steel and reinforced concrete and glass.
And even more impressive, the entire project was completed five months out of Skagway.
It's not a good thing.
It's a good thing.
What a time.
Oh, I'm sorry, but we're already over.
Capacity for opening night, we cannot accommodate you.
If you wouldn't mind us stepping aside.
Thank you so much.
It's okay, I worked it out with Jake.
Is he here?
I could speak to him.
We let Jake go this morning.
Thank you so much.
What's going on here?
One second, one second.
Oh, sir.
I'm a very important man, but maybe you could help me out.
Please, you're tearing me apart.
But I'm sorry, I can't help you.
If you wouldn't mind.
Oh, Mr. Fuller, how nice to see you.
We have a lovely table for you.
Thank you.
This way, please.
Let's go to the bar.
I'm natural.
Wait a few.
What?
I'm scared of heights.
Oh, no.
I've just never been this high up before.
I'm so sorry.
This night's such a disaster.
I really wanted it to be perfect.
Hey.
It is perfect.
Because I'm with you.
Ah.
Are you okay?
I think I'll live.
Yeah.
Hey, look, free champagne.
That's my favorite kind.
Can I run it?
Okay.
I'll be right back.
Excuse me, where's the ladies room?
Other side of the dance floor.
Thank you.
Hi, sweetie.
Is everything all right?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
How far along are you?
What?
Oh, no.
No, I'm not.
I don't know exactly.
Maybe one or two months.
That's wonderful news.
Isn't it?
I haven't told my boyfriend yet.
Does he love you?
Yes.
Then he won't let go.
Thank you.
Of course.
Bye.
Okay.
It's almost over.
Oh.
Hey, what?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I think so.
Come on.
Let's get some fresh air.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry.
I wanted to...
You go first.
Okay.
I was gonna do us a dinner.
But seeing as we have this view...
Hey.
Don't throw that penny.
You could kill somebody.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Of course.
Yeah.
Fatass.
Um...
These past few years...
I've been absolutely magical.
And that's, uh...
That's because of you.
Iris...
I want to spend the rest of my life with you.
You mean...
With us?
What?
Sorry.
I...
I'm the luckiest guy in the world.
What?
You're not upset?
Are you kidding me?
No, this is...
This is incredible.
Really?
We're gonna start a family.
Um, so...
Will you?
Yes.
Ah!
Um...
Is it too tight?
It's perfect.
Hey.
Let's go sober.
Shut up.
No!
Well...
I realize vector multiplication is scary, but it's not that scary.
All right, that's it for today.
We'll start prepping for the final next week.
Ms. Reyes!
We need to talk.
Don't throw that penny.
You could kill somebody.
Oh, this dream is ruining my life.
Mine too.
Every night, Steph...
God, I'm not getting any sleep.
Shit, I'm sorry.
Um...
Can I tell you something?
Yeah?
What's up?
So the woman in my dream, her name is Iris, right?
Okay.
That was my grandmother's name.
I, uh, I think I'm dreaming about her.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
The thing is, I never even met her.
I don't even know if she's alive.
Okay, well...
Either go home and find out about Grandma and hope that stops the dreams, or stay here and die in your sleep.
For real.
Because I will murder you.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, yeah, okay.
Love you.
Love you too.
Go home.
Quietly.
Hey, there she is.
Hey, Dad.
Welcome home, sweetie.
I'm so glad you're here.
Yeah, me too.
I know.
So great to see you.
Thank you, thank you.
Hey, sorry.
Charlie took your room a while ago, and my files are in his room, so I made up the pullout for you.
Is that okay?
Yeah, yeah, no, that sounds totally fine.
Uh, hey, do we still have that box of Mom's old stuff?
It had, uh, some photos, like an address book.
It's phone numbers in it.
Uh, why do you want that?
Oh, it's not a big deal.
I just, I thought I saw it lying around here somewhere.
Stephanie, what's going on?
Okay, this is gonna sound really, really weird, but I, uh, I just need to find Mom's mom, Iris.
Uh, okay.
Yeah, that is weird.
And you know, I got rid of those boxes years ago, after Mom left.
Oh, hi, Charlie.
Hey.
Um, hi, Steph.
How are you?
It's so nice to see you.
Yeah, sure.
Uh, going to the cousins?
Whoa, now?
Look, your sister just got home.
I thought we might, uh...
Actually, you know what?
I can, I can drive you.
I was wanting to see them anyways.
That's fine.
Hey, if you're gonna see your cousins, please don't talk about Iris.
Don't go out.
Yeah.
Yeah, no problem.
All right.
Bye, love you.
Love you, too.
Charlie?
Can you just take these out, please?
I'm trying to talk to you.
What's your problem?
What?
You haven't said anything this entire time.
Steph, why are you here?
I mean, I'm only coming home for holidays.
I have to tell you something.
But you have to promise not to tell Dad.
Are you pregnant?
No, I'm not pregnant, Charlie.
I don't know.
That's not...
I mean, you're in college.
Can you just promise me you won't tell Dad?
Why would I tell Dad?
It's serious, Charlie.
Okay.
Um...
I am on academic probation.
Whoa.
Stop!
If I don't get my grades up...
This is kind of a big moment for me.
This is kind of funny.
You're a class president, Miss Valedictorian.
If I don't get my grades up, I will lose my scholarship.
Oh.
I'm both, sorry.
What happened?
I can't sleep.
Every time I close my eyes, I have this same recurring nightmare about Iris.
Our grandmother.
I don't...
I mean, it has to mean something.
I don't know.
I dream weird things.
I dreamed a hot dog ate me last night.
Like, the hot dog was eating me.
Okay.
Ah!
Dude, can you just do something?
Just move a little bit.
I have to look underneath.
Do me a kindness.
Do you remember what happened last night?
What's going on?
I can't find Paco.
Dude, again?
Who's Paco?
Hey, cuz.
Oh my gosh, hey, can you help us look?
And just watch your feet where you're stepping.
Yeah, yeah, sure.
I gotta talk to your dad first.
What the fuck are you doing home?
Oh, dude, she's fucking out of school.
Hey, welcome to the club.
Eric, dude, have you looked anywhere?
Paco's not upstairs.
Oh, but look who's down here.
Hi, Julia.
Oh my gosh.
Hi, Ben.
Charlie.
There's my little Romeo.
So, we had to prom-pose him with Jenny-go.
She said yes.
Oh my gosh.
Who's Jenny?
Oh, he met her in Junior Lifeguards.
Junior Lifeguards?
Charlie, I didn't know you were doing Junior Lifeguards.
Okay, so what are you gonna wear?
I'm just gonna keep it simple.
Black blazer.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Stephanie!
Oh my gosh.
Hi, honey.
How long are you here for?
Not long.
Is Uncle Howard around?
Yeah, yeah, he's up back.
I'll get him.
Howard!
Stephanie's here.
Come in.
Great.
You look a little tired.
Is everything okay?
Stephanie!
Look at you!
Come here, come here.
Oh, sweetie.
Oh, it's so good to see you.
Hey, are you hungry?
I was gonna make some lunch.
No, actually, I came here because I wanted to talk to you about your mother.
Iris.
I know you don't like to talk about her.
There's not much to tell.
Hey, kids, come on, lunch!
It's just that I've been having this recurring nightmare about her.
Oh, honey, it's probably just a stress.
You should try melatonin.
Okay, but the weird thing is, I've been dreaming about a real place from 50 years ago.
It was like a restaurant called The Skyview.
You know what it is?
Did Iris tell you about it?
What did she say?
Okay, did she say anything?
Maybe if I could talk to her...
Talk to who?
Steph is dreaming about Grandma Iris.
Psycho granny?
I thought she was dead.
Well, she's dead to us.
Stephanie, Iris Campbell is a very deeply disturbed woman.
Look, if I could just talk to her, then maybe I can get these dreams to stop.
Steph, just drop it.
I don't get it.
What happened that was so bad?
For one thing, she's the reason that your mother's so screwed up.
What?
Look, I just don't want to talk about this anymore, okay?
Uncle Howard, please, I just need to know.
Look, Stephanie, after our father died, Iris just snapped.
She wouldn't let us go to school.
She locked us inside the house.
She obsessed about all the horrific ways we could die.
And eventually it got so bad, I mean so bad,
that the state came in and they took your mother and I away from her.
But it didn't end there.
She tracked us all through foster care, and when the kids were born,
she started sending us these horrible letters,
that were full of obituaries and these disturbing pictures of dead bodies.
We had to move so she couldn't contact us anymore.
So, uh, do you still have any of those letters?
No.
I...
Stephanie, listen to me.
That woman is a sick and dangerous person.
And for your well-being and your safety, stay the hell away from her.
I believe you.
I found Paco!
I'm sure he'd love to be in the living room right now.
Come on, guys.
How did he ever get in there?
I need you to help me.
You heard your uncle.
Just let it go.
You don't understand.
My whole life is falling apart because of this dream.
And not only that, I feel like I'm losing my mind.
Please, you are the only person who can help me.
Howard would never forgive me if I put you in touch with Iris.
Please.
Whatever you do, do not look in the bottom drawer of the dining room cabinet.
Hi, um, I'm here to see Iris Campbell.
Did you not see the signs?
Uh, uh, yeah, yes, I did.
Then get the fuck out of here.
I'm your granddaughter.
Stephanie, empty your pockets.
Phone, keys, everything.
Well, I'm not dangerous.
It's not you I'm afraid of.
Uh.
Come in slowly.
Shut the door.
Quick, quick, quick.
Don't move.
Oh my god.
It really is you.
I can see your mother in you.
Hi, um.
Stop, stop.
Don't move.
Not until I tell you.
Trying to trick me, aren't you?
Getting me to let my guard down.
I.
There you go.
Run.
Sit.
Okay, um.
That's it.
So.
How is Darlene?
Your mom?
Okay.
Uh, no, I don't know.
She left when I was ten.
So we don't see her anymore.
Oh.
But you saw my letters.
That's why you're here, right?
No.
Um.
I'm actually here because I've been dreaming about the sky view.
Yeah.
Yeah, every single night for the past two months it's the same dream.
In it, you're on a date but then the dance floor breaks and then there's an explosion and then you fall and die.
Yeah.
Yeah, everyone dies.
It wasn't just your dream.
It was my premonition.
Years ago at the sky view I got a glimpse into the future and saw what death was about to do.
Hey, don't throw that penny.
You could kill somebody.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Of course.
These past two years have been absolutely magical and that's all because of you.
No, no, no.
This isn't right.
Is that a no?
Everyone's going to die.
The whole building is going to come down.
Are you serious?
The penny.
Iris?
Give it to me.
What are you doing?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Iris?
I saved a lot of lives that night.
They were meant to be saved.
They closed the restaurant after that.
Said it needed additional renovations.
But it never reopened.
Eventually they tore it down.
So you stopped the disaster?
Yes.
But death doesn't like it when you fuck with his plans.
So over the years he came back and he killed everyone who was there that night.
Including my Paul.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Did you say death came back?
He's a relentless son of a bitch.
Won't stop till he finishes the job.
But I taught myself how to see him coming.
To anticipate his every move.
Been keeping him at bay for years now.
And now he's got me.
Cancer.
Oh.
Believe that shit?
Sorry.
Got the diagnosis two months ago.
Wait.
That's when I started having my dream.
See?
It's a sign.
Okay, but why am I dreaming about what you saw?
Maybe my cancer passed my premonition on to you.
Maybe it's fate's demented sense of humor.
Who the hell knows?
What matters is that when the universe speaks you pay attention.
I see you, you fuck.
Huh?
Um.
Who are you talking to?
Death.
He thinks I'm distracted because you're here.
I have to teach you everything in this book.
It'll take some time to learn the basics.
So you'll need to stay here.
Stay here?
The outside world is too dangerous.
I haven't stepped out there in twenty years.
In here, we can be safe.
Oh.
See that?
Yeah.
This is all my research.
My life's work.
Look, I'm sorry.
I can't.
I can't stay here.
I have to get back to school, but, you know, I'll come back and I'll visit.
No!
I'm sick!
I won't be alive that long.
You can't leave.
Don't you see?
Death is coming for our family.
You don't believe me?
No.
I think I made a mistake.
I think it was probably just a dream.
No, wait!
At least take the book!
This book is a lifeline.
It will show you everything you need to know to keep our family safe.
You still don't believe me?
Step back.
Seeing is believing.
Hey, Steph.
Her face really exploded right in front of you.
Hey!
Just leave her alone.
It's my bad, Steph.
I'm just curious.
Hey.
How are you holding up?
Sorry Uncle helped.
You were right about ours.
I never should have went there.
Honey, there's no need to apologize.
I'm so sorry you had to go through that.
She said something to me before she died.
She said death was coming for our family.
That's crazy, right?
I can't believe it.
I emailed her.
I just didn't think she'd show up.
Come on.
Is that Mom?
Yeah.
Really?
Wow.
Don't be ridiculous.
Come on.
Get down here.
Come here.
Welcome to the barbecue.
Steph.
If she's going to Uncle Howard's house, then I'm not.
You can get a ride with Dad.
You're not even going to talk to her?
Come on.
You don't remember her like I do.
Just give her a chance.
Why?
Charlie, she abandoned us and now she rolls in here?
After all these years and wants to act like nothing happened?
Because who would do that, right?
Wait, what?
Nothing.
No.
What's that supposed to mean?
I tried calling you so many times and nothing.
Same with Julia.
You used to be best friends.
You don't even talk anymore.
Okay.
Well, I'm sorry.
I've just been distracted the last couple of months because of this and this nightmare.
What about before that?
It's been like this ever since you left.
You're mad at Mom, but you haven't been around either.
I'm not like her.
Okay?
I'm not crazy.
No, you're right.
You're not crazy.
Okay.
You just don't care.
Now you got it, watch out for splinters.
Hey, there she is.
Hey.
Come here.
I'm so glad you made it.
Of course.
Come on in.
Hey, everybody.
Come on.
Come on over.
I made cookies.
That's great.
Can I try one?
Yes, of course.
Does this have peanut butter?
Yeah.
Are you trying to kill my brother?
Oh, my God.
Bob is allergic.
Yeah.
I totally forgot.
I'm so sorry.
The important thing is that you're here.
So, Bobby Bartender, drinks.
Drinks all around.
Family.
You don't get to pick the one you get.
You just got to love the one that you got.
Now, our mother, she lived alone until the day that she died.
And her death should be a reminder to all of us to enjoy life,
and spend the time that we have together because we're not going to get any back.
I love you guys.
Cheers.
Oh, my God.
There's a bug in there.
I got it.
- I think, you got it.
- Just watch.
- I'm trying to get a new job.
- That's great!
Charlie!
Get up here.
Do you want me to join you?
Good to see you.
The setup you've got here.
Well, I wanted the kids to have a happy childhood unlike some people I know.
You're not talking about us, are you?
Oh, no.
We had a great childhood.
Look at me.
I turned out fabulous.
Yep.
Howard.
What is that?
It looks like a house key.
Come on.
You know, we got the spare room,
and it's got to be better than bouncing around trailer parks.
I don't think this is a good idea.
It's never too late for a second chance.
I'm sorry.
They're better off without me.
Pick up.
Come on.
You got to me, all right?
You got to me.
Hey, guys, come show us your back flip.
What?
No, no, no.
Yeah, come on, Uncle Howard.
Come on, Howard.
Howard.
Oh, yeah.
There you go.
All right, here we go.
Watch out.
Wait, stop!
Nice catch, Andy.
Alright, here we go.
Come on, Howard.
Here we go.
Careful, Howard!
Stephanie.
I'm glad you decided to come.
Now the whole family's here!
I'm okay.
Alright.
Good.
And he shall wipe away every tear from their eyes.
What is all this stuff?
Okay.
I found these papers in Iris' book.
They are obituaries and articles for the people who were at the Skyview,
on the night that Iris had her premonition.
Each one of these people went on to die in some weird and messed up way.
And not only that, they all died in the same order as Iris' premonition.
Hundreds of people were supposed to die that night, but Iris stopped the disaster.
So, death came back for them one by one.
Since there were so many survivors, it took years for death to get to all of them.
But eventually it got to Iris.
I mean, she was the last to die in the premonition.
It was her and a little boy.
But she was prepared.
She single-handedly held off death for decades.
Stephanie, sweetie.
I don't think this is the appropriate time for this.
Yeah, I mean, none of this even has anything to do with us, right?
Why are we even here?
It has everything to do with us.
Because death took so long to make its way through the survivors, these people went on to have families.
Families that they never should have had.
So death took them too.
Don't you see this?
Death is coming for us because we were never supposed to exist.
Okay, so why everybody in this room is on death's hit list?
Bobby, Doc, that's what she's saying.
No, no, no.
Dad and Aunt Brenda are safe because they're not part of Iris' bloodline.
Okay.
Following the pattern, death makes its way down each branch by age.
So because Uncle Howard was the oldest, it'll start with his family first, meaning Eric, you're next.
Go fuck yourself.
Then it'll go for Julia, then Bobby.
Then it'll come for our branch, starting with Darlene, then me, then Charlie.
Charlie.
You buying this?
I don't know.
This is so messed up.
I mean, you're turning our dad's death into some kind of fucked up conspiracy theory.
What is wrong with you?
No, no, no, no, no.
It's not, it's not a conspiracy theory.
That's enough.
We're all gonna die.
Stop!
I can't listen to this for one more minute.
That crazy woman's nonsense has caused enough pain and suffering for this family.
Hang on.
Aunt Brenda, please just leave it alone.
Okay, in Iris' book, she mentions somebody who cheated death and survived.
Stephanie.
Eric, no, wait.
I'm worried about you.
Stop it.
I'll be taking care of this.
Come on, Bobby.
Brenda.
Let's go.
No, no, no, you can't.
I'm sorry.
Please.
You believe me, right?
I'm sorry.
Julia.
Look, I love you.
But sometimes I really hate you.
I know.
I know how convincing all of this can be, but it's not real.
How can you say that?
I know Iris taught you all of this.
Don't let my mom's beliefs derail your life the same way they did mine.
Thank you so much for that advice, but I really don't need a mom anymore.
All right, open wide.
Very good.
Just gonna pinch hard.
Ready?
Five, four, three, two.
Good job.
I'm gonna hit the club.
I need you to lock up.
And don't touch any of my liquor.
No, no, you didn't say anything about locking up.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I didn't say shit about closing, dude.
And cry me a river.
I hope you burn in hell.
You believe that shit?
My old man just died.
I come in as a favor to that asshole, and now he wants me to lock up.
You know what that is?
It's inconsiderate.
Anyway, you're all done.
Thank you.
Hey, five-star review, yeah?
Like and subscribe and all the things.
No, I can't forget this evening or your face as you were leaving, but
I guess that's just the way the story goes.
And now it's only fair that I should let you know what you should know.
I can't live, if living is without you.
I can't give.
I can't give anymore.
God dammit.
Charlie, wake up.
I've been trying to call Eric all night.
He's not answering me.
I don't know where he is.
I'm worried.
I'm sure he's fine.
Well, have you heard from him?
I'm going over there.
I need to check on him.
You're coming too, Charlie.
I think he's gone to voicemail.
Is that him?
My friend just set the test recorder to burn down last night.
What?
Steph, Steph!
Ow!
Eric?
Oh, yeah, no, of course it's you.
Dude!
We heard about the fire.
We thought you were dead.
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
I'm so worried about you.
Yeah, fuck.
Fire said I was lucky as fuck that I was wearing that leather jacket.
Barely got burned.
Really my favorite jacket, though.
What is this?
Oh, yeah, check it out.
I got branded.
Sick, right?
You like it?
You said you were asleep.
You're blowing up my phone like a goddamn stalker.
What do you want me to do?
No, I don't get it.
You should be dead.
Right, yeah, yeah.
Or, you know, maybe...
Maybe death's not actually coming for our family.
Because that would be fucking crazy.
Jesus shit!
Or maybe I'm invincible.
Eric?
Eric!
Yeah?
Eric, wait.
Stop.
Just wait, okay?
Just because death didn't kill you last night doesn't mean that you're safe.
Stay away from that tree trimmer!
Ooh.
Gonna move on its own, Steph?
Is that what it's gonna do?
It could fall.
And stay away from these kids.
I'll take my chances.
Steph, how's a couple kids with a soccer ball gonna kill him?
I mean, I don't know.
The trimmer could fall and hit the leaf blower guy,
which causes him to blow stuff into the kids' eyes and then take the ball into his face.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Soccer ball in my face?
That does sound deadly.
I should be more careful.
Hey!
What's up?
What happened to you?
Charbroiled by death.
Eric, huh?
Kiki, that was pretty bad.
Oh, wait, let me see that.
Eric, just stay away from the truck.
Oh, what?
This truck?
Stop!
Oh, my God.
Please.
This truck right here?
But it's such a beautiful truck!
Stop!
Don't touch it!
Eric, just wait!
Stop!
You like that?
Oh, my God.
Uh-oh!
Eric's testing death again!
What's gonna happen?
Stop doing that!
How about that?
I'm just trying to help you.
Okay.
Honestly, we're so done with your garbage.
Can you please...
For the 1500th time, no one gives a shit about your stupid little death curse, okay?
So take a hint and leave us alone, because death's not coming for our family.
Whoa!
Should've believed you, Steph.
No, I, uh...
I screwed up the order, and now Julia's dead.
It's my fault.
What happened was traumatic and awful.
It's not your fault.
It's my fault.
Well, it's not your fault.
It is my fault.
Stephanie, you were only wrong about the order, because there's something you shouldn't know.
Eric isn't Howard's biological son.
I'm sorry, what are you talking about?
And, Stephanie, I didn't believe you, so I didn't say anything to you, and now my little girl's dead.
Well, I don't understand why you had an affair.
You and your father and I were having such a hard time.
But it was good, because I got you.
I got you out of it.
I was gonna read that, but I'm just gonna read that.
It doesn't matter, because Howard loved you so, so much.
Who is it?
Who's been around all that?
Gerard Fenbury.
Oh!
Gerard Fenbury?
Yes.
Oh, shit.
No, no, no, no!
Gerard fucking Fenbury?
You don't know what we're going through.
Oh, God.
What, is this why you always wanted to play catch?
Oh.
Okay.
So, that means that if it's going in the right order, then I'm next, right?
You gotta help me, Steph.
I don't think that I can.
I mean, I thought I did, but I don't...
No, but you can.
I mean, you predicted exactly what was gonna happen.
You just got the order wrong, because you didn't have all the information, Charlie.
What do you mean, predicted?
She saw everything.
The trimmer, the blower, the soccer ball, like...
It was like there were pieces to a puzzle, and she just had to put them together, you know what I mean?
Is that true?
Darling, please, do not encourage this.
Marty, I mean...
I mean, it's everything in Iris' book, it's...
It's like, it's like an equation, it's math.
Stephanie, if you can see how all of this fits together, we might have a chance.
Steph, you devastated this family when you walked out, but we've been okay without you.
I'm begging you not to traumatize our kids anymore.
It's real this time.
I'm going for a walk.
I can appreciate that our family is clearly gonna need some counseling in the future, but...
can we focus on the fact that we're all about to die, right?
I mean...
I mean, Steph, didn't you say that Iris knew someone that cheated death or something?
Yeah, um...
Right here, somewhere, it says...
That, um...
Right here.
J.B. found someone who survived, but it doesn't say anything about who this J.B. was or...
Wait a minute, I know that name.
My mom used to write me letters,
and she sometimes would talk about a friend of hers named J.B. who worked at a hospital.
Um...
Um, something, uh, something river hospital, uh, uh, deep river, uh, peace river hospital, uh, clear...
Hope, Hope River?
That's it!
Shit, it's like an hour away.
I'm going.
I'm gonna go find him and talk to him myself.
Well, I'm coming with you.
That's it, okay, yeah, yeah, let's, let's go.
Ozzy, I...
What?
You need to stay here with your mom and save her.
Yeah, fuck that, are you kidding me?
I'm not staying here by myself.
It's too dangerous on the road for you, you can't...
No, I read Gammy's death book, okay, alright?
I mean, there's like a thousand house-related deaths in that thing, man.
You trip down the stairs, fall...
down a toilet or something, I don't, I don't know, but I'm not, I'm not...
No way, I'm not staying here.
Hang on, hang on.
Hey, okay, too fast.
Okay, okay, we'll go slow, we'll go slow.
I'm gonna go open up the truck.
Charlie, check the back.
Got it.
Be careful, the steps are slippery sometimes.
Oi!
Any of you fuckers doing nut check?
Excuse me?
You made cookies in that thing with peanut butter in them just a few days ago.
This poor bastard so much as even touches a nut, his throat is gonna close up tight and...
You understand, where's the peanut butter?
Cabin and about the sink.
Thank you.
I'm so sorry, Bobby, I just...
Hey, okay.
All clear.
Thank you.
You're a good brother, Eric.
Nut check.
What?
Oh!
God!
It was good, I get it.
Come on.
It's only getting worse.
Dammit.
Wait!
I'm coming with you, bro.
Someone's gotta protect you.
Dad's calling, again?
Tell him we just went for a ride with Mom.
He's not gonna believe that.
At least it'll buy us some time.
Time?
Death doesn't get us your dead will.
I always keep them where I can see them.
I mean, you could've just had the real thing, but it's okay, not everyone wants to be a mom.
Is that what you think?
That I don't wanna be a mom?
Look, I was raised by a woman who taught me to see death everywhere.
I thought I could put it behind me, but then when I had you and your brother,
all I could see were a hundred different ways that you and Charlie could die.
I didn't want you to leave the house.
I would freak out on you guys over nothing.
One day, I looked at your face, and I saw the same scared little girl that I was growing up,
and I knew that if I stayed, I was gonna ruin your life.
I have no idea if I did the right thing.
But I'm here for you now.
The front desk is this way.
Hi, um, we're looking for JB.
And who are you?
The front desk told us we could find him down here, is that you?
William John Bloodworth.
But my friends call me JB.
I've been waiting for you, Stephanie.
Charlie.
So, which one of you...
I was sorry to hear about Iris.
She was a special woman.
How did you know her?
She saved my life.
When?
The sky view.
I went to work that night.
JB, honey, I told you, you gotta stay back there while I'm on stage.
I wasn't supposed to be there.
Except, of course, to die.
So all that time, she wasn't just protecting our family, she was protecting you too.
Years later, she tracked me down.
Helped me see the truth.
We traded ideas.
I helped her fortify her cabin.
We became friends.
I even helped her get the best medical care I could, considering her condition.
Iris said that you'd found somebody who stopped death and survived.
Yes.
And how do we do that?
There are only two ways.
By killing, or by dying.
If you take a life, you get the time that person had left.
What?
No, I'm not gonna kill someone.
Maybe we should let the guy finish.
Then to truly break the cycle, you have to die.
What does that mean?
A long time ago, a young woman named Kimberly Corman found herself on death's list, just like you.
And when her turn finally came, she died.
Flatlined.
But her doctor managed to bring her back, and that broke the chain.
Well, alright then, we'll do that.
What are you talking about?
Why didn't Iris try that?
It's risky.
And if you fuck with death and lose, things can get very messy.
Hang on, hang on.
Okay, wait.
There has to be another way.
Please, you have to help us.
For years, people have been coming to me for advice.
Well, I'm tired.
I'm done with all that.
And now I'm sick, just like Iris.
There's no running this time.
Fact is, you're all gonna die.
And after that, I will too.
Now that my old friend is gone, I'm retiring.
So what?
You're just gonna leave us here?
I intend to enjoy the time I have left.
And I suggest you do the same.
Life is precious.
Enjoy every single second.
You never know when.
That's fantastic.
No.
No, that can't be it.
There has to be something here.
There has to be another answer.
He gave us an answer.
Bobby's gotta die.
Eric!
Are you fucking insane?
We're not killing Bobby.
Am I the only guy that just listened to that dude?
There's only one way.
We kill Bobby.
We resuscitate him, and then boom, you're all off death's list.
Congratulations.
There has to be something else, right?
I mean, there has to be another solution, right, Steph?
No.
No, there's nothing else we can do.
Okay, it's over.
Hey, you gotta trust me on this, okay?
She's giving up on you.
I'm not going to.
Look, Iris found a way to hold death off for decades.
So will we.
I trust that guy.
Do you trust that guy?
He was awesome.
He was charismatic, and you know that as well.
Eric and Bobby are gone.
Shit.
Shit!
I don't think I like this.
Hey, dude, we're in a hospital.
Remember, there's doctors everywhere.
We kill you, they bring you back, everybody's safe.
We're heroes.
That is literally the opposite of keeping you safe.
Huh?
You want to kill someone and take the time they have left?
How?
How would you even know how many years they have?
No.
Well, I mean, no.
No, of course not.
No, we would never.
Don't touch those babies.
Look, bottom line, flatline is your best option.
What do you have to lose?
How would we even do that?
See, I got an idea.
Yeah.
But it's a little nuts.
Your allergy is deadly, right?
Well...
Look, all right, if I'm going out, it's not going to be on those sort of insulted bitches,
all right?
Give me those.
Nice choice.
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
Come on.
Hey, all right, come on.
You know, maybe this is a sign so we can just...
Ow!
Hey, dude, maybe we can just bail now.
I'm not giving up.
Can you help?
It's all right, we work here.
Maintenance, it's fine.
Put your headphones back on.
Dude, it's going to fall.
It's going to fall.
It's falling!
Hold it!
Easy work.
Now what?
Hey, hang here.
I've got to get something.
Don't move.
What are you talking about?
Where's the bathroom?
They weren't in the RV?
No.
Look, if Eric was trying to cut Bobby, where would they be?
I don't know, but there's a million ways to die in a hospital.
Can I help you?
Excuse me?
No, just...
Lovely day today.
Got much time left?
I hope so.
All the talent belonging to man devices there.
Dude, turn the car back on.
Come on, sit down.
Sit, sit, sit.
I'll be right back.
Hey, where's your EpiPen?
It's right here.
Give it to me.
Why?
What is that?
Give it.
Listen, the whole idea is that you have to die.
Remember, this keeps you alive.
Now sit.
Dude, we need to hurry.
Come on, go.
All right, meet up.
Hey man, the plan's great, but, you know, if it doesn't work out...
It's going to work, Bobby.
Yeah.
Yeah, but, you know, just in case, and I die for real, will you just, um...
Will you look after Paco?
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Dude, I'm just saying, turtles live to be like 100 years old, and it's like, look at me, look at me.
Brother, I'm not going to take care of Paco because you are going to be okay.
Me and you, we are going to fix things for everyone, right now.
Honestly, I'm not going to let you die.
Technically, I'm not going to let you die, but then I'm going to bring you back.
Come on.
You got this.
Oh my God.
What?
It's very good, I know.
So what?
Okay, other than good, what are you feeling?
Nothing.
You got to be kidding me.
What, you're telling me you're not allergic anymore?
I don't know, man.
Hey, you're doing it.
Bobby, you're doing it.
Hey, I'm here with you.
I'm here with you.
Hey, hey, I can't give you that.
Bobby, Bobby.
Hey, hey.
Wait.
Bobby, just go for it and play.
Bobby, in the wheelchair.
Try calling him again.
This is the only way we can do this.
Oh my God.
Yeah.
Why is Eric dead if he's not related to Iris?
When you fuck with death, things get messy.
We have to get out of here.
It's not safe.
And go where?
Nowhere is safe.
Except Iris' cabin.
She was able to survive there for decades.
Yeah, and then she got her face blown off.
She only died because she left the cabin.
Outside is dangerous, but inside is the safest place that there is.
It's the only place where we have any advantage.
So we just lock ourselves in a cabin forever?
Not you.
Me.
Mom, you can't leave.
We just got you back.
If anybody's gonna live in that cabin, it's me.
And as long as I am alive, death can't touch you.
Mom, let me do this.
He'll never let you get there on your own.
But I can see him coming.
We have to do this together.
You better.
Let's go.
Okay.
You should drive.
Yeah.
Shit!
Look at this place.
It's gonna be impossible to get through that gate.
He's about to make a move.
I don't know what it is.
We need to get you inside now.
Wait.
Wait, what?
Stop!
Okay, let's get inside.
Shoot!
What?
No, no, no.
Don't wait for me.
Just get inside.
Steph, if you get inside, I'll be safe.
Go.
Okay, come on.
I'll save you, sister.
I'm gonna stay alive as long as I can.
Charlie.
Are you okay?
Just breathe.
Breathe.
Charlie, what happened?
Are you okay?
You died, and I brought you back.
You brought me back.
We're safe now.
Mom.
She saved us.
Let's go home.
Well, there he is.
Wow, okay, Charlie.
All right, give us a spin.
You look really good.
I'm a great stylist.
Come on, we'll be late.
Where's Jenny?
I think she's still inside, didn't we?
Here, let me fix this.
I'm really happy you could be here for this.
Me too.
Oh.
You okay?
Yeah.
Can I have one cookie, please?
Thank you.
Steph, I want you to meet Jenny's dad, Dr. Reddick.
Hey, Bart, nice to meet you.
You too.
We just adore Charlie.
And I understand he's quite the lifesaver.
Oh, yeah, you heard about that.
He brought me back from the dead.
Yeah.
What?
Well, technically, you weren't dead.
Well, I mean, if you were unconscious and Charlie got you breathing again,
then your heart didn't stop.
But regardless, way to go, Charlie.
So she wasn't dead?
Exactly.
She was lucky Charlie was there.
Yeah, everything happens for a reason.
Jenny!
Jenny.
Jenny, you look like a million bucks.
You okay?
Run!
- Oh my god, that was close.
- Are you okay ?
Yeah.