Long ago, in ancient China.
The Peacocks ruled over Gongmen City.
They brought great joy and
prosperity to the city.
For they have invented 'fireworks'.
But their son, Lord Shen
saw darker power in the fireworks.
What that brought color and joy,
could also bring darkness and destruction.
Shen's troubled parents
consulted a Soothsayer.
She foretold,
that if Shen continued
down this dark path,
he would be defeated by
a warrior of black and white.
The young lord set out
to change his fate.
But he did next,
only sealed it.
Shen returned to his
parents full of pride.
But in their faces,
he saw only horror.
He was banished
from the city forever.
But Shen swore revenge.
Someday, he would return,
and all of China would
bow at his feet.
It's almost done Lord Shen.
But we ran out of metal.
Search the furthest villages.
Find more metal!
China will be mine.
And then the Dragon Warrior
joined the Furious Five.
And they became the most
awesome kung fu team ever.
Enough talk, let's fight.
Listen, you can hear the
Dragon Warrior training right now.
Stop him! That's too dangerous!
Stay focus.
Thirty-seven...
Why is he doing that to his face?
Thirty-eight bean buns!
Yes, new record!
You monster!
Keep going! Hit forty!
He'll never hit forty.
You got it buddy.
I'm going for forty!
Do it!
No problem.
I'm going to make it.
He did it!
- Well done, Po!
Your training has paid off.
Oh, Master Shifu.
Got to go. See you later!
You will save those for me, right?
Inner peace.
Oh, inner peace.
Master Shifu.
What have we got?
Pirates?
Vandals of Volcano Mountain?
Whatever it is, I'll take them down.
Cause I am in the mood.
I need to get something done,
you know what I mean?
What are you doing?
One of Master Oogway final teachings.
Awesome!
How did you do that?
Inner peace.
Inner peace. That's cool.
Inner peace of what?
It's your next phase of training.
Every master must find
his path to inner peace.
Some choose to meditate for 50 years.
And became just like this.
Without the slightest
taste of food or water.
Or..?
Some find it through pain and suffering.
As I did.
Po, the day you were chosen
as Dragon Warrior,
was the worst day of my life.
By far, nothing else came close.
It was the worst most painful,
mind destroying horrible moment,
I have ever experienced.
But once I realized the
problem was not you,
but within me,
I found inner peace.
And was able to harness
the flow of the universe.
So that's it.
I just need inner peace?
My inerts are already super peaceful.
So all I need to do is
just get this thing going.
Inner peace, you're going down.
Now show me what you were
doing there with your feet.
I saw you just sort of fanciful foot work.
Po, bandits approaching
the Musicians' Village.
Danger.
Tell those musicians to start
playing some action music,
because it is 'On'.
Don't worry Master Shifu.
I'll master inner peace
as soon as I get back.
No snack stop this time.
Ha-ha-ha!
Snack stop.
Wait, are you serious?
Get all the metal you can find!
Grab the metal!
Help...Help...Help...Help!
That's everything.
Let's get out of here!
Wings of justice!
The Dragon Warrior.
The panda? That's impossible.
My fist hungers for justice.
That was... my fist.
Get them!
Come on!
Take that!
Po! Incoming!
Thanks, Mantis!
Tigress! Double-jump strike!
Feet of Fury!
Tigress!
Monkey!
Viper!
Mantis!
Bunny! What?
Oh, sorry.
Crane, go!
I am on it!
Is everyone okay?
Yeah! Awesome!
I got this.
Po!
Chew on that, tubby.
Are you okay?
What happened?
I think I saw...
I think...
I got to go.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming to
Dragon Warrior Noodles and Tofu.
Some more tea? Lemon sauce?
If you need anything, just ask.
Feet of Fury!
Dragon Warrior's mop.
It must be very good.
Hey! No touching!
You'll get the mop dirty.
He once waited on me.
- Awesome.
Yes, I have a stain to prove it.
Hey, where is the Dragon Warrior?
He doesn't work here anymore.
He's busy out there
protecting the valley.
The Dragon Warrior.
Po!
You should have told
me you were coming.
Hi, Dad.
I would have save you some stinky tofu.
Dad, can I talk to you?
Of course, son.
In honour of my son,
free tofu dessert for everybody,
...with purchases.
It's so good to see you, Po.
Have you lost weight?
I can almost put my wings around you.
Well, maybe a little.
Poor you. You must feel weak.
Let me get you some soup.
No, that's okay, Dad.
I'm not hungry.
Not hungry?
Po, are you alright?
Yes, I'm fine. I'm just...
Earlier today, I was fighting these bandits.
Nothing... too... dangerous.
And then, the strangest thing happened.
Ah... I had this crazy vision.
I think I saw my Mom...
... and me, as a baby.
Mom?
A baby?
Dad?
What do you mean?
How do I say this?
Where did I come from?
Well you see...son.
Baby geese come from a little egg.
Don't ask me where
the egg comes from.
Dad, that's not what I meant.
I know it's not.
I think it's time I told you something,
I should have told you a long time ago.
Okay.
You might have been kind of...
...adopted.
I knew it.
You knew?
Who told you?
No one.
Come on, Dad.
But if you knew,
why didn't you say anything?
Why didn't you say anything?
How did I get here, Dad?
Where did I come from?
Actually,
you came from this.
It was just another day
at the restaurant.
Time to make the noodles.
I went out to the back,
where my vegetables
had just been delivered.
There were cabbages, turnips, radishes.
Only there were no radishes.
Just a very hungry baby panda.
There was no note.
Of course, you could have eaten it.
I waited for someone
to come looking for you.
But no one did.
I brought you inside.
Fed you.
Gave you a bath.
And fed you again.
And again.
And tried to put some pants on you.
And then I made a decision
that would change my life forever.
To make my soup with hot radishes.
And to raise you as my own son.
Hsiao Po. My little panda.
And from that moment on,
both my soup and my life,
have been that much sweeter.
And my little Po,
that's the end of the story.
Look at me.
No, don't look at me.
That's it?
That can't be it!
There’s got to be more, Dad.
There was a time you ate
all my bamboo furniture.
It was imported too.
One Dumpling, please.
Dragon warrior's size.
Po, your story may not
have such a happy beginning,
but look how it turned out.
You got me,
you got Kung Fu,
and you got noodles!
I know but I have so many questions.
Like how did I ever fit
into this tiny basket?
Why didn't I like pants?
And who am I?
Watch your fall.
Good.
Shen?
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
Now we got the pleasantries
out of the way,
please leave my house.
Your house?
Didn't you see the Peacock
on the front door?
There you are, Soothsayer.
It seems that your fortune telling skills
are not as good as you thought.
We shall see, Shen.
Oh, you shall see, old goat.
Where were we?
What do you want, Shen?
What is rightfully mine.
Gongmen City.
Gongmen is under the stewardship
of the Master's Council
and we will protect it even from you.
I'm so glad you feel that way.
Otherwise, I would have dragged
that thing here for nothing.
What is in the box, Shen?
Want to see it?
It's a gift.
It's your parting gift.
In that it will part you.
Part of you here,
part of you there,
and part of you
where you were there...
... staining the wall!
You insolent fool!
Show off.
That is a warning.
You are no match for our Kung Fu.
I agree.
But this is.
Are you familiar with the
Master of Gongmen City?
Master Thundering Rhino?
- Yes.
Son of the legendary Flying Rhino?
And slayer of the ten thousand
serpents in the Valley of Woo?
He's died.
That... that's impossible.
Rhino's Horn Defense isn't
pervious to any technique.
It was not any technique.
Lord Shen has created a weapon.
One that breathes fire
and spits metal.
Unless he is stopped,
this could be the end of Kung Fu.
But I just caught Kung Fu.
And now, you must 'save' it.
Go! Destroy this weapon!
And bring Lord Shen to justice!
Okay, here we go!
Wow...wow...wow!
Wait a second.
How can I do this?
How can Kung Fu stop something
that stops Kung Fu?
Remember Dragon Warrior,
anything is possible,
when you have inner peace.
Inner peace... inner peace... inner peace.
Peace on.
Oh Po!
Po, I got you a travel pack.
I packed your food for weeks.
Cookies, buns, vegetables,
and I even packed all your action figures.
See!
Oh, I don't know what those are.
Never seen them before in my life.
Dad, you got scratches on my Tigress.
I also packed your paintings
of our best time together.
Just in case you get lonely.
That's you and me making noodles.
And that's you and me eating noodles.
And that's me giving you a piggyback ride.
Ain't that, cute?
On second thought, I'll hang on to this one.
Hey, they're waiting for me.
Of course. You have a job to do.
Far from home.
In a strange city,
fill with strange people
and strange noodles.
Facing horrible danger
from which you might never return.
Don't go Po!
I got to go.
I am the Dragon Warrior.
It's kind of my job to save Kung Fu.
And if I don't.
What am I?
You're my son.
Right?
Po, it's time.
Goodbye.
Don't worry, Mr. Ping.
He'll be back
before you can say noodles.
Noodles.
Come on guys, let's go!
Yeah!
Mama?
Mom? Dad?
Is that you?
Oh hi.
Hey, son, you're back.
...Uh..?
Honey, what are you doing here?
But I thought...
We replaced you dear,
with this lovely radish.
Radish?
It's quiet, polite, and frankly,
it does better Kung Fu.
No... No... No!
Wait!
Ouch!...Hoo..!
Radish...Radish...Radish!
Inner peace...
Inner peace.
Uurrr...
Urghh...Urrghh!
Inner peace...inner peace...inner peace...!
I'm a...training.
The mast is not a worthy opponent.
I'm ready.
Okay. So serious.
Ha...ha...haa...ouch!
I think I prefer the mast.
Apologies.
I used to punch the iron wood trees
by the palace.
Now I feel nothing.
That's severely cool.
Again!
So, this punching iron wood trees,
how long did you've to do that?
Twenty years.
Oh, twenty years?
Is there any faster way,
until you don't feel anything?
No!
Besides,
I don't think hard style is your thing.
Po, why are you really out here?
I just found out that my dad
isn't really my dad.
Your Dad, the goose?
Must have been quite a shock.
Ya.
And this bothers you?
Are you kidding me?
We are warriors, right?
Nerves of Steel!
Soul of Platinum!
Like you!
So hardcore you don't feel anything.
I was...
- So what are you talking about?
Nothing...nothing.
Po's having Daddy issues.
I'm so lucky, I don't have
any problem with my Dad.
Maybe it's Mom ate his head
before I was born.
No, no, no!
Mantis, this isn't about you.
Po is the one freaking out.
I'm not freaking out.
Po!
I'm freaking in.
What?
We're here.
Gongmen City.
My father's throne.
He used to let me play
here beside him.
Promising someday this throne
would be mine.
A little to the left.
But it's so heavy, Master.
Thirty years, I've waited
for this moment.
Everything must exactly
how I envisioned it.
And I envisioned it
a little to the left.
Perfect.
With the weapon by my side...
... a more bit more.
With the weapon by my side,
all of China will bow before me.
We move out in three days,
when the moon is full
and the tide is high.
Now you old goat.
Why don't you tell me my...
...fortune?
The future.
I was going to say 'future'.
Look into your bowl and
tell me what glory awaits.
If you continue on your current path,
You will find yourself,
at the bottom of the stairs.
I see,
I see... pain.
Ouch!
And anger.
How dare you?!
That is the finest silk in the province!
Followed by denial.
This is not fortune telling.
You're just saying what's happening right...
...now?
The most important time is now.
But if you really want to see the future.
Oh, what do you see?
A Peacock...
is defeated by a warrior
of black and white.
Nothing has changed.
That's impossible and you know it.
It's not impossible.
And he knows it.
Who?
Lord Shen!
I saw a panda.
A Panda?
A Kung Fu Warrior.
He fought like a demon.
Big and furry.
Soft and squishy.
Kind of plush and cuddly.
There are no more pandas.
Even with his poor eye-sight,
he can see the truth.
Why, is it that you cannot?
Find this panda and
bring him to me!
Yes Sir!
One panda lives.
That does not make you right.
You are right.
Being right, makes me right.
Then I'll kill him and make you wrong.
Will you stop that?
That must be Shen's palace
on the other side of the city.
Great!
We'll march in and proclaim,
we're the Dragon Warrior
and the Furious Five.
And we're here to bring you to justice.
What are you doing?
This place is crawling with wolves.
Hey, isn't that guy who
hammered you on the face?
I do not like that guy.
We need to get to that tower
without being spotted by those wolves.
Got it. Stealth mode.
Ouch!
Ah, get out of my way!
Hmm...and where does this...ouch!
Woo!
Hello... I couldn't help...
Ouch!
Okay. Anyway, where was I?
Where's Po?
How come we lose a guy that big?
Guys?
Hehe, Po.
- What!?
Sorry.
So that was stealth mode, uh?
Let's be honest, it's not one
of my stronger modes.
...any gold, nickel or lead...?
This rice is raw!
You stole all my metal pots.
Either you cook my rice
or I'll cook you!
Po, do something.
How am I suppose to help her
cook rice without getting caught?
Wait, I have a better idea.
Hey.
- Hey.
We are here to liberate the City
and bring Shen to justice.
You will need help.
Thank you, brave sheep.
But it is too dangerous.
I can't let you.
- Oh, oh, not me.
It's not safe to speak here.
Right.
I'm talking about Masters Ox and Croc.
They are in Gongmen jail at
Black Dragon Alley.
What?
They are still alive?
They must be in that
jail gathering intelligence,
hatching a plot to use their awesomeness,
to defeat the weapon.
Okay let's go.
Thanks, sheep.
Hey, stop that costume!
Get them!
Sorry.
Take that!
Keep going!
- Faster!
Hey stop!
Ah...ha...ha.
Now!
Got you!
Spread out!
Search everywhere!
Right over there!
Is there a part of "everywhere"?
Yes, then search there.
They must be close.
I can feel the kung fu
chill riding up my spine.
Sorry, Po. It's just me.
Look, Gongmen jail.
Oh, it's cute.
Cute, uh?
Nice work, Po.
At the first sight of trouble,
I'll give you a signal.
'Kaka', 'kiki'.
You mean like crane does?
- Yes!
Excuse me, when have I
ever make that noise?
Master Ox!
Master!
The ferocious Master Croc.
And Master Storming Ox.
I can't believe we're rescuing
actual Legends of Kung Fu.
We are going to free you from those
bondages and injustice. No problem.
There's got to be a key around here.
No, they wouldn't leave a key around here.
Oh good, you found it!
Come on, you guys! Yeah!
We're coming for you, Shen!
Guys, are we going or not?
Do you want to meet us there later?
You do want to take back your city, right?
Of course we do.
But if we stand up to Shen,
he'll turn the weapon on the city.
Listen to yourselves.
You're protecting Gongmen city
by not protecting Gongmen city?
If we all fight together...,
then the weapon would kill everyone.
Oh, would it?
Then we use...a sneak attack.
We get inside and then...
And then you'll be stopped.
By the unstoppable weapon.
Nothing is unstoppable except for me,
when I am stopping you from
telling me something is unstoppable!
Master Ox, I'm not letting
you stay in the cell!
I like to see you get me out!
You guys see that?
It's called being awesome.
Come on! Whatever
happened being a hero?
The only hero in this
town is a dead one!
Like I said, you're not
getting me out of the cell!
Yes!
Alright, let's go.
I get the top bund.
It's time to surrender, panda.
You...
'Kung Fu' is dead.
I...
You...
Kung Fu is...dead?
Fine!
You stay in your prison affair.
With bars made of hopelessness
and all you get is three
square meals of shame!
With despair for dessert.
We'll take on Shen
and prove to all those
who're hungry for justice!
And honour, that Kung Fu still lives!
Yeah...
Monkey?
You! You're mine!
I'll tell you what is going to be yours.
My fist in your plush
cuddly super soft face.
Oh-oh.
Get him!
Get me out of here!
- Yes Sir.
Stop him!
Faster.
Go, Po!
Loose him!
Yes Sir!
Viper!
- Hang on!
Watch out!
It's very uncool!
Try this!
Guys!
Maybe something smaller!
No! No!
Not in my mouth.
We better go this way!
Pardon me!
Okay, pardon me.
Fire! Fire!
We lost them.
Yeah! Again!
Cranes, catch.
Guys, guys, give me a shove!
Mantis, now.
Is that all you got to defeat us
like a big old fluffy cloud?
This cloud is about to bring the thunder!
Your turn!
Why are there so many signs?
Come here.
I like to squash you!
Yes! Taste the defeat!
Let me tell you something.
Next time you mess with a panda,
you better bring a whole army...
Guess nobody told you.
You mess with a Wolf,
you get the fangs.
I hit you twice.
What are you going to do now?
We surrender.
You could chain my body but
you'll never chain my warrior spirit.
Hey, don't forget the little guy.
Did you just call me...
Po, what are you doing?
Trust me, I got a plan...
No way!
Eight point acupuncture cuffs?
Just like the ones they held Tai Long.
The more you move, the tighter they get.
These are the best cuffs.
Greetings Panda.
At last we meet.
No, no, no.
We meet at last.
Yes, that's it.
Greetings, Panda. We meet...
- You are afraid for a reason.
- I'm not afraid.
He's coming to me in chains.
- If anyone should be afraid, it's...
- You!
Don't even think about it.
I hope this turns out better than your
plan to cook rice in your stomach
by eating it raw and drinking boiling water.
This plan is nothing like that plan.
- How?
- Cause this one is going to work.
Keep moving.
Ahh... my old enemy.
Stairs.
Thanks for carrying me,
these last few flights.
I threw up a little bit on the third floor.
Someone might want to clean that up.
Is there some sort of
evil janitor or something?
Greetings, Panda. We meet...
Hey, how are you doing?
Hey...
You've grown up bigger than I thought.
Hey, enough of the poking around.
Strong. Healthy.
Look, I don't know who you are,
but please stand aside, Sir.
That's a lady.
Oh, sorry.
The beard threw me.
It's kind of misleading.
False avatar.
Enough of this nonsense!
Bring the prisoners to me.
Sorry, ma'am.
Get ready guys.
Keep your eyes peeled for the weapon!
Sparrow kick!
We did it!
I just kung fu'ed it?
Did you guys see that?
I was all like...
Do you actually believe this is the
warrior destined to defeat me?
I do not. I 'know' he is!
Oh, look at him.
A lifetime to plot his revenge
and he comes to me on his knees.
What? A lifetime?
I didn't have a lifetime.
We only heard of Master Rhino
a few days ago.
And we came to avenge him!
You came to avenge nothing else?
Oh Yes! All the pots
and pans that you stole!
We want those back!
Nothing else?
Probably did some evil stuffs along the way.
I don't know.
What else did you do?
You don't know?
Know what?
What is so funny?
So many things that you
clearly do not know!
Okay, enough of these riddles!
Would you guys spill the beans?
First, we come in and the weapon is tiny.
Surprised it's big.
And then the lady over here,
I think is a guy, he's...
...Oh!
The only reason you're still alive...
is that I find your stupidity
...mildly amusing.
Thank you.
But I find your evilness
extremely annoying!
Who do you think you are, panda?
Who do you think I am, peacock?
Why are we laughing?
Take aim.
Fire!
Well, light that... thing!
I did!
Fear the bug!
Get the weapon!
Tigress!
You... you were there.
Yes... yes I was.
You just let Shen get away.
At least we destroyed the weapon.
Fire!
Now, he's got way more!
Wow..ow!
My wings!
Help! Po!
- Coming!
Help me up!
No! Get him down!
Use the ropes!
Run, run little panda!
Wow!... Ahh!
I'll help, come on.
We need you to focus.
I got it! I got it!
Bring it down!
We're trapped!
This way.
Ha..ha..ha..haa!
Goodbye!
Fire!
Get back!
The only way out is up!
Follow me. Come on!
Where are they going?
To the top. Come on!
- Keep going!
Here we go!
You idiot!
Ouch! My nose.
Call in the wolves!
All of them!
I want them ready to move!
The 'Year of the Peacock' begins now!
Right now?
Cause it's the middle of the year.
So you only get like a half
of the year of the peacock.
Get the wolves ready.
We load in the ships now.
Now!
Now! Now! Now! Now!
Move! Move! Move! Move!
This way.
Come.
Oh, you!
What did you do?
It's chaos up there.
What happen to stopping Shen?
Yah?
Guys, come on.
Give me a little credit.
I meant for him to get away.
Cause...
... it was a trick, a plot.
I was thinking of figuring
out his plot more.
That makes no sense.
Wait a minute... it sure does.
Po, the truth!
You had Shen. What happened?
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Ya, okay. He caught me off guard.
The truth.
Fine.
They will keep you far from danger.
Real far.
What?
You're staying here.
Wait!
I have to go back!
You're staying here!
I'm going and you can't stop me!
Okay. I wasn't ready that time.
Guys, don't!
Ready.
Look!
Stay down.
I have to get to him.
Then tell me why!
He was there, okay?
The Peacock was there,
the last time I saw my parents.
He knows what happened.
Where I came from.
Who I am.
Look, I'm going.
I have to know.
The hardcore can't understand.
Tigress! No!
The hardcore do understand.
But I can't watch
my friend be killed.
We're going!
Hey, maybe you can't
watch me being killed.
Stop being a wimp.
And she's back.
Don't worry kid.
You're better off here.
You're wrong, Soothsayer.
We sail to victory tonight.
Your magic panda is clearly a fool.
Are you certain the panda is the fool?
You just destroyed your
ancestors' home, Shen.
A trivial sacrifice.
When all of China is my reward.
When will you be finally satisfied?
Will the subjugation of the whole world
finally make you feel better?
It's a start.
I might as well convert the
basement into a dungeon.
The cup you choose
to fill has no bottom.
It is time to stop this madness.
Why on earth would I do that?
So that your parents
can rest in peace.
My parents hated me.
Do you understand?
They wronged me.
And... I will make it right.
They loved you.
They loved you so much that having
to send you away, killed them.
The dead exist in the past.
And I must turn to the future.
Set the soothsayer free.
She's no use to me.
Goodbye, Shen.
I wish you happiness.
Happiness, must be taken!
And I will take mine.
Hurry it up!
If all of those weapons
leave the building,
China will fall.
We bring down the building.
Hey guys.
How about this?
Oh!
This will work.
Alright, let's go.
I can't feel my face.
Dumb hell crow... year of the Peacock.
Hey.
Keep it cool, keep it cool.
You!
Where are you going?
On your feet!
And wipe those stupid
grins off your faces.
Move, you dogs! Faster! Faster!
Load them all!
Greetings, Panda.
Tell me what happened that night?
What night?
That night!
Oh, that night.
Yes!
Yes, I was there.
As I watched your parents abandoned you.
It was a terrible thing.
I believe it went something like this!
Happy New Year's gift!
Hope you like it.
Cause you can't return it.
Po?
What is he doing here?
Return it! Return it!
Are you willing to die
to find out the truth?
You bet I am!
Although I prefer not to.
We got them! Go!
Looking for me?
I said that too soon, didn't I?
Po!
Po, get away from him.
No more running, Shen!
So it seems.
Now, answers.
Oh, you want to know so badly.
You think knowing will heal you, uh?
Fill some craters in your soul.
Well, here's your answer.
Your parents didn't love you.
But here...,
let me... heal you.
No..ooo!
Huh!... Ohhh!
Ya, like you can
make me drink that.
Argh...arghh...
If I wanted you dead,
I would have left you in that river.
Why did you save me?
So you can fulfill your destiny.
What are you talking about?
Where am I?
What is this place?
I'm surprised you
remembered so little.
But you were so little
when it happened.
Perhaps you do remember.
Remember what? It's just a stupid nightmare.
Nightmare? Or memory?
This was a thriving village.
Yang Shen was in line
to rule Gongmen City.
But he wanted more.
I foretold that someone
would stand in his way.
A panda.
But I never could have
foretold what came next.
Kill them all.
Take our son and
run away! Go!
Stop fighting. Let it flow.
Your story may not have
such a happy beginning.
But that does not make you who you are.
It is the rest of your story.
Who you choose to be.
So, who are you, panda?
I am Po.
And I am going to need a hat.
Such sad-sad faces.
But now is a time only for joy.
You are going to be a part
of something beautiful.
Once you reach the harbour,
in front of all the world.
You and your precious
Kung Fu will died.
Then China will know
to bow before me.
Set sail!
Honestly guys, I never
thought I'll die like this.
I always thought I'll meet
a nice girl and settle down
and she'll eat my head.
So sad.
We cannot give up hope.
Po would want us to remain strong.
Hardcored! Right, Tigress?
Lord Shen, what about the bridge?
Nothing stands in my way.
Fire!
You coward!
Po?
How many times
do I have to kill
the same stinking panda?
Shen!
A panda stands between
you and your destiny!
What?
Prepare yourself for
a hot serving of justice.
And bring the terror to an end.
What?
And now... free the Five!
Fist of Destruction!
Okay.
Take him!
Ready?
This way now...
... that way...
You can't follow me.
Just get him!
Come on.
No, no, don't shoot!
Don't shoot!
Shoot!
Don't shoot! Cross fire!
Attack!
Catch your freedom.
Monkey!
Impressive, Dragon Warrior.
What's your plan?
Step one, free the Five.
What's step two?
Honestly, I didn't think
I'll make it this far.
Stop Shen before he gets to the harbour.
Guys!
Viper, puppet of death!
Tigress!
Master Ox!
Jump!
And Croc!
Vengeance is served.
Why did you...?
Your friend there is very persuasive.
Master Shifu!
Quickly!
Use their boats to block the way.
Crane!
Wings of Justice!
Kaka!
What?
I..love..you..guys!
Why aren't we firing?
They're taking all gunmen, Sir!
And getting close!
Fire then! Go fire that gun!
But Sir!
That's our own...(people).
I said fire at them! Fire!
No!
Po!
Tigress?
As you wish,
let's finish this.
Fire!
Inner Peace. Inner Peace. Inner Peace.
Again!
Kill him!
Somebody, kill him!
What?
No!
Keep firing! Keep firing!
Skadoosh.
How did you...
How did you do it?
You just keep your elbows up
and keep the shoulders loose.
Not that. How did you find peace?
I took away your parents.
Everything.
I scarred you for life.
See, that's the thing, Shen.
Scars heal.
No, they don't.
Wounds heal.
Oh, yes. What do scars do?
They fade I guess?
I don't care what scars do.
You should Shen.
You got to let go of that stuff from
the past cause it just doesn't matter.
The only thing that matters
is what you choose to be now.
You're right.
Then I choose...
... this!
That was pretty hardcore.
Po, come here!
Don't ever do that again please.
It seems you have found inner peace.
At such a young age.
Well, I had a pretty good teacher.
What do you mean he's not here?
It's my son's birthday.
All he wanted was to meet
the Dragon Warrior.
How about some Tofu
birthday cake instead, uh?
You know, I think we'll just
try again another time.
When do you think he'll be back?
I don't know, okay?
I don't know!
Maybe never. I'm worried, okay.
But that's my job. I'm his Dad.
I mean, I was his Dad.
Why did...
- ...he go and save China?
I know why. But Why?
He's just one little panda.
So, how did it go?
Did you save China?
Yeap.
Well, I knew you would.
That's why I had new signs made.
My son saved China.
You too can save.
Buy one dumpling get one free!
Hey, that's a pretty good deal.
Would you like to try one?
Maybe later.
There's something I should tell you.
While I was gone,
I found a village where I was born.
I found out how I ended
up in that radish basket.
You did?
I know who I am.
You do?
I am your son.
Po.
I love you, Dad.
I love you too, son.
Delicious fat radishes.
You are probably hungry.
Let me make you something to eat.
What are you talking about?
I'll cook.
No, no, I'll cook.
- Dad.
This is something I can do.
You saved China.
No, it's the least I can do.
You raised me.
Po.
- Dad.
Po!
- Okay.
Let's both cook...together.
Together.
No, I'll cook.
My son is alive!