HOST: Tomorrow marks the one-year anniversary....
....since Volee Air Flight 180
exploded and crashed....
....shortly after takeoff from JFK Airport.
It’s a disaster that's affected many.
None more so than
Mount Abraham High School....
....which lost 40 students
and four faculty members in the crash.
But it was the events after the crash....
....that has turned this tragic story into something even stranger.
The survivors who managed
to get off the plane before it crashed....
....died soon thereafter in a series of mysterious and bizarre accidents.
Now, to some,
these deaths are just tragic coincidences....
....but to others, they're an indication that there are more sinister events taking place.
That's the contention of
uh, tonight's guest.
~ Thank you for joining us this evening.
GUEST: Thank you for having me.
Ahem. And I appreciate you using the word "sinister. "
Most people say "supernatural. "
They think I'm talking about ghosts and witches and stuff like that.
HOST: Well, here's your chance
to set the record straight, so....
GUEST:
Great. Okay, well....
....I believe that there 's a sort of force....
....uh, an unseen malevolent presence that's all around us every day.
And it determines when we live and die.
And some people call this force the devil.
You know, but I think
that whole religious thing is....
So I prefer to call it death itself
HOST: So I'm surrounded by death?
GUEST: Absolutely. Absolutely.
Every day, everywhere, all the time.
And that's what I want people
to understand....
....that death has this grand design that we all it into.
So when Alex Browning got off that plane and took the other survivors with him....
....he basically screwed up death 's plan.
And that's what I'm trying
to warn people about.
HOST: And the fact that all of the survivors have died is your evidence of this?
GUEST: Well, it's not so much
that the survivors died....
....but it's the way that they died.
I mean, there were so many weird, seemingly random things about the way they died.
It just didn't make sense.
You know, that's the proof
that there's something out there~~
HOST: Wait, that's not proof l mean, that is your interpretation of events....
....that can't be proven
in order to support your ideas.
MALE VOICE: Kimberly.
GUEST: Yeah, but you should be
more open-minded~~
HOST: What happened after
that was just coincidence.
GUEST: May I finish?
A mere coincidence would have
one or two of these kids die.
But not all of them
including their teachers.
HOST: Yes, but people die all the time, so why should this be any different?
It forced people to question
these so-called everyday coincidences.
What if they were something more?
~ What if you could do something about it?
HOST: Ha, ha.
Please, are you listening to yourself? This is crazy.
You're saying we should be on guard every morning when we leave the house?
GUEST: That's exactly what I'm saying.
Exactly it.
And in order to survive....
....the only way to survive
is to look beneath the visible world.
Because in the end,
no one can escape death.
And today may be your day to die.
Okay, I'll can you.
Kimberly, you sure you've got everything? Credit card, cell phone, AAA card?
Dad, it's Daytona, not Somalia.
All right. Fix-A-Flat,
road flares, sun block, mace?
Condoms, whips, chains.
Just kidding, Mr. Corman.
~ Don't worry, I'll keep an eye on her.
~ Heh.
Oh, that makes me feel a lot better. Thanks.
~ Okay.
~ Alrighty.
Can we go get the guys?
I'm getting horny. Ha-ha-ha.
Go on.
KIMBERLY: Okay, I'll call you.
Whips and chains. That's nice.
~ Whatever, your dad's cool.
~ Yeah.
(LAUGHING)
Buckle up!
Watch it!
~ Oh, easy, Kimmy. First year of driving?
~ Sorry.
~ Oh, my God.
DANO: Fucking freak.
(LAUGHING)
Dano, shouldn't we, uh, help your mom?
Oh, good one, man.
Yeah, you're hilarious.
(LAUGHING)
~ You're not getting any of my weed. Nothing.
~ Whatever.
~ What are we gonna do in Daytona?
DANO: Oh, baby.
We're gonna see lots of honeys.
We're gonna get drunk.
We're gonna smoke this big
"El Gagerero."
~ Have this awesome party on the beach.
KIDS (CHANTING): Pileup! Pileup! Pileup!
Pileup! Pileup! Pileup!
REPORTER: A candlelight vigil
to mark the one-year anniversary....
....of the crash of Flight 180....
....will be held at 8 p.m. tonight at the Mount Abraham High School auditorium.
SINGER (ON RADIO): Highway to hell
(WOMAN SINGING lNDISTINCTLY
ON RADIO)
(DANO LAUGHING)
Oh, my God.
(RINGING)
Hello?
CORMAN (OVER PHONE): Hey, it's Dad.
~ Uh, hey, what's up?
~ Your car's leaking transmission fluid.
~ So I want you to get it checked right away.
~ Okay, yeah.
~ I'll~~ Okay.
~ I mean it. Take care of it, okay?
(COUGHING)
~ ls that someone coughing?
~ Yeah, okay. I'll take care of it.
~ I'll talk to you later. Love you.
~ Bye, honey.
~ What did you do?
~ Oh, dude, look at those titties!
~ Shut up.
~ You missed that? You missed that? Aw.
That's too bad. That's too bad.
Oh, shit! Fuck, man, there's a cop behind us. Pull into the right lane now.
Shit.
(HORN HONKING)
Seriously, put it out.
~ Put that thing out.
FRANKIE: All right.
Wait, wait, wait.
~ Get rid of it.
~ Shit.
Hey, it's Kat. Listen~~
Oh, what the hell?
No. Just wait. Not you.
(CHUCKLES)
(BEEPING)
I think we better pull over
and check the car, because~~
Kimberly, the car is gonna be fine.
Your dad's gonna be fine,
you're gonna be fine. Okay?
SHAINA: Look at that guy.
He's drinking a beer.
Oh, yeah, that's real responsible.
RAPPER (ON RADIO): Got money now. So I keep my tee closer
Hate on, hater
'Cause I'm still in the game
Just killin' your brain
Makin' sure you feelin' the pain
Willin' to aim
Six shots fillin' your frame
You ever hear of the ozone layer, asshole?
(RAPPER RAPPING INDISTINCTLY
ON RADIO)
What? I'm wearing my seatbelt.
You gonna bust me, bitch?
Agh!
Son of a bitch.
Fuck!
(SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING)
~ Oh, my God!
~ Watch out!
TIM: Stop!
~ Oh, my God!
~ Watch out!
~ Aah!
(SCREAMING IN DISTANCE)
Shaina?
(SCREAMS)
Oh, God!
Help me! Help! Aah!
Help me! Help!
(SCREAMING)
FRANKIE: Ha-ha-ha
~ Oh, easy, Kimmy. First year of driving?
(GUYS LAUGHING)
FRANKIE:
Dano, shouldn't we help your mum?
DANO: Oh, good one, man.
Yeah, you're hilarious.
KIDS (CHANTING):
Pileup! Pileup! Pileup!
~ Oh my God.
~ What?
There's gonna be a huge accident. We're all gonna die. I just saw it.
That's it. My turn to drive.
~ No, I'm serious.
~ Kim, what's wrong?
~ What are you doing?
~ Oh, my God.
REPORTER: ~~of Flight 180
will be held at 8 p.m. tonight....
....at the Mount Abraham High School auditorium.
"Highway to Hell."
~ "Highway to Hell."
~ "Highway to Hell"?
SINGER (ON RADIO):
I'm on a highway to hell
Okay, Kimberly, you're scaring me.
(HORNS l-HONKING)
FRANKIE: Green means go, Kimmy.
_Uh__
Are you out of your mind?
What are you doing?
What the fuck, Kimberly?
What's this?
(HORNS l-HONKING)
Kimberly, you just gotta breathe.
Oh, shit, shit. Five-O's coming.
~ Let's fucking roll.
~ What?
~ Oh, God.
~ Do you know how much weed I have?
Okay, Dano, just shut up. Just stay cool.
(RAPPER RAPPING instinctively
ON RADIO)
Oh, fuck. I'm going to jail.
Fuck, I'm going to jail.
~ What's going on here?
~ I think there's gonna be a huge pileup.
I saw it.
There were bodies everywhere.
There were logs~~
I saw it. It just happened.
All right, miss, I'd like you
to please step out of the vehicle.
(l-HONKING)
Just pull over!
I know, Mummy's hungry too.
Come on.
Come on!
Oh, fuck this.
I'm gonna get this and we're gonna go.
Fuck.
What the hell is going on up there?
ISABELLA: Excuse me!
Is there any way
that we could drive around?
~ I have a delivery~~
~ You need to get back into your vehicles.
~ Just move it~~
~ Now.
That's it!
That's the truck
that's gonna kill everybody.
~ You need to stop that truck.
~ I told you, you have to calm down.
Why won't you listen to me?
(CRASH)
~ Fuck!
~ Oh, my God.
This is unit 13 requesting medical assistance and backup for a major traffic accident....
Kimberly, what's going on?
No!
(SOBBING)
Listen, sir,
this girl is really freaked out.
All of them are scared,
as you can imagine.
Scared? These people are the luckiest sons of bitches on the planet.
Get this guy, Evan Lewis.
Yesterday the kid wins the lotto.
Today some Loony bitch blocks traffic and he avoids the worst pileup in years.
I should be so damn unlucky.
Go babysit the rest of them.
I'll be done with Lewis in a minute.
~ Excuse me. Not to sound insensitive, but....
~ I need to get to class.
We're doing the best we can. We'll get you out of here as soon as possible.
EUGENE:
I just think it's a bunch of bullshit.
Listen, I know you've gone over all this with Detective Suby....
....but would you mind telling me what happened?
It was like I was there.
I knew something bad was gonna happen even before it did.
~ I just felt wrong, just like....
~ Just like what?
Look, I know this sounds crazy, but you guys all heard about Flight 180, right?
Kid who got off the plane?
Well, it happened a year ago today.
My premonition was just like his.
~ What are you talking about?
EUGENE: Come on.
You must have read about the kid who had a dream about a plane blowing up....
....so he got his buddies off the plane....
....and then the thing blew up
like in his dream?
~ Yeah.
~ But did you hear what happened after?
So a month goes by, right?
Everything seems cool.
But then all the survivors
start to die one by one.
Because when your number's up,
your number's up, right?
You know, some people even said
that death itself was stalking them....
....hunting each one down....
....until they were all dead.
(LAUGHING MAN MANIACALLY)
Please.
THOMAS: There was one survivor.
Clear Rivers is in a padded room at the Stonybrook Institution.
Well, that's encouraging.
KAT: Okay, you want me
to believe that this is true....
....that this is happening all over again? Ugh.
I don't know why we're even here.
What do you want from me?
But if I was never meant to pull over, we all should have died in that pileup.
Which means death
could be coming for us.
Yeah, like what if we're all getting that Different Strokes curse or something?
I think you're all are certifiable.
I can't believe I've been listening to this crap. Let's go.
~ Let's go, Tim.
THOMAS: Mrs. Carpenter, please.
Kimberly!
On, baby.
~ Are you okay? Shh, shh.
~ I'm so sorry.
You can all go now.
Thank you for your patience.
It's okay.
Could I ask you something?
Anything.
Did Mom ever have any, I don't know, um, weird feelings about anything?
What do you mean?
Um....
Like visions or premonitions.
Sweetie, are you sure you're okay?
Dad, I know this sounds crazy,
but I'm really scared for the others.
I don't know, I just~~
I have this really bad feeling.
What?
It's not over yet.
(DOOR OPENS)
Jesus Christ!
Shit.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
TAWNY (ON MACHINE):
Hey, Evan, it's Tawny.
Sorry I haven't called.
Hey, listen,
I heard about your lottery win.
Let's hook up. Call me.
(MACHINE BEEPS)
Yeah.
NICKIE (ON MACHINE): Hi, Evan, it's Nickie. We met at Tucker's party last year.
I know it's been a while,
but I've been thinking about you.
Just wanted to say congratulations, so give me a call.
555-0123. Bye.
You little bastard.
Shit.
(GRUNTING)
Come on. Come on.
Fuck.
Ugh! Come on.
Fuck! Jesus.
(PHONE RINGING)
EVAN (ON MACHINE):
This is Evan. Leave a message.
If you're looking for Rick, I don't know where he is or when he's coming back.
GUY (ON MACHINE): Evan, call me
when you get in, you lucky fuck.
Ha!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Agh!
Jesus.
Come on.
(GRUNTING)
Shit, I'm lucky.
Jesus Christ! Ha.
No, Mother,
just turn on any station.
Well, I don't know how you missed it. it's been on all day.
Yes, Mother, Channel 4 is fine.
Okay, you know~~ Look, here it is. I gotta go, okay? Mm-mm! I gotta go!
~~Reach them. To recap our top story....
....Route 23 was backed up
for almost nine hours today.
A record-breaking pileup
killed an estimated 18 people.
Emergency crews spent hours
sifting through the wreckage....
....hoping to recover any survivors from this tragic collision.
So far, police are refusing
to release the names of the victims....
....until the families are notified.
The camera of a highway patrol car managed to catch this shocking footage.
~ A semi comes careening across the road....
~ Oh, my God.
....and smashes into a red SUV.
~ The SUV driver was beside her vehicle.
~ No. Um~~
~ The quick actions of a trooper saved her life.
~ Leave it.
He pulled her back at the last second just as the semi ploughed into the vehicle.
~ The passengers inside the SUV....
~ Oh, oh, oh!
You guys see that?
Shit, I was there, baby.
In other news, a freak accident
took the life of a lotto winner.
~ Friends say Evan Lewis....
~ Eh, shh.
....was on top of the world
after recently winning $250,000.
But in e tragic turn of events,
Lewis died today....
....while trying to escape a fire in his apartment.
He managed to make it out
of the building....
....but somehow the ladder
on the fire escape slipped and impaled him.
Investigators believe Lewis
died instantly.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Come in.
Hey, buddy.
I want you to take this
so you get some sleep.
And then tomorrow it's off to the dentist, which I know you love.
Now get some rest.
~ Mom.
~ Yeah?
You think those guys were
BS-ing us today?
Yeah.
Some people just need some rewiring, that's all.
Lights out.
At the request of the patient,
you'll relinquish any sharp objects, such as:
"Nail files, pencils, pens, safety pins, bobby pins, your necklace....
...."matches, lighters, belts, belt buckles, earrings, hair clips, glasses, shoelaces....
....paper clips, watches, money clip, pocket knives, food, drinks, keys, cell phone~~"
You have a cell phone on you?
"~~poisons, pills, medications."
Great. And let me see your nails.
Good. Then I think we're all done.
Wait. Um~~
Is she dangerous or something?
No, honey. She expects you are.
WOMAN:
No, please, help me. No, no, no.
MAN: Get him off me. Get him off me. Get him off me.
How long are they gonna keep
her locked up?
Depends on her, I guess.
She's voluntary.
~ Clear Rivers?
~ Don't come any closer.
They told me that you had something to do with the crash on Route 23.
Look, I don't know how to explain it....
....but I saw the pileup
before it happened.
And I saved some people.
And now you think death is after you.
Nice work.
Maybe if you're real lucky,
you'll wind up in here with me.
Anything else?
One person died in an accident last night. What if the others are in danger too?
Well, if you put them on the list, they're already dead.
List? What list?
Death's list.
The survivors of Flight 180
died in the exact order....
....they were originally meant to die in the plane crash.
That was death's original design.
The list.
I was supposed to die in that crash with my friends. So I'm next?
You said that someone else
died last night.
That means someone must
have intervened.
Officer Burke pulled me away
from the crash that killed my friends.
Congratulations.
You'll be the last to go.
But don't worry. Once the others are dead, it'll come back for you.
It always does.
This doesn't make sense.
You said that you die in the order you're originally meant to.
But my friends died last
in my premonition, not first.
Wait.
Died last?
Backwards.
Are you sure?
KIMBERLY: In my premonition,
that Nora woman and her kid died.
Then Evan, then me and my friends.
Why is this even happening to me?
That's what Alex used to ask himself.
So, what am I supposed to do?
Clear.
~ Watch out for the signs.
~ What?
Have you ever seen anything
creepy or ominous?
An in-your-face irony kind of thing?
The songs on the radio.
Yeah, the guy in the beer truck, everything on the road.
Well, don't ignore it.
Recognizing those signs usually means the difference between life and death.
You gotta help me.
~ I don't have to do anything.
~ But you beat it.
Take a look around.
What did I beat, Kimberly?
If you were smart, you'd save yourself, forget about the others.
How can you say that?
You have a responsibility.
My friends are dead.
That's how I can say that.
And this is what happened to Alex when I was responsible for him.
Get out.
Before you hurt me or yourself.
~ All right, you know what?
~ What?
I think you're a coward.
You hide out in here
because you're too damn bitter....
....and selfish to help any other person.
In my opinion, you're already dead.
I tried calling you last night.
Your father said you were sleeping.
~ Evan Lewis is dead.
~ Yeah.
I've been getting calls all morning from everyone who was on the on-ramp.
We're meeting tonight at my apartment.
Wait, wait,
so you believe all this death stuff?
Well, at first, no, I didn't.
Until last year when I was dispatched to clean up one of the Flight 180 survivors.
Clean up, I don't....
~ Did you see that?
~ See what?
~ Pigeons.
~ Pigeons?
~ It's a sign.
~ A sign of what?
If Clear's right about the order....
....then Nora and Tim are gonna be attacked by pigeons.
~ I'm not following you.
~ They're next on death's list.
If we don't find them, they're gonna die.
JEAN: Ahem. The doctor's ready for you now.
If he gives me the gas and I wake up with my pants unbuttoned, we ain't paying.
(LAUGHS)
Tim.
There you are.
What happened to you yesterday, Tim?
We missed you in here.
We got hung up by that accident
on Route 23.
Good Lord. How lucky that you're okay.
Your mom says
you've been having some pain lately.
Not really.
I'm disappointed, Tim.
Does your mom know you've been smoking?
Uh-huh. Agh.
Yeah, that one's gonna have to be filled.
Damn those pigeons.
How many times am I gonna have
to replace those goddamn windows?
Okay. This will only sting for an moment.
Open big.
Little wider.
Wider.
Okay.
Agh, God. How do they expect me to....?
Would you rather just have
the laughing gas?
~ Yeah.
Jean, I'm gonna need you in here.
(CONSTRUCTION EQUIPMENT WHINING)
No, you're gonna have to speak up. There's too much noise.
What? I can't hear you.
Excuse me, what?
Yes, the 6th at 2 p.m.
Jean! Let me get this started.
Now, Tim, you'll be awake,
a little groggy....
....but you're not gonna be able to move much.
(BUZZING)
Okay, great, thanks.
All right, uh, turn around.
The cleaning lady said they're at the Ellis Medical Complex off of 14th.
(GLASS SHATTERS)
Goddamn it anyway.
NORA: Okay, I got it.
JEAN: I can't find a box!
Not again. Be careful.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
There we go.
DENTIST: Jean, how's Tim doing in there?
What did he say about your tooth?
~ Did he say~~?
~ I can't remember.
THOMAS: Nora!
~ The pigeons!
What? Pigeons?
Hey, whoa, whoa! Kid, kid!
Whoa, whoa!
~ No!
~ Tim!
MAN: Look out!
~ Stay back! Stay back!
~ No! Please, no!
(STAMMERS)
(SOBBING)
Nora's not coming.
She won't leave her son.
~ No, but she's next. We have to~~
~ Right now I don't think she cares.
This is really happening again, isn't it?
I hoped we'd get there
and they'd be fine....
....and Clear Rivers was just full of shit....
....and Evan Lewis' death
was just some freak accident.
But we're all gonna die, aren't we?
I'm so scared.
I know you didn't ask for any of this....
....but I don't think you have it in you to quit either.
A second one just died.
A 15-year-old kid.
I hope you're ready for this.
It's this way.
How is this guy gonna help us anyway?
He seemed to know a hell of a lot more about death than he ever told us.
Well, shouldn't we knock first?
He probably already knows we're coming.
Hello, Clear.
I've been expecting you.
Oh, my God.
~ That's Evan Lewis.
~ Come to pick my brain?
Just a simple question and
we'll leave you alone with your new friend.
Dead....
....yet still fresh. Ha, ha.
Look, we drove a long way to get here....
....so if you happen to know how to stop death....
....it would be really great if you told us.
You can't cheat death.
There are no escapes.
Bullshit.
You told me death has a distinct design.
But Alex and I cheated death not once, but dozens of times.
The design is flawed. It can be beaten.
Such fire in you now.
People are always most alive
just before they die.
Don't you think?
(WHISTLING)
Look, please.
If you know of anything
that could help us....
....what harm could it do?
Only new life can defeat death.
What the hell does that mean?
Some people say
there's a balance to everything.
For every life, there's a death. For every death, there is a life.
But the introduction of
life that was not meant to be....
....that can invalidate the list, force death to start anew.
You have to follow the signs, Kimberly.
How do you know my name?
~ Whoa, heh.
THOMAS: All right, wait a second.
"New life defeats death.
Follow the signs."
I mean, where did you find that guy?
I know. I mean, I thought he was supposed to help us, not freak us out.
What the fuck are you thinking?
Heh.
I'm thinking suck on my junk, beyotch.
Little punk.
~ What is it?
~ What did you see?
(COUGHING)
(HORNS HONKING)
(BARKING)
(COUGHING)
You have to tell us, what did you see?
Kimberly, look at me.
You have to tell us. What did you see?
I was driving a white van....
....and I must have lost control, because I crashed into a lake.
~ And I drowned.
~ You were there?
I can practically taste the water in my mouth.
Remember? The on-ramp.
There was a pregnant woman
in a white delivery van.
He said only new life can defeat death.
If she gives birth to a baby
that would've died in that car crash....
....a brand-new soul that was never part of death's design~~
It throws the whole list out of whack and we start over with a clean slate.
~ Seems like a reach, don't you think?
~ What else could it mean?
~ Find the lady's number.
~ Don't have it. She never came to the station.
We have to find her, warn her about the lake so she can stay alive to have the baby.
~ That'll be an easy conversation.
CLEAR: How will we find her?
There could be thousands of white vans in the state.
Hey.
I'm a cop, remember?
Wait, that's it.
Got it.
With the plate number,
I can put out an APB.
Here we go.
The vehicle is a delivery van registered to Marcus and Isabella Hudson.
We should pick them up pretty quickly.
Come on, let's get to the meeting.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
Hey, hold the door!
Hey, let go of my shoe!
Give me my shoe!
I wrote to management two weeks ago about these bumpers.
Is that dog shit, dude?
Ew.
Uh, you got something on your....
Heh. it's still there, bro.
Here, I can get it for you.
No, it's all right.
I'll do it if you want me to do it.
Just let~~ I'll~~ Let me do it.
What?
Hey, man. How you doing?
Listen, any word on that white van yet?
Okay, well, keep checking.
(CLEARS THROAT)
~ Does anybody have a Valium?
~ Oh, yeah.
Here.
You're just gonna want to take
half of that.
Keep them coming.
If what you're saying is true,
that means I'm next.
This is crazy, people. Come on.
First death is stalking us
and now premonitions? What?
You're not next, Nora.
Nobody has to be next. That's the point.
We need to help each other
in order to get through this.
Oh, this cannot be happening.
See, because my career is at a peak and I finally met a quality guy.
I just bought a house.
Maybe if you shut the fuck up,
you'll live.
Yeah, like I'm gonna take advice from you.
Okay, look, if you know what to look for, you have a fighting chance.
If I call and say, I don't know, "subway," get to a high-rise fast.
A place where no subway
could ever possibly go. Get it?
CLEAR: Okay, you guys, listen.
Just because Kimberly
has these visions....
....it doesn't mean we're not all capable of seeing signs to some extent.
Okay, okay, look. I gotta call bullshit.
I mean, I've sat here and listened to all your theories and all your stories....
....and I think it's just all bullshit.
Call it what you want.
it'll keep your ass alive.
Darling, my ass is alive. Huh?
Has been all day.
There is nobody after us but you, trying to make us all crazy.
(ALL SCREAM)
I should have seen that coming.
~ Yeah.
~ If death is out to get you....
....why don't you just
get the hell away from us?
She's the only one
that's dealt with this before.
We need to look out for each other from now on. Sleep in shifts.
We need to safe-proof this death-trap.
~ Get you to step out of the van, miss?
~ Are you kidding me?
~ What did I do?
~ This vehicle's been reported stolen.
Ugh.
Screw this. I'm going for a smoke.
No, no, no, it's not safe out there.
So? Nora's gotta bite it
before me anyhow, huh?
Oh, you people have no sense of humor.
Nora, you okay?
Four years ago, my husband died.
Now Tim. There's nothing left for me.
Look, don't say that, okay?
If it is my time to go and be in heaven with my family, I can accept that.
You gotta trust me, okay?
We can fight this.
We stick together long enough
for her to have her baby~~
If you'll excuse me,
I have a funeral to plan.
Nora.
~ What do you think you're doing?
~ I'm finished. I'm out.
~ Don't leave, Eugene.
~ Look, look.
I control my life, all right?
Not some crazy list
that death has put together.
~ Well~~
~ I'll carve that into your tombstone.
EUGENE: You may scare these people, but I'm not buying that shit.
RORY: Be careful, man.
~ Hey.
~ What?
~ Even if you don't believe, give this to Nora.
I'm just gonna put this in the....
....closet
Aah!
Sorry.
Whoa.
A man with hooks?
Man with hooks.
Hey, I think I see a man with hooks.
Is that....
~ ....a sign?
KIMBERLY: Oh, my God.
~ Do you guys see that?
CLEAR: He's right.
~ The phone.
~ Shit.
(CLEARS THROAT)
What the fuck?
(RINGING)
~ Hello?
~ Nora.
~ Who is this?
~ Can you hear me?
Officer Burke, I can't~~
I can't hear you. What?
What? What does he~~? What?
A man with hooks is gonna kill you.
What, what? What is it, Nora?
(SHOUTS)
~ Wait, wait, wait.
~ No! Let go of me!
~ Wait, wait, Nora!
~ Get me out of here!
~ Will you stop it?
~ Let me help.
Let me go!
(SCREAMING)
Let go of me!
Help me!
Kat!
(ALL SHOUTING)
Oh, my God.
Help me!
~ Wait!
~ I don't want to die!
(GRUNTS)
(ALL SCREAM)
Aah, let me out.
Good, I got it, thanks.
They found the van.
Isabella's being held at
the Greenwood Lake sheriff's station.
~ It almost kicked my ass.
~ Eugene, what is it?
~ I control my life!
~ What happened, Eugene?
~ You hear me, you reaper cocksucker?
KIMBERLY: Calm down.
~ What happened? Where's Nora?
~ Back the fuck up!
~ Whoa, okay!
What's wrong, man?
Just tell us what happened.
THOMAS: All right, give me the gun.
~ Give me the gun.
~ No! Fuck no!
Whoa, Eugene,
you just gotta chillax, bro, okay?
~ You just gotta calm down, man.
~ Give me the gun. Give me the gun.
~ No, no, no!
~ Don't do it! Don't do it!
~ I ain't going out like that.
~ Eugene, no!
~ On my terms! You hear me?
RORY: Oh, my God!
(GUN CLICKING)
RORY: God!
You don't keep it loaded?
~ Maybe they're all duds.
~ Six in a row?
Never. That's impossible.
It wasn't his turn to die.
Can we find the pregnant woman now, please?
RORY: Is this safe, guys?
I mean, someone in this car
is about to get whacked.
Do the rest of us really feel
like sitting next to him? Or her?
Hopefully her.
Okay, guys, let's not panic.
lsabella's safe.
How do you know?
You said she was gonna drive into a lake.
How can she
if she's in protective custody?
Look at me.
Come on.
Does it look like I'm in the condition to commit grand theft auto? This is insane.
Look, hopefully the district judge will have it all sorted out by Monday morning, okay?
(SCOFFS)
Marcus.
Marcus, Marcus.
When I get out of here,
I am going to sue his....
(WATER DRIPPING)
~ Oh, my God.
~ What? What now?
~ My water just broke.
~ What?
My water, it just broke.
I'm gonna have my baby.
No, not here.
No, you can't do this to me.
~ Don't just stand there. Get me to a hospital.
~ Just give me a second to think! Um~~
I am not gonna have my baby
in a jail cell!
~ Get me to the hospital!
~ Okay, okay! Just~~ Uh~~
Sheriff Perry, this is, uh~~
Uh, Deputy Adams. Come back.
God, I need the car!
Sheriff Perry, I need the car.
My van. My van. Take my van.
Um, okay. Okay. Yeah, we'll go.
We'll go. Uh~~ Yeah, we'll go.
Here.
Come on, come on.
EUGENE:
Y'all wanna hear something crazy?
It's not the first time I cheated death.
Kid came to school with a knife, killed his teacher.
Huh.
Teacher would have been me....
....but I was transferred
to another school two days before.
That's fucking weird, man.
You want weird? Last year,
my partner and I were heading out....
....when a call came in about
a train wreck.
Frank decided to let me handle it alone.
He died that night in a shootout.
If that call had come in
just '1O seconds later, I'd be dead too.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry, heh. it's just I got one too.
Okay, last May,
I'm supposed to go and stay....
....at this cheesy little bed-and-breakfast in Pennsylvania.
Anyhow, there's this major gas leak that no one knows about....
....and all the guests suffocated during the night.
~ So, what happened?
~ I don't know. I never made it.
The bus I was on splattered some girl all over the road.
Was that in Mount Abraham?
Yes. How did you know?
That bus you were on killed
Terry Chaney.
She was supposed to die on Flight 180.
Hey, do you guys remember
that theater in Paris....
....that collapsed last year
and killed everybody inside?
Well, I had tickets to go.
But one night, you know, I'm in Paris and I'm, heh, just tripping on acid....
....and sipping lattes and such.
And then all of a sudden....
....this dude out of nowhere
just gets whacked by this falling sign.
~ Carter.
~ Wait, wait, wait.
The teacher I replaced,
her name was Val Lewton.
She was from Mount Abraham.
She died in an explosion.
Shit. The call about the train wreck that saved my life....
....that was the night
I scraped up Billy Hitchcock.
Wait a minute. Wait, wait.
Who are these people?
The people who got off of Flight 180.
CLEAR: They were my friends.
Kimberly, tell us what happened.
About a year ago,
my mom and I were at the mall.
I was supposed to meet her outside, but I got caught up watching this news report....
....about some kid that committed suicide.
I kept thinking, "How can you strangle yourself in the bathtub? That's stupid."
I don't know, it felt wrong. And yet....
I heard, um,
some gunshots and I ran outside.
Some kids were trying to steal
my mom's car.
She tried to fight them off,
she was a fighter, and they killed her.
After the funeral, I kept thinking that it should have been me.
I guess everyone must think that.
But I guess I was right.
(GROANING)
Get there.
~ Could you drive a little faster maybe? God.
~ I'm going as fast as I can.
When we got off Flight 180,
it didn't just change our lives.
It affected everyone and everything we've come into Contact with since.
I'm not sure I'm understanding you.
Being alive after we were supposed to die, it caused an outward ripple.
A rift in death's design.
So if you had never gotten
off the plane....
....we wouldn't be alive in the first place.
Yes, that's why death
is working backwards.
It's tying up all the loose ends, sealing the rift once and for all.
(SCREAMS)
Whoa!
Oh, Shit!
Jesus Christ!
(SCREAMS)
Hang on.
(KAT GASPS)
~ Is everybody all right?
~ Oh, God. Aah!
Oh, God.
~ God, Eugene.
~ He can't breathe.
Oh, my legs!
(GASPING)
ISABELLA: No, please.
~ It's not gonna wait.
~ I gotta go help those people.
Do you want to deliver this baby?
ISABELLA: Those people can help. Let's go.
Officer Adams reporting e vehicle collision off 9-A at the 180 mile marker.
All emergency vehicles to the scene.
~ We have to go. Go!
~ Okay, okay, okay!
Just~~ Okay, okay!
We're going. We're going. We're going.
~ Easy, easy. Keep his head up.
~ Here, here, here.
I think he has a collapsed lung.
MAN: Everyone okay?
~ Call an ambulance!
You're gonna be all right, buddy. Come on.
KIMBERLY: Stay with us.
Hey, hey, you!
Hey! Come on. Help me out.
You gotta get me out of here before this thing explodes or something, okay?
I think it's okay. I don't smell any gas and nothing's dripping.
All right, get this thing off me. Just pull. Hurry.
~ Okay. Be careful. Ready? Okay.
~ Okay. Okay.
Aah! Oh, God, Jethro! Jesus Christ!
I gotta be able to use my legs
when I'm done.
I'm so~~ Dad!
(SIREN WAILING)
~ Eugene, everything's gonna be okay.
~ Without a respirator, he won't make it.
We're gonna get you to the hospital. Be careful with that!
Check the gauges on the regulator and watch out for overdoses.
~ And look out for potholes and puddles.
~ You can't come in, miss.
And watch out for power lines!
RORY: Watch it!
You trying to get yourself killed, little boy?
You gotta use your head, man.
MAN: Get that news van back.
~ Thanks.
Okay, let's go.
How's she doing?
I don't know.
I think she's gonna be okay.
~ Can I ask you a question?
~ Yeah.
When I die, uh....
....is it gonna hurt?
I don't know.
You're gonna die after me, right?
Yeah, I guess so.
Would you take these?
And if I die, um....
....would you throw out all my drugs and my paraphernalia and my porno?
Just, you know, anything
that's gonna break my mom's heart.
Please?
Thank you.
REPORTER: This is Cheyenne Jacobson reporting live from the Gibbons farm.
Sheriff Perry, Officer Burke.
I'm trying to get some information on Isabella Hu~~
She did?
Okay. Thanks. Great.
Kimberly. lsabella's at Lakeview Hospital. They're prepping her for delivery.
~ We gotta go now.
~ What about Kat?
I'll go talk to her.
Hi.
Just find Isabella
and get this thing over with, okay?
Go on. I'll be fine.
~ Where's Rory?
~ I don't know.
Wait.
(ENGINE REVVING)
Could you be a little quieter
with that thing?
Yeah, sure.
I'll just put it on quiet mode.
That would be good.
Rory.
MAN 1: Oh, my God!
MAN 2: Somebody get out there!
~ We have to get to the hospital now.
~ Well, take my truck. The keys are in it.
~ Unh~~
CLEAR: Kimberly!
Kimberly! Kimberly.
What do you see?
What are we looking for?
No, it's not here.
This one was different.
It was like the van crashing into the lake.
I was in a hospital, there was screaming and a nurse was trying to choke me.
I couldn't see her,
but I could see her name tag.
It was right in my face. Kalarjian.
I think a nurse named Kalarjian
is gonna try and kill Isabella.
(SCREAMS)
Listen to me, Isabella.
I need you to stop pushing.
What's wrong? Is my baby all right?
The cord's around the neck.
This baby's in trouble.
REPORTER (ON TV): A bizarre accident has left two people dead....
....one of them killed by
a safety device meant to protect us.
Ironically, the woman
was impaled through the head....
....after her emergency airbag deployed.
She was trapped in her vehicle
after it crashed near Greenwood Lake.
Suddenly the airbag went off....
....sending her head flying backward into a metal pipe, killing her instantly.
(SIREN WAILING)
Isabella Hudson. What room is she in?
We may need to do a stat Caesarean. Get Dr. Kalarjian up here now.
Dr. Kalarjian, code blue, Delivery Room 6.
I'm just gonna wait outside,
because I'm in the way here.
~ Don't you dare leave me.
~ Okay, okay.
You guys, get to Isabella.
I'm going to find Eugene.
NURSE (ON INTERCOM):
Dr. Kalarjian, code blue, Delivery Room 6.
Dr. Kalarjian, Delivery Room 6, code blue.
NURSE: Dr. Kalarjian, in here, hurry!
~ That's her.
~ No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait!
(MACHINE BEEPING)
Contractions have stopped. Arrest in descent halfway through the birth canal.
WOMAN: Bad tracing. it's losing oxygen.
The cord's compressed.
~ Down to 40.
~ Oh, God! What's happening?
NURSE: Where's Kalarjian?
Dr. Kalarjian!
~ Dr. Kalarjian!
~ Not now, I'm busy.
~ Hey! Hey!
~ Police business.
(BEEPING RAPIDLY)
(GASPING)
MAN: Just push a little more.
~ Oh, oh.
Oh, no.
Isabella, is the baby okay?
You can't be here.
I have to ask you to leave.
I need to know if the baby's all right. I need to know if the baby's all right.
(CRYING)
It's a boy.
(SHOUTS)
(LAUGHING)
Thank you. Congratulations.
Who the hell are they?
Oh, my God.
~ Clear.
~ I can't find Eugene.
~ No, no, don't worry. She had the baby.
~ It's okay. it's over. it's okay.
THOMAS: Kimberly.
CLEAR: What did you see?
I don't think Isabella
was supposed to die in that pileup.
~ What's the premonition of the lake mean?
~ Try to remember.
Bloody hands.
Someone with bloody hands.
Eugene.
Only new life defeats death.
What is that supposed to mean?
You saw an ECG machine and what else?
Bloody hands.
What else did you see, Kimberly?
Wait.
Eugene.
(ALARM WAILING)
Oh, God, no!
Bloody hands.
It's me. The premonitions are about me.
~ What?
~ Crash cart.
Let's go! Move it!
KIMBERLY: Dr. Kalarjian.
ECG machine.
The lake. The white van.
What are you talking about?
KIMBERLY: New life.
THOMAS: What is it?
I know what I have to do to save us.
~ I have to die.
~ No, no, that's crazy.
You can't give up now.
We have to fight this thing.
Get Kalarjian.
(GRUNTS)
BLUDWORTH: Only new life can defeat death.
NORA: If it is my time to go and be in heaven with my family, I can accept that.
ISABELLA: Aah!
REPORTER: Flight 180....
KIMBERLY: I know what I have to do to save us.
REPORTER: There are no known survivors.
KIMBERLY: I have to die.
NURSE: Ready and clear.
Nothing.
(DEFIBRILLATOR HUMMING)
NURSE: Ready and clear.
Nothing.
KALARJIAN: Come on.
NURSE: Ready, clear.
She's back!
Epinephrine, 2 milligrams, IV push.
I want her prepped and stabilized for ICU.
Welcome back.
They lost you for a minute there.
Hey. We did it.
Thanks to you, we cheated death.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
WOMAN: Would you like some wine?
KIMBERLY: I think I'll stick to our beer, thanks.
All right.
This is really great, Mrs. Gibbons.
Thank you so much for inviting us.
It's our pleasure.
~ So how are you doing, Kimberly?
~ Good. Yeah. Um....
I had a fun summer.
I don't know, I guess things are pretty much getting back to normal.
Brian, I think you better go check that barbecue. Ha-ha-ha.
Oh, hey, careful.
Those things are dangerous.
Trust me,
I've been through closer calls.
Yeah, me too. Dad, you should tell them about the news van thing.
What's that?
Brian was almost hit by that news van that day in the field.
And your friend Rory, he, um,
he pulled him back at the last second.
Saved his life.
MRS. GIBBONS:
You never told me that, Peter.
Boy, that was lucky.
Brian!
(SCREAMING)