Okay. Let's see
where we are.
Uh, we could move this,
get rid of that,
kill that.
That kind of freaks me out.
Don't need her. Uh, we can get
rid of that.
That's done. Okay,
we could start with this.
I know it's a hard-hitting
piece, but come on, you guys,
it's the Internet.
We need traffic, traffic,
traffic. What do you got?
How about this?
Perfect.
Now, doesn't she look
smart and knowledgeable
about immigration reform?
ALL: Yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
She does, right?
I'm fucking with
you people. This
isn't a porn site.
What are we, nerds
trying to look at boobies?
Come on, keep looking.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Shit! Hello?
Hey! Baby, where are you?
Are you still at work?
No! Not even close.
Just so you know,
the movie starts
in 10 minutes.
I know!
Give me your pants.
What?
I'll buy you lunch
tomorrow. Come on.
No.
I'm your boss.
Give me your pants.
Please try not to be
late. I really hate
missing the beginning.
I know. I know.
Give me your pants.
I'm coming, baby.
I'm almost there!
How far away?
I think I see you!
Where are you?
I'm here.
So am I.
So many people.
What are you wearing?
I'm wearing the
only clothes outside
the theater,
because I'm
the only person
outside the theater!
I love that outfit.
You look so sexy in that.
You know that
I love this movie.
If a prostitute and
a ruthless businessman
can fall in love,
then anyone can.
I know this means a lot
to you, which means it
means a lot to me.
Well, apparently
it doesn't.
I'm looking at you
right now. I can see you!
MAN: Jamie!
Hey!
Hey.
Oh, you made it.
Yeah. Hey.
Hi.
Sorry I'm late.
It's okay. I got
us sandwiches.
I got you turkey,
no cheese,
gluten-free bread.
You sure this was
prepared in a
nut-free facility?
Yes, I'm fully aware
of your allergies.
Hey, I'm here!
I'm here.
I'm really sorry.
We missed  Your Body
Is a Wonderland.
Okay. Only one song.
That's not so bad, right?
It was fucking
Your Body Is a
Wonderland!
Well, the good
news is, he has so
many good ones.
Here's an idea. Next time,
instead of being late,
just shit on my face.
'Cause that's kind of
the same thing as missing
Your Body Is a Wonderland.
Okay, come on.
We really gotta go in.
really tall boots.
Julia Roberts is
about to put on her
Um...
We need to talk.
I think we should
take a break.
we should chill for
a while, you know?
I just feel like
You're doing this?
You're breaking
up with me?
You said I was
your soul mate.
I did? When?
When we were at that
bed and breakfast
having sex.
But, you know,
that doesn't...
That doesn't what?
Count.
I was tied up at
work. I'm sorry.
Maybe you should
care a little bit
less about work
and a little more
about the girl
that you're dating.
'Cause last time
I checked, work
doesn't reassure you
up your ass doesn't
make you gay.
that liking a finger
I never said
"Go up." Okay?
I just said lightly
around... It's like
a little button.
You know what?
Not your issue
anymore.
Is this why
you were late?
You were worried
about how to break
up with me?
Oh, no, no.
I was trying to
decide what to wear.
So, you went with
sneakers and a hoodie.
Yeah.
What, are you gonna
take the SATs after this?
Don't lash
out, okay?
You're better
than that.
I'm really not.
I just think we're
heading in different
directions.
Yeah, you to the
John Mayer concert
and me not.
Thank you for doing
this before the concert,
by the way.
Best breakup
(MOUTHING) ever.
He is the Sheryl Crow
of our generation!
Let me just ask
you a quick question.
And just know that
I am not at all crushed
by this breakup.
So, be honest. Why?
Wait, is this a trick?
No.
Just pure
anthropological
research.
Okay. You want
someone to sweep
you off your feet,
but you're more
interested in getting
swept off your feet
than the someone
who's doing the
sweeping.
You seem like you've
got it totally together,
but you're actually
really emotionally damaged.
Also, you have, like, really
big eyes, and that freaks me
out sometimes...
Thank you.
That's enough.
It is not you
at all.
Of course it's me!
You can't say that.
You're breaking up with me!
It's not. It's me.
I don't like you
anymore.
This is my fault.
You deserve better
than me.
You're a
great guy.
A little too emotionally
unavailable, if you ask me.
I didn't.
I really want to
stay friends.
Let's stay friends.
Sure.
Totally.
(MOUTHING)
John Mayer.
John fucking Mayer!
Come here, you.
You're gonna
get through this.
Why do relationships always
start off so fun and then
turn into suck-a-bag-o-dicks?
I really have to stop
buying into this bullshit
Hollywood cliche of true love.
Shut up, Katherine
Heigl! You stupid liar!
I'm just gonna work
and fuck. Like
George Clooney.
I'm just gonna
shut myself down
emotionally.
Like George Clooney.
Hello.
Seat up,
please, sir.
Is that the
Hudson River?
No. It's the
East River.
So we won't be
landing on it, then,
like that flight,
you know, with
that captain they
keep giving medals to?
That pilot
was a hero.
Asshole.
Plane actually did
a lot of the work.
JAMIE: I think I found
the perfect guy to fill
that job at  GQ.
No, he's landing early.
I'm scrambling.
No, he's not sold on
the job yet, but I'll
get him there. I always do.
I'm even picking him
up in a hybrid.
He's from LA. I figured
he's into all that bullshit.
Hey, sir, what's that
tall building over there?
Empire State Building.
No, no, no, no.
No. The other one.
The really, really tall
one with the antenna on
top of it, the windows.
That is Empire
State Building.
Oh, yeah. You're
right.  King Kong.
Hey...
Oh, hey! Are you
done with this?
All met up?
Great. Welcome
to New York,
Ms. Penderghast.
Yeah.
Oh, no. Oh.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Okay.
Can you hand
me my bag?
Sure. Which one?
The one with
the straps.
Okay.
MAN: There.
Thank you.
Welcome to
New York, sir.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
That's me.
Which one, the
blue or the yellow?
No. The makeshift
sign made out of
lipstick, that's me.
You're Dylan Harper.
I am.
I'm Jamie Rellis.
You're picking me
up from the airport.
Hi. Yes, I am.
You always pick
people up like this?
Uh, yeah, you know,
I like to keep
things interesting.
Welcome to
New York.
Thank you.
You're not exactly what
comes to mind when you
think headhunter.
Yeah, I prefer "executive
recruiter." Headhunter
sounds a little creepy.
You did stalk me
for six months.
Kind of creepy.
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
Oh, here, here, here,
I'll take it.
You're really gonna
carry my bag?
You're that girl?
No. I'm gonna
change your life.
I'm that girl.
My life is already
pretty great.
Oh, really? 'Cause you
wouldn't be here if your life
were already pretty great.
A free trip to New York.
I'd be an idiot to turn
that down.
Well, then I guess you
must have been an idiot
for the past six months.
Ooh, yeah, a lot of
people would say
longer than that.
JAMIE:  It's a huge
opportunity, Dylan.
Art director of
GQ magazine. This
is the big leagues.
I mean, no offense
to your little blog
on the Internet.
Which got six million
hits last month.
with my boobs
I could put up a video
of me mixing cake batter
and it will get
eight million hits.
It's been done.
Dunkin-My-Tits-Hynes.com.
Really?
question that you are
talented at what you do,
Well, look, there's no
but this is  GQ.
New York's
so crowded.
Look around.
I'm from LA, okay?
I like my open spaces.
What are you,
a gazelle?
Come on, what's really
worrying you about this?
took something legendary
I don't know. I don't
want to be the guy who
and shit the bed
with it. Excuse
the expression.
Well, then don't be
the guy who shit the
bed. Excuse the expression.
Be the guy who made
the bed legendary again.
Listen, we'll get some
coffee in you before the
interview. You'll be fine.
Some green tea, soy,
organic hemp bullshit.
I'm sorry, not coffee.
DYLAN: Really hot
in New York.
Doesn't it get hot in LA?
Yeah, it gets hot in LA,
but it's the humidity.
In LA, if it's
90 degrees, it feels
like 90 degrees. But...
Right.
If it's hot
in New York,
it's 90 degrees, it's
like 100,000 degrees.
about weather is
really fascinating,
This conversation
but lucky for me,
we are here.
So, good luck.
Whatever happens,
happens. I told you,
I don't really want it.
Act like you do so
that I look good.
Just do me a favor?
I... I can do that.
Okay. Go get 'em.
This is great,
by the way.
(GAGGING)
(GARGLES AND SPITS)
Watch it!
Ugh!
Hey!
You're still here?
Uh, yeah. Well,
it's my job.
Nice.
So, tell me,
how'd it go?
You're safe for a
little while longer.
They bought it.
Well, thank you.
I owe you one.
(CELL PHONE BEEPING)
Uh, this is from you.
It's your offer.
They called about
five minutes ago.
Wait, I... I  got it?
Congratulations. Offer
expires at midnight.
Why didn't you just
tell me instead of
texting me?
'Cause it's
more dramatic.
Dylan, you are not
gonna shit the bed.
I've seen your work.
It's amazing.
It's a huge move.
Would you uproot your
entire life for a job?
Be honest.
Well, no. For a job,
probably not.
But for New York?
Yeah, I would.
Which is why I'm
not gonna try to
sell you on the job,
I'm gonna sell
you on New York.
It's New York!
I've seen  Seinfeld.
Not the bullshit
tourist version.
Puppy dog eyes.
Nice touch.
Yes! Come on.
Let me buy
you a drink.
What's wrong?
What... What are you
waiting for?
The light to change.
You LA folk
are so cute.
Come on.
Come on,
it's fine.
See?
Yep.
I'm gonna die.
Here we have
Brooklyn Bridge,
downtown Manhattan,
and right in front of us,
an outdoor bar.
Aha!
Alcohol. Now
we're talking.
You know,
I like you.
I'll give you your
choice of closes.
How I close you
on this job.
What?
Okay.
So we got the
flattery close.
Dylan, you are
so good at what
you do.
The take-it-or-
leave-it close.
if you take it.
I get paid regardless.
Man, I don't care
The sympathy close.
(LAUGHS)
You see, my
kidneys are failing...
Why do women think
the only way to get
a man to do what they want
is to manipulate him?
History. Personal
experience.
Romantic comedies.
Come on, you're here for
a reason, whether you
want to admit it or not.
want to know their options?
Yeah, to explore an
option. Who wouldn't
Someone who's in
the perfect situation.
Are you in the
perfect situation?
Job? Absolutely.
Everything else?
None of your business.
(CHUCKLES)
Shaun!
Jamie!
Hey!
up, baby?
What are you doing here?
Hey, what's
You look great.
(MOUTHING)
Shaun White?
You been, uh, working out?
Nope. Just been
eating a lot.
Ah, okay.
Yeah.
Do you want a drink?
Yeah!
Let me get you
a drink. Yeah?
Okay.
Careful! Careful.
Sorry.
Hey, bro, that
was like a double
McTwist 1260.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Yeah, like the trick.
Yeah, yeah,
yeah. Dylan.
Jamie, you want
to get this guy
out of my face
before I break his
fucking skull?
Sorry, bro.
No disrespect.
I'm a huge fan.
You don't fucking know
me, man! Don't talk to
me like you know me!
What, you think I'm
all chill 'cause
I snowboard and shit?
One more word,
I'll fuck you up
like dynamite!
Dynamite?
Aw, I'm just
playing, bro.
Any friend of Jamie's
is cool with me.
It's all
good, man.
All good.
I'm whispering in
the ear of a dead man.
I'll see
you later.
Good to see you.
Bye, honey.
Shaun White
seems really great.
Nice dude.
know him again?
I took his virginity.
How do you
Oh, so you guys have
known each other
for a while?
No, it was like
eight months ago.
Wow.
So does the carpet
match the drapes?
floors, if you
know what I mean.
Uh, it's hardwood
My God!
Terrible visual.
Totally kidding,
by the way. Just
an old friend of mine.
conditioner.
You guys use the
same leave-in
His hair had
nice body.
Can I get two
gyro number sixes,
extra sauce?
looking for?
The cops.
What are you
Come on.
The cops?
Yep.
Come on!
Where are you
taking me?
You'll see.
Well, here's
your open space.
Run, gazelle. Run!
(CHUCKLES)
Wow. This is
unbelievable.
I know.
Okay, this was
not on  Seinfeld.
Come on, what's your
dad think about all this?
About what?
Well, he must
have an opinion.
He used to write
for the  LA Times
for 23 years.
Somebody did
their homework.
I have this thing
at work. It's
called, uh,
Google.
Come on, what's he
think about the job?
Actually, I
didn't ask him.
Well, then you must
know what he'd say.
Uh, he'd tell me
to go with my gut
and that he'd be proud of me
no matter what I did.
Sounds like a
really great man.
Yeah, he is.
Hey, do you want to
see something really cool?
I always want to see
something really cool.
What...
Come on.
Okay.
Only place in the
city you can actually
see the stars.
Wow.
Yeah.
It's pretty
awesome.
I know.
I like to come
up here to think.
Just when it gets a
little too much for me
down there, it's like...
It's like my
New York version
of a mountaintop.
Best part,
no cell reception.
(LAUGHING)
You take all
your recruits
up here?
Actually, never
really taken
anyone up here.
Really?
Yeah.
Thanks.
If you tell anyone
about this, I will
rip your ears off
and staple them
to your neck.
city seems really
violent.
Everyone in this
(CHUCKLES)
Ooh, come on, let's go.
One last stop.
We're just
getting comfortable.
I know you are. Come on.
It's New York.
Now hustle.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
Oh, you're showing me
Times Square.
This is not
touristy at all!
Oh, would you shush? Come on.
to power-walk
everywhere we go?
Do we have
Yes.
So everybody just
kind of walks wherever
they want, then.
How 'bout right here?
What do you mean?
We're here.
Oh, my God,
it's 1988.
All right, smartass,
give it five seconds.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(LAUGHING)
What is this?
It's a flash mob.
Like on  Oprah!
Exactly.
Should we get
out of the way?
No, no. Enjoy it.
Take it all in.
It's pretty
damn cool.
Right?
(CHUCKLING)
It's kind of rad.
Do these people
get paid for this?
No. No. They kind of
just do it for fun.
It's nice to feel
like you're a part
of something.
New York can be
a little bit
lonely at times.
And you're trying
to sell me on it.
Every place can
be a bit lonely
sometimes.
Oh, be careful!
Oh, my God.
Come down.
Okay.
Shit. Get
back down.
Okay.
I'm in.
What?
You sold me.
Really?
I'll take the job.
Oh, my God!
What, are you surprised?
No! No. Oh, you
are gonna crush it!
Amazing.
You can all go home
now! Thank you!
Very funny.
Come on.
ALL: Congratulations,
sell-out!
Thank you,
thank you.
All I'm saying is,
it wasn't so much
the pilot's skill
that landed that plane
on the river as much as
the mechanics of the aircraft.
Are you saying
that Captain Sully
wasn't a hero?
No, no.
Uh, there were just
other factors.
Are you not
an American?
Hey, fuckface, you want
to get your shit out
of my car or what?
I... Yeah.
Welcome to New York.
Go and fuck a dick.
(GRUNTS)
Fuck.
So, all I ask is that you
give me a little bit of
time to gain your trust.
I know that I'm new at this,
but what I lack in experience
I make up for in cliches.
So, my door is always open.
(CROWD LAUGHING)
But seriously,
my door is
always open.
My first order
of business,
lighter doors.
Okay.
Thanks, guys.
Welcome, Dylan.
Hey, man.
Tommy Bollinger,
sports editor.
Tommy, I've read
your articles.
Love your writing.
Just trying to
keep it realsies.
Listen, I'd love to
take you out one night
and troll for cock.
What?
You got some pretty
boys out there in LA,
in this town
is ri-dick-ulous.
but the quality
We can tear
this shit up.
I'm not gay,
Tommy.
Really? Oh, I just assumed,
art director and,
you know...
Hey. No skin,
more pipe for me.
By the way,
doing a piece on
racism in hockey.
I'd love to get your
concepts on the font.
but I could be persuaded
to Courier New.
I'm thinking Helvetica,
But what the fuck
do I know? I'm just
the sports editor.
You sure
you're not gay?
Yep.
I'm sure.
Okay.
All right.
Hey.
I'd knock, but you
don't have a door.
I don't.
No.
Hey, check this out.
SINGER:
♪ Dunkin-My-Tits-Hynes.com ♪
Yeah, it really does exist.
I told you, but
not that. This.
Awesome.
more awesome if
this happened.
But it'd be even
Wait for it.
Nice!
I got in touch with
a guy who puts flash
mobs together.
We're thinking about
using them for
guerrilla advertising.
Taking something
so pure and
commercializing it?
Knew I found
the right guy.
Here I am.
Okay. Here's
your contract.
Sign it and I will
be out of here.
(SIGHS) Okay.
A whole year? Oof!
Why do I get the feeling
this is the first real
commitment you've ever made?
T-Mobile,
two years.
It's not.
And, fuck, do I
regret that one.
Do me a favor.
Don't quit or get fired
before the year's up,
because otherwise
I don't get my bonus.
Wait, I can leave
whenever I want?
What's the point
of this contract?
Just sign the damn thing.
Okay.
Nice doing business
with you, Dylan Harper.
Hey, I was thinking of
getting some lunch.
Do you know a place?
Are you asking me out?
Whoa, I'm not
asking you out.
I'm asking you to
show me a restaurant.
I mean, I'm the only friend
you have in New York. You
don't wanna complicate that.
I know. I'm not
asking you out.
I mean, sure,
we'd have fun,
roll around,
get into some erotic
humiliation fantasy.
Erotic?
faces, end badly, and we'd
never speak to each other...
But it'd all blow up in our
I'm not fucking
asking you out!
I swear to God!
Okay. You don't
like me like that.
You don't have to
be so mean about it.
I'm sorry.
I didn't...
God, you're such
a girl. Come on,
it's my treat.
So was it an easy move?
It was tough
leaving my dad.
Yeah.
My sister gave
me some shit.
But, uh, timing
was right.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Timing was really right.
Is that your sister?
No. My ex.
She's great.
Loves John Mayer.
Oh. (GAGS)
Wants us to
stay friends.
(GAGGING)
can cure me of my
emotional unavailability.
She's also convinced she
unavailable?
Oh, yeah.
You're emotionally
Oh, my God. I'm emotionally
damaged. I haven't seen
you at the meetings.
I'm done with the
relationship thing.
Girl, you are preaching
to the congregation.
Choir.
What?
"Preaching to the choir."
You're supposed to
preach to the congregation.
That's the expression.
Did you understand
what I was saying?
Then don't be
a dick about it.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Oh, my God.
Do you mind?
Please.
Great.
Hello. You've reached
Dylan Harper's cell phone.
He's emotionally
unavailable, but
if you'd like...
John fucking Mayer!
Hello?
really do have
shitty cell service.
Wow. Hello? You
Uh-huh. Right?
Yeah.
I'm gonna have some
friends over tomorrow.
Why don't you come,
and you can meet
some new people?
I'm gonna have to
check my schedule.
I'm really busy.
I work at  GQ now.
It's not some little
blog on the Internet.
(LAUGHS)
(KNOCKING)
Hey.
You made it.
Sorry I'm late.
No, no. Please, come in,
come in. Thank you.
Hey, everybody! Hey!
This here is Dylan.
He's from LA.
(EVERYONE BOOING)
He's the reason I can
afford all this beer.
(EVERYONE CHEERING)
Okay, all right.
Am I an animal?
Yeah.
Fuck, I'm pretty
good at this.
Lieutenant Kali's a West
Coast street artist I got
into about five years ago.
His postmodern
interpretation...
This shit is amazing.
I know, right?
Ooh!
You will be able to find the
perfect candidate to fill the
position at your company.
Okay, here we go.
First up is Joey Morena,
who's fluent in Vietnamese
and has had 10 years
of experience in
the culinary field.
I can't do
this anymore.
No, I think we
both need to
go get happy.
It's not adding up to
100 anymore.
Yeah.
Looks like New York's
all out of blueberries.
Goodbye, Flapjack.
(MELANCHOLY MUSIC PLAYING)
Taxi! Taxicab!
Flapjack.
DYLAN: Why do all
these movies have
such bad music?
know how to feel
every single second.
It's so that you
"I'm heartbroken."
(DYLAN HUMS SAD MUSIC)
"I'm getting married
to the man of my dreams."
(SCATTING HAPPILY)
"I'm sneaking
through an office."
(SUSPENSEFUL SCATTING)
Madison, wait!
Madison!
Bryce.
I was at Grand
Central Station?
How did you know
You're not. You're
in Los Angeles, where
this movie was shot.
I know you better than
you know yourself.
And your crazy
friend Susie across
the hall told me.
Susie.
Why are you here?
To tell you that
I love that sunsets
make you cry,
and I don't care that
you failed your real
estate exam,
and I'm glad that you
have a five-date rule.
(LAUGHS)
And that I love you.
Not as much as
I love you.
ANNOUNCER: (ON PA)
Now boarding, track 5, love.
God, I wish my
life was a movie
sometimes.
You know, I'd
never have to worry
about my hair,
or having to go
to the bathroom.
And then, when I'm
at my lowest point,
some guy would chase
me down the street,
pour his heart out,
and we'd kiss.
Happily ever after.
I mean, a horse
and carriage?
Come on, that
is awesome.
Not as awesome as
this ambiguously
upbeat pop song
that has nothing
to do with the plot
the end to try
to convince you
they put in at
this shitty movie.
that you had a
great time at
You know, why don't they ever
make a movie about what
happens after the big kiss?
They do. It's
called porn.
God, I miss sex.
Right? I mean,
sometimes you just
need it. It's like...
I don't know, it's like
cracking your neck.
gotta come with
complications?
Why does it always
And emotions.
And guilt.
Guilt.
It's women's fault.
What?
You heard me. "Hold me.
Let's spend the rest
of our lives together."
Oh, please, you
are no better.
"Oh, yeah, baby,
come on, now. Say
my name. Yeah...
(GRUNTS)
"I'm done.
How was I?"
Who have you
been with?
Why can't it not
be like that?
It's a physical act.
Like playing tennis.
they're playing tennis.
Two people should be
able to have sex like
Yeah, I mean,
no one wants to go
away for the weekend
after they
play tennis.
You shake hands,
get on with your shit.
It's just a game.
Yeah.
Mmm.
Do you want
more beer?
Mmm-hmm.
Okay.
Jamie!
Yeah?
Let's play tennis.
What?
Let's have sex like
we're playing tennis.
Get the hell
out of here.
Don't laugh. This
could be great.
This could take
all the weirdness
out of it.
Well, we talked
about this. I don't
like you like that.
I don't like you like
that either. That's
why it's perfect.
(CHUCKLES) I don't even
know if I find
you attractive.
That's cute.
Well, I do have
a thing for jerks.
Okay, well, do you
even find me attractive?
That's cute.
No, no, no.
Before you got
to know my
awesome personality.
Strictly physical.
First time
you saw me.
people talking?
Yeah.
This is just two
Two girls over drinks
at Bennigan's. Go.
I liked your eyes. I didn't
think I'd ever seen such
big, beautiful eyes.
Your lips. Yeah.
I thought you might
be a good kisser.
I am.
Your breasts.
What about them?
They intrigued me.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, I think
they're so tiny.
They're still
breasts.
Thanks.
I liked your hands.
Mouth.
Butt.
Voice.
Chest.
Eyes.
You said that.
I meant it.
You swear you don't
want anything more
from me other than sex?
You swear you
don't want anything
more from me?
I know how you
girls get. Tick-tock,
tick-tock.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
I'm pulling up
my Bible app.
You have a
Bible app?
Yes. I am a good girl.
Hand on the iPad.
Okay.
(HEAVENLY MUSIC PLAYING)
Wait, no.
Why can't they
figure this out?
No... This thing
thinks I'm you
and you're me.
Keep your hand still.
I'll move the iPad.
It's actually
making me dizzy.
Hold on.
(MUSIC CUTTING IN AND OUT)
There we go.
No relationship.
No emotions.
Just sex.
Whatever happens,
we stay friends.
Swear.
BOTH: Swear.
Okay.
So I guess we
should just start.
Okay.
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
I'll serve.
That's really...
That's enough
of the tennis.
Let's go to
the bedroom.
the couch? It's
less emotional.
What's wrong with
The bedroom
has better light.
And since we're just
friends, I don't have to be
insecure about my body.
Come on, okay?
You're beautiful.
You have nothing to
be insecure about.
No, you see,
that is way too
emotionally supportive
and you need to
just lock that down.
a little bony.
Much better.
Your ass is
My nipples are
sensitive, I don't
like dirty talk,
and had I known this was gonna
happen, I would have shaved
my legs this morning.
My chin is ticklish,
I sneeze sometimes
after I come,
and if I'd have known
this was gonna happen,
I wouldn't have shaved
my legs this morning.
Okie-dokie.
Oh!
socks on.
Intimacy issues.
I keep my
Great, 'cause feet
gross me out.
Daddy issues.
Great.
I can work
with that.
Should be fine.
I can't believe
I'm doing this.
Should we stop?
We could just
go for a run.
Are we getting
too old for this?
I don't know.
Sex?
No, casual sex.
It just... I don't know.
Feels a little collegey.
Oh. I could sing some
Third Eye Blind.
Okay.
♪ Closing time,
One last call for alcohol...
That's not Third Eye Blind.
I'm pretty sure that's
Third Eye Blind.
Nope.
whiskey or beer,
I know... ♪
♪ Finish your
What's wrong?
We're just doing
this once.
I totally agree.
Okay.
Great.
Little faster.
More circular.
(CHUCKLES) Watch my chin.
Touch my ears.
Okay.
Oh! Kiss my neck.
Say my name.
Dylan Francis
Harper Jr.
Not my full name.
Sorry, I had to
fill out a lot of
your paperwork.
Stop talking.
Okay.
Oh, my God,
you're really... Oh.
Oh. (LAUGHING)
A, B, C, D, E,
F, G, H, I, J, K,
L, M, N, O, P...
Uh, Dylan, I...
Relax.
Just a friend
going down on
another friend.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Tornado.
(FLAPPING TONGUE)
Ow, ow! What, what?
What are you trying
to do? Dig your
way to China?
I'm good at this.
Says who?
Every girl
I've been with.
Well, they're either
lying or their vaginas
are made out of burlap.
So, relax. You're
not a lizard.
Okay, fine.
♪ So gather up
your jackets... ♪
A little to the right.
Okay.
A little bit
more to the left.
Roger that.
Now go down.
Here we go.
A little more...
Whoa, too far!
Sorry.
(MOANING)
(SCREAMING)
What's wrong?
Nothing!
When women start
to scream, it could
be misconstrued.
Just keep going!
(SCREAMS)
Yeah, you know it.
Well, let me tell
you how I like it.
See, most girls
think you should
start off soft,
but if you just get
in, really go for it...
(MOANING)
(SNEEZING)
Yeah, you know it.
Mmm.
Ugh!
(BOTH SIGHING)
(SIGHS)
Let's go
with Obama.
No, no, no, no!
It's too easy,
too predictable.
Go with Shaun.
He's stylish,
transcendent of sport,
has an ass like a kumquat.
I hear he's
kind of a jerk.
No, he's not.
You're just
threatened
by him
greatest snow sport
athlete in the universe
because he's the
and he gets more
squirrel than
an oak tree.
Hey, Dylan?
Jamie Rellis is in
the lobby for you.
Okay, thanks.
Let's hit this
after lunch.
Okay, guys?
Nobody wants to
fuck Obama, brah.
He's got ears
like an elephant.
That's not the
part of an elephant
you want.
Hi!
Hi.
Sorry to just show
up like this.
No, no, no,
it's fine.
So...
Wanna take a walk?
Love to.
Great. Okay.
Okay, so about
what happened, I...
It was crazy and we
shouldn't have done it.
Exactly. No, no, exactly.
I mean, it is
so not me.
I totally agree.
Let's forget it
happened.
Great. I mean,
look, I've had
one-night stands.
We both have had one-night
stands, none of which
we're proud of, but...
Really?
Look, to think
that you and I
could just have sex
compromising anything
was just so...
and without it
Misguided.
Exactly.
I was gonna call
you this morning.
But you didn't.
But I didn't.
already coming between
us and I really...
And you see, it's
I just don't
want it to.
It's not going to.
Look, I know that I act
all tough and I talk all
tough, but really...
It's just a front to
protect yourself from
your own vulnerability.
What are you,
my fucking
therapist now?
No, I'm a friend. Who
knows that every time
you curse, you blink.
rejecting the word.
It does not.
Like your body's
Fuck you.
Blinked.
No, I didn't
fucking blink.
Blinked again.
Shit.
Ah, didn't blink.
okay with.
(LAUGHS)
"Shit" you're
It was stupid.
Yes.
We're friends,
let's stay friends.
Yes. Yes, this,
I don't wanna lose this.
Me neither.
Great.
Fantastic.
Portrait for the
lovely couple?
(MOANING)
What the hell
are we doing?
I don't know.
Rub my hair.
Kiss my neck.
(GIGGLING)
Watch my nipple.
All right, all right.
I didn't know you
had a tattoo.
Yeah.
Why didn't I
notice that before?
Because we
were drunk.
Was it your dog?
No. Never had one.
But everyone
else did.
And I thought having
a dog meant you had
a normal family,
I desperately
wanted.
which at 17
So as a sign of
rebellion you
got a tattoo
of the most
conventional thing
you could think of.
It was super
awesome back then.
Check it.
Okay.
A lightning bolt?
Eighteen.
Wanted superpowers.
Yeah.
I was a little into
Harry Potter back then.
Were you also gay back then?
Harry Potter doesn't
make you gay!
Okay.
Are you sure
about this?
Are you?
No.
Me neither.
How was your day?
It was okay.
I had a turkey
sandwich for lunch.
How was that?
It wasn't that good.
How was your day?
Still trying to figure
out that subway system.
It is tricky.
(CHEERING)
And it's
out of here!
My butt.
What?
Oh, my butt.
Really?
No, I mean my butt,
it's cramping. Can
you grab a pillow?
Okay, yeah, yeah.
So, no butt?
No.
(SNEEZING)
Really? Already?
Just kidding.
Do you like this position?
Yeah, it's all right.
I gotta be honest,
I feel a little
emasculated.
A naked girl is lying
on top of you and you
feel emasculated?
Little bit.
You do know what that
word means, right?
Yes, I know
what it means,
and I feel it.
all right,
you big baby.
Okay,
Chinese fire drill.
Okay. Go!
(GRUNTING AND GROANING)
Okay.
(BOTH SIGH)
Do you feel
manly now?
I do.
Okay. Put it in.
That's not funny.
(LAUGHING)
It's kind
of funny.
It's kind of funny.
Hold on.
What's wrong?
I have to
go to the
bathroom.
What? Now?
Yes, now. I had
a lot of watermelon.
What's going on in there?
Do you know how
hard it is to pee
with a hard-on?
No, actually.
It's like two lanes
of traffic merging into
one. It takes time.
Hmm.
Are you pooping?
No.
Why are you
sitting down?
It's easier to control.
You want a mess in here?
No. No, no. Sorry.
(SPUTTERING DRIBBLES)
(LOUD GUSHING NOISES)
Oh!
Yeah.
Yup.
What? Did I leak?
Did you wash
your hands?
Oh, come on, dude.
I know we're just
friends, but I'm
still a lady.
Now get back in there,
wash your hands and then
bring that fine ass back here.
If you keep talking
to me like that, I'm
not gonna come back.
(GROANING)
My hammies are killing me.
Have a banana,
they're in the fridge.
Why would you keep
bananas in the fridge?
It dries them out.
It doesn't.
They have a peel.
It's not armor.
Air still gets in.
Do you want a
banana or not?
Not if they're dry.
I'm not an animal.
At least I
have food
in the house.
All you have
at home is
drinkable yogurt.
I like to drink
my yogurt. It's
a timesaver.
Well, then you think
you could use that time
to shave your stubble.
Your whiskers
are like knives.
Now, see, if you were my
girlfriend, I couldn't tell
you to shut up right now.
And because you're
just my buddy,
I can tell you
that if you don't start
shaving up here, I'm
gonna stop shaving down there.
Hey, hey. Hey... Whoa!
Mom!
"Mom"?
Whoa, whoa.
I don't know what
you're doing.
My eyes are covered.
I can't see you
putting on your
black underpants.
Jamie, baby,
I missed you.
Oh, baby.
Did your boobs
get bigger?
Mom, I'm over here.
Oh, hey, baby.
Oh, no, they didn't.
What are you doing here?
Oh. Victor turned out to
be a total Lombard.
L-O-M-B-A-R-D.
"Lots Of Money
But A Real Dullard."
Victor, her fiance.
Ex-fiance.
What happened?
Nothing. He
was just blah.
I mean, nice, but
it was like
talking to dirt.
I woke up one day
and I said,
"Lorna..." I'm Lorna.
Dylan.
I said, "Lorna, this
is not your bliss.
"Just because
you're 39..."
Forty-eight.
have to settle. He's
not an insurance claim."
"...it doesn't mean you
So I caught the first
plane off the island.
Cleveland's
not an island.
Oh, baby, it is.
Anyway, here
I am. It's so
good to see you.
You never told
me you had a
hot boyfriend.
He's not my
boyfriend, Mom.
We're just friends.
Oh, I love it.
That's right.
Ooh. It's like the
'70s in here.
Ooh! That was a better
time. Just sex.
A little grass,
a little glue...
Not during pregnancy.
(WHISPERING)
Well, not during
the final trimester.
But no
complications.
It's great!
Okay, well, that's
technically, I guess,
what this is.
That's exactly
So my daughter
is just your
slampiece?
No, no.
"Slampiece"?
I'm just kidding.
Slam away.
Have fun.
I think this
is great.
The only thing is,
it takes you off
the market.
The whole reason
you go to the market
But what the hell.
is to buy the
produce, which
you already got.
It's so good to see
you, baby. I'm only
gonna be here a few weeks.
I'm starving.
You got any gin?
It's in the
kitchen.
You gotta go.
Is she wearing
Axe body spray?
I don't know. Come on.
LORNA: Bananas in the
refrigerator? What
are you, Puerto Rican?
That is terrible, Mother.
Just joking. Your dad
was Puerto Rican.
What? You said
that he was Greek.
Potato, potato...
Get your shoes.
Okay. All right.
Well, not...
Just go, just go.
I'll just put
these on on
the bike?
Yeah.
Okay.
It was nice to
have met you...
LORNA: Hey.
And your pants
are coming off.
Oh, my... Mom!
Mom, please!
Back, back!
That's what I'm
talking about!
We're kicking every
gay ass out here!
I don't say that
pejoratively,
I say it hopefully.
Hold it.
Any of you gay?
Not even you?
Come on, man.
Come talk to me after.
Give me five minutes
of your time.
I might be able to let
you see some reason.
(MEN WHOOPING AND HOOTING)
(CHEERING)
Look at you
in the house!
Come on, baby!
I'm supposed
to meet up
with Jamie.
Who's that,
that headhunter?
Uh-huh.
What, you guys
going out now?
No, no, no, we're just
friends. We're messing
around a little bit.
What do you mean?
Sleeping together.
But it's just sex.
That never works, bro.
She's a girl. Sex always
means more to them even
if they don't admit it.
Jamie's different.
Does she have a
penis where most
girls have a vagina?
No penis.
Then she's
no different.
What do you
know about
women, anyway?
Dude, I've turned
down more tail than
you'll ever have.
Yeah, bro.
You're gay.
But the offers still
keep rolling in,
naturally. Look at me.
And, hey, I love
women. They're
beautiful, majestic,
mysterious,
mesmerizing
creatures.
Smart, empathetic.
Far superior to men
in every way.
And if I had a choice,
I would be with women
to my dying day.
But me likes cock
so I'm strict-aly
dick-aly.
So it's always just
about sex, then?
No. I've been in
love. I went down
that rabbit hole.
You know what
I discovered?
Friday night with,
It's not who you
want to spend
it's who you want
to spend all day
Saturday with.
Feel me, Felix?
every Saturday for
the rest of your life.
Yeah, but then it's
It's okay, you
don't get it.
It's no big deal.
But you will.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
One day, you'll meet
someone and it'll literally
take your breath away.
breathe. Like no
oxygen to the lungs.
Like you can't
Like a fish...
Yeah, I get it, Tommy.
Yeah, you don't.
Nice work on that
new online site,
by the way.
What was the font
on that headline?
It was Times Roman.
Times Roman.
Inspired.
I'm out.
You have a boat?
I live in Jersey.
And I ain't
taking no ferry.
Unless it's out to
dinner and a show.
Bam!
Hey.
Yeah.
You and that Dylan? Way to go.
I mean the whole
friendship-sex thing.
Kudos, baby, kudos.
(LAUGHS)
It's not that big
of a deal.
It's just surprising.
you were a true-love
kind of girl.
I always thought
Uh, whatever, Mom.
It's not like it's stopping
me from anything.
That's what I thought
back in '78.
And every year since.
I'm just...
I'm flattered, actually.
The apple doesn't
fall far from the tree.
It's just surprising.
There, done. It's...
There we go.
Okay.
Oh, you look great!
You look great.
You look like a princess.
Yeah!
Really?
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey, my friend gave
me his house in Montauk
for July 4th.
Let's you and me
go away together.
No men, no bullshit.
Just mother-daughter.
Like a Nora Ephron movie.
(SCOFFS)
When was the last time
we spent a full weekend
together?
in Vermont. We got snowed in
with the ski instructor.
When I was eight, that time
Demitri.
Bill.
He reminded me a lot
of your father.
Dark curls, olive skin,
Cold War accent.
My father was Russian?
I don't remember.
But what I do remember
is we drank a lot of vodka
and shot a lot of guns.
Mom, this "who's your daddy"
game is getting really old.
I know I haven't been
the best mother
in the world...
I'm sorry,
were you waiting
for me to jump in?
Come on!
Go away with me.
Come on. Come on.
(LAUGHING)
Okay, we'll do it.
It'll be fun, yeah?
(SIGHS)
(GASPS)
Mom...
I was trying to bond!
or sniff glue.
(LAUGHS)
It was either this
Sorry about my mom.
I thought she was funny.
Yeah, she's really funny
when she's asking for money,
and she's hilarious
when she needs
a place to stay.
Dylan, I think I wanna
start dating again.
Listen, I think
we should stop this.
Hmm.
Yeah?
I kind of think
you're right.
Right?
♪ Every new beginning
comes from some other
beginning's end ♪
That actually makes sense
right here.
Who would've thought
Third Eye Blind
could be so prophetic?
Not Third Eye Blind.
I'm pretty sure
that's Third Eye Blind.
Do you wanna go
grab some lunch?
Yes.
Okay.
You're buying.
What?
Okay.
Oh.
Pants.
Shirt.
So this is
the end of this?
I guess so.
But it's good.
Yeah.
And we did it.
With no bullshit.
Shirt.
Sweater.
We managed to actually
stay friends.
Yup.
Yeah.
Okay. So, what is
your type, anyway?
No, I don't have
a type.
It's more about
what's inside.
Oh, please!
Okay, what about her?
DYLAN: Uh, yeah. I could get
to know her inside.
And she's reading a book.
It's probably Nicholas Sparks.
I'm gonna go
talk to her.
What?
What do you mean, "What?"
We said we wanted
to date again.
I'm gonna go
talk to her.
Now?
Here, in front of
all of these people?
I didn't say I was gonna
rape her. I said I was
gonna go talk to her.
Excuse me. I'm Dylan.
Nice to meet you.
Oh,  The Notebook.
(INAUDIBLE)
DYLAN:
Nice meeting you.
Well?
We talked.
We laughed.
Yeah.
She's Belgian.
Explains the reading.
I showed her
where the balcony was,
because that's where
she is meeting up
with her husband.
Oh!
(LAUGHING)
DYLAN: Anniversary trip
to New York.
Three kids.
Christof, Karlina
and Pepijn.
Shut up.
Why are you still laughing?
At least I gave it a shot.
Fine. I'll go next.
See if I still have game.
Okay.
Oh, okay.
Yes.
Right here.
Eleven o'clock.
Iced coffee.
Handsome,
but doesn't know it.
Staring at a tree,
which means he's actually
in the park for nature
and not to watch
women sunbathe.
Or he's retarded.
Don't care.
I'm going in.
(SCATTING)
Excuse me.
Yes?
Hi.
Hello.
I'm Jamie.
Yeah. Yeah,
that works.
Oh, hi.
Okay.
Nice to meet you.
(MOUTHING) Oh, my God!
(SCATTING)
Okay. His name is Parker.
He's a children's oncologist.
(SCATTING)
And I have a date
this Saturday.
(SCATTING A FANFARE)
Nice.
Thank you.
Why'd you wave to me?
I told him you were
my gay best friend,
so he wants to set you up
with his brother.
(SCATTING MOCKINGLY)
PARKER: College, med school,
and I haven't slept since.
JAMIE: I can't believe
you actually cure cancer.
Well, me and God.
What?
I'm kidding.
Can you imagine someone
who would actually say that?
(EXHALING DEEPLY)
Yeah, I could.
I've been out with
a lot of them.
Cancer doctors?
No, assholes.
Yeah.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, hopefully you're
all done with that.
Although, I gotta warn you,
lot of cancer doctors,
big assholes.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, and, uh, brain surgeons,
huge perverts.
While they're doing this,
a little bit of that.
Hey.
(JAMIE LAUGHING)
Thank you.
When can I see you again?
Right now.
Ah.
I'm just kidding.
Okay.
Can you imagine someone
who would actually say that?
JAMIE: I played the tuba
in high school.
World's stupidest instrument.
Especially when you move
eight times.
Why'd you move?
My mom really likes
to break up with guys,
and she was really good at it.
Was your dad one of them?
No, no, he was
long before that.
I actually never knew my dad.
I'm sorry. That sucks.
All right, look,
I think I should probably
tell you something.
Please don't tell me
you're a dude.
Because that'll be like
the third time
since I moved here,
and I don't think
I can handle that.
I have a five-date rule.
You know, like,
five dates before we...
Yeah.
I saw it in a movie.
I thought I'd give it a try.
You're worth waiting for.
I'm sure that was the line
in the movie you saw.
(LAUGHING)
PARKER: That's awesome.
This four-year-old that
I've been working on
for the last couple months,
he's gonna be fine.
That's great.
Yeah.
How is a guy
like you single?
I've just been waiting
for someone to come up
to me in the park
and compliment me
for looking at the trees
and not the sunbathers.
I meant it.
It was impressive.
Actually, if I'm gonna be
completely honest with you,
I was sleeping standing up.
I worked 36 hours straight.
I don't even know
how I got to the park.
How is a girl
like you single?
(CHUCKLES)
Oh...
I have issues.
One might even
call me damaged.
Actually, one did
Get out of here.
Damaged how?
I kind of believe
in true love.
That there might be
a Prince Charming
out there for me.
(CELL PHONE BEEPING)
Oh.
Listen, I know this is
probably a no because all you
do is work like a dull boy,
but if would you like
to come get a beer?
Ah, I'm good.
No, it's not a gay bar.
And there'll be
just as many hot girls
as hot guys.
(PHONE BEEPING)
You know what?
I will come out.
All right.
Let's find you a lady.
(SCOFFS)
You're still
not gay, right?
Nope.
Okay.
What?
Do you know what today is?
Date number five.
I wasn't even counting.
Wanna go in the bedroom?
No. Here's fine.
(SNARLING)
I am so glad
I met you tonight.
(MOANING)
Me, too.
(CONTINUES SNARLING)
What are you thinking?
Just how great you are.
(MOANS)
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
(SNIFFING)
Annie, hey.
Who the fuck is Annie?
My sister.
Better be. I'll cut her.
Of course I'm coming.
Yeah, I'm taking the 4th off,
so I'll be there
for three days.
(SNIFFING)
(BLOWING)
Yeah. How's Dad?
Any worse?
All right,
tell him I said hi.
Bye, Banannie.
I want you to meet
my parents.
No, you... Really?
(MOANING)
God!
(CLOSING TIME
RINGTONE PLAYING)
♪ I know who I want
to take me home
to take me home ♪
Hey. Hold on, hold on.
No, just hold on.
Just give me a second.
I gotta go find
a place to talk. Okay.
(LORNA GRUNTING)
Shit. Shit.
Just hold on.
Oh, sorry.
Hold on.
I was out pretty late
last night.
When I got in,
you and your girlfriend
were on the couch
so I just crashed in your bed.
He's not a girl.
He smells like a girl.
You smelled him?
I wanna buy marshmallows.
What did you say?
For Montauk this weekend.
I wanna do a campfire,
like when you were little.
Okay.
And then we're gonna
look for sticks.
I hear you. Sticks.
And then we're gonna sing.
We're gonna...
(SNORING SOFTLY)
Just hold on a second.
Okay.
What's up?
Do you think guys care more
about global warming
or how to wear white pants
to a cookout?
JAMIE:  Well, that depends.
Do you have a hot model
in a bikini standing
on an icecap?
No. Ski slope.
I'd still go with pants
to a cookout.
Yeah, me, too.
How's your boy Parker?
Still staring at trees?
Yeah, he's still
looking up at trees,
Two coffees.
but, um, this time it's
actually in my apartment.
It's the fifth date already?
Maybe. Thank you.
Did you guys "fifth-date"?
How dare you!
A lady never tells.
I know.
That's why I'm asking you.
(LAUGHS)
Hey. I gotta go.
You have a great trip in LA
and call me when you land.
Okay.
JAMIE: Parker.
Hey.
Um...
I got us coffees.
Nonfat, one sugar,
one Splenda.
I gotta get going.
Oh, what?
I thought you weren't
on call today.
I'm not,
but I got that thing...
I got stuff.
This...
They just called me.
Really?
Yeah.
The sneak-out.
How incredibly cliche of you.
I just...
I don't think I can be
your Prince Charming.
God, you totally didn't get
anything that I was saying,
did you?
No, no, no.
I think you're great.
Yeah, you, too.
Hey, you know what?
You and I should stay friends.
Really?
No, go fuck yourself.
DYLAN:
Who sleeps standing up?
You know,
you'd be really proud of me.
I didn't even blink
when I told him
to go fuck himself.
You did just then, though.
This does not count.
I'm not in the moment.
I don't know,
maybe I suck in bed.
Trust me,
you don't suck in bed.
Thank you.
So needy.
Hey, maybe the guy's
married or something.
No, did a background check
at work.
Single, no criminal history,
credit report 720.
Background check.
Did you do one on me?
How could you possibly
max out an Old Navy card?
After college I was
really into cargo pants.
Dylan, I gotta stop thinking
it's not me.
I mean, it's gotta be me.
It's not you.
Nothing is wrong with you.
He's a guy.
You gave him
a five-date challenge,
he got you and cut out.
Forget the douche.
He's a dick.
He's a dick-douche.
Go have fun with your mom.
Okay.
Oh. Almost forgot.
I got you something.
It's Lieutenant Kali,
the street artist
we talked about.
I got him to do something
for you. "F-tale." Fairy tale.
I know you're into
that girly shit, so...
This is so cool.
Dylan,
that's actually really sweet.
It's cool, right?
Yeah. Thank you.
Hey, I'm gonna need
to borrow cab fare.
I'm not taking that thing
on the subway.
I don't wanna get rolled.
No problem.
As long as you get
your feet off my bed.
They're disgusting.
What are you doing?
Why are you doing that?
You're an animal.
Stop doing that.
An animal. Stop.
Hey, Ma.
Ma. Come on,
we gotta get on the road.
Come on.
Ma?
Ouch.
Why did I think that
this time would be
any different?
Come with me to LA.
What?
It's 4th of July,
everybody's left the city.
What else are you gonna do?
You're very sweet for asking,
but it's fine.
You know what,
I'll just stay here.
I'll be fine alone.
You're not a baby
in a hot car.
I know you'll be fine alone.
you to come
because it would help me.
I'm actually asking
You'd be a great distraction
for my family.
They'd forget all about
drilling me for being single.
Won't they think
that we're together?
Not if I tell them we're not.
And they'll believe you?
Yeah, we're one of these
crazy families that doesn't
lie to each other.
PBS is doing
a documentary on us.
Come on, they'll love you.
home a carny.
All fast-talking and brusque,
like I'm bringing
You're really nice to ask,
but I'm just gonna stay here.
Go to the gym.
I just got you a ticket
with my miles, it's done.
Meet me at JFK.
But...
No buts.
Like you were
gonna go to the gym.
I wasn't.
LA's so nice.
And everyone's so genuine
and level-headed.
Hmm.
(LAUGHING)
Thanks for this.
You're good peeps.
You're the good peeps,
dude.
You haven't met my family.
You don't know
what you're in for.
Okay.
(SIGHING)
You know these planes
pretty much land themselves?
Nobody cares.
You sound like an asshole.
She's from New York.
I'm sorry.
Wow. This looks normal.
It is.
Thank you.
Wow, you grew up here?
It was my grandfather's.
He bought it
when there was
nothing else here.
My dad and my sister
and her son live here now.
What... (LAUGHS)
Why would you
move to New York?
by some headhunter.
(LAUGHS)
I was conned
You're here.
Sammy!
Hey, Uncle Dylan.
What's up, buddy?
(GRUNTS)
How are you?
Jamie, this is my nephew,
Sam the Magnificent.
Hello.
May I offer you a light
for your cigarette?
I'm sorry,
I don't smoke.
Just pretend.
He's a magician.
Of course I'll have
a cigarette.
Smoking is great for you.
(GASPS)
Wow. Thank you, good sir.
My pleasure, my lady.
Oh, my God.
I got it, I got it.
Sammy. I got it, I got it.
Just stay still.
I got it, I got it.
Sammy! Are you okay?
(ANNIE EXHALING DEEPLY)
All part of the illusion.
Jet Skis later?
Definitely.
DYLAN:
Still into magic, huh?
Yep. But I'll take
that over him sexting
his friends any day.
Dilbert!
Banannie.
(GRUNTING)
(LAUGHING)
Jamie,
this is my sister, Annie.
Hi.
Thank you for having me.
Oh, please.
It's nice to have
Dylan bring a girl home.
We're just friends.
Oh, no, I know.
If you were his girlfriend,
he never would've
brought you here.
This one has intimacy issues.
I know.
Dylan.
Dad.
Dylan. Oh, man.
Hey.
How you doing, buddy?
I'm good.
I miss you guys,
but I'm good.
Oh!
Dede Spencer?
Uh, Jamie. Dylan's friend.
Oh. I'm sorry. I...
That's okay.
No, for a minute you reminded
me of a girl I used to know.
No, that's okay.
It happens.
Nice to meet you.
Pleasure meeting you.
You have a beautiful house.
Thank you.
Pool's a little cold,
but it's very expensive
to heat, so...
I think I'm gonna go in
and check the tide tables
'cause I'm gonna take
the boat out early
in the morning.
You should come.
Oh, I would love to.
We sold the boat.
The doctor doesn't want you
driving the boat anymore.
(SIGHS)
Turning to mush.
No.
It's good to see you, buddy.
Nice to meet you.
It was nice meeting you, too.
Jamie. See?
Yes.
What's with the pants?
He doesn't like
them anymore.
He's getting worse.
It's so good
to have you here.
Go show her the beach.
Let me show you
the beach. Come on.
Okay.
Go, get sandy.
Get all messed up.
Okay.
JAMIE: Dylan never told
me about your dad.
Yeah, it's been tough on him.
They were real close.
Dylan doesn't quite know
how to deal with
the Alzheimer's.
I'm sorry.
He'll be his regular old self
and everything seems fine,
and then just in a flash,
he's gone.
That's Dylan when he was nine.
Are those braids?
He was going through
a Kris Kross phase.
Remember them?
♪ Kris Kross will make you
Jump! Jump! ♪
(LAUGHING)
Is that your mom?
No, that's Dylan's
speech therapist.
He had a stutter.
It got real bad
when he was nervous.
He had a rough childhood.
"character-building."
Math tutor?
His math tutor called it
No, we're talking, like,
eight times six equals 1,200.
But he's very visual,
thank God.
(LAUGHING)
Can you please explain
to me this photo?
That is my 12th-birthday
surprise party.
Hey.
Amazing moment.
I'm exhausted.
I'm gonna go to bed.
Jamie, you all good
with your room?
Yeah. No, it's perfect.
Thank you.
Thank you for everything.
(MOANING SOFTLY)
Sammy and I built
a saw-a-girl-in-half box,
so just be careful
on your way to bed.
He's not using a real saw,
is he?
Of course he is.
He's magnificent.
I'll make sure he brushes his
teeth, and you, don't believe
anything she says.
She's a liar.
(LAUGHING)
He's a pretty special guy.
Yeah, I think so.
(KNOCKING)
(WHISPERING)
Jamie. Hey.
(WHISPERING) Hey.
You up?
Yeah. Come in.
I thought you were
going to bed.
I was.
But then I realized
we were both
single again, so...
Oopsy.
(GASPS)
Dude, no.
Why not?
I washed my hands.
With soap this time.
Are you serious?
Why would you just assume?
You cracked your neck on the
porch. This thing.
That's your tell, remember?
I cracked my neck
because we were on
a flight for six hours,
and you were yapping my ear
off about how planes
all fly themselves,
and it actually kinked
my neck a bit.
So, no?
No. Not having sex with you.
They have an app for that.
No, wait.
Is it your special time?
Nope, you're good to go.
We talked about this.
Plus, I just got dumped, so...
Okay, I'm sorry.
I thought this would be
a good way to take
your mind off him.
No, I don't function that way.
Sex is not gonna help.
But you know what will?
Emotional support.
Before we were sex without
emotion, and now we're
emotion without sex.
Exactly.
I just need you
to be my friend right now.
Okay. So I'll listen to you
while you give me a hand job.
No.
I'm kidding. I got it.
Good night.
Wait, hold on! Friends can
still hang out and,
I don't know, listen to music.
Listen to music?
♪ Jump! Jump!
The Mac Dad will make you... ♪
I'm gonna kill Annie.
used to like them.
I didn't like these guys.
I can't believe you
I don't even remember...
♪ Don't try to compare us
to another bad little fad
♪ I'm the mac and I'm bad
give you something
that you never had
♪ I'll make ya jump, jump
Wiggle and shake your rump
♪ 'Cause I'll be kicking up
something that make you
wanna jump
♪ How high? Real high
'Cause I'm just so fly
And then there's something,
I don't know what
he says right there...
♪ Inside-out is wiggity
wiggity, wiggity wack ♪
Are you kidding me?
These dudes were da bomb.
Everybody had Girbauds,
we all wore 'em backwards.
The baseball jerseys.
(TURNS OFF MUSIC)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
I went as Kris Kross
three years in a row
for Halloween.
Oh, you poor kid.
I'm not proud of it.
Hey, I borrowed
one of your books.
I hope that's okay.
Like this.
No.
Surprise!
(SCREAMS)
(JAMIE LAUGHING)
(ROMANTIC BALLAD PLAYING)
Have you really never brought
a girl home before?
I brought you here.
Mmm-mmm.
I mean like a real girl.
Not a friend.
A real girl?
Yeah.
I guess not.
and state.
Ah, yes.
Separation of church
Build up as many walls
as possible.
That's really healthy.
What, are you talking
to me about walls?
Yeah.
What about you
and your mom?
You couldn't get me out
of there fast enough
when she walked in on us.
That was for your own
protection. Okay?
I'm just surprised she didn't
try to slip you her
number or something.
She did.
She put it in my phone.
Under "MILF".
Oh, my God.
It's cool, we only
hooked up, like, twice.
(LAUGHS)
I'm starting to get
a mental image.
Well,
I have a video image.
Oh! No. Just stop it.
Just stop it.
(EXCLAIMS IN DISGUST)
Just wrong.
What?
Nothing.
Just glad I met you.
Yeah, well,
knowing you doesn't
suck either.
But I thought you said...
I know what I said.
(GASPS)
Oopsy.
(BANGING)
Ow!
God.
Lasorda was a good pitcher,
but he was an even
better manager.
I wasn't saying
he's not a great manager.
Wrecking Crew?
He's underappreciated
as a pitcher,
that's all I'm saying.
We get it. Guys.
Hi.
Good morning.
Is it always
this beautiful out here?
Good morning.
Well, in between the fires
and the floods,
we get about 10 good days.
Oh.
No, no. Here.
You two sit together.
Are you sure?
Oh, yeah, no, no.
You don't have
to do that, Dad.
I know.
I wanna look at the boat.
I love that boat.
Oh. Here. Sorry.
Great. Thanks.
Here.
Thank you. This... Okay.
Coffee, my lady?
Oh. Yes, please.
Thank you.
Woah!
All right, man!
Look at you!
That's pretty impressive.
ANNIE: Yay, Sammy!
DYLAN: All right!
Oh. Oh, buddy.
Your shirt's leaking.
Oh, no, that's...
Apologies.
Here.
You okay?
Yeah.
You?
See them, Sammy?
Yeah. Woah!
Pretty cool, huh?
Yeah.
God, it's nice.
I do miss the mornings out
here. Right before it burns
off, it really is beautiful.
I like Jamie.
And she's pretty, too.
Hey, easy, dude.
Don't you go casting
a spell on her.
I'm a magician, not a wizard.
You and your gay Harry Potter.
You can't deny that going
to Hogwarts wouldn't be
life-changing.
I miss you.
I miss you, too, bud.
Mom misses you.
And so does Grandpa.
Does he say anything?
No. But sometimes
he calls me Dylan.
He said that he didn't
want the job.
That he was just coming
to New York to explore
his options.
What a crock of gas.
You fly across the country
to explore your options?
Please. I don't think so.
Exactly! Please, I knew
I had him the second
he got off that plane.
Oh, did you, now?
Yeah.
you leapt onto the baggage
carousel barefoot
Was that the same second
and acted out a scene
from  Will and Grace?
(EMBARRASSED LAUGH)
She did?
Oh, yeah,
you should have seen her.
"Ah, look at me,
I'm goofy but cute."
You know what?
It was all part of my plan.
Quite a plan.
Did you major in Planning
at Headhunting College?
So clever.
It's not a real college,
by the way, buddy.
You guys bicker like
you're an old married couple.
Here, pick a card,
my lady.
Okay.
Oh, no, not that one.
The one on top.
This is a good one.
So...
Yeah?
Shuffle.
Did you get her
an engagement gift?
We're not engaged, Dad.
We're not together.
We're just friends.
All right, you don't wanna
label it. I understand.
But get her some jewelry.
The only thing your mom
loves is jewelry.
I don't care how upset she is,
I get her jewelry,
she lights right up.
Where is she, anyway?
She's not here, Dad.
I know, that's why I asked.
Where is she?
She's not coming.
Why not?
She doesn't live with you
anymore, Pop.
You're not married.
MR. HARPER: What?
She left about 10 years ago.
I don't understand.
She divorced you, Dad.
I have to call her.
Dad, you can't.
Stop telling me what to do.
Get your...
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(ALL GASPING)
SAM: Grandpa!
ANNIE: Dylan, get...
DYLAN: You okay, Dad?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Here, let me help you up.
No, don't. Don't!
(PANTING)
Here we are.
This is beautiful.
Yeah, this is where I used
to come to think. My rooftop.
Okay, how high
do you think
that fence is?
I'm a little over 6 foot.
Looks like it's
about three of me.
So six times three...
Ninety-two feet.
That's really tall, right?
Yeah.
But they don't want you
to get up there, so I guess
that makes sense.
Wait. Six times three...
Oh, God, you poor kid.
What's up?
Come on.
What? What?
Where are you going?
Jamie, no, no, no, no, no,
wait. They take this shit
seriously, okay?
Look at all the cameras.
This is the only landmark
this city has other than
the Scientology Center.
And if any of these cameras
are hooked up to the actual
Scientology Center,
that was an inappropriate joke
and I apologize.
I believe in the freedom
of science fiction.
(COUGHING)
Pussy! Oh, sorry.
Pussy!
Come on!
JAMIE: You really never been
up here before?
DYLAN: No.
I've also never transferred
heroin in my rectum,
'cause it's against the law.
You know, sometimes a simple
yes or no answer is adequate.
Hey, why didn't you tell me
about your mom?
She's not worth
talking about.
That's rough.
So is leaving
your husband and kids.
Yeah, you never told me
about him either.
You know,
there's a lot of stuff
you didn't tell me.
I don't want your pity.
I can handle anything
except that look
in people's eyes.
That one.
Who cares
what anybody thinks?
He's the smartest man
I've ever known.
He's the only person
I'd ever go to for advice.
He's my dad.
Dylan,
he's still the same man.
When I see the way
people look at him now...
It doesn't matter
how people look at him.
All that matters
is how you look at him.
Yeah, but he's walking around
without his pants.
Everyone's staring.
So what?
It's embarrassing.
He needs to know
that nothing has changed.
That he's still that
same man to you.
Can we stop talking
about this?
Yeah, that's really smart.
Let's just not talk
about our feelings.
I'm trying not to.
Come on. Is something going
on here? You've been acting
really weird.
No, I haven't.
Yeah, you have.
Is this about what happened
the other night?
What, sex?
That doesn't mean anything.
You know that.
Right.
And I haven't been
acting weird.
Okay.
Oh, my God!
Oh, shit!
I told you!
Well, I'm sorry!
Fuck!
OFFICER:  This is the LAPD.
You are trespassing.
Get down from the sign.
We gotta jump.
JAMIE: Dylan, jump!
(STUTTERING) I'm frozen.
Come on, get down!
Sir, this is
your last warning.
Use the ladder!
I have a fear of heights!
(STUTTERING)
And also helicopters!
They don't make sense to me!
What do you mean
you have a fear of heights?
Why would you come up here?
You called me
(STAMMERING) a pussy!
NEWS ANCHOR:  A bizarre
situation this afternoon
in the Southland.
The LAPD rescued a local man
from the Hollywood sign,
the city's only real landmark.
They actually wrapped you
in a foil blanket!
Did you run a marathon
before this?
Okay. Give me...
No!
No, no. I wanna save it.
I gotta save it.
No. That's enough!
Give me the remote! Shut up!
No, I wanna watch it
over and over.
Ow, ow, ow!
Foil wrapper...
(PREPARES TO SPIT)
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
It's okay,
it'll be up on YouTube.
(ANNIE SIGHS)
Hey, you're still good
to take Dad that week
I have to go to DC
for Sam's class trip, right?
Yeah, he's gonna stay
with me in New York.
Oh, good.
So, when are we gonna
see Jamie again?
I don't know.
Did you have a fight
with your girlfriend?
What's your problem?
She's not my girlfriend.
Why don't you believe me?
I would believe you
if you didn't lie to me.
I saw you creeping out
of her room the other night.
Like you had just had sex,
if you know what I mean.
Yes, I know what you mean,
you just said it.
And how do you know
what I look like
after I have...
I'm not talking to you
about this, okay?
We're not together.
Dylan.
Enough!
I'm not talking about it.
Dylan.
Forgot my saw.
I'll be right back.
(LAUGHING)
I'll wait here.
Don't worry about me.
Friends who have sex?
What are you, in college?
It doesn't matter,
it's over.
Why?
Because we don't like
each other like that.
Okay, you know what?
Can we just talk about this?
Sit down.
What more are you
looking for?
Who says I'm looking
for anything?
Dylan.
I don't know,
but it's not Jamie.
Why, because you're
great together?
Because you're actually
friends with each other?
Because this is the happiest
I have ever seen you?
I don't know what
to tell you.
She's not for me.
I don't like her
like that.
You liked her enough
to have sex with her.
It's just physical.
Like playing tennis.
I don't even know
what that means, Dylan.
I haven't seen you
this dumb since you
got that candy corn tattoo.
It's a lightning bolt!
With extra powers!
Dylan, you can't name
one thing that's
wrong with her.
I can never
go out with her.
She's too fucked up.
Okay, she doesn't
want a boyfriend.
She's too damaged.
Magnum P.I. couldn't
solve the shit going on
in her head.
Wow. You'll say anything
right now
not to admit that
you're perfect for each other.
Why am I still having
this conversation?
Because I'm right.
Good talk, Annie.
Dylan.
(SIGHS)
I don't think
the three-point line
would have done anything.
He was taller
than anyone alive.
No, but it helped Kobe.
Kobe Bryant is incredible.
It helped him.
You're men.
You like sports.
Scored 81 points. Please.
Hey! We were
waiting for you.
I actually got
a call from work.
I have to be on
a red eye tonight
back to New York.
Tonight?
Yeah.
Tomorrow's the 4th.
I know, it sucks.
Well, at least let me
drive you to the airport.
No, no. It's fine. Stay.
I already called a cab.
It's out front.
But thank you
guys for everything.
And thank you for
letting me stay here.
It's been pretty great.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Hey.
Everything okay, buddy?
Yeah, buddy.
Everything's great.
I just really gotta go.
So, um, thank you again.
I'm sorry I gotta go.
Let Dylan drive you.
Yeah.
ANNIE: Do you wanna take
some food to go?
SAM: Do you want me to
saw you in half?
You can send your
bottom part to New York
and your top
half can stay here.
(CHUCKLES)
Or the whole of
you could stay.
Okay, I'm sorry.
I gotta go.
Ah...
DYLAN: Jamie!
(CAR DRIVING AWAY)
She's gone.
She hopped in the cab.
We should eat.
You hungry, buddy?
Yeah.
Okay. Hand me your plate.
(CELL PHONE BEEPING)
Hey, bro. You hungry?
'Cause I'm going to
get something to eat.
Thanks, man.
I think I'm just
gonna work through lunch.
A work ethic. I love it.
That is why this country
is still number one.
Well, behind
Germany and France
and Belgium and
Japan and China and...
Thank God for Bangladesh.
(LAUGHS)
Oh, by the way, why did you
take your door off
its lovely hinges?
It was dumb, man.
Something I saw in
a management book.
Oh, right, right.
Like, that's how
Warren Buffett got rich.
He took doors
off of things.
Hey, everybody wants
a shortcut in life.
My guidebook is very simple.
You wanna lose weight?
Stop eating, fatty.
You wanna make money?
Work your ass off, lazy.
You wanna be happy?
Find someone you like
and never let him go.
Or her, if you're into
that kind of creepy shit.
(SIGHS)
(CLOSING TIME
RINGTONE PLAYING)
(BEEPS)
Hi, you've reached
Jamie Rellis.
I can't pick up
the phone right now,
but please leave a message
and I'll call you back.
(LAUGHING)
Mom, Mom, you gotta
point it at the screen.
You gotta tell
it where you are.
Fine. I'm over here
pouring myself a drink.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Oh. Booty call.
I can take a walk
around the block.
No, no.
Nope, that's okay.
This is your apartment.
I don't wanna twat-block you.
That's Dylan, right?
He seemed pretty great.
You met him once.
Well, that's more than
anybody else you've dated.
I don't know, you think
maybe I keep my worlds apart
for some crazy reason?
I am an asshole.
We're looking for someone
to lead the redesign
of our entire website.
Someone to turn it
completely upside down.
But you can't tell me
what company you work for?
Uh, for
confidentiality reasons,
uh, no.
Can you give me a hint?
We may or may not be
the largest seller
of purchased
goods on the Internet.
And by "purchased goods,"
I mean books.
You just placed
the new art director
over at GQ,  right?
Uh, yeah.
That's the type
of guy we want.
Shoot, that's
the guy we want.
Can you get him
to come out to us?
No longer have
a relationship with him.
Can you get to him?
He's still in the first
year of his contract,
so that would
be inappropriate.
So is paying full price
for a book at Barnes & Noble,
but people do dumb shit.
(PHONE DIALING)
Hi, you've reached
Jamie Rellis.
I can't pick up
the phone right now,
but please leave a message
and I'll call you back.
Wow, right to voice mail.
Didn't even ring.
Jamie.
How'd you know
I was up here?
Only place in the city
you don't get reception.
Right.
Why are you avoiding me?
I'm not.
Really? Come on, Jamie.
Well, Dylan,
I don't know if you've heard,
but I am seriously fucked up.
I mean, Magnum P.I.
couldn't solve the shit
going on up here.
Oh, my God, I'm sorry.
But I'm just gonna go
and try to fix the shit
going on up in my head,
if that's even possible.
I shouldn't have said that.
I was just trying to
get my sister off my back.
She thought we
liked each other.
Yeah, me, too, Dylan.
I thought we were friends.
But friends don't go
talking shit about each other,
which must mean
that you and I were
actually never friends.
That all you wanted
was to get in my pants.
What?
You jumped at the chance
at your dad's house.
You cracked your neck.
I thought you were
giving me a sign.
We talked about this.
Oh, my God, really?
You pulled my robe off.
"Oopsy." Remember?
Yeah. And then you
snuck out of the room.
"Oopsy." Remember that?
Are you pissed off at me
because I didn't cuddle?
(EXASPERATED SIGH)
Isn't that why we started
this whole arrangement
in the first place?
You wanted this.
I wanted this?
Just me?
God, you are just
like every other guy.
The sad thing is, Dylan,
I actually thought
you were different.
Different from what?
I'm not your boyfriend,
I'm your friend.
Well, with friends like you,
who needs friends?
And, uh, thank you for
ruining my mountaintop.
Asshole.
Hey, man,
you can't be up here.
Okay.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Bryce, is this for me?
Yeah. And so is this.
Madison, will you marry me?
You bet your ass, Flapjack!
I love New York.
I love you.
Oh, my God. Look,
the Empire State Building.
Wow.
Oh, look,
the Statue of Liberty.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(CELL PHONE RINGS)
Hello, this is Jamie.
What do you mean they
went to him directly?
Well, is he gonna take it?
No, no, no, no, no.
I'll handle it.
I'll call him right now.
Okay.
(PHONE DIALING)
Hey, this is Dylan.
Leave a message.
Argh.
Excuse me. May I help you?
Oh, hi. Um, where's
Dylan Harper?
He's at a photo shoot
for the sports issue.
That's right. The photo shoot.
Um, where was that again?
I'm sorry.
Who are you?
One of the models.
I have the perfect
body for Photoshop.
Yeah, this gets
more angular,
these get longer,
and this gets
way more Christian.
Mmm-hmm.
So where did you
say he was again?
Sports is the last
chance we have
of bringing our
world together, bro.
to shoot some photos
that speak to that,
So I just wanted
of all people
through sports.
to the unification
PHOTOGRAPHER: Okay, guys.
Let's go.
TOMMY: That's it.
Beautiful.
Okay, now put your
arms around each other,
like you like each other,
like you love each other.
Too gay?
A little bit.
Throw some girls in there.
Come on, ladies. Hop to.
Okay, look.
Just blend in.
Girls, girls.
Okay, let's go
boy, girl, boy...
Dylan.
...boy, boy, boy, boys.
What are you doing here?
You met for another job!
What, are you
gonna leave now?
I don't know. Yeah,
I took one meeting.
I can't believe you.
Come here.
(SIGHS)
Is this your way of
getting back at me?
What?
You know that if you leave
before a year is up,
I get screwed.
Oh, right.
If I did leave,
which I don't know yet
because all I did
was take one meeting,
I'd write you a check
for your bonus.
Whatever it is,
I'll pay for it.
Happy now? We good?
Why didn't you tell
me you were looking?
That's personal.
And we're not
friends anymore.
You made that pretty clear.
See, all I wanted to do
was have sex with you.
Remember?
Pretend you were
the best friend
I'd ever had.
Open up to you
like I've never
done with anyone ever.
And then when
the sex stopped,
invite you to LA
for the weekend to,
(SCATTING DRAMATICALLY)
introduce you to my family.
I'll send you a check
if I take the job.
Don't bother.
TOMMY: Why don't you
pick him up?
Yeah. Just pick him on up.
Oh, you little
Christ figure, you!
(PHONE RINGING)
Hey, Dyl.
Dad's coming into
Newark Airport, right?
Yeah, he leaves
at 9:00 our time.
9:00.
So it's a five-hour flight,
three-hour time difference,
so he gets in at
32:00?
5:00.
Be there at 5:00, Dylan.
Right. How is Dad?
Ah.
He's lost more
often than not now.
But then he has
these moments of real clarity.
It's hit or miss.
Okay.
How's Jamie?
That's over.
Oh, Dylan!
Okay, we're done.
Don't be an idiot, please.
tomorrow at the airport.
Thank you, Annie.
I'll pick up Dad
32:00 sharp.
I love you.
JAMIE: I don't know
what it is.
to start looking for
a replacement for him,
I just can't get myself
assuming that he leaves.
Do you want some
motherly love advice?
Not really.
Oh, good, 'cause
I don't know how to do that.
What I do know is that
it's no great goddamn secret
you live in fear of
repeating my mistakes.
And you're not wrong,
so learn from me.
Do you know how many men
in my life I thought
were really perfect?
Eighty.
One.
Eighty-one?
Oh.
It was your dad.
Greatest man I ever met.
Obviously. Look at you.
How smart you are, how great,
how funny, how driven.
Your vaguely
Middle Eastern beauty.
Sure as hell
didn't all come from me.
Okay, but, seriously, Mom,
do you really not remember
where my dad's from?
Or is it like
a coping mechanism?
A little of both.
(LAUGHING)
Okay.
But I'm pretty
sure he's Eurasian.
(LAUGHING)
I mean, we all have
our Prince Charming,
you just gotta know
him when you see him.
Mom, it's Prince Charming.
You should just know.
Well, your Prince
Charming isn't coming
to rescue you in
a horse and carriage.
That's not who you want.
I mean, you're looking
for a man to be your partner.
To take on the world with.
You gotta update
your fairy tale, baby.
My Prince Charming?
You.
Mom.
Hey.
A wheelchair.
Like I'm an invalid.
How was the flight?
I'm hungry.
You know they
don't serve food
in coach anymore?
You'd think with
these new planes,
they practically
fly themselves,
they could get rid
of a pilot and use his
salary for a hot lunch.
I know, right?
Let's get you some food.
God.
DYLAN: The engineering
on these planes
is so advanced.
Completely computerized.
It's like
playing a video game.
Exactly.
God. How long have
we been waiting here?
It's ridiculous.
I'll be right back, okay?
Excuse me.
We've been waiting a while.
Harper.
Yeah, I got you.
I got you.
I have to seat people
in the order they came.
I totally understand that,
but I'm with my dad
and he's not in
the best shape.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Is there no way we could,
like, squeeze a table?
No, I gotta go
by the list. Sorry.
Dad?
Shit. Dad?
You gonna join me?
Absolutely.
Excuse me, sir. I'm sorry,
you cannot do this.
Could I get a steak,
medium, please?
Sir, this is
the Daily Grill.
Make that two.
Dede? Dede!
Dad.
(SIGHS)
Who is Dede?
Jesus. She's just a girl
that I met in the Navy.
Was...
(CLEARS THROAT)
She was the love of my life.
Okay?
Why didn't you tell
me about her before?
This is not something
you discuss
with your children.
And besides,
I have you and Annie.
I have no regrets.
So tell me now.
She was the love of my life.
And I was too
stupid to realize it,
and I lost her
because of something
so dumb I don't even remember.
And I never
really got over her.
one of the reasons
your mom left.
And I think that may be
You know, my friends
used to say
that when Dede and I
looked at each other,
it was electric.
And I let her go.
I just let her go.
Because I was too damn proud
to tell her how
I really felt about her.
I'll tell you something
that I wish I knew
when I was your age.
And I know you've heard
a million times,
"life is short."
But let me tell you something,
what this is teaching me
is that life is goddamn short
and you can't
waste a minute of it.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
The girl I brought
home to LA, Jamie?
Yeah, what's
going on with her?
I think I messed it up.
Fix it.
She won't talk to me.
Maybe she'll listen.
There's always a way.
If you think
there's even a chance
that she could
be it, you fix it.
Did Annie put you
up to this?
Who's Annie?
I'm kidding.
What, I can't joke
about this?
(LAUGHING)
Jesus Christ, Dad.
I don't know
what else to do.
Let's go.
You don't want to
finish your steak?
We're eating in
the goddamn airport.
I can leave the steak.
Come on.
Yeah, hey,
this is Dylan Harper
from  GQ.
We met a few
weeks ago at the...
Right. Hey, can I ask you
a huge favor?
Oh. I am so sorry, sir.
It's my fault.
You just scared me.
No, no. My fault.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm good.
Here, let me
help you with that.
Thanks, man.
You're really nice.
All right.
Hey, safe travels.
All right,
thanks, man.
Okay, thank you.
Oh.
You gotta be
fucking kidding me.
All right,
let's dance,
Clowny Brown.
What's your
problem with me?
I saw you at
that bar with Jamie.
be with this
How could such
an awesome girl
over this?
I've been trying to
take that little monkey
to pound-town for years.
you say hello.
What?
I'll tell her
You missed a little.
There you go.
Dylan! I got a cab.
Come on.
I ever run into you again,
I'll crush your earlobes
and make soup
stock out of them.
You have
a vivid imagination.
I do!
I'm gonna get in
the cab now.
I'm gonna go make soup!
What's the matter with her?
I don't know.
God! I thought LA was bad.
This traffic is terrible.
Is there another
way into the city?
DYLAN: I owe you
big time, Tommy.
You'll make it up to me.
Actually, I was
heading into town anyway.
Tonight's the Butterfly Ball.
Great place to pick up dudes.
You okay, Dad?
Are you kidding?
1937 Chris-Craft?
Couldn't get
any better, buddy.
Nice.
Yeah. Hi,
this is Dylan.
We met at...
Right.
Can I ask you
a huge favor?
My number.
Here's the remote.
My friend Dave
from across the hall,
his oven broke, so
he'll be using the kitchen.
Your friend Dave is
here using the kitchen
or watching me?
Go.
Holy...
What?
"How to wear white
pants to a cookout."
Did you scoop
the  Times on this?
I smell Pulitzer.
All right, all right.
Just say hello to
her for me, will you?
See you, Dad.
Thanks, man.
Hi, Dave
from across the hall.
(SLOWLY AND LOUDLY)
Hi, Mr. Harper.
How are you?
And now we know
why you're here.
Mom, I'm over by
the Lexington exit.
Where are you?
LORNA:  I'm standing right
by the guy in the tie.
There are
a million guys
in ties.
So look for the guy
I'm standing next to.
Ugh. You never do what you
say you're gonna do.
When am I gonna learn?
Just hang on, baby.
(JUMP BEGINS PLAYING
OVER THE PA)
What?
I don't think
I'm gonna be able
to make it after all.
Something came up.
Let's meet tomorrow.
I'll be on the stairs.
Right across from you.
Oh, my God.
Have a great night, baby.
(CLOSING TIME
BEGINS TO PLAY)
(MOUTHING THE WORDS)
What is this?
It's  Closing Time,
by the band Semisonic!
It's not Third Eye Blind.
Can you believe that?
No, no, no.
Not the song. This.
You said you wanted your life
to be like a movie.
Sorry I had to use
the real Grand Central
instead of the fake one.
Listen, Jamie, I'm...
I'm having
trouble hearing you!
Yeah, I didn't
really think this through.
I guess in the movies
the guy pours his heart out
and they put
the music in later.
What?
I messed up.
I was scared.
Look at what happened
with my mom and my dad.
Of course I was scared.
So I ruined it.
Everything that
happens in the day,
all I can think to myself is,
"I can't wait to
tell Jamie about this."
When I see someone
cursing, all I picture
is you blinking.
And when I hear
a kid's been cured
of cancer,
I pray it's not
by that douchebag,
tree-hugging fucking doctor
who ran out on you.
I mean, cancer
being cured is awesome,
but, you know,
I wish someone else did it.
Come on.
Hey, I miss you.
Yeah, I miss you, too.
But you're not wrong,
I am damaged.
So am I. Who isn't?
That's what
makes us so awesome.
And our tattoos.
Yeah.
Oh. No, no, no.
Oh, shut up.
It's not what you think.
Jamie, will you be
my best friend again?
That is so lame.
Oh. I know.
Prince Charming shit,
though, right?
That's some
Get up.
Okay.
Look, I can live without
ever having sex
with you again.
It'd be really hard.
(LAUGHS)
Hey, I want my
best friend back,
because I'm
in love with her.
Under one condition.
Anything.
Kiss me.
In public?
In front of
all these people?
I did not ask you to...
You can all go home now.
Okay. So...
What do we do now?
Have our first date.
Okay.
Oh, my God!
Did you get
a horse and carriage?
Yeah, that's not for you.
Oh, thank God.
Horses actually
scare the shit out of me.
Really?
Yeah.
DYLAN: So, where are you from?
Outside of Philly, actually.
Interesting.
I'm from LA,
just moved to New York.
Interesting.
Didn't really ask,
but go on.
What? I'm excited,
I'm on a first date. So...
JAMIE: This isn't
weird at all.
We're okay.
Yeah. Thank you.
So...
Yeah, fuck it.
Roll credits,
roll credits, roll credits.
And here come the outtakes.
Because if the actors had
a good time making it,
it must be good.
You bet your ass, Jason.
Oh, my God,
I just called him Jason.
(EVERYONE LAUGHING)
Look, the crew's laughing.
Oh!
They made me do it!
They made me do it.
(EVERYONE LAUGHING
AND CHEERING)
It's my favorite part.
(GRUMBLING)