They say if you want to glimpse
the future, just look behind you.
I used to think that was bollocks.
But now I realize...
...you can't outrun the past.
When we were kids, you'd start fights
with the toughest bastards in the yard.
But I was the one who had to step in
and finish them.
You'd steal from the corner shop,
but it was me
who'd brave the old man's belt.
I'd hoped you'd outgrown it.
That playing the gangster
made you harder, smarter, better.
But deep down, I guess I always
knew you'd end up like this,
despite everything I did teach you.
Still, you're my flesh and blood.
So you remain my cross to bear.
Rest now, little brother,
while I settle your one last score.
You take care of my brother.
Anything happens to him,
I will come by looking for you.
Here. Hold this.
Grenade!
Come on, Dom.
So where are you taking me?
They say an open road helps you think about
where you have been, where you're going.
So you don't remember any of this yet?
That's not fair.
You know I don't.
So what is it exactly that
you're trying to show me?
That.
Race Wars.
We used to come here?
"Come here"?
We invented it.
Keep it under 9,000 RPMs.
Kid's going to fry his pistons
after the first 200.
You know that's not my style.
I got to ride or die, right?
How about you just ride on this one?
Are you ready?
I know you're ready!
Go!
Hey, nice job.
Hey!
That's the girl I heard so much about.
Where you been at, ghost girl?
Ghost girl.
Letty, what the hell?
Huh?
Damn, dawg!
Girl's still got that swing, homie.
You never could take a punch.
Right, right.
Hey, man. I am glad you're back, man.
It's good to see you!
Good to see you, Hector.
All right. We made it, Jack.
- Yeah, we made it!
- Yeah, we made it.
Now I just got to find that door button.
Buddy, where's the door button at?
Do you know?
Hi.
Hey.
Yeah, of course. I am new to this.
Yeah, you don't seem like the minivan type.
No, not exactly.
Hey, buddy,
you going to give me a high five?
Wait, wait, wait! Wait, high five!
All right. Yeah, buddy.
Appreciate it. Thank you.
Don't worry.
You will get used to this in no time.
Yeah, that's what I am afraid of.
First time I saw this,
I thought it was kind of funny.
I guess now the joke's on me.
What are you doing?
What I should have done a long time ago.
Stop it!
Look at it.
It's the truth.
That's the date that I lost my memory.
That's the date that Letty died...
and I was born.
No. You never died.
Do you know how hard it is for me
when you look at me
and you see me through
15 years of memories?
Every beautiful moment we have ever had.
I see it in your eyes.
I can't give that to you.
I got nothing.
You got me.
And you have got only a piece of me.
I have to find myself.
For me.
Goodbye, Dom.
You're disappointed, aren't you?
What are you talking about?
The last arrest.
He was too easy. Target didn't even run.
Ah, it's okay.
Gives me a chance to hit the iron.
Also lets me work on my stamping skills.
You're a terrible liar.
See you tomorrow, boss.
- I will see you then.
- Don't stay too late.
I will stay as long as I want, woman.
I knew you would say that.
Elena?
What's this?
It's the letter of recommendation
you asked for.
Just know I meant every word in there.
Thanks, Hobbs. Thanks for everything.
Come on, way too sentimental right now.
- Get home. Good night.
- Okay. Good night.
Just one sec.
You sure as hell ain't the IT guy.
So you better start talking before
I break that finger six different ways
and stick it right
where the sun doesn't shine.
Agent Hobbs, right?
That's right.
I am also the last man on Earth
whose computer you want to be hacking into.
You just earned yourself
a dance with the devil, boy.
You're under arrest.
I don't care about your computer.
I am here for the team
that crippled my brother.
There ain't no goddamn team.
It was just one man,
and he's standing right in front of you.
The lady was right.
You are a terrible liar.
Goddamn IT guys.
Hobbs!
On me!
Elena!
Hobbs?
Hobbs!
All right, buddy. We got to go.
We're going to be late.
Come on.
Okay, what do you think?
Parking brake slide right up to the school?
Where's Mommy?
I don't know. She's up there.
She's coming.
Here we go.
Watch your head.
Dom, you have a package out here!
It's from Tokyo.
Tokyo?
What? Is Han trying to convert me
over to a turbocharger?
All right, you ready?
There we go.
Hey, buddy. Cars don't fly.
Hey, cars don't fly.
This one did, huh?
Brian in a minivan. Things have changed.
He's struggling, Dom.
He doesn't want me to see it,
but the white picket fence is like
an anchor on him. I can tell.
I tried to talk to him the other night.
You know what he said?
He doesn't miss the girls. He doesn't miss
the cars. He misses the bullets.
Let him settle in. Give him time.
How does nine months sound?
I am having another baby.
And you didn't tell him, did you?
You got to tell him.
I don't want him to be disappointed
with his life.
With me.
He will never be disappointed with you.
You're the best thing
that's ever happened to him.
Thank you.
Yeah?
Dominic Toretto.
You don't know me. You're about to.
Get down!
Jack!
Shattered his collarbone,
fractured his leg in two places.
He only regained consciousness
this morning.
The first thing he said was, "Get me Dom."
He's in there.
Are you okay?
I am fine.
He's waiting. Let's go.
Got something for you.
Your files.
Thank you.
You risk life and limb to save
the free world and what do they give you?
Jell-O and a bad '70s TV show.
You know, it's got its perks.
- Sponge baths ain't that bad.
- Dad!
I am sorry, baby.
"Dad"?
Honey, I want to introduce you
to somebody. He's a, uh...
He's an old friend.
Go on and say hello.
Dominic Toretto, right?
My dad said he kicked your ass once.
Young lady, watch your mouth.
Your dad's on heavy pain meds.
I can understand
if his history is a little hazy.
I doubt it.
All right, honey, that's enough. I want you
to go get something to eat with Elena
while me and Toretto have a talk.
You hear me?
- Come on, lady. Let's get some cookies.
- Watch that mouth.
Who did this?
You remember Owen Shaw?
The one we tore half of London down
trying to get.
Well, this is his big bad brother.
Take a look at this.
Deckard Shaw.
British Special Forces assassin.
The kind of unique asset that no
government would ever admit to employing.
Black Ops boys.
Worse. They created a monster.
They felt Shaw was a necessary evil
until eventually,
they decided he was unnecessary.
The powers that be felt that he knew
just a little bit too much.
The asset became a liability.
So they sent in 20 elite operatives
to retire him.
And they missed.
That was six years ago,
and Shaw's been a ghost ever since.
Until now.
How do I find him?
The official answer is, you don't.
He killed Han. Almost killed my family.
He also tried to put me
in a body bag, too.
Which is why when I get out, I am
going to put a hurt on him so bad
he's going to wish his mama
had kept her legs closed.
But until then,
my official answer to you...
...is stand down.
Now, you know I can't do that.
I do know you, Dom.
Which is why now I give you
the brother-to-brother answer.
You do whatever it is you got to do.
When you find that sumbitch,
just do me one favor.
What's that?
Don't miss.
Thank you so much for letting us stay,
Mando. I hope it's not a problem.
Listen, Dom needed a safe delivered
to Rio in two days. That was a problem.
Hosting his family in
the Dominican Republic, that is vacation.
Anyone messes with you here,
they mess with the entire country.
You will be safe.
Yeah, yeah, they're here.
I picked them up myself at the airport.
Hold on.
Your brother.
Dom.
Yeah, Mia, it's me. How's it going there?
We're at Mando's.
This place is like a fortress.
You should see Brian.
He's in full FBI mode.
He built a surveillance hub in
Mando's garage and everything.
What about you?
Did you find out who's after us?
Looks like the sins of London
have followed us home.
How did Buster take the news?
I can't tell him. If he knew about
the baby, he'd stay here with us.
And with all that's going on,
you're going to need him by your side.
Just watch out for him. Keep him safe.
And come home together.
Tell Brian I will see him in LA
in two days.
Where are you going?
Tokyo.
I am bringing Han home.
Authorities are still trying to determine
the motive behind this daring attack
here at the office
of the US Diplomatic Security Service
in downtown Los Angeles
less than 36 hours ago.
Facts are still coming in,
but what is known is the suspect
entered the building's fourth floor...
Hey.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
This guy's just relentless.
That's why Dom needs you.
You two need to find this guy
and you need to stop him
before he does any more damage
to our family.
You know, I just...
I have screwed up so many things.
I couldn't live with myself
if I screw this up, too.
You won't.
I believe in you.
I believe in us.
That's all that matters.
I love you, Brian.
I love you, baby.
Just promise me, after this, we're done.
No more jobs, no more enemies.
Come back to us.
I won't let you down, Mia.
I know.
Hey, yo, Sean!
Hey, check this out, man.
This dude over here
want to race the new DK.
Not tonight, Twinkie.
Said he knew Han.
Han said you was fast,
but not that damn fast.
Who said American muscle can't drift?
Han mentioned he left his enemies
in his rearview.
He never talked about it much.
Always playing it close to the vest.
We found a couple things by the crash.
Wasn't much left.
Gisele.
Oh, yeah.
There's one more thing.
I found this.
Must have meant something to him.
When you find the guy that killed Han,
what are you going to do?
Words ain't even been invented yet.
They say to live in the hearts
of those we leave behind....
...is not to die.
But he put you in this grave.
So now I will do the same to him.
I can't do no more funerals.
First, Han.
Now Hobbs is laid up, of all people.
We're being hunted.
You know he's out there
somewhere watching, right?
I hope so.
Means he's close.
Just promise me, Brian,
no more funerals.
Just one more.
His.
You never should have messed
with a man's family.
I told your brother the same thing.
Reinforced your chassis.
It's like going into a ring
with weighted gloves.
Your mistake.
I am not here to play games.
See, you and me,
we're from different worlds.
Trust me, I have seen a lot meaner streets
than the ones you're used to.
Stick around.
It's going to get a lot meaner.
You thought
this was going to be a street fight?
On the ground.
Now!
Drop him or I will drop you!
Whoa, whoa. Easy, guys.
We're on the same team here.
Mr. Toretto, I am here on the
recommendation of a mutual friend of ours.
- Mr. Hobbs.
- Who the hell are you?
Me? I am just a guy.
I am Mr. Nobody.
It's a big entrance for a nobody.
And the guy that put our mutual friend
in the hospital?
You just let him get away.
I think I might have just
saved your ass there, Dom.
Listen, you think you could
let go of my guy there?
He's beginning to turn a little blue.
I appreciate that.
Ah, here they come.
Listen, Dom. There's a war going on
between shadows and ghosts like me.
You and your team unwittingly walked
into the middle of it in London,
and it appears it's now followed you home.
It's up to you.
I am going to have a beer.
You're welcome to join me.
By the way, I can get you Deckard Shaw.
Belgian ale.
Oh, man, those monks got it right.
I mean, I don't know about
the whole celibacy thing,
but when it comes to beer...
Would you like one?
I am more of a Corona man myself.
Ah...
Your file's not only detailed,
it's, uh, extremely entertaining.
Look, Shaw's power is that he's a shadow.
He's really good at getting in and
out of places without being seen
and leaving nothing
but a body count in his wake.
I mean, he's a legitimate English badass.
But to be honest with you, Dom,
I don't give two shits about Deckard Shaw.
It's you I want.
Because you and I can help each other
get what we both need.
I am listening.
Just recently a private military company
led by a wanted terrorist
named Mose Jakande
kidnapped a hacker known only
by the name "Ramsey".
Now, Lady Liberty's got her panties
in a bunch over this, but rightfully so,
because this Ramsey has created
something interesting.
- Bring it up.
- Yes, sir.
Say hello to God's Eye.
Now, this little bastard hacks into
anything that's on the digital network.
That means every cell phone, satellite,
ATM machine and computer. Simultaneously.
If it's got a microphone or a lens,
God's Eye can find you.
So you invited me here to
show me a tracking device.
On steroids. Lots of them.
Let me put it to you this way.
It took us nearly a decade
to find Osama bin Laden.
With this, we'd have located him anywhere
on the planet in a couple of hours.
Now, that's a serious piece of machinery
that could be catastrophic
in the wrong hands.
But for some very nauseating
political reasons,
any rescue plans involving
any US government forces or entity
has been strictly ruled out.
And that's why I need you.
But why do I need you?
I mean, I could go back outside,
enjoy the rest of the Coronas,
let Shaw come to me.
You could do that.
How's that working out for you so far?
You got one friend in the ground,
another one in the hospital.
And then, of course, there's that little
issue of the bomb that destroyed your home.
Shaw lives in a world
that doesn't play by your rules.
Like it or not,
you live in that world now, too.
You want to know how to kill a shadow?
You just shine a little light on it.
If you get the God's Eye for me,
I have already got authorization
for you to use it until you get Shaw.
You go from the hunted to the hunter.
And there's no place on Earth
Shaw can hide from you.
More importantly, you and your family
don't go to any more funerals.
You get Ramsey, you get the God's Eye,
you get Shaw.
Well, that's the wind-up and the pitch.
Now that I have given you
this incredibly sensitive
and highly classified information,
what do you think, Toretto?
I think you already know
what I am going to do.
Good.
But it will be my way. And my crew.
I assumed you might say that.
Which is why I have taken the liberty
of gathering your team.
This is crazy.
What the hell is going on in here?
Our intelligence suggests that Ramsey
will be transported by an armed motorcade
through the Caucasus mountain range.
If they clear this range and reach their
destination, Ramsey is as good as gone.
So let me get this straight.
There's only one road that leads in or out,
sheer drops on every side,
a motorcade from hell protected by a small
army from one mile in either direction?
Yeah, that's about it.
- You done?
- No, I am not done.
So you all wanted me to break into
a police station. Fine.
Then you asked me to stop a tank.
I wasn't happy about it, but I did it.
Then you came up with this brilliant idea
to shoot down
one of the largest airplanes ever.
I shot that shit out of the sky.
Mmm. It's nothing.
But this right here, my friend,
happens to be the stupidest idea
I have ever heard of in my life.
I forgot that you were the only one
to bring the plane down.
No, no. The only thing I have ever seen him
take down was "No Knees" Denise.
Remember, at prom?
Really, Brian?
You're going to do that right here?
See, you all trying to get me off my point.
All I am saying is, I am tired of everybody
around me making all the decisions.
This time, I lead.
Seriously. If I don't start
making decisions, I am out.
All right, Roman.
What do you got?
I mean, I wasn't trying to get into
the whole leadership thing, like, now.
You know what I am saying? I was just, kind
of, talking about, like, at some point.
Like, you know, when we...
Whatever. I mean, I think...
Let's hit it from here.
- I don't think that that's-
- No, no, no, don't think.
That's my job.
Okay.
It is impossible to hit it there.
That is literally the most
secure spot on the mountain. Why?
Because you cannot physically access it.
See, that's what makes it so sweet.
Because it's the place that
they least expect us to hit them from.
As much as I hate to admit it,
he's onto something there.
What do you think, Dom?
- Here?
- Yeah.
I think we got a plan.
Completely wrong thinking.
And I like it.
You see? I am good at this.
"Good"? Okay.
How are you planning on
getting on that road?
Well, Tej?
I think I may actually have a plan
for that.
What? I delegated.
That's what good leaders do.
Leader!
You know, when I was reading your files,
I was impressed with what you have
accomplished with your team.
But meeting them now,
I have got to say, Dom,
you have truly got a gift.
Consider my workshop your new playhouse.
I think you will find our cars
extremely appealing.
And your team is now complete.
I went to the house.
I was looking for you everywhere.
You scared the shit out of me.
You will never be alone.
Wherever you go...
Tell no one.
Where did you find that?
Found in Han's car.
It was left as a message.
A message I plan on returning.
Can you ride?
Yeah, of course I can.
Han was my family, too.
Brian!
We're going to need long-travel suspension,
limited-slip differentials on all of them.
How you doing?
Tej! I want the demon love child
between that...
...and that.
That's a lot of armor.
It's just going to add more weight.
Slow you down.
This time, it ain't just about being fast.
Yeah, I am good.
From the streets.
You know what I am saying?
It's nothing.
Hey, Roman, you're freaking out, ain't you?
No.
Yeah, you are.
I said no.
Listen, man, it takes a grown man
to embrace his feelings.
If you need to cry, just go ahead and cry.
As your friend, you know I am concerned
about your well-being,
which is why I took the precaution
of putting some adult diapers
in your glove compartment.
Yo, can you just chill out, man?
I have seen some crazy shit, Dom,
but this really could make some waves.
So let's just try to keep it
as low-key as possible, huh?
Don't I always?
I will tell you what, you knock it down
a couple of notches this time
and I will swap out my Belgian
for a keg of Corona.
You'd be doing yourself a favor, there.
Can somebody just walk me through
what we're supposed to be doing?
Come on, Rom, this is your plan.
You got to embrace it.
No, this was not my plan.
Oh, yeah, here we go. Game time.
Roman, you need some fresh air?
Because you're about to
get a whole lot of it.
Okay, here we go!
Just when you didn't think
it could get any better, huh?
Oh, shit!
Whoo!
Now we're moving.
Everybody good? Everybody make it out?
You just didn't tell them that this is
not for you! This is not your mission!
Hey, Rom? Hey, what's up, man?
Talk to me, come on!
- I can't do it.
- The hell you can't!
Come on, man! You throw that thing
in reverse and get your ass out here now!
Look, I can't do it, okay?
Listen to what I am saying.
Now isn't the time!
I am going to stay up here with the pilot.
We going to circle around and make sure
we holding it down from up here!
You're running out of time!
The chute is guided by GPS!
You don't have to do anything!
- Tej!
- I am already on it.
Hey, man, listen.
I am sorry to let you all down, okay?
I am going to go ahead and stay up here.
No, brother. I am sorry to let you down.
What?
What do you mean you-
Tej! What are you doing?
Oh, shit!
Tej!
I hate you, Tej!
Get ready! Ground's coming fast!
Come on, baby. Come on.
Oh, yeah!
Touchdown, baby!
Car check. Call it in.
- Check.
I am good. Let's do this.
Hello? Please, man.
Get me out of here, somebody!
No! The trees!
Oh, shit.
Sit tight, Roman.
We will come back for you.
This is not the plan!
All right, you got one chance
to hit them here, Dom.
You miss,
they will make it to their black site
and they will squeeze whatever
information they need out of Ramsey.
The device and your chance of ever
getting Shaw will be gone for good.
That ain't going to happen.
I will see you at the pickup.
Ramsey will be in the bus.
Then let's do this.
Captain, we have company.
Four cars, inbound.
Oh, shit!
- Tej, shield!
- I am on the way.
All right, formation.
Bulletproof, baby.
Can't touch this
Punch it!
Strike!
Guns free.
No...
Get out of the way!
Those aren't guns,
those are goddamn cannons!
Armor-piercing rounds!
Hook them up.
Brian, Tej, blow it!
Lock it up.
Huh?
Brian, you're up.
Little closer, Tej!
Ramsey?
Stay away from me! Stay back!
Don't you touch me!
My name's Brian.
I am going to get you out of here
but I am going to need you
to settle down, all right?
I am going to cut those things off of you.
Sir?
Sir, we have
an unidentified vehicle approaching.
Come on! Closer!
You're going to have to jump.
- No! No! No!
- We don't have time! Come on!
- We got to get out of here.
- Come on.
- I am not jumping!
- Look at me! Look at me!
You don't jump, we're going to die.
Okay?
You're jumping. Come on!
One.
Two!
Well, well, well.
Take my hand!
Welcome to the party, Mr. Shaw.
Letty, stay with Brian.
Oh, shit....
What are you doing? This is crazy!
Keeping you alive.
There's a cliff. Cliff!
Cliff! There's a cliff!
Shit....
Too slow.
Yeah!
I am back, bitches!
You good?
Thank you.
- Roman, get back to the others.
- What about you?
Don't worry about me.
I have to say, I am impressed.
I would very much like to know the name of
the man who is causing me so much trouble.
There's no way out of there.
What is he doing?
He's frozen like a damn deer in headlights.
Toretto ain't no deer.
Come on, Dominic.
Give us the girl, and I will let you live.
What are you going to do?
You might want to put on your helmet
for this one.
Helm...
Target the driver.
Damn it! What is he thinking?
You're insane!
You're pointing the wrong way.
Am I now?
Fire on my mark.
Interesting.
Three!
Two!
Hold on.
One!
Fire!
Looks like our demon love child worked.
That's one way down a mountain.
Where's Ramsey?
Hello Kitty is awake.
She don't look like a hacker to me.
Oh, yeah?
And what do hackers look like?
They don't supposed to look like that.
I am just saying, like,
you know how they normally wear them
little, weird glasses that's all crooked,
and pimples all over their face
from drinking soda?
I mean, trust me, with a body like that,
you ain't going to park it
behind a computer.
How are you feeling?
Did you hit your head?
Feeling nauseous? Ears ringing? No?
Where's my shoe?
Oh, it flew off when you crashed.
If you start experiencing any of
those things, let me know, okay?
I don't know whether to
thank you for rescuing me
or kick your ass for
throwing me off a cliff.
Thank us or kick our ass, huh?
How about you tell us where that device is?
I mailed it to a friend. In Abu Dhabi.
That was pretty easy.
That other team would have tortured you
for that information.
I didn't trust them. I trust you.
Now, why would you trust us?
You barely know us.
I know enough.
Ex-cop. Military, something like that.
The way you took out them guys
shows training.
Tech guy, offended by the hacker remark,
naturally.
Alpha.
Mrs. Alpha.
Joker.
Wrong.
Double alpha.
Man candy. You know what I am saying?
Man, sit your candy ass down.
The disrespect is real around here.
Life is binary. Zeroes and ones.
Only two things keep a group like this
together.
Fear or loyalty.
And I don't see a drop of fear
among you guys.
Very impressive.
Just one thing. They're not married.
She's so off, it's crazy.
You just going to roll with it?
You're telling me there can't be
a double alpha in one group?
You work for US government?
We got similar interests.
Tej, call it in.
We're going to the Middle East!
Hey.
Hey, Dom. It was pretty wild
on that mountain, huh?
No, it was too close.
But we got the job done.
You know what the crazy thing is, is...
You miss the bullets.
Yeah, that's messed up, huh?
Brian, I have seen you jump
from trains, dive from planes.
Hell, I saw your courage
the day I met you.
Right.
Want to know the bravest thing
I ever saw you do?
Be a good man to Mia.
Being a great father to my nephew, Jack.
Everyone's looking for the thrill,
but what's real is family.
Your family.
Hold on to that, Brian.
It's hotter than I thought it would be.
Yeah, well, we are in the desert,
so it would be hot.
Oh, no, I ain't talking about the weather.
- My, my, my.
- Hmm.
Now, that is a woman
that's worth falling out a plane for.
Get out of there, man, I got dibs on that.
You have seen me looking at that.
Did you just say "dibs"?
What are you, in the fourth grade?
Man, can you just get out of there?
I mean, it's a free market.
What are you talking about?
Get out of there.
Rock, paper, scissors for her.
Are you guys for real right now?
Look at you.
You both look whupped already.
You got stalker eyes.
I tried to call dibs on Ramsey
two years ago.
Her knee, my balls.
Trust me, you don't want to do that.
Hey! Ramsey!
Hello, Safar.
I see you make some new friends.
Yeah, some short-tempered new friends.
I need the speed drive I sent you.
Where is it?
Oh, good.
You will be pleased to know I sold it.
You sold it?
You hear that?
I asked you to take care of it.
Why on earth would you sell it?
We're going to need it back.
Impossible.
Safar, I stashed something inside it.
It's important.
Okay, okay. Uh. Good news. It is safe.
And the bad news?
It is very safe.
I sold it to a Jordanian prince
living up there.
Trust fund billionaire.
Said he wanted to use it for his supercar.
Now, see, this?
This, I like. Billionaire, supercar...
What makes it so super?
242 miles per hour, top speed.
And it's bulletproof.
242...
Am I the only one aroused right now?
It's, like, you know what I am saying?
Whatever.
Where does he keep it?
In his penthouse. Tower number one.
Now, why in the hell would he
keep his car in his penthouse?
He's a billionaire, my friend.
He can do whatever he wants.
Now, tomorrow happens to be
the longest day of the year.
The prince wants to celebrate it
and host a party tomorrow afternoon.
So you can get us up there, right?
Sure. But, uh....
....not dressed like that.
What?
Is something wrong?
There's a billion things wrong.
But not in this moment.
You look handsome.
I feel awkward.
You and me both.
Just seeing you dressed like this
just reminds me of something.
Of what?
Old times.
You okay?
Yeah. I am fine.
Showtime.
No, no, no. Listen, man. They're
telling me they party like this every day.
On this level, they party every day.
This is crazy.
I might have to move out here.
I think I am going to start a new culture.
It's called Blarab.
You know, like "black Arab".
How are we looking, Tej?
We're almost in position.
Okay, so this is how it works.
We got to move in sync
if we're going to pull this off.
So let's go over it to make sure
everyone clearly understands their roles.
Roman, that means you.
You know what, you're being real
unprofessional right now, Tej.
The God's Eye chip is hidden in a speed
drive installed in the prince's car,
which he keeps in a safe room vault.
I make 8 to 10 plainclothes security.
Not to mention the prince....
...and his personal bodyguards.
Security cameras are clustered by the
north wall. That's where the vault is.
We got to get in that vault, we got
to tap into the security system,
which can be accessed
in the prince's bedroom.
All right, guys, I am going in.
Excuse me.
Oh, I was just looking for the...
- The party is that way.
- What?
This room is off-limit-
Now, once we're tapped in,
Ramsey and I can hack into
the network and pop the door
so you can get in and get that shit.
Wait, wait, wait. You missed a step.
What about my steps?
What am I supposed to be doing?
No, we didn't miss anything.
You're special teams.
So when we need you, do what you do best.
And that is?
Shine brightly like
only Roman Pearce can do.
See? Now we talking.
All right, Tej, I am in.
All right, find the phone jack.
The tap always runs behind that.
It's going to be a
350-megahertz CAT5e cable.
They probably got
a couple dozen back there,
but this will be the bonded pair
with the plenum coat.
English, Tej.
It will be the orange wire.
All right, ladies and gentlemen,
we are in the pilot seat.
All right, Roman.
Do whatever it is you do.
It's your birthday, right?
Are you Jasmine?
Oh, God, no. Not the birthday routine.
Take my hand. Happy birthday to you.
This way, this way.
Excuse me, so sorry.
I am coming through, sorry.
Right this way.
Listen, excuse me one second.
- My brother, my brother.
- Man, you ain't supposed to...
Sir, thank you so much.
All right, listen, people.
Please, everybody, gather around.
Understand something, right now.
Listen to what I am telling you all.
We are here to celebrate
Jasmine's 18th birthday.
Happy birthday, my dear.
Oh, I wish I didn't see that.
Ramsey, open it up for us.
Copy that. You're in.
Do you realize what this is?
Lykan HyperSport.
$3.4 million.
Zero-to-60 in less than three seconds.
There's seven of these things in the world,
and this guy keeps it locked up in a vault.
Nothing's sadder than
locking a beast in a cage.
And now I really want
to punch him in the face.
Okay.
Let's get to work.
You got this, right?
Go.
Would you believe I knocked him out
with my charm?
You ain't that charming, bitch.
No, no, no.....
Tej, your magic trick is failing.
We're losing systems.
I know.
I see it.
Tej, talk to me.
I am trying, but their security system
is locking us out.
All right, listen, ladies and gentlemen...
Oh, there he is. These are your dancers?
This is a party, baby!
Some of you all probably went
to the bathroom and noticed
that all the hairspray was missing.
Yep. She did it.
Thank you.
And we're so happy for you to be here.
You look like you got some missiles
underneath that dress. No?
He did not just...
Did you just say that?
Oh, shit! Not the gate! Not the gate!
Brian, faster!
We're playing all the defense
we can up here,
but we're going to lose.
You got to hurry up.
Thank God you showed up.
These parties bore me to death.
Guys, get out of there right now.
You have got an army heading your way.
Brian, get out! Forget it!
Tej, we're taking the car.
This is what I do. You know
what I am saying? As far as I am-
My man, what's...
Letty? Letty, talk to me. Are you okay?
Guys, I can't hold it.
I am losing the final gate.
You got to get out of there.
Tear out the dash!
Go through it.
Wait, wait, wait.
Now, just hold on, man.
Time to unleash the beast.
Let's go!
Stay with me, I got you.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Dom, cars don't fly!
Cars don't fly!
Holy shit!
No brakes!
What?
Shit!
No, no, no!
No!
- Got it!
- Get out!
Still miss the bullets, Brian?
Ah! There they are. Disaster.
I am sorry.
I get you an invite to
the most exclusive party in Abu Dhabi.
Safar...
No, no, no. You steal the host's car,
and you jump it between two buildings.
Actually, it was three buildings.
Oh! Two, insult. Three, honor.
My bad.
Well, well, well. I have to say,
you have got an interesting interpretation
there of "low-key", Mr. Toretto.
You know, Dom, I thought
we had an understanding.
Sometimes you have to play
the hand you're dealt.
That's why I prefer to be the dealer.
Good night.
Ah...
I am being kicked out of my own garage.
This is great.
Uh, may I?
Brian....
...give it to him.
All that trouble for this little...
...thing.
With all due respect, Dom,
you really did great work back there.
All of you.
All of my men are now standing by
and are fully at your disposal.
Your call.
Ramsey.
Fire it up and find me Shaw.
Oh, damn, this is crazy.
Thank you.
All right, give me a second.
What is it doing now?
It's hunting.
Hacking into the security cameras
at Etihad Towers.
That's the last place you saw Shaw,
so that's where we will start.
That's him, right there.
Wait, wait.
What are these numbers right here for?
It's bio-mapping Shaw's face.
It will run it against every camera.
Every audio device in this hemisphere.
Bingo. Looks like he's holed up here.
That's perfect.
Automated factory, no people,
lots of places to hide.
You just changed the face of manhunts
forever.
Congratulations.
Hey, can I check my email real quick?
Dawn's up in two hours.
We're going to go take down Shaw then.
Go get changed.
We should go now.
Just you, your team, and me.
I thought you said at dawn.
My guys are racers,
the best drivers in the world.
But they ain't killers.
Told you he'd say that.
I know you too well, Dom,
and I am going with you.
Well, looks like we got
a nice little hunting party.
Let's go bag a shadow.
Ten klicks out, boys.
Get ready to rock and roll.
Here we go. Weapons hot.
You ready for this?
Yeah.
I hope you're enjoying your last meal.
This is it?
This is all I warrant?
A dozen men?
I think you will find
it's more than enough.
I am ready to meet my maker.
Are you?
What were you expecting, Toretto?
To catch me off guard?
Me standing here, waving a white flag?
You ever heard the saying,
"The enemy of my enemy is my friend"?
I don't have friends. I got family.
Well, I got a lot of friends.
Two-two formation! Sheppard, peel one!
Brian, leave it!
Get down!
I got you.
God's Eye.
You didn't really think I was going
to walk in there naked, did you?
You got hit bad.
Look, Toretto.
I know you won't listen to me.
You're not going to want to hear
what I have to say.
But the truth is, you really ought to....
...try that Belgian ale, man.
It's something special.
Belgian ale, huh?
Hey, we got to get you to a hospital.
No, you're not.
I carry my own health insurance.
SOCM medics on standby.
They're already inbound.
Pull over, kid.
Dom, you got to protect Ramsey.
As long as she's alive,
she can lock them out of God's Eye,
and they know that.
That means they're not going to stop
coming until they have got her.
And this time, when they come
they're going to come with
everything they have got.
- I am not leaving you.
- You're not.
I am leaving you.
Go now, Dom.
A war is coming to us,
whether we like it or not.
If a war is coming,
we're going to face them on the streets
we know best.
I am all for winging it,
but this is crazy, man.
We got mercenaries with
some real heat on us.
I mean, I ain't scared or nothing, but...
Man, I don't even have a gun!
Gun?
We got a whole city.
And we may have more than that.
If they use God's Eye, it will tap the
cameras around town to find our location.
Which means we could plant a virus.
And then break in when they access it.
So you're talking about hacking
my hacking device. It's brilliant.
Yeah, but there's one problem.
The signal strength.
We can't start a hack on them until
they're within a two-mile range.
That's really close.
Close? These guys are military.
If they're within two miles of us,
we're already dead.
I don't know about you all,
but I didn't really plan on dying today.
Only one way to stay alive.
We play keep-away with Ramsey.
What?
They can't hit us if we keep moving.
And I will take Shaw.
So, basically, we're just gearing up
for a big game of hot potato, huh?
- Which car is the potato?
- Girl, you're the potato.
Why does it feel like
I am not going to see you again?
I will come back for that.
Promise?
Promise.
- Brian, are you okay?
- Mia, listen to me.
Something's about to go down.
And if you don't hear from me in 24 hours,
I need you to take Jack and move on.
You understand?
You understand what I am saying?
No, I can't do that, Brian.
No, I can't.
We're going to have another baby.
It's a little girl.
And she's going to need her father.
So you have to finish what you're doing
and you have to come home to her.
You have to come home to us.
I am sorry I didn't tell you before.
I was scared you'd be disappointed
with domestic life.
You know, the best decision I ever made
was stepping into the store and...
....buying that first sandwich.
It was such a bad sandwich.
I know, right? But I ate a lot of them.
Uh...
I love you, Mia.
Don't do that.
What?
The way you said it. It's like goodbye.
Say something else.
Okay. Kiss Jack for me.
I will.
I love you, Brian.
I love you, Mia.
One last ride.
Boot up God's Eye. Find them.
I am getting something.
I got a positive ID. It's Toretto.
God's Eye is placing him
at Hill and Seventh.
Should we follow him?
No. Let Shaw take care of him.
Find Ramsey.
Yes, sir.
I don't know why we got to
keep driving around like this.
Why can't we just pull over somewhere,
park, gather our thoughts in,
like, a bunker somewhere?
Because it does not work like that.
We got to stick close enough
to the bad guys
in order to get in range for Ramsey
to hack them.
But we got to be mobile enough
not to get shot like fish in a barrel.
So, do me a favor, focus on the mission
and keep us from getting killed.
Got her. Target acquired.
She's riding shotgun in a blue GT-R.
Guys, they're here.
How many cars?
Uh, none. And that's kind of the problem.
Okay, let's give them the tour.
Break on my mark.
Three, two, one.
Go!
Splitting up won't work.
Can't hide from God's Eye.
They're in range.
Ramsey, start the hack.
Initiating.
Now.
Sir, I think someone's trying to
hack the system.
It's Ramsey.
Send in the Predator! Take her out!
Releasing Predator.
I think we lost the chopper.
I think we got
bigger problems than that!
Oh, my God.
What are you doing?
We're going old school!
Watch out!
It's coming back around!
Predator's back on him.
- Ready missiles!
- Roger that.
Fire!
Oh, shit!
Football's hot! I need to lateral!
Rom, where are you?
Running back charging in!
Meet me on Third and Spring.
You got it!
I am halfway there.
- Grab your computer! Get in the window!
- Why?
Do it! Now!
You got to go! Right now!
Fire!
Come on!
Hit!
He made it!
I can't believe we pulled that off.
Wait, wait, wait.
- We're still being hacked.
- What?
God's Eye is still tracking Ramsey.
Keep the drone in pursuit of her. The
signal has to be coming from somewhere.
Back to throw.
Here comes the blitz. Number 94 sacks him!
Breaking news out of Los Angeles tonight.
In what can only be described
as vehicular warfare,
police are engaged in
a high-speed pursuit...
I got it. They're piggybacking the hack
off that satellite tower right there.
Take it out!
Toretto.
Wait. What happened? We were almost there.
They have cut the signal!
I can't finish the hack!
What do you mean?
Brian, they took out the tower!
Dad, what's going on?
Daddy's got to go to work.
All right, baby girl.
Elena's going to be here in a little bit.
You know our drill.
Give me three for the road.
You thought
this was going to be a street fight?
You're goddamn right it is.
There has to be another way.
Wait. I am seeing half a dozen
cell towers between Sixth and State.
Brian, if you can get to the top of
any one of those buildings around there,
we can reroute the signal manually
and finish the job.
I am on it.
Sir, did you hear that? O'Conner
is on foot, heading for a repeater.
He's going to try to reinitiate the hack.
Keep the drone on the girl.
Kiet, O'Conner's on foot somewhere
between Sixth and State.
Don't let him make it there.
Them boys is on us!
Man, them boys ain't ready for this!
Shit!
First the tank, then the plane.
Now we got a spaceship?
That's not a spaceship, that's a drone!
Oh, it's a drone?
Now, you going to break it down
and be articulate
like you already know
what the hell is going on?
Shut your ass up and drive the car!
Letty, the football's on fire!
We need help!
Hang on! I am coming!
Ramsey, get ready to go again!
Drone has missile lock.
Fire!
Target destroyed.
Let's see if we have a connection.
If I can get back in...
Wait, wait, wait! God's Eye still has her.
How can that be?
Get up. Come on!
Let's go! Let's go!
They switched her under the bridge.
What?
Got to get out of here.
It's on your trail and it's coming fast.
Got it.
So, if this car goes down,
who's coming to save us?
Save us, honey? We're it.
Where are they now?
Six blocks east, hauling ass.
Where are we headed, Tej?
There's a service elevator
past the maintenance sector.
It will take you
directly up to the repeater.
Brian, you got to hurry!
Too slow!
It's coming back!
We will lose them in the tunnel.
Got it.
Fire!
I can't shake this thing!
Predator has missile lock.
Take it out!
No way.
Wait! What happened?
Sir, someone just double-tapped our drone.
What?
Hey, did you bring the cavalry?
Woman, I am the cavalry.
Of course you are.
Who is that?
That's Hobbs.
I am at the repeater.
The access cable's in the base.
Just plug it into your phone
and Ramsey will be back online.
Ramsey, go!
Brian did it. We're back in!
We have got God's Eye back.
We lost the God's Eye!
What? Shit!
Military's inbound.
Three minutes and closing.
We need to get the hell out of here.
Tej, Roman, I am on my way!
All right, homie, I will see you there.
I have eyes on Toretto.
Shaw is in the way.
Then it seems our friendship is at an end.
Do it!
Thing about street fights....
...the street always wins.
Goodbye, Toretto.
Take him out! Take down the bastard!
This son of a...
No!
Duck!
I need some help over here!
We're getting nailed!
I need some backup!
No! No! Son of a bitch!
He's getting away!
No! Stop him!
Don't miss.
Dom!
Come on, buddy.
Is he breathing?
I want you to keep his head tilted up,
all right? Keep it back like this.
Pinch his nose, keep his head tilted.
Breathe into him, now. Go.
Good. Come on, Dom.
Come on, Dom. Come on!
God damn it! You come on! You breathe!
Go, go! Breathe.
Come on. Damn it. Let's go.
Come on, Dom, I need you to breathe.
Come on! Come on, Dom!
- Come back! Come on, buddy.
- Stop it.
Dom, come on! Come on!
Back off!
Will you stop? Breathe into him.
- Get off of him!
- You breathe into him!
- Back off!
Back off!
Please.
Dom.
Dom, baby.
I know you're hurting right now.
But I want you to listen.
Stay awake.....
....and focus on me.
I remember everything.
It came to me like a flood.
I remember that night
in the Dominican Republic.
The night we got married.
Oh, my...
Will this do?
We have eternity in this moment.
You will never be alone again.
I vow wherever you go, I go.
You ride, I ride.
You fight, I fight.
And if you ever die on me, Dominic Toretto,
I am going to die with you.
I love you, Letty. I will always love you.
If you die, I die.
And I am not ready to leave this place yet.
This moment is still ours.
I remember everything.
I remember it all.
It's about time.
Why didn't you tell me we were married?
Because you can't tell someone
they love you.
Holy shit.
You sure you brought enough backup
with you, Hobbs?
Oh, they ain't mine.
They're here to protect you...
...from me killing your ass.
You do know none of this
will keep me, right?
Well, once you dig through
38 feet of concrete and steel,
my fist and a body bag will be
waiting for you on the other side.
So I suggest you get to digging, boy.
Whoo-hoo....
Daddy! Come play.
Yeah.
Look at him. Look at him.
Yeah, buddy.
- Duty calls. It does.
- Hey, babe, come on.
Let's get Mama. Yeah!
Here we go.
Because the sun is out,
I am kind of medium rare,
but I can get, like, well done.
Like, really dark.
What you nudging me for?
Close your mouth for two seconds.
Just open your eyes, man.
Beautiful.
That's where he belongs.
Home.
Where he's always belonged.
Things are going to be different now.
One more time.
You aren't going to say goodbye?
It's never goodbye.
Hey. You thought you could leave
without saying goodbye?
I used to say I live my life
a quarter-mile at a time.
And I think that's why we were brothers.
Because you did, too.
This is your car.
My car?
It's official. You're all free.
Home sweet home.
What's happening, dude?
Thanks for the invite.
Want to go for a drive?
No matter where you are,
whether it's a quarter-mile away...
...or halfway across the world,
the most important thing in life
will always be the people in this room.
Right here, right now.
Salud mi familia.
Salud.
You will always be with me.
And you will always be my brother.