- You all right?
- Hmm.
Never been north before?
Never seen snow before.
Beautiful, eh?
I can breathe again.
Down south,
the air smells like pigshit.
You've never been down south.
- I've been to Winterfell.
- That's the North.
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
GENDRY: How'd you live up here?
How'd you keep
your balls from freezing off?
TORMUND: You got to keep moving.
That's the secret.
Walking's good.
Fighting's better.
Fucking's best.
There's not a living woman
within a 100 miles of here.
We have to make do
with what we've got.
(SOFTLY)
This one is maybe not so smart.
Davos says he's a strong fighter.
Good.
That's more important
than being smart.
Smart people don't come up here
looking for the dead.
So, you met this Dragon Queen, huh?
And?
And she'll only fight beside us
if I bend the knee.
You spent too much time
with the free folk.
Now you don't like kneeling.
Mance Rayder was a brave man.
A proud man.
The King-beyond-the-Wall
never bent the knee.
How many of his people died
for his pride?
You still mad at us, boy?
You sold me to a witch.
Priestess.
I'll admit,
it is a subtle distinction.
We're fighting a great war.
- Wars cost money.
- I wanted to be one of you.
I wanted to join the Brotherhood
but you sold me off.
Like a slave.
Do you know what she did to me?
She strapped me down on a bed,
she stripped me naked...
Sounds all right so far.
...and put leeches on me.
Was she naked, too?
She needed your blood.
Yes, thank you, I know that.
Could have been worse.
She wanted to kill me.
In fact, they would have killed me
if it wasn't for Davos...
But they didn't, did they?
So what you whinging about?
I'm not whinging.
Your lips are moving, and
you're complaining about something.
That's whinging.
This one's been killed six times.
You don't hear him bitching about it.
Good lad.
JON: The first time I went north
of the Wall was with your father.
He was a good man.
He deserved a better son.
Were you with him at the end?
I was a prisoner of the wildlings.
But we avenged him.
I want you to know that.
Every mutineer found justice.
Can't think of a worse way
for him to go.
The Night's Watch was his life.
He would have died to protect
every one of those men.
And they butchered him.
I hate that he died that way.
My father was
the most honorable man I ever met.
He was good, all the way through.
And he died
on the executioner's block.
Your father wanted
to execute me, you know.
I heard.
He was in the right, of course.
Didn't make me hate him any less.
Glad he didn't catch you.
Me, too.
Your father gave me this sword.
Changed the pommel
from a bear to a wolf.
But it's still Longclaw.
Lord Commander Mormont
thought you'd never
come back to Westeros.
But you are back.
And it's been in your family
for centuries.
It's not right for me to have it.
He gave it to you.
I'm not his son.
I brought shame onto my house.
I broke my father's heart.
I've forfeited the right
to claim this sword.
It's yours.
May it serve you well,
and your children after you.
(SIGHS)
Father used to watch us from up here.
He wouldn't say much.
You probably don't remember.
You were inside knitting all the time.
I remember.
One time, the boys were
shooting arrows with Ser Rodrik.
I came out here after
and Bran had left his bow behind.
Just lying on the ground.
Ser Rodrik would have cuffed him
if he saw.
There was one arrow in the target.
There was no one around.
Just like now.
No one to stop me.
So I started shooting.
And every shot, I had to go up there
and get my one arrow and walk back
and shoot it again.
I wasn't very good.
Finally, I hit the bull's-eye.
Could have been the 20th shot,
or the 50th.
I don't remember.
But I hit the bull's-eye,
and I heard this...
I looked up,
and he's standing right here,
smiling down at me.
I knew what I was doing
was against the rules.
But he was smiling
so I knew it wasn't wrong.
The rules were wrong.
I was doing what I was
meant to be doing and he knew it.
Now he's dead.
Killed by the Lannisters.
With your help.
What?
That's your pretty handwriting.
Septa Mordane
used to crack my knuckles
'cause I couldn't write
as well as you.
"Robb, I write to you today
with heavy heart.
"Our good king Robert is dead.
"Killed from wounds
he took in a boar hunt..."
You don't have to read it. I remember.
"Father has been charged with treason.
"He conspired with Robert's brothers
against my beloved Joffrey
"and tried to steal his throne.
"The Lannisters are treating me well
and providing me with every comfort.
"I beg you, come to King's Landing,
"swear fealty to King Joffrey,
and prevent any strife
"between the great houses
of Lannister and Stark.
"Your faithful sister, Sansa."
- They forced me to do it.
- Did they?
With a knife at your throat?
Did they put you on the rack
and stretch you
until your bones started to pop?
You don't know what it was like.
I was a child.
So was I.
I would have let them kill me
before I betrayed my family.
They told me it was the only way
to save Father.
And you were stupid enough
to believe them.
(SCOFFS)
I remember you.
Standing on the platform
with Joffrey and Cersei
while they dragged Father
to the block.
I remember the pretty dress
you were wearing,
I remember the fancy way
you did your hair.
- You were there?
- I was there.
Standing in the crowd
near Baelor's statue.
And what did you do?
Did you come running to the rescue?
Did you fight off the Lannisters
and save Father?
- I wanted to.
- But you didn't.
Just like me.
I didn't betray him.
I didn't betray Robb.
I didn't betray our entire family
for my beloved Joffrey!
You should be on your knees
thanking me.
We're standing in Winterfell again
because of me.
You didn't win it back.
Jon didn't win it back.
He lost the Battle of the Bastards.
The Knights of the Vale won the battle
and they rode north for me.
While you were off, where?
Traveling the world?
I was training.
Training.
Well, while you were training,
I suffered things
you can never imagine.
Oh, I don't know about that.
I can imagine quite a lot.
You never would have survived
what I survived.
I guess we'll never know.
What are you going to do
with that letter?
I don't know yet.
Who did you show it to?
Where did you find it?
You're scared, aren't you?
What are you scared of?
You didn't commit any crimes.
No one's going to hang you.
- Arya...
- You're scared I'll show it to Jon
and he'll be angry.
No, that's not Jon.
He'll understand,
you were just a scared little girl.
All alone with the wicked Lannisters.
Do you know how happy Cersei would be
right now if she saw us fighting?
This is exactly what she wants,
it's what she's always wanted,
to tear us apart.
You're scared the Northern lords
will read it.
They wouldn't think much of Lady Sansa
if they knew how she did
Cersei's bidding.
What would little Lyanna Mormont say?
She's younger than you were,
when you wrote this.
Are you going to say,
"But I was just a child"?
You're angry.
Sometimes anger makes people
do unfortunate things.
Sometimes fear makes them
I'll go with anger.
You're the one they call the Dog.
- Fuck off.
- (CHUCKLES)
They told me you were mean.
Were you born mean,
or you just hate wildlings?
I don't give two shits
about wildlings.
- Gingers, I hate.
- Gingers are beautiful.
We are kissed by fire.
Just like you.
Don't point your fucking finger at me.
Did you trip into the fire
when you were a baby?
I didn't trip, I was pushed.
And ever since, you've been mean.
Will you fuck off?
I don't think you're truly mean.
You have sad eyes.
You want to suck my dick, is that it?
"Dick"?
- Cock.
- Ah.
Dick.
I like it.
I bet you do.
TORMUND: Nope, it's pussy for me.
I have a beauty waiting for me
back in Winterfell.
If I ever get back there.
Yellow hair,
blue eyes,
the tallest woman you've ever seen.
Almost as tall as you.
Brienne of Tarth.
You know her?
You're with Brienne of fucking Tarth?
Well, not with her yet.
But I see the way she looks at me.
HOUND: How does she look at you?
Like she wants to carve you up
and eat your liver?
You do know her.
We've met.
I want to make babies with her.
Think of them. Great big monsters.
They'd conquer the world.
How did a mad fucker like you
live this long?
I'm good at killing people.
You don't look much like him.
Who's that?
Your father.
I suppose you favor your mother.
You knew him?
Of course I did. When he was Hand,
he sent me off hunting
for the Mountain.
Your wildling friend told me
the Red Woman brought you back.
Thoros has brought me back six times.
We both serve the same lord.
I serve the North.
The North didn't raise you
from the dead.
The Lord of Light never spoke to me.
I don't know anything about him.
I don't know what he wants from me.
He wants you alive.
Why?
I don't know.
That's all anyone can tell me.
"I don't know."
So what's the point in serving a god
if none of us knows what he wants?
I think about that all the time.
I don't think it's our purpose
to understand.
Except one thing.
We're soldiers.
We have to know
what we're fighting for.
I'm not fighting so some man or woman
I barely know can sit
on a throne made of swords.
So, what are you fighting for?
Life.
Death is the enemy.
The first enemy, and the last.
But we all die.
The enemy always wins.
And we still need to fight him.
That's all I know.
You and I won't find much joy
while we're here.
But we can keep others alive.
We can defend those
who can't defend themselves.
"I am the shield
that guards the realms of men."
Maybe we don't need to understand
any more than that.
Maybe that's enough.
Aye.
HOUND: That's what I saw in the fire.
A mountain like an arrowhead.
THOROS: Are you sure?
We're getting close.
DAENERYS:
Do you know what I like about you?
I honestly don't.
You're not a hero.
Oh.
I've been heroic on occasion.
I once charged through the Mud Gate
of King's Landing and...
DAENERYS:
I don't want you to be a hero.
Heroes do stupid things, and they die.
Drogo, Jorah, Daario, even this...
Jon Snow.
They all try to outdo each other.
Who can do the stupidest,
bravest thing.
TYRION: It's interesting,
these heroes you name.
Drogo, Jorah, Daario, even this...
Jon Snow.
They all fell in love with you.
Jon Snow's not in love with me.
TYRION: Oh, my mistake.
I suppose he stares at you longingly
because he's hopeful
for a successful military alliance.
He's too little for me.
I didn't mean...
As heroes go, he is quite little.
I know you're brave.
I wouldn't have chosen
a coward as my Hand.
So...
If all goes well,
I'll finally get to meet your sister.
From everything
you've told me about her,
she'd rather murder me
than speak with me.
Oh...
First she'd torture you
in some horrible way,
then she'd murder you.
Nobody trusts my sister
less than I do, believe me.
But if we go to the capital,
we'll go with two armies,
we'll go with three dragons.
Anyone touches you,
King's Landing burns down
to the foundation stones.
And right now she's thinking
of how to set a trap.
Of course she is.
And she's wondering what trap
you're laying for her.
DAENERYS: Are we?
Laying any traps?
If we want to create
a new and better world,
I'm not sure deceit and mass murder
is the best way to start.
Which war was won
without deceit and mass murder?
Yes, you'll need to be ruthless
if you're going to win the throne.
You'll need to inspire
a degree of fear.
But fear is all Cersei has.
It's all my father had, and Joffrey.
It makes their power brittle.
Because everyone beneath them
longs to see them dead.
Aegon Targaryen got
quite a long way on fear.
He did.
But you once spoke to me
of breaking the wheel.
Aegon built a wheel.
If that's the kind of queen
you want to be,
how are you different
from all the other tyrants
that came before you?
So we walk into the lion's den.
My brother promised me he'd keep
a grip on the Lannister forces.
Forgive me, but I don't care
about any Lannister promises.
Except yours.
And I promised him I'd keep you
from doing anything impulsive.
Impulsive?
This will be a difficult negotiation.
We are sitting down with people
who want to see us both headless.
My sister's likely to say
something provocative.
And?
And you have been known
to lose your temper from time to time.
As all great leaders do.
When have I lost my temper?
Burning the Tarlys, for instance.
DAENERYS: That was not impulsive.
That was necessary.
- Perhaps.
- Perhaps?
Perhaps the father needed to die,
and not the son.
Perhaps they both needed
time to contemplate their mistakes
in the solitude of a cold cell.
We had no time
to discuss the possibilities
before you ended their possibilities.
One could be forgiven for thinking
you're taking your family's side
in this debate.
I am taking their side.
You need to take your enemy's side
if you're going to see things
the way they do.
And you need to see things
the way they do
if you're going to anticipate
their actions,
respond effectively, and beat them.
Which I want you to do very much.
Because I believe in you
and in the world you want to build.
But the world you want to build
doesn't get built all at once.
Probably not in a single lifetime.
How do we ensure your vision endures?
After you break the wheel, how do
we make sure it stays broken?
You want to know who sits
on the Iron Throne after I'm dead.
Is that it?
You say you can't have children.
But there are other ways
of choosing a successor.
The Night's Watch has one method.
The ironborn, for all
their many flaws, have another.
We will discuss the succession
after I wear the crown.
Your Grace, I saw hundreds of arrows
fly towards you
when you fought
on the Blackwater Rush.
And I saw hundreds of arrows miss.
But any one of them could have
found your heart and ended you.
You've been thinking about my death
quite a bit, haven't you?
Is this one of the items you discussed
with your brother in King's Landing?
I'm trying to serve you
by planning for the long term.
Perhaps if you planned
for the short term,
we wouldn't have lost
Dorne and Highgarden.
We will discuss the succession
after I wear the crown.
(WIND HOWLING)
Look.
HOUND: A bear.
Big fucker.
Do bears have blue eyes?
(PANTING)
(GROWLS)
(ROARING)
(SCREAMING)
(ROARS)
(YELLING)
(SCREAMS)
We have to get him back to Eastwatch.
(WEAKLY) Flask.
(SOFTLY) Go on.
(THOROS WINCING)
(WOUNDS SIZZLING)
(THOROS PANTING)
You all right?
I just got bit by a dead bear.
Aye. You did.
Funny old life.
Right then.
We're off.
- Where did she get it?
- I don't know.
She seems very resourceful.
You're worried.
We're asking 20,000 men
to fight with us
in the worst winter
any of them have ever seen.
The weather will be
the least of their problems.
I mean, many of them will be happy
to find a good reason to go home.
- You question their loyalty?
- Their loyalty is to Jon.
Jon is not here.
I haven't heard from him in weeks.
You're the Lady of Winterfell.
The King chose you
to rule in his absence.
And rule you have.
Wisely.
Ably.
They see that. They respect you.
Some may even prefer you.
Yes, they turned their backs on Jon
when it was time to retake Winterfell,
then they named him their king
and now they're ready
to turn their backs on him again.
How far would you trust men like that?
They're all bloody wind vanes.
If they found out
that I wrote that letter,
a woman who's already married not one
but two enemies of her house,
by the time Jon comes back,
he'll have no army left.
Arya's not like them.
She's your sister.
You may have disagreements
but she would never betray her family.
She would if she thought
I was going to betray Jon.
Is that what she thinks?
I don't know what she thinks.
I don't know her anymore.
Perhaps Lady Brienne could help.
She's sworn to protect
both of Catelyn Stark's girls.
Is she not?
She is.
And if one of you were planning
to harm the other in any way,
wouldn't she be honor bound
to intercede?
She would.
Something I've always wanted to know.
All right.
How drunk were you when you
charged through the breach on Pyke?
If I'm being honest, I don't remember
charging through the breach.
Some of the lads told me about it
the next morning.
- Sounded like a good scrap.
- Aye.
It was a proper scrap.
The ironborn thought
you were some kind of god.
The way you were
waving that flaming sword.
I thought you were the bravest man
I ever saw.
Just the drunkest.
(CLANGING NOISES IN DISTANCE)
Where's the rest of them?
If we wait long enough,
we'll find out.
(ALL YELLING)
(CHOKING)
(JON GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(WIGHT SNARLING)
(SCREECHES)
(MUFFLED SCREECHING)
(DISTANT SCREECHING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Run back to Eastwatch.
Get a raven to Daenerys,
tell her what's happened.
I'm not leaving you.
You're the fastest. Go! Now!
You're faster without the hammer.
Give it.
Give it!
Come on!
(ICE CRACKS)
Stop!
(SNARLING)
Go!
(PANTING)
(GATE OPENS)
What happened?
Where are the others?
(WEAKLY) Raven...
We need to send a raven!
Get the maester! Now!
(WIGHT SNARLING)
(WIGHT SCREECHES)
(SNARLING IN DISTANCE)
Thoros.
They say it's one
of the better ways to go.
BERIC: Lord of Light,
show us the way.
Come to us in our darkness
and lead your servant into the light.
We have to burn his body.
We'll all be close behind him,
unless the Lord of Light is
kind enough to send us a bit of fire.
BERIC: Lord of Light,
come to us in our darkness.
For the night is dark
and full of terrors.
(SWORD SIZZLES)
(FIRE CRACKLING)
We'll all freeze soon,
and so will the water.
When you killed the White Walker,
almost all the dead
that followed it fell. Why?
Maybe he was the one who turned them.
We can go for the Walkers,
maybe we'll stand a chance.
No.
We need to take that thing
back with us.
There's a raven
flying for Dragonstone now.
Daenerys is our only chance.
No. There's another.
Kill him.
He turned them all.
You don't understand.
The Lord brought you back.
He brought me back.
No one else, just us.
Did he do it to watch us
freeze to death?
Careful, Beric. You lost your priest.
This is your last life.
I've been waiting for the end
for a long time.
Maybe the Lord brought me here
to find it.
Every lord I've ever met's
been a cunt.
Don't see why the Lord of Light
should be any different.
WOLKAN: My lady.
My lady?
It's an invitation.
To King's Landing.
My lady,
you are the Lady of Winterfell.
I am.
And you will represent my interests
at this gathering as you see them.
They invited you. They want you there.
I will not set foot in King's Landing
while Cersei Lannister is queen.
They want another Stark prisoner,
they can come and take me.
Until then,
I'll remain where I belong.
I have work to do here.
BRIENNE: It's not safe.
Well, Ser Jaime will be there.
You said
he treated you honorably before.
I'm not worried about me.
It's not safe
leaving you with Littlefinger.
(SIGHS) I have many guards who'd
happily imprison him or behead him
whether or not you're here.
BRIENNE: And you trust their loyalty?
You trust he hasn't been speaking
to them all behind your back?
Let me at least leave Podrick behind
to watch over you.
He has become a competent swordsman...
I do not need to be watched over
or minded or cared for.
I'm not a child. I'm the Lady
of Winterfell and I'm home.
This is the safest place for me.
My lady.
I swore an oath
to protect you and your sister.
If I abandon you...
The trip to King's Landing
is long, Lady Brienne,
and you won't be traveling
on summer roads.
The sooner you leave, the better
your chances of making it on time.
Yes, my lady.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(LOW GROWLING)
TYRION: You can't.
The most important person in the world
can't fly off to
the most dangerous place in the world.
Who else can?
No one.
They knew the risks when they left.
You can't win the throne
if you're dead.
You can't break the wheel
- So what would you have me do?
- Nothing.
Sometimes nothing
is the hardest thing to do.
If you die, we're all lost.
Everyone. Everything.
You told me to do nothing before
and I listened to you.
I'm not doing nothing again.
(ROARING)
(GRUNTS)
Dumb cunt.
Oh, fuck.
(YELLS)
(GROWLS)
(SCREECHES)
Fall back!
Come on!
(YELLING)
Help me!
(SCREAMING)
(ROARING)
Jon!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(ROARING)
Go!
Go now! Leave!
(GASPING)
(STRAINING)
(WHEEZING)
Uncle Benjen. How?
You ride for the pass.
- Come with me.
- There's no time.
Go!
We'll meet again, Clegane.
Fucking hope not.
(DRAGON SCREECHES)
It's time to go, Your Grace.
A bit longer.
(HORN BLOWS)
(MAN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
MAN: Open the gate!
- ARYA: Not what you're looking for?
- (GASPS)
I have hundreds of men here
at Winterfell, all loyal to me.
They're not here now.
What are these?
ARYA: My faces.
- Where did you get them?
- In Braavos.
While I was training to be
a Faceless Man.
What does that mean?
Back in Braavos,
before I got my first face,
there was a game we used to play.
The Game of Faces.
It's simple.
I ask you a question about yourself,
and you try to make lies
sound like the truth.
If you fool me, you win.
If I catch a lie, you lose.
Let's play.
I don't want to play.
How do you feel about Jon being king?
Is there someone else you think
should rule the North instead of him?
Those faces, what are they?
You want to do the asking?
Are you sure?
The Game of Faces
didn't turn out so well
for the last person
who asked me questions.
Tell me what they are.
We both wanted to be other people
when we were younger.
You wanted to be a queen.
To sit next to a handsome young king
on the Iron Throne.
I wanted to be a knight.
To pick up a sword like Father
and go off to battle.
Neither of us got to be
the other person, did we?
The world doesn't just let
girls decide
what they're going to be.
But I can now.
With the faces, I can choose.
I can become someone else.
Speak in their voice.
Live in their skin.
I could even become you.
I wonder what it would feel like
to wear those pretty dresses,
to be the Lady of Winterfell.
All I'd need to find out
is your face.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I wish I could take it back.
I wish we'd never gone.
I don't.
If we hadn't gone,
I wouldn't have seen.
You have to see it to know.
Now I know.
The dragons are my children.
They're the only children
I'll ever have.
Do you understand?
We are going to destroy
the Night King and his army.
And we'll do it together.
You have my word.
Thank you, Dany.
Dany?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Who was the last person
to call me that?
I'm not sure, was it my brother?
Mmm.
Not the company you want to keep.
All right.
Not "Dany."
How about "my queen"?
I'd bend the knee, but...
What about those
who swore allegiance to you?
They'll all come to see you
for what you are.
I hope I deserve it.
You do.
You should get some rest.
(JON SIGHS)
(CHAINS CLANKING)