I think that in this world,
and in the real medieval world
marriage was definitely
politics by other means.
It was one of the
prime sources of glue
that held people together
in larger societies.
And one of the
fundamental things
that sets up the whole
drama of our series.
Marriage was a way to
bind two families together.
It was a form of
political alliance.
And royal marriages are one of
the ultimate in examples of this.
Sync and transcript by lost0ne
www.addic7ed.com
The Gods are good
Sir Lorus, I will gladly
wed your sweet sister.
You will be my queen,
and I will love you
from this day,
until my last day.
[Cheering and applause]
The real bomb that goes off
in Kings Landing in season 3,
is the arrival of the Tyrells
They're very powerful,
they're very wealthy.
And they control
a lot of cards.
So the family dynamic
between the Lannisters
and the Tyrells,
is quite charged.
Joffrey and Margaery's marriage
had nothing to do with
love or even affection,
it was purely about
stabilising the kingdoms,
and lessens the chance
of some kind of uprising that we
saw start to take place in season 2.
Tell me what you think of her.
With the Tyrells beside us
we'll crush the northerners.
Hang their lords,
burn their strongholds,
sow their fields with salt,
and no one will think of
rebelling for another century.
He's not even thinking
of Margaery as a woman
he's thinking of her as
an abstract principle
that will help further their
families political aim.
It just make Tyrons
job much much easier.
The Tyrells allow them to
solidify their hold on the South.
I have seven kingdoms
to look after
and three of them
are in open rebellion.
His prime objective is to ensure
the survival of the Lannisters
and maintain the status quo
and only change it
for the betterment for him and
the rest of the Lannister clan.
And the way to ensure your legacy
and so forth is through marriage.
For the Tyrells I think the idea
that their eldest daughter
is going to be queen is
immensely attractive.
Margaerys clearly got a hunger,
and is incredibly ambitious.
Do you want to be a queen?
No.
I want to be the queen.
Margaery knows exactly
how to play the game
better than almost anybody else
She of course is
the granddaughter
of one of the great matriarchs
in our world: Olenna Tyrell.
She is the mother of the present
Lord of Highgarden:
Mace Tyrell.
And, she is a very sharp lady.
I want you to tell me the truth,
about this royal boy.
We've heard some troubling tales.
Is there any truth to them?
Sansa is an interesting girl
you know shes beautiful
and she comes
from a famous family
and I want to find out about all sorts
of levels of information definitely.
I think they want to get to
the top, by hook or by crook.
That's part of the fun, isn’t it.
She realises that Sansa
is a very valuable piece
in the Game of Thrones.
So far as the realm knows,
Bran and Rickon are dead.
Therefore:
If Robb Stark falls, Sansa Stark
is the key to the North
I believe I have a
possible solution.
Their plan is to get
Sansa to marry Sir Loras,
the Knight of Flowers.
But there are a lot of spies,
there are a lot of listening ears so...
before they can really
put their plan in motion
the Lannisters get wind of this.
We need to act first and
kill this union in it's crib.
And how do we do that?
We find Sansa Stark
a different husband.
- Wonderful
- Yes, it is.
Tyrion is in love with
Shae at this moment
but he's forced
into this marriage
that I really don't
want to be a part of.
But at least if he marries
Sansa he can protect her.
Especially from Joffrey.
All you have to do is get
a son in the Stark girl.
He'll be Lord
of Winterfell one day.
You can rule the North
in his name.
You'll have two women and a
whole kingdom of your own.
And then, Tyron turns the
tables onto Cersei and says
and says she has an
arranged marriage as well.
I am Queen Regent,
not some broodmare.
You're my daughter!
You will do as I command
and you will marry Loras Tyrell
and put an end
to the disgusting rumors
about you, once and for all.
My children.
Now the Lannisters
will control the South
as well as the North.
As well as the Iron Throne, it's all
for the glory of House Lannister.
My mother always told me
you Westerosi were a grim lot.
Grim, stinking barbarians
that would row
across the Narrow Sea
and steal us from our beds.
Did you ever think
you'd marry one?
When we first meet
Robb Stark in season 3
the tables have
changed somewhat.
Robb is in a very difficult position
he was engaged to one of the Frays
but he's followed his heart not
his head, he married Talisa.
And by breaking his vow
he's angered a once
very powerful ally.
If I had the sense
the Gods gave a fish,
I'd hand you both
over to the Lannisters.
- Why don't you?
- Stark, Tully,
Lannister, Baratheon,
give me one good reason
why I should waste
a single thought on any of you?
Walder Fray could have remained
neutral in this conflict and
that had it's own risks,
but he saw an opportunity to
vastly enhance the *** of
House Frey, and he took it.
So now what he
cares about is
the political contract
that was violated.
This is not a world where
the idea of marrying for love
makes any sense to anybody.
Cat has this
instinctive feeling.
Talisa is the catalyst that
starts the demise almost.
For a king to break his word
is something that she just
can not really accept.
Because in this world,
nothing goes unanswered
Walder Fray is a
dangerous man to cross.
- You arranged it.
- And you agreed to it.
You gave him your word.
Treat your oaths recklessly and
your people will do the same.
The decision to marry Talisa
definitely divided Robb's bannermen
they're gonna be
the people who say
I pledge my allegiance
to this person
and I'm gonna stick with
him, no matter what.
They're also gonna be the
people who wonder maybe
I need to reassess who
he is, as a leader.
Yo don't think we can win.
I think you lost this war
the day you married her!
After Robb married Talisa
I think things changed,
we lost some of
our men, my army are
angered at that,
and it's the one dishonorable thing
that I feel Robb has done since...
since we've got to know him.
I need men to replace the
Karstarks who marched home.
There is only one person
in this kingdom
with that kind of army who hasn't
already sided with the Lannisters.
The man whose daughter
I was supposed to marry--
Walder Frey.
Robb not only deprived Walder of
his chance to see his daughter
as queen but also, Walder still
guilty of rebelling against
Tywin in the Iron Throne.
And that puts Walder Frey
and his entire family at risk
So something that
Robb has to try to do
is mend a lot of broken bridges
and see if he can the damage
that he's done by a
lot of bad decisions
We will do whatever we can to
give Lord Frey what he needs.
Not what--
whom.
Our father requires
Lord Edmure to wed
one of his daughters.
He was due a King
to marry one of his
daughters to and...
Edmure Tully, while he is the
important person in his
own right and is the air of
the Tully household.
It's still kind of the door prize
in the political marriage race.
I've won every battle,
but I'm losing this war.
If we don't do this
and do it now,
we're lost.
It's something you see time
and again in Game of Thrones
is characters who kind of
casting off their allusions and
learning what it means to
rule and to seize power
and the truth is, all these
families see it as a tool so
whether it's the Tyrells
marrying Margaery to Joffrey,
or Tywin trying to figure out
how to insure his legacy by
marrying Tyrion to Sansa
and Cersei to Lorus.
Marriage is one of the main
tools of political maneuvering and
we're gonna see it again
and again in this world.
Sync and transcript by lost0ne
www.addic7ed.com