Cleaned, many errors corrected, missing
dialog dashes added and re-synced by Tronar
Welcome to Westeros where
the fight for the kingdom is on.
Anyone can die.
Where great families live
and die for the Iron Throne.
- Dracarys!
- Your heart is in your mouth.
Those scenes are breathtaking.
- Some are noble.
- Jon Snow's everybody's hero.
- Some are not.
- Aarrgghh!
Aw, he's so bad!
- I have her!
- So many kings and queens
- but only one can rule.
- You cannot deny her strength.
Run!
The Wall is down and
the dead are coming.
You can't have
a cliffhanger greater than that.
Oof! When's it start?
This is what Game Of Thrones does,
it sucks you in.
So let's fly through
the saga to date
and get you ready for season eight.
As season one opens,
it's the calm before the storm.
King Robert Baratheon rules
from the capital King's Landing
- but his days are numbered.
- To be king or queen in Westeros,
you sit on the
Iron Throne and you rule over
the Seven Kingdoms
from King's Landing.
Start the damn joust
before I piss myself!
He's locked in a
loveless marriage and
only chose his queen for her family's
name to hold his kingdom together.
On Robert's part,
there's no love involved.
Don't you get tired?
Every day.
It could've been anybody
and it happens to be Cersei.
I felt something
for you once you know.
- I'm very sympathetic to Cersei.
- I know.
She was completely in love with him.
She... she was in awe of him almost
and he turned into
this semi-abusive drunk.
Was it ever possible for us?
Was there ever a time,
ever a moment?
No.
You may think, initially,
'Oh, that poor
'lady married to that terrible
man.' But don't underestimate her.
This unhappy couple have three
golden-haired children to their name
but Cersei keeps
a deadly secret from Robert.
The children are not his.
The truth will be discovered
on a royal trip north
and it's here that
our story really begins.
The king has asked his old ally
Ned Stark to help him rule.
Ned and his wife Catelyn
govern the North,
fiercely loyal to the crown.
The Starks stand for loyalty,
integrity, bravery.
They are really
the moral compass of the show.
They're the good guys
and they're the ones
that you find yourself
rooting for from the start.
The couple have five children,
three sons and two daughters.
And the decimation
of this happy family
will reverberate
throughout our tale.
They're almost too
innocent for that world.
King Robert arrives
with his queen Cersei
and with them
is the whole Lannister clan.
That's Jaime Lannister,
the queen's twin brother.
Oh, the Lannisters. They're blond,
they're beautiful,
they're arrogant, so fuck them.
It's the Lannisters
who are going to introduce
a lot of trouble into the lives
of the Starks from this point.
King Robert has decided to ask
Ned to be the hand of the king.
Nine years I haven't seen you,
where have you been?
Guarding the North for you.
Robert realises that he... too late,
that he's surrounded himself
by enemies, really.
The only person he can trust is Ned.
I need you, Ned,
down at King's Landing
not up here where
you're no damn use to anybody.
More importantly, during the visit,
Bran Stark goes climbing
one day, gets to the
top of the tower and
discovers the Lannisters'
deep dark secret.
The secret is that
Cersei the queen
is actually sleeping
with her brother Jaime.
The Lannisters, oh, God!
Ugh! Oh!
Pffff! They are...
I have never seen a family...
I mean, talk about dysfunctional.
Oh!
Stop! Stop.
It's incest, which,
even in Westeros,
is generally frowned upon. It also
means that King Robert's children
are not actually his children.
It's all right.
He saw us!
I heard you the first time.
He knows what it means too
and he knows that if the incest
is discovered, not only will he
and his sister be put to death
but their three children
may very well too.
And so for Jaime Lannister,
the greatest swordsman in Westeros,
there's only one solution.
The things I do for love.
Here's a convenient way.
The kid will die,
it'll look like he fell
and our kids will be safe.
First in a coma,
Bran will later awake
with no memory of how
he fell or what he saw.
The royal secret is safe
for now and only the viewer
has seen what the
Lannisters will do to keep it.
Everything went
pear-shaped after that
and really that's the whole
chain of events starting.
King Robert still wants Ned
down in the capital,
so this will be the last ever
time we see the Stark family
all together, a family which
includes Ned's son out of wedlock,
the bastard Jon Snow.
Ned must now leave his family
and follow King Robert south,
taking his daughters
Sansa and Arya with him.
The reason I think the first
season of Game Of Thrones works
is it's essentially about this
good family that just wants to
essentially be left alone and serve
their king and their country.
The family is ripped apart and thrown
into situations they never anticipated.
They are bound for the capital
King's Landing,
where Ned's new task
will be to protect King Robert
from those who would unseat him.
And in season one, viewers learned
the greatest enemies
live in exile overseas.
The Targaryens.
They were dethroned by
King Robert in the last war.
The only surviving members
of the family
are a brother and sister
called Viserys and Daenerys.
The siblings are the children of
the Mad King who was killed in war.
Viserys dominates
his younger sister.
Viserys has more than a touch
of the Targaryen madness
and, you know,
sometimes he's protecting her
but he's also trying to treat
her as a... as a bargaining chip.
Come forward, my dear.
In search of an army,
Viserys makes a pact with
a savage tribe, the Dothraki.
Offering his beautiful young
sister in marriage to their leader,
Khal Drogo. She's the only
bargaining chip he has,
he doesn't have any wealth any more,
he doesn't have any armies
but he has her who he
can trade to this horse lord.
I would let his
whole tribe fuck you,
all 40,000 men and their horses
too, if that's what it took.
He's power hungry
but to a nasty degree.
He doesn't really care
how or by what means,
he just wants to be
important and looked up to.
But his plans backfire.
Daenerys and Khal Drogo fall in love
and become quite the power couple.
Suddenly, she finds herself, with Khal
Drogo, empowered. People are obeying her.
Tell him I want what was bargained
for or I'm taking you back.
He completely underestimates
not only Dany but Khal Drogo.
What's he saying?
He says yes.
You shall have a golden crown.
It's a real coming-of-age story
throughout the first season.
She really grows into herself.
Look away, Khaleesi.
No.
This is one of the
turning points for Daenerys.
I think this is when you
realise that she's prepared
to sacrifice anything
for the greater good.
A crown for a king.
Aarrgghh!
Aaaarrrrgggghhhh!
Argh! Ugh! Ugh!
He was revolting.
He was utterly, utterly revolting.
And that was the moment that
she escaped from her shell.
When she became the woman
and not the kowtowed girl.
And as the Targaryens grow in power,
we learn that King Robert
faces another challenge
to his northernmost borders.
Threats which led
past rulers to build
this giant wall of ice
to keep out wild things beyond.
It's protected by the
legendary Night's Watch.
The Night's Watch are a small army
who guard the northern
border of the country.
In season one, there's lots
of fighting for the throne
but actually, in the background,
there are these creatures appearing
north of the Wall that nobody
has seen for thousands of years
and no-one wants to believe they're
there but they certainly are.
We hear the characters
saying that this is all folklore,
that this is all made up
but, for the viewer,
we see that, basically,
these characters do exist.
They are there.
Ugh!
The White Walkers
are terrifying mostly because
you're not 100% sure you know
what they're capable of doing
or what their motives are.
They are a serious threat.
In season one,
in search of a purpose,
Jon Snow ventures to the Wall
and joins the Night's Watch,
a leader in the making.
Jon Snow's everybody's hero.
Jon Snow's one of my favourite
characters. He's the dude.
He's also in search of answers.
The question of Jon...
Jon Snow's parentage
has been one of the
burning topics amongst,
not only the show's fans,
but book fans for many decades.
Jon Snow is Ned Stark's bastard son.
He brought him back from a war
and we never really
learned who the mother is.
Um, understandably,
Catelyn, Ned's wife,
isn't too fond of Jon
for that reason.
Try as she may, um,
she could never make peace
with that, with the fact
that Ned was unfaithful.
But down in the capital
King's Landing,
Ned Stark has a much
greater challenge to face.
His daughter has fallen
for Prince Joffrey.
She's presented with
marrying the future king,
live in a beautiful castle,
go to banquets,
have beautiful dresses to wear.
A fairy tale story.
Ned has discovered the queen
and her brother are lovers
and this will be
his family's undoing.
When the king returns from his hunt,
I'll tell him the truth.
You must be gone by then,
you and your children.
I will not have
their blood on my hands.
Before he gets the chance to talk to King Robert,
King Robert gets killed on a hunting trip.
Joffrey is now king and without
Robert to protect him,
Ned is tried for treason.
He confesses,
believing it will save his daughter
but misjudges the new ruler.
He's been stuck up
in the North too long
and has no idea how
the real world operates,
how to really deal with the
kind of... the politics of Westeros.
Bring me his head!
You will not!
That's when you realise nobody
is safe in this world at all.
No! Stop them!
When I saw Sean Bean pushed down...
...that was the only scene that
really has brought a tear to my eye.
It's cruel, it's heartbreaking,
but there's a point
to the children witnessing this.
If they want to survive,
they have to start to be resilient.
They have to learn from this.
It was at that moment, you realised
what Game Of Thrones was really about.
It's here that the
Stark family splinters.
Arya is whisked away by a Night's
Watch brother loyal to Ned,
leaving Sansa
at the mercy of Joffrey.
Robb Stark reacts
with murderous rage
to the news that his father
has been beheaded.
Robb's the heir and he's not only
picking up his father's mantle
as Lord of Winterfell but he's
picking up a much older mantle.
The crown that no-one has worn for
300 years, the Kingdom of the North.
It will lead to all-out war
between the Starks
and the Lannisters
who are led by its patriarch
Tywin Lannister.
Tywin Lannister is one
of the great warriors
and battle strategists of the age.
His legacy is uppermost
in his mind all of the time.
In these next few months,
we could establish a dynasty
that will last a thousand years.
Or we could collapse into nothing
like the Targaryens did.
All of his hopes are in Jaime.
As well as his twins,
Cersei and Jaime,
he has a son he despises,
Tyrion, known as the Imp.
You're wounded.
Good of you to notice.
Tyrion doesn't look like a warrior.
He doesn't look like a kingmaker,
there's no way that he can
assume the position of Tywin.
I hear we won. I would say Tyrion
is one of my favourite characters.
How he's managed to last
this long is amazing to me.
As war rages in Westeros,
over the Narrow Sea,
Daenerys loses a husband
but gains astonishing new powers.
She walks into
Khal Drogo's funeral pyre
with fossilised dragon's eggs.
Oh, what an epic scene.
Season one ends
with the sight of Daenerys
emerging from a fire unscathed
with her dragons hatched.
These creatures
are extraordinary creatures,
the likes of which have not
been seen in hundreds of years.
Blood of my blood.
You see these three dragons
around her and you're, just, like,
they're gonna be awesome
when they're grown.
The innocence is gone, she's it.
You know, she's the force now.
As the dragons are born, she
comes more and more into her own
until the power
becomes innate to her.
It's about a new era. The whole
first season is essentially
the old era dying out
and the new era beginning.
And by the end,
she has a sense that she knows
that she's bound for greatness.
And after the break, watch
those dragons grow in season two.
Welcome to Westeros where
the fight for the kingdom is on.
Welcome back to Game Of Thrones,
"The Story So Far", where season two
marks a new reign of tyranny
in the capital King's Landing.
Joffrey is brutalising his subjects
as well as his bride-to-be,
Sansa Stark.
You can't!
What did you say?
Sansa has learned some
painful lessons along the way.
The chivalrous knights and gallant
princes that she dreamed of,
she got a gallant prince
and he turned out to be Joffrey.
Killing you would send
your brother a message.
She's a prisoner in the worst place
imaginable, enduring all kinds
of psychological and sometimes
physical abuse from these captors.
Leave her face.
I like her pretty.
He's a bully
and we don't like bullies.
Joffrey is the character
throughout the series
that the audience loves to hate.
I heard a disgusting lie
about uncle Jaime. And you?
He's a despicable human being.
Cersei's smart enough to
realise that Joffrey is perhaps
not what she might have hoped for
and he's getting out of her
control now and he's a danger,
in part, even to her and even
to other members of the family.
What you just did
is punishable by death.
Joffrey's enemies are everywhere.
Chief amongst them, and just
across the bay at Dragonstone,
is Stannis, brother
of the late King Robert,
who believes the throne
should be his.
Stannis has learned that Robert's
children are Lannister bastards,
which means that it is Stannis
who is next in line.
So Stannis Baratheon, who knows King
Joffrey is the product of incest,
decides to send ravens out to all
the corners of the Seven Kingdoms,
letting them know
the Lannister secret.
In order to claim the throne,
Stannis enlists
the Red Priestess, Melisandre,
who was on her own mission to find
the right ruler for Westeros.
She believes Stannis is the
saviour of the world, basically.
He's supposed to be
on the Iron Throne.
And her magical powers
have no limits, I think.
There's... There's so much that
we don't know that she can do.
However, Stannis isn't the
only one after the throne.
His younger brother, Renly,
also believes he has a claim
and so war is inevitable.
The Iron Throne is mine by right.
All those that
deny that are my foes.
The whole realm denies it,
from Dorne to the Wall.
They both think they should be king
but I'm on Stannis's side,
so screw Renly.
Rather than fight
it out on the battlefield,
Stannis finds
another way to kill his brother.
Family ties don't mean
an awful lot in Westeros.
The powerful sorcery of
the Red Priestess is revealed
when she gives birth
to a sinister weapon.
Aarrgghh!
The shadow baby is basically
just a way to kill Renly
and it comes out of me
in a great way.
I think Melisandre, she's
always lived by this religion.
If she's got something to do,
she's gonna do it
and she's not gonna let
other people stand in her way.
What I think is brilliant
about Game Of Thrones,
it's a fantasy world but it's
a completely realistic depiction of
how power works. What power does to
people, what people do to get power,
what happens when they fall short, when they
miss the mark. That's why it's so brilliant.
Ugh!
Ugh-ugh!
When Renly is murdered,
it leaves behind his widow,
Margaery Tyrell,
who belongs to the Tyrell family,
who are very rich and
powerful in their own right.
Calling yourself king
doesn't make you one
and if Renly wasn't a king,
I wasn't a queen.
She knows how to play the game. She
really knows how to play the game.
Do you want to be a queen?
No.
I want to be THE queen.
As one would-be king is extinguished,
another rises up
as season two sees a small but
vicious family enter the fray.
A seafaring house that commands the
greatest fleet of ships in Westeros.
It is led by Balon Greyjoy,
whose son Theon,
a captive of the
Starks since childhood,
has finally made it back home.
We take what is ours.
Your time with the wolves
has made you weak.
Theon Greyjoy has grown up
with the Stark family,
he was a sort of a prisoner
from a war in the past.
He now returns to his motherland,
which is the Iron Islands
and decides to betray the Starks.
You would have our father
bow down to your other family?
I have no other family!
Theon's sister Yara,
a battle-hardened warrior,
is now heir to the Iron Islands.
Yara is strong and fierce.
When Theon comes back
and stakes his claim,
she's worked too hard for this
and is not giving that up.
To prove his loyalty,
Theon invades Winterfell.
The ravens are informing
my father of my victory here.
This leaves the Stark
family home in chaos
and he takes the younger
Stark brothers captive.
Prince Theon.
I yield to Prince Theon.
Across the Narrow Sea,
Daenerys Targaryen is learning
valuable lessons
in her quest to return
to Westeros and seize the throne.
She's desperate to be a good ruler.
That she can, you know,
go to bed at night saying,
'I think I'm doing things
the right way.'
As Daenerys's power grows
so do her dragons
but as news of their
existence spreads,
they become highly sought after.
When she's in Qarth, everybody
kind of thinks, 'Who are you?
'We'll just take your dragons.
and you're not powerful any more.'
Dracarys!
People have underestimated her
the whole way.
And it is in season two
that we finally see
the dragons kill for Daenerys.
Aarrgghh!
As Daenerys gets stronger in exile,
Jon Snow and the Night's Watch
are on a mission beyond the Wall
where the true scale of the
threat to the kingdom is revealed.
Blow the horn. Somebody come.
The army of the dead is on its way
and it's gonna kick off sooner
or later and really, you know,
they've got to get out of there
as fast as they possibly can.
One blast for friends, two for foes.
And three for White Walkers.
The threat of winter
coming is very much
a myth to the people of the south.
They're not
really taking it seriously.
They don't know about the undead
and all the horrors
that are coming towards them.
Three blasts.
Come on!
So what we learn
in season two is that
the White Walkers
are very much real.
They're nothing like we've
ever seen before in television.
They're not just zombies,
they're not just statues,
they're walking
ice cubes, basically.
Um, they're, they're really
bad and they're really scary
and it's literally... I think it's
got to be a fight of ice and fire.
We have all these kingdoms
wanting to fight for the throne
and they think that that is what
ultimately the battle is about.
But really, at the end of the day,
they're not looking at
what's the real problem here
and it's the White Walkers.
And it's in season two,
in King's Landing,
where we see that Tyrion
may just be an asset
to the war when Stannis
launches an attack on the city.
I'll leave you dead.
The battle of Blackwater
was his moment.
He was the best person to speak
to the people of King's Landing
and to get them to protect their,
their... their... their city
because he knows
what it's like to fight,
he knows what it's like to have
your back up against the wall.
We like an underdog.
And when they...
When the underdog manages
to come out on top,
it's a cause for celebration.
Those are brave men
knocking at our door.
Let's go kill them!
Tyrion manages to get the
troops fired up by giving
a good speech and then
heads out with them to fight
Stannis on the bay.
He doesn't last very long,
he gets knocked out
after a couple of minutes.
Tyrion is upstaged
by his father Tywin,
who arrives with
his own massive army.
He's been bolstered by the Tyrells,
who firmly joined the cause
and they crush the Stannis attack.
Certain people
have luck on their side.
Other people don't.
Possibly Stannis is one of those...
...very, very unlucky characters
who are destined not to achieve
- their goals.
- Let's fight!
Tywin's pretty lucky.
Fortune tends to smile on him
- when it should damn him.
- Father.
And yet, against all the odds,
that battle is won.
The battle is over.
We have won.
Season three begins,
Daenerys has set sail on a mission.
She and her dragons may have
grown in power and stature
but securing an army
still eludes her.
So she ventures to a place
where she can buy one.
She knows she needs an army,
a powerful army,
if she ever wants to
reclaim the Westerosi throne
and the best bet for
that are the Unsullied.
I have dragons.
I'll give you one.
She appears to want to
trade the dragon for slaves.
She seems to have made
this daft agreement
to give away her best dragon.
She hands over the dragon.
Next thing you know,
once she has control
of the Unsullied...
...then it's very easy
to say to the dragon
who still will listen to her
and not to him, 'Burn him.'
Dracarys!
No! No! No!
Because you would take power
if you have the force of a dragon,
they're pretty impressive creatures.
She's been the mother of dragons
and knew she was destined
for greatness but now she
really is a queen with an army.
To then see that she
has thousands of people
on her team and then you get,
like, this swoop past.
She's got these, like,
fire-breathing mythical creatures
that they're
just gonna tear shit up.
As this young Targaryen
gains followers,
in King's Landing, a young
Tyrell is gaining influence.
Margaery has replaced Sansa
in Joffrey's affections,
a reward for her family's
military support at Blackwater.
I imagine it must be so exciting
to squeeze your finger here
and watch something die over there.
Margaery is a woman
who's on top of her game,
she's controlling where she's going,
she's a proper feminist icon.
But the Tyrells' ambitions
are not going down well
with Cersei Lannister. Alana
is the matriarch of the family
and she advises her granddaughter on
how best to play the political game,
so that she might
take power in King's Landing.
To make matters worse, her soulmate
Jaime is a prisoner of war.
He is held first by Brienne of Tarth
then both are captured
by a northern faction.
Looks like your woman's
getting the better of you.
This is all bundled up in when Jaime
starts thinking about other people.
- You're only making it worse.
- Argh!
His efforts to stop Brienne being
raped are the beginning of that.
You know who she is, don't you?
Argh! It's good when those
little bits of goodness
come in those characters
that are so devilish as well.
Just give you
a little light in there.
Lord Selwyn would pay
his daughter's weight
in sapphires if
she's returned to him.
It being Game Of Thrones,
it doesn't get him anywhere.
Argh! Argh! Aarrgghh!
Another one of those Game Of Thrones
moments which has so much more
going on in it than just him
losing his hand. He's the greatest
swordsman in Westeros we're told,
so he can't do that any more.
He's now made a good friend in
her and he's seen a lot of things
and I'm sure he's questioning what
being a Lannister is about as well.
Yet, without his hand, we see
Jaime Lannister at his most heroic.
The heartless knight who pushed
Bran Stark from the tower
finds new honour in season three.
He's left, he's left her behind,
he's abandoned her
and he's on his way
to King's Landing
and then his captors mention
what's gonna happen to her.
Not fair? And then he decides
to return and save her.
And it is in season three that
we witness the fearsome work
of another powerful family,
the Boltons,
who are scheming
to take control of the North.
I think the Boltons want
what everyone else seems to want,
it's power and status.
Kill me!
You're no good to me dead.
We need you.
Ramsay, a bastard son of the family,
enjoys torturing his enemies,
including Theon Greyjoy,
who he took prisoner when sacking
Winterfell after Ned's demise.
Historically, the Boltons have
always been just under the Starks,
kind of the Starks have
always been on top of them,
so I think they feel
that now is their time to rise.
You don't look like
Theon Greyjoy any more.
It's unbelievable what Ramsay
is capable of doing to people.
Freak!
He's just all about the mind.
He's all about
making you doubt yourself.
He's all about getting in there
and making you insecure
and making you feel like
you can't go up against him.
Another hostage at large
in season three is Arya Stark
kidnapped by the Hound.
The disgraced knight
plans to find Arya's family
and trade her for cash.
Remember what happens
to children who run.
One of the great double acts of Game
Of Thrones is the Hound and Arya.
Don't! Don't kill him.
There's something so perversely
magical about that pairing,
sort of warped mentor-protege
relationship that develops.
In his desire to claim a ransom,
the Hound heads for the Twins
where he knows Arya's mother
and brother, Catelyn and Robb Stark,
are attending a wedding.
The Twins is a strategic river
crossing controlled by the Frey family
and the Starks need them
on side for their war effort.
Walder Frey is a very
bitter nasty old man
who controls a small but
significant area in the kingdom.
I was pledged to marry one
of you and I broke that vow.
If he's been let down by
Robb Stark after this promise,
if he shows any kind of forgiveness
or, 'Just let it go.
'He didn't want to marry my
daughter, he married someone else.'
He would lose face in that world,
it's a vicious world
he's operating in.
The Stark family offer
Robb's uncle to make amends,
they're here for that wedding,
a terrible mistake.
Also at the wedding is Roose,
head of House Bolton.
Traditionally loyal to the Starks
but not for much longer.
Robb's decision not to marry
Walder Frey's daughter,
he knows he's alienating and going
to upset a very powerful house
and a very, very powerful man.
So he changes his allegiance.
Catelyn, in her heart,
knew that you do not break a promise
if you are the king of the North
and you certainly don't break
it to Walder Frey. Your grace...
He's probably laid awake for nights
just planning it and timing it
and working out just how
it's gonna work out.
The moment where Cat
sees that Roose Bolton
is wearing chain mail
is a powerful moment.
Why would you wear
chain mail to a wedding?
What is the purpose of chain mail?
It's to prevent you getting killed.
Robb!
Catelyn and Robb and his wife
and all the others,
nobody saw it coming.
The Red Wedding is the event
that pretty much decimates
an entire generation
of the Stark family.
Within the Game Of Thrones,
Walder Frey's not playing
the Game Of Thrones.
He's not attempting to be the king.
He's actually perfectly
happy with what he's got.
He has his own little fiefdom
and he's sitting in the chair
watching terrible things.
Robb is such an amazing character,
I think
you kind of want
him to be the king...
Mother...
..and to win.
The Lannisters send their regards.
It's brutal. 'I'm going to let you know
this information just before I kill you.'
It's another illustration of what
Tywin Lannister is prepared to do.
Aarrgghh!
And in that case, he's got somebody
else to do his dirty work.
It's the cruelty of it
and it's the relishing of it.
Everything goes to hell
at the Red Wedding.
Arya Stark arrives
at the Twins to witness
her brother's desecrated body and
loses any last shred of innocence.
She's there.
She's at the Red Wedding,
she's outside and
she was so close, you know,
she was so close to seeing
them again, she was so close.
The path that she goes on,
she learns to become stronger
and fight and also
she was after revenge.
And when she comes across
her family's killers later...
- You little shit.
- ...she matches their brutality.
She's had to go over
to the dark side,
that's what makes her interesting.
In order to survive in that world,
you have to match what is given you.
And so, by the end of season three,
all the elder Starks have
gone from the Game Of Thrones.
Only the children remain, orphaned
and scattered across Westeros,
including Bran Stark,
still paralysed from his fall.
He's fled Winterfell with a loyal
band of followers heading north.
So, Hodor we know as
a very loyal character.
- All right, Hodor?
- Hodor.
He lost the use of his legs and
Hodor's the person that carries him
around and takes him everywhere,
um, being the big giant
of a man that he is.
It's all right,
the wolves will protect him.
Him and his brother Rickon
are the two last male heirs
to the Stark household.
Um, and, yeah, it's fast depleting,
we're running out of Starks.
I think it's all about Rickon and
Bran kind of sticking together
and, you know, seeing how their
adventures and journeys play out
to kind of find this lost happiness
and this lost family
that they're searching for.
Bran Stark is very much
on his own journey to discover
the roots of this ancient
magic that's reappearing
in the kingdom
throughout the season.
And yet, amid this loss,
comes a small victory.
Unlikely hero Samwell Tarly stumbles
on a weakness of the White Walkers.
Samwell reaches for
all he has to hand,
an old dragonglass spear
he once found in the ground.
Ugh!
To his astonishment it... it works.
The spells are shattered
and it's melting before him.
And stay with us to see wedded bliss
vanish after the break. He's choking!
Welcome to Westeros where
the fight for the kingdom is on.
Welcome back to Game Of Thrones,
"The Story So Far".
We're in season four,
a royal wedding in King's Landing
unites two great houses of Westeros,
the Tyrells and the Lannisters.
Season four begins
with the wedding between
King Joffrey and Margaery Tyrell,
And as we know from
experience in Westeros,
weddings are not happy occasions.
It's full of injured parties
with scores to settle.
Chief among them is Oberyn Martell
and his lover Ellaria Sand.
In that first meeting
with Cersei and Tywin...
Ellaria Sand.
My lord, my lady.
...they see Ellaria
as being sort of scum.
Ha! I can't say
I've ever met a Sand before.
Oberyn has a zest for life and all
the beautiful things that the world
has to offer.
None of it is as beautiful
as his own rage
and taste for revenge.
Oberyn is seeking vengeance
for his sister's brutal death
at the hands of the Lannisters.
The rape and murder of women and
children is considered distasteful.
Oberyn has a massive grudge
against the Lannisters
and he's sort of coming to
the wedding to just sniff out
what's going on and to get justice.
There's been too much amusement...
Joffrey really uses
the wedding as an excuse
to be as horrible as he can.
Uncle, you can be my cup bearer.
And the way he treats Tyrion
and everybody at that table,
he's just hideous.
You're watching him
being a total arse.
And so when an unseen hand
poisons the newly wed king...
Idiots! Help your king!
Move away!
...it's the moment of retribution the whole
of the Seven Kingdoms have been waiting for.
I think everybody
who watches Game Of Thrones
was hoping this day would come.
Ugh!
I wanted to kill him
in such a way that the viewers
were reminded that here's
a 13-year-old boy who's dying.
Though it is actually the Tyrells
that have poisoned Joffrey,
it is Tyrion who is blamed.
This is really the point
where Tyrion's fragile bonds
with his family begin to unravel.
Take him! Take him!
Take him!
In plot terms, the death of Joffrey
is another shaking of the board
where the pieces are scattered.
And also it's one of those things
that elevate the whole series
from merely a story into a saga.
As the royal family grows weaker,
news from Westeros
reaches Meereen where Daenerys
has conquered the city
but she is not yet ready to
capitalise on her enemy's weakness.
King Joffrey Baratheon is dead.
Murdered at his own wedding.
This would appear
to be a really good time
for her to finally make
her play for the Iron Throne.
She has the dragons
and she has the army
and she has the
strength of character.
But actually she has
new responsibilities now
and she has unfinished
business where she is
and she's still trying
to learn how to rule.
And to compound matters,
her dragons have grown so big
that Daenerys has started
to lose control of them.
Ugh!
They get bigger as her power increases,
the harder it is for her to manage.
And that's where the
story then has to go.
All they're going to
bring is complexity.
And when one of the dragons
kills a child and abandons her,
Daenerys is left with no other
choice but to chain the other two.
She's just locked up her dragons,
so can she unleash them again
and will they forgive her?
Without the mighty
force of her dragons,
Daenerys is faced with a dilemma
as to what to do next.
She's definitely going through a
sort of a dark night of the soul,
I think, where she's trying to
determine, have I got what it takes?
And so, in season four,
as Daenerys remains in exile
across the Narrow Sea,
Sansa Stark has fled the capital
and taken refuge with her aunt Lysa,
who has been seduced
by an arch schemer.
Littlefinger is playing a very
chaotic game and he thrives on that.
Oh, my sweet wife.
For Littlefinger, it's all
about getting power, I think,
and using Lysa
as a pawn along the way.
Argh!
Sansa has witnessed Lysa's murder
and covers for Littlefinger.
Sansa's one of these
poor characters who's been
mistreated all through the series.
She's seen a lot of horrible,
horrible things happen
and she's never been able to take
control and this is the first time.
Actually, she's got
nothing else to lose.
He tried to reason with her,
promised her
she was the only woman
he'd ever loved.
But she stepped
through those doors...
What you discover is that she's
been learning this entire time.
She's been listening,
she's been watching.
She's been taking
Littlefinger's lessons to heart.
So, from one Stark
protege to another.
Sansa's sister Arya
is still the Hound's hostage
but they're now on an equal footing.
Who would pass the Bloody Gate?
The bloody Hound, Sandor Clegane.
He's her captor
but he's also her protector
and, you know, she's seen his own
pain and his own fear at times
and they've shared
some dangerous situations.
But when the Hound
is gravely injured in battle,
Arya is forced to
strike out on her own.
Fuck it! I'm ready.
Now he's wounded and he's dying
and she's remembering
all he said about mercy
and he's asking for mercy
and by mercy he means, you know,
a quick thrust to kill him.
And she doesn't give it to him.
Kill me.
She won't put him out of his misery,
she won't give him the easy way out,
she's going to leave
him there to suffer.
Another wandering Stark is
Arya's crippled brother Bran,
who has made it north of the Wall
in search of a Three-Eyed Raven
who he believes
will help him walk again.
All the time, aided by his
loyal travelling companion Hodor.
I think Hodor's more
than just Bran's legs.
I mean, I think he means a lot
to Bran, you know, someone to...
He's always been there through
absolutely everything, you know.
Even though he can't speak,
he can only say one word,
he's always someone
that's looking after him.
You know, in a world of evil, he's
probably one of the only good ones.
Clearly, Bran
is very important because
he's trekked all the way up north
to a cave where this raven
has been summoning him
for the past couple of seasons
and now he's in this cave
with the Three-Eyed Raven,
we're gonna find out what the grand
scheme of things is for Bran.
You'll never walk again.
But you will fly.
His powers, he's getting stronger
and there's gonna be some really
exciting things happening, I think.
We're gonna find out
more and more about him.
At the Wall, the Night's Watch
suffers a huge Wildling attack
at Castle Black but in season four
they get a powerful new ally.
Stannis Baratheon, who's
been away licking his wounds
after the Blackwater defeat
joins them with his vast army.
The Battle of the Blackwater
was a huge and crushing defeat
at the end of season two and it's
taken them basically two seasons
to sort of rebuild from that.
And his arrival means that Jon Snow
could have a new ally in the
battle against the White Walkers
beyond the Wall. If my father had
seen the things that I've seen,
he'd also tell you to burn
the dead before nightfall.
All of them.
Season four draws to
a mighty climax in King's Landing
when the ultimate father-and-son
showdown comes to a head.
Tyrion is tried for murder.
I'm guilty of being a dwarf.
- You're not on trial for being a dwarf.
- Oh, yes, I am.
I've been on trial
for that my entire life.
Finally, Tyrion just says,
'You know what this is about.
'It's because I'm a dwarf.'
You know.
And he's absolutely right,
that is what it's about.
He's put on trial for
a murder he doesn't commit.
His father deserts him
and betrays him.
I demand a trial by combat!
I mean, trial by combat, you can get
someone to fight for your honour,
so whether you're wrong or not,
as long as they win the fight,
that's what matters.
He names Oberyn Martell
as his champion.
You're going to fight that?
I'm going to kill that.
I think Ellaria has total faith
in the Red Viper,
her lover's powers as a fighter.
But the minute she sees
the Mountain, she doubts it.
The one thing that he's ever lived
for is to avenge his sister's death
and he knows that now that the
opportunity is presenting itself,
there is no question that
he will get what he wants.
You killed my sister!
And he does get what he wants by
forcing a confession out of him.
It's not exactly how he expected it.
Aarrgghh!
I killed her children.
He still technically
got what he wanted.
Aarrgghh!
Then I raped her. Aarrgghh!
Then I smashed
her head in like this.
Argh!
She's lost the man who was her
protector, who was her champion,
who was everything that
she believed in in her world.
Tyrion Lannister...
With his champion defeated, Tyrion's
life now hangs in the balance.
...you are hereby sentenced to death.
In Westeros, the pursuit of justice
is as futile as anything else.
Oh, get on with it,
you son of a whore.
Is that any way to
speak about our mother?
Tyrion is released from jail
by his brother Jaime
and told to go and
board a ship and run away.
Instead, he decides
to check in on his father.
Mmm!
But it's his former lover Shae
that he discovers in Tywin's bed.
Tyrion then kills Shae
in a sort of fit of jealousy
and then takes a crossbow
and goes to find his father.
Tyrion.
Put down the crossbow.
Tywin really has
had it coming to him.
Ugh!
I don't know how much more Tywin
could have got away with, really.
Especially after what
he's put Tyrion through.
- You're no son of mine.
- I am your son.
This is someone who spent his whole
life trying to win his approbation,
as much as he hated him, he
really wanted that, you know.
Obviously that's
never gonna happen now
because he put a crossbow
bolt in his groin.
Ugh! What it means, is when
a big character like that goes,
there's gonna be a power vacuum
and there's gonna be hustling
and jostling to get into his place.
I am the queen!
I am the queen! I'm not...
Join us after the break where,
in season five,
a new power rises in King's Landing.
Welcome to Westeros where
the fight for the kingdom is on.
Welcome back to "The Story So Far".
Where, in season five,
a royal wedding unsettles Cersei.
Her son Tommen is now king
and has fallen under the spell
of his new queen Margaery,
much to Cersei's dismay.
When Margaery'd come in his life,
I think he was just
enjoying life so much.
Judging from the king's enthusiasm,
the Queen Mother
- will be a queen grandmother soon.
- Wouldn't that be a lovely day?
Him being king was just a whole
new excitement, a whole new life.
Cersei empowers religious fanatics
to help her topple her rival,
Queen Margaery.
I can't hear it.
I am the queen!
Cersei brings back
the Faith Militant
because, in her mind, this is
her wiping the slate clean,
this is her taking an opportunity
to claw back a little bit of power.
But Cersei's engineered
her own downfall.
Royalty is no longer above the law
and fanatics come for her next.
It's hard to see how anybody would
be able to get the power back
from the High Sparrow
and Septa Unella.
Move. There's another
contender to power in Westeros
and it's religion.
It's the power of the faith.
They want to remove
all the excesses.
To strip Cersei of all her finery
and encourage her, in inverted
commas, to become clean.
It's such a sexualised
form of humiliation.
A sinner comes before you.
Watching Cersei
do the walk of atonement,
something happened that
I thought would never happen
and that is I felt compassion.
No matter what she'd done
previously, she didn't deserve this.
And so season five sees her
left naked before her subjects
to atone for her infidelities.
Who would've thought we
would've felt sorry for Cersei
- until the walk of shame?
- It was very, very tough for her.
Very few women could have done
what she did, complete that walk.
People love to hate her,
so you see her
trying to maintain
this regal presence
but she can't.
Stripped down to her, literally,
physically and emotionally
and psychologically, stripped
down to her most vulnerable
and then swept up into the
arms of the beast that she...
that she invited into the world.
The strange creation
that is her new knight.
It's just a brilliant twist.
When Cersei's picked up
by the Mountain
and Qyburn tells her
what's happened,
the brilliant look
across Cersei's eyes
of, 'Whatever happens,
I will get these people.'
Also getting a new ally
in season five is Daenerys,
in the form of Tyrion.
After killing his father,
he's fled across the Narrow Sea,
a fugitive on the run.
He was a Lannister and he
had all the money in the world
and a noble name
and a big bag of gold
can buy you a lot.
All that's gone now.
He's totally at the mercy
of the people he's travelling with.
Who are you?
- And then the unthinkable happens.
- I am the gift.
He's captured and handed over
to his family's greatest enemy,
the Targaryen
queen in waiting, Daenerys.
My name is Tyrion Lannister.
And between them,
they are an extraordinary force.
Protect your queen!
She appoints him as
her political adviser.
But when a civil rebellion begins,
Tyrion gets to witness Daenerys
transform into a true Targaryen.
The symbol of the Targaryens
coming to claim their power
is on the back of a dragon because,
I mean, there's not much you can do
when you're standing on the ground
and a dragon's coming at you.
Daenerys has had the dragons
now for quite some time now
but that moment she gets on Drogon
and rides him for the first time,
that is her claiming her birthright.
The dragon riders are what
the Targaryens are all about.
That is how they
wielded their power.
Everybody
painted that picture of Daenerys
flying her dragon,
it never really happened.
And they've waited so many years
to see that and she finally does
and she does it in a wicked way
where she's escaping death.
Daenerys, she's got
the greatest name ever.
Stormborn, Mother of Dragons.
Daenerys Stormborn Targaryen,
I love that name.
She's got these dragons as back-up
and then she's got Tyrion,
who knows King's Landing,
who knows the political
side of things
and he's been
through battles as well.
Yet, as season five ends,
Daenerys's dragon delivers
her to an uncertain fate.
The last thing we see
of her in season five,
surrounded by Dothraki,
back where she started.
And season five is one
of vengeance for Arya.
The young Stark follows her mentor
to Braavos to become an assassin.
To serve well,
a girl must become no-one.
Arya's relationship
with Jaqen is fascinating.
He is utterly mysterious
and she is seduced by his power.
I didn't come here to sweep floors.
No? Why come then?
You said I could be your apprentice.
The power of death,
the power to choose who dies.
And Arya uses her new skills
to slaughter Meryn Trant,
a name on her kill list of people
who have destroyed her world.
- Argh!
- Arya's just a wee assassin.
Argh! Argh!
She made him suffer
in the best way possible
and she thoroughly enjoyed it.
But you must remember
what Arya has been through.
There is a sense of vengeance
rather than a sense of justice.
As Arya explores vengeance,
back home, the battle is on
for the Stark family home.
Stannis Baratheon
is marching on Winterfell,
now held by the Boltons.
But sometimes sacrifices
must be made to ensure victory.
He's going after something and it
is... it's increasingly futile.
In a desperate move,
Stannis follows the advice
of a red priestess
who promises him victory
if he makes an unspeakable
offering to the Lord of Light.
She managed to convince him
to burn his own daughter.
That's one of the most chilling
scenes, I think, of season five,
when... when he burns his child.
She's believed in this god
for so many years, I think that
if it's not to do with the god, she
kind of just blocks everything out
and I think that's what happened
as she blocked out the fact
that she was going
to be sacrificing a child.
She was sacrificing
the king's blood.
Melisandre really did believe that
Stannis was going to be the one
who would bring everything together
and he was going to be the ruler
of the Seven Kingdoms and she
put a lot of her heart and soul
- into helping him.
- But it proves to be his undoing.
His men desert him and Melisandre,
realising all is lost,
- flees to Castle Black...
- Your grace.
...leaving Stannis to advance
to Winterfell on his own.
Speak up.
It can't be worse than mutiny.
He's had a rough old time,
Stannis, hasn't he?
Because really he should be the king
from after Robert Baratheon dies
but every battle, he loses he
becomes further and further
involved with this kind of fantasy.
And awaiting Stannis
at Winterfell are the Boltons,
who tried to cement
their position in the North
with a tactical marriage
to Sansa Stark,
orchestrated by master
manipulator Petyr Baelish.
She shouldn't trust Littlefinger,
I mean,
why are you gonna trust
Littlefinger, I mean, jeez!
He is the dodgy car
salesman in Game Of Thrones,
offers you everything
and gives you nothing.
May I introduce my son,
Ramsay Bolton.
Now the Boltons have established
themselves at Winterfell,
bringing in a Stark will solidify
their position in the North.
But it's a huge miscalculation
that traps her in another
brutal relationship.
Ramsay is a horrible, cruel,
evil, power-hungry man.
He took psychotic nature
to another level.
I mean, he went there,
and he went some.
Oh, no, no, no.
You stay here, Reek.
You watch.
Fellow prisoner Theon Greyjoy,
aka Reek, is too terrified to help.
I think we all thought he should have stepped
in on the wedding night, let's be frank.
- With Ramsay distracted by battle...
- You're leaving it to me?
...Sansa is caught
attempting to escape
and it's only then that Reek finds
the courage to become Theon again.
- Ugh!
- Stop! Ugh!
That was a moment we all
needed to see. Theon again
had been so much
at the mercy of Ramsey
that finally he had a moment
where he could do good.
And so, by the end of season five,
Sansa has jumped either to
her death or to her freedom.
It's someone being
pushed in every way
to the absolute limit
of their will to live
and having come through that,
she's obviously gonna be
quite a different person.
As Sansa and Theon leap
from the walls of Winterfell,
nearby, Stannis is facing
defeat by the vast Bolton army.
I think Stannis had given up.
I think even before
they'd gone into battle,
I think he was going there to die.
Fate finally catches up with Stannis
when he comes face to face
with Brienne of Tarth
who's sought vengeance
for Renly's death since season two.
She is probably the toughest person
going about... about Westeros.
Argh!
But as Stannis bows out,
Jon Snow comes up against a greater
foe when he ventures to Hardhome
to make peace with the Wildlings.
This alliance is sacrilege
but when the White Walkers
launch a full attack,
Jon sees his hunch is right.
All humans must unite to fight them.
What's so great about the
whole White Walker mythology
is the way it has been building
throughout the series.
Who knows what they want?
They would bring
death and destruction
to absolutely everything.
Up until this point, they've
been semi-mythical characters.
It's been the White Walkers
in those cold lands
that no-one ever goes to
and here they are in front of the
heroes and they're very real
and it's a very real danger.
I don't think the White Walkers
are afraid of anything.
I think fear is just
not in their vocabulary.
And then Jon and the viewers
see the Night King reveal
that he has a greater power.
He can raise and recruit the dead.
It's a challenge to Jon
and, 'Look what I can do.'
Forget all the other
battles that are going on,
you know, battles for castles
and kingship, you know.
He's got to focus his army.
But on Jon's return to Castle Black,
in the final minutes of season five,
viewers witness
the cruellest blow of all
in a gut-churning finale.
When I saw the cross with traitor
written on it, I thought, 'Oh, no,
'they're not gonna kill him.'
And then they did!
For the Watch.
You root for him but the great
thing about Game Of Thrones is
your heroes can die at any second.
For the Watch.
They're all members
of the Night's Watch
and no matter what
one of their brothers has done,
what they did was
worse than what he did.
And so season five
ends on betrayal and death.
Is this really the end for Jon Snow?
Season six begins
at the scene of a crime.
Jon Snow lies slain at Castle Black
and all hopes are pinned
on the red priestess
and her magic to bring him back.
Game Of Thrones needs Jon Snow.
We do, we need him
to finish what he started.
As viewers hope
for Jon's resurrection,
we learn that Melisandre
harbours a great secret.
The reveal of ancient Melisandre
was definitely one of the most
stunning surprises in season
six of Game Of Thrones.
It shows how much
older she actually is
and how much longer she's been
believing in this god for.
Then we see her
use this power for Jon.
She tries to bring him back to us,
to resurrect him, it doesn't work.
When the wolf started
to sort of make some noise,
that's when I thought... I think
everyone thought Jon Snow's alive.
And then it's just that moment of...
Jon Snow has returned and all
of Westeros rejoices.
And after the miracle
of Jon's rebirth
comes a partial reunion
of scattered Starks
when Sansa arrives at Castle Black
and together they'll gather forces
in a bid to retake the North.
Sansa's become majestic
but she's also become savvy.
She's lost that naivety.
A monster has taken
our home and our brother.
We have to go back to
Winterfell and save them both.
She's a queen, really.
In terms of being
from a powerful family
and being able to make decisions
and tell other people to do stuff,
I think she's gonna tell
other people to do stuff.
As one former Bolton
captive looks for revenge,
another looks for redemption.
I am Theon Greyjoy.
Last living son of Balon Greyjoy.
Theon returns again
to the Iron Islands.
But, following his
father's mysterious death,
renounces his claim.
- And she is your rightful ruler.
- Aye!
Theon, by backing Yara,
shows that he's learnt
from his massive fall
and humiliation and castration
and he's learnt
who is the more powerful person.
Yara! Yara! Yara! Yara!
I'm Euron Greyjoy.
I claim the Salt Throne.
But it's not all plain sailing
for Yara. Her uncle Euron arrives
and immediately
scuppers her plan to rule.
Euron comes in and we know
he's killed the father
and Yara announces
that he's killed the father
and you think that's
gonna be the end of him.
He led us into
two wars we couldn't win.
I apologise to you all
for not killing him years ago.
He is just
the most insane creation.
He's cocky, he's arrogant.
He could start a fight
in an empty room.
I wasn't born to be king.
I paid the iron price
and here I stand.
Euron! Euron!
All the men will still
side with a another man
because he's shown such
ruthlessness and cunning.
With Euron crowned king,
Theon and Yara flee,
taking part of the fleet with them.
They stole our best ships.
They are headed across the
Narrow Sea to join Daenerys
who's been a hostage of the Dothraki.
But now burns their leaders
and converts the tribe.
The huge Dothraki horde.
We're gonna finally get a lot
of different power factions
coming together
in a very scary explosive way.
And she bags herself a navy
by forging an alliance with Yara
who pledges her fleet of ships.
But as Great Houses unite for war,
beyond the Wall, we learn
more about the deathly foe
which threatens them all.
While time training
with a Three-Eyed Raven,
Bran Stark uncovers a great secret.
White Walkers were created
from the First Men.
The Children Of The Forest
invented the White Walkers
to help protect their own race.
It was an innocent
defence to do that.
But clearly it has
gone out of control.
And when the White Walkers
come for Bran,
- there are terrible casualties.
- Hodor is a goner.
- Hold the door!
- A completely pure act of protection.
There was nothing...
There was no greater goal
to what he did
other than protect Bran.
Everyone who's basically just given
in order to give way for Bran
and there must be a reason, right?
We know he's become
the Three-Eyed Raven.
But how's he going
to use those powers.
And as the Three-Eyed Raven,
Bran resolves a great Stark secret
when he sees Jon Snow's
mother is Ned's sister Lyanna.
You understand what Ned's been
going through the whole time.
He made out that it was his son,
his bastard son,
but it was really his nephew.
But it confirms Jon Snow
is still half Stark
and, in season six,
he and Sansa march
on their family seat of Winterfell
to fight Ramsay Bolton
in what goes down in history
as the Battle of the Bastards.
Ramsay's now top dog, having murdered
his father and newborn brother.
If you want to say... You're going
to die tomorrow, Lord Bolton.
When you play the Game Of Thrones,
you either win or you die, you know,
and she knows
it's about winning now,
she's had enough of all the rest,
it's time to win.
She offers her insight.
You think he's going to fall into your
trap, he won't. He's the one who lays traps.
She's lived with this man
for a long time and she knows
that...
that he is cruel to the core.
Sansa's words go unheeded.
Ramsay baits Jon
with his hostage Rickon.
Run to your brother.
It shows a lot about
how Ramsay's mind works.
He's calculating, he's always
thinking about the next move.
You know, it's very interesting how
Machiavellian he can be as well.
I think everybody who was watching
that episode for the first time,
I think they all thought he was
probably likely going to make it.
Ugh! Argh!
It was just kind of
cut so short and I think
that's kind of what
Game Of Thrones is always about.
Ramsay Bolton's, like,
'Yes I've got you now, boy,
'just in the
middle of no-man's land.'
That's what Game Of Thrones
does so brilliantly,
it's constantly pitting good
moral forces against bad ones
and you don't just win
because you're good.
Argh! Argh!
They were surrounded
by the entire army,
they were being driven into the mud.
Ramsay should have won, he was
much more conniving and cunning
and if it hadn't have
been for Sansa coming in
at the last minute,
then he probably would have won.
She's a strong independent woman.
She's really powerful
and she saves the day
and I think that's brilliant.
This was probably their first
major victory in six years.
They're suddenly inside the castle.
Winterfell.
It seems Jon will kill Ramsay.
But he then leaves
Sansa to take the scalp.
There was only one way to kill him and
Sansa found the right way to do it.
She knows what she's gonna do
and she knows he deserves it.
All memory of you will disappear.
If you were face to face
with your nemesis
and you had the opportunity,
you'd take it.
Aarrgghh! Argh!
She's hardcore.
She has the makings of a Cersei.
The king is born!
But it's Jon Snow who becomes
king as the season ends,
with the Starks controlling the
North and Sansa is by his side.
She's a character
that will surprise people
because she's not what she seems.
And neither is Sansa's sister Arya.
Blinded and stabbed in her
training as a faceless man,
she's now back in Westeros
to deal with Walder Frey.
She's gone on this mad journey.
Arya comes in disguise,
having chopped up Walder's sons.
They weren't easy to carve.
She wanted him to see who she was.
The face comes off, there's a knife.
The last thing you'll ever see
is a Stark smiling
down at you as you die.
She's been caught up in it so young
that she's turning into
this child soldier.
Ugh! Ugh!
Revenge is a dish best taken cold.
I literally cannot wait now
for her and Cersei to face off.
In fact, Cersei elevates
revenge to an art form
in season six as the Lannisters fight
for their family's very survival.
These royal lovers
are united in grief
after the Sand Snakes
killed their daughter.
The Lannisters are all about power.
They're all about revenge.
We're the only ones who matter,
the only ones in this world
and everything
they've taken from us
we're going to take back and more.
It doesn't matter how long it takes,
they will get you back.
With Jaime sent away
to fight revolt,
Cersei is left alone to face judgment
by the Faith Militant.
We are told that Cersei
is going to turn up for a trial
but we know perfectly well
she's not going to.
But it's now she plays
a game-changing hand.
She was always going
to have a dastardly plan.
The man who was sent by Cersei
to hold Tommen in that room...
There's something wrong. Margaery
knows what's up in an instant.
The High Sept is packed with
those who've wronged Cersei.
The Tyrells, High Sparrow
and Faith Militant.
The amazing thing is the spectacle is
incredible and you never know it's coming.
This isn't gonna end well.
Cersei has, of course,
unleashed wildfire.
She's wiped out
this fantastic building,
she's destroyed all her enemies.
That's what makes
Cersei so brilliant,
she's been to the
absolute lowest place
that you could possibly go
and she still comes out on top.
In the moment where she gets
her revenge on everyone else,
she loses the only thing that
she has left that matters to her.
Knowing that his mum's
the one that's
pretty much murdered his wife...
- ...what has he got to live for?
- Tommen's death
leaves the Iron Throne empty,
so a new reign begins.
A witch told her
that she was cursed
and that all
of her children would die.
It didn't stop her from loving her
kids and trying to protect them
at any cost but she accepts
very swiftly her fate.
And so Jaime returns to a new world
order, courtesy of his sister.
She's devastated the Tyrells.
Now the Lannisters are once more
a force to be reckoned with.
Queen Cersei
sitting on the Iron Throne.
The fact that a woman has
managed to achieve that position
and get that much power, Tywin,
he would probably have been
reluctantly proud.
Then you go, 'OK, well, what are you
going to do with this Iron Throne?'
Jaime, he knows, not a lot of good.
He's wondering who she's going to
become now that she has the power.
As one queen takes the throne,
another sets sail
to challenge her for it.
Finally Daenerys,
the Targaryen queen,
is on her way to Westeros
with a vast alliance
she spent six seasons amassing.
We're now getting to crunch time.
The dragons flying overhead,
everybody on the boats,
'We're coming.'
Join us after the break
for the Targaryen invasion.
Welcome to Westeros where
the fight for the kingdom is on.
Welcome back to "The Story So Far"
where, in season seven, Daenerys
finally lands on home soil,
her birthplace Dragonstone...
...along with her huge
alliance of power players.
To see this female character rise
to power and get to the point
where she's commanded thousands
of men, it's so magical.
Her allies want immediate invasion.
We have an army,
a fleet and three dragons.
We could hit King's Landing now,
hard, with everything we have.
The city will fall within a day.
Ellaria wants to take Cersei out
and all the Lannisters.
That's what she wants
and she feels now that her
and the Tyrells and the Greyjoys,
they're all there together,
just go and rip them out.
Tens of thousands will
die in the firestorm.
It's called war.
Who can win against these dragons?
But to avoid being seen
as foreign invaders,
Daenerys's hand Tyrion
has a more cunning plan.
You can't have
everybody hating you.
You've got to have
some people inside.
I think that's what
Tyrion is there for.
Then comes a fateful meeting.
In need of more allies, Daenerys
summons the king in the North,
Jon Snow.
He comes but with his own agenda.
He's learned there
is dragonglass there.
Jon's biggest goal is to prove
to the southern part of Westeros
that the Night King is real
and that this threat's coming.
- The dead are the enemy.
- The dead?
The overall battle for humanity
itself is the greater battle.
Daenerys allows Jon to search
for this natural treasure.
Beneath dragonstone
is more dragonglass
than they'll ever need
to defeat the White Walkers
and it is key, in fact,
to defeating the White Walkers.
And they find ancient cave paintings.
- The enemy is real.
- Proof of White Walkers.
It's always been real.
He's taking the first steps
towards convincing Daenerys
that that threat is real and looking
for the ally he needs to fight it.
I will fight for the North.
When you bend the knee.
Aware of the impending invasion,
in the capital Queen Cersei
is more than up for a fight,
amassing weapons and allies
to face down the enemy.
Cersei is ruthless but she's
incredibly canny and clever
and that's why she's lasted so long.
To think I listened to father
for 40 years and know nothing.
Cersei is very much
a chip off the old block.
We must stand together
if we hope to stop her.
The powerful Tarlys
reluctantly join them.
Randyll is the most successful
general in Westeros
and considered invincible.
She has three full-grown dragons,
Your Grace.
The same as Aegon when he
conquered the Seven Kingdoms.
How do you propose to stop them?
He acknowledges their power.
It's like saying, 'They've got
nuclear weapons, we don't.'
In fact, Cersei has
two secret new weapons.
A giant anti-dragon machine
and an approaching wildcard
with his very own fleet.
I love Euron Greyjoy.
He's set his heart on Cersei.
You invited the Greyjoys
to King's Landing.
- Not all of them.
- Well, it looks like all of them.
He wants power, he wants
to marry Cersei Lannister.
So here I am
with a thousand ships
and two good hands.
So, he says,
'OK, I'll bring you a present.'
I won't return to King's Landing
until I have that for you.
So he goes off with his fleet.
Euron... He delivers
a victory for Team Cersei,
knocking out her enemy's armada.
They get invaded
by Euron and his madness.
Aarrgghh!
So swashbuckley.
I mean, properly swashbuckley.
He manages to encircle Theon
and Yara's much smaller fleet.
And he takes Yara prisoner.
I have her. Come and get her.
Theon escapes in a really
embarrassing and cowardly way.
Poor Theon. I mean,
he abandons his sister.
Jumps overboard early on in season
seven. Theon's scared of everyone.
Euron also captures
Ellaria Sand and her daughter.
And that is the gift
Euron presents to Cersei
because, of course, Ellaria
murdered Cersei's daughter Myrcella.
I'm the prize to take back to Cersei
so she can get her revenge on me,
which I don't want.
I give you what
no other man could give.
Justice.
He's pushing and
pushing and pushing...
There's only one reward I want.
...a wedge between, you know,
these kind of star-crossed lovers.
You shall have
what your heart desires...
...when the war is won.
In a double bluff,
Cersei lets her enemies
capture her family's ancestral home.
So, they're able to take Casterly
Rock surprisingly easily.
And, of course, that puts
them a little bit on edge.
In fact,
it's a strategic distraction...
...allowing Jaime to take his army
south to conquer House Tyrell
and steal its fortune.
The Lannisters, led by Jaime,
have very cleverly
gone to Highgarden.
I remember when the Lannisters
did go to pay their debts
by basically stealing
a load of gold from Highgarden.
That is where the money is and,
of course, they owe the Iron Bank
not an insignificant sum.
And Jaime goes to confront Olenna
who is, you know, kind of, like,
the last Tyrell of any consequence.
She's almost sitting there waiting
for him, she knows what's coming.
How will it happen?
It was almost like a business
appointment, wasn't it?
It was like, 'Oh, hello.
And now you need to die.'
As a viewer, you were just winded.
But in her very last breath, Olenna
reveals she killed King Joffrey.
Tell Cersei,
I want her to know it was me.
Boom! You know, it's, like,
Game Of Thrones just delivers,
doesn't it?
When news of the Lannister
victories reaches Daenerys,
she furiously abandons Tyrion's
softly, softly strategy
and she finally invades Westeros.
She's just had enough,
she is raining down her aggression
on top of them.
They're coming!
She's tired of being,
you know, bottled up
and being told that she shouldn't do
this. This is who she knows she is.
As the Lannister and Tarly
troops are eviscerated,
Jaime is confronted by the true
scale of the Dragon Queen's army.
He has looked into the
face of the future of war
and they're on
the losing side of it.
They might have held against
the charge of the Dothraki
but not when you've got
a dragon flying towards you.
Jaime makes this absolutely
ridiculous decision
to have one final choice
and be the queen slayer,
forgetting there's a gigantic
dragon just over his shoulder.
After Jaime escapes,
Daenerys gives the survivors,
along with Randyll Tarly,
a brutal ultimatum.
Join her or fry.
Randyll is captive at this point
and resigned to his fate.
Step forward, my lord.
He's unimpressed by Daenerys
co-opting a foreign army
of savages and laying waste to those
that she encounters in battle.
- You will not kneel?
- I already have a queen.
She needs to stake her ground here
and she needs to make examples
of her enemies when they
refuse to bend the knee,
so that she can do
what she ultimately
needs to do politically
in this country.
Dracarys.
What sort of leader
will Daenerys be?
Will she be a fair ruler
or will she be the Mad King?
Away from the fighting,
the remaining Stark family
is reunited in season seven
as Bran and Arya finally make it home
to the delight of Sansa,
the new Lady of Winterfell.
They're not the
people that they were.
They're not the kids that had those
cute little wolf pups
back in series one.
You came home.
But it's not as harmonious
as one would hope.
They haven't been together
for so long and they
viewed the past in
entirely different ways.
I remember you standing on that
platform with Joffrey and Cersei
when they dragged
father to the block.
They are sisters but they could,
in a blink, become sworn enemies.
You should be
on your knees thanking me.
We're standing in Winterfell
again because of me.
We were expecting sisterly love
and tears and all of that.
It was quite the opposite of that,
wasn't it?
And in the shadows, Littlefinger
is stoking the tension between them.
What do you think she's after?
You think, 'Is this all going
to implode from the inside?'
You stand accused of murder.
You stand accused of treason.
How do you answer these charges...
...Lord Baelish?
But it all backfires
for the arch schemer
as he's finally outwitted
and beaten at his own game.
The youngest wolves of the pack
have found their way to unite
and use all their skills together.
None of you knows the truth.
You've held a knife to his throat.
Bran has now been replaced
by this Three-Eyed Raven...
You said,
'I did warn you not to trust me.'
...who is this all-seeing,
all-knowing,
kind of slightly sinister power.
He just didn't see it.
He is the puppeteer.
I was expecting him
to be much more clever.
Turn family against family,
turn sister against sister,
that's what you did
to our mother and Aunt Lysa.
And that's what
you tried to do to us.
He's got his comeuppance...
..at the hand of Ned's kids.
And even farther north,
a vital quest has begun.
In order to unite the warring
kingdoms of Westeros against
the true enemy heading their way,
Jon Snow leads a mission
beyond the wall.
It's their plan to go north,
capture a wight...
...and bring it down south
and just show people
for once and for all
that there is this threat.
After bagging a wight,
they are surrounded.
And it falls on Daenerys and
her dragons to fly to the rescue.
She's there to save Jon.
There's a mad battle
raging on all sides
but the moment the Night King just
very slowly picks up an ice spear...
Ugh!
This is a pretty massive moment.
Not only does he kill the dragon...
...the Night King has gained one of
the most powerful weapons imaginable.
They escape with
a captive wight in tow
but it comes at a great cost
as the Army of the Dead
swarm in to claim their prize.
When he kills the dragon, you're
devastated. You think that's it.
When he revives the dragon
and it becomes one of them,
it's more than a turnaround,
it's pretty devastating.
Which leads to a dramatic reveal
as Daenerys and Jon bring their
deadly evidence down to the capital.
Against the odds,
Jaime's persuaded Cersei to meet
her enemies at a peace summit.
They plan to beg her for a truce
and to join the fight
against the dead.
Cersei and Daenerys coming
face to face for the first time
that's, you know,
the clash of titans.
There are so many
of them at play there.
You've got the Greyjoys,
you've got the Lannisters.
And suddenly Euron is so volatile.
- We are all facing a unique...
- Theon!
I have your sister.
If you don't submit to me here now,
I'll kill her.
When there's that first face-off,
you've got Cersei
and Daenerys over here.
- You have my word.
- The word of a would-be usurper.
There is no conversation that
will erase the last 50 years.
We have something to show you.
When the Hound releases the wight...
And the dead come out
and go straight for Cersei.
...it is the visceral payoff
that we've all been waiting for
and it is the theatrics
that Jon and Tyrion intend.
This is the only thing I've
ever seen that terrifies me.
It seems Euron Greyjoy
is turning tail
and deserting his queen.
They call your bluff,
they don't actually have anyone
get killed in that scene,
it becomes something else entirely.
A darkness is
coming for us all.
And Cersei appears
to support a truce.
We'll face it together.
When she agrees,
you just think, 'Oh,
'this is just going
to go horribly wrong.'
In fact, nothing is as it seems.
We'll meet at Lord Harroway's Town
and march together to Winterfell.
- Ser Jaime.
- Your Grace.
He's organising the troops,
saying, 'We're going to go north,
'we're going to help people out,
let's get it together.'
And then she's, like, 'You're stupid.
We're not doing that.'
Do you really think
Euron Greyjoy will turn tail
and sail back to the Iron Islands?
You see Cersei not sending
the Lannister troops
but instead sending Euron Greyjoy
down to Essos for the mercenaries.
You plotted with Euron Greyjoy?
She will stop at nothing Cersei.
Even though Cersei
has revealed she's pregnant
with a Lannister baby to bolster
their dynasty, Jaime now leaves her.
Those Lannisters, man. They have
a complicated relationship.
He's a man of honour and, in the end,
he's going to be true to his word.
As one incestuous pairing
hits the rocks,
another is setting sail.
Jon has now bent the knee to Daenerys
and they can
no longer deny their love.
It's almost like seeing
a god and a goddess.
You've been wanting
them to become lovers
and you get the loving moment as
you're totally given the information
that you're
watching incest right now.
In fact, Jon's fallen
for his own auntie.
In a vision, Bran sees that Jon's
father is Dany's older brother
Rhaegar Targaryen.
Prince Rhaegar married Lyanna Stark
in a secret ceremony,
which makes Jon Aegon Targaryen's
true heir to the throne.
He's never been a bastard.
He's the heir to the Iron Throne.
Even if culturally
Game Of Thrones can handle incest,
you know Jon and Daenerys probably
won't be able to handle that.
But eclipsing all developments
and personal struggles,
in the North, the season ends
on a cataclysmic event
that changes the game
for every living human being.
This is the moment that we were told
could never happen.
The Wall can never come down.
You see the army
kind of coming out of the forest.
And then you hear something.
Oh, that's just changed
the whole ballgame here.
It didn't occur to me that we
would have a dragon White Walker.
But when that happened, you thought,
'Oh, yes, this is inevitable.'
Now this takes us on
a whole different journey.
That's when you know
it's on for next season.
There's nothing to protect
them in the south any more.
I mean, you can't have
a cliffhanger greater than that.
I don't know what's going
to happen but I can't wait.