It's coming from the courtyard.
It's the Lord Commander!
Help me get him inside.
Thorne did this.
How many of your brothers
do you think you can trust?
Trust?
The men in this room.
Does the wolf know you?
We need all the help we can get.
Ser Davos.
I saw him in the flames
fighting at Winterfell.
I can't speak for the flames,
but he's gone.
He was our Lord Commander.
He never should have been!
You all know why you're here.
Jon Snow is dead.
Who killed him?
I did.
And Bowen Marsh and Othell Yarwyck
and the other officers in this castle.
- Murderers!
- Traitors!
You're right!
We've committed treason, all of us.
Jon Snow was my Lord Commander.
I had no love for him.
That was no secret.
But I never once disobeyed an order.
Loyalty is the foundation
on which the Night's Watch is built.
And the Watch means everything to me.
I have given my life,
we have all given our lives
to the Night's Watch.
Jon Snow was going to destroy
the Night's Watch.
He let the wildlings through our gates
as no Lord Commander has
ever done before.
He gave them the very land
on which they reaved
and raped and murdered.
Lord Commander Snow did
what he thought was right,
I've no doubt about that.
And what he thought was right
would have been the end of us.
He thrust a terrible choice upon us.
And we made it.
He'll have seen we didn't come.
Thorne will have made it official by now.
Castle Black is his.
I don't care who's sitting
at the high table.
Jon was my friend.
And those fuckers butchered him.
Now we return the favor.
We don't have the numbers.
- We have a direwolf.
- It's not enough.
I didn't know Lord Commander Snow for long,
but I have to believe he wouldn't have
wanted his friends to die for nothing.
If you were planning to see tomorrow,
you picked the wrong room.
We all die today.
I say we do our best
to take Thorne with us when we go.
We need to fight,
but we don't need to die.
Not if we have help.
Who is gonna help us?
You're not the only ones
who owe your lives to Jon Snow.
Bolt the door. Don't let anyone in.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
She was 11 the first time
I saw her.
The kennelmaster's daughter.
She smelled of dog.
I wasn't much older,
but everybody was already afraid of me.
You certainly were.
Myranda wasn't though.
What could I do to her
that those hounds couldn't?
She was fearless.
There was nothing she wouldn't do.
Your pain will be paid for
a thousand times over.
I wish you could be here to watch.
Shall I have a grave
dug for her, my lord?
Or would you rather the men build a pyre?
Buried, burned?
This is good meat.
Feed it to the hounds.
Your command of the cavalry
was impressive.
Thanks to you,
the false king Stannis Baratheon is dead.
Do you know who struck the killing blow?
- No.
- A shame.
I'd reward the man.
Still, a great victory.
Do you feel like a victor?
I rebelled against the crown
to arrange your marriage to Sansa Stark.
Do you think that burning
wagons in the night
and mowing down tired,
outnumbered Baratheons
is the same as facing
a prepared and provisioned Lannister army?
No.
A reckoning will come.
We need the North to face it.
The entire North.
They won't back us without Sansa Stark.
We no longer have Sansa Stark.
You played your games with her.
You played your games
with the heir to the Iron Islands
and now they're both gone.
I have a team of men after them
with some of my best hounds.
They won't get far.
I'm glad to hear it.
Without Sansa,
you won't be able to produce an heir.
And without an heir, well...
Let's hope the maesters are right
and Lady Walda's carrying a boy.
We can't stop.
We have to cross here.
- I can't.
- It's the only way to throw off the hounds.
But it's too cold. I can't.
I won't make it. I'll die.
I've seen what his hounds do to a person.
This way is better.
Over here. Come on.
Sansa.
Tell them to settle down!
Stay here. I'll lure them away.
- No, I won't make it without you.
- You will.
Go north, only north.
Jon is Lord Commander at Castle Black.
He'll help you.
See somebody, eh?
- There they are!
- Get them!
Where is Lady Bolton?
- Dead.
- Liar.
She broke her leg jumping
from the ramparts.
I left her to die in the snow.
Got something! Run!
Resist. Stay.
Stay.
I can't wait to see
what parts Ramsay cuts off you this time.
Rider!
- Who is it?
- It's a bloody woman.
No! Please! Don't!
Lady Sansa,
I offer my services once again.
I will shield your back and keep your counsel
and give my life for yours if need be.
I swear it by the Old Gods and the New.
And I vow
that you shall always
have a place by my hearth
and...
Meat and mead at my table.
And I pledge to ask no service of you
that might bring you dishonor.
I swear it by the Old Gods and the New.
Arise.
Your Grace,
I'm sorry to disturb you.
A ship from Dorne has
sailed into the harbor.
Myrcella.
Do you remember the first time
you saw a dead body?
Mother.
All I could think about when she died
was what would happen to her now.
Every day, every night,
what does Mama look like now?
Has she started to bloat?
Has her skin turned black?
Have her lips peeled back
from her teeth?
I think about locking Myrcella
in a crypt.
I think about her beautiful little face
starting to collapse.
Don't think about it.
I have to.
I have to. It's not right
she has to suffer alone.
She's not suffering. She's gone.
No one can hurt her anymore.
She was good.
From her first breath,
she was so sweet.
I don't know where she came from.
She was nothing like me.
No meanness, no jealousy, just good.
I know.
I thought if I could
make something so good,
so pure,
maybe I'm not a monster.
Listen... Listen to me.
She was my daughter and I failed her.
No, I knew this would happen.
The witch told me years ago.
She promised me three children
and she promised me they'd die.
And gold their shrouds.
Everything she said came true.
You couldn't have stopped it.
It's prophecy. It's fate.
- You don't believe that.
- Of course I do.
You told me yourself when Father died.
You said we had to stay together.
You said people would try to tear us apart,
take what's ours.
That was a prophecy too.
I didn't listen to you,
and everything you said came true.
Fuck prophecy.
Fuck fate. Fuck everyone who isn't us.
We're the only ones who matter,
the only ones in this world.
And everything they've taken from us,
we're going to take back and more.
We're going to take everything there is.
The seven hells
brim with the souls of saintly men.
They scream in agony
and their shame is so great,
they do not feel the flames,
for now they see if not for a single sin
they concealed, they were saved.
I'd like to see my brother.
- Confess.
- Please.
How is he? At least tell me that.
Confess.
I am the queen
and I demand to see my brother.
Sinners don't make demands.
They make confessions.
Septa Unella.
Our other guests need you.
There.
Septa Unella can be overzealous
at times.
I'll speak with her.
My brother, can you tell me how he is?
It isn't Ser Loras that brings me here.
Your husband misses you dearly.
The love between a man
and wife is sacred.
It reflects the love the
gods have for all of us.
But sin leads us away from the sacred.
And only confession can purge sin.
I have nothing to confess.
So you believe you are pure?
Perfect?
Wholly without sin?
None of us are.
You have started down the path.
But you have many miles to go.
I always envied Oberyn.
He lived.
He truly lived.
Sailed around the world.
Fought men from every country.
Lay with the most beautiful women alive.
- And men.
He experienced everything
while I sat here in Dorne
trying my best to keep my people
alive and well fed.
But that is life.
We each have our roles.
Oberyn was born to be an adventurer.
And I was born to rule.
The gods are not fools.
You would have been a lousy adventurer.
And Oberyn,
he would have been a terrible ruler.
Your mother is a brilliant woman,
you know that?
Prince Doran.
The Princess Myrcella.
When was the last time
you left this palace?
You don't know your own people.
Their disgust for you.
Elia Martell, raped and murdered,
and you did nothing.
Oberyn Martell, butchered,
You're not a Dornishman.
And you're not our prince.
My son, Trystane...
Your son is weak, just like you.
And weak men will never rule Dorne again.
I told you I'm not hungry.
We're not here to feed you.
We're here to kill you.
You want her to do it or me?
We are family.
I don't want to hurt you.
Her or me?
You.
Good.
Smart boy.
You're a greedy bitch, you know that?
We're never going to fix
what's wrong with this city
from the top of an 800-foot pyramid.
We'll be fine.
We're dressed like common merchants.
You walk like a rich person.
You've spent a lot of time studying
the way rich people walk?
You walk as though the paving stones
were your personal property.
I used to steal from people like you
when I was a boy.
It's a good thing
you're not a boy anymore.
Because you have no cock.
For your baby.
To eat.
She thinks you want to eat her baby.
His Valyrian is terrible.
He only wants to give you money,
so your baby can eat.
Mhysa means mother in Valyrian.
I know what mhysa means.
- Who wrote it?
- Hard to know.
Our queen is not as popular in Meereen
as she used to be.
The Sons of the Harpy?
Very possibly.
Daenerys Targaryen took away
their most valuable property,
told them human beings
weren't even property to begin with.
You can see why they're unhappy.
Of course,
it could also be the freed men.
For the night is dark and full of terrors.
The Lord of Light sent the
Mother of Dragons to you,
and those who love the
darkness chased her away.
Many of the former slaves feel
that Daenerys has abandoned them.
She did fly away on a dragon
and not come back.
How will you respond?
Will you wring your hands, while you
wait for the Mother of Dragons to return?
Or will you take up her flames yourselves?
Will you fight for your own salvation,
now that Queen Daenerys
is not here to fight for you?
It's a problem.
Fear has brought Meereen
to a standstill.
Whoever you are, wherever you go,
someone in this city
wants to murder you.
We can't fight an enemy
we don't know.
The Sons of the Harpy planned their
attack in the fighting pits very carefully,
which means they take orders
from someone.
And have you started
looking for that someone?
My little birds have already taken wing.
Soon they'll return,
singing songs of men in gold masks.
Well, we won't be sailing to Westeros
anytime soon.
Goat?
Ram.
Do you think our friend got him?
Don't know anything else
that can melt a ram's horn.
We're on the right path then.
Perhaps she's tired of being queen.
I don't think she likes it very much.
She's too smart to like it.
Maybe she's flown somewhere else,
somewhere far away from men like us.
I've been all over the world.
There's no escaping men like us.
There's no escaping her, eh?
You keep coming back. Why?
You know why.
Isn't it frustrating
wanting someone
who doesn't want you back?
Of course it is.
You're a romantic. I admire that.
Sometimes I look at you and I think,
so that's what I'll be like when I grow old.
If you grow old.
If I grow old.
I hope I do.
I want to see what the world looks like
when she's done conquering it.
So do I.
Huh, an army?
Not an army.
A horde.
Dothraki?
They have her.
Maybe she saw a ghost.
My friend's mother saw a ghost
and her hair turned white.
Pink people are afraid of the sun.
It burns their skin.
This one stands too long in the sun
and her hair goes white.
You think she's got white pussy hair too?
You ever been with a girl
with white pussy hair?
Only when I was fucking your grandma.
I'll ask Khal Moro for a night with you.
What do you think?
Pretty eyes, but she's an idiot.
She doesn't have to be smart
to get fucked in the ass.
I like to talk when I'm finished.
Otherwise, we might as well be dogs.
No.
For you, my Khal.
The white-haired girl
we found in the hills.
Look at those lips, blood of my blood.
Blue-eyed women are witches.
It is known.
Cut off her head,
before she casts a spell on you.
Even if I was blind,
I'd hear my wives say,
cut off her head
and I'd know this woman is beautiful.
I'm glad I'm not blind.
Seeing a beautiful woman naked
for the first time,
what is better than that?
Killing another Khal?
Yes, killing another Khal.
Conquering a city
and taking her people as slaves,
and taking her idols back to Vaes Dothrak.
Breaking a wild horse,
forcing it to submit to your will.
Seeing a beautiful woman naked
for the first time
is among the five best things in life.
Do not touch me.
I am Daenerys Stormborn
of the House Targaryen,
the First of Her Name, the Unburnt,
Queen of Meereen,
Queen of the Andals
and the Rhoynar and the First Men,
Khaleesi of the Great Grass Sea,
Breaker of Chains and Mother of Dragons.
You are nobody,
the millionth of your name,
Queen of Nothing,
slave of Khal Moro.
Tonight I will lie with you,
and if the Great Stallion is kind,
you will give me a son.
Do you understand?
I will not lie with you.
And I will bear no children,
for you, or anyone else.
Not until the sun rises in the west,
and sets in the east.
I told you she was a witch.
Cut off her head.
I like her. She has spirit.
I was wife to Khal Drogo,
son of Khal Bharbo.
Khal Drogo is dead.
I know.
I burnt his body.
Forgive me. I did not know.
It is forbidden to lie with a Khal's widow.
No one will touch you.
You have my word.
If you will escort me back to Meereen,
I will see that your khalasar is given a
thousand horses, as a sign of my gratitude.
When a Khal dies,
there is only one place for his khaleesi.
Vaes Dothrak.
The Temple of the Dosh Khaleen.
To live out her days with
the widows of dead khals.
It is known.
But there has to be a price
to pay for everything.
I know, but have you tried
telling him that?
Thank you.
Who'd go there after what
happened to that Kingsguard?
Probably had it coming.
Maybe so, but I'm not risking it.
- Just can't do it.
- All right.
Honesty as well. He gets it.
Are you listening, blind girl?
Do you hear them talking?
Do any of them talk to you?
No.
So sad.
Stand and fight, blind girl.
I can't see.
That's your problem, not mine.
See you tomorrow.
Ser Davos, we have no cause to fight.
We are both anointed knights.
Hear that, lads? Nothing to fear.
I will grant amnesty to all brothers
who throw down their arms before nightfall.
And you, Ser Davos,
I will allow you to travel south
a free man with a fresh horse.
And some mutton.
I'd like some mutton.
What?
I'm not much of a hunter.
I'll need some food if I'm gonna
make it south without starving.
We'll give you food.
You can bring the Red Woman
with you if you like.
Or you can leave her here with us,
whichever you choose.
But surrender by nightfall
or this ends with blood.
Thank you, Ser Alliser.
We'll discuss amongst ourselves
and come back to you with an answer.
Boys, I've been running
from men like that all my life.
In my learned opinion, we open that door...
And they'll slaughter us all.
They want to come in,
they're gonna come in.
Aye, but we don't need to
make it easy for them.
Edd is our only chance.
It's a sad fucking statement
if Dolorous Edd is our only chance.
There's always the Red Woman.
What's one redhead gonna do
against 40 armed men?
You haven't seen her do
what I've seen her do.