Where you gonna go?
South.
What are you gonna do?
Get warm.
I was with you
at Hardhome.
We saw
what's out there.
We know
it's coming here.
How can you
leave us now?
I did everything I could.
You know that.
- You swore a vow.
- Aye, I pledged my life to the Night's Watch.
- I gave my life.
- For all nights to come.
They killed me, Edd!
My own brothers.
You want me to stay
here after that?
Riders approaching!
Open the gate!
This is good soup.
Do you remember those kidney
pies Old Nan used to make?
- With the peas and onions?
- Mmm.
We never should
have left Winterfell.
Don't you wish we could
go back to the day we left?
I want to scream at myself,
"Don't go, you idiot."
How could we know?
I spent a lot of time thinking
about what an ass I was to you.
I wish I could
change everything.
We were children.
I was awful,
just admit it.
You were
occasionally awful.
I'm sure I can't
have been great fun.
Always sulking in the corner
while the rest of you played.
- Can you forgive me?
- There's nothing to forgive.
- Forgive me.
- All right.
All right,
I forgive you.
You'd think after
thousands of years,
the Night's Watch would have
learned how to make a good ale.
Where will you go?
Where will we go?
If I don't watch over you, Father's
ghost will come back and murder me.
Where will we go?
I can't stay here,
not after what happened.
There's only one place
we can go.
Home.
Should we tell the Boltons
to pack up and leave?
We'll take it back
from them.
I don't have an army.
How many wildlings
did you save?
They didn't come here
to serve me.
They owe you
their lives.
You think they'll be safe here if Roose
Bolton remains Warden of the North?
- Sansa.
- Winterfell is our home.
It's ours and Arya's
and Bran's and Rickon's.
Wherever they are,
it belongs to our family.
We have to fight for it.
I'm tired of fighting.
It's all I've done
since I left home.
I've killed brothers
of the Night's Watch.
I've killed wildlings.
I've killed men that I admire.
I hanged a boy
younger than Bran.
I fought and I lost.
If we don't take back the North,
we'll never be safe.
I want you to help me.
But I'll do it myself
if I have to.
My lady.
Ser Davos.
Will you stay here
at Castle Black?
I will do
as Jon Snow commands.
You serve Jon Snow now?
He's the prince
that was promised.
Forgive me, my lady,
I thought that was Stannis.
What happened
down there?
There was a battle.
Stannis was defeated.
And Shireen?
What happened
to the princess?
I saw what happened.
I saw Stannis' forces
defeated in the field.
My lady,
I'm Ser Davos Seaworth.
We've met before.
I was Kingsguard
to Renly Baratheon.
Before Renly was assassinated
with bloodmagic.
That's in the past now.
Yes, it's in the past.
It doesn't mean
I forget.
Or forgive.
He admitted it,
you know.
Who did?
Stannis.
Just before
I executed him.
The Defender of the Vale!
Uncle Petyr!
My lord.
Come and see.
I missed your name day.
Go on.
A falcon!
A gyrfalcon.
The greatest and rarest
of birds.
Last time
I saw you, Baelish,
you told me you were taking Sansa
Stark home with you to the Fingers.
Indeed I was.
And yet not long ago,
we received reports
that she has been married to
Ramsay Bolton in Winterfell.
On our way to the Fingers, we were set
upon by a large force of Bolton men.
Seemed to know exactly when we were traveling
and exactly whom we were transporting.
Do you take me
for a fool?
Tell me, Lord Royce,
how many people knew of my
travel plans with Sansa Stark?
I shared my intentions
with you
and no one else.
Slander a man
in his own home,
you might find yourself
crossing swords with him.
Your home is the Vale.
The Lord of the Vale stands before us.
And only his judgment
concerns me.
Shall we throw him
through the Moon Door?
My lord.
My lord, I have always been
faithful to House Arryn.
To your father, to your mother,
and now to you.
Do you believe him,
Uncle Petyr?
Lord Royce has served
the Vale well.
He's enjoyed a distinguished
military career.
If we could trust
his absolute loyalty,
he would make a capable
commander in the wars to come.
You can trust my absolute
loyalty, my lord.
I think he deserves one more chance.
What do you say?
Fine.
I bring good news.
My friends in the North tell me
Sansa has escaped Winterfell.
I expect she's headed
to Castle Black
where her brother serves
as Lord Commander.
But she won't be safe there,
not with the Boltons after her.
She's my cousin.
We should help her.
That was my instinct as well.
Our lord has spoken.
Gather the Knights
of the Vale.
The time has come
to join the fray.
You invite the enemy
into our city?
I did.
As a clever man
once told me,
"We make peace with our enemies,
not our friends."
I don't make peace
with the queen's enemies.
I kill
the queen's enemies.
Yes, that's
the military approach.
And how has that worked
here in Meereen?
I represent
the diplomatic approach.
Our queen tried to make
peace with the Masters
and they tried
to murder her.
We enter these negotiations
with open eyes.
Trust me.
My own recent experience with slavery
has taught me the horrors
of that institution.
How many days
were you a slave?
Long enough to know.
Not long enough
to understand.
I bought this dwarf
for a single gold honor.
And somehow you've risen
to the top of the Great
Pyramid of Meereen.
It's most impressive.
And now you speak for the
Good Masters of Astapor.
Here's to reversals
of fortune.
We came here
to meet the queen
and instead we're greeted
by a dwarf and a eunuch.
Let's make this simple, shall we?
Tell me what you want.
We want you to leave
Slaver's Bay.
Take your dragons and
your mercenaries and go.
Queen Daenerys won't stay
in Meereen forever.
Her path takes
her westward.
When we last met,
I offered her ships
so she could return to Westeros where
she belongs. She refused them.
She refused them because
hundreds of thousands
of men, women, and children
still lived in chains.
As they have
since the dawn of time.
- Not anymore.
- You think you're a free man now?
You still follow orders.
Just because your master
has silver hair and tits
doesn't mean
she's not a master.
Friends, friends,
friends, please.
There have always been those with wealth
and power and those with nothing.
That is the way of the world. I'm not
here to change the way of the world.
Slavery is the way
of our world.
You don't need slaves
to make money.
There haven't been slaves in
Westeros for hundreds of years
and I grew up richer
than any of you.
But our queen recognizes
that she erred
by abolishing slavery
without providing
a new system to replace it.
So here
is the queen's proposal.
Slavery will never
return to Meereen,
but she will give the other
cities of Slaver's Bay
time to adjust
to the new order.
What does that mean?
Instead of abolishing
slavery overnight,
we will give you seven
years to end the practice.
Slaveholders
will be compensated
for their losses,
of course, at fair prices.
In exchange,
you will cut off
your support for
the Sons of the Harpy.
We do not support
Fine, fine, but you will
cut it off all the same.
I do hope you accept,
my friends.
You will not receive
a better offer.
Let us sail
on the tide of freedom
instead of being
drowned by it.
And as a parting gift
to our honored guests...
Give freedom a chance.
See if it doesn't taste every bit
as good as what came before.
Perhaps I should
translate for you.
We speak
the Common Tongue.
- Excellent.
- You met with the slavers today.
I did.
Our brothers and sisters
died fighting this scum.
Now you invite them to our
city and drink wine with them.
I imagine
this room was built
so the rulers could
intimidate the ruled.
But I am not your ruler.
I'm not
the Breaker of Chains.
I'm not the Unburnt.
And I am certainly not
the Mother of Dragons.
You are a stranger here.
So why do you represent Meereen
in these talks with our enemies?
Because our queen
chose me as her advisor.
Until she returns
from her travels...
When does she return?
Soon.
You have my word.
We don't know you. We don't trust you.
We know Torgo Nudho.
We fight with him against the Masters.
We trust him.
And that is exactly why Grey Worm
took part in these negotiations.
As commander of the Unsullied, he
knows how to defeat the slavers
and he knows when
it is time to make peace.
You have made peace
with the slavers?
We offered terms.
- Do not use me for your lies.
- Those men respect you.
They respect me because
they know who I am.
- They know I am loyal.
- As do I.
I am loyal to my queen,
not you.
If you betray her work,
you are my enemy.
I am not betraying her work.
I am trying to save her city.
You promised the slavers
they could keep slavery.
For a short time.
Seven years is not a
short time for a slave.
You're right.
Slavery is a horror that
should be ended at once.
War is a horror that
I can't do both today.
You are wrong
to trust these men.
I don't trust the Masters.
I trust their self-interest.
They're trustworthy
if they're convinced
that working with me
is in their self-interest.
You don't know them.
You don't understand them.
We are not human
in their eyes.
They look at me
and see a weapon.
They look at her
and see a whore.
They look at me and they see
a misshapen little beast.
Their contempt
is their weakness.
They'll underestimate us every time and
we will use that to our advantage.
You will not use them.
They will use you.
That is what they do.
You all right?
Why don't you sit
and catch your breath?
I'm fine.
I don't think you
could ride the dragon.
20 years ago, maybe.
- What?
- Our queen.
She's wild, you know.
Don't let her size fool you.
It's hard enough for me
and I'm a young man.
You, I don't think
your heart could take it.
Must make you angry
that our queen chose me.
Makes me sad.
You'll disappoint her before long.
- She'll move on.
- We'll all disappoint her before long.
We need each other right now.
After we're done needing each other...
Oh, I don't want to fight you,
Jorah the Andal.
What do I have to gain?
If I win, I'm the shit
who killed an old man.
If I lose, I'm the shit
who was killed by an old man.
You didn't get much
discipline as a child, did you?
None.
The road running
through the Horse Gate,
they call that
the godsway.
Eastern Market,
Western Market.
When Khal Drogo died, she was supposed
to come here and join the Dosh Khaleen,
the widows
of the dead khals.
That's where they
would have taken her,
the Temple
of the Dosh Khaleen.
What are you doing?
It's forbidden to carry
weapons in the sacred city.
Isn't it forbidden to sneak into
their city and steal their khaleesi?
If they spot us
and we're unarmed,
we'll say we're traders heading
for the Western Market.
But if they see
weapons...
You're asking a dog
to hand over his teeth.
There's 100,000
of them down there.
We can't fight our way out.
We wait till dark,
and then we'll find her.
Uh...
I'm very attached
to this knife.
Don't worry.
It didn't touch you.
You know what happens?
I know what happens.
I'll do it myself.
I should have been
born a Dothraki.
Come on.
Told you,
I'm very attached to this knife.
You all right?
If they find a body
with a stab wound,
the whole city
will be looking for us.
Huh.
Mm-hmm.
- No, don't hurt her.
- She'll give us away.
We have to go now.
We will never get out
of Vaes Dothrak alive.
All we can do is try.
No.
We can do more than that.
And you're going
to help me.
If I were to let you leave right now,
where would you go?
What would you seek out?
I'd go to my brother,
my husband, my family.
Of course, but for you,
that means seeking out money,
finery, power.
Seeking out your family
means seeking out sin.
I'm not maligning you.
I sought
those things out, too.
To the exclusion
of all else.
My father was a cobbler.
He died when I was young
and I took over his shop.
He was a simple man
and he made simple shoes.
But I found that the more
work I put into my shoes,
the more people
wanted them.
Fine leather,
ornamentation,
detailing,
and time.
Time most of all.
Dozens of hours
spent on a single pair.
Quality takes time.
Yes.
I imagine
you've worn a year
of someone's life
on your back.
The highborn liked to cover
their feet with my time
and they paid well
for the privilege.
I used their money
to buy a taste of their
lives for myself.
Each time I indulged,
I felt myself ascending
to something better.
And one day you walked
through a graveyard
and realized it was
all for nothing
and set out on the path
to righteousness.
Book of the Stranger,
verse 25.
You know
"The Seven-Pointed Star."
Septa Unella reads it to me.
At me.
Yes, yes, she does enjoy
reading at people.
You're close.
But it wasn't
a graveyard.
It was a feast.
I bought old fine wine
and young pretty girls
and invited my friends
to come and share it all.
We passed around the wine,
passed around the women,
and soon we fell
into a stupor.
I woke before dawn.
I could barely stand.
Everyone else was asleep on
the couches or on the floor,
lying in heaps next
to their fine clothes.
The truth of their bodies
laid bare.
I could smell them
beneath the incense
and the perfume
and the fine food that had
already started to turn.
And I saw it
with perfect clarity.
I saw what my sins were.
The gold I had, the wine I drank,
the women I used,
my ceaseless struggle
to maintain my position.
It was all part
of a story.
A story I was telling
myself about who I was.
A collection of lies
that would disappear
in the light.
The people I was trying
to climb away from,
the beggars
in the street,
the poor,
they were closer to the
truth than I ever was.
So what did you do?
I left to go
and find them.
I didn't even
put on my shoes.
I walked out the door
and never went back.
Come, let's go and see him.
- Who?
- Your brother.
Loras.
Listen to me.
You need to stay strong.
I can't stay strong.
I never was strong.
You are strong.
You are the future
of our house,
the future
of our family.
- I don't care about that.
- Shh!
Shh.
Have you...
have you told them that?
That you don't care?
I just want it to stop.
Help me.
They want me
to help you.
They want me to help
tear you down.
That's why he's letting me see you.
I know it is.
And if either of us give in to
what they want, then they win.
Let them win.
Just make it stop.
Please.
All right.
And now, how to avert disaster
with our current predicament.
This High Sparrow.
I have dealt with fanatics of
every description, Your Grace.
Not setting them off,
that's the most important thing.
You are beset with enemies
both within and without.
What are you doing here?
I am advising the king
on our current predicament.
- Leave.
- I am a member of the small council.
The king...
Is this a small
council meeting?
Obviously not.
I'm here to lend my
wisdom and my support.
Thank you for your counsel,
Grand Maester.
That will be all
for now.
Your Grace.
Since I've missed the past
several small council meetings,
I wanted to speak to you
about a few things.
I've been thinking
about the High Sparrow.
As have we all,
unfortunately.
We need to be careful
in dealing with such a man.
To prevent things from
escalating any further.
We have to be careful
not to antagonize him.
He has Margaery.
We can't put her at risk.
- He's dangerous.
- Look at me.
What did they do to me?
To the king's own mother?
It's all right.
It's done.
It's in the past.
And of course
Margaery's safety
is paramount.
You don't
like Margaery, do you?
Whether I like her or not
is completely unimportant.
Margaery is the queen.
Queens must command respect.
Kings even more so.
Not just for their own sake,
but for everyone's.
The High Sparrow has no
respect for kings or queens.
No respect for anything
in this world.
He has no use for the
things of this world.
He wants to knock them down
and replace them with what?
With fantasies.
With beggars
in the street.
With nothing.
Mother...
there's something
I want to tell you.
Something the High
Sparrow told me.
You've spoken with him?
I promised him I wouldn't tell anyone.
If he found out I told...
It would be a breach of confidence
which he would not take lightly
given his constant
prattling about the truth.
I am your mother.
You can always trust me.
The small council meeting has been
postponed on the king's orders.
I would have thought we were
perfectly clear the first time.
- You're not welcome.
- You once spoke of your respect for our father
because he understood the necessity
of working with one's rivals.
My dear, you have been stripped
of your dignity and authority,
publically shamed,
and confined to the Red Keep.
What's left to work with?
Cersei is the mother
of the king.
She has the king's ear
and his trust.
And the king has been
speaking regularly
with the High Sparrow about
Queen Margaery and Ser Loras.
The High Sparrow
seized power
knowing full well we'd
bicker amongst ourselves
instead of
seizing it back.
Here we are.
Well done to us.
Now the future
of the Seven Kingdoms
rests in his dirty
peasant hands.
In a few days, he'll have
a trial for me.
But before that, Queen Margaery
will make her walk of atonement.
Yes, Margaery
will repent her sins
before the good people
of the city.
Oh, no.
That cannot happen.
That will not happen.
I agree.
You've got the second
largest army in Westeros.
You'll bring them
into the city,
stop Queen Margaery's
humiliation before it starts,
and take her back
into Crown custody.
The king has ordered me to take no
action against the High Sparrow
or the Faith Militant out of
fear for the queen's safety.
You will take
no action at all.
When the Tyrell armies come,
you will stand down.
Are you expressly forbidden
from standing down?
No, but if the king
should call...
The whole thing will be over before
anyone can call on you to do anything.
When the High Sparrow is in
custody or dead, preferably,
and Margaery's back
at Tommen's side,
do you think the king
will be angry at the outcome?
You hate these fanatics
as much as we do.
You hate what they've
done to your son.
Do you want Lancel back?
Or have you given
him up for good?
Of course
I want him back.
Then stand aside
and let the people that took
him from you be destroyed.
If it doesn't
go as planned,
the sparrows have
many friends in this city.
We'll have civil war.
Many will die.
Many will die
no matter what we do.
Better them than us.
They told me you were home
and I didn't believe it.
"Theon Greyjoy?"
I said.
"He's dead.
He's been dead
a long time."
He let you go?
I escaped.
I can't hear you.
Look at me.
Men died trying
to rescue you.
Good men.
My men.
I'm sorry.
You were my brother.
You were a spoiled little cunt,
but you were my brother
and I risked
everything for you
and you betrayed me.
I know.
I know and I'm sorry.
Stop saying that.
He broke me.
He broke me
into 1,000 pieces.
- I know.
- You don't know.
He sent us
one of those pieces.
That's why
I came for you.
Why did you come here?
Where else could I go?
You heard Father was dead and you
thought you'd claim the crown?
No, no. I only heard he
died after we docked.
You happen to show up on Pyke
right before the kingsmoot?
I didn't know.
You think any ironborn
wants you to be king
after what you've done?
I don't want
to be king.
What do you want?
I should have listened to you.
You're the only one...
That doesn't matter anymore.
Stop crying.
Look at me.
Tell me what you want.
You should rule
the Iron Islands.
Let me help you.
They've cleaned
you up nicely.
You know who I am?
A lord.
Yes.
You've seen my banners?
The flayed man.
Does that worry
you at all?
You eat them after?
No.
Then I've seen worse.
You served the Starks?
Aye.
They put me in chains
and put a sword
at my throat,
so I served them.
The Starks have been
gone for a long time,
but you kept
protecting Rickon.
He'd fetch a good price
to the right buyer.
I served his family
a long time.
Didn't get no wages.
Way I see it,
I'm owed.
Be that as it may,
Rickon's not yours
to sell anymore.
He's mine.
So what use could I
possibly have for you?
I can give you
what you want.
And you're sure
you know what that is?
Same thing
men always want.
And when they really want it,
they give it a bath first.
You're a good talker.
I like that.
You're a much better talker
than Theon Greyjoy.
That so?
I had to work hard
to get him talking.
But he talked.
They all do.
He told me everything.
All about the Stark boys,
who helped them escape,
and how she did it.
Open the gate!
Sorry about the food.
It's not what
we're known for.
That's all right.
There are more important things.
A letter for you,
Lord Commander.
I'm not Lord
Commander anymore.
"To the traitor
and bastard Jon Snow.
You allowed thousands
of wildlings past the Wall.
You have betrayed
your own kind.
the North.
Winterfell is mine, bastard.
Come and see.
Your brother Rickon
is in my dungeon.
His direwolf's skin
is on my floor.
Come and see.
I want my bride back.
Send her to me, bastard, and I will not
trouble you or your wildling lovers.
Keep her from me and I will
ride north and slaughter
every wildling man, woman, and
babe living under your protection.
You will watch as I skin them living.
You..."
Go on.
It's just more
of the same.
"You will watch as my soldiers
take turns raping your sister.
You will watch
as my dogs
devour your wild
little brother.
Then I will spoon your eyes from their
sockets and let my dogs do the rest.
Come and see.
Ramsay Bolton, Lord of Winterfell
and Warden of the North."
Lord of Winterfell
and Warden of the North.
His father's dead.
Ramsay killed him.
- And now he has Rickon.
- We don't know that.
Yes, we do.
How many men does
he have in his army?
I heard him say 5,000 once when he
was talking about Stannis's attack.
How many do you have?
That can march and fight?
2,000.
The rest are children
and old people.
You're the son of the last
true Warden of the North.
Northern families are loyal.
They'll fight for you if you ask.
A monster has taken
our home and our brother.
We have to go back to
Winterfell and save them both.