(WIND RUMBLING)
(SAMWELL SHIVERING)
NORTHMAN 1: Oi!
NORTHMAN 2: Mind out.
Move!
(PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
NORTHMAN: Look, on the west wall!
SOLDIER 1: Get down to the crypt!
(BABY CRYING)
SOLDIER 2: Just hold.
MAN: We'll take him.
(PANTING)
- LADY MORMONT: Come on, help the lads!
- (GASPS)
SOLDIER 3: Yes, my lady.
LADY MORMONT: Quickly, now! Quickly!
Get those in position.
SOLDIER 3: Come on.
SOLDIER 4: Close the gate!
SOLDIER 5: That's it.
(GRUNTS)
(WIND WHISTLING)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(DRAGON ROARING)
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(HORSES SNORTING AND NICKERING)
(SAMWELL CLEARS THROAT)
Oh, for fuck's sake.
You took your time.
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(HORSES SNORTING)
(WIND WHISTLING)
(DRAGONS GROWLING SOFTLY)
(SCREECHES)
(HORSE NEIGHING IN DISTANCE)
(HORSES SNORT)
Do you speak their tongue?
Tell them to lift their swords.
(WIND WHISTLING)
(SPEAKING DOTHRAKI)
(SWORDS CLANKING)
(CHANTING IN VALYRIAN)
(DOTHRAKI WARRIORS EXCLAIMING)
(DOTHRAKI WARRIORS
YELLING TRIUMPHANTLY)
Valar Morghulis.
Valar Dohaeris.
Open the gate!
SOLDIER 1: Open the gate!
SOLDIER 2: Open the gate!
MAN: Come. Come on.
Easy.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
There's no need to execute me,
Ser Davos.
I'll be dead before the dawn.
(DOTHRAKI WARRIOR
SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY)
(DOTHRAKI WARRIORS
YELLING AND ULULATING)
(ALL CONTINUE YELLING
AND ULULATING)
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(GHOST PANTING AND GROWLING)
(YELLING CONTINUES)
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
(DOTHRAKI WARRIORS
SHOUT IN DOTHRAKI)
Cease fire!
(WIGHTS SNARLING IN DISTANCE)
(YELLING FADING)
(YELLING STOPS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(HOOFBEATS POUNDING)
(STIFLED NEIGHING)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(HORSE SNORTING HEAVILY)
(HORSE NEIGHS)
(GASPING)
The Night King is coming.
The dead are already here.
(DROGON ROARS)
(BREATH TREMBLING)
(WIGHTS SNARLING IN DISTANCE)
(SOLDIERS GASPING QUIETLY)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(SNARLING GROWS LOUDER)
- (RUMBLING)
- (SNARLING CONTINUES)
- (GREY WORM SHOUTS IN VALYRIAN)
- (UNSULLIED GRUNT)
- (WIGHTS SCREECHING)
- (SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
(SOLDIERS GROAN AND SCREAM)
(YELLING)
Stand your ground!
- (WIGHTS SNARLING)
- (SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(BRIENNE GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(DROGON ROARS)
(SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(RHAEGAL ROARS)
- (WIND HOWLING)
- (GRUNTING)
(RHAEGAL SCREECHES)
(UNSULLIED GRUNTING RHYTHMICALLY)
(GRUNTING)
(DROGON SCREECHES)
ARYA: Get down to the crypt.
SANSA: I'm not abandoning my people.
ARYA: Take this and go.
I don't know how to use it.
Stick them with the pointy end.
(SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(SOLDIERS GRUNTING AND YELLING)
(WIGHT SCREECHES)
(HORSE NEIGHS)
(GRUNTING)
(BRIENNE YELLING)
- (WIGHTS SNARLING)
- (SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
SAMWELL: Edd!
Edd!
- (GASPING)
- (HISSING)
(WHIMPERING)
(PANTING)
(DISTORTED GRUNTING AND YELLING)
DOLOROUS EDD: Sam, get up!
- (WEAPON STABS)
- (GASPS)
(STRAINED) Oh, God. Sam.
(WIGHT SNARLING)
- (DOOR CLOSES, LOCKS)
- (GASPS)
(PEOPLE WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY)
(WIND HOWLING)
(RHAEGAL SCREECHES)
(JON GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
- (DROGON ROARS)
- (JON GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(JON GRUNTING)
(DRAGONS SCREECHING)
(GRUNTING)
Fall back! Fall back!
Fall back!
SOLDIER: Come on!
Open the gate!
SOLDIER 1: Open the gate!
SOLDIER 2: Let us in!
(CLAMORING)
SOLDIER 1: Open the gate!
SOLDIER 3: Open the gate!
SOLDIER 4: Keep moving!
SOLDIER 5: Come on!
(CLAMOR CONTINUES)
LADY MORMONT: Keep moving, fast.
SOLDIER 5: To your posts.
SOLDIER 6: Go!
SOLDIER 7: Keep moving!
SOLDIER 1: Come on, run!
SOLDIER 8: Keep moving!
(CLAMOR CONTINUES)
- (WIGHTS SNARLING)
- (SHOUTING IN VALYRIAN)
Protect the retreat!
Stand your ground!
(UNSULLIED GRUNT)
- (WIGHTS SNARLING)
- (UNSULLIED GRUNTING)
(SOLDIERS CLAMORING)
- (WIGHTS SNARLING)
- (SWORDS CLASHING)
(SCREECHING)
Dany!
(WIND WHISTLING)
(PANTING)
SOLDIER 1: Grab your weapon now!
SOLDIER 2: Guard the barricades!
SOLDIER 3: Through that pass!
BRIENNE: Hey! Hey! Hey!
SOLDIER 4: Close up the gaps!
Go! Hey! Go! Go!
Get in! Get in!
Get in! Come on!
(GREY WORM SHOUTING COMMAND)
(UNSULLIED GRUNTING RHYTHMICALLY)
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
(GRUNTING)
SOLDIER 1: Move!
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
(PANICKED SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(UNSULLIED SOLDIERS
SHOUTING IN VALYRIAN)
Retreat!
- (IN ENGLISH) Come on!
- Come on!
LADY MORMONT: Protect the gate!
SOLDIER 1: Protect the gate!
They're coming! Come on!
Fall back!
(UNSULLIED GRUNT)
(PANTING HEAVILY)
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
(SOLDIERS SCREAMING)
Light the trench!
SOLDIER 2: Wait!
SOLDIER 3: Light the trench!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTS)
(DROGON SCREECHING)
She can't see us.
Light the trenches!
- (WIGHTS SNARLING)
- (SOLDIERS YELLING)
SOLDIER 1: With a torch,
light the trenches!
- Right there.
- SOLDIER 2: Torch it!
Light the trenches!
(WIGHT SNARLS)
- (WIGHT SNARLS)
- (GRUNTS)
(PANTING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTING)
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
(UNSULLIED SOLDIER
SHOUTING IN VALYRIAN)
(UNSULLIED GRUNT)
(UNSULLIED SOLDIER
SHOUTS IN VALYRIAN)
(ALL GRUNT)
(UNSULLIED SOLDIER CONTINUES
SHOUTING IN VALYRIAN)
(GRUNTING)
- (SHOUTS IN VALYRIAN)
- (UNSULLIED GRUNT)
(CHANTING IN VALYRIAN)
(SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(SOLDIER SHOUTS INDISTINCTLY)
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
(CONTINUES CHANTING IN VALYRIAN)
- (WIGHTS SNARLING)
- (SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(CHANTS HALTINGLY)
(SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(RESUMES CHANTING IN VALYRIAN)
(WIGHTS SCREECHING)
(GASPS SOFTLY)
(UNSULLIED SOLDIER
SHOUTING IN VALYRIAN)
(UNSULLIED GRUNTING)
Clegane.
(BABY CRYING)
WOMAN: (WHISPERING)
You must try not to worry yourself.
(PEOPLE WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY)
(SIGHS)
At least we're already in a crypt.
If we were up there,
we might see something
everyone else is missing.
Something that makes a difference.
(SCOFFS)
What?
Remember the Battle of Blackwater?
I brought us through the Mud Gate.
- And got your face cut in half.
- And it made a difference.
If I was out there right now...
You'd die.
There's nothing you can do.
You might be surprised
at the lengths I'd go
to avoid joining
the Army of the Dead.
I could think of no organization
less suited to my talents.
Witty remarks
won't make a difference.
That's why we're down here,
none of us can do anything.
It's the truth.
It's the most heroic thing
we can do now...
look the truth in the face.
Maybe we should have stayed married.
You were the best of them.
What a terrifying thought.
It wouldn't work between us.
Why not?
The Dragon Queen.
Your divided loyalties
would become a problem.
MISSANDEI: Yes.
Without the Dragon Queen,
there'd be no problem at all.
We'd all be dead already.
(WIND WHISTLING)
They lit the trench.
Bran...
I just want you to know...
I wish...
The things I did...
Everything you did
brought you where you are now.
Where you belong.
Home.
I'm going to go now.
Go where?
(FAINT CAWING)
(RAVENS CAWING)
(WIND HOWLING)
(HEAVY WINGBEATS)
(CAWING CONTINUES)
(WIGHT SCREECHES)
(WIGHTS CONTINUE SCREECHING)
(SNARLING)
Man the walls!
SOLDIER 1: Man the walls!
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
Man the wall!
Man the walls!
(CLAMORING)
Come on!
Get out there! Get moving!
Come on. Come on! Come on!
Go, go, go!
Come on!
(ARCHERS GRUNTING)
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
(HEAVY WINGBEATS)
(VISERION SCREECHES)
(SCREECHING)
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
SOLDIER 1: They're against the wall!
(ARCHERS GRUNTING)
Get more men up here!
- Fill the gaps, quickly!
- Get in there!
SOLDIER 2: They're climbing the walls!
- Relieve the archers!
- SOLDIER 2: Relieve the archers!
Archers on top!
SOLDIER 1: Move up!
SOLDIER 2: Go, go! Come here!
- Come on!
- SOLDIER 3: Move back!
- SOLDIER 4: Stand away!
- Go on, go on. Go! Go.
SOLDIER 3: Step back.
SOLDIER 4: All the way, archers!
(PANTING)
(SPEAKS VALYRIAN)
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
SOLDIER 1: Hold the wall!
SOLDIER 2: The wall,
they're coming up!
SOLDIER 3: Hold the wall!
SOLDIER 4: Hold the wall!
Draw!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Come on!
(SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(SNARLS)
(SOLDIER YELLS)
(GRUNTS, SCREAMS)
(JAIME YELLS)
(BRIENNE GRUNTING)
SOLDIER: They're coming up!
(GRUNTS)
(STRAINING)
(BRIENNE YELLS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Look out!
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
- (WIGHT SNARLING)
- (YELPING)
(YELLS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (SAMWELL WHIMPERS)
(YELLING AND GRUNTING)
- (WIGHTS SNARLING)
- (SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(DISTRAUGHT SCREAMING)
- (WIGHTS SNARLING)
- (SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(SHUDDERING)
- (CHOKES)
- (CONTINUES SHUDDERING)
(GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
- (WIGHT SNARLS)
- (GRUNTING)
Clegane!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GRUNTING)
(SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(LADY MORMONT SHRIEKS)
(GRUNTS)
- (SNARLING)
- (ARYA GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
(SOLDIER SCREAMS)
- (SOLDIERS GRUNTING AND SCREAMING)
- (GROWLING)
(GROANING)
(SOLDIERS GRUNT)
- BERIC: Clegane!
- (BREATHING HEAVILY)
Clegane, we need you!
You can't give up on us.
Fuck off! We can't beat them.
Don't you see that, you stupid whore?
We're fighting Death!
They can't beat Death.
- (ARYA YELLING)
- (WIGHT SNARLING)
(GRUNTS)
Tell her that.
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING)
(LADY MORMONT GASPING)
- (GROWLS)
- (CHOKING)
(BONES CRACKING)
(LABORED BREATHING)
(GROWLS)
Ahhh!
(SCREECHING)
(SOLDIERS SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(SCREECHES)
(ROARS)
(WIND WHISTLING)
(DRAGON ROARS)
(JON GRUNTS)
(ROARING)
(DAENERYS WHIMPERING)
(STRAINING)
(PANTING)
(MUFFLED CLANG)
(MUFFLED CLATTERING)
(HINGES CREAK SOFTLY)
(PANTING QUIETLY)
(FOOTSTEPS)
(SHUFFLING)
(SWORD SCRATCHING)
(FAINT RATTLING, METAL CLINKS)
(METAL CLINKS)
(WIGHT CROAKS)
(SNARLING)
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
(GASPS SOFTLY)
(INHALES)
(MUFFLED SNARLING)
- (BREATHING SHAKILY)
- (MUFFLED FOOTSTEPS)
(SNARLING CONTINUES)
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
(PANTING)
(WHIMPERING)
- (SNARLING CONTINUES)
- (GASPING)
(SNARLING ECHOES)
- (MUFFLED SNARLING)
- (MEN YELLING IN DISTANCE)
(ALL BREATHING SHAKILY)
(MEN SCREAMING IN THE DISTANCE)
- (DOORS THUDS LOUDLY)
- (ALL GASP)
SOLDIER 1: Open the door!
- (MUFFLED SHOUTING)
- (MUFFLED DOOR BANGING)
SOLDIER 2: Open the door!
SOLDIER 3: Come on!
SOLDIER 4: Open the door!
Open the door!
- (SOLDIERS CLAMORING)
- (WIGHTS SCREECHING)
SOLDIER 4: Please!
Open it!
- (SOLDIERS SCREAMING)
- (SCREECHING CONTINUES)
(SCREAMING AND SCREECHING STOP)
(WIND WHISTLING)
(BOTH PANTING SOFTLY)
(MUFFLED RATTLING)
- (MUFFLED THUD)
- (GASPS)
(MUFFLED WIGHTS SNARLING)
(MUFFLED SCUFFLING)
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS)
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
(CRIES OUT)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (PANTING)
- (ARYA WHIMPERING)
HOUND: Come on! Go!
- Come on!
- BERIC: Run!
(HOUND YELLING)
(BERIC YELLING)
- (GASPS)
- (BERIC GRUNTS)
(SNARLING)
(BERIC AND ARYA GRUNTING)
HOUND: We've gotta go!
- (GROANING)
- (ARYA SHRIEKS)
- (WEAPON STABS)
- (GRUNTS)
(GRUNTS)
- (SNARLING CONTINUES)
- (PANTING)
(ARYA GRUNTS)
(LABORED BREATHING)
(WHEEZES)
(SIGHS)
(EXHALES SOFTLY)
MELISANDRE: The Lord brought him back
for a purpose.
Now that purpose has been served.
I know you.
And I know you.
You said we'd meet again.
And here we are.
At the end of the world.
You said I'd shut many eyes forever.
You were right about that too.
Brown eyes...
green eyes...
and blue eyes.
- (DOOR BANGS)
- (WIGHTS SNARLING)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
(SNARLING AND SCREECHING)
What do we say to the God of Death?
Not today.
(WIGHTS SNARLING NEARBY)
(WIND HOWLING)
Here they come!
Steady, lads.
Steady now.
Make every shot count.
(SNARLING)
MAN 1: Over there!
(SNARLING CONTINUES)
MAN 2: There!
(SCREECHES)
(SOLDIERS SCREAMING)
(SCREECHING)
(DRAGONS ROARING)
- (DRAGONS SCREECHING)
- (GASPS)
(SCREECHING CONTINUES)
Get off.
(GRUNTING)
(JON YELPS)
(GRUNTS)
(SCREECHING)
(JON GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(ROARS)
(SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(DROGON ROARING)
Dracarys.
(DROGON ROARS)
(DROGON SCREECHES)
(DAENERYS GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
(WIND HOWLING)
(GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(PANTS)
(PANTING)
(WIND WHISTLING)
- (SNARLING)
- (JON YELLS)
(WALL RUSTLING)
(GASPS)
(SNARLS)
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
(CRYING)
(ALL WHIMPER)
- (SNARLING)
- (GASPING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
Come on! Come on!
No! No, no, no!
(WIGHTS GROWLING)
(MEN GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(WIGHTS SCREECHING)
(GROWLS)
- Bran!
- Go!
- (WIGHTS SNARLING)
- (DROGON ROARS)
(GASPING)
(DROGON SNARLING)
(DROGON SCREECHING)
(WHIMPERING)
(DROGON CONTINUES SCREECHING)
(GRUNTS)
(WIGHTS SCREECHING)
(GASPS)
(DAENERYS WHIMPERING)
(SOLDIERS GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
(SAMWELL WHIMPERING)
(YELLS)
(JON GRUNTING)
(ALL GRUNTING)
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
(JON PANTING)
(JON GRUNTING)
(HISSING)
(JON GRUNTS)
(YELPS)
(GRUNTING)
- (MEN SCREAMING)
- (GRUNTS)
(MAN GRUNTS)
(GASPS)
- (WIGHTS SNARLING)
- (GRUNTING)
- (MAN SCREAMING)
- (THEON GRUNTING)
(SNARLS)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTING)
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING)
- (WIGHTS SNARLING)
(GASPING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(KISSES)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(DRAGON SCREECHING)
(GRUNTS)
(ALL GRUNTING)
DAENERYS: Jorah!
(WIGHTS SNARLING)
(GATE CRASHING)
(VISERION SCREECHES)
(JON GRUNTS)
(THEON GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
(SOBBING QUIETLY)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING HEAVILY)
BRAN: Theon.
You're a good man.
Thank you.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(YELLING)
(THEON GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
(JON GRUNTS)
(GROANING WEAKLY)
(GROANING STOPS)
(GRUNTS)
(VISERION ROARS)
(GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
(WIND WHOOSHES)
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
(ARYA GASPING)
(WIGHTS SCREECH)
(ROARING)
(WEAKLY) I'm hurt.
(SOBBING)
(CONTINUES SOBBING)
(HEAVY WINGBEATS)
(DROGON SCREECHES SOFTLY)
(PANTING)