Writen And Synchronized By : Hadi Farsi
H a d i . F a r s i @ Y a h o o . C o m
People love their king.
They know I saved the city,
they know I've won the war.
The war's not won.
It's tempting to see your enemies
as evil.
But there's good and evil on both sides
in every war ever fought.
They have a choice.
They can live in my new world,
or they can die in their old one.
Thing  ... are be tense right now
I don't think I'm talking my way out
of this one.
The wildlings breach the Wall
they'll roll over everything and every one.
Get any opportunity, what do we do
to those who hurt the ones we love?
I want to know which side you're on.
Tell your father I'm here.
And tell him the Lannisters are not
the only ones that pay their debts.
You fight over him like beasts
until you tear him apart.
I will burn our House to the ground
before I let that happen.
Polize?
tonight we fight!
There's only one Hell.
The one we live in now.
If you want justice ... you've come to the wrong place.