1
00:00:06,137 --> 00:00:10,385
<i>(Theme music playing )</i>

2
00:00:10,805 --> 00:00:18,841
<b><font color=#FFFF00>♪  ♪ </font></b>
<b><font color=#00FF00> Game of Thrones S06E02 </font></b>
<font color=#00FFFF>Home</font>
Original Air Date on May 01, 2016

3
00:00:18,941 --> 00:01:39,288
<b><font color=#FFFF00>♪ ♪</font></b>

4
00:01:39,296 --> 00:01:46,821
<b><font color=#FFFF00>♪ ♪</font></b>
Precisely Synchronized by <font color=#00FF00>srjanapala</font>


5
00:01:49,832 --> 00:01:51,492
<i><font color=#FFFF00> (Theme music playing ends) </font></i>

6
00:01:53,905 --> 00:01:56,428
( ravens cawing )

7
00:01:58,491 --> 00:02:01,414
<i>- ( cawing continues )
- ( wings flutter )</i>

8
00:02:03,108 --> 00:02:23,718
<i>( weapons clanking, Cawing again
echoing )</i>

9
00:02:23,821 --> 00:02:25,521
<i>( boys grunting, echoing )</i>

10
00:02:25,616 --> 00:02:39,675
<i>(Weapons clanking, boys grunting)</i>

11
00:02:40,657 --> 00:02:41,953
Give him another go, Ned.

12
00:02:43,643 --> 00:02:44,455
That's my father.

13
00:02:45,921 --> 00:02:46,912
And my Uncle Benjen.

14
00:02:47,960 --> 00:02:50,627
Keep your shield up or I'll
ring your head like a bell.

15
00:02:59,127 --> 00:03:00,308
They were all so happy.

16
00:03:02,547 --> 00:03:03,406
So were you once.

17
00:03:06,709 --> 00:03:07,718
( horse whinnies )

18
00:03:09,522 --> 00:03:11,512
- ( horse whinnies )
- Stop showing off.

19
00:03:13,027 --> 00:03:14,160
Benjen:
Lyanna!

20
00:03:14,694 --> 00:03:15,652
My Aunt Lyanna.

21
00:03:16,387 --> 00:03:18,035
<i>I've seen her statue in the crypt.</i>

22
00:03:19,499 --> 00:03:21,063
My father never talked about her.

23
00:03:28,439 --> 00:03:30,849
Benjen: <i>Would you get out of here?
We're sparring.</i>

24
00:03:31,080 --> 00:03:33,480
Who are you gonna spar with
when Ned goes off to the Eyrie?

25
00:03:35,107 --> 00:03:35,935
Benjen:
<i>I don't know.</i>

26
00:03:36,302 --> 00:03:37,264
What about him?

27
00:03:39,685 --> 00:03:41,505
Wylis, come here.

28
00:03:47,078 --> 00:03:48,073
Hodor?

29
00:03:49,407 --> 00:03:51,066
Benjen: <i>But he's got giant's blood.</i>

30
00:03:51,185 --> 00:03:54,316
And you've got training. Sounds
like a fair match to me.

31
00:03:54,963 --> 00:03:57,279
Benjen always lifts his chin
when he's about to charge.

32
00:03:57,526 --> 00:03:59,750
And lowers it when he's
going to dodge, my lady.

33
00:04:00,364 --> 00:04:01,388
Hodor talks?

34
00:04:07,947 --> 00:04:10,253
You leave the fighting
to the little lords, Wylis.

35
00:04:10,719 --> 00:04:13,039
Come along, now.
It's no place for you.

36
00:04:13,344 --> 00:04:15,763
Oh, Nan, look at the size of him.

37
00:04:15,962 --> 00:04:18,115
If he ever learned to
fight, he'd be unstoppable.

38
00:04:18,200 --> 00:04:20,993
Well, he's never going to learn to
fight because he's a stable boy.

39
00:04:21,376 --> 00:04:22,187
So leave him be.

40
00:04:23,714 --> 00:04:24,605
It is time to go.

41
00:04:25,611 --> 00:04:27,420
Please, a little longer.

42
00:04:31,685 --> 00:04:32,871
( gasps )

43
00:04:34,495 --> 00:04:35,031
<i>( raven caws )</i>

44
00:04:40,492 --> 00:04:42,770
You finally show me
something I care about

45
00:04:43,379 --> 00:04:44,686
and then you drag me away.

46
00:04:45,700 --> 00:04:47,588
It is beautiful beneath the sea,

47
00:04:49,005 --> 00:04:50,876
but if you stay too long,
you'll drown.

48
00:04:51,338 --> 00:04:55,002
I wasn't drowning.
I was home.

49
00:05:05,575 --> 00:05:06,192
<i>( raven caws )</i>

50
00:05:08,574 --> 00:05:09,145
Wylis.

51
00:05:10,861 --> 00:05:11,895
Hodor.

52
00:05:12,611 --> 00:05:13,575
I saw you as a boy.

53
00:05:14,659 --> 00:05:15,517
You could talk.

54
00:05:17,827 --> 00:05:18,128
What happened?

55
00:05:20,486 --> 00:05:21,099
Hodor.

56
00:05:27,029 --> 00:05:27,720
Where's Meera?

57
00:05:30,470 --> 00:05:30,981
Hodor.

58
00:05:58,656 --> 00:05:59,549
You shouldn't be here.

59
00:06:00,510 --> 00:06:01,978
It's not safe outside the cave.

60
00:06:02,736 --> 00:06:03,995
It's not safe anywhere.

61
00:06:07,842 --> 00:06:09,893
I saw that Hodor wasn't always Hodor.

62
00:06:10,228 --> 00:06:11,927
- Hodor.
- <i>His real name is Wylis.</i>

63
00:06:12,430 --> 00:06:15,590
And he could talk and
fight and-- and then--

64
00:06:17,838 --> 00:06:18,277
What's wrong?

65
00:06:22,392 --> 00:06:24,583
The Three-Eyed Raven
says there's a war coming.

66
00:06:25,162 --> 00:06:26,964
And we're going to fight it in there?

67
00:06:28,866 --> 00:06:30,616
( scoffs )

68
00:06:56,815 --> 00:06:58,288
Brandon Stark needs you.

69
00:07:01,871 --> 00:07:03,954
For what?
I sit in there

70
00:07:04,073 --> 00:07:06,072
and I watch him have his visions
and nothing ever happens.

71
00:07:06,459 --> 00:07:08,237
He isn't going to stay here forever.

72
00:07:08,918 --> 00:07:12,105
And out there he needs you.

73
00:07:38,624 --> 00:07:40,452
Alliser:
<i>It's time, Ser Davos.</i>

74
00:07:41,332 --> 00:07:43,270
Open the door and the men inside

75
00:07:43,284 --> 00:07:45,538
can rejoin their brothers in peace.

76
00:07:51,461 --> 00:07:55,384
We'll even set the wolf free north
of the Wall where it belongs.

77
00:07:59,469 --> 00:08:01,449
Nobody needs to die tonight.

78
00:08:05,526 --> 00:08:07,069
I've never been much of a fighter.

79
00:08:14,954 --> 00:08:16,720
Apologies for what
you're about to see.

80
00:08:16,883 --> 00:08:18,494
( Ghost growling )

81
00:08:24,664 --> 00:08:25,440
Come on.

82
00:08:43,258 --> 00:08:44,089
( growling )

83
00:08:45,966 --> 00:08:53,732
<i>( loud thudding )</i>

84
00:08:59,540 --> 00:09:07,137
(Loud Thud) (Door breaks)

85
00:09:07,186 --> 00:09:12,213
( shouting )

86
00:09:13,091 --> 00:09:14,272
Attack!

87
00:09:14,856 --> 00:09:15,716
( shouts )

88
00:09:22,564 --> 00:09:23,851
Fight, you cowards!

89
00:09:27,421 --> 00:09:28,315
( growls )

90
00:09:56,685 --> 00:09:58,291
You fucking traitor.

91
00:09:58,856 --> 00:10:00,940
The only traitors here are the ones

92
00:10:01,075 --> 00:10:03,727
who shoved their knives into
their Lord Commander's heart.

93
00:10:05,213 --> 00:10:07,245
For thousands of years
the Night's Watch

94
00:10:07,298 --> 00:10:09,688
has held Castle Black
against the wildlings.

95
00:10:11,045 --> 00:10:11,958
Until you.

96
00:10:12,315 --> 00:10:17,414
( shouts )

97
00:10:22,299 --> 00:10:25,159
Throw them into the cells
where they belong.

98
00:10:39,844 --> 00:10:40,923
<i>( door opens )</i>

99
00:10:58,276 --> 00:10:59,615
Tormund:
<i>Took a lot of knives.</i>

100
00:11:03,730 --> 00:11:05,529
I'll have my men
get the wood for a fire.

101
00:11:07,599 --> 00:11:08,724
Bodies to burn.

102
00:11:18,260 --> 00:11:19,693
<i>- ( people laughing )</i>
- Man:<i> Shh, hey.</i>

103
00:11:20,248 --> 00:11:23,747
Right, so there she is,
high and mighty Queen Cersei,

104
00:11:23,847 --> 00:11:25,627
tits and ass jiggling in the breeze.

105
00:11:26,684 --> 00:11:28,731
All of a sudden she looks my way.

106
00:11:29,208 --> 00:11:31,725
Gives me a little smile
like, "Well?"

107
00:11:32,211 --> 00:11:34,628
So, all right, you know,
I've never been shy

108
00:11:34,715 --> 00:11:37,383
and I'm blessed down south,
so I put it right out.

109
00:11:37,519 --> 00:11:40,386
- ( laughing )
- She's never seen anything like it.

110
00:11:40,472 --> 00:11:42,855
I mean, she's used to her
brother and from what I hear,

111
00:11:42,941 --> 00:11:45,142
Jaime Lannister's half
an inch shy of an inch.

112
00:11:45,226 --> 00:11:46,976
Ooh!

113
00:11:47,061 --> 00:11:50,952
She sees it and I swear to
the gods she licks her lips.

114
00:11:51,052 --> 00:11:52,017
( laughing )

115
00:11:52,152 --> 00:11:53,498
Well, you all know me.

116
00:11:53,520 --> 00:11:55,139
You know I wouldn't lie about this.

117
00:11:55,156 --> 00:11:57,572
( laughter )

118
00:12:10,589 --> 00:12:13,390
<i>( footsteps )</i>

119
00:12:31,278 --> 00:12:34,331
<i>- ( birds chirping )
- ( distant dog barking )</i>

120
00:12:41,817 --> 00:12:43,240
<i>( door opens )</i>

121
00:13:13,815 --> 00:13:15,033
Get out of my way.

122
00:13:15,329 --> 00:13:17,217
King's orders, Your Grace.

123
00:13:20,552 --> 00:13:21,688
What are the king's orders?

124
00:13:22,222 --> 00:13:24,781
He would like you to remain
in the Red Keep, Your Grace,

125
00:13:24,940 --> 00:13:25,946
for your own protection.

126
00:13:28,342 --> 00:13:30,661
You're barring me from attending
my own daughter's funeral?

127
00:13:31,097 --> 00:13:34,289
Forgive me, Your Grace, by the king's
command, I cannot let you pass.

128
00:13:37,574 --> 00:13:38,492
I would like to speak to my son.

129
00:13:38,906 --> 00:13:40,853
He has left the Red Keep, Your Grace.

130
00:14:00,728 --> 00:14:01,822
( exhales )

131
00:14:11,477 --> 00:14:12,233
She grew up.

132
00:14:13,897 --> 00:14:14,673
Jaime:
<i>Almost.</i>

133
00:14:16,032 --> 00:14:18,231
Have we caught Prince
Trystane's killers?

134
00:14:21,036 --> 00:14:22,227
I expect it was Mother.

135
00:14:23,239 --> 00:14:24,504
Your mother wouldn't do that.

136
00:14:25,326 --> 00:14:25,763
Yes, she would.

137
00:14:29,113 --> 00:14:30,406
Are you angry with her?

138
00:14:32,261 --> 00:14:34,211
- Of course not.
- Then why didn't you let her come?

139
00:14:34,920 --> 00:14:36,306
She has every right to be here.

140
00:14:37,757 --> 00:14:41,454
They told me she wouldn't
be allowed in the sept.

141
00:14:43,043 --> 00:14:43,576
If she had tried--

142
00:14:43,767 --> 00:14:45,865
I'm not putting
your mother in a cell ever again.

143
00:14:46,684 --> 00:14:47,792
Not while I'm here.

144
00:14:51,238 --> 00:14:52,996
Why haven't you gone to see her?

145
00:14:57,363 --> 00:14:59,877
Everything she endured,
she did it for you.

146
00:14:59,977 --> 00:15:01,267
Don't you think I know that?

147
00:15:06,123 --> 00:15:07,063
I'm sorry.

148
00:15:09,926 --> 00:15:10,910
But I can't.

149
00:15:11,845 --> 00:15:12,337
Why not?

150
00:15:14,632 --> 00:15:16,826
When the Faith Militant
seized her and Margaery,

151
00:15:18,833 --> 00:15:19,875
what did I do?

152
00:15:21,678 --> 00:15:23,840
When they paraded her through
the streets like a whore,

153
00:15:25,890 --> 00:15:26,744
what did I do?

154
00:15:27,982 --> 00:15:29,443
We all fail sometimes.

155
00:15:30,950 --> 00:15:34,237
The king is supposed to be
the Protector of the Realm.

156
00:15:34,438 --> 00:15:37,544
If I can't even protect my
own wife or my own mother,

157
00:15:37,592 --> 00:15:38,804
what good am I?

158
00:15:40,009 --> 00:15:42,310
Go and see your mother
and ask her to forgive you.

159
00:15:45,300 --> 00:15:46,425
Your Grace.

160
00:15:47,586 --> 00:15:49,191
Lord Commander.

161
00:15:49,957 --> 00:15:51,131
I want to see my wife.

162
00:15:52,225 --> 00:15:54,536
The gods wait for Queen Margaery

163
00:15:54,636 --> 00:15:57,315
to confess her crimes
and seek their mercy.

164
00:15:58,182 --> 00:16:00,878
The king must wait as well.

165
00:16:01,185 --> 00:16:02,964
Go and see your mother, Tommen.

166
00:16:14,033 --> 00:16:15,565
You're a bold man.

167
00:16:15,918 --> 00:16:16,899
( chuckles )

168
00:16:17,407 --> 00:16:18,312
On the contrary.

169
00:16:19,173 --> 00:16:20,601
I fear a great deal.

170
00:16:22,043 --> 00:16:24,255
The Father, the Mother,

171
00:16:25,370 --> 00:16:26,175
the Warrior.

172
00:16:37,444 --> 00:16:40,096
Do you know why we use these stones?

173
00:16:42,282 --> 00:16:43,616
To remind us not to fear death.

174
00:16:45,285 --> 00:16:48,470
We close our eyes on this world
and open them on the next.

175
00:16:48,556 --> 00:16:50,653
You must long for the next life.

176
00:16:52,911 --> 00:16:53,933
In truth, I fear that, too.

177
00:16:54,145 --> 00:16:57,042
You imprisoned
and humiliated my sister.

178
00:16:57,082 --> 00:16:59,758
Your sister sought the gods' mercy

179
00:17:00,203 --> 00:17:02,086
and atoned for her sin.

180
00:17:02,171 --> 00:17:03,601
What about my sins?

181
00:17:06,676 --> 00:17:09,536
I broke a sacred oath and
stabbed my king in the back.

182
00:17:12,065 --> 00:17:13,449
I killed my own cousin.

183
00:17:14,602 --> 00:17:16,199
When the gods judged
my brother guilty,

184
00:17:16,404 --> 00:17:18,269
I helped him escape their justice.

185
00:17:20,483 --> 00:17:22,221
What atonement do I deserve?

186
00:17:25,581 --> 00:17:27,749
You would spill blood
in this holy place?

187
00:17:28,723 --> 00:17:29,737
Oh, the gods won't mind.

188
00:17:30,453 --> 00:17:32,577
They've spilled more blood
than the rest of us combined.

189
00:17:34,876 --> 00:17:35,477
Go on, then.

190
00:17:37,128 --> 00:17:40,248
I deserve it.
We all do.

191
00:17:40,848 --> 00:17:42,497
We are weak, vain creatures.

192
00:17:43,552 --> 00:17:46,142
We live only by the Mother's mercy.

193
00:17:47,215 --> 00:17:48,501
( footsteps )

194
00:18:01,740 --> 00:18:04,466
They should be closer if you
mean for them to save you.

195
00:18:04,825 --> 00:18:05,596
I don't.

196
00:18:06,687 --> 00:18:08,486
They'd never reach me
before you struck.

197
00:18:09,831 --> 00:18:11,145
I've fought against worse odds.

198
00:18:11,584 --> 00:18:13,111
No doubt many of us would fall.

199
00:18:14,671 --> 00:18:16,989
But who are we, hmm?

200
00:18:17,807 --> 00:18:19,106
We have no names, no family.

201
00:18:20,561 --> 00:18:22,824
Every one of us
is poor and powerless.

202
00:18:24,566 --> 00:18:25,246
And yet together,

203
00:18:27,068 --> 00:18:28,789
we can overthrow an empire.

204
00:18:47,227 --> 00:18:47,674
( bird screeching )

205
00:18:55,849 --> 00:18:56,554
<i>( door opens )</i>

206
00:19:00,055 --> 00:19:00,781
Tommen:
<i>Mother.</i>

207
00:19:13,321 --> 00:19:15,540
Did they put her in the
red gown or the gold?

208
00:19:17,575 --> 00:19:19,017
Gold.

209
00:19:19,377 --> 00:19:21,580
Good. It was always her color.

210
00:19:24,166 --> 00:19:26,741
I'm sorry for keeping you here.

211
00:19:29,756 --> 00:19:31,309
<i>I shouldn't have,
but I was--</i>

212
00:19:34,762 --> 00:19:36,161
I didn't want to lose you again.

213
00:19:38,100 --> 00:19:39,093
I understand.

214
00:19:42,104 --> 00:19:42,969
I'm glad to see you.

215
00:19:47,109 --> 00:19:48,691
I know I should have come sooner.

216
00:19:49,746 --> 00:19:52,531
I wanted to.
I was wrong.

217
00:19:54,451 --> 00:19:55,505
It's all right.

218
00:19:59,281 --> 00:20:00,131
No, it isn't.

219
00:20:03,128 --> 00:20:04,949
I should have executed all of them.

220
00:20:05,931 --> 00:20:07,504
I should have pulled down the sept

221
00:20:07,800 --> 00:20:10,223
onto the High Sparrow's head
before I let them do that to you,

222
00:20:11,970 --> 00:20:13,562
as you would have for me.

223
00:20:15,441 --> 00:20:17,564
You raised me to be strong...

224
00:20:20,147 --> 00:20:21,020
and I wasn't.

225
00:20:23,118 --> 00:20:24,235
But I want to be.

226
00:20:27,822 --> 00:20:28,821
Help me.

227
00:20:33,996 --> 00:20:35,030
Always.

228
00:20:47,011 --> 00:20:49,479
<i>( bird screeching )</i>

229
00:20:55,437 --> 00:20:58,793
<i>( liquid pouring )</i>

230
00:21:02,361 --> 00:21:03,828
( tsks )

231
00:21:03,913 --> 00:21:06,084
If I lost my cock,
I'd drink all the time.

232
00:21:10,703 --> 00:21:11,809
Meaning no offense.

233
00:21:13,175 --> 00:21:15,369
He makes dwarf jokes,
I make eunuch jokes.

234
00:21:15,744 --> 00:21:17,170
I do not make dwarf jokes.

235
00:21:17,230 --> 00:21:19,150
- You think them.
- ( sighs )

236
00:21:19,332 --> 00:21:24,045
So, the fleet.
It's been burned.

237
00:21:24,245 --> 00:21:28,025
We are searching for the men who burned
the ships, but nobody saw anything.

238
00:21:28,226 --> 00:21:30,339
Surely there's some good
news lurking somewhere.

239
00:21:30,611 --> 00:21:32,894
Astapor and Yunkai have
stopped asking us for aid.

240
00:21:33,781 --> 00:21:35,515
Perhaps they can
tell us their secret.

241
00:21:36,434 --> 00:21:38,169
The Masters have retaken both cities.

242
00:21:39,111 --> 00:21:43,208
Outside of Meereen, the whole of Slaver's
Bay has returned to the slavers.

243
00:21:45,412 --> 00:21:49,509
What about the dragons? We have two
of them here beneath the pyramid.

244
00:21:49,916 --> 00:21:50,940
They are not eating.

245
00:21:51,750 --> 00:21:54,330
They haven't touched any food
since Queen Daenerys left.

246
00:21:54,587 --> 00:21:56,573
Daenerys is the dragon queen.

247
00:21:57,425 --> 00:22:00,000
Can't very well let the dragons
starve, that's obvious.

248
00:22:00,344 --> 00:22:03,433
If a dragon does not want to eat,
how do you force him to eat?

249
00:22:03,764 --> 00:22:06,118
Dragons do not do well in captivity.

250
00:22:06,318 --> 00:22:08,233
- How do you know this?
- That's what I do.

251
00:22:09,115 --> 00:22:11,089
I drink and I know things.

252
00:22:13,511 --> 00:22:16,487
The dragons Aegon used
to conquer Westeros

253
00:22:16,562 --> 00:22:18,663
ranged over hundreds of miles.

254
00:22:19,349 --> 00:22:20,586
Then Daenerys's ancestors

255
00:22:20,834 --> 00:22:22,854
started chaining them up in pens.

256
00:22:24,289 --> 00:22:25,414
A few generations later,

257
00:22:26,341 --> 00:22:29,283
the last dragons
were no larger than cats.

258
00:22:30,129 --> 00:22:32,487
They must be unchained
or they'll waste away.

259
00:22:34,634 --> 00:22:35,169
Missandei,

260
00:22:36,892 --> 00:22:39,490
how many times were you in the
company of these dragons?

261
00:22:40,430 --> 00:22:43,628
- Many times.
- And did they ever harm you?

262
00:22:44,784 --> 00:22:45,294
Never.

263
00:22:46,331 --> 00:22:47,486
Dragons are intelligent.

264
00:22:48,421 --> 00:22:51,014
More intelligent than men
according to some maesters.

265
00:22:52,231 --> 00:22:53,366
They have affection for their friends

266
00:22:53,822 --> 00:22:55,015
and fury for their enemies.

267
00:22:57,326 --> 00:22:59,589
- I am their friend.
- Do they know that?

268
00:22:59,863 --> 00:23:02,760
They will. It's time
they had their supper.

269
00:23:05,359 --> 00:23:06,949
<i>( door closes )</i>

270
00:23:32,059 --> 00:23:34,417
<i>( metal scraping, clanging )</i>

271
00:24:03,786 --> 00:24:06,787
( growling )

272
00:24:06,905 --> 00:24:09,156
( chains rattling )

273
00:24:14,831 --> 00:24:17,716
( roars )

274
00:24:27,345 --> 00:24:30,264
( roars )

275
00:24:33,820 --> 00:24:35,263
I'm friends with your mother.

276
00:24:36,439 --> 00:24:39,458
( roaring )

277
00:24:43,163 --> 00:24:44,431
I'm here to help.

278
00:24:45,918 --> 00:24:47,950
Don't eat the help.
( chuckles nervously )

279
00:24:48,085 --> 00:24:51,421
( roaring )

280
00:24:52,757 --> 00:24:54,022
When I was a child,

281
00:24:54,260 --> 00:24:57,678
an uncle asked what gift
I wanted for my name day.

282
00:24:57,964 --> 00:25:00,598
I begged him for one of you.

283
00:25:00,683 --> 00:25:03,605
"It wouldn't even have to be
a big dragon," I told him.

284
00:25:06,056 --> 00:25:07,732
"It could be little
like me."

285
00:25:14,983 --> 00:25:18,583
Everyone laughed like it was the
funniest thing they had ever heard.

286
00:25:20,156 --> 00:25:21,553
Then my father told me

287
00:25:22,442 --> 00:25:25,824
the last dragon had died
a century ago.

288
00:25:27,318 --> 00:25:29,207
I cried myself to sleep that night.

289
00:25:38,926 --> 00:25:40,079
But here you are.

290
00:25:55,830 --> 00:25:57,569
( gasps )

291
00:25:57,769 --> 00:26:49,756
( growling )

292
00:26:49,955 --> 00:26:51,058
Next time I have an idea like that,

293
00:26:51,143 --> 00:26:52,542
punch me in the face.

294
00:26:58,100 --> 00:27:03,004
<i>- ( thunder rumbling )
- ( female merchant shouting )</i>

295
00:27:04,270 --> 00:27:06,057
<i>( footsteps )</i>

296
00:27:06,944 --> 00:27:08,001
What's your name?

297
00:27:08,863 --> 00:27:10,196
<i>( coins clink )</i>

298
00:27:10,281 --> 00:27:11,781
( grunts )

299
00:27:11,916 --> 00:27:15,118
<i>( thunder rumbles )</i>

300
00:27:15,253 --> 00:27:16,057
What's your name?

301
00:27:17,423 --> 00:27:20,791
- No one.
- I don't believe that.

302
00:27:20,877 --> 00:27:22,468
- ( grunts )
- You don't believe that.

303
00:27:22,476 --> 00:27:23,078
( grunts )

304
00:27:23,385 --> 00:27:23,685
( panting )

305
00:27:38,814 --> 00:27:50,981
( shouting )

306
00:27:54,665 --> 00:27:55,241
Who are you?

307
00:27:58,669 --> 00:27:59,505
No one.

308
00:27:59,804 --> 00:28:01,299
If a girl says her name,

309
00:28:02,307 --> 00:28:04,604
a man will let her sleep
under a roof tonight.

310
00:28:05,394 --> 00:28:06,773
A girl has no name.

311
00:28:07,814 --> 00:28:09,586
If a girl says her name,

312
00:28:09,648 --> 00:28:11,392
a man will feed her tonight.

313
00:28:12,911 --> 00:28:13,838
A girl has no name.

314
00:28:16,106 --> 00:28:17,273
If a girl says her name,

315
00:28:17,408 --> 00:28:19,236
a man will give her eyes back.

316
00:28:22,321 --> 00:28:23,392
A girl has no name.

317
00:28:31,740 --> 00:28:32,586
Come.

318
00:28:42,302 --> 00:28:43,204
Leave it.

319
00:28:44,306 --> 00:28:45,953
<i>A girl is not a beggar anymore.</i>

320
00:28:47,475 --> 00:28:54,912
<i>( thunder rumbling )</i>

321
00:28:55,817 --> 00:28:58,148
We came upon the bodies
on our way here.

322
00:29:00,028 --> 00:29:03,190
Half a dozen men?
Your best hunters?

323
00:29:03,391 --> 00:29:04,775
They obviously had help.

324
00:29:05,128 --> 00:29:07,740
I didn't think Lady Sansa
killed them all by herself.

325
00:29:09,300 --> 00:29:10,970
Thank you for this report,
Lord Karstark.

326
00:29:12,320 --> 00:29:13,495
We know where she's going.

327
00:29:14,172 --> 00:29:15,537
Her brother's at Castle Black.

328
00:29:15,906 --> 00:29:17,341
Ned Stark's last surviving son?

329
00:29:17,410 --> 00:29:19,710
Jon Snow is a bastard, not a Stark.

330
00:29:21,146 --> 00:29:23,081
So was I, Father.

331
00:29:23,280 --> 00:29:25,133
Your hold on the North
will never be secure

332
00:29:25,218 --> 00:29:27,567
as long as a Stark
can walk through that door.

333
00:29:27,767 --> 00:29:30,328
Castle Black isn't defended
on the southern side.

334
00:29:30,527 --> 00:29:33,963
And the few men left are barely men at all.
Farm boys and thieves.

335
00:29:34,362 --> 00:29:38,280
With a small force, we could storm
the castle, kill Jon Snow--

336
00:29:38,416 --> 00:29:41,281
Murder the Lord Commander
of the Night's Watch?

337
00:29:41,480 --> 00:29:43,770
You'd unite every house
in the North against us.

338
00:29:45,742 --> 00:29:47,881
We don't need
every house in the North.

339
00:29:48,081 --> 00:29:50,495
<i>The Umbers, the Manderlys,
and the Karstarks</i>

340
00:29:50,579 --> 00:29:52,609
command more soldiers than all
the other houses combined.

341
00:29:54,635 --> 00:29:57,329
With their support,
none could challenge us.

342
00:29:57,689 --> 00:30:01,325
The Starks lost my house the day
King Robb cut off my father's head.

343
00:30:02,481 --> 00:30:04,168
It's time for new blood in the North.

344
00:30:13,824 --> 00:30:16,272
If you acquire a
reputation as a mad dog,

345
00:30:16,359 --> 00:30:17,924
you'll be treated as a mad dog.

346
00:30:18,578 --> 00:30:21,090
Taken out back and
slaughtered for pig feed.

347
00:30:22,403 --> 00:30:23,234
Maester:
<i>My lords.</i>

348
00:30:24,837 --> 00:30:26,529
<i>Lady Walda has given birth.</i>

349
00:30:27,306 --> 00:30:28,298
A boy.

350
00:30:29,341 --> 00:30:31,483
<i>Red-cheeked
and healthy.</i>

351
00:30:31,977 --> 00:30:33,804
My congratulations, Lord Bolton.

352
00:30:44,608 --> 00:30:45,788
Congratulations, Father.

353
00:30:47,779 --> 00:30:49,926
I look forward to meeting
my new brother.

354
00:30:54,953 --> 00:30:56,555
You'll always be my firstborn.

355
00:30:58,876 --> 00:30:59,890
Thank you for saying that.

356
00:31:01,261 --> 00:31:02,863
It means a great deal to me.

357
00:31:06,100 --> 00:31:08,767
- <i>( flesh squelches )</i>
- ( groans )

358
00:31:40,004 --> 00:31:41,222
Maester Wolkan,

359
00:31:42,391 --> 00:31:45,767
<i>send ravens to all the northern houses.
Roose Bolton is dead.</i>

360
00:31:47,610 --> 00:31:48,973
Poisoned by our enemies.

361
00:31:56,913 --> 00:31:57,891
How did he die?

362
00:32:01,993 --> 00:32:04,611
Poisoned by his enemies.

363
00:32:04,918 --> 00:32:07,181
You're talking to your lord.
Use respect.

364
00:32:09,289 --> 00:32:10,850
Forgive me, my lord.

365
00:32:14,296 --> 00:32:16,331
Send for Lady Walda and the baby.

366
00:32:17,849 --> 00:32:19,542
She's resting, my lord.

367
00:32:23,220 --> 00:32:24,724
At once, my lord.

368
00:32:40,157 --> 00:32:51,527
<i>( men shouting )</i>

369
00:32:51,728 --> 00:32:52,134
There he is.

370
00:32:52,221 --> 00:32:53,645
Isn't he wonderful?

371
00:32:57,844 --> 00:32:59,157
May I hold him?

372
00:33:00,982 --> 00:33:02,109
Of-- of course.

373
00:33:13,110 --> 00:33:13,887
Little brother.

374
00:33:16,198 --> 00:33:17,585
Lord Bolton sent for us.

375
00:33:18,200 --> 00:33:19,646
Have you seen him?

376
00:33:28,429 --> 00:33:30,899
Of course.
Follow me, Mother.

377
00:33:41,109 --> 00:33:43,110
<i>( dogs barking )</i>

378
00:33:49,118 --> 00:33:51,069
Where is Lord Bolton?

379
00:33:52,957 --> 00:33:55,574
- ( barking continues )
- ( clanging )

380
00:34:01,249 --> 00:34:03,083
- Down!
- ( barking stops )

381
00:34:03,217 --> 00:34:06,086
<i>- ( baby fussing )</i>
- Walda:<i> It's all right. Come on, shh.</i>

382
00:34:06,220 --> 00:34:09,641
<i>It's cold out here, Ramsay.
I need to feed him.</i>

383
00:34:15,766 --> 00:34:18,220
Ramsay, where is your father?

384
00:34:19,939 --> 00:34:20,646
Ramsay.

385
00:34:29,698 --> 00:34:30,628
Where is Lord Bolton?

386
00:34:38,459 --> 00:34:39,885
I am Lord Bolton.

387
00:34:45,967 --> 00:34:47,800
( crying )

388
00:34:50,622 --> 00:34:51,335
Ramsay.

389
00:34:52,640 --> 00:34:53,554
Ramsay, please.

390
00:34:54,443 --> 00:34:56,533
I'll leave Winterfell.
I'll go back to the Riverlands.

391
00:35:02,486 --> 00:35:03,413
Please.

392
00:35:04,489 --> 00:35:05,459
Ramsay.

393
00:35:08,376 --> 00:35:09,433
He's your brother.

394
00:35:13,165 --> 00:35:14,828
I prefer being an only child.

395
00:35:15,802 --> 00:35:18,418
<i>( dogs growling )</i>

396
00:35:18,505 --> 00:35:20,054
( whistles )

397
00:35:20,173 --> 00:35:22,673
( barking )

398
00:35:22,759 --> 00:35:25,260
( screaming )

399
00:35:25,345 --> 00:35:27,562
<i>( flesh tearing )</i>

400
00:35:35,991 --> 00:35:38,420
Brienne:
<i>I saw her with a man.</i>

401
00:35:38,495 --> 00:35:40,405
I don't think he hurt her.

402
00:35:40,912 --> 00:35:43,242
She didn't want to leave him,
he didn't want to leave her.

403
00:35:46,269 --> 00:35:47,535
You don't know which way she went?

404
00:35:47,688 --> 00:35:49,404
I spent three days looking for her.

405
00:35:50,457 --> 00:35:51,656
She disappeared.

406
00:35:54,295 --> 00:35:55,533
How'd she look?

407
00:35:55,880 --> 00:35:56,892
She looked good.

408
00:35:58,133 --> 00:36:00,429
She wasn't exactly
dressed like a lady.

409
00:36:02,522 --> 00:36:03,413
No, she wouldn't be.

410
00:36:06,309 --> 00:36:07,621
What happened at Winterfell?

411
00:36:19,907 --> 00:36:21,903
I should have gone with you
while I had the chance.

412
00:36:23,579 --> 00:36:26,073
It was a difficult choice, my lady.

413
00:36:30,921 --> 00:36:32,937
We've all had to make
difficult choices.

414
00:36:34,423 --> 00:36:38,259
<i>- ( birds screech )
- ( horse whinnies )</i>

415
00:36:53,863 --> 00:36:56,081
We shouldn't be lighting fires.

416
00:36:56,166 --> 00:36:57,249
It's not safe.

417
00:36:57,334 --> 00:36:58,518
He won't stop hunting us.

418
00:36:58,677 --> 00:37:00,352
We just have to make it
to Castle Black.

419
00:37:00,552 --> 00:37:02,749
Once we're with Jon, Ramsay
won't be able to touch us.

420
00:37:03,123 --> 00:37:05,620
Jon will have me killed the
moment I step through the gate.

421
00:37:05,743 --> 00:37:06,682
I won't let him.

422
00:37:07,595 --> 00:37:09,582
I'll tell him the truth
about Bran and Rickon.

423
00:37:11,995 --> 00:37:14,492
And the truth about the farm
boys I killed in their place.

424
00:37:15,140 --> 00:37:17,322
And the truth about
Ser Rodrik, who I beheaded.

425
00:37:21,061 --> 00:37:22,620
And the truth about Robb,
who I betrayed.

426
00:37:25,700 --> 00:37:27,768
When you take the black,
all your crimes are forgiven.

427
00:37:27,820 --> 00:37:29,604
I don't want to be forgiven.

428
00:37:32,416 --> 00:37:34,265
I can never make
amends to your family

429
00:37:34,358 --> 00:37:35,445
for the things I've done.

430
00:37:38,047 --> 00:37:39,886
They'll keep you safer
than I ever could.

431
00:37:45,656 --> 00:37:46,724
You're not coming with us?

432
00:37:50,357 --> 00:37:55,944
I would have taken you
all the way to the Wall.

433
00:37:56,144 --> 00:37:56,349
I would have died to get you there.

434
00:38:00,542 --> 00:38:01,510
( crying )

435
00:38:13,202 --> 00:38:14,606
May I take one of the horses?

436
00:38:19,042 --> 00:38:20,159
Where will you go?

437
00:38:24,049 --> 00:38:24,699
Home.

438
00:38:28,888 --> 00:38:31,855
<i>( thunder rumbling )</i>

439
00:38:34,846 --> 00:38:36,860
Yara: <i>The Glovers have
retaken Deepwood Motte.</i>

440
00:38:39,065 --> 00:38:40,595
And the ironborn who held it?

441
00:38:41,201 --> 00:38:43,672
They died fighting to a man.

442
00:38:45,990 --> 00:38:47,759
What is dead may never die.

443
00:38:48,293 --> 00:38:49,670
What is dead may never die.

444
00:38:50,580 --> 00:38:51,457
But they did

445
00:38:52,715 --> 00:38:54,441
and our invasion died with them.

446
00:38:55,469 --> 00:38:58,338
Deepwood Motte was our last
stronghold on the mainland.

447
00:38:58,422 --> 00:38:59,811
Then we will take more.

448
00:39:00,124 --> 00:39:03,257
Why? For more pinecones and rocks?

449
00:39:05,847 --> 00:39:07,759
Because I order it.

450
00:39:07,799 --> 00:39:09,748
We can defeat anyone at sea,

451
00:39:10,558 --> 00:39:12,255
but we'll never hold
lands and castles

452
00:39:12,272 --> 00:39:13,504
against mainland armies.

453
00:39:13,757 --> 00:39:16,523
Not if our captains defy my orders,

454
00:39:16,643 --> 00:39:20,968
abandon their posts, and sacrifice
our men on foolish missions.

455
00:39:20,981 --> 00:39:22,921
I won't apologize
for trying to rescue Theon.

456
00:39:22,933 --> 00:39:23,994
Then where is he?

457
00:39:24,135 --> 00:39:25,390
Where is your kingdom?

458
00:39:27,486 --> 00:39:30,409
We took those castles because the
northerners marched off to war.

459
00:39:30,971 --> 00:39:32,444
That war is over.

460
00:39:32,977 --> 00:39:34,788
The last time
we provoked them too far,

461
00:39:34,912 --> 00:39:37,399
I watched from that window
as they breached our walls

462
00:39:37,416 --> 00:39:38,846
<i>and knocked down our towers.</i>

463
00:39:39,753 --> 00:39:41,514
<i>I lost two brothers that day.</i>

464
00:39:41,570 --> 00:39:43,387
And I lost three sons.

465
00:39:45,934 --> 00:39:47,673
The War of the Five
Kings, they call it.

466
00:39:47,678 --> 00:39:49,193
Well, the other four are dead.

467
00:39:49,681 --> 00:39:52,851
When you rule the Iron Islands, you
can wage all the peace you want.

468
00:39:52,917 --> 00:39:54,739
But for now, shut your mouth and obey

469
00:39:54,786 --> 00:39:57,368
or I will make another heir who will.

470
00:40:04,130 --> 00:40:05,996
<i>( thunder crashing )</i>

471
00:40:06,082 --> 00:40:08,382
( wind howling )

472
00:40:36,650 --> 00:40:37,657
Let me pass.

473
00:40:41,376 --> 00:40:43,509
You fool, move aside for your king.

474
00:40:45,054 --> 00:40:46,571
Haven't I always, brother?

475
00:40:57,007 --> 00:41:00,955
I thought you'd be rotting
under some foreign sea by now.

476
00:41:02,583 --> 00:41:04,479
What is dead may never die.

477
00:41:07,235 --> 00:41:09,797
Has the custom changed
since I've been gone?

478
00:41:10,288 --> 00:41:12,038
Aren't you supposed
to repeat the words?

479
00:41:12,624 --> 00:41:15,247
You can mock our god without my help.

480
00:41:15,794 --> 00:41:17,502
I don't mock the Drowned God.

481
00:41:18,664 --> 00:41:20,524
I am the Drowned God.

482
00:41:21,634 --> 00:41:23,149
From Oldtown to Qarth,

483
00:41:23,187 --> 00:41:26,628
when men see my sails, they pray.

484
00:41:27,258 --> 00:41:30,093
( wind howls )

485
00:41:36,067 --> 00:41:38,705
( chuckles )
You're old, brother.

486
00:41:39,605 --> 00:41:40,965
<i>You've had your time.</i>

487
00:41:41,524 --> 00:41:42,859
Now let another rule.

488
00:41:43,944 --> 00:41:46,275
I heard you lost your mind

489
00:41:47,197 --> 00:41:49,698
during a storm on the Jade Sea.

490
00:41:50,367 --> 00:41:54,798
They tied you to the mast to
keep you from jumping overboard.

491
00:41:55,841 --> 00:41:56,786
They did.

492
00:41:57,159 --> 00:42:00,685
And when the storm passed,
you cut out their tongues.

493
00:42:02,230 --> 00:42:03,271
I needed silence.

494
00:42:05,252 --> 00:42:06,895
What kind of an ironborn

495
00:42:07,425 --> 00:42:10,376
loses his senses during a storm?

496
00:42:12,424 --> 00:42:14,264
I am the storm, brother.

497
00:42:15,646 --> 00:42:17,244
The first storm and the last.

498
00:42:19,452 --> 00:42:20,674
And you're in my way.

499
00:42:24,923 --> 00:42:28,750
( screaming )

500
00:42:34,802 --> 00:42:36,969
<i>( thunder crashes )</i>

501
00:42:59,529 --> 00:43:02,577
Lord, take your servant Balon
back beneath the waves.

502
00:43:04,135 --> 00:43:06,485
Feed the creatures of your
kingdom on his flesh.

503
00:43:07,517 --> 00:43:09,008
Pull his bones down to your depths

504
00:43:09,075 --> 00:43:11,966
to rest beside his ancestors
and his children.

505
00:43:12,545 --> 00:43:13,999
All: What is dead may never die.

506
00:43:24,123 --> 00:43:25,774
I'm going to find out who did this.

507
00:43:26,862 --> 00:43:28,994
I'm going to feed them to
the sharks while they live.

508
00:43:31,789 --> 00:43:33,054
I swear it by the Salt Throne.

509
00:43:34,286 --> 00:43:36,249
The Salt Throne is not
yours to swear upon,

510
00:43:37,239 --> 00:43:38,971
not unless the kingsmoot chooses you.

511
00:43:39,426 --> 00:43:41,167
My father would have
wanted me to rule.

512
00:43:41,177 --> 00:43:44,036
Your father does not get to choose.
The law is clear.

513
00:43:46,917 --> 00:43:47,971
Perhaps you'll win.

514
00:43:49,169 --> 00:43:51,814
Perhaps you'll be the first woman
in history to rule the ironborn.

515
00:43:53,675 --> 00:43:54,533
And perhaps not.

516
00:44:10,410 --> 00:44:10,609
<i>( knocks )</i>

517
00:44:12,279 --> 00:44:13,089
Come in.

518
00:44:20,121 --> 00:44:22,770
I'm sorry, my lady.
Didn't mean to interrupt.

519
00:44:23,926 --> 00:44:25,244
You interrupt nothing.

520
00:44:37,725 --> 00:44:39,993
I assume you know why I'm here.

521
00:44:42,147 --> 00:44:43,647
I will after you tell me.

522
00:44:43,782 --> 00:44:45,696
It's about the Lord Commander.

523
00:44:46,068 --> 00:44:47,465
The former Lord Commander.

524
00:44:49,872 --> 00:44:50,685
Does he have to be?

525
00:44:54,828 --> 00:44:55,830
What are you asking?

526
00:45:00,568 --> 00:45:04,266
Do you know of any magic...

527
00:45:06,100 --> 00:45:07,039
that could help him?

528
00:45:08,688 --> 00:45:09,388
Bring him back?

529
00:45:09,678 --> 00:45:12,014
If you want to help him,
leave him be.

530
00:45:12,099 --> 00:45:12,896
Can it be done?

531
00:45:14,684 --> 00:45:16,719
There are some with this power.

532
00:45:16,853 --> 00:45:19,564
- <i>How?</i>
- I don't know.

533
00:45:19,624 --> 00:45:20,810
Have you seen it done?

534
00:45:24,328 --> 00:45:26,453
I met a man who came
back from the dead,

535
00:45:26,464 --> 00:45:27,752
but the priest
who did it--

536
00:45:30,626 --> 00:45:31,802
it shouldn't have been possible.

537
00:45:31,887 --> 00:45:34,837
But it was.
It could be now.

538
00:45:35,373 --> 00:45:36,865
Not for me.

539
00:45:41,848 --> 00:45:42,353
Not for you?

540
00:45:47,954 --> 00:45:50,261
I saw you drink poison that
should have killed you.

541
00:45:51,813 --> 00:45:54,044
I saw you give birth
to a demon made of shadows.

542
00:45:54,230 --> 00:45:55,361
Everything I believed,

543
00:45:57,369 --> 00:45:59,766
the great victory
I saw in the flames,

544
00:46:00,386 --> 00:46:01,743
all of it was a lie.

545
00:46:06,711 --> 00:46:07,943
You were right all along.

546
00:46:09,192 --> 00:46:10,546
The Lord never spoke to me.

547
00:46:11,581 --> 00:46:12,701
Fuck him, then.

548
00:46:13,214 --> 00:46:13,992
Fuck all of them.

549
00:46:17,147 --> 00:46:19,627
I'm not a devout man, obviously.

550
00:46:20,686 --> 00:46:23,826
Seven gods, drowned gods,
tree gods, it's all the same.

551
00:46:27,517 --> 00:46:29,288
I'm not asking the Lord
of Light for help.

552
00:46:30,403 --> 00:46:34,538
I'm asking the woman who
showed me that miracles exist.

553
00:46:36,861 --> 00:46:37,954
I never had this gift.

554
00:46:39,163 --> 00:46:40,066
Have you ever tried?

555
00:47:54,749 --> 00:48:00,906
( speaking Valyrian )

556
00:48:06,513 --> 00:48:07,678
( sizzles )

557
00:48:34,795 --> 00:48:39,466
( continues speaking Valyrian )

558
00:49:22,467 --> 00:49:26,936
( continues speaking Valyrian )

559
00:50:10,270 --> 00:50:13,489
<i>( continues faintly )</i>

560
00:50:24,170 --> 00:50:25,683
( sighs )
Please.

561
00:51:03,081 --> 00:51:05,081
( scoffs )

562
00:52:15,880 --> 00:52:20,139
( gasping )

563
00:52:20,239 --> 00:52:28,339
<b><font color=#FFFF00>♪ ♪</b></font>
Precisely Synchronized by <font color=#00FF00>srjanapala</font>


564
00:52:28,439 --> 00:53:32,339
<b><font color=#FFFF00>♪ ♪</b></font>

565
00:53:32,439 --> 00:53:33,768
<b><font color=#FFFF00>(Music playing ends)</b></font>

