http://subscene.com/u/659433
Improved by: @Ivandrofly
♪ Theme music playing ♪
♪ Game of Thrones S04E06 The Laws of Gods ♪
♪ and Men Original Air Date on May 11, 2014 ♪
== sync, corrected by
elderman == @elder_man.
♪ Theme music ends ♪
(SEAGULLS CALLING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
Your Grace, if you'd like
to sit, I'm sure that...
We've been here since midday.
Easterners have a difference
sense of time, I've often found.
Once I was waiting for Salladhor
Saan here in Braavos.
Together, we were going to run
three shiploads of the finest...
(DOORS CLOSE)
Welcome to the Iron Bank.
Please, sit.
What can we do for
you, Lord Stannis?
This is Stannis of
the House Baratheon,
King of the Andals
and the First Men,
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms
and Protector of the Realm.
The Iron Throne is
currently occupied
by Tommen of the
House Baratheon,
King of the Andals
and the First Men,
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms
and Protector of the Realm.
He shares no blood with me.
He is a bastard born of incest.
As was his brother before him.
Yes, we have heard this story.
It's not a story.
It's the truth.
The king's grandfather
tells a different story.
A story about a jealous uncle
whose attempts to usurp the
throne from the rightful king
cost the Seven Kingdoms
dearly in blood and gold.
Gold you loaned him.
And you feel your blood gives
you a claim on our gold?
More than any man living.
Across the Narrow Sea,
your books are filled
with words like
"usurper" and "madman"
and "blood right."
Here, our books are
filled with numbers.
We prefer the stories they tell.
More plain.
Less open to interpretation.
How many fighting men
remain loyal to you?
4,000.
And how many ships do you have?
The ones still
afloat, Ser Davos,
not at the bottom
of Blackwater Bay.
32.
And how much wheat
and barley and beef
and pork do you produce
on Dragonstone
to feed your 4,000 men
on your 32 ships?
None.
You can see why these numbers
seem unlikely to add up
to a happy ending
from our perspective.
I'm afraid we must respectfully
decline your request.
But we thank you for paying
us the honor of your visit.
My lord.
I'm not a lord, Ser
Davos Seaworth.
You would not be either here.
In Braavos,
thieves are not
rewarded with titles.
Well, strictly speaking, I
didn't do the thieving.
That would be the pirates.
I just moved what they stole
from one place to another.
This is the payment
that was demanded
by King Stannis for my crimes.
I consider it an
honest accounting.
He's an honest man and
he's your best chance
to get back the money
you've sunk into Westeros.
Which is a lot, I imagine.
Wars are expensive.
The war is over.
As long as Stannis lives,
the war is not over.
Who's the real power
in King's Landing?
- Ser Davos...
- Humor me.
- Tywin Lannister.
- How old is Tywin Lannister?
67.
67. And when he dies,
who's in command?
A half-grown boy,
the product of incest?
Cersei Lannister, a queen
whose people despise her?
Jaime Lannister, a man best
known for killing the king
he was sworn to protect?
When Tywin's gone,
who do you back?
That is a problem
for another time.
Begging your pardon, I think
it's a problem for now.
There's only one reliable
leader left in Westeros.
Stannis.
He's got the birthright.
He's in his prime.
He's a tried and tested
battle commander.
And he doesn't just talk
about paying people back,
he does it.
SAAN: The lookout sees a
pirate ship sailing their way.
The captain shouts
to his first mate,
"Bring me my red shirt."
The first mate brings the red
shirt and the captain puts it on.
And when the pirates
try to board,
the brave captain leads
his men to victory.
A few days later, the
lookout screams,
"Two pirate ships!"
The crew is shivering
like scared mice.
But the courageous
captain hollers,
"Bring me my red shirt!"
After the battle, the
first mate asks,
"Captain, why do you call for
your red shirt before battle?"
The captain replies,
"So that if I am stabbed,
you will not see me bleed."
The next morning the
lookout screams,
"10 pirate ships!
- "We are surrounded!"
- (WOMEN LAUGH)
The crew goes silent.
They all look to
their brave captain,
waiting for his usual command.
Calm as ever, the
captain bellows...
WOMEN: "Bring me
my brown pants!"
(LAUGHS)
You think they ever met a pirate
who didn't tell them that joke?
- Davos.
- (CHUCKLES)
I heard you were rotting in
a dungeon in Dragonstone.
Only half rotted.
(LAUGHS)
Join us, my friend. Join us.
- This is Lhara.
- (GASPS)
- And this is...
- I am Lhara.
(SQUEALS)
(LAUGHS)
She's an artist,
this one, truly.
No time, I'm afraid.
We sail at sunrise.
We?
You, me... we.
(SCOFF S)
Once I thought
this man loved me.
Now I know he despises me.
He wants to see me die poor
and alone on some cold...
You won't be alone.
And you won't be poor.
There's a chest of the good
stuff left back at your house.
I gave it to your wife.
(WOMEN LAUGH)
You're not my friend, my friend.
(LAUGHS)
I'll see you at sunrise.
YARA: "I give you
until the full moon"
to order all ironborn
scum out of the North
and back to those shit-stained
rocks you call home.
On the first night
of the full moon,
I will hunt down every
islander still on our lands
and flay them living,
the way I flayed the
20 ironborn scum
I found at Winterfell.
In the box you'll find
a special gift...
Theon's favorite toy.
He cried when I took
it away from him.
Leave the North now or
more boxes will follow
with more Theon.
Signed Ramsay Snow,
natural born son
of Roose Bolton,
Lord of the Dreadfort
"and Warden of the North."
Yes!
YARA: They skinned
our countrymen
and they mutilated my brother,
your prince.
Your prince.
Everything they've done to him,
they've also done to you.
Yes! Yes!
YARA: As long as they can hurt
our prince with impunity,
the word ironborn means nothing.
- (MOANING LOUDLY)
- (METAL CLINKING)
(MYRANDA MOANING)
(GRUNTS)
Go left.
(MEN WHISPERING)
(GROANS)
- Theon Greyjoy.
- I don't know...
I'm here for Theon Greyjoy.
Take me to the dungeons.
He's not in the dungeons.
(DOGS PANTING)
(RASPY BREATHING)
(DOOR OPENS)
- (ALARM RINGING)
- (MEN SHOUTING)
- Last cage on the right.
- Thank you.
(GURGLES)
-  (SWORDS CLANGING)
- MAN: This way!
(BARKING)
(WHIMPERING)
We're going home.
No!
It's all right. It's me, Yara.
You can't trick me.
Tell him. Tell him you
couldn't trick me.
I'm not tricking you, Theon.
I'm saving you.
Not Theon! Reek!
- Reek! My name is Reek!
- FIRST MATE: They're here.
If they catch us in
here, we're trapped.
Help me with him.
No, you can't!
- You can't!
- You're Theon Greyjoy.
No, I don't believe her!
I know who I am!
I'm Reek! Reek! Loyal Reek!
Good Reek!
I've always been Reek!
- (DOGS BARKING)
- (THEON WHIMPERING)
This is turning into
a lovely evening.
(SHOUTING)
(SNARLING, BARKING)
- (GROANS)
- (LAUGHS)
THEON: I'm Reek!
Loyal Reek!
Aah! Theon!
Give me my brother and no
more of your men will die.
You've got bigger balls
than he ever did.
But with those big
balls of yours...
how fast can you run?
(CAGE RATTLING)
(DOGS BARKING)
Make for the ship, now.
But your brother.
My brother is dead.
RAMSAY: I have a treat for you.
A reward.
Reward?
Yes, Reek.
Those creatures who
came in the night,
they wanted to take you away.
And you didn't let them.
You remained loyal.
I... I didn't want
them to take me.
I was so scared.
- I didn't want them...
- Yes, yes, Reek.
It's a bath.
For you.
Remove those rags.
Now.
The britches, too, Reek.
Take them off.
(WHIMPERING)
(WATER SPLASHES)
(WHIMPERS)
(GASPS)
Do you love me, Reek?
Yes, of course, my lord.
Good.
Because I need you to
do something for me.
Something very important.
There's a castle, you see.
Some bad men hold this castle.
I need your help to
take this castle back.
But how can...
I need you to play a role.
To pretend to be
someone you're not.
Pretend to be who?
Theon Greyjoy.
(GOATS BLEATING)
(WATER SPLASHES)
(ROCK THUDS)
(ROARING)
(BLEATING)
(MISSANDEI SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
(SPEAKING LOW VALYRIAN)
He is a goatherd.
He says he prayed for your victory
against the slave masters.
I thank him for his prayers.
(SPEAKS LOW VALYRIAN)
(SPEAKING LOW VALYRIAN)
It was your dragons, he says.
They came this morning
for his flock.
(SPEAKS LOW VALYRIAN)
He hopes he has not
offended Your Grace,
but now he has nothing.
Tell this man I am sorry
for his hardship.
- (TRANSLATING)
- I cannot bring back his goats,
but I will see he is paid
their value three times over.
(SPEAKING LOW VALYRIAN)
Send the next one in.
(SERVANT SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
Queen Daenerys.
Tales of your beauty
were not exaggerated.
I thank you.
Mine is one of the oldest and
proudest families in Meereen.
Then it is my honor
to receive you.
My father, one of
Meereen's most respected
and beloved citizens,
oversaw the restoration
and maintenance of its
greatest landmarks.
This pyramid included.
For that, he has my gratitude.
I should be honored to meet him.
You have, Your Grace.
You crucified him.
I pray you'll never live to see
a member of your family
treated so cruelly.
Your father crucified
innocent children.
My father spoke out against
crucifying those children.
He decried it as a criminal
act, but was overruled.
Is it justice to answer
one crime with another?
I am sorry you no
longer have a father,
but my treatment of the
masters was no crime.
You'd be wise to remember that.
What's done is done.
You are the queen and I
am a servant of Meereen.
A servant who does not wish to
see its traditions eradicated.
And what traditions
do you speak of?
The tradition of funeral rite.
Proper burial in the
Temple of the Graces.
My father and 162
noble Meereenese
are still nailed to those posts,
carrion for vultures,
rotting in the sun.
Your Grace, I ask that you
order these men taken down
so that they might
receive proper burials.
And what of the slave children
these noble Meereenese crucified?
They were rotting
in the sun as well.
Would you have begged me for
their right to a proper burial?
Your Grace, I cannot def end
the actions of the masters.
I can only speak to you as a
son who loved his father.
Let me take his body down.
Let me have him
brought to the temple
and buried with dignity
so that he might find
peace in the next world.
Bury your father,
Hizdahr zo Loraq.
Thank you, my queen.
How many more?
There are 212 supplicants
waiting, Your Grace.
212?
Send the next one in.
These meetings aren't always going
to be this early, are they?
I was up late last night.
So, does this mean I am a
master of something now?
Coins, ships?
Lord Tywin and I
already determined
that I shall be the Master
of Ships long before you...
Lord Tywin, it's a great honor
to have been granted a
seat on this council. I...
TYWIN: The trial
begins this afternoon.
We only have the morning
for affairs of state.
Shall we begin?
VARYS: Sandor Clegane
has been spotted
in the Riverlands, my lord.
A coward and a traitor.
My birds tell me the Hound
slaughtered five of our soldiers.
I believe the phrase "fuck
the king" was uttered.
Disgraceful.
TYWIN: What would it take
to make the common soldier
stupid enough to try his
luck with the Hound?
10 silver stags seems
a generous bounty.
Make it 100. What else?
More whispers from
the east, my lord.
The Targaryen girl?
Daenerys has taken up
residence in Meereen.
She has conquered the city
and rules as its queen.
Conquered with what?
VARYS: She commands an army
of Unsullied, my queen.
Some 8,000 strong.
She has a company
of sellswords...
the Second Sons.
She has two knights
advising her...
Jorah Mormont and
Barristan Selmy.
And she has three dragons.
Baby dragons.
Larger every year, Your Grace.
Mormont is spying on her for us.
No longer. He appears to
be fully devoted to her.
As for Ser Barristan,
it would seem
he took his dismissal
from the Kingsguard
a bit harder than anticipated.
He's an old man.
He wasn't fit to protect my son.
Joffrey didn't die on his watch.
Dismissing him was as
insulting as it was stupid.
Don't tell me you're worried about
a child halfway across the world.
A child with two seasoned
warriors counseling her
and a powerful army at
her back, Your Grace.
Lord Varys is right.
I have been to Essos and seen
the Unsullied firsthand.
They are very impressive
on the battlefield.
Less so in the bedroom.
Dragons haven't won
a war in 300 years.
Armies win them all the time.
She must be dealt with.
How, my lord?
By force?
Eventually, if it comes to that.
Can your little birds find
their way into Meereen?
Most certainly, my Lord Hand.
Mmm. Lord Tyrell, be a good man.
Fetch my quill and paper.
(FOOTSTEPS)
Prince Oberyn.
Lord Varys...
Only Varys. I'm not
actually a nobleman.
No one is under obligation
to call me lord.
And yet everyone does.
You seem quite knowledgeable
about the Unsullied.
Did you spend much
time in Essos?
Five years.
May I ask why?
'Tis a big and beautiful world.
Most of us live and die
in the same corner
where we were born
and never get to see any of it.
I don't want to be most of us.
Most of us aren't princes.
(CHUCKLES)
You are from Essos.
Where? Lys?
I have an ear for accents.
I've lost my accent entirely.
I have an ear for that as well.
How did you get here?
It's a long story.
One you don't like
telling people.
People I trust.
My paramour Ellaria, she would
find you very interesting.
You should come to the
brothel and meet her.
We brought our own wine, not
the swill they serve here.
We have some lovely boys
on retainer, but...
You did like boys before?
Really?
Girls? Hmm.
I hope you won't be offended when
I say I never would have guessed.
Not at all.
But I was never interested
in girls, either.
- What then?
- Nothing.
Everybody is interested
in something.
Not me.
When I see what desire
does to people,
what it's done to this country,
I am very glad to
have no part in it.
Besides, the absence of desire
leaves one free to
pursue other things.
Such as?
(KEYS CLINKING)
Let me guess, I've
been pardoned.
Really?
Father's orders.
Well, we mustn't
disappoint Father.
(CROWD MURMURING)
MAN: Kingslayer!
I, Tommen of the
House Baratheon,
First of my Name,
King of the Andals
and the First Men,
and Lord of the Seven Kingdoms,
do hereby recuse myself
from this trial.
Tywin of the House
Lannister, Hand of the King,
Protector of the Realm, will
sit as judge in my stead.
And with him Prince Oberyn
of the House Martell
and Lord Mace of
the House Tyrell.
And if found guilty...
may the gods punish the accused.
Tyrion of the House Lannister,
you stand accused by the
Queen Regent of regicide.
Did you kill King Joffrey?
No.
Did your wife, the Lady Sansa?
Not that I know of.
How would you say he died, then?
Choked on his pigeon pie.
So you would blame the bakers?
Or the pigeons.
Just leave me out of it.
(CROWD MURMURING)
The crown may call
its first witness.
Once we'd got King
Joffrey safely away
from the mob, the
Imp rounded on him.
He slapped the king
across the face
and called him a vicious
idiot and a fool.
(CROWD GASPS)
It wasn't the first time the
Imp threatened Joffrey.
Right here in this throne room,
he marched up those steps and
called our king a half wit.
Compared His Grace
to the Mad King
and suggested he'd
meet the same fate.
And when I spoke in
the king's defense,
he threatened to have me killed.
Oh, why don't you tell them
what Joffrey was doing?
- TYWIN: Silence.
- Pointing a loaded crossbow at Sansa Stark
while you tore at her
clothes and beat her.
Silence!
You will not speak
unless called upon.
You're dismissed, Ser Meryn.
Basilisk venom,
widow's blood,
wolfsbane,
essence of nightshade,
sweetsleep,
tears of Lys,
demon's dance...
(MUMBLING)
blind eye...
I think you have made your
point, Grand Maester.
You have a lot of
poison in your store.
Had, Prince Oberyn.
My stores were plundered.
By whom?
PYCELLE: By the accused,
Tyrion Lannister,
after he had me
wrongfully imprisoned.
TYWIN: Grand Maester,
you examined King
Joffrey's corpse.
Was it without question
poison that killed him?
Without question.
(CROWD MURMURING)
This was found on the
body of Dontos Hollard,
the king's fool.
He was last seen
spiriting Sansa Stark,
the wife of the accused,
away from the feast.
She wore this necklace
the day of the wedding.
Residue of a most rare
and terrible poison
was found inside.
Was this one of the poisons
stolen from your store?
It was. The Strangler.
A poison few in the
Seven Kingdoms possess.
And used to strike down
the most noble child
the gods ever put
on this good earth.
(CROWD MURMURING)
CERSEI: "I will
hurt you for this.
A day will come when you
think you are safe and happy
and your joy will turn
to ashes in your mouth
"and you will know
the debt is paid."
Your own brother
said this to you?
Shortly before the Battle
of Blackwater Bay.
I confronted him about his plans
to put Joffrey on the front lines.
As it turned out,
when the attack came,
Joff insisted on remaining
at the battlements.
He believed his presence
would inspire the troops.
Tyrion said,
"And you will know
the debt is paid."
What debt?
I discovered he'd
been keeping whores
in the Tower of the Hand.
I asked him to confine
his salacious acts
to the brothel where
such behavior belongs.
He wasn't pleased.
Thank you, Your Grace,
for the courage of
your testimony.
MACE: Do you remember the
precise nature of this threat?
VARYS: I'm afraid I do, my lord.
He said, "Perhaps you should
speak more softly to me, then."
Monsters are dangerous
"and just now kings are
dying like flies."
And he said this to you at a
meeting of the small council?
Yes.
After we received word
of Robb Stark's death.
He didn't seem
gladdened by the news.
Perhaps his marriage
to Sansa Stark
had made him more sympathetic
to the northern 'cause.
(CROWD MURMURING)
You're excused, Lord Varys.
Father, may I ask the
witness one question?
One.
You once said
that without me, this city would
have faced certain defeat.
You said the histories
would never mention me,
but you would not forget.
Have you forgotten, Lord Varys?
Sadly, my lord,
I never forget a thing.
We will adjourn for now.
Toll the bells in an hour's time.
GUARD: Clear the court!
(CROWD CHATTING)
JAIME: You'd condemn
your own son to death?
I've condemned no one.
The trial is not over.
This isn't a trial.
It's a farce.
Cersei has manipulated
everything and you know it.
I know nothing of the sort.
- You've always hated Tyrion.
- He killed his king.
As did I.
Do you know the last order
the Mad King gave me?
To bring him your head.
I saved your life so you
could murder my brother?
- It won't be murder. It'll be justice.
- Justice?
I'm performing my sworn
duty as Hand of the King.
If Tyrion is found guilty, he
will be punished accordingly.
- He'll be executed.
- No, he'll be punished accordingly.
Once you said family
is what lives on.
All that lives on.
You told me about a dynasty
that would last 1,000 years.
What happens to your
dynasty when Tyrion dies?
I'm a Kingsguard,
forbidden by oath to carry
on the family line.
I'm well aware of your oath.
What happens to your name?
Who carries the lion banner
into future battles?
Your nephews?
Lancel Lannister?
Others whose names I
don't even remember?
What happens to my dynasty
if I spare the life of
my grandson's killer?
It survives through me.
I'll leave the Kingsguard.
I'll take my place
as your son and heir
if you let Tyrion live.
Done.
When the testimony's concluded
and a guilty verdict rendered,
Tyrion will be given
the chance to speak.
He'll plead for mercy. I'll allow
him to join the Night's Watch.
In three days' time, he'll
depart for Castle Black
and live out his
days at the Wall.
You'll remove your white
cloak immediately.
You will leave King's Landing
to assume your rightful
place at Casterly Rock.
You will marry a suitable woman
and father children
named Lannister.
And you'll never turn your
back on your family again.
You have my word.
And you have mine.
(BELL TOLLING)
Not going well, is it?
- You're going to be found guilty.
- Oh, you think so?
When you are, you need to
enter a formal plea for mercy
and ask to be sent to the Wall.
Father's agreed to it.
He'll spare your life and allow
you to join the Night's Watch.
Ned Stark was promised
the same thing
and we both know how
that turned out.
JAIME: Father is not Joffrey.
He'll keep his word.
How do you know?
Do you trust me?
Keep your mouth shut.
No more outbursts.
This will all be over soon.
The crown may call
its next witness.
(FOOTSTEPS)
State your name.
Shae.
Do you swear by all the gods
that your testimony will
be true and honest?
I swear it.
Do you know this man?
Yes. Tyrion Lannister.
How do you know him?
I was handmaiden to
his wife Lady Sansa.
This man stands accused of
murdering King Joffrey.
What do you know of this?
I know that he's guilty.
(CROWD GASPS)
He and Sansa planned
it together.
(CROWD MURMURING)
TYWIN: Silence!
Continue.
SHAE: She wanted revenge
for her father,
her mother, her brother.
She blamed their
deaths on the king.
Tyrion was happy to help.
He hated Joffrey.
He hated the queen.
He hated you, my lord.
He stole poison from the
Grand Maester's chamber
to put in Joffrey's wine.
OBERYN: How could you
possibly know all this?
Why would he reveal such
plans to his wife's maid?
I wasn't just her maid.
I was his whore.
- (CROWD MURMURING)
- MACE: I beg your pardon?
You said you were his...
His whore.
How did you come to
be in his service?
He stole me.
I was with another man,
a knight in your
lordship's army.
But when Tyrion
arrived at the camp,
he sent one of his
cutthroats into our tent.
He broke the knight's arm and
brought me to Lord Tyrion.
"You belong to me now," he said.
"I want you to fuck me like it's
my last night in this world."
(CROWD LAUGHS)
Silence. Silence!
(LAUGHING STOPS)
OBERYN: And did you?
Did I what?
Fuck him like it was his
last night in this world.
(CROWD LAUGHS)
I did everything he wanted.
Whatever he told
me to do to him.
Whatever he felt
like doing to me.
I kissed him where he wanted.
I licked him where he wanted.
I let him put himself
where he wanted.
I was his property.
I would wait in his
chambers for hours
so he could use me
when he was bored.
He ordered me to call him
"my lion," so I did.
I took his face in
my hands and said,
"I am yours and you are mine."
(CROWD MURMURING)
Shae.
Please don't.
I am a whore.
Remember?
That was before
he married Sansa.
After that, all he
wanted was her.
But she wouldn't let
him into her bed.
So he promised to kill
King Joffrey for her.
(CROWD CLAMORING)
Father,
I wish to confess.
I wish... to confess.
(CROWD QUIETS)
You wish to confess?
I saved you.
I saved this city
and all your worthless lives.
I should have let
Stannis kill you all.
- (CLAMORING)
- TYWIN: Tyrion.
TYWIN: Do you wish to confess?
Yes, Father.
I'm guilty.
Guilty. Is that what
you want to hear?
You admit you poisoned the king?
No, of that I'm innocent.
I'm guilty of a far
more monstrous crime.
I am guilty of being a dwarf.
You are not on trial
for being a dwarf.
TYRION: Oh, yes, I am.
I've been on trial for
that my entire life.
Have you nothing to
say in your defense?
TYRION: Nothing but this...
I did not do it.
I did not kill Joffrey,
but I wish that I had.
Watching your
vicious bastard die
gave me more relief than
1,000 lying whores.
(CROWD CLAMORING)
I wish I was the monster
you think I am.
I wish I had enough poison
for the whole pack of you.
I would gladly give my life
to watch you all swallow it.
- Ser Meryn. Ser Meryn.
- (CROWD SHOUTING)
Escort the prisoner
back to his cell.
I will not give my life
for Joffrey's murder.
And I know I'll get
no justice here.
So I will let the
gods decide my fate.
I demand a trial by combat.
(CROWD SHOUTING)
== sync, corrected by
elderman == @elder_man.
♪ "Rains of Castamere" playing ♪
♪ theme music ends ♪
http://subscene.com/u/659433
Improved by: @Ivandrofly