(WIND HOWLING)
- (BIRD SCREECHES)
- (MAN SHOUTS)
(HORSE NEIGHS)
MAN 1: Look out!
MAN 2: Fire!
- (MEN SHOUTING)
- (HORSE WHINNIES)
(SHOUTING CONTINUES)
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(SCREAMING)
(COUGHING)
DAVOS: A band of 20 men, maybe less.
They were in and out
before anyone spotted them.
Burned our food stores to the ground,
all our siege weapons destroyed.
- Dozens of tents were...
- Horses?
We're still getting a count,
but hundreds are dead.
Twenty men rode into our camp
without a single guard sounding the alarm?
The Northerners know more about their land
than we ever will.
Put last night's guards in chains.
Either they fell asleep
or they conspired with the enemy.
- Find out the truth and then hang them.
- Your Grace.
Unless there's a thaw,
we can't press forward to Winterfell
and we don't have enough food
to get us back to Castle Black.
We're not returning to Castle Black.
Forgive me, I never claimed
to be an expert in military matters,
but if we can't march forward
and we won't march back...
Have the dead horses butchered for meat.
MAN 1: Halt!
- MAN 2: Halt!
- (MEN COUGHING)
MAN 3: There it is!
Open the gates.
(RUMBLING)
(BABY CRYING)
JON: It was a failure.
It wasn't.
I went to save them. I failed.
You didn't fail him.
Or him.
Or her.
Every one of them is alive
because of you and no one else.
I don't think that fact's lost on them.
You have a good heart.
It'll get us all killed.
Get out of my way.
(SIGHS)
You sent for me?
Find some healthy horses
and a few knights to guard you.
I'm sending you back to Castle Black.
Tell the Lord Commander
his king commands him
to send food, supplies, fresh horses.
In return, when I take the throne,
I'll make sure the Night's Watch
has all the men it requires.
He can guard all 19 castles on the Wall
if he so wishes.
You named me your Hand.
Yes.
The King's Hand should
never abandon the king,
especially in time of war.
You're not abandoning me.
You're obeying a command.
A boy with a scroll
could deliver this message.
And if Jon Snow refuses
the boy with the scroll,
what does the boy say?
I didn't name you Hand
for your expertize in military matters.
Ride for Castle Black.
Don't come back empty-handed.
Perhaps Queen Selyse
and Princess Shireen could accompany me.
My family stays with me.
At least let me take Shireen.
A siege is no place for a little girl.
My family stays with me.
(MEN COUGHING)
What's this one now?
The Dance of Dragons: A True Telling
by Grand Maester Munkun.
Now that sounds like a proper story.
Ser Byron Swann wanted
to kill the dragon Vhagar.
He polished his shield for a week
so that it was like a mirror.
And he crouched behind
it and crept forward,
hoping the dragon
would only see its own reflection.
But the dragon saw a dumb man
holding a mirrored shield.
And burned him to a crisp.
(LAUGHS)
Thus ending the dragon-slaying career
of Ser Byron Swann.
I made you something.
- Do you like it?
- He's beautiful.
- Thank you.
- You're very welcome.
Will you make me a doe, too?
So that he can have company?
Of course I will.
But why am I getting a present?
Because you deserve it.
My son was always on me,
trying to teach me to read.
Gods, I was stubborn about it.
Made it this far without reading.
Seemed to me I could make it to the grave.
Wish I'd listened to him.
This is my own poor way
of saying "thank you."
For teaching me to be a grown-up.
I'll be gone for a few days.
I want to hear all about
The Dance of Dragons when I'm back.
You'll read it yourself.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
Prince Doran.
Forgive us. We started without you.
Please, sit.
Princess Myrcella.
Uncle.
What a lovely dress.
You don't like it?
- You must be cold.
- Not at all.
The Dornish climate agrees with me.
Prince Trystane.
How's your jaw?
A fleabite.
What are you doing in Dorne?
Looking after the safety of my niece.
And rather than send a raven
or speak to me directly,
you decided to enter my country in secret
and abduct our guest by force?
We received a threatening message.
The princess's necklace
in the jaws of a viper.
That necklace was stolen from my room.
Oh, excellent.
A last meal before the beheading?
Oh, I can't behead you.
Many in Dorne want war.
But I've seen war.
I've seen the bodies piled
on the battlefields.
I've seen the orphans
starving in the cities.
I don't want to lead my
people into that hell.
No, you want to break bread
with the Lannisters.
And that is precisely what we are doing.
Let us drink to Tommen,
the First of His Name,
King of the Andals and the First Men,
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms.
(SLAMS)
King Tommen insists
on his sister's return to the capital?
I'm afraid he does.
I cannot disobey my king's command.
She will return with you to King's Landing.
And my son, Prince Trystane,
will accompany you both.
If the alliance between
the Iron Throne and Dorne is to continue,
their engagement must stand.
I accept.
One more thing.
My brother was named to the Small Council
before his death.
Your father understood the importance
of keeping Dorne in the fold.
With Oberyn gone,
Trystane will take his place
on the Small Council.
You have my word.
The word of a Kingslayer.
No wonder you can't stand.
You have no spine.
You are mother to four of my nieces,
girls I love very much.
For their sake,
I hope you live a long and happy life.
Speak to me that way again, and you won't.
May I inquire as to the
fate of my man Bronn?
Tell me, in King's Landing,
how do they punish a commoner
who strikes a prince?
He said it was just a fleabite.
The fault is mine. Bronn is merely
a soldier following my orders.
If anyone should be punished, it's me.
Prince Trystane must learn judgment
if he is to rule one day.
I'll let him decide.
I have learned the value of mercy
from my father.
- I'll set your man free.
- You're a good man.
On one condition.
(HANDS SLAPPING)
Why do we play? I'm better than you.
I'll always be better than you.
Have I ever missed once?
I don't think I have. I can't recall.
You must love humiliation. Or pain.
Which do you love most?
(WINCES)
That one hurt, didn't it?
You going to cry?
Give up, little sister.
- You're going to miss.
- Oh, I never miss.
You will. You're thinking too much.
Now you're nervous. "What if she's right?"
Luck.
Now it's my turn.
You're too slow.
You've always been too slow.
(CELL DOOR UNLOCKS)
Am I gonna be happy at
the end of this walk?
You'll find out very soon.
Say it one more time, handsome.
Who am I?
The most beautiful woman in the world.
And that's the truth.
- Slut.
- (TYENE LAUGHS)
Prince Doran, Ser Bronn of the Blackwater.
I didn't realize
there were knights of the Blackwater.
Only the one.
I believe you've already
met Prince Trystane.
Prince.
Sorry about the other day.
JAIME: Prince Trystane here
is a man of mercy.
He's agreed to grant you your freedom.
I'm glad to hear it.
Pie looks good.
There was one condition.
- (GRUNTS)
- (BRONN GROANS)
Perhaps some soup instead.
- (MERCHANTS SHOUTING)
- ARYA: Oysters, clams, and cockles.
Oysters, clams, and cockles.
Oysters, clams, and...
How much for your little clam? (LAUGHS)
Oysters, clams, and cockles.
Come on.
Some oysters, girl!
I'm talking to you.
Is, uh...
- Girl!
- MAN: Tie her up!
THIN MAN: Are you deaf? Girl!
Girl!
My lord.
SAILOR; My lord.
TYCHO: Lord Tyrell.
On behalf of the Iron Bank,
may I be the first to welcome you
to the Free City of Braavos.
I hope yourjourney was trouble-free.
A bit of chop the last few days.
Nothing too awful.
Good to see the old chap
still guarding the harbor.
And how goes the harvest in the Reach?
Ah, the vintners say this might be the best
year for red grapes in half a century.
If we come to a satisfactory arrangement,
I'll be sure to send
a cask of the Arbor's finest your way.
I'm afraid I don't partake.
Oh.
Some consider usury
distasteful, dishonorable.
Pure nonsense, of course.
I'm glad we see eye to eye on this matter.
Did you know that at one point Maegor III
tried to outlaw it in the Seven Kingdoms?
Wanted to arrest anyone
caught charging interest
and cut off both their hands.
Most unfortunate for the glovers.
MACE: If a man charges
no interest on a loan,
then he has nothing to gain
and everything to lose, so why chance it?
Whereas the promise of reward
makes a man willing to gamble.
We are not gamblers
here at the Iron Bank, Lord Tyrell.
You are the world's best gamblers.
And all those bets you won built this.
(come CLINK)
(DOOR OPENS)
MACE: We should celebrate.
TYCHO: I'm afraid I still
have a good deal of work to do.
MACE: Nonsense. Work's over. Do you sing?
TYCHO: I don't have that gift.
It's not a gift. It's a skill.
Anyone can learn it.
(SINGING)
So give me a kiss by the Long Canal
And give me two kisses in Salty Town
For we're going to die tomorrow
The bareheaded beggar
The king with his crown...
MERYN: Thought that old shit
would never stop singing.
Wasn't bad, though.
The Tyrells can all rot in hell.
Treasonous cunts.
They were going to make
that boy-fucker Renly king.
This is the place, lads.
The sleekest little minks in Braavos.
- You buying?
- Oh, I'm buying.
But I never was good at sharing.
- (CHATTER)
- (MUSIC PLAYING)
Sell your fish somewhere else.
Oh, let her in, Brusco. I'm hungry.
Come here, sweetness.
They say oysters get the juices flowing.
We'll take half a dozen.
Three coppers.
Here's a silver because the lady likes you.
Too old.
Brea.
MADAME: I have just the one. Anara.
Our most expensive girl.
But well worth it, I assure you.
Too old.
Do you have what I want or not?
Of course. Of course.
- (GAS PS)
- These fresh?
Come on, the lads are hungry.
Nothing better for your cockstand
than fresh oysters.
GUARD 1: Here. Thank you.
GUARD 2: I'll have one.
Any vinegar?
Who let this girl in? Shoo! Shoo!
(GUARDS CHUCKLE)
Good.
I'll tell you when we're done.
You'll have a fresh one for me tomorrow?
Of course.
MADAME: I'll have you whipped, girl.
Go, go on. Out, out, go.
(WHISPERING)
Valar Morghulis.
And?
The thin man wasn't hungry today.
Perhaps that is why a man is thin.
- Tomorrow.
(THUDS)
A girl has work to do.
Your rebellion is over.
You can swear your allegiance to me now,
or you can die.
(CRYING)
I believe in second chances.
I don't believe in third chances.
You write like a seven-year-old.
Your maester kindly agreed
to copy it over for me.
- He didn't try to make you pay?
- Mmm-mmm.
Maybe he's changed.
The queen will be thrilled to know
you're bringing her daughter home.
She will.
- You love her very much, don't you?
- Of course, she's my niece.
I wasn't talking about her.
You think I disapprove?
Why?
Because people disapprove
of that sort of thing where you are from?
They disapproved of Oberyn and me
where you are from.
Here, no one blinked an eye.
100 years ago,
no one would have blinked an eye at you
if you'd been named Targaryen.
It's always changing,
who we're supposed to love
and who we're not.
The only thing that stays the same
is that we want who we want.
I know your daughter had no part
in the terrible thing
that happened to the man I love.
Perhaps even you are innocent of that.
(TENT FLAP RUSTLES)
Father.
Aren't you cold?
No. What are you reading?
The Dance of Dragons.
What's it about?
It's the story of the fight
between Rhaenyra Targaryen
and her half-brotherAegon
for control of the Seven Kingdoms.
Both of them thought
they belonged on the Iron Throne.
When people started declaring
for one of them or the other,
their fight divided the kingdoms in two.
Brothers fought brothers,
dragons fought dragons.
By the time it was over,
thousands were dead.
And it was a disaster
for the Targaryens as well.
They never truly recovered.
The Dance of Dragons.
Why is that a dance?
It's just what they call it.
Hmm. Doesn't make much sense.
I think it's poetic.
If you'd had to choose
between Rhaenyra and Aegon,
who would you have chosen?
I wouldn't have chosen either.
It's all the choosing sides
that made everything so horrible.
Sometimes a person has to choose.
Sometimes the world forces his hand.
If a man knows what he is
and remains true to himself,
the choice is no choice at all.
He must fulfill his destiny
and become who he is meant to be.
However much he may hate it.
It's all right.
You don't even know what I'm talking about.
It doesn't matter. I want to help you.
Is there any way I can help?
Yes, there is.
Good. I want to.
I'm the Princess Shireen
of House Baratheon.
And I'm your daughter.
(SIGHS)
Forgive me.
Where's my father? I want to see my father.
It will all be over soon.
(CRYING) No.
Where's my father?
No, you can't do this.
Father, where are you?
Please, let me see my father.
Don't let her do this.
Please let go!
Let me see my father! Where are you?
Please!
- SELYSE: It's what the Lord wants.
- No.
- Please! Let go! No!
- It's a good thing.
- A great thing.
- SHIREEN: Stop!
- Please!
- MELISANDRE: Hear us now, my Lord.
SHIREEN: You can't do this! MELISANDRE:
For you, we offer up this girl...
- Please!
- ...that you may cleanse her with your fire
and that its light may lead our way.
SHIREEN: No, please let me see my father.
If we don't act, we'll all starve here.
All of us.
But if we make this sacrifice...
Accept this token of our faith, my Lord,
and lead us from the darkness.
Lord of Light, show us the way.
Mother, please!
- Mother!
- We can't.
- There's no other way. She has king's blood.
- Please don't do this!
- Please don't!
- MELISANDRE: Lord of Light, protect us.
- Father, please!
- For the night is dark and full of terrors.
Father, don't do this! Please!
Mother, no! Please, help!
Don't do this!
Please, Father! Mother, help!
- No.
- No, please! Don't do this!
Don't do this, please, Mother!
Please, Mother! Help!
Mother, help!
Please don't do this, Mother!
Please, Mother!
Please! No!
- (FIRE CRACKLING)
- (SHIREEN SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING STOPS)
No!
(CROWD CHEERING)
(DRUMS BEATING)
(DRUMMING STOPS)
Where have you been?
Just making sure everything is in order.
- (HORSE NEIGHS)
- (GATE OPENS)
(CHEERING)
(CHEERING STOPS)
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
Free Citizens of Meereen!
By the blessings of the Graces,
and her majesty the Queen,
welcome
to the Great Games!
- (CHEERING)
- (DRUMS BEATING)
My Queen, our first contest.
Who will triumph:
the strong,
or the quick?
I fight and die for your glory,
oh glorious Queen.
They're waiting for you.
Clap your hands.
(CHEERING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- (GROANS)
- (DAARIO CHUCKLES)
That one, the smaller man.
No question,
that's where you should put your money.
The smaller man it is.
I'm not putting my money anywhere.
Kings and queens never bet on the games.
Perhaps you should
go find someone who does.
People used to bet against me
when I fought in the pits.
He would have bet against me.
Common novice mistake.
I've spent much of my life in this arena.
And in my experience, large men do triumph
over smaller men far more often than not.
Has your experience
ever involved any actual fighting?
You yourself?
Have you ever tried to kill another man
who was trying to kill you?
Whenever I got into the pit
against a beast like that one,
the crowd saw me,
all skin and bone back then,
then they saw a pile of angry muscles
ready to murder me.
They couldn't get
their money out fast enough.
But the pile of angry muscles
never had any muscles here
or here.
And the big men were always too slow
to stop my dagger
from going where their muscles weren't.
Yes, whenever I saw a beast like that one
standing across from me
making his beast faces,
I knew I could rest easy.
- (SHOUTING)
- (CROWD CHEERING)
You don't approve?
There's always been more than enough death
in the world for my taste.
- I can do without it in my leisure time.
- Fair enough.
Yet it's an unpleasant question,
but what great thing has ever been
accomplished without killing or cruelty?
It's easy to confuse
what is with what ought to be,
especially when what is
has worked out in your favor.
I'm not talking about myself.
I'm talking about
the necessary conditions for greatness.
That is greatness?
That is a vital part
of the great city of Meereen,
which existed long before you or I
and will remain standing
long after we have returned to the dirt.
My father would have liked you.
- (GATE OPENS)
- (CROWD CHEERING)
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
We ask again: Who will triumph?
One day your great city
will return to the dirt as well.
- At your command?
- If need be.
A Meereenese champion?
And how many people will die
to make this happen?
If it comes to that,
they will have died for a good reason.
Those men think
they're dying for a good reason.
DAENERYS: Someone else's reason.
So your reasons are true
and theirs are false?
They don't know their own minds,
but you do?
Well said. You're an eloquent man.
Doesn't mean you're wrong.
In my experience, eloquent men are right
every bit as often as imbeciles.
Or a Westerosi knight?
(JORAH SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
I fight and die for your glory,
oh glorious Queen.
- Your Grace...
- Shut your mouth.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(G ROANS)
- (GROANS)
- (CHEERING)
- You can end this.
- She cannot.
You can.
(CROWD CHANTING)
(SCREAMS)
(SHOUTING)
(BOOING)
(MAN SHOUTING)
(CROWD GROANS)
(CROWD BOOING)
(GROANING)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Protect your queen!
(CROWD SCREAMING)
Go!
Your Grace!
Come with me. I know a way out.
I know a way...
(MISSANDEI SCREAMS)
Stay close.
This way.
The other side. Follow me.
Protect your queen!
(MEN SHOUTING)
- (DROGON ROARS)
- (GASPS)
(ROARING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(ROARS)
(SCREAMING)
(SCREECHES)
Drogon!
- (SPEAR PIERCES)
- (ROARING)
Valahd.
(DRAGON ROARS)