A house of ghosts, Khaleesi. lt is known.
Where are the guards?
No guards.
The warlocks kill with sorcery, not steel.
Let them try.
Moon of my life.
This is dark magic, like the magic
that took you from me.
Took you from me before l could even...
Maybe l am dead and l just don't know it yet.
Maybe l am with you in the Night Lands.
Or maybe l refused to enter the Night Lands
without you.
Maybe l told the Great Stallion to go fuck
himself and came back here to wait for you.
That sounds like something you would do.
Or maybe it is a dream.
Your dream, my dream...
...l do not know.
These are questions
for wise men with skinny arms.
You are the moon of my life.
That is all l know...
...and all l need to know.
And if this is a dream...
...l will kill the man who tries to wake me.
Take all the gold and jewels.