(WATER DRIPPING)
(VOICES WHISPERING)
Valar Morghulis.
Valar Dohaeris.
I've been sweeping this floor for days.
Good.
I didn't come here to sweep floors.
No? Why come, then?
You said I could be your apprentice.
You said you'd teach me
how to be a Faceless Man.
A man teaches a girl.
Valar Dohaeris. All men must serve.
Faceless Men most of all.
I want to serve.
A girl wants to serve herself.
Here we serve the Many-Faced God.
To serve well,
a girl must become no one.
Which one's the Many-Faced God?
I see the Stranger. I see the Drowned God.
I see the weirwood face.
There is only one god.
A girl knows his name.
And all men know his gift.
Where are they taking him?
- (BELLS TOLLING)
- (PEOPLE SHOUTING)
- Queen Margaery!
MAN: Queen Margaery!
Queen Margaery!
- MARGAERY: I am his and he is mine.
- TOMMEN: I am hers and she is mine.
BOTH: From this day until the end of my days.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Did I hurt you?
No. You were lovely.
- It all happened so fast.
- Yes. (CHUCKLES)
I was scared maybe I hurt you.
- It sounded like...
- No, no, no.
You're very sweet.
The sweetest king who ever lived.
This is all I want to do all day,
every day, for the rest of my life.
(LAUGHS) Wouldn't that be glorious?
Shouldn't we rest a little while?
Just to catch our breath?
There's no rush, is there?
Of course not.
Are you hungry?
Should I have them bring you
some cake or pomegranate juice?
No, I'm fine.
I just want you all to myself.
I want to know everything there is to know
about King Tommen, First of His Name.
King Tommen.
Still sounds strange to me.
Does Queen Margaery sound strange to you?
So strange.
- Husband.
- Wife.
(LAUGHS)
Sometimes it feels odd.
I'm the king,
I've married the most
beautiful woman in the world,
and it's all because my brother died.
I understand.
But it's not your fault.
You know that, don't you?
You mustn't feel guilty.
I don't feel guilty.
That's what's odd.
Do you like to sail?
I love to sail.
I do, too.
I think we're going to be very happy,
you and I.
I do, too.
Living in a tower
so high it touches the clouds.
Of course, my grandmother
couldn't wait to go home.
The capital's not for everyone, I suppose.
Does your mother like it here?
I don't think so.
She told me
never to trust anyone in King's Landing.
It's so wonderful
to have her watching over you.
A lioness guarding her cub.
Well, but I'm a man now.
You are.
And the king.
But you'll always be her baby boy.
I suppose.
I adore her. She's always been
so generous with me, so kind.
And the horrors she's had to endure...
Losing her husband,
her eldest child, and her father.
It's no wonder she's so protective of you.
She'll never let you out of her sight.
CERSEI: You look very much in love.
The first days of marriage
are often so blissful.
She's certainly very pretty, isn't she?
Like a doll. She smiles quite a lot.
Do you think she's intelligent?
I can't quite tell.
Not that it matters.
Do you ever miss Casterly Rock?
There's nothing for me in Casterly Rock.
That's where you grew up.
You always told me
that you liked the people there better.
You said that King's Landing
smelled of horse dung and sour milk.
(CHUCKLES)
Why are we speaking of Casterly Rock?
The way that you talked about it,
I always thought that you missed it.
That you...
That it was your real home.
This is my real home now,
where my family lives.
I want you to be happy, Mother.
I know that.
I know you do. My sweet boy.
But wouldn't you be happier
in Casterly Rock?
MARGAERY: I said,
"Darling, surely four times is enough.
- "Are you trying to set a new record?"
- (WOMEN GIGGLING)
He said, "Well, what is the record?
I'm sure we can break it."
Mother.
Welcome.
Don't you look lovely?
Marriage agrees with you.
Can we bring you anything to eat or drink?
I wish we had some wine for you.
It's a bit early in the day for us.
No, no, I can't stay.
I just wanted to let you know
if there's ever anything I can do for you...
You are very sweet.
Tommen seems quite taken
with his new queen.
I absolutely adore him.
You raised a gallant young man.
I'm forever grateful.
Good.
Good. I'm glad to hear you're happy.
Ecstatic. I really am.
- Exhausted, to be honest.
- (WOMEN GIGGLE)
But what could I expect?
He is half lion, half stag.
(WOMEN LAUGH)
I'll leave you to it, then.
Oh, forgive me.
I haven't been at court for long.
I get so confused.
What's the proper way to address you now?
Queen Mother or Dowager Queen?
There's no need for such formalities.
In any event,
judging from the king's enthusiasm,
the Queen Mother will be
a Queen Grandmother soon.
Won't that be a lovely day?
Can you imagine the celebrations?
They'll ring the bells all day and night.
Remember,
anything you need.
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
(LAUGHTER ECHOING)
(HORSE NEIGHS)
(MEN SHOUTING)
(ANIMALS SQUAWKING)
(FLIES BUZZING)
(CAWS)
BOLTON: We can't hold the North
with terror alone.
RAMSAY: You can't hold the North
if you let these lesser lords insult us.
BOLTON: I sent you there to collect taxes,
not bodies.
RAMSAY: Lord Cerwyn refused to pay.
Said the Warden of the North
would always be a Stark,
and he'd be damned
if he'd kiss a traitor's boot.
BOLTON: He left you no choice.
I flayed him living,
along with his wife and brother.
Made his son watch.
And?
The new Lord Cerwyn paid his taxes.
I've something important to tell you.
Stop eating and listen.
We don't have enough men to hold the North
if the other houses rise up against us.
Do you understand that?
Our pact with the Lannisters protects...
I had a pact with Tywin Lannister.
And Tywin Lannister is dead.
The remaining Lannisters are
a thousand miles away dealing with that fact.
They've never once,
in the history of the Seven Kingdoms,
sent their army this far north.
If you think they will for us, you're a fool.
We've become a great house
by entering into alliances with other houses,
and parlaying those alliances
into greater power.
The best way to forge a lasting alliance
isn't by peeling a man's skin off.
The best way is marriage.
Now that you're a Bolton by royal decree,
it's high time you married a suitable bride.
And as it happens,
I've found the perfect girl
to solidify our hold on the North.
SANSA: That's Moat Cailin.
Yes, a bit shabby, isn't it?
You've been here before?
On our way down to King's Landing
with my father and Arya.
Where are you taking me?
Home.
The Boltons have Winterfell.
Your marriage proposal, it wasn't for you.
No.
Roose Bolton murdered my brother.
He betrayed my family.
He did.
He serves the Lannisters.
For now.
- I won't go.
- Winterfell is your home.
- Not anymore.
- Always.
You're a Stark.
Dying your hair doesn't change that.
You're Sansa Stark, eldest surviving child
of Ned and Catelyn Stark.
Your place is in the North.
I can't marry him. You can't make me.
He is a traitor. A murderer!
You're not marrying Roose Bolton.
No, you'll be marrying
his son and heir, Ramsay.
One day he'll be Warden of the North
and you...
- No.
- Sansa.
No, you can't make me. I will starve myself.
I will die before I have to go there.
I won't force you to do anything.
Don't you know by now
how much I care for you?
Say the word and we turn the horses around,
but listen to me.
Listen.
You've been running all your life.
Terrible things happen to your family
and you weep.
You sit alone in a darkened room
mourning their fates.
You've been a bystander to tragedy
from the day they executed your father.
Stop being a bystander. Do you hear me?
Stop running.
There's no justice in the world.
Not unless we make it.
You loved your family.
Avenge them.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
MAN: Banners!
PODRICK: How do we get through there?
BRIENNE: We don't.
We go around.
Takes us miles out of the way.
We'll lose sight of them.
BRIENNE: Doesn't matter.
I know where they're going.
Aren't you getting a bit old to be a squire?
How did you end up squiring for the Imp?
He hates that nickname.
Well, he's not here to complain about it,
is he?
I squired for a knight named Ser Lorimer
during the War of the Five Kings.
One night, he had a bit too much to drink,
and he was famished, so he borrowed a ham.
He borrowed it?
He wasn't a thief.
He was drunk, and hungry,
and he wasn't thinking.
I was drunk, too.
He gave me half the ham.
Next morning,
one of the guards saw him passed out
under a wagon
with the hambone still in his hand.
They hanged him that afternoon.
They tied the noose for me, too,
but Lord Tywin heard
my family name was Payne,
so he pardoned me,
and sent me to King's Landing
to squire for his son.
As punishment for both of you.
It didn't seem that way.
Lord Tyrion was always very good to me.
Yes, all your lords have been very kind to you.
All except me.
Sorry, you had to squire
for such a nasty person.
I'm not sorry.
You're the best fighter I've ever seen.
You beat the Hound.
I'm proud to be your squire.
I'm sorry I'm always snapping at you.
If you didn't snap at me,
I wouldn't learn anything.
You want to be a knight, Pod?
Yes.
Starting tomorrow,
we'll train with the sword twice a day,
before we ride in the morning
and after you make camp in the evening.
And I'm going to show you
how to ride properly.
Thank you.
I can't knight you,
but I can teach you how to fight.
I suppose that's more important.
You weren't a knight,
but you were a Kingsguard
to Renly Baratheon, weren't you?
I was.
Lord Tyrion said he was a good man.
He was.
How did you end up serving Renly?
When I was a girl, my father held a ball.
I'm his only living child,
so he wanted to make a good match for me.
He invited dozens of young lords to Tarth.
I didn't want to go,
but he dragged me to the ballroom.
And it was wonderful.
None of the boys noticed
how mulish and tall I was.
They shoved each other
and threatened to duel
when they thought it was their turn to dance.
They whispered in my ear
how they wanted to marry me
and take me back to their castles.
My father smiled at me, and I smiled at him.
I had never been so happy.
Till I saw a few of the boys sniggering.
And then they all started to laugh.
They couldn't keep
the game going any longer.
They were toying with me.
"Brienne the Beauty," they called me.
Great joke.
And I realized I was the ugliest girl alive.
A great lumbering beast.
I tried to run away,
but Renly Baratheon took me in his arms.
"Don't let them see your tears," he told me.
"They're nasty little shits,
"and nasty little shits
aren't worth crying over."
He danced with me,
and none of the other boys could say a word.
Renly was the king's brother after all.
But wasn't he...
Lord Tyrion said he was...
Yes, Pod, he liked men. I'm not an idiot.
He didn't love me. He didn't want me.
He danced with me because he was kind,
and didn't want to see me hurt.
He saved me from being a joke.
From that day until his last day.
And I couldn't save him in return.
Nothing's more hateful
than failing to protect the one you love.
One day I will avenge King Renly.
But you said a shadow murdered him.
How do you fight a shadow?
A shadow with the face of Stannis Baratheon.
I know it was Stannis. I know it in my heart.
Stannis is a man, not a shadow.
And a man can be killed.
- Lord Commander.
- Your Grace.
I'd like to speak alone.
Olly is my steward now,
as I was Lord Commander Mormont's.
I want him to attend my meetings
to learn from men with experience.
One day he might command.
Very well.
Have you considered my offer?
I have.
And I thank you for it.
You do me great honor.
All my life I wanted to be Jon Stark.
Say the word and you will be.
But I have to refuse you.
I'm Lord Commander of the Night's Watch.
My place is here.
I'm giving you the chance
to avenge your family,
to take back the castle where you grew up.
To rule the North.
I wish I could fight beside you.
Believe me, I do.
But I swore a sacred vow at the godswood.
I pledged my life to the Night's Watch.
You're as stubborn as your father.
And as honorable.
I can imagine no higher praise.
I didn't mean it as praise.
Honor got your father killed.
But if your mind's made up,
I won't try and dissuade you.
May I ask how long you plan
to stay at Castle Black?
Are you bored of us already?
You saved us from Mance Rayder's army.
We will never forget that.
But it's a question of survival.
The Night's Watch can't continue
to feed your men
and the wildling prisoners indefinitely.
Winter is coming.
I know it.
We march on Winterfell within the fortnight,
before the snows trap us here.
And the wildlings?
If they'd rather burn than fight for me,
so be it.
I leave their fate to you.
You could execute them.
That's the safest course.
Or you could see if this Tormund fellow
is more willing to compromise
than Mance ever was.
I assume the brothers of the Night's Watch
would rather see the wildlings dead.
Most of the brothers, yes.
There's little love for the free folk here.
You're the Lord Commander. Your decision.
(DOOR OPENS)
You have many enemies in Castle Black.
Have you considered
sending Alliser Thorne elsewhere?
Give him command of Eastwatch-by-the-Sea.
I heard it was best
to keep your enemies close.
Whoever said that didn't have many enemies.
DAVOS: He sees something in you.
Might not be apparent from his tone,
but it's the truth.
He believes in you.
I'm sorry I disappointed him.
The king is a complicated man,
but he wants to do what's right
for the Seven Kingdoms.
As long as he's ruling them.
He's the one true king.
He has a blood right to that throne.
I've sworn to stay clear of the politics
of the Seven Kingdoms.
Have you now?
How does the Night's Watch vow go again?
I'll bet you've got it memorized
since you got here.
Night gathers and now my watch begins.
No, not that bit. The bit at the end.
I am the sword in the darkness,
the watcher on the walls,
the shield that guards the realms of men.
- I pledge my life...
- Right, that's enough.
The shield that guards the realms of men.
That's what you swore to be.
Now, I'm not a learned man,
but the best way to help the most people
might not be sitting in a frozen castle
at the edge of the world.
It just might mean wading in the muck,
getting your boots dirty,
and doing what needs to be done.
And what needs to be done?
As long as the Boltons rule the North,
the North will suffer.
Just one man's opinion.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(DOOR OPENS)
What do you want?
Who are you?
What?
You, who walk in here
with a coin you never earned,
whose value you do not respect.
Who are you?
No one.
Ow!
- Cunt!
- A lie.
A sad little lie. Who are you?
I told you, I'm...
Do that again, and...
Who are you?
You're about to find out.
What are you doing?
We were only playing. The Game of Faces.
- A girl is not ready.
- Clearly not.
I am ready.
For what?
For whatever you want.
To be a Faceless Man. To be no one.
JAQEN: Whose sword is that?
It belongs to Arya Stark.
Arya Stark's sword, clothes, stolen silver.
A man wonders,
how is it that no one came to be
surrounded by Arya Stark's things?
(SIGHS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
What do we do with them after we wash them?
MAN 1: Open gate!
MAN 2: Honor guard, stand to!
MAN 3: Hold up. Easy.
Lady Sansa. Welcome.
Lord Bolton.
May I introduce my son, Ramsay Bolton?
It's an honor to meet you, my lady.
I'll bring you a bowl of hot water.
You must want to wash.
Thank you.
Welcome home, Lady Stark.
The North remembers.
(MEN CHATTING)
Sam?
Maester Aemon?
He apologizes for not being here.
He's not feeling well.
Take good care of him.
- Brothers.
- (CHATTER STOPS)
As you all know too well,
it's long past time to dig a new latrine pit.
(MEN LAUGHING)
First Builder Yarwyck and I
have decided to appoint a latrine captain
to oversee this crucial task.
(MEN LAUGH)
Brian.
Seems like a good job for a ginger.
- That's him!
- That's him.
Ser Alliser.
You have more experience
than any other ranger at Castle Black.
You proved your valor many times over
while defending the Wall
from the wildling attack.
I name you First Ranger.
MEN: Hear, hear!
(POUNDING ON TABLES)
Lord Janos.
I'm giving you command of Greyguard.
Greyguard is a ruin.
Yes, the fort is in a sorry state.
Restore it as best you can.
First Builder Yarwyck can spare 10 of his...
JANOS: I was charged
with the defense of King's Landing
when you were soiling
your swaddling clothes.
Keep your ruin.
(MEN SHOUTING)
- All right! That's enough of that.
- (SHOUTING STOPS)
You mistake me, my lord.
That was a command, not an offer.
Pack your arms and armor,
say your farewells,
and ride for Greyguard.
I will not go meekly off to freeze and die.
Give it to one of the fools
who cast a stone for you.
I will not have it. Did you hear me, boy?
I will not have it!
Are you refusing to obey my order?
You can stick your order up your bastard ass.
(MEN MURMURING)
Take Lord Janos outside.
Olly, bring me my sword.
- Get out.
- You cannot do this!
Get your hands off me! Scum, all of you!
If the boy thinks he can frighten me,
he's mistaken.
Yes, very mistaken.
Disgrace!
I have friends.
Important friends in the capital.
- You'll see.
- Kneel!
If you have any last words, my lord,
now's the time.
I was wrong. You're the Lord Commander.
We all serve you. I'm sorry.
Not only for this, for all I've done and said.
I was wrong.
My lord, please! Mercy! Mercy!
I'll go! I will! (SOBBING)
Please.
I'm afraid.
(WHIMPERING)
I've always been afraid.
(WOMEN GIGGLING)
You have served us well, my son.
Thank you, Father.
Which of the Seven will you worship today?
The Maiden.
Always the Maiden.
SEPTON: And the Stranger.
- Two is extra, you realize?
- Yes, yes.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
(GASPS)
What are you doing?
This establishment belongs
to Lord Petyr Baelish. You can't...
(GROANS)
You have profaned our faith,
the faith of our fathers and forefathers.
I am the High Septon of the...
- You are a sinner.
- (GROANS)
And you shall be punished.
- (CRACKS)
- Ah!
(WOMAN LAUGHS)
- Sinner.
- SPARROWS: Sinner.
- Sinner. Sinner.
- MAN 1: Repent!
Sinner.
- Sinner.
- (GROANS)
Sinner. Sinner.
- MAN 2: Shame on you.
- SPARROWS: Sinner.
(DOORS CLOSE)
Your Grace, Grand Maester, Lord Tyrell...
Uh...
It doesn't matter.
As the High Septon of the Faith of the Seven,
I give voice to the will of the gods
and am their foremost servant in this world.
An insult to me is an insult to the gods.
An assault on my person
is an assault on our very religion.
- You were assaulted?
- I was.
By those fanatics
who call themselves Sparrows.
They humiliated me, they beat me,
they left me naked and bleeding
on the cobblestones.
I am lucky to be alive.
I heard this assault
began in Littlefinger's brothel.
This is a rather shocking thing to hear.
SEPTON: I tend to both the highest born
and the lowliest amongst us.
Even prostitutes
may earn the mercy of the Mother.
So, you were ministering
to the needs of these devout prostitutes?
A man's private affairs ought to stay private.
What do you want from us, High Septon?
Justice.
I ask that you protect our faith
by arresting these criminals
and throwing them in the Black Cells.
I ask that you execute their leader,
this so-called High Sparrow.
He's a threat to everything we hold sacred.
If he goes unpunished...
And where do I find this man?
This High Sparrow?
I don't think this is a good idea.
Nonsense, Ser Meryn.
These are deeply religious people.
Where can I find the High Sparrow?
MAN 1: Seven blessings.
- (PEOPLE COUGHING)
- (FLIES BUZZING)
(BABY CRYING)
- MAN 2: Thank you.
- MAN 3: Just a little more.
(BABY CONTINUES CRYING)
WOMAN 1: Thank you.
MAN 4: Thank you.
A young man said I'd find
the High Sparrow back here.
- Where is he?
- High Sparrow?
Sounds ridiculous, doesn't it?
Like Lord Duckling or King Turtle.
Still, it's meant to.
We're often stuck with the names
our enemies give to us.
The notion that we're all equal
in the eyes of the Seven
doesn't sit well with some, so they belittle me.
WOMAN 2: Seven blessings to you.
Seven blessings to you, my dear.
It's only a name.
Quite an easy burden to bear.
Far easier than hers.
CERSEI: Why no shoes?
Because I gave them away
to someone who needed them more.
We all do that.
It stops us from forgetting what we really are.
Is that why you came to King's Landing?
To remind everyone?
Everyone? Hard enough job
reminding myself.
Well, I tell them no one's special,
and they think I'm special for telling them so.
Perhaps they're right.
It would be comforting to believe that,
wouldn't it?
Have the gods sent you here to tempt me?
I hope not.
I had assumed
you'd only come here to arrest me
for that incident with the High Septon.
An unacceptable way
to treat the chosen representative
of the gods in this world, wouldn't you say?
Hypocrisy is a boil.
Lancing a boil is never pleasant.
Although they could have been
more careful with the blade.
The High Septon came to speak to me today.
He doesn't want me to arrest you.
He wants me to execute you.
I wouldn't presume
to know your thoughts on the matter.
My thoughts on the matter
are in line with your own.
The High Septon's behavior was corrosive,
as was his attitude.
Having a man like that reside in the sept
eats away at the faith from the inside.
So now he resides
in the Red Keep dungeons instead.
The faith and the crown are the two pillars
that hold up this world.
One collapses, so does the other.
We must do everything necessary
to protect one another.
(SQUEAKING)
- (FLESH SQUELCHES)
- (RAT SQUEALS)
Your Grace.
Send a raven with this message
to Littlefinger at the Eyrie,
or wherever he's slithering about.
At once, Your Grace.
How's your work coming along?
Very well.
You've made progress?
More than I expected.
- Still a way to go, but...
- Very good.
I'll leave you to it, then.
Make sure Littlefinger is clear
on the meaning of the word "immediately."
(BOTTLES RATTLE)
Shh.
Easy, friend.
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
RAMSAY: She really is lovely.
I hope I can make her happy.
I hope so, too.
I've become quite fond of Lady Sansa
during our travels together.
She's suffered enough.
I'll never hurt her. You have my word.
I've heard very little about you,
which makes you quite a rare thing
as lords go.
I haven't been a lord very long.
I was a bastard.
And you're not anymore.
Allow me a moment alone with Lord Baelish.
Yes, Father.
And thank you, Lord Baelish.
I'm forever in your debt.
He seems pleased.
Shouldn't he be?
I assure you, she's still a virgin.
Tyrion never consummated the marriage.
By the law of the land, she is no man's wife.
Inspect her, if you must.
I'll leave that to the brothel keeper.
It's her name I need, not her virtue.
Then I have delivered everything I promised.
And you're prepared for the consequences
when the Lannisters hear
I've wed Sansa Stark to Ramsay?
The Lannister name
doesn't mean what it once did.
Tywin is dead.
He kept his house in power
through sheer will.
Without him,
Jaime has one hand and no allies.
Tommen is a soft boy, not a king to fear.
The queen will be enraged.
Queen Margaery adores Sansa.
Cersei is Queen Mother,
a title whose importance
wanes with each passing day.
And yet she still has friends,
men in important places
whom she can ask for favors.
A message for you from Cersei Lannister.
A rider arrived from the Eyrie
shortly before dawn.
Apparently she thinks you're still in the Vale.
A message for me, you say?
Strange that the seal is broken.
I'm sure you understand my position,
Lord Baelish.
If you receive word in the night
from the Queen Mother,
it does make me question our new alliance.
The Lannisters made you
one of the great lords of Westeros,
yet here you are in the North
undermining them.
Why gamble with your position?
Every ambitious move is a gamble.
You gambled when you drove a dagger
into Robb Stark's heart.
It appears that your gamble paid off.
You're Warden of the North.
I had Tywin Lannister's backing.
Who supports me now? You?
The Eyrie is mine.
The last time the lords of the Eyrie
formed an alliance with the lords of the North,
they brought down the greatest dynasty
this world has ever known.
I'd like to borrow one of your birds.
Cersei will expect a reply.
I'd like to read the reply.
I have to get out of this wheelhouse.
Volantis is a large city.
The likelihood of you being spotted here
increases a hundredfold.
Mmm, I have to get out of this wheelhouse.
(SIGHS) I'm not sure how many new ways
I can find of saying this.
I will not be of any use to Daenerys Targaryen
if I lose my mind.
I can't remember the last face I saw
that wasn't yours.
It's a perfectly good face.
I am losing my mind.
If anyone recognizes you,
you'll lose more than that.
Look, we are thousands of miles
from Westeros.
What am I?
One more drunk dwarf.
(KNOCKS)
- DRIVER: Whoa!
- (HORSES NEIGH)
(SEAGULL SCREECHING)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING)
WOMAN: We have to go now.
Come on, hold it. Hold it.
Are you ready?
Slaves.
Yes, the Volantene masters
are very organized.
Flies for dung shovelers.
Hammers for builders.
Tears for whores.
Lest they forget.
(WOMAN SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
Lord cast your light upon us.
(CROWD REPEATING)
For the night is dark and full of terrors.
We should keep moving.
(CROWD REPEATING)
I was once as you are now.
Bought and sold,
scourged and branded,
The only red priest we had in King's Landing
was Thoros of Myr.
This one's much better-looking.
The Lord of Light hears your voice.
He hears the king as he hears the slave;
he hears the Stone Men in their misery.
Stone men.
Good luck stopping
the spread of greyscale with prayer.
You'd have better luck
dancing away the plague.
He has sent you a savior!
From the fire she was reborn
to remake the world!
The Dragon Queen!
We're going to meet the savior.
You should have told me.
Who doesn't want to meet the savior?
Come on.
Let's find a brothel.
- (PEOPLE SHOUTING)
- (ANIMALS CALLING)
MAN: Build your house in a day.
(SPEAKING VALYRIAN)
It's good luck to rub a dwarf's head.
It's even better luck to suck a dwarf's cock.
See? We blend right in.
Just two more travelers mad with lust.
VARYS: Thank you.
(SNIFFING)
What curious hair.
The Mother of Dragons!
(MEN LAUGH)
It appears you're not
the only Targaryen supporter.
We were just heading east to see you.
I've got a dragon for you.
How much to make him spit fire?
Someone who inspires priests and whores
is worth taking seriously.
What makes you worth that much?
- I'm magic.
- I'll bet you bloody are.
(LAUGHING)
Well, she's taken.
Where are you going?
I need to speak to someone with hair.
- Hello.
You've got no drink.
You've got no money.
Do I look like a man without money?
Never trust looks.
Until quite recently,
I was one of the richest men in the world.
(LAUGHS)
But who needs wealth
when you can make a woman laugh?
I always pay my debts.
I'm well known for it.
(LAUGHTER)
You like her.
They all like her.
They all want to fuck a queen.
That's because they've never met a queen.
You're just saying that.
You know how to spot a liar.
If I could pick any girl here,
I would pick you.
Why?
Because you have a skeptical mind.
All right, then. I'm warning you,
we're going to have to wash you first.
Come on.
I'm sorry, I can't.
Of course you can. You're shy.
I'm not.
Have another drink.
Gladly, but this, I can't do.
Believe me, no one is more shocked than I am.
I hope it passes.
What will I do in my spare time?
Go for a piss. That's a start.
(URINATING)
(MUG SPLASHES)
No need to worry. I was just...
Oh.
I thought you were someone else.
Show's almost over.
I'm sure there are girls inside
who'd be happy to oblige.
You've made some kind of mistake.
Why don't you tell me
what you think you're doing, and then...
I'm taking you to the queen.