(MAN BREATHING HEAVILY)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(CONTINUES BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GHOST PANTING)
(WHINING)
(GASPING)
- (JON GRUNTS)
- Easy, easy. Easy.
What do you remember?
They stabbed me.
Olly...
He put a knife in my heart.
I shouldn't be here.
The lady brought you back.
Afterwards, after they stabbed you,
after you died, where did you go?
What did you see?
Nothing.
There was nothing at all.
The Lord let you come back for a reason.
Stannis was not the prince
who was promised,
but someone has to be.
Could you give us a moment?
(DOOR CREAKING)
(SOFTLY) You were dead.
And now you're not.
That's completely fucking mad, seems to me.
I can only imagine how it seems to you.
I did what I thought was right,
and I got murdered for it.
Now I'm back.
- Why?
- I don't know.
Maybe we'll never know.
What does it matter?
You go on.
You fight for as long as you can.
You clean up as much of the shit as you can.
I don't know how to do that.
I thought I did,
but I failed.
Good.
Now go fail again.
(DOOR OPENS)
They think you're some kind of god.
The man who returned from the dead.
I'm not a god.
I know that.
I saw your pecker.
What kind of god would
have a pecker that small?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(WINCES)
(JON WINCING)
Your eyes are still brown.
Is that still you in there?
I think so.
Hold off on burning my body for now.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
That's funny.
(JON SNIFFLES)
You sure that's still you in there?
(BOTH LAUGH)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(SAMWELL GROANS)
- You all right?
- Yes. Yes, I'm fine.
Did I ever tell you I used to think
the sea was called "the see"
because it was nothing but water
as far as the eye could see?
I don't think so.
Sea, see.
They're spelled different,
but they sound the same.
Yeah. They do.
It was before I learned
how to read, obviously.
Sam, are you going to be sick?
(RETCHING)
Won't be long. We'll be in the south soon.
I'm excited to see Oldtown.
Captain says it's the most beautiful city
in Westeros.
- Are you going to vomit again?
- No. No, no, no. Um...
The Citadel doesn't admit women.
There won't be a place for you there,
or for little Sam.
I stayed at Castle Black.
There's no women allowed there.
The Citadel isn't Castle Black.
I don't have a Jon Snow or Maester Aemon
to help me bend the rules.
I'll stay in Oldtown, then.
By yourself? With a baby and no money?
So if we're not going to Oldtown,
where are you taking me?
To my home. Horn Hill.
My father's... Well, my father.
But my mother's a kind woman
and my sister's lovely.
They'll take care of you both.
"Wherever you go, I go, too."
That's what you said.
(STUTTERS)
I said that because
I want you and Little Sam to be safe.
That's all I want.
To become a maester so I can help Jon
when the time comes,
so you'll be safe.
Us and everyone else in the world.
I don't care about them.
Well, no, I do,
but I don't really. (CHUCKLES)
I care about you and him.
I know that, Sam. And he does, too.
You're the only one who ever has.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
If you think it's for the best,
we trust you.
I'd feel better if you threw something
at me and stormed off.
I'd never do that to
the father of my son.
(SAM COOS)
(RETCHING)
(COUGHS)
(HORSES WHINNYING)
(HORSES WHINNY IN THE DISTANCE)
(HORSES APPROACHING)
That's my father.
The man beside him is Howland Reed,
Meera's father.
Ser Arthur Dayne.
The Sword of the Morning.
Father said he was the best
swordsman he ever saw.
Lord Stark.
I looked for you on the Trident.
We weren't there.
Your friend, the Usurper,
would lie beneath the ground
if we had been.
The Mad King is dead.
Rhaegar lies beneath the ground.
Why weren't you there
to protect your prince?
Our prince wanted us here.
Where's my sister?
I wish you good fortune in the wars to come.
And now it begins.
No. Now it ends.
- (YELLING)
- (ALL GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(SHOUTS)
(GURGLES)
(GROANS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
He's better than my father.
Far better.
But Father beat him.
Did he?
I know he did.
Heard the story a thousand times.
(GURGLES)
(GRUNTS)
He stabbed him in the back.
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
What's in the tower?
That's enough for one day.
We'll visit again another time.
I want to see where he's going.
Time to go.
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
Father!
(GASPS)
Why did you do that? Take me back there.
I want to go back.
No.
(RAVEN CROWS)
He heard me.
Maybe. Maybe he heard the wind.
The past is already written. The ink is dry.
What's in that tower?
I want to go back there.
I've told you many times,
stay too long where you don't belong
and you will never return.
Why do I want to return?
So I can be a cripple again?
So I can talk to an old man in a tree?
You think I wanted to sit here for 1,000 years
watching the world from a distance
as the roots grew through me?
So why did you?
I was waiting for you.
I don't want to be you.
(CHUCKLES) I don't blame you.
You won't be here forever.
You won't be an old man in a tree.
But before you leave, you must learn.
Learn what?
Everything.
(OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
Hey, Great Khaleesi. Move your ass.
Welcome home, Khaleesi.
(DOOR CREAKING)
Go.
(DOOR OPENS)
What are you doing?!
Take your hands off me!
I will have your heads!
You have made a mistake.
One you will regret.
I am the wife of the Great Khal.
We know who you are.
I remember you eating
the stallion's heart.
Why didn't you come to us
after Khal Drogo died?
Because I am Daenerys Stormborn,
the Breaker of Chains,
the Queen of Meereen
and the Mother of Dragons.
My place is not here with you.
You were the wife of the Great Khal.
You thought he would conquer the
world with you at his side.
He didn't.
I was the wife of the Great Khal.
Khal Savo.
I thought he would conquer the world
with me at his side.
You're young.
We were all young once.
But we all understand
the way things are.
You will learn as well,
if you are fortunate enough
to stay with us.
Where else would I go?
Every Khaleesi becomes Dosh Khaleen.
Yes. Immediately after the death
of their khal.
But you went out into the world.
That is forbidden.
All the khalasars have returned
for the Khalar Vezhven.
They will decide which cities will be sacked
and which tribes will be enslaved.
And now they must decide what to do
with Khal Drogo's silver-haired widow.
With luck, your place will be here
with us, Mother of Dragons.
It is the best you can hope for, now.
I don't know how you stand it
in all that leather.
If we could have the room.
You look lovely today, my dear.
You really do.
How you climbed all those steps
without breaking a sweat.
If you're going to torture me,
just call them back and get on with it.
I am not a torturer.
Though it so often is what people deserve.
And it does provide answers.
But they're usually the wrong answers.
My job is to find the right answers.
Do you know how I do that?
I do it by making people happy.
I'd like to make you happy, Vala.
That's your name, isn't it? Vala.
(CHUCKLES) That's all right.
I know who you are and what you've done.
You've done a lot.
You've sacrificed your body for a cause,
which is more than most people do.
And you've helped the Sons of the Harpy
murder the Unsullied and the Second Sons.
The Unsullied and the Second Sons
are foreign soldiers,
brought here by a foreign queen
to destroy our city and our history.
I understand.
Well, that makes perfect sense
from your perspective.
I have a different perspective, of course.
I think it's important that you try to see things
from my perspective,
just as I will try to see them from yours.
Because that is the only way
that I can make you and Dom happy.
That is how you pronounce it, "Dom"?
I'm afraid
I don't really speak the language.
Such a handsome boy.
Those big, brown eyes.
Good luck keeping the ladies away.
Yes, you're a true liberator, aren't you?
You won't torture me,
you'll just threaten my son.
Children are blameless.
I have never hurt them.
Your boy is in no immediate danger,
this I swear to you.
But between us, dear,
you did conspire to kill the queen's soldiers.
We both know the penalty for that crime.
How will poor Dom get on
without his mother?
And with his breathing problem.
If I tell you anything, they'll kill me.
So either you kill me or they do.
Yes, from your perspective,
this is a problem.
There is a third option, though.
A ship leaving tomorrow for Pentos.
I've already booked passage
for a woman and her young son.
I'll even throw in a bag of silver
to help you start again.
Though I'm afraid we'll have to ask
one of our leather-clad friends
back in to carry it.
Far too heavy for me.
The boat sails at dawn.
You need to decide now.
A new life for you and Dom, or...
What should we do while we wait?
To pass the time, what should we do?
What should we talk about?
You speak 19 languages.
You must occasionally use some of them
to talk about things.
You two, you spend
a great deal of time together.
What would you be talking about
if I weren't here?
Patrol.
When I am going on patrol
with the Unsullied.
What we see on patrol.
Who we captured on patrol.
That's good. That's very good.
But that's a report.
I was thinking more of a conversation.
A wise man once said,
"The true history of the world
"is the history of great conversations
in elegant rooms."
Who said this?
Me. Just now.
All right, no conversations.
Let's play a game.
You don't play games?
Either one of you, ever?
Games are for children.
My master Kraznys
would sometimes make us play games.
There, that's a start.
Only the girls.
Oh... No, no, no.
Not that. Of course, not that.
Innocent games. Fun games. Drinking games.
MISSANDEI: We do not drink.
Until you do.
All right. No drinking.
We can play without drinking.
It's a wonderful game. I invented it.
Here's how it works.
I make a statement about your past.
If I'm wrong, I drink.
And if I'm right...
(GASPS)
Maybe we can't play without drinking.
(DOOR OPENS)
Oh, you took your time.
VARYS: Sorry.
I was busy learning
who funds the Sons of the Harpy.
Some things you can't rush.
You found out?
The Good Masters of Astapor
and the Wise Masters of Yunkai.
With help from their friends in Volantis.
TYRION: You see?
You don't even have to worry
about the local rebellion.
We only have to worry about
the three rich foreign cities paying for it.
We conquered Astapor and Yunkai once.
We will do it again and execute the Masters.
If the Unsullied march off to
re-conquer Astapor and Yunkai,
who will remain to defend
the free people of Meereen?
If we do not fight them,
how can we stop them?
We cannot.
The Masters speak only one language.
They spoke it to me for many years.
I know it better than my mother tongue.
If we want them to hear us,
we must speak it back to them.
May it be the last thing they ever hear.
You may be right.
So we will fight them?
- Possibly.
- Possibly?
It's a conversation.
Tell me, can your little birds get a message
to the Good Masters of Astapor,
the Wise Masters of Yunkai,
and benevolent enslavers of Volantis?
Of course. Men can be fickle,
but birds I always trust.
(CHILDREN MUTTERING)
QYBURN: Your eye looks much better, Arthur.
How's your mother's jaw?
Better.
And your father?
No one's seen him.
And no one will.
That worked out rather nicely.
Will Lord Varys ever come back?
I don't think so.
Do you miss him?
He was nice.
He called us his little birds.
He gave us sweets.
It's funny you should mention that.
Guess what I happened to find today.
Candied plums from Dorne.
(LAUGHING)
Now remember,
if any of your friends like sweets or need help,
they can always come to me.
All I need in return are whispers.
(DOOR OPENS)
QYBURN: No need to be afraid.
This is Ser Gregor.
He's friends with all my friends.
Run along now.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
- Varys's little birds?
Your little birds now, Your Grace.
What did you do to him exactly?
I haven't been able to get a clear answer.
Oh, a number of things.
Does he understand what we're saying?
I mean, to the extent that he ever understood
complete sentences in the first place.
He understands well enough.
So tell him to march into the Sept
and crush the High Sparrow's head
like a melon.
The High Sparrow has hundreds
of Faith Militant surrounding him.
Ser Gregor can't face them all.
And he won't have to.
He'll only have to face one.
Has the Faith leveled official charges yet?
Not yet.
That is one trial by combat
I look forward to watching.
Don't stop at the city.
I want little birds in Dorne,
in Highgarden, in the North.
If someone is planning on
making our losses their gains,
I want to hear it.
If someone is laughing at the queen
who walked naked through
the streets covered in shit,
I want to hear.
I want to know who they are.
I want to know where they are.
PYCELLE: As bad as Lord Varys was,
Qyburn is worse.
I told them all. I told them.
He's arrogant, dangerous.
You don't get thrown out of the Citadel
without good reason.
And no one listened to my advice.
So here we are.
And what he's done to Gregor Clegane
is an abomination.
We never sanctioned this experiment.
And I, for one,
think it would be in our best interest
to have the beast...
(PYCELLE FLATULATES)
- Can I help you?
- Why are you here?
- My mother...
- I was invited, my dear,
to help deal with several troublesome issues,
such as the queen's imprisonment.
Thank you for bringing it up.
It's well past time we addressed
the abuses I endured.
Margaery is the queen.
You are not the queen
because you're not married to the king.
I do appreciate these things
can get a bit confusing in your family.
This is a Small Council meeting.
You have no position on the Small Council.
I'm the Lord Commander of the Kingsguard.
The Lord Commander of the Kingsguard
does have a position on the Small Council.
Grand Maester Pycelle,
would you sanction that statement?
Well, uh... (MUTTERS)
I would say Ser Gerold Hightower
had a seat on the Mad King's council.
Of course, that was the Mad King.
King Robert saw things differently.
And King...
What about Myrcella's death, Uncle?
Do you consider the murder
of your own blood a troublesome issue?
The same women who murdered Myrcella
have overthrown House Martell
and taken control of Dorne.
We've got a lot to discuss.
All of us, together.
And seeing as you cannot make us leave,
we best get on with it.
No, we cannot make you leave.
And you cannot make us stay.
Not unless you're gonna have
that thing murder us all.
(DOOR OPENS)
(GROANS SOFTLY) Your Grace.
My mother would like to see
her daughter's final resting place.
Ah, I'm sorry, Your Grace.
That's not possible. Not yet.
When will it be possible?
When she's fully atoned for her sins.
You cut off her hair
and marched her naked through the streets
in front of the whole city.
That wasn't the full atonement?
No.
She must stand trial before seven septons,
so we can learn the true extent of her sins.
I want you to
let her see Myrcella's resting place.
I am the king.
You are.
And what does that mean to you?
It means a great deal to me.
The Crown and the Faith
are the twin pillars of the world.
Do you know who told me that?
Your mother.
My mother who is unclean?
My mother who still needs to atone
after all you've put her through?
How do you think the Mother Above
first came to us?
How did men and women first come to
feel the Mother's presence, hmm?
It was through their own mothers.
There's a great deal of falsehood in Cersei.
You know that.
But when she speaks of you,
the Mother's love outshines it all.
Her love for you is more real
than anything else in this world
because it doesn't come from this world.
But you know that.
You've felt it.
You've seen her when she talks to you.
Yes.
It's a great gift. One I never had.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Envy.
One more thing for me to atone for.
Your Grace, do you... May I? Do you mind?
It's my knees.
- Of course.
- (CHUCKLES)
When your mother
made her walk of atonement,
she did it to get back to you.
I still don't understand
why you want to put her
through any more than she's already endured.
It's not what I want.
It's what the gods want.
They make their will known to us,
and it's up to us to either accept or reject it.
Please.
If we're to be just and good, then we accept it.
All of us, even kings.
A true leader avails himself
of the wisest counsel he can.
And no one is wiser than the gods.
My grandfather once said something similar.
Except for the part about the gods.
The gods worked through him
whether he knew it or not.
As they work through your mother.
There's so much good in all of us.
The best we can do
is to help each other bring it out.
(SCRAPING)
- (ARYA GASPS)
- Who are you?
ARYA: No one.
(GROANS)
Who were you before you came here?
Arya Stark. (GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
Tell me about Arya Stark's family.
Her father was Eddard Stark.
Her mother was Catelyn Stark.
She had one sister,
Sansa, and four brothers.
(GROANS)
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
Three brothers.
Robb, Bran, Rickon.
(ARYA GROANS)
And a half-brother Jon.
And where are they now?
ARYA: They may be dead for all a girl knows.
(SNIFFING)
Tell me about the Hound.
(GRUNTING)
ARYA: Also dead.
ARYA: Arya Stark left him to die.
He was on her list.
He was not on her list anymore.
She had taken him off it.
Why? Didn't she want him dead any longer?
ARYA: She did and she did not.
She sounds confused.
Yes, she was.
Who else was
on Arya Stark's funny little list?
(GROANING)
ARYA: Cersei Lannister.
Gregor Clegane.
Walder Frey.
WAIF: That's a short list.
That can't be everyone you want to kill.
Are you sure you're not forgetting someone?
Which name would you like a girl to speak?
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
JAQEN: If a girl tells me her name,
I will give her eyes back.
A girl has no name.
Come.
If a girl is truly no one,
she has nothing to fear.
Who are you?
No one.
The Umbers are a famously loyal house.
Famously loyal to the Starks.
And you, Lord Karstark,
your people share blood
with the Starks, don't they?
But here we are. Times change.
When my father became Warden of the North,
your house refused to pledge their banners.
Your father was a cunt.
My beloved father, the Warden...
Your father was a cunt,
and that's why you killed him.
I might have done the same to my father
if he hadn't have done me
the favor of dying on his own.
My father was poisoned by our enemies.
Mmm.
Why have you come to Winterfell,
Lord Umber?
The bastard Jon Snow
led an army of wildlings past the Wall.
We're farther north than any of you fuckers.
Wildlings come down,
we always have to fight them first.
I like fighting wildlings.
Been doing it all me life.
But there are too many of them
for us to beat back alone.
So now you've come seeking help?
We need to help each other.
The colder it gets, the farther south
those goat-fuckers will roam.
Won't take them long to get here.
You think a horde of wildlings
can take Winterfell?
If they get Jon Snow leading them, maybe.
He knows this place better than we ever will.
Pledge your banners to House Bolton,
swear loyalty to me as Warden of the North,
and we will fight together
to destroy the bastard
and all his wildling friends.
I'm not kissing your fucking hand.
Traditionally a bannerman
kneels before his lord.
I'm not doing that either.
Why would I trust a man
who won't honor tradition?
Your father honored tradition.
Knelt for Robb Stark.
Called him King of the North.
Was Robb Stark right to trust your father?
Then it appears we're at a bit of
an impasse.
Fuck kneeling and fuck oaths.
I've got a gift for you.
A girl, I hope. I prefer redheads.
A girl, aye.
(SMALLJON LAUGHS)
A wild one.
I like them wild.
And a boy, nice and young.
The way Karstark likes them.
(PANTING)
- Who's this?
- Rickon Stark.
How do I know that's Rickon Stark?
Welcome home, Lord Stark.
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
It's time.
If you have any last words, now is the time.
You shouldn't be alive. It's not right.
Neither was killing me.
My mother's still living at White Harbor.
Could you write her?
Tell her I died fighting the wildlings.
I had a choice, Lord Commander.
Betray you or betray the Night's Watch.
You brought an army of wildlings
into our lands.
An army of murderers and raiders.
If I had to do it all over
knowing where I'd end up,
I pray I'd make the right choice again.
I'm sure you would, Ser Alliser.
I fought, I lost.
Now I rest.
But you, Lord Snow,
you'll be fighting their battles forever.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
(CHOKING, GASPING)
We should burn the bodies.
You should.
What do you want me to do with this?
Wear it. Burn it.
Whatever you want.
You have Castle Black.
My watch is ended.