Tyrion Lannister:
How long does it go on?
Cersei:
Until we've dealt with all our enemies.
Tyrion Lannister:
Seven kingdoms united in fear of Tywin Lannister.
Unknown Character:
The Night's Watch can't stop them …
Kings and their armies can't stop them.
Stannis Baratheon:
The darkness will devour them all,
unless I triumph.
Stannis Baratheon:
We do not choose our destiny …
We must do our duty now …
Great or small, we must do our duty …
Daenerys:
Explain to me how you propose to defeat us.
Joffrey:
I am the king!
Everyone is mine to torment.
Daenerys:
I shall show you no mercy.
Robb Stark:
Take his home, take his gold, take his power,
If we don't do this, and do it now, we're lost.
A wildling:
We're finally going to war.
Mance Raydar:
I'm going to light the biggest fire the North has ever seen!
Unknown Charaacter:
I forbid you to die!
Jon Snow:
Big men fall just as quick as little ones.
Unknown Character:
Do you hear them screaming ...
Crying for their gods?