Game of Thrones - Stagione 7 Episodio 6 "The Episode That Came Before The Title"
Translation: TutorGirl, il.busto, blackwork, Blackmamba87
Translation: Yossarian, Lysine, Sylmaril, darthdread
Revision: TutorGirl
::Italiansubs:: [www.italiansubs.net]
All right?
Were not you ever been to the North before?
I had never seen snow.
Nice, right?
I can breathe again.
In the South, the air smells of pig shit.
You've never been to the South.
- I was at Winterfell.  - What is the North.
How do you live here?  How can you not freeze you to the bone?
You have to move all the time, that's the secret.
Walking is fine, fighting is better ...
fuck it is the maximum.
There are women living within hundreds of miles here.
You have to make do with what you have.
That does not seem very smart.
Davos says he is a strong fighter, he's good.
It is much more important than being smart.
Smart people are not up here in search of the dead.
Then...
You've met the Queen of Dragons, eh?
Then?
We will fight on our side if I kneel.
You spent too much time with the Free People.
Now you do not like your knees.
Mance Rayder was a great man.
A proud man.
The King Beyond the Wall that you never knelt.
How many of these people died for his pride?
Are you still mad at us, kid.
- you have sold to a witch.  - A priestess.
Admittedly the difference is subtle.
We are fighting a massive war.
- The wars cost.  - I wanted to be one of you.
I wanted to join the Brotherhood, but you sold me.
As a slave!
You know what I did?
I was tied to the bed, he stripped me naked ...
- So far it does not seem so terrible.  - he has covered me with leeches.
- She was naked, too?  - you needed your blood.
Yes, please, I know that.
- It could have been worse.  - He wanted to kill me!
- they would have killed me if it was not ... - But they did not!
Or wrong?  So what you're bitching?
I'm not griping.
Your lips are moving and you're complaining about something.
That's complaining.
This guy was shot six times and not feel the protest.
Good boy.
The first time I went to the north of the Barrier was with your father.
He was a good man.
He deserved a better son.
You were with him when he died?
I was a prisoner of the Brutes.
But the retribution.
I want you to know that I executed all the mutineers that I found.
I do not think there was a worse way for him to leave.
The Night's Watch were his life.
He would die to protect every one of those men.
And they slaughtered.
I can not stand that he died that way.
My father was the most honorable man I've ever known.
It was good, from all points of view.
Yet he died on the scaffold.
Your father wanted to execute me, you know?
I heard it.
It was the side of right.
Not that he would have hated less.
I'm glad you did not take.
Me too.
It was your father gave me this sword.
He turned the knob to bear wolf.
But it's still Long Claw.
Look, Commander Mormont
She thought that you would never have returned to the western continent.
But he came back.
And it has been in your family for centuries.
It is not fair that takes me.
He gave it to you.
I'm not his son.
I brought shame to my House.
I broke my father's heart.
I've lost the right to claim this sword.
It's yours.
It may serve you well well.
And your children after you.
Our father often looked at us from up here.
He did not talk much.
You probably do not remember it, you were in knitting all the time.
I remember.
Once the boys were shooting arrows with Ser Rodrik.
I came here after.
And Bran had left his bow.
There, resting on the ground.
Ser Rodrik would have caught her if I saw her.
There was an arrow in the target.
There was no one around,
just like now.
No one could stop me.
So I began to pull.
And each shot went over there to take back the arrow and came back to throw again.
I was not very good.
Eventually I hit the bull's-eye.
It must have been the twentieth or fiftieth attempt, I do not remember.
But I hit the bull's-eye.
And then I heard clapping.
I looked up ...
and he was standing right there, smiling at me.
I knew I was doing something against the rules.
But he was smiling, so I knew that I was not wrong.
They were the rules to be wrong.
I was doing what was in my fate and he knew it.
But he's dead now.
Killed by Lannister.
With your help.
Thing?
It's not your handwriting?
Septa Mordane I was cracking his fingers because you wrote as well.
"Robb,
I write to you with heart full of sadness.
Our good King Robert is dead
from injuries sustained during the boar hunt. "
You do not have to read it, I remember.
"Our father was accused of treason.
He conspired with Robert's brothers against my beloved Joffrey
and he tried to take his throne.
The Lannister treat me very well and I do not miss anything.
Please do: come to King's Landing, swears allegiance to King Joffrey
and stop any conflict between the great houses Lannister and Stark.
Your sister trusted, Sansa. "
- they are forced to write it!  - But really?
With a knife to your throat?
They tortured on a tripod until the bones began to break?
You have no idea of ​​the situation, I was a little girl!
I was too!  I would have her killed before betraying my family.
They told me that was the only way to save our father.
And it was stupid enough to believe him.
I remember you.
You were on the platform with Joffrey and Cersei, when our father dragged to the gallows.
I remember your beautiful dress and your elegant hairstyle.
- You were there?  - I was there there.
Standing in the crowd, near the statue of Baelor.
And what did you do?  She went to her rescue?
Combattesti against the Lannisters, and didst Dad?
- I wanted to.  - But you did not.
Just like me.
But he betrayed.  And I do not even betrayed Robb.
I do not betrayed my entire family for my beloved Joffrey!
You should kneel down to thank me.
We're back at Winterfell just because of me.
You have not won back you nor Jon, who lost the Battle of the Basterds.
The battle have won the Knights of the Valley, who came up north for me.
While you what you did, you turned to the world?
I was training.
Training?
Well, while you addestravi,
I suffered the pains that you can not even imagine.
I do not know what you've been through, but I can imagine many things, trust me.
I would never have survived what I went through.
I guess we'll never know.
What will you do with that letter?
I do not know yet.
To whom have you done reading?  Where do you find it?
You're afraid, are you?
What are you afraid of?
You have not committed any crime.
It will not be hanged.
- Arya ... - Topics that the monsters to Jon, you get angry.
No.
Are not you afraid of Jon.
You'll understand, you were just a scared little girl.
All alone with the Lannisters evil.
You know what Cersei would be happy to see us fight this way?
That's what I want, that's what he always wanted,
- he wants to divide us.  - Are you afraid that the Lord read the North.
Their opinion of Lady Sansa would worsen if they knew they had to Cersei orders.
What would the little Lyanna Mormont?
It's younger than you, than when you wrote this letter.
You will say to you too: "But I was only a child"?
Are you angry.
Sometimes anger does make people reckless actions.
Sometimes the fear is making reckless actions.
I prefer anger.
You are what they call "Mastiff".
Get up from the cock.
They were told that you were mean.
You are well born, or you'll irritate the wildlings?
I do not really give a fuck of Brutes.
I hate Rose.
The Rosci are beautiful.
We kissed by fire.
Just like you.
Not puntarmi with that finger prick.
Inciampasti in the fire when you were little?
Do not tripped, I drove there.
And since then it has become petty.
You rise from the fuck?
I do not think you're really mean.
You look sad.
Do you want to suck the bird, right?
Bird?
The cock.
Bird.  I like it.
I had no doubt.
No, I like pussy.
My beautiful is waiting for me at Winterfell.
If I could ever go back.
Blond hair, blue eyes.
The world's tallest woman.
High almost as much as you.
Di Brienne Tarth?
- Do you know her?  - Shit, you're with Brienne of Tarth?
Well, I'm still with her,
but I've seen how he looks at me.
And how do you look?
He looks at you as if to disembowel you and eat your liver?
Then you know it seriously!
I cross.
I want to have children with her.
Just think, the huge monstrous children who go to conquer the world.
How did a crazy asshole like you to live so long?
I'm good at killing people.
It does not look like much.
A chi?
Your father.
You'll get caught by your mother.
Did you know him?
Of course I know him.
When he was First Knight.
He sent me in search of the Mountain.
Your Brutes have told me that the Red Donna brought you back to life.
Thoros has revived me too.
Six times.
Both serve the same Lord.
I serve only North.
The North did not make you resurrect.
The Lord of Light has never spoken to me.
I do not know anything about him and do not know what he wants from me.
He wants to see you alive.
Because?
Non lo so.
Everyone says to me the same thing.  "I do not know".
What sense does it serve a god if no one knows what he wants?
It's something I think about constantly.
I do not think that our purpose is to understand.
Except for one thing.
We are soldiers.
We need to know what we're fighting.
I do not fight so that a man or a woman I know not sit on a throne of swords.
Then what you fight?
For the life.
Death is the enemy.
The first enemy ...
and also the last.
But we all die sooner or later.
The enemy will always win.
But we still have to fight it.
That's all I know.
You and I do not find joy in this life.
But we can keep alive other people.
We can defend those who can not defend themselves.
We are the shield that will guard the domain of men.
Maybe the only thing to understand is that.
Maybe we just that.
Aye.
In the fire I saw this place.
A mountain like the tip of an arrow.
Are you sure?
We are approaching.
You know what I like about you?
- I have not the foggiest idea.  - That you're not a hero.
They are heroic enough, from time to time.
I led the charge to the Mud Gate to King's Landing ...
I do not want you to be a hero.
The heroes do stupid things and die.
Drogo, Jorah, Daario, even that ...
Jon Snow.
They'll compete to see who is better.
To make the most stupid thing and heroic.
Of course it's interesting, now that you have appointed them ...
Drogo, Jorah, Daario, even that ...
Jon Snow...
They fell in love all of you.
- Jon Snow is not in love with me.  - Ah, I'll be wrong.
Certainly looks at him earnestly hopes
to forge a strong and lasting military alliance.
It's too low for me.
- That is, I did not mean ... - You're right, it is quite low.
I know you are brave.
I would not choose a coward as my First Knight.
So ...
If everything goes according to plan, I'll finally know your sister.
Although, from what you tell me, I think they will try to kill me rather than talk.
Before you would do unspeakable torture techniques, then kill you.
Nobody trusts my sister less of myself, believe me.
But at the time to reach the capital, we'll go with two armies and three dragons!
Should they try to hurt you, King's Landing would be devoured by the flames.
And now he'll be setting a trap.
Certainly.
We are wondering what trap have in Serbia for her.
And we have it?
A trap?
If we are going to create a new, better world ...
I do not think it is appropriate to start with betrayals and massacres.
And what new world did not begin with betrayals and massacres?
Of course, you have to be ruthless if you want to conquer the throne.
You will need to stir up a certain degree of fear, but fear is all that has Cersei.
That's all I had my father, and Joffrey.
Fear undermines the power.
Because anyone who is subjected their longs their death.
I think that Aegon Targaryen has thrived there, on fear.
It's true.
But you told me you want to break the wheel.
Aegon has created the wheel.  If you're going to be this kind of queen,
What will make you different from tyrants who preceded you?
Then shall we enter into the lion's den.
My brother promised me that will keep at bay the troops Lannister.
Forgive me, but I do not give any credence to promises of Lannister.
- Except yours.  - And I have promised him
that I would have dissuaded from engaging in any impulsive action.
Impulsive?
It will be a difficult negotiation.
We parlamenteremo with people who want us dead.
My sister will certainly say something to provoke you.
E...?
It is known that easily lose his temper at times.
- That is what great leaders.  - When have I lost my temper?
- When you burned the Tarly, for example?  - It was not an impulsive act.
It was a necessary act.
- Maybe.  - Maybe?
Maybe it was necessary to kill the father, not the son.
Maybe they both need to meditate on their mistakes in a cell.
We could not discuss such possibilities, you have destroyed in one shot.
Sorry, but I think in this case will be on the side of your family!
Of course I stand on their side!
You have to put yourself on the side of your enemy, if you want to understand their point of view.
And you have to understand their point of view, if you want to predict their actions,
respond effectively and beat them!
What you strongly suggest you do.
Because I believe in you and in the world you wish to build.
But the world you intend to build not build it all at once,
maybe just not even your whole life.
How are we going to ensure that your vision will survive?
After you've broken the wheel, as we will make sure that no one will rebuild?
Want to know who will sit on the Iron Throne after my death.
You said he could not bear children.
But there are other ways to choose a successor.
The Night's Watch have a method.
The Iron Men, though not without flaws,
- they have another.  - We will discuss my succession after
- my coronation.  - Majesty, I saw hundreds of arrows
be popped out to you during your assault on the Black Water,
and I've seen hundreds mancarti.  But each of these could have hurt you to the heart
- and kill you.  - a long time to imagine dead Steps.
It is one of the topics you have discussed with your brother to King's Landing?
I try to serve you thinking long-term.
Maybe, if I thought the short term, we would not have missed and Dorne Highgarden.
We will discuss my inheritance
after my coronation.
Look!
A bear.
A great fuck in the ass.
The bear has blue eyes!
We must bring him Eastwatch.
My flask.
Proceed.
Are you OK?
I have just been bitten by a huge dead bear.
Aye.
That's right.
Buffa life.
Power.
Issa!
- Where did you get?  - I do not know.
It seems to be full of surprises.
Are you worried.
We ask twenty thousand men to fight with us in the worst winter ever seen.
And the climate will be the least of their problems.
Many of them will be happy to have a reason to return home.
- Put questioned their loyalty.  - Their loyalty is towards Jon.
Jon is not here and I have not heard from him in weeks.
You are the Great Lady Winter.
The King has chosen you to rule in his absence.
And you're navigating.
Wisely.
In a manner capable.
They saw it all and respect you.
Some will prefer, too.
Yes, they turned to Jon when we resumed Winterfell,
then they elected him their king and now they are ready to turn their backs again.
How much would you trust such men?  They are damned flags.
If they found out I wrote that letter ...
A woman who married not one but two enemies of their families.
When he comes back Jon will no longer have an army.
Arya is not like them.
She's your sister.
You will also have discussions, but would never betray his family.
He would if he thought you were going to betray Jon.
- Is that what you think?  - I do not know what he thinks.
I do not know more, now.
Maybe Lady Brienne can help.
He has sworn to protect both daughters of Catelyn Stark.
Is not it?
Yup.
And if one of you meant to harm the other,
it would be his duty to intervene?
Yup.
There's one thing I've always wanted to know.
Tell me.
How you were drunk when you came into the breach in the walls of Pyke?
To be honest, I do not remember being passed into the breach.
Someone told me about the next morning.
- It looked like a good battle.  - Aye.
It was a very good fight.
The Iron Men thought I was a god,
while troubledst the flaming sword.
I thought you were the bravest man I ever saw.
Only the most drunk.
- Where are the others?  - If we wait too long we will find out.
Attack!
Back to Eastwatch.  Send a crow to Daenerys and tell her what happened.
- No, I do not leave you.  - You are the fastest.
Go, now!
You'll be faster without the hammer, give it to me.
Dammelo!
- Let's go.  - Power!
Come on!
Fermi!
Run!
What happened?
- Where are the others?  - Crow ...
We need to send a crow ...
Call the Master, now!
Marriage?
I think it's one of the best ways to die.
Lord of Light,
show us the way ...
Guide us off by darkness and lead your servants towards the Light.
We must burn the corpse.
We will follow all shortly.
Unless the Lord of Light is not kind enough to give us a bit 'of fire.
Lord of Light ...
to break down our darkness.
'Cause the night and' dark and full of terrors.
There congeleremo soon ...
and even water.
When you killed the stranger,
almost all the deaths that followed him have fallen.
Because?
Perhaps it was he who had transformed them.
We can point to the Others.
- Maybe then we will succeed.  - No ...
We need to bring back that thing.
There is a direct raven Dragonstone.
Daenerys is our only chance.
No.
There's another one.
Kill him ...
Li has transformed all of him.
You do not understand...
The Lord brought you back to life, and me too.
No one else, just us two.
Do you think he did it to see us freeze to death?
Careful, Beric, you lost your priest.
This is your last life.
It's a long time since the end appearance.
Maybe the Lord brought me here to meet her.
All the Lord that I have ever met are assholes.
I do not see why the Lord of Light should be different.
Mia lady.
Mia lady...
It is an invitation to King's Landing.
- My lady, you are the Lady of Winterfell ... - I am.
And you will represent my interests in this meeting.
They invited you, want you.
I do not set foot in King's Landing with Queen Cersei Lannister.
If you want another prisoner Stark, they can come get me.
Until then, I'll stay in my place.
I have work to do here.
It's not safe.
There will Ser Jaime, you said that he treated you well in the past.
I'm not worried about me!
There is sure to leave you with Littlefinger.
A lot of guards imprigionerebbero decapiterebbero or without you.
And they trust their loyalty.
Do you think he will not be put to talk behind your back.
At least let me leave Podric to control you.
- You become responsible ... - I do not need to be controlled,
or cured, or taking charge.
I'm not a little girl, I am the Lady of Winterfell, and I'm home.
This to me is the safest place.
Mia lady...
I have taken an oath to protect you and your sister, if I ...
The journey to King's Landing is long, Lady Brianne, and the roads are icy.
First-party and more opportunity you will have to arrive on time.
Yes, my lady.
You can not!
The person most important in the world can not fly to the most dangerous place!
- And who else could?  - Nobody.
They were aware of the risks when they left.
You can not achieve the Throne if you're dead.
You can not break the wheel if you're dead.
Then what would you have me do?
Nothing.
Sometimes, nothing is the hardest thing to do.
If you die ...
we will all be lost.
Everything and everyone.
You've already convinced him not to do anything before, and I've listened to you.
I will not do it again.
damn assholes.
Fuck!
Fuck.
Retreat!
Courage!
Help!
Jon!
Go away!
Get out, now!  Go away!
Zio Benjen.
- Can you ride up to the passage?  - Come with me.
There's no time.
Are!
We'll meet again, Clegane.
I hope not, fuck.
Time to go, Your Majesty.
Another moment.
Open the gates!
Not quite what you mean, right?
I have hundreds of men here at Winterfell, all loyal to me.
But they are not in this room.
What are these things?
My faces.
Where did you get these?
A Braavos,
during my training at the Faceless Men.
What does it mean?
A Braavos...
before getting my first face ...
I used to play a game ...
the game of the faces.
It's simple: I ask you a question about yourself
and will you invent lies instead of telling the truth.
If you can fool me,
you won.
If you unmasked,
you lost.
Come on, let's play.
I do not want to play.
How do you feel about the fact that Jon is the king?
Do you think that maybe you're better suited to rule the North?
Those faces ...
what are they?
Is that your question?
Are you sure?
The game did not end well for the last person who asked questions.
Tell me what they are.
We dreamed of being different people, from small.
You wanted to be a queen,
and sit on the Iron Throne beside a beautiful king.
I wanted to be a knight,
and a sword, like our father, and go into battle.
No he has become the person you dreamed.
Well, it's true that girls do not decide to become a person.
Now I can do it ...
thanks to those faces, I can choose.
Can I become someone else,
speak with his voice,
living in his skin.
I might even be you.
I wonder how it feels ...
to have those beautiful dresses ...
to be the Great Lady Winter.
All you need me ...
your face.
I'm sorry.
I am so sorry.
I wish I could go back.
I would never come here.
Io no.
If we had not come, I would not have seen.
You have to see it to understand.
Now I understand.
Dragons are my children,
the only ones I will ever have,
you understand it?
We will destroy the King of the Night and his army ...
and we will do it together.
You have my word.
Thanks, Dany.
Dany?
No one called me that for a long time.
Perhaps the last was my brother.
And I have good memories of him.
Alright then...
I call you Danny.
How about my queen?
I would be happy...
to kneel down, but ...
And all that you have sworn allegiance?
Will they see you for who you are.
I hope I deserve it.
I'll meriti.
You should rest.
:: Omino Spanish that puts the tape and goes home Addicted :: [www.italiansubs.net]
www.tvsubtitles.net