You want Scotch? Pre-war!
I don't drink.
I know you.
You have been talking to the
Tattaglia family... right?
I think you and I can do business.
I need someone strong like you.
I heard you are not happy
with the Corleone family.
Want to join me?
What's in it for me?
$50,000, to start with.
Not bad!
Agreed?
Hey, Paulie, did you fart?
- I'm sorry ab...
- It's alright.
You gotta know.
The hit taken out on your
father was just business.
Look. I have much
respect for your father.
But his thinking's outdated!
And you have to understand.
I am a man of honor.
I under...stand.
Very clearly...
I'm glad.
And you need to be clear wht I'm
working with the Tattaglia family.
All I want is peace.
Violence is costly.
As you well know.
Now let's stop this nonsense...
I want to... um...
What?
How do I say this...
You ok?
Okay, I want you to
understand something
You're Italian just like your father.
Your father's in bad shape.
Surely you can see that when he's
better he will need your help.
This fighting has to end.
You need to help me.
So we can end this...
I kiss your hand, Don Tommasino.
Why are you so far
from the house?
You know I'm responsible to
your father for your life.
The bodyguards are here.
It's still dangerous...
We've heard from Santino
in New York...
Your enemies know you're here.
Did Santino say
when I can go back?
Not yet.
It's out of the question.
Where are you going now?
Take my car.
I want to walk.
Be careful.
Where have all the men gone?
They're all dead from vendettas.
There are the names of the dead.
Mamma mia what a beauty.
I think you got hit
by the thunderbolt.
In Sicily, women are more
dangerous than shotguns.
Did you have a good hunt?
You know all the girls
around here?
We saw some real beauties.
One of them struck our
friend like a thunderbolt.
She would tempt the devil himself.
Tempt the devil...
Ah, I understand... really put together...
Really put together.
...together
Such hair, such mouth!
The girls around here are
beautiful... but virtuous.
This one had a purple dress...
And a purple ribbon in her hair.
A type more Greek than Italian.
Do you know her?
There's no girl like
that in this town.
My God, I understand!
What's wrong?
Let's go.
It's his daughter.
Tell him to come here.
You don't understand... it's his daughter!
Call him.
Fabrizio, you translate for me.
Who is this? He sounds American...
Come to my house Sunday morning.
My name is Vitelli.
What's her name?
...this is my daughter, Apollonia...
and this is Michael Corleone.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
What's the problem with your eye.
No, no. It's nothing. It's fine.
It's safer to teach you English!
I know English...
Greetings, Don Tommasino.
How are things in Palermo?
Michael is teaching me to
drive... watch, I'll show you.
How are things in Palermo?
Young people don't respect
anything any more...
times are changing for the worse.
This place has become
too dangerous for you.
I want you to move to a villa
near Siracusa... right now.
What's wrong?
Bad news from America.
Your brother, Santino,
they killed him.
Come on. Let's go.
Let's go... you promised.
Get the car.
Calo, where is Apollonia?
She's going to surprise you.
She wants to drive.
She'll make a good American wife.
Wait, I'll get the baggage.
Where are you going?
Wait there! I'll drive to you.