Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[arrow whistling]
[faint whinnying]
[steel clanging]
[roaring]
[faint crowd roar]
[men chanting, indistinct]
...salute you.
[roaring faintly]
[birds chirping]
[chickens clucking]
[woman] Be gentle, Hanno.
[goat bleating nearby]
[grunts]
[loud horn blowing]
[men shouting in distance]
[horn continues blowing]
[seagulls calling]
[wood creaking]
[man] We invoke you by your great names
to come to our aid.
Defeat the Romans.
Destroy their ships,
their engines of war,
and their soldiers.
We will prevail.
Ozalsces.
Arishat.
[faint shouting]
[man] Hanno.
You did not make an offering today.
I prefer to sacrifice a Roman.
[chuckles]
[Arishat] Where you are,
I am, too.
[Hanno] And where you are,
I am, too, forever.
My wife.
[man shouts indistinctly]
[excited chattering]
[muffled drums beating]
[mast creaking]
The wind is too strong.
Furl sail and strike water.
Furl sail, strike water!
[man] Furl sail and strike water!
- [men shout in reply]
- [drums thudding]
[grunting with effort]
Strike water!
[horn trumpeting]
[men chanting rhythmically]
[Hanno] They have no lands
but the ones they've stolen.
Wherever they go,
they leave destruction and call it peace.
This is the last free city in Africa Nova.
Today, we go into battle.
Pray that your god is with you.
If he is not, he is no god.
[men chuckling]
We've nothing to fear.
Where death is, we are not.
Where we are,
death is not.
- Stay together and listen for my commands.
- [men mutter assent]
[Hanno] Your eyes up and your head out.
[overlapping shouts]
[indistinct chatter]
[man shouting commands]
Fire!
- [men screaming]
- [man] Ready your weapons!
Again!
We're ablaze on the right!
Keep formation!
Pull!
[man] Archers ready.
Release!
[arrows hissing]
Nock!
Draw!
Loose!
[man] Archers!
[grunts]
[screaming]
Fire!
[all screaming]
- Raise the tower!
- Back astern!
[all chanting]
Keep cranking.
[all grunting]
Drop drawbridge!
The drawbridge is stuck!
[grunting]
[screaming]
- [grunts]
- Sir!
[Hanno] Loose!
Back.
[all yelling]
[exhales]
[battle grunts]
[yells]
[gurgling]
Archers!
There!
Kill her!
Arishat!
[muffled roar]
[faint echoing rumble]
[thunderclap]
[faint, echoing] Arishat.
[faintly] Arishat!
[panting]
[Arishat, whispering] I'll wait for you.
[screaming]
[gasping for breath]
[coughs]
[Roman officer] Check all the bodies!
Leave nothing!
[gasping]
[sobs]
[horn pealing]
[people shouting, crying]
[people exclaiming, wailing]
[loudly] I claim this city...
for the glory of Rome.
Vae victis.
[quietly] Woe to the conquered.
[people wailing in distance]
- [flesh sizzles]
- [man screams in pain]
[Roman soldier] Next!
[pained grunt]
[man] Move it!
[Hanno grunting]
[gulls calling]
- Down the stairs!
- Downstairs!
[men coughing, groaning]
[hull creaking]
[draws shuddering breath]
[waves splashing]
- [softly] Hey.
- [groans]
What damage have they done you, eh?
[chuckles bitterly]
- Lift it up. Easy, easy.
- [groans]
Hold that.
[pained groan]
Arishat?
I am sorry, my son.
I have not long.
This galley
is sailing us to something
I cannot endure.
I am ready... to be taken to another place.
- Stay here a while longer.
- [chuckles]
- [light chuckle]
- [pained grunt]
I remember well when you first
were brought to us.
A lonely boy from the desert. Guileless.
Afraid.
You embraced everything we taught you.
You found Arishat's love.
Your soul was replenished.
[chuckles] When I die,
my ancestors will meet me
in the next world.
Who will meet you?
Hanno,
I am done.
Do not let them change what you are.
[young Hanno panting]
[boys chattering]
[horses whinnying]
- [horses snorting]
- [hoofbeats approaching]
Have you seen this boy?
[panting]
Eama! Eama!
[woman] You must go alone now, Hanno.
Never let them find you.
[woman's breath trembling]
Go. Go.
[bell ringing]
[men murmuring]
[people cheering]
[overlapping, excited chatter]
[crowd roaring]
[crowd chanting]
Acacius! Acacius! Acacius!
Emperor Geta.
Emperor Caracalla.
General Acacius.
I have taken Numidia in your names
that your dominion may eclipse that
of every emperor that came before you.
Crown him with laurels, brother.
[crowd cheering]
[all chanting] Acacius! Acacius! Acacius!
[monkey hooting softly]
[Geta] In honor of your conquest,
there will be games in the Colosseum.
I require no games in my honor.
Serving the Senate and the people of Rome
is honor enough for me.
You are too modest, Acacius.
It does not suit a general
as accomplished as yourself.
The glory is yours, not mine.
I only ask for some respite from war
to spend time with my wife.
Your wife, yes. [sniffs]
Remember the privileges
we have granted her?
[sword scraping]
Where is she now
to ignore such an occasion?
There are victories yet still to come.
Persia.
India.
[chuckles]
Both... must be conquered.
Rome has so many subjects.
She must feed them.
They can eat war. [laughs]
Your triumphs will be celebrated
as a tribute to the greatness
of the Roman people.
- [men shouting]
- [horses whinnying]
[man] Go to hell!
[people jeering]
[piercing animal shrieks]
[men shouting]
[announcer] Macrinus of Thysdrus,
- master of gladiators!
- [horn playing fanfare]
[crowd roars]
[animal screeching nearby]
[animal snarling]
- [screeching continues]
- [loud thumping]
Stay close.
- [snarling, thumping continue]
- [chains rattling]
[door thudding]
[crowd roaring]
[shouting, jeering]
[announcer] Aediles
and the town councilors,
distinguished guests,
citizens of Antium...
[jeering continues]
...behold the fate
of the conquered enemies of Rome:
The barbarian Numidians
and their chieftain,
Jugurtha!
[loud thudding]
- [snarling]
- [teeth snapping]
[man shouting, indistinct]
- [blows]
- [baboon shrieks]
[screeches]
[yells]
- [screeches]
- [Hanno yells]
[growling]
[guttural hooting]
[screeching in agony]
This one is interesting.
[all cheering]
[grunts]
[spits]
[yelling]
[baboon choking]
I'll buy him.
[crowd chanting]
- [horse approaching]
- Halt! Who goes there?
General.
[woman murmuring softly]
My lady.
I thank the gods
that brought you back home safe.
Thank the Army. They protected me.
Mm.
Let me feed you.
[indistinct chatter]
- [men grunting]
- [weapons clashing]
[trainer] Go.
To the wall.
[trainer] The arena is a sacred temple.
For the bravest of you,
the road to glory runs through the arena.
The arena turns slaves into gladiators
and gladiators into free men.
You have worms.
I know this one. He eats monkeys.
[men laughing]
[indistinct chatter]
[trainer] Go. Sit. Eat.
[groans softly]
[man hoots quietly]
[men hooting]
[men mimicking baboons]
[hooting continues, louder]
[chuckles]
You.
[trainer] Hanno, get up.
What is your native language?
I speak them all.
You don't answer
because you can't or because you won't?
Mm, all right.
Violence... is the universal language.
Viggo, put him through his paces.
He can fight an ape.
Let's see if he can fight a man.
[grunts]
[Hanno groans]
[Hanno exhales heavily]
[both grunting]
[groans heavily]
[chuckling]
[explosive grunt]
[Macrinus] Enough!
[panting]
Very good.
Hose him down.
Bring him to me.
[grunts]
Ah!
A strong jaw.
Good arms.
[sniffs]
Better smell.
[chuckles lightly]
You will do well.
It is an art,
choosing gladiators.
Some choose entertainers.
Some choose brute force.
I choose rage.
[Macrinus chuckles]
Crowd loves blood.
And they love those who love blood
as much as they do.
And you, my friend, rage
pours out of you like...
like milk...
from a whore's tit.
You will be quite the fighter.
Not for you.
You're right, you do not fight for me.
I put you in the ring,
you fight or you die.
The choice is yours.
But whose head could I give you
that would satisfy this fury?
The entire Roman Army's.
[hearty laugh]
Too much.
Mm.
The general will do.
General?
- General Acacius?
- Mm.
Use your rage in my service,
and you will have his head
ready for your sword.
Serve me and I will serve you. Deny me...
and you will die.
[thunder rumbles in distance]
There are times I wished
you'd abandoned me
rather than fight their wars.
I've made my choice.
I can live with it.
But my patience with those two
is at an end.
Leta?
You may go to your quarters now.
We need nothing more.
To hear wives and mothers
mourning their dead
on that beach at Numidia...
Lucilla.
No more.
I will not waste
another generation
of young men for their vanity.
If I fight another campaign,
it must be to depose them.
When will your troops arrive?
They land at Ostia in ten days.
How many of them
will be loyal to you alone?
All of them.
The emperors do not have
the support of the people.
The people are weary
of the madness, the tyranny.
[sighs]
What is the dream of Rome
if her people are not free?
[chuckles softly]
[whimpers]
[excited chatter]
[laughing]
[man] Enjoy yourself, everyone,
to excess!
Thank you. Thank you.
[castrato singing to lively music]
Oh!
[laughs] Please, drink.
Ah! Excuse me. Macrinus!
I knew the provinces
were not enough for you.
- I'm just here for the games.
- Ah, well,
you won't be disappointed.
Rome has all the games
that men like you like to play.
Men like me, Thraex? Men like us.
I know nothing happens
in Rome unless you've tasted it first.
[both laughing]
What is my purpose here?
You'll find out soon enough.
What's this we hear
about you being interested
in standing for election
to the Senate, Macrinus?
Me? No, I'm, uh...
I don't even know how to use an abacus.
But I do understand that
it's customary for your guests
to make wagers at these affairs?
How large a sum did you have in mind?
A thousand gold denarii?
Two.
Two?
- Denarii.
- [chuckles]
[sighs deeply]
[knife scraping]
Stand back! Stand back!
My emperors.
Lords, ladies and gentlemen, and senators.
For your entertainment,
the art of combat!
[crowd murmurs, clapping]
[Thraex] May I present
the barbarian versus,
from my own stable, the mighty Vichek!
[applause, cheers]
- This is your gladiator?
- It is.
[Thraex] Three rounds, hand to hand.
Swords!
We want swords. A fight to the death.
No quarter to be offered... or given.
- Fight now!
- [swords scraping]
Brother,
let's not kill each other
for their amusement.
[Vichek yells, grunts]
[excited murmuring]
[both yell, grunt]
[cackling]
[both yelling]
[Vichek panting]
[yells]
[sword clattering]
[scattered cheers, applause]
[Hanno groans]
[scattered cheers]
[applause]
[Geta] Remarkable!
[giggling]
Remarkable!
- Thraex, he looked expensive.
- [dry chuckle]
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Remarkable.
From where do you hail?
Speak.
- I said speak.
- He is from the colonies, Your Majesty.
His native tongue is all he understands.
"The gates of hell are open night and day.
Smooth is the descent,
and easy is the way.
[laughing] But...
to come back from hell
and view the cheerful skies,
in this the task and mighty labor lies."
[panting]
Virgil, Your Majesty.
[Caracalla] Poetry!
[laughter]
- Very clever, Macrinus.
- Thank you.
I've grown so bored, but you surprise me.
To amuse you is my only wish.
We are amused, we are amused.
We are amused.
And we all look forward
to seeing your poet
perform in the arena.
As do I, Your Majesties.
Thank you.
Viggo?
[Viggo] Come with me.
You fought well today,
but you were lucky, too.
The lines you recited.
You didn't learn that
in Africa, I know that.
- A good verse travels far.
- Mm.
Who taught you poetry?
A captured Roman officer.
I was posted guard over him
and he used to tell us tales
to pass the time.
And what became of this prisoner?
Oh, we ate him.
As barbarians do.
[chuckling] As barbarians do.
And where were you born?
Why does my past matter if it is my future
to die for you in the arena?
Tell me what use have I for Roman money.
A gladiator
- can buy his own freedom.
- Mmm.
- His liberty.
- [chuckles]
The Roman dream.
No, the slave dreams not of freedom
but of a slave to call his own.
Cicero.
Is that what you were raised on, Macrinus?
What did you have to do for Roman money?
You promised me a head.
Earn your keep
and you can have anyone's head.
[stone scraping]
[door unlatches, opens]
[thunder rumbling]
[Lucilla] Father,
protect us and guide us.
Senators.
My lady.
My lady, I wish we were
meeting in better times.
Better times will come.
And why are we here?
[Acacius] To take back the city.
And restore Rome to where she should be.
An exciting venture.
- When?
- On the final day of the games.
My army waits for my command at Ostia.
Five thousand soldiers loyal to me...
will enter Rome and then the Colosseum,
where they will arrest the emperors
for their crimes against the Senate
and their people.
Uh, this plan is ambitious and risky.
Rome will be yours to administer and to--
Marcus Aurelius talked
of restoring power to the Senate,
but that was a generation ago.
Much has changed.
The people have not seen hope
for many years.
But with time... and guidance...
[sighs sharply] Lucilla,
you are the daughter of Marcus Aurelius.
He had my loyalty.
And so do you.
Senator Thraex?
Politics follows power, my lady.
Take back what is rightfully yours...
and the Senate will support you.
Thank you.
Food! Food!
When I was told of this place,
they never mentioned the stink.
That would be Hanno.
[laughter]
Well, you'll have to
put up with me as I am.
[laughing]
And what's that up there? A wolf?
The twins there, they were outcasts.
Left in the hills to die.
That wolf found them
and she suckled them on her milk.
Raised by an animal. It's in their blood.
How do you know this place?
I know the chaos they brought.
This city infects everything it touches.
I never dreamt it would be so big.
Don't fall for it.
This city is diseased.
[peasants] Food! Food!
[children chattering]
[elephant trumpeting]
[indistinct chatter, laughter]
[man] You! Barbarian scum!
- [grunts]
- [people yelling]
[woman] Help me. Please, help me!
[all pleading]
[horses whinnying]
[crows squawking]
- Ah!
- Thraex.
About our wager.
Ah. The barbarian.
Yes, I haven't forgotten,
I always repay my debts.
I was merely going to suggest
that perhaps your luck might change.
Shall we say double or quits?
- Ah.
[both laughing]
[people shouting, indistinct]
[man] Get back!
Fresh meat.
Line up! Line up!
[faint crowd cheering]
[cheering continues, louder]
Play! Play!
[playing simple fanfare]
Emperor Caracalla.
Emperor Geta.
Citizens of Rome!
[crowd cheering]
These sacred games
are held to honor the victory of Rome
over the barbarians of Numidia.
[crowd booing]
Go! Go!
[announcer] And to honor
Rome's legionary commander,
General Justus Acacius!
- [crowd cheering]
- [man] Long live Acacius!
[announcer] And with him
Lucilla, the daughter
of Emperor Marcus Aurelius.
[crowd cheering]
- [woman, faintly] Lucilla!
- [man] Mother of Rome!
Acacius.
General.
[crowd roars]
[chanting] Acacius! Acacius! Acacius!
Acacius! Acacius! Acacius!
Speak to them.
[man faintly] Speak to us!
[cheering ebbs]
I am not an orator
or a politician.
I am a soldier.
I have seen bravery
in men and women during war.
And even once in this arena.
So if you ask anything of the gods...
ask for that same bravery.
Because Rome needs it now.
[applause, cheers swelling]
[crowd chanting]
Acacius! Acacius! Acacius!
[chanting continues]
[announcer] From the South Gate,
fighters from the stable
of Macrinus of Thysdrus!
From the stables
of Emperors Caracalla and Geta themselves,
the undefeated champion:
Glyceo the Destroyer!
[crowd roars]
Hold.
[growling]
[grunting]
[roaring cheers]
[rhino roaring]
[Hanno] Hold.
Hail Caesars!
[crowd chanting] Glyceo! Glyceo! Glyceo!
[chanting continues]
[rhino roars]
Hold together and when it charges,
break for the wall.
[man] Why should I?
[Hanno] Hold!
Hold!
Break!
Cowards!
[yells]
[groaning]
- [yells]
- [axe clattering]
[huffing]
To the wall!
[grunts heavily]
[rhino groaning loudly]
[grunts]
- Come on!
- [roars]
[grunts]
[screaming]
[cheering]
[giggling]
[guttural roaring]
[rhino bellowing]
[excited cheering]
[rhino groaning]
[gasps]
[both grunting]
[roaring]
Brother, it's that poet, is it not?
I can't remember.
That night was a blur.
"The gates of hell are open night and day.
Smooth the desc--" I forget.
"Smooth the descent..."
"Smooth is the descent,
easy is the way."
Shield!
[yelling]
[crowd chanting] Mercy! Mercy! Mercy!
Blood.
Lucilla,
shall we show mercy?
Mercy.
[chanting continues]
No mercy!
Your life has been spared by the gods--
I would sooner face your blade
than accept Roman mercy!
[both grunting]
[attacking yell]
[grunts]
[crowd roaring]
[chanting] Kill! Kill! Kill!
Kill! Kill! Kill!
[yelling]
[crowd chanting] Hanno! Hanno! Hanno!
[cheering intensifies]
[rhino groaning]
The road to freedom
doesn't run through the arena.
It leads to this.
Go to your cells.
[all cheering, clapping]
Hanno! Hanno! Hanno!
[panting]
[dog whimpers]
Come on, let's go.
"Gates of hell are open night and day.
[voice wavering] Smooth is the descent...
[crying]...easy is the way."
[boy] There, there, there, there.
And I've got you.
I'm Maximus, the savior of Rome!
Scatto and Argento.
[people cheer, echoing]
[gasping softly]
Lucius is safe?
[Lucilla] Lucius!
[horse whinnies]
[Lucilla] Lucius,
you're the sole heir to the throne now.
There are men who want to kill you
so they can take power.
I promise I'll bring you back
as soon as it's safe.
Mother, why can't you come with me?
[crying] I... I have to stay here
for your sake.
[sniffles] And for the sake of Rome.
Remember who you are.
And that I love you.
I love you.
[man] Come.
Give me your leg.
Go. Go!
[horse whinnies]
[doctor] So...
[Hanno grunts]
What's your name?
[exhales]
I'm Ravi. I'm a doctor.
Because... more men die of infected wounds
than out there, in the arena.
This needs to be cleaned,
it needs to be stitched and...
[exclaims softly]...it is going to hurt.
Mm.
This is Devil's Breath and opium.
It's for the pain.
You should breathe in.
[inhales sharply, grunts]
[deep inhale]
[Ravi] I've been here so long now,
I don't even notice anymore.
I've done more amputations
than I can count.
- Where'd you learn your trade?
- Why do you ask?
You've got a heavy hand.
I used to be a gladiator myself.
Ah.
- And would you have bested me?
- [Ravi chuckles]
In your prime, of course.
In your current state,
I could best you now.
[laughs]
Luckily for you, I have put down my sword.
- So now I spend my days...
- [groaning]
...saving lives instead of taking them.
[inhales, grunts]
And why such a change so late in life?
What we do in life
echoes in eternity.
[panting softly]
I feel like I know those words.
[Ravi chuckles] I can't take credit.
It's written on one of the tombs.
Over the bones of a gladiator.
- [sharp grunt of pain]
- [Macrinus] My champion!
I smell Devil's Breath!
[laughing]
My... champion.
Did you hear that crowd?
- Did you hear that crowd?
- Mm-hm.
You have something.
I knew it from the start.
- Did you now?
- Yes. The Greeks call it...
thymos.
Smoke.
Rage.
That rage is your gift.
Like the great Achilles.
Never let it go.
It will carry you to greatness,
my champion.
[horses whinny, snort]
Thank you
for inviting me.
This is truly an honor.
I hear you are the talk of the court.
[kissing hand]
Yes.
We've met before.
- Have we?
- Long ago.
Where?
I was in the service of your father's army
on his African campaign.
You served with my father?
[groaning]
Mm.
I had the privilege
of reading his "Meditations."
Mm.
"The best revenge
is to be unlike him
who performed the injury."
I hear you've been arming half the legions
in the entire empire,
and here, now, in Rome...
you're gaining influence
by sponsoring gladiators.
I do it for the love of the sport.
And where did you find these gladiators?
They're usually prisoners of war.
Or vagrants. Why do you ask?
A man can choose to fight...
and stay alive.
It's the same in life as it is
in the arena, is it not?
Who is this?
That is my father as a youth.
[Macrinus] She had a child?
Mm. [swallows]
It's common knowledge.
When Commodus was killed,
- the boy disappeared.
- Mm.
- But who would care?
- Lucilla would care.
- More wine!
He was of the royal bloodline, after all.
And his father?
[senator] Ostensibly, Lucius Verus.
See, it was an arranged marriage.
She was 14.
- Mm.
- Females were not his taste.
- Nor mine, some days.
- Nor yours!
[both laugh]
No, no, no.
By rumor, you see, she took lovers.
And by rumor,
the real father... was Commodus.
- Brotherly love, you see?
- Yeah.
If he died,
- there has to be remains.
- Mm.
And if he lived,
that would make him about...
Um, well, let's work it out.
- He was about 12 when he died?
- Yes.
So that would make him...
[heavy door rumbling]
[squeaking]
[hoofbeats thudding]
My lady.
Gracchus.
- Please come.
- Thank you.
Gladiator...
do you know me?
Do you have a family?
A wife. Arishat.
Arishat.
She was killed
under your husband's command.
[sighing] Rome drowns in its own blood.
And yet you enjoy
the pleasures of the Colosseum.
There is much you do not understand.
Lucius.
I do not know who you think I am.
[Lucilla's breath trembles]
My name is Hanno,
and I have no mother,
or none that I can remember.
[sniffles]
[crying] I'm so sorry.
If your son were here,
I feel sure he would tell you
not to grieve him.
For he would not be the boy
that you sent away.
That boy is dead.
You may think I have little worth.
You may think I betrayed you.
But I need you to know...
if you will not have your mother's love,
then take your father's strength.
You need it.
His name was Maximus Decimus Meridius.
And I see him in you.
Get out.
[Gracchus] My lady, we must go at once!
[Lucilla sobs]
Lucius, you were loved
by myself and by your father.
[sniffles]
Your name was on his lips--
Get out!
[panting]
[door shuts]
[Lucilla exhales]
Lucius is alive.
Are you certain?
Yes.
I know my son.
I spoke to him tonight.
He may be lost to me for what I did,
but he lives.
The third day of the games is tomorrow.
Most fighters won't survive.
Acacius,
you must help him.
- Help him?
- [crying] Yes.
I failed him then.
I know I did.
I cannot fail him now.
The army is in Ostia.
If we wait a few days...
He could be dead by then.
Acacius,
I would willingly give my life for Rome,
but I will not give my son's.
[Viggo] And one.
And two.
- And one.
- [all groaning with effort]
Together. Timing, timing, timing!
And one. And two.
And one.
Pause, pause!
We won't get far like this.
[all laughing]
Just him. You go.
Go!
Let's see how far you can go
on your own without your team.
Ready?
One!
And two!
Timing, timing!
Come on, more!
[grunts]
[Viggo] More!
[Lucius groans loudly]
[heavy grunt]
Leave him.
[indistinct chatter]
[huffs, grunts]
[cork pops]
[stammering] It's just vinegar, my friend.
[pained groan]
There will be no more opium for you.
There is plenty of pain waiting
for you in the next life.
I don't know why
you are so greedy for it in this one.
Are you a free man, Ravi?
[dry chuckle] "Free."
I am. Mm.
I laid down my sword
and I swore never to pick it up again.
And yet you choose this hell?
Mm-hm.
What was your home before?
Varanasi.
And why don't you go back?
I wish I could.
- [breath hissing]
- But... Eh-eh-eh.
- I met a woman. [laughs]
- Ah.
- It's always a woman.
- Always.
She is from Londinium.
Britannia. You know.
So now...
our sons, they speak only Latin.
My daughter's eyes,
they are as blue as yours.
[chuckles lightly]
We are Romans now.
I grew up hearing stories
at my grandfather's knee.
He used to talk
of the dream that was Rome.
It was so fragile,
you could only whisper it...
or it would vanish.
[whispering] So,
what was this dream?
A Rome where all could live
under fair law and be protected.
A Rome of the Senate.
A Rome of hope.
Your grandfather,
he sounds like a dangerous man.
Hm.
The odds are against you.
[light chuckle]
The odds are always against me.
Don't worry, old man.
- Eh?
- [both laughing]
[muttering]
- You should get some rest. Hm?
- Mm.
Your men will need you
to lead them tomorrow.
[gates rumbling open]
- [crowd cheering]
- [drums thudding]
This is about survival.
Survive!
[announcer] In the name of Poseidon,
we celebrate the glory of naval war.
[Lucius] They have archers.
Be ready. Listen for my commands.
Stay together and pull as one, yes?
[all] Yes!
- Yes?
- Yes!
[hull creaking]
[announcer] Today we relive
the Battle of Salamis!
[crowd cheering]
The Trojans versus the Persians!
- Oars out!
- [all] Oars!
And... pull!
[all grunting explosively]
- Archers!
- [men yelling]
Archers!
Pull!
- [all grunting]
- [screams]
Pull!
[grunts, screams]
[muffled screaming]
[all yelling]
Pull! To my time!
And... now!
Left side! Ready, and
ship oars now!
Oars in! Oars in!
Get down!
[screams]
[straining]
[crowd cheering]
And pull! And pull!
[men grunting rhythmically]
[man] Don't stop!
[grunting]
Pull!
[men shout in unison]
And right!
Ready to ram!
[Romans shouting, indistinct]
And brace! Brace!
[all yelling]
[all shouting]
[cheering]
[all grunting]
[gasping]
[soldier] Everyone regroup!
[screaming]
[fighting grunts]
[grunts]
[crowd exclaiming]
Praetorians!
[crowd chanting] Hanno! Hanno! Hanno!
Move, move.
[chanting continues]
[announcer] In the name of the emperors...
the victor is Hanno!
[all chanting in support]
Who did this?
Who did this?!
- It was me!
- I did it!
- [men] I did it! I did it! I did it!
- It was me!
Geta will want retribution for all of you.
Did you learn to shoot in the same place
you learned to recite poetry?
Be glad it wasn't me,
or that arrow would have found you.
[men laughing]
[indistinct chatter]
[faint music playing]
Be seated.
I have news for you.
He's here, sir.
[door opens]
[Macrinus] Oh, still here.
[Thraex laughs nervously]
Macrinus.
- [Macrinus chuckles]
- Welcome.
Yes, I'm listening.
You know this is my house now.
Your debt to me is over 10,000 denarii.
You know that.
[chuckles, stammers]
I have other things. Uh...
Cattle. Art!
Truth, then.
What do you... want?
Truth. That's what I want.
Nothing happens in Rome
without your knowledge.
You have the senators' trust.
You have Lucilla's trust.
More importantly, you have my trust.
You wish my... loyalty?
I own...
your house.
I want your loyalty.
I...
Tell me. I have heard...
of a plot...
- to dethrone the emperors.
- Yes.
But the plan has been delayed, uh...
A gladiator is to be rescued
from the arena.
- Tonight.
- Mm.
- I don't know why.
- I know why. I know who.
Pack.
Quickly.
- [pounding on gate]
- [man] Open up!
[rats squeaking]
[mastiffs growling]
[man] Open for the emperors' guard!
[pounding on door]
[heavy knocking]
My Lady, come with us.
[all grunting with impact]
Thanks to the civic virtue
of men like Thraex and Macrinus,
your insurrection
has been revealed.
The honor,
the dignitas that Rome
has bestowed upon you...
all this you have forfeited
by your treachery.
Please, Emperor Geta.
Torture me if you want,
but do not lecture me.
Your name will be forgotten!
Lost... to history.
You are damned, General.
[laughing]
- [Geta] You laugh.
- You damn me?
I don't care.
Everything is forgotten in time.
Empires fall. So do emperors.
[Caracalla] Why wait?
- I will gut him right now!
- No, no, no!
Let them be. Come! Come!
His death must be public.
Public? [grunts]
Hang his entrails from the city gates!
And crucify her!
Crucify her!
Take them away!
- [Caracalla yells]
- [Geta] Shh! Shh! Shh!
Thank you, Macrinus.
Come on.
In these last days,
I have come to think of you
not as a subject
but as a true friend.
Thank you.
Thank you so much. But as a friend,
I must counsel caution.
Acacius is a hero of Rome.
Crucifixion is for thieves.
Christians.
- It's too common.
- He is a traitor. He must die.
I agree.
Let the gods decide
his fate in the Colosseum.
Let the gods decide.
You know, last night I woke,
dreaming of a dark river.
This time, for the first time,
I was crossing it.
[Ravi] Hm.
Well, you know, where I come from,
crossing a river,
it represents forgiveness.
Represents... salvation.
Where I come from,
it means you're already dead.
[chuckles]
But as I saw it, I was not afraid.
For...
For someone was waiting
for me on the other side.
There. [sniffs]
Who is this man?
Scratched out?
Maximus.
I saw him fight once.
- He was magnificent.
- Mm.
Yeah. My time in the arena,
it was after his,
but many still talked of him
in whispers, you know?
Spoke of him.
What he did.
I met him once.
He was kind.
He bowed to no one.
Come with me.
- Hmm?
- Come. With me.
When a rebel gladiator dies,
we bury them here.
"What we do in life echoes in eternity."
This is Argento.
This is Scatto.
[cheering, applause]
[drums thudding]
[metal clanking]
[horns playing fanfare]
Cheers.
And stop.
For his treason against the lives
of the emperors and the Roman state,
General Justus Acacius,
an enemy of the people!
[all chanting] Acacius! Acacius! Acacius!
- [man] We love you, Acacius!
- You are a hero!
Acacius! Acacius! Acacius!
[chanting continues]
[crowd roaring]
[crowd jeering loudly]
- [Acacius] Vae victis.
- [soldiers] General.
[all shouting, grunting]
[pained yell]
[grunts]
[crowd cheering]
[panting heavily]
[scattered shouts] Acacius!
[crowd chanting]
Acacius! Acacius! Acacius!
[all continue chanting]
[announcer]
From the vanquished city of Numidia,
the victor of two conquests
in the Colosseum...
Go now. Vae victis.
[crowd chanting] Hanno! Hanno! Hanno!
- Hanno!
- [crowd cheering]
Oh, Lord, any honor I have,
- I will give it to you!
- It's too late.
[announcer] The Roman traitor or
the barbarian hero.
Let the gods decide.
Lucius... wait.
Wait! Wait!
[both grunting heavily]
[overlapping cheers and jeers]
I am a vessel.
Fill me with vengeance
and vanquish the betrayer.
[attacking grunts]
- We love you, Acacius!
- Move it!
Pick it up!
[woman] Bravo, Hanno!
[man] We love you, Acacius!
- [man 2] What are you waiting for?
- [man 3] You will die!
[cheering and booing]
[crowd whooping]
[both grunting heavily]
[crowd groaning]
[pained grunting]
[panting]
[Acacius] I know who you are.
Lucius Verus Aurelius.
[crowd groaning]
[crowd exclaiming]
Acacius has raised his hand!
He has surrendered.
[all muttering]
Let the gods decide.
[monkey screeching]
The gods have rendered their judgment.
Do what you must.
But on my death, you have to know...
I love your mother, Lucilla.
And your father...
Maximus.
I would have died for him.
Kill him!
[man] Let him live! Please!
[crowd chanting] Live! Live! Live! Live!
Kill him!
- [grunts]
- [Geta] Kill him!
Archers!
- No!
- [Geta] Kill him!
[crowd chanting] Acacius! Acacius!
[Caracalla] Kill him!
Kill him!
Kill him! Kill him!
[crowd continues chanting]
[sobbing] Acacius!
[arrow whistling]
[crowd exclaiming]
[grunting]
[Lucilla] No!
No!
Acacius!
Damn you!
[breath heaving]
Death will be too good for you!
Is this how Rome treats its heroes?
Tell me!
If his life has no value,
what are yours worth?
The gods have spoken!
[crowd booing loudly]
[shouting, jeering]
[crowd chanting]
Hanno! Hanno! Hanno! Hanno!
[crowd booing]
For our own safety,
we should return to the palace.
[crowd booing loudly]
[crowd] Hanno! Hanno! Hanno!
[all jeering]
[soldier] Stay back! Stay back!
[booing and jeers, echoing]
[crowd noise fades]
[thunder rolling]
[Lucius, faintly] Arishat!
[door opens]
We had a bargain.
I gave him to you. You let him live.
And you got what you wanted.
I always get what I want.
Why did you let him live?
You bought a gladiator, not a slave.
My will is my own.
Ah...
How blue is your blood?
Perhaps the heart of a Roman
beats in that chest. [chuckles]
The greatest temple Rome ever built.
The Colosseum.
Because this is what they believe in.
Power.
They gather here to watch
the strong strike down the weak.
- There has to be something else.
- There is nothing else.
- There has to be another Rome.
- There is no other Rome.
- The "dream"?
- Mm.
The dream of Rome?
It's an old man's fantasy.
Who are you?
What was your name
before you traded it for a Roman one?
You'll never know.
I have a destiny.
The gods delivered you to me.
You will be my instrument.
I will never be your instrument,
in this life or the next.
- [door opening]
- That will not be my destiny.
But I will see your end.
[people shouting, yelling in distance]
[monkey chittering]
What else could I do?
He and his bitch were plotting to kill us.
Don't you hear them?
They're calling for our heads!
The Praetorians will put down this crowd.
- Like they have every other.
- You brought this on us.
- Filthy ape!
- [monkey squeaking in fear]
[Macrinus] Perhaps you should, uh,
take Dondus elsewhere to comfort him?
Forgive my brother's outburst.
The disease that infects his loins
has spread to his brain.
- Every day he gets worse.
- I will reason with him.
[all yelling, shouting]
[Dondus hooting]
[singsong] I see you.
I see you.
Caracalla, Caracalla!
Come on, stand up.
Get up, get up. Not you.
All right, there you go.
Now, listen to me.
What's the matter?
[panting] Nothing's ever mine.
Everything is ours, always.
Even in the womb... [stammering]...he tried...
to cut my umbilicus
so that I couldn't have any more air.
- You remember that, do you?
- Certainly.
- Come, sit.
- One cannot forget.
My conscience compels me.
What?
Sit.
Your brother
means to blame you
in front of the entire Senate...
But I did not do it!
...for what's happening in the streets.
- The chaos!
- He's lying!
No testimony can be more damning
than one brother against another.
That's a lie! He always lies!
He can be very persuasive.
So? What will they do to me?
Oh, I don't dare imagine.
But imagine this:
What will they do to Dondus?
What will they do
to Dondus?
[Dondus chittering softly]
It's your decision.
[people shouting angrily]
[angry shouts continue]
Brother.
Put down the blade.
You lie.
- Give it to me.
- You always lie!
- Give it--
- [grunts]
[chuckles]
[Geta exclaiming]
Look at me. Look at me. Look at me.
- Lie!
- Listen to me. Break the spell.
- Break the spell!
I've always protected you.
Because I love you.
Come back. Help me.
[blade plunges]
[faint, indistinct chatter]
[keys jingling]
Lucius.
[hinges creaking]
Never could have imagined
the fates would lead us here.
[Lucius chuckles dryly]
And yet here we are.
Everything has brought us full circle.
You sent me away and yet fate
brought me back
to the very ground where he died.
[Lucilla] This ring...
belonged to my father.
He gave it to your father, Maximus,
as a token of trust.
I gave it to Acacius for his valor.
This ring belonged to my wife.
I shall wear it next to yours.
I am truly sorry for Acacius.
I could not see the man.
[sniffles]
He was a soldier of Rome.
There was a plan.
He was readying troops at Ostia
under the command of Darius Sextus.
Troops he was to lead
against the emperors.
Acacius. Maximus. Marcus Aurelius.
They lived and died for Rome.
We all do.
Is it true they intend to kill you?
[chuckles lightly]
One man or another
has had a sword against my neck
since the day my father died.
But now that I've found you,
it doesn't matter.
I am not afraid.
I've become well versed
in losing the things that I love.
But now that I've found you,
I have no desire to lose you again.
[exhales shakily]
- You stand like him.
- Mm.
Alert.
Proud.
I do not have his strength.
I wish that were true.
I wish I were telling you
to flee this place.
[keys jingling]
[door unlocks]
Go now.
[Lucilla sighs]
Strength and honor.
[thunder rumbling faintly]
[Caracalla] As Emperor,
I have convened
the Senate to appoint my First Consul
and bestow upon him the power
to administer the military
and civic functions of the Empire.
I name...
Citizen Dondus!
[Senate murmuring]
[Dondus chittering]
[Caracalla] Hail Dondus!
Hail Dondus!
- [clearing throat] Hail Dondus.
- Hail Dondus!
[all] Hail Dondus!
As Second Consul...
I name...
Citizen...
Macrinus!
Hail Macrinus!
[all] Hail Macrinus!
There will be
a triumphal parade to celebrate.
There will be games
and mass executions.
[chittering]
Long live the Empire!
- [Macrinus] Long live the Empire!
- [all] Long live the Empire!
[applause subsides]
Sit down.
I happen to have...
with good fortune and not a little skill...
the remaining emperor's ear.
[all gasping, murmuring]
I can speak logic to it...
and tame the madness in the street. But...
to restore order...
I must have power...
and command
over the Praetorian Army.
Ballot...
or hand?
- Aye!
- [all] Aye!
Your humble servant.
Put your hands down.
You can sit down.
[Macrinus] Rome must fall.
I need only give it a push.
[Lucilla] And after Rome falls...
[dry chuckle]...what then?
You are your father's child.
His dream of Rome was never a dream.
It was a fiction.
"The best revenge is
to become unlike the one
who did the injury."
I have made myself unlike your father.
He spoke of dreams, I speak of truth.
And the only truth in my Rome
is the law of the strongest.
I was owned
by an emperor.
Now I control an empire.
Where else but in Rome can a man do that?
Do you recognize your father's mark on me?
If there is anything
you need...
in these last hours,
we will provide.
Your death will clear my path
to the throne.
Tomorrow there will be games.
And at them...
I will prevail.
[door clangs shut]
[keys jingling]
Ravi!
Can you get me a message
to Ostia by morning?
What is in Ostia?
There is an army.
I'm asking you
to risk yourself, my friend,
in the service of something greater.
Ride to Ostia.
Take this ring to General Darius Sextus.
Are you listening?
Darius Sextus.
He will know it as Acacius's ring.
[clears throat] And, uh,
who shall I say has
sent me with this ring?
I am Lucius Verus Aurelius.
The Prince of Rome.
Tell him I am summoning the army
to the defense of a new Republic.
[inhales]
- Should I trust you?
- Yes.
- Should I?
Ravi! I need your keys.
Thank you.
Stop! Come back!
[panting]
[inhales sharply]
Who gave you this?
Lucius Verus Aurelius.
The Prince of Rome.
[horses snort, whinnying]
[crowd cheering in distance]
[whispering] Must we kill Lucilla?
[quietly] Until she dies,
you will never know peace.
Ever.
[horns playing fanfare]
The people love her.
Her death will incite the mob.
If she dies and the streets
rise up in anger,
I shall deliver them Caracalla's head
and the people shall acclaim me.
That, my friend, is politics.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
Today will be your last fight, champion.
And our master has bestowed on you...
the wooden sword of freedom.
But you have to earn it first.
Today, you're gonna defend your mother.
- [soldier shouting]
- [grunting]
[all yelling]
[grunting explosively]
Wood or steel, a point is still a point!
[arrows whistling]
[Lucius] Wait for me.
In honor
of the acclamation of Emperor Caracalla,
First Consul Dondus
and Second Consul Macrinus,
and as punishment for her conspiracy
against the empire,
for her calumnies against
the emperor's imperial bloodline
and for fomenting military mutiny
along with her husband,
the queen will face divine justice
at the hands of the Praetorian Guard.
[crowd cheering faintly]
I am not a general.
But we are all soldiers.
And up until now,
we have fought for nothing more
than another day's survival.
What will you have us do?
Well, you can return to your cells
if you do not wish to fight this battle.
- [all laughing]
- Or...
you can join me.
And fight for a freedom
far beyond these walls.
[all] Aye!
There once was a time when
honor meant something in Rome.
In this Rome
I no longer believe that exists.
We must find it!
[all murmuring in agreement]
[Lucius] And know this:
Where death is, we are not.
Where we are,
death is not!
By my sword.
Strength and honor.
[all] Strength and honor!
Strength and honor!
[indistinct shouting]
[growling]
[snarling]
Let it not be said
that the emperor is not merciful.
The queen will be granted
a single gladiator
to defend her
against the Praetorian Guard.
[crowd jeering]
The champion, Hanno!
[crowd roars]
[people chanting] Hanno! Hanno! Hanno!
[all booing]
[all shouting]
[grunting]
Yes!
Summon the cavalry. Put this down at once.
This is war! Real war!
The army of Acacius is advancing
just outside of Rome, sir.
We can still outflank them.
They have only 5,000 troops, no more.
How many are we?
Six thousand. Perhaps more.
Ride to the gate and hold them.
[aggressive grunting]
[cheering]
[screams]
[yelps, whimpering]
[all shouting angrily]
[screams]
- [arrow whistles]
- [grunts]
Filthy scum!
[Lucilla] Lucius!
Give me the bow.
[bow creaking]
[both gasp]
Go, my son. Lucius--
Shh-sh-sh-sh...
Horse!
[people shouting, clamoring]
[yelling furiously]
[indistinct shouts]
[feet marching]
[man shouting cadence]
Will nothing kill this barbarian?
My name is Lucius Verus Aurelius!
[Macrinus] A man does not become
emperor by bloodline alone.
It must be taken by force
and kept by force.
Are you such a man as this?
[Lucius] I don't fight for power.
I fight to free Rome from men like you
and to return it to them.
The gods themselves want Rome reborn.
They sent me... to fulfill that task.
And what if your gods
sent me here to kill you?
Huh?
It's time to end this, Macrinus!
[aggressive yell]
[horses bellowing]
[both grunting]
[swords clashing]
[both yelling]
- Hah!
- [screams]
[grunts]
[blade clanging against breastplate]
[metallic clangs echoing]
[Lucilla] Strength and honor,
my son.
[grunts]
[yelling]
[groans in pain]
[panting]
[pained groan]
You look to me to speak.
I know not what to say other than
we have all known too much death.
Let no more blood be spilt
in the name of tyranny.
My grandfather, Marcus Aurelius,
talked of a dream that would be Rome.
A dream that my father,
Maximus Decimus Meridius,
died for.
An ideal.
A city for the many
and a refuge for those in need.
A home worth fighting for.
A home that Maximus
spent his life defending.
That dream is lost.
But dare we...
rebuild that dream together?
What say you?
Aye!
[all] Aye! Aye! Aye! Aye!
[all chanting]
Mother.
Speak to me, Father.
English (US) - SDH