(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(BELL TOLLING)
Mod fx square, dx.
So, please finish
Percival for next time.
I know many of you
had this as undergraduates,
but it won't hurt to brush up.
Thank you, Steven.
(STUDENTS LAUGH)
I also put an
advanced Fourier system
on the main
hallway chalkboard.
I'm hoping that one of you
might prove it by the end
of the semester.
Now, the person to do so will
not only be in my good graces
but also go on
to fame and fortune
by having their
accomplishment recorded
and their name printed
in the auspicious MIT Tech.
Former winners
include Nobel laureates,
Fields Medal winners,
renowned astrophysicists
and lowly MIT professors.
(STUDENTS LAUGHING)
Well, that's all.
If you have any questions,
I'm sure that Tom
has the answers.
(APPLAUSE)
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
Hi, Will.
Krystyn,
how are you doing?
I'm all right,
how are you?
Good.
I didn't get on
Cathy last night.
No? Why not?
No.
I don't know.
Cathy!
CATHY: What?
Why didn't you give me
none of that nasty
little hoochie woochie
you usually throw at me?
Oh, fuck you.
And your Irish curse,
Chuckie.
Like I'd waste my energy
spreadin' my legs for that
Tootsie Roll dick?
Go home and give
it a tug yourself.
MORGAN: Tootsie Roll!
Toots!
(CHUCKLING)
She's missin' a tooth,
Will.
She's got skin problems.
I don't...
Plus, it's like 5-2
Morgan ends up marryin' her,
you know what I mean?
There's only so many times
you can bang your friend's
future wife.
It's wrong.
Where you goin'?
I'm gonna take off.
Fuck you, you're takin' off.
It's, like, what, 10:00 p.m.?
I'm tired.
Irish curse?
She don't know.
There ain't
no Irish curse.
(BUFFER HUMMING)
(BUFFER CLICKS)
(CHALK CLICKING CHALKBOARD)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Out!
Stop pressuring
me back.
Stop crowding the plate!
Which one will it be?
You're gonna get charged,
you know that?
You think I'm afraid of you,
you big fuck?
You're crowdin'
the fuckin' plate.
Hey, Casey is bouncin' up
a bar at Harvard next week.
We should go up there.
What are we
gonna do
up there?
I don't know.
We'll fuck up some smart kids.
Probably fit right in.
Ow! Fuckin' punk.
Oh, what's up?
You still tough?
Come on!
Come on. Come on.
That's it. Come on.
I'd hold you forever here
In my arms
Professor Lambeau?
Yes?
I'm in your
applied theories
class.
We're all up
at the math
and science building.
Come here.
It's Saturday.
(CHUCKLES)
Unless, you wanna have
a drink with me tonight?
(CHUCKLING) Maybe.
We just couldn't wait
until Monday to find out.
Find out what?
Who proved
the theorem.
This is correct.
Who did this?
Jack?
It wasn't me.
Nemesh?
(CHUCKLING) No way.
Come on, Joey, now!
Billy, McNamara's up.
CHUCKIE:
Come on, kid!
Joey, dig it out!
Dig it out!
Son of a bitch!
Bring it down, Mac!
That's how to do it! Attaboy!
Take two, Mac. Take two.
Hey, Morgan, who's the girl
with the striped pants?
She's got a nice ass.
MORGAN: Yeah, that's
a real nice ass.
CHUCKIE: Who's the guy
she's with?
That fuckin' guinea.
I hate that little bitch.
Will knows him.
Yeah, I do.
Yeah, fuckin'
Carmine Scarpaglia.
That guy used to
beat the shit
out of me in kindergarten.
That guy?
Yeah.
Fuck this.
Let's get some food.
Oh, what, Morgan, you're not
gonna go talk to her?
Fuck her. (BURPS)
I could go for a Whopper.
Let's go to Kelly's.
Morgan, I'm not goin'
to Kelly's just because
you like the takeout girl.
It's 15 minutes
out of our way.
What the fuck are we gonna do?
We can't spare 15 minutes?
MORGAN: Double burger.
Double burger.
Chuck, I had
a double burger.
Would you shut the fuck up?
I know what you ordered.
I was there.
So, give me
my fuckin' sandwich.
What do you mean,
your sandwich? I bought it.
Morgan, how much money
you got on you?
MORGAN: I said I'd get change
when I get the snow cone.
I said that before
when we pulled up.
Why don't you
give me my sandwich
and stop bein' a prick.
All right, well,
give me your fuckin' 16 cents
that you got on you now.
We'll put
your fuckin' sandwich
on layaway.
Here we go.
Keep it right up here
for ya.
We'll put you on a program.
Every day you come in here
with your six cents,
at the end of the week,
you get your sandwich.
MORGAN: Why you gotta
be an asshole?
CHUCKIE: What am I,
fuckin' sandwich welfare?
I think you should
establish a good line
of credit.
Like how you bought
your couch.
Payment plans.
Remember how your mother
brought in $10
every day for a year.
She finally got her couch
Rent-A-Center style.
Can I have my food, please?
CHUCKIE: Here's your fuckin'
double burger.
STUDENTS: Whoa!
Hey, hold up, Chuck.
Slow it down.
Who do we got?
WILL: I don't know yet.
MAN: Hey, douchebag!
(GLASS SHATTERING)
Yeah, you, you skank face!
Shut the fuck up.
MAN: Why don't you lick
my love stick?
We just seen the guy
15 minutes ago at the park
if we was gonna fight him,
we should've fight him then.
We got snacks now.
Shut up, Morgan, you're goin'.
MORGAN: I'm not goin'.
CHUCKIE: So, don't go.
MORGAN: I'm not going.
Fucking go, Morgan.
Let me tell you somethin'.
If you're not out there
in two fuckin' seconds,
when I'm done with them,
you're next.
Carmine, it's me, Will.
Remember, we went
to kindergarten together.
Way down the street
There's a light in his place
He opens the door
He's got that look
on his face
(BELL TOLLS)
BOY: Fuckin', let's go, man.
Step on his fuckin' head.
Get his ass on the ground.
Stomp that motherfucker.
BOY: Motherfucker, die!
Carter!
Come on!
(GROANING)
(BELL CLANGING)
CHUCKIE: Will! Will, come on!
CHUCKIE: Will, come on.
Let's go. Let's go.
Easy, brother, easy.
Hey, what's up
fellas, thanks for comin' out.
Come here!
Whoa! Whoa!
(GROANS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER
OVER POLICE RADIO)
Ah. Fuck.
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
Is it just my imagination,
or has my class
grown considerably?
Well, by no stretch
of my imagination
do I believe
you've all come here
to hear me lecture.
Rather,
to ascertain the identity
of the mystery math magician.
So, without further ado,
come forward, silent rogue,
and receive thy prize.
Well, I'm sorry to disappoint
my spectators,
but it seems there will be
no unmasking here today.
However, my colleagues and I
have conferred,
and there is a problem
on the board right now
that took us
more than two years to prove.
So, let this be said,
the gauntlet has been
thrown down,
but the faculty have answered
and answered with vigor.
(WHISTLE)
Hey, when's the arraignment?
Next week.
(CHALK CLICKING ON CHALKBOARD)
(CHATTERING)
Sorry.
What are you doing?
That's people's work.
You can't graffiti here.
Don't you walk away from me!
Hey, fuck you!
Oh, you're a clever one.
What's your name?
(DOOR CLOSES)
Oh, my God.
Looks right.
(CHEERING)
Will, how retarded
do you gotta be to get
fired from that job?
I mean, how hard is it
to push a motherfuckin'
broom around?
Bitch, you got fired
from pushin' a fuckin' broom.
I got fired
'cause management
was restructuring.
Yeah, restructuring
the amount of retards
they had workin' for 'em.
Shut up. You get canned
more than tuna, bitch.
At least I got a motherfuckin'
job right now, don't I?
Yeah.
Why'd you get fired, Will?
Come on.
Management was restructuring.
My uncle could probably
get you on a demo team.
Can he do that?
You kiddin' me?
I asked you yesterday
if I could get a job.
And I told you "No"
yesterday.
What's up, Casey?
What's up, Case?
What's up, big Case?
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Let's sit over here.
Oh, this is... This is
a Harvard bar, huh?
I thought there'd be, like,
equations and shit
on the walls.
I will take a pitcher
of the finest lager
in the house.
Time-out.
I'm gonna have to bust
a little move on them Harvard
hotties down there at the bar.
Work some magic.
Get some pussy for us.
(LAUGHING)
Oh, hello.
Hi, how are you?
Fine.
So, do you ladies...
Come here often?
CHUCKIE: Do I come here?
I come here a bit.
I'm here, you know,
from time to time.
Do you go to school here?
Yep.
Yeah, that's it.
I think I had a class
with you.
Oh, yeah?
What class?
History.
SKYLAR: Maybe.
CHUCKIE: Yes, I think
that's what it was.
You don't necessarily...
May not remember me.
You know, I like it here.
It doesn't mean 'cause
I go here, I'm a genius.
I am very smart.
Hey.
Hey, how's it goin'?
How are ya?
Good. How ya doin'?
What class
did you say that was?
BOTH: history.
Yeah.
Just history?
It must have been
a survey course then, huh?
Yeah, it was.
It was surveys.
Right.
You should check it out.
It's a good course.
It'd be a good class.
CLARK: How'd you like
that course?
CHUCKIE: You know, frankly,
I found that class, you know,
rather elementary.
Elementary.
You know, I don't
doubt that it was.
Yeah.
I, uh,
I remember that class.
It was...
It was just between
recess and lunch.
Clark, why don't you
go away?
CLARK: Why don't you relax?
Why don't you just go away?
I'm just havin' fun with
my new friend. That's all.
Are we gonna have a problem?
No, no, no, no.
There's no
problem here.
I was just hoping you might
give me some insight into
the evolution of
the market economy in
the Southern colonies.
My contention is that,
prior to the
Revolutionary War,
the economic modalities,
especially in
the Southern colonies,
could most aptly
be characterized as
Agrarian pre-capitalist.
Let me tell you somethin',
all right.
Of course that's
your contention. You're
a first-year grad student.
You just got finished readin'
some Marxian historian,
Pete Garrison, probably.
You're gonna be convinced
of that till next month
when you get to James Lemon.
Then you're gonna be talkin'
about how the economies of
Virginia and Pennsylvania
were entrepreneurial
and capitalist way back
in 1740.
That's gonna last until
next year.
You're gonna be in here
regurgitating Gordon Wood
talkin' about, you know,
the pre-revolutionary utopia
and the capital-forming
effects of
military mobilization.
(SCOFFS)
Well, as a matter of fact,
I won't,
because Wood
drastically underestimates
the impact of...
Wood drastically
underestimates the impact
of social distinctions
predicated upon wealth,
especially inherited wealth?
You got that from Vickers'
Work in Essex County.
Page 98, right?
Yeah, I read that, too.
Were you gonna plagiarize
the whole thing for us?
Do you have any thoughts
of your own on this matter?
Or is that your thing?
You come into a bar.
You read some obscure passage.
And then pretend...
You pawn it off as your own...
As your own idea
just to impress some girls?
Embarrass my friend?
See, the sad thing
about a guy like you is,
in 50 years,
you're gonna start doin'
some thinkin' on your own.
You're gonna come up
with the fact that there are
two certainties in life.
One, don't do that.
And two, you dropped 150 grand
on a fuckin' education
you could've got
for $1.50 in late charges
at the public library.
(ALL CHUCKLING)
Yeah, but I will
have a degree
and you'll be servin' my kids
fries at a drive through
on our way to a skiing trip.
(CHUCKLING)
Maybe, but at least
I won't be unoriginal.
If you have a problem
with that, we could just
step outside.
We could
figure it out.
No, man, there's no problem.
It's cool.
It's cool?
Yeah.
Cool.
Fuckin' damn right, it's cool.
How do you like me now?
My boy's wicked smart.
I just spent three minutes
in this fuckin' place
and run into a Barney, huh?
There it is.
They were fine, man.
I was gonna, we was gonna
close the deal,
but then Chuck...
Uh, Billy insulted one of them
and the heavyset girl said
I had a receding hairline,
and I was
a few pounds overweight.
And I was, like,
"Go fuck yourself."
I swallowed a bug.
(CHUCKLING)
Hi.
You're an idiot.
What?
I've been sitting
over there for 45 minutes
waiting for you
to come and talk to me.
But I'm tired now,
and I have to go home.
I couldn't sit there anymore
waiting for you.
I'm Will.
Skylar.
Oh, and by the way,
that guy over there,
Michael Bolton clone,
he wasn't sitting with us,
so to speak.
I know.
I kinda got that impression.
Good. Okay.
Well, I've got to go.
Gotta get up early
and waste some more money
on my overpriced education.
No, I didn't mean you.
That's all right.
There's my number.
Maybe we can go out
for coffee sometime.
All right, yeah.
Maybe we can just get together
and eat a bunch of caramels.
What do you mean?
When you think about it,
it's as arbitrary
as drinkin' coffee.
Oh, yeah. Okay.
Uh, right, then.
Yo!
Hey, fuck you,
there goes them fuckin'
Barneys right now with their
skiing trip.
Hold on.
We should've beat
that old bitch's ass.
Do you like apples?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Well, I got
her number.
How do you like them apples?
(CHUCKLING)
We arrived tonight
Our mouths were opening
I turned off the light
So, come on, night
Everyone is gone
Home to oblivion
So, come on
So, come on, night
GERRY: Tom.
Excuse me?
Is this the buildings
and grounds office?
Yeah. What can I do
for you?
I just need the name
of a student who works here.
No students work for me.
Well, could you please check?
I have this guy
who works in my building.
He's about this high.
Which one is your building?
Two. Building two.
Look, if anything was stolen,
I should know...
No, no, no.
It's nothing like that.
I just need his name.
I can't give you his name
unless you have a complaint.
This is Professor Lambeau.
And this is
Professor Hayes.
Tom, please.
This is important.
Please.
Willie didn't show
for work today.
(SIGHS)
Got this job through his PO.
You can call him.
PO?
HEAD CUSTODIAN:
Yeah, parole officer.
Thank you.
Asshole.
(CHUCKLING)
WILL: There is a lengthy
legal precedent, Your Honor,
going back to 1789,
whereby a defendant
can claim self-defense against
an agent of the government
if that act is deemed
a defense against tyranny,
a defense of liberty.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Your Honor,
Henry Ward Beecher,
in Proverbs from the Plymouth
Pulpit, 1887,
said, and I quote...
LAWYER: 1887?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
This is the 20th century,
Your Honor.
He's gonna make a mockery
of the courtroom.
I am afforded the right
to speak in
my own defense, sir,
by the constitution
of the United States.
This is the same document...
Don't tell me
about the constitution
of the United States.
"Liberty,"
in case you've forgotten,
is a soul's right to breathe.
When it cannot
take a long breath,
laws are girded too tight.
Without liberty,
man is a syncope.
Man is a what?
Ibid, Your Honor.
JUDGE: Son, my turn.
I've been sitting here
for 10 minutes now
lookin' over this
rap sheet of yours.
I just can't believe it.
June '93, assault.
September '93, assault.
Grand theft auto,
February of '94.
Where, apparently,
you defended yourself
and had the case thrown out
by citing
"Free property rights
of horse and carriage"
from 1798.
Joke.
January '95,
impersonating an officer.
Mayhem, theft, resisting.
All overturned.
I'm also aware that
you've been through
several foster homes.
The state removed you
from three because of
serious physical abuse.
You know, another judge
might care, but you hit a cop.
You're going in.
Motion to dismiss is denied.
$50,000 bail.
(GAVEL POUNDS)
Thank you.
WOMAN: All rise.
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
WILL: Uh, Skylar?
Yep.
Hey, it's Will.
Who?
It's Will.
You know, the really funny,
good-looking guy you met
at the bar the other night.
I don't recall meeting anyone
who matches that description.
I think I'd remember.
Oh, all right, you got me.
It's the ugly, obnoxious,
toothless loser
who got hammered
and wouldn't leave you
alone all night.
Oh, Will! I remember.
(WILL CHUCKLING)
How are you?
I was wondering
if you'd call me.
Yeah, look, I was wondering...
Yo, what's up, baby?
Hold on one second.
What you doing?
Hey.
What's up, baby?
Want some of my ass?
Herve, I remember you
from juvie. How you doing?
Oh, yeah,
sorry about that.
I was wonderin' maybe
we could get together
sometime this week.
You know, sit out at a cafe.
Maybe have some caramels.
Oh, that sounds wonderful.
Yeah?
Yeah, sure. Where are you?
Uh, well, actually,
this is just a shot
in the dark,
but there's no chance
that you're pre-law,
is there?
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Nice talking to you.
What the fuck
do you want?
I'm Gerald Lambeau.
Professor you told
to fuck himself.
Well, what the fuck
do you want?
I've spoken to the judge,
and he's agreed to release you
under my supervision.
Really?
Yeah.
Under two conditions.
What are those?
First condition is
that you meet with me
every week.
What for?
Go over the proof
you're working on,
get into
some more advanced...
Combinatorial mathematics,
finite math.
Sounds like a real hoot.
And the second condition
is that...
That you see a therapist.
(CHUCKLING)
I'm responsible
to submit reports
on those meetings.
If you fail to meet with
any of those conditions,
you will have to serve time.
All right. I'll do the math,
but I'm not gonna meet
with any fuckin' therapist.
It's better
than spending that time
in jail, isn't it?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(DOG BARKING)
I read your book,
and "Mike" was havin'
the same problems
that "Chad," the stockbroker,
was havin'.
Absolutely right.
Right on the button.
Good for you, Will.
Very nice.
Thank you.
Will, the pressures,
and I'm not judging them,
I'm not labeling them,
but they are destroying
your potential.
No more shenanigans.
No more tomfoolery.
No more ballyhoo.
You're right.
God, I know.
You're not gonna get off
that easily. Come on, Will.
A bit more.
Well, I mean,
I do do things, you know?
What kind of things?
I do things that, you know,
I mean, I hide from people.
You hide, do you?
No, no. I mean,
I like, I go places.
I interact, you know.
Really? What sort of places?
Just certain clubs.
More, that's nice.
Yes, what sort of clubs?
Like, uh, like Fantasy.
Fantasy, that's nice.
A bit more.
It's something like
when you get in there and...
The music, like, owns you.
It's like that house music.
It's like...
(IMITATING DANCE MUSIC)
You know, you start dancin'.
Boom, boom, boom. Yes.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
(SIGHING)
Do you find it hard to hide
the fact that you're gay?
(STAMMERING)
What are you talking about?
What?
Look, buddy, two seconds ago,
you were ready
to give me a jump.
A jump? Are you...
(LAUGHING)
I'm terribly sorry
to disappoint you.
Hey, I don't have a problem
with it. I don't care
if you putt from the rough.
What are you...
Putting from the rough?
What on earth
are you talking about?
A difficult theorem
can be like...
A symphony.
It's very erotic.
THERAPIST:
You go somewhere else.
I can't handle this.
Wow.
WILL: Thank you, Henry.
(GRUNTING) Ah, Henry.
Hi, Gerry.
Hey, you know something?
I can't do this
pro bono work anymore.
It's just not...
It's not worth it.
What happened?
Well, I'm going on national
television next week.
I mean, I haven't got time
to tell you, much less talk to
that raving loony in there.
An absolute lunatic,
he is.
GERRY: Henry.
RICH: Okay, you are
in your bed, Will.
Now, how old are you?
WILL: Seven.
What do you see?
WILL: Something's in my room.
What is it?
It's like a...
It's a figure.
It's hoverin' over me.
You are in a safe place,
Will.
It's... (SIGHS)
It's touchin' me.
Where is it touching you?
It's touching me
down there.
And I'm nervous.
RICH: You don't have to be
nervous, Will.
We start dancin' and dancin'.
It's just beautiful,
because we can make
a lot of love
before the sun goes down.
Skyrockets
in flight
Afternoon delight
Hey, hey, hey
Jesus.
Skyrockets in flight
(HUMMING)
I'm sorry, Rich.
I have better things to do
with my time.
Hey, hey
afternoon delight
Come on, one dance!
You really hypnotized me,
you know?
For God's sake, Will.
What? Oh, come on. He left.
You can't pin that on me.
I told you to cooperate
with these people.
Look into my eyes.
Get out, Will.
I don't need therapy.
That's enough. Get out!
(IMITATING SPOOKY SOUND)
I called Mel Weintraub
this morning to see...
Oh, what's the use?
What do you want to do?
(SIGHS)
Well, there is someone.
Who is he?
He used to be my, uh...
My roommate in college.
Trust. Very important
in a relationship.
It's also very important
in a clinical situation.
Why is trust
the most important thing
in making a breakthrough
with a client?
Maurine,
stop the oral fixation
for a moment and join us.
Vinnie.
Um...
Because, uh...
Trust is, uh...
Trust is life.
Wow, that's very deep.
Thank you, Vinnie.
Next time, get the notes
from your brother.
If a patient doesn't feel
safe enough to trust you, then
they won't be honest with you.
Then there's really no point
for them being in therapy.
I mean, hey, if they don't
trust you, you're never gonna
get them to sleep with you.
That should be the goal
of any good therapist.
Nail them while
they're vulnerable.
That's my motto.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Oh, good, everyone's back.
Welcome back, everybody.
Hello, Sean.
Hey, Gerry.
Um, ladies and gentlemen,
we are in the presence
of greatness.
Professor Gerald Lambeau,
Fields Medal winner
for combinatorial mathematics.
Hello.
SEAN: Anyone know what
the Fields Medal is?
It's a really big deal.
It's like the Nobel Prize
for math.
Except they only give it out
once every four years.
It's a great thing.
It's an amazing honor.
Okay, everybody,
that's it for today.
Thanks. We'll see you Monday.
We'll be talking about Freud.
Why he did enough cocaine
to kill a small horse.
Thank you.
How are you?
It's good to see you.
Good to see you.
Sean, I think I got something
interesting for you.
What, you have to have
blood and urine?
What's up?
Why didn't you come
to the reunion?
Ah. You know.
I've been busy.
You were missed.
Really?
So, how long has it been
since we've seen each other?
Before Nancy died.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I was in Paris.
It was that damn conference.
I got your card.
It was nice.
(GRUNTING)
Come here.
Now, that's a takedown.
Hey, what happened?
Did you get leniency or what?
I got, uh, probation
and then counseling
two days a week.
Joke. You're a smoothie.
Come on, Morgan!
Just submit!
(GROANING)
(CHUCKLING)
Hey, Bill,
just get off him.
We're gonna miss the game.
I've got a full schedule.
I'm very busy.
Sean, Sean.
This boy is incredible.
I've never seen anything
like him.
What makes him
so incredible, Gerry?
You ever heard of Ramanujan?
Yeah, yeah.
No.
It's a man.
He lived over 100 years ago.
He was Indian.
Dots, not feathers.
Not feathers, yeah.
He lived in this tiny hut
somewhere in India.
He had no formal education.
He had no access
to any scientific work.
WAITER: Coffee?
You, sir?
Just a little.
But he came across
this old math book,
and from the simple text,
he was able to extrapolate
theories
that had baffled
mathematicians for years.
Yes, continued fractions.
He wrote, uh...
Well, he mailed it
to Hardy at Cambridge.
Yeah, Cambridge. Yeah.
And Hardy immediately
recognized the brilliance
of his work.
And brought him over
to England, and then they
worked together for years,
creating some of the most
exciting math theory
ever done.
This Ramanujan,
his genius
was unparalleled, Sean.
Well, this boy's
just like that.
Hmm.
But he's...
He's a bit defensive.
Hmm.
I need someone
who can get through to him.
Like me?
Yeah, like you.
Why?
Well, because you have
the same kind of background.
What background?
Well, you're from
the same neighborhood.
He's from Southie?
Yeah.
Boy genius from Southie.
How many shrinks
you go to before me?
Five.
Let me guess. Barry?
Yeah.
Henry? Not Rich.
Sean, please.
Mm-hmm.
Just meet with him
once a week.
Please?
GERRY: It's a poker game
with this kid.
Don't let him know
what you've got.
He probably even
read your book,
if he could find it.
SEAN: It's gonna be hard
for him to find.
Hi, Will.
Hi.
This is Sean Maguire.
Will Hunting.
How are you?
Yeah, let's get started.
Yeah, let's do it. I'm pumped.
(CLAPS)
Let's let the healing begin.
Will you excuse us?
Yeah, please, Tom.
You, too, Gerry.
Yeah, of course.
How are you?
(DOOR CLOSES)
Where you from
in Southie?
I like what you've done
with the place.
Oh, thanks.
Do you buy
all these books retail
or do you send away for, like,
a "shrink kit" that comes with
all these volumes included?
Do you like books?
Yeah.
Did you read
any of these books?
I don't know.
How about
any of these books?
Probably not.
What about the ones
on the top shelf?
You read those?
Yeah, I read those.
Good for you.
What do you think about them?
I'm not here
for a fuckin' book report.
They're your books.
Why don't you read them?
I did. I had to.
Must've taken you a long time.
Yeah, it did.
United States of America:
A Complete History, Volume I.
Jesus.
If you wanna read
a real history book,
read Howard Zinn's
A People's History
in the United States.
That book'll fuckin'
knock you on your ass.
Better than Chomsky's
Manufacturing Consent?
Do you think
that's a good book?
You fuckin' people baffle me.
You spend all your money on
these fuckin' fancy books.
You surround yourselves
with them
and they're the wrong
fuckin' books.
What are the right
fuckin' books, Will?
Whatever blows
your hair back.
Yeah.
Haven't got much hair left.
Hey, you know you'd be
better off shoving that
cigarette up your ass.
It'd probably be healthier
for you.
Yeah, I know.
It really gets in the way
of my yoga.
You work out, huh?
What, you lift?
Yeah.
Nautilus?
No, free weights.
Oh, really?
Free weights, huh?
Yeah. Yeah, big time.
Yeah?
Just like that.
What do you bench?
285. What do you bench?
You paint that?
Yeah. Do you paint?
Uh-uh.
Do you sculpt?
No.
Do you like art?
Do you like music?
This is a real piece of shit.
Oh, tell me what
you really think.
Just the linear
and impressionistic mix makes
a very muddled composition.
It's also a Winslow Homer
rip-off, except you got
Whitey rowing the boat there.
Well, it's art, Monet.
I wasn't very good.
That's not really
what concerns me, though.
What concerns you?
It's the coloring.
You know what the
real bitch of it is?
It's paint-by-number.
Is it color-by-number?
Because the colors
are fascinating to me.
Are they really?
You bet.
I think you're about
one step away from cutting
your fucking ear off.
Really?
Oh, yeah.
Think I should move
to the south of France,
change my name to Vincent?
You ever heard the saying,
"Any port in a storm"?
Yeah.
Yeah, maybe that means you.
In what way?
Maybe you're in the middle
of a storm, a big fucking
storm.
Yeah, maybe.
The sky's falling on your
head. The waves are crashing
over your little boat.
The oars are about to snap.
(SNIFFS)
You're just pissing
your pants. You're crying
for the harbor.
So maybe you do
what you gotta do to get out.
You know, maybe you became
a psychologist.
Bingo. That's it.
Let me do my job now.
You start with me. Come on.
Maybe you married
the wrong woman.
Maybe you should
watch your mouth.
Watch it right there, chief,
all right?
Ah.
That's it, isn't it?
You married
the wrong woman.
What happened?
What, did she leave you?
Was she, you know...
(WHISTLING)
Banging some other guy?
If you ever
disrespect my wife
again, I will end you.
I will fucking end you.
Got that, chief?
Time's up.
Yeah.
At ease, gentlemen.
(DOOR OPENS)
GERRY: You okay?
Look, I'll understand
if you don't wanna meet
with him again.
Thursday, 4:00.
Make sure the kid's here.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Well, you look lovely
in those glasses.
Thank you very much.
They're just beautiful.
Yes, I always wanted
dark blue eye shadow.
Wonderful.
Growing up in England,
you know, I went to
a very nice school.
You know, it was kind of
progressive, organic,
do-it-yourself,
private school.
Then Harvard.
Hopefully med school.
You know, I figured out,
by the end,
my brain's gonna be worth
$250,000.
That sounded horrible,
didn't it?
(CLACKING)
Bring me another Mai Tai!
Yeah, that's cool.
I mean, I bet your parents
were happy to pay.
No, I was happy to pay.
I inherited the money.
Wow. Is Harvard getting
all that money?
No, Stanford.
I'm going there in June
when I graduate.
All right, so you just wanted
to use this sailor
and then run away, huh?
I was gonna, you know,
experiment on you
for anatomy class first,
obviously.
In that case, that's fine.
Hey, you wanna see
my magic trick, Skylar?
Of course.
All right.
Promise to...
All right. (CHUCKLES)
This one's for you, Rudolph.
Wait, wait. You need my wand.
All right, give me a hit.
Thank you. All right.
I'm gonna make
all these caramels
disappear.
You ready?
Ready.
One, two, three.
(GASPS)
(CHUCKLES) They're all gone.
That was my...
It works better
when I have my rabbit.
Well...
(CLEARS THROAT)
I don't really date,
you know, that much.
How very unfortunate...
I think for me.
(CHUCKLING)
You know what I mean?
I know you've been
thinking about it.
Oh, no, I haven't.
Yes, you have.
No, I really haven't.
You were hoping to get
a good night kiss.
No, you know, I tell ya,
I was hoping to get
a good night laid.
(LAUGHING)
But I'll settle for,
like, a kiss, you know?
How very noble of you.
Thank you.
Mm.
No, I was
hoping for a kiss.
Well, I think we should
just get it
out of the way now.
Right now?
Yeah.
Come on.
(GIGGLING)
I think I got
some of your pickle.
(LAUGHING)
You again, huh?
Come with me.
So what's this?
A Taster's Choice moment
between guys?
This is really nice.
You got a thing for swans?
Is this, like, a fetish?
Is it something, like,
maybe we need to
devote some time to?
Thought about what you said
to me the other day.
About my painting.
Ah.
Stayed up half the night
thinking about it.
Something occurred to me.
I fell into a deep,
peaceful sleep and haven't
thought about you since.
You know what
occurred to me?
No.
You're just a kid.
You don't have
the faintest idea of what
you're talking about.
Why, thank you.
It's all right.
You've never been
out of Boston.
Nope.
So if I asked you about art,
you'd probably give me
the skinny
on every art book
ever written.
Michelangelo?
You know a lot about him.
Life's work,
political aspirations.
Him and the Pope.
Sexual orientation.
The whole works, right?
I bet you can't tell me
what it smells like
in the Sistine Chapel.
You never actually stood
there and looked up
at that beautiful ceiling.
Seeing that.
If I ask you about women,
you'll probably
give me a syllabus of
your personal favorites.
You may have even been laid
a few times.
But you can't tell me
what it feels like to wake up
next to a woman
and feel truly happy.
You're a tough kid.
I ask you about war,
you'd probably throw
Shakespeare at me, right?
"Once more into the breach,
dear friends."
But you've never
been near one.
You've never held
your best friend's head
in your lap
and watch him gasp
his last breath looking
to you for help.
If I asked you about love,
you'd probably quote me
a sonnet,
but you've never looked
at a woman and been
totally vulnerable.
Known someone that could
level you with her eyes.
Feeling like God put
an angel on Earth
just for you,
who could rescue you
from the depths of hell.
And you wouldn't
know what it's like
to be her angel.
To have that love for her
be there forever.
Through anything.
Through cancer.
And you wouldn't know
about sleeping sitting up
in a hospital room
for two months,
holding her hand,
because the doctors
could see in your eyes
that the terms
"visiting hours" don't
apply to you.
You don't know
about real loss,
'cause that only occurs
when you love something more
than you love yourself.
I doubt you've ever dared
to love anybody that much.
I look at you.
I don't see an intelligent,
confident man.
I see a cocky,
scared-shitless kid.
But you're a genius, Will.
No one denies that.
No one could possibly
understand the depths of you.
But you presume to know
everything about me because
you saw a painting of mine.
You ripped
my fucking life apart.
You're an orphan, right?
Do you think I'd know
the first thing about
how hard your life has been?
How you feel? Who you are?
Because I read Oliver Twist?
Does that encapsulate you?
Personally,
I don't give a shit
about all that,
because you know what?
I can't learn
anything from you
I can't read
in some fucking book.
Unless you wanna talk
about you.
Who you are.
Then I'm fascinated.
I'm in.
But you don't wanna
do that, do you, sport?
You're terrified
of what you might say.
Your move, chief.
(KNOCKING)
(MACHINERY HUMMING)
(RINGING)
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
Professor Valenti,
are you calling me again?
Freak.
Oh, God.
Christ, who did you call?
No one. I forgot the number.
MORGAN: You fucking retarded?
You went all the way out there
in the rain and you didn't
bring the number?
No, it was your mother's
900 number. I just ran
out of quarters.
Why don't we
get off on mothers?
I just got off yours.
(LAUGHING)
BILLY: That's pretty funny,
Morgan. That's a
fucking nickel, bitch.
Keep antagonizing me.
Watch what happens.
All right, then, Morgan.
MORGAN: Watch what happens.
BILLY: All right, then,
Morgan.
MORGAN: Keep fucking with me.
No smoking.
What do you mean,
he didn't talk? You were
in there for an hour.
He just sat there
counting the seconds
until the session was over.
Pretty impressive,
actually.
Why would he do that?
To prove to me he doesn't
have to talk to me
if he doesn't want to.
What is this? Some kind of
staring contest
between two kids from
the old neighborhood?
Yeah, it is,
and I can't talk first.
GERRY: We know your theory,
Alexander,
but the boy's found
a simple geometrical picture.
A tree structure won't work.
GERRY: Look now, he's joining
the two vertices.
But I can do the sum.
It's how you group the terms,
Alexander.
But, Gerry.
If we do the whole thing
this way, then...
Hey, look, look.
I wrote it down.
It's simpler this way.
Sometimes
people get lucky.
You're a brilliant man.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(WHISTLING)
WILL: You know,
I was on this plane once,
and I'm sitting there, and...
The captain gets on,
he does his whole, you know,
"We'll be cruising
at 35,000 feet," but then
he puts the mike down.
He forgets to turn it off.
Mm-hmm.
So he turns to the copilot.
He's, like,
"You know, all I could use
right now is a fucking
blow job and a cup of coffee."
So the stewardess fucking goes
bombing up from the back
of the plane
to tell him that
the microphone's still on.
This guy in the back of the
plane's like, "Hey, hon,
don't forget the coffee."
(CHUCKLING)
You ever been on a plane?
No, but it's a fucking joke.
It works better if I tell it
in the first person.
Yeah, it does.
I have been laid,
you know?
Really?
Good for you.
Big time, big time.
Big time, huh?
I went on a date last week.
How'd it go?
It was good.
Going out again?
I don't know.
Why not?
Haven't called her.
Christ, you're an amateur.
I know what I'm doing.
Yeah.
Yeah. Don't worry about me.
I know what I'm doing.
Yeah, but this girl was, like,
you know, beautiful.
She's smart. She's fun.
She's different from most
of the girls I've been with.
So call her up, Romeo.
Why, so I can realize
she's not that smart?
That she's fucking boring?
You know, I mean, you don't...
This girl's, like,
fucking perfect right now.
I don't wanna ruin that.
Maybe you're perfect
right now. Maybe you
don't wanna ruin that.
But I think that's
a super philosophy, Will.
That way, you can go through
your entire life without ever
having to really know anybody.
My wife used to fart
when she was nervous.
She had all sorts
of wonderful idiosyncrasies.
You know, she used to fart
in her sleep.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Just thought I'd share that
with you.
One night it was so loud,
it woke the dog up.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
She woke up and gone, like,
"Was that you?"
I said, "Yeah." I didn't have
the heart to tell her.
Oh, God.
She woke herself up?
(LAUGHING)
Yes.
Oh, Christ.
But, Will, she's been dead
two years and that's
the shit I remember.
It's wonderful
stuff, you know?
Little things like that.
Yeah, but those are the things
I miss the most.
Those little idiosyncrasies
that only I knew about.
That's what made her
my wife.
Boy, and she had the goods
on me, too. She knew
all my little peccadilloes.
People call these things
imperfections,
but they're not.
That's the good stuff.
And then we get
to choose who we let into
our weird little worlds.
You're not perfect, sport.
And let me save you
the suspense.
This girl you met,
she isn't perfect, either.
But the question is
whether or not you're perfect
for each other.
That's the whole deal.
That's what intimacy
is all about.
Now you can know
everything in the
world, sport,
but the only way
you're finding out that one
is by giving it a shot.
You certainly won't learn
from an old fucker like me.
Even if I did know,
I wouldn't tell a pissant
like you.
(CHUCKLING)
Yeah, why not?
You told me every other
fucking thing. Jesus Christ.
Fucking talk more than
any shrink I ever seen
in my life.
I teach the shit.
I didn't say I knew
how to do it.
Yeah.
(SIGHS) You ever think about
getting remarried?
My wife's dead.
Hence the word "remarried."
She's dead.
Yeah, well, I think that's a
super philosophy, Sean.
I mean, that way, you can
actually go through the rest
of your life
without ever really knowing
anybody.
Time's up.
Hold it open.
Okay.
Thanks.
(CHATTERING)
(PIANO PLAYING)
SKYLAR:
I am happy with you
I know I'm about
to love you
Yeah, yeah, yeah
You know him
(KNOCKING)
Oh, my, you made me...
G minor seventh.
Saddest of all chords.
Hello.
Hey.
Where have you been?
I'm sorry. I've been, like...
I've been really busy, and...
(CLEARS THROAT) But...
Me, too.
Yeah. I...
I thought you'd call.
Yeah, um...
I mean, we had
a really good time.
I had a really good time, too.
I mean, I just... I...
I'm sorry, you know.
I blew it.
No. No, I mean,
you know, it's all right.
Yeah, um, so, I was
wondering if, uh...
If, you know, you'd give me
another crack at it.
You know, let me
take you out again.
(GASPS) I can't.
All right.
Oh, no, I didn't...
I didn't mean
I can't, like, ever.
I just can't right now.
I've got to assign
the proton spectrum
for ibogamine.
Although it sounds really,
really interesting, it's
actually fantastically boring.
All right...
Maybe some other time.
Like tomorrow?
Um, yeah, all right.
Okay.
Bye.
(BELL TOLLING)
(KNOCKING)
What are you doing here?
I couldn't wait
till tomorrow.
Where the fuck
did you get this?
I had to sleep
with someone in your class.
Oh, I hope it was the one
with the open-toed sandals
and the really bad breath.
Come on. Let's go
have some fun.
No, I've got to learn this.
Well, you're not going into
surgery tomorrow, are you?
No.
Let's go.
(BELL RINGS)
(CROWD SHOUTING)
Oh, my God!
My dog is winning!
Come on, Misty!
Come on! Run!
Look at that!
Come on!
Look, there he goes.
Misty, run! Come on!
COMMENTATOR:
There's Misty...
We won. (LAUGHS)
He totally won!
So did you grow up
around here, then?
Not far.
South Boston.
(EXHALES)
Still glowing from my win.
Yeah...
Look at you.
You're so happy.
And what was
that like, then?
It was normal, I guess.
Nothin' special.
Do you got lots of
brothers and sisters?
Do I have a lot of
That's what I said.
Well, Irish catholic,
what do you think?
Right. That's right.
COMMENTATOR:
The winner...
How many?
You wouldn't believe me
if I told you.
Why? Go on. What? Five?
No.
Seven? Eight?
How many?
I have 12 big brothers.
You do not! (CHUCKLING)
Have 12 brothers.
No, I swear to God.
I swear to God.
I'm lucky 13 right here.
Do you know
all their names?
Do I... Yeah,
they're my brothers.
What are they called?
Marky, Ricky, Danny, Terry,
Mikey, Davey, Timmy, Tommy,
Joey, Robby, Johnny and Brian.
Say it again.
Marky, Ricky, Danny, Terry,
Mikey, Davey, Timmy, Tommy,
Joey, Robby, Johnny and Brian.
And Willy.
Yeah.
Willy?
Will.
Wow.
Do you still see all of them?
Yeah, well,
they all live in Southie.
I'm livin' with
three of 'em right now.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
I'd like to meet them.
Yeah, we'll do that.
Oh, you know,
I read your book last night.
Oh, so you're the one.
(LAUGHS)
Do you still, uh...
Do you still counsel veterans?
No, I don't.
Why not?
Well, I gave it up
when my wife got sick.
You ever wonder what your life
would be like if you, uh,
if you never met your wife?
What? Wonder if I'd be
better off without her?
No, no, no, I'm not saying,
like, better off.
No.
I didn't mean it like that.
It's all right.
It's an important question.
'Cause you'll have
bad times, but that'll
always wake you up
to the good stuff
you weren't paying
attention to.
And you don't regret
meeting your wife?
Why? 'Cause of the pain
I feel now?
Oh, I got regrets, Will,
but I don't regret a single
day I spent with her.
So when did you know, like,
that she was the one for you?
October 21, 1975.
Jesus Christ.
You know the fuckin' day?
Oh, yeah, 'cause it was
game six of the World Series,
biggest game
in Red Sox history.
WILL: Yeah, sure.
My friends and I
had slept out on sidewalk
all night to get tickets.
You got tickets?
Yep. Day of the game
I was sittin' in a bar,
waitin' for
the game to start
and in walks this girl.
It was an amazing game though.
You know, bottom of
the eighth, Carbo tied it up.
It was 6-6.
It went to 12.
Bottom of the 12th,
in stepped Carlton Fisk,
old Pudge.
Steps up to the plate.
You know, he's got
that weird stance.
WILL: Yeah, yeah.
And then... Boom!
He clocks it, you know.
High fly ball
down the left field line!
Thirty-five thousand people
on their feet,
yellin' at the ball.
But that's nothin',
'cause Fisk, he's wavin'
at the ball like a madman.
Yeah, I've seen that.
He's going,
"Get over! Get over!"
Right.
"Get over!"
And then it hits
the foul pole.
(EXCLAIMS) He goes
ape-shit, and 35,000 fans...
You know they charged
the field, you know.
Yeah, and he's
fuckin' blowin'
people outta the way.
(SHOUTING)
"Get outta the way!
Get outta the way!"
I can't fuckin'
believe you had tickets
to that fuckin' game!
Yeah!
Did you rush the field?
No, I didn't rush
the fuckin' field.
I wasn't there.
What?
No, I was in a bar, havin'
a drink with my future wife.
You missed Pudge Fisk's
home run?
Oh, yeah.
To have a fuckin' drink
with some lady you never met?
Yeah, but you should have
seen her. She was a stunner.
I don't care if, fuckin'...
Oh, no, no,
she lit up the room.
I don't care if Helen
of Troy walks into the room.
Oh, Helen of Troy!
That's game six! Oh, my God,
and who were these
fucking friends of yours?
They let you
get away with that?
Oh, they had to.
What did you say to 'em?
I just slid my ticket
across the table.
And I said, "Sorry, guys.
I gotta see about a girl."
"I gotta go see about a girl"?
Yes!
That's what you said?
I had to.
And they let you
get away with that?
Oh, yeah. They saw it
in my eyes that I meant it.
You're kiddin' me?
No, I'm not kidding you, Will.
That's why I'm not talkin'
right now about some girl
I saw at a bar 20 years ago
and how I always
regretted not goin' over
and talkin' to her.
I don't regret the 18 years
I was married to Nancy.
I don't regret the six years
I had to give up counseling
when she got sick,
and I don't regret
the last years when
she got really sick.
And I sure as hell don't
regret missin' a damn game.
That's regret.
Wow!
(SIGHS)
Would have been nice
to catch that game though.
I didn't know Pudge
was gonna hit a home run.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
You know, I'm very,
very useful on the court.
I'm extremely tall.
You're not that tall.
I dunk.
(RATTLING)
Will I ever play
in the NBA?
"It is decidedly so."
Hmm.
Why do we always stay here?
'Cause it's nicer
than my place.
Yes, but I've never
seen your place.
I know.
(LAUGHS)
When am I gonna meet
your friends
and your brothers?
Well, they don't really
come down here that much.
I think I can make it
to South Boston.
It's kind of a hike.
Is it me you're hiding
from them or
the other way around?
All right, we'll go.
When?
I don't know.
We'll go sometime next week.
What if I said I would not
sleep with you again until
you let me meet your friends?
(GROANS)
I'd say it's, like,
4:30 in the mornin'.
They're probably up.
SKYLAR: Oh, my God.
Men are shameless.
If you're not thinking
with your wiener, then you're
acting directly on its behalf.
(LINE RINGING)
You bet. And on behalf
of my wiener, can I get
an advance payment?
I don't know. Let's ask.
"Outlook does not look good."
CHUCKIE: (ON PHONE) What?
WILL: Fuck the... Hey, Chuck.
No. Nothing. Go back to sleep.
(SLAMS PHONE)
"Outlook does not..."
That's the same thing
that told you, you was
gonna play in the NBA.
Well exactly, so look out.
You'd better start buying
some season tickets.
Mm! I plan to. I'm tall.
I like wearing shorts.
Hook, hook. Dunk, dunk.
You're not that tall.
Yes, I am.
Maybe I'm all
about three points.
I'm all about home runs.
(LAUGHS)
SKYLAR: Stop mixing your
sporting metaphors.
(CHUCKLING)
The leprechaun's got his dick
in the monkey's ass.
And Morgan comes runnin' in,
goin', "I don't mind it.
I don't mind..."
(LAUGHING)
Well, I can't believe you
brought Skylar here.
When we're fuckin'
all bombed and drinkin'.
I know, Morgan.
It's a real rarity
we'd be all drinkin'.
My uncle Marty drinks.
He'll go on a bender
for six, eight months.
Did I ever tell ya
what happened to him
when he was drivin'
up there and got pulled over?
I told you guys, right?
WILL: Marty, Marty, yeah!
Let me tell ya what
happened to my uncle Marty,
because you oughta know this.
He's always tellin' stories.
Every time we come here
he's got another story.
But we all heard this one.
Go ahead. Say it anyways.
I will go ahead.
Thanks a lot.
Guess I have the floor now.
Um, yeah my uncle Marty's
drivin' home, right?
Bombed out of his tree,
right? Just hammered out of
his gourd. Just wrecked.
This state trooper sees him,
pulls him over. So my uncle's
fucked basically.
Got him out of the car,
tryin' to make him
walk the line.
He gets out of the car, pukes,
and the statie's pretty sure
he's over the legal limit.
So he's about to
throw the cuffs on him
and put him in jail.
All of a sudden, 50 yards down
the road, there's this huge
fuckin' boom. Right.
So Statie gets real spooked.
He turns around...
He got shot?
No. So... So... You
heard this story before.
Yeah, Morgan,
stop. Stop.
Some other guy's car
had hit a tree. Okay.
There was an accident.
(COUGHS)
Anyway...
MORGAN:
How could he hear...
Shut the fuck up!
You're drivin' him nuts.
I'm gonna break your neck.
Shut up!
WILL: He told you
the story once before.
So he tells my uncle,
"Stay here. Don't move."
So Statie goes runnin'
down the road to deal
with the other accident.
After a few minutes
of just lyin' in
his own piss and vomit,
my uncle starts wonderin'
what he's doin' there.
Gets up, gets in his car
and just drives home.
The next mornin'
my uncle's just passed out.
And he hears this knockin'
at the door.
(KNOCKING)
So he goes downstairs,
pulls the door open,
"What?"
It's the state trooper
that pulled him over.
Statie's like,
"Fuck you mean, 'What?'"
"You know what. I pulled you
over last night is what,
and you fucking took off."
He's like, "Bitch, I never
seen you before in my life.
"I've been home all night
with my kids. I don't know
who the fuck you are."
He's like, "You know who I am.
Let me get in your garage."
My uncle's like, "What?"
He said, "You heard me.
Let me get in your garage."
He was like, "All right.
Fine." Takes him out to
the garage, opens the door.
And there's...
The statie's police cruiser
is in my uncle's garage.
(LAUGHING)
He was so fuckin'...
He was so fuckin' hammered
he drove the wrong car home.
And the best part
about it is,
the fuckin' state trooper
was so embarrassed
he didn't do anything.
He'd been drivin' around all
night in my uncle's Chevelle,
lookin' for the house.
All right, Chuck,
what the fuck is
the point of your story?
He got away.
That's the point.
Well, question...
BILLY: Come on. Stop.
I'm tryin' to
clarify somethin'.
You're embarrassing him.
You're too embarrassed to ask
it doesn't make any sense.
I does make sense,
if you listen to the story
and quit askin' questions.
Morgan, let's see if you can
get this one. I've got
a little story for you.
All right, there's
an old couple in bed,
Mary and Paddie.
And they wake up on
the morning of their
50th anniversary.
And Mary looks over
and gazes adoringly at Paddie.
She's like,
"Oh, Jesus, Paddie.
"You're such a good-looking
feller. I love ya.
"I want to give ya
a little present.
"Anything your
little heart desires,
I'm goin' to give it to ya.
"What would ya like?"
Paddie's like,
"Oh, gee, Mary.
That's a very sweet offer.
"Now, in 50 years,
there's one thing
that's been missing,
"and, uh, I would like you
to give me a blow job.
"I would like for it."
And Mary's like, "All right."
She takes her teeth out,
puts 'em in the glass.
And she gives him a blow job.
Afterwards, Paddie's like,
"Yeah, geez, now that's
what I've been missin'.
"That was the most beautiful,
earth-shattering thing ever!
"Beautiful, Mary!
I love ya!
"Is there anything
that I can do for you?"
Mary looks up to him
and she goes,
"Give us a kiss."
Oh!
CHUCKIE: Oh, my God!
(ALL CHUCKLING)
CHUCKIE: That's filthy.
MORGAN: It's not that filthy.
I've heard filthier.
(LAUGHING)
Get off of me!
Al right. See you guys later.
All right.
Take it easy, Bill.
So, Skylar,
thanks for comin' by.
Changed my opinion
of Harvard people.
Oh, well you don't want to
rush to judgment on that one,
'cause they're not all
like me.
Oh. I'm sure.
It was nice to meet ya.
Oh.
Take it easy.
Slowly back away.
Oh, come on. Brother.
I don't know
what you're doin', dude.
You're givin' us a ride.
What the fuck
do I look like to you?
Come on, Chuck.
You're walkin', bitch.
Will's takin' the car.
All right, thanks, sucker.
I appreciate it.
I don't know what you're
gettin' all serious about.
You're droppin' me off first.
Dude, it's really
out of the way.
Oh, okay. Just 'cause you
don't have to sleep in your
one-room palace tonight...
Don't start
thinkin' you're bad.
All right, all right, come on.
Hey, wait a minute.
You said we were
gonna see your place.
No, not tonight.
Oh, no, not tonight.
Not any other night.
He knows once you see
that little shit-hole
he's gettin'
dropped like a bad habit.
But I wanted to meet
your brothers.
No, we're gonna do that
another time.
All right.
Need them keys.
The stewardess hears this
and goes haulin' ass
down the aisle.
And I yell,
"Don't forget the coffee."
(CHUCKLES)
No shit!
You didn't say that.
For Christ's sake,
Marty, it's a joke.
I know someone that
actually happened to, Marty.
A joke?
Gerry. Have trouble
findin' the place?
Hi.
No, I took a cab.
Timmy, this is Gerry.
We went to college together.
How you doin'?
Nice to meet ya.
Pleased to meet you.
Can I get you a beer?
Um, no, just a Perrier.
That's French
for club soda.
Huh, club soda, yeah.
Couple of sandwiches, too.
Sure.
Pt it on my tab.
You ever plannin'
on payin' your tab?
Yeah, chief, got the winning
lottery ticket right here.
What's the jackpot?
Twelve million.
I don't think
that'll cover it.
SEAN: Yeah, but it will cover
your sex change operation.
Nuts?
No, thank you.
So, you wanted
to talk about Will.
Well, it seems
to be going well.
I think so.
Have you talked to him
at all about his future?
No, we haven't gotten
into that yet. We're still
bangin' away at the past.
Well, maybe you should.
My phone's been ringing
off the hook with job offers.
What kind?
Cutting-edge mathematics,
think tanks.
The kind of place
where a mind like Will's
is given free rein.
That's great that there are
offers, but I don't really
think he's ready for that.
I'm not sure
you understand, Sean.
What don't I understand?
TIMMY: Here you go, guys.
Thanks, Tim.
Yeah, thank you.
Just so you don't
get sticky fingers, huh.
Tim, can you help us?
We're tryin'
to settle a bet.
Uh-oh.
You ever heard of Jonas Salk?
Sure. Cured polio.
You ever heard
of Albert Einstein?
Hey.
(POOL BALLS CLATTERING)
GERRY: How about Gerald
Lambeau? Ever heard of him?
No.
Thank you, Tim.
TIMMY: So who won the bet?
I did.
(POOL BALLS CLATTERING)
(SIGHS)
This isn't about me, Sean.
I'm nothing compared
to this young man.
You ever hear of
Gerald Lambeau?
In 1905 there were hundreds
of professors renowned for
their study of the universe.
But it was a 26-year-old
Swiss patent clerk,
doing physics in his spare
time, who changed the world.
Can you imagine if Einstein
would have given that up
just to get drunk
with his buddies
in Vienna every night?
We all would have
lost something.
Tim would never
have heard of him.
Pretty dramatic, Gerry.
No, it isn't, Sean.
This boy has that gift.
He just hasn't
got the direction,
but we can give that to him.
Hey, Gerry, in the 1960s,
there was a young man
graduated from
University of Michigan.
Did some brilliant work
in mathematics.
Specifically,
bounded harmonic functions.
Then he went on to Berkeley.
He was assistant professor.
Showed amazing potential.
Then he moved to Montana, and
he blew the competition away.
Yeah, so who was he?
Ted Kaczynski.
Haven't heard of him.
Hey, Timmy!
TIMMY: Yo!
Who's Ted Kaczynski?
TIMMY: Unabomber.
That's exactly
what I'm talking about.
We gotta give
this kid direction.
Yeah...
He can contribute to
the world, and we can
help him do that.
Direction's one thing.
Manipulation's another.
Sean...
We have to let him find...
Sean, I'm not sitting at home
every night
twisting my mustache
and hatching a plan
to ruin this boy's life!
I was doing
advanced mathematics
when I was 18,
and it still took me
over 20 years to do something
worthy of a Fields Medal.
Well, maybe he doesn't want
what you want.
There's more to life
than a fuckin'
Fields Medal.
This is too important, Sean,
and it's above
personal rivalry.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute, Gerry.
Let's talk about the boy.
Why don't we give him time
to figure out what he wants?
That's a wonderful theory,
Sean. It worked wonders
for you, didn't it?
Yeah, it did,
you arrogant fuckin' prick!
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry
that I came here today.
I came here out of courtesy.
I wanted to keep you
in the loop.
Nice to be in the loop.
The boy's in a meeting
right now I set up for him
over at McNeil.
Well, Will,
I'm not exactly sure
what you mean.
We've already
offered you a position.
Nobody in this town works
without a retainer, guys.
You think you can
find somebody who does,
you have my blessing.
But I think we all know
that person is not gonna
represent you
as well as I can.
MAN: Will, our offer
is $84,000 a year.
(SIGHS) Retainer!
Retainer.
You want us to give you
cash right now?
Whoa-ho-ho. Easy...
Now, I didn't say that.
Allegedly,
your situation, for you,
would be concurrently
improved if I had
$200 in my back pocket
right now.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I don't think I can...
Larry?
I've got $73.
Will you take a check?
Let me tell you somethin'.
You're suspect.
Yeah, you. I don't know
what your reputation is
in this town,
but after the shit
you tried to pull today,
you can bet
I'll be lookin' into you.
Now, any business
we have heretofore,
you can speak with
my aforementioned attorney.
Good day, gentlemen.
And until that day comes,
keep your ear
to the grindstone.
MAN: Taxi, taxi.
How's it goin'?
Fine.
Yeah.
Good.
You want some help?
No!
Come on. Give me
one little peek, and we'll
go to the batting cages.
No.
It is actually important
that I learn this.
It's really important.
To me, okay?
All right. All right.
Why don't we just
hang out here all day?
Yes, why don't we?
All right, Mr. Nosey parker.
(CHUCKLES)
Seeing as you're intent
on breaking my balls.
Let me ask you a question.
All right.
Do you have
a photographic memory?
I don't know.
I just kind of remember.
You know, I mean,
how do you remember
your phone number?
You know, you just do.
(LAUGHS)
Well, have you studied
organic chemistry?
A little bit.
Oh, just for fun?
Yeah, for kicks.
Yeah, it's so much fun
studying organic chemistry.
Are you mad?
(LAUGHS)
Have you completely
lost your mind?
Nobody studies it for fun.
It's not a necessity,
especially for
someone like you.
Someone like me?
Yeah.
Someone who divides
their time, fairly evenly,
between batting cages
and bars.
I would hardly say
it was a necessity.
Oh.
You know, there are very
smart people here at Harvard.
And even they have to study,
because this is really hard.
And yet...
(SIREN WAILING)
You do it so easily.
I don't understand. I...
I don't understand
how your mind works.
Did you play the piano?
I want to talk about this.
No, I'm trying
to explain it to you.
Do you play the piano?
Yeah, a bit.
All right, so when you look at
a piano, you see Mozart.
I see Chopsticks.
All right, well,
Beethoven, okay?
He looked at a piano,
and it just made sense
to him. He could just play.
So what are you saying?
You play the piano?
No, not a lick.
I mean, I look at a piano,
I see a bunch of keys,
three pedals
and a box of wood.
But Beethoven, Mozart...
They saw it.
They could just play.
I couldn't paint you
a picture. I probably can't
hit the ball out of Fenway,
and I can't play the piano.
But you can do my
o-chem paper in under an hour.
Right. Well, I mean, when
it came to stuff like that,
I could always just play.
That's the best
I can explain it.
Come here. I have
to tell you something.
Huh?
I have to tell you something.
Oh.
Well...
It's not fair.
What's not fair? What?
I've been here for four years,
and I've only just found you.
Well, you found me.
SKYLAR: Are you awake?
No.
Yes, you are.
Will, come to
California with me.
What?
I want you to come
to California with me.
You sure about that?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, but how do you know?
I don't know.
I just know.
Yeah, but how do you know?
I know because I feel it.
Because that's a really
serious thing you're saying.
I know.
You could be in California
next week...
And you might find out
something about me
you don't like and...
You know, maybe you wish
you hadn't said that,
but, you know,
it's such a serious thing,
you can't take it back.
And now I'm stuck in
California
with someone
that doesn't really want to
be with me,
just wish they had
a take-back.
A what? What's a take-back?
I don't want a take-back.
I just want you to come
to California with me.
Well, I can't go to
California with you, so...
Why not?
Well, one, because
I got a job here.
And, two,
because I live here.
Look, um, if you don't
love me, you should just
tell me because...
I'm not sayin'
I don't love you.
Then why?
Why won't you come?
What are you so scared of?
What am I so scared of?
Well, what aren't
you scared of?
You live in this safe
little world where
no one challenges you...
And you're scared shitless,
to do anything else...
Don't tell me about my world.
I mean, you just want to have
your little fling with the guy
from the other side of town.
Then you're gonna go off
to Stanford. You're gonna
marry some rich prick
who your parents
will approve of.
And just sit around with
the other trust fund babies
and talk about how you
went slummin', too, once.
Why are you saying this?
What is your obsession
with this money?
My father died when I was 13,
and I inherited this money.
You don't think every day
I wake up, and I wish that
I could give it back.
That I would give it back
in a second
if it meant I could
have one more day with him.
But I can't,
and that's my life,
and I deal with it.
So don't put your shit on me
when you're the one
that's afraid.
I'm afraid?
What am I afraid of?
What the fuck am I afraid of?
You're afraid of me.
You're afraid that
I won't love you back.
You know what?
I'm afraid, too.
But fuck it, I want to
give it a shot. At least
I'm honest with you.
I'm not honest with you?
No, what about
your 12 brothers?
All right.
(BELT BUCKLE JINGLES)
No, you're not going.
You're not leaving.
What do you want to know?
That I don't have 12 brothers?
That I'm a fuckin' orphan?
You don't want to hear that.
I didn't know that.
You don't want to hear...
I didn't know it.
I got fuckin' cigarettes
put out on me
when I was a little kid.
Honey,
I didn't know that.
That this isn't
fuckin' surgery.
The motherfucker stabbed me.
You don't want to hear
that shit, Skylar!
I do want to hear that.
Don't tell me
you want to hear that shit!
I want to hear it
because I wanna help you...
Help me? What the fuck?
What do I got,
a fuckin' sign on my back
that says, "Save me?"
No.
Do I look like I need that?
No, God, I just want to be
with you...
Don't bullshit me!
Because I love you.
I love you!
Don't you fuckin'
bullshit me!
(SOBBING)
I love you.
I want to hear you say
that you don't love me.
Because if you say that,
then I won't call you...
(SNIFFLES)
And I won't be in your life.
(SOBBING)
(SOBS)
I don't love you.
You do.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CRYING)
(GIGGLING)
Most people never get to see
how brilliant they can be.
They don't find teachers
that believe in them.
They get convinced
they're stupid.
I hope you appreciate
what he's doing,
because I've seen how much
he enjoys working with you,
not against you.
Hello, Will.
Tom, can you get us
some coffee?
Sure.
Now, let's see.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Good. This is correct.
I see you used Maclaurin here.
WILL: Yeah, I don't know what
you call it, but...
This can't be right.
This would be
very embarrassing.
Did you ever consider...
I'm pretty sure it's right.
Hey, look, can we
do this at Sean's office
from now on?
Because I got to knock off
work to come here and
the commute is killin' me.
Yeah, sure. But did you
think of the possibility...
That's right.
It's right.
Just take it home with you.
What happened
at the McNeil meeting?
I couldn't go.
I had a date.
So I sent my
chief negotiator.
On your own time, you can do
whatever you like, Will.
But when I set up a meeting
with my associates,
and you don't show up,
it reflects poorly on me.
Then don't set up
any more meetings.
I won't.
I'll cancel 'em.
I'll give you a job myself.
I just wanted you to see
what was out there.
Maybe I don't want to spend
the rest of my fuckin' life
sitting around
explainin' shit to people.
I think you could show me
some appreciation.
A little appreciation?
Do you know how easy
this is for me?
Do you have any fuckin' idea
how easy this is?
This is a fuckin' joke.
I'm sorry you can't do this.
I really am.
Because I wouldn't have to
fuckin' sit here and watch you
fumble around and fuck it up.
Then you'd have more time
to sit around and get drunk
instead, wouldn't you?
You're right.
This is probably
a total waste of my time.
You're right, Will.
I can't do this proof.
But you can.
And when it comes to that,
it's only about just a handful
of people in the world
who can tell the difference
between you and me.
But I'm one of them.
Sorry.
Yeah, so am I.
Most days I wish
I never met you.
(EXHALES)
Because then I could
sleep at night.
I didn't have to walk around
with the knowledge
that there was
someone like you out there.
(DOOR CLOSES)
I didn't have to watch you
throw it all away.
(DOG BARKING)
(PLUNKING NOTES)
Bill, hold it.
Did you hear that?
(MAN MOANING)
Morgan!
(WOMAN GROANING)
If you're watchin' pornos in
my mom's room again, I'm gonna
give you a fuckin' beatin'!
(WOMAN MOANING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(FOOTSTEPS RUNNING
DOWNSTAIRS)
(PANTING)
What's up, fellas?
Morgan, why don't you jerk off
in your own fuckin' house.
That's fuckin' filthy.
I don't have a VCR
In my house.
Come on.
Not in my glove.
I didn't use the glove.
That's my
Little League glove.
What do you want me
to do?
I mean, what's wrong
with you?
You'll hump
a baseball glove?
I didn't...
I just used it
for cleanup.
(LAUGHING)
Stop jerkin' off
in my mother's room.
Is there another
VCR In the house?
It's just sad, bro.
So why do you think
I should work for the
National Security Agency?
Well, you'd be working
on the cutting edge.
You'd be exposed to
the kind of technology
that you wouldn't see
anywhere else,
because we've classified it.
Superstring theory,
chaos math,
advanced algorithms.
Code breaking.
Well, that's one aspect
of what we do.
Oh, come on.
I mean, that is what you do.
You guys handle 80% of
the intelligence workload.
You're seven times
the size of the CIA.
We don't like to brag
about that, Will,
but you're exactly right.
So the way I see it,
the question isn't,
"Why should you work
for the NSA?"
The question is,
"Why shouldn't you?"
Why shouldn't
I work for the NSA?
(CHUCKLES)
That's a tough one,
but I'll take a shot.
Say I'm workin' at the NSA
and somebody puts
a code on my desk.
Something no one else
can break.
Maybe I take a shot at it
and maybe I break it.
I'm real happy with myself
because I did my job well.
But maybe that code was
the location of
some rebel army
in north Africa
or the Middle East.
And once they have
that location,
they bomb
the village where
the rebels are hiding.
Fifteen hundred people
that I never met, never had
no problem with, get killed.
Now the politicians
are saying,
"Oh, send in the Marines
to secure the area,"
'cause they don't give a shit.
It won't be their kid
over there gettin' shot,
just like it wasn't them when
their number got called
'cause they were up
on the National Guard.
It'll be some kid from Southie
over there takin' shrapnel
in the ass.
He comes back
to find the plant
the used to work at
got exported to the country
he just got back from,
and the guy who put
the shrapnel in his ass
got his old job
'cause he'll work for 15 cents
a day and no bathroom breaks.
Meanwhile, he realizes the
only reason he was over there
in the first place
was so that we could install
a government that would
sell us oil at a good price.
And of course,
the oil companies used
a little skirmish over there
to scare up
domestic oil prices.
A cute little ancillary
benefit for them,
but it ain't helpin' my buddy
at 2.50 a gallon.
They're takin'
their sweet time bringin'
the oil back, of course.
Maybe they even took
the liberty to hire
an alcoholic skipper,
who likes to drink martinis
and fuckin' play slalom
with the icebergs.
It ain't too long till
he hits one, spills the oil
and kills all the sea life
in the North Atlantic.
So now my buddy's out of work,
he can't afford to drive,
so he's walkin' to
the fuckin' job interviews.
Which sucks because
the shrapnel in his ass
is givin' him
chronic hemorrhoids.
And meanwhile, he's starvin',
'cause every time he tries
to get a bite to eat,
the only blue plate special
they're servin'
is North Atlantic scrod
with Quaker State.
So what did I think?
I'm holdin' out
for somethin' better.
I figure, fuck it.
While I'm at it, why not
just shoot my buddy,
take his job,
give it to his sworn enemy,
hike up gas prices, bomb
a village, club a baby seal,
hit the hash pipe
and join the National Guard?
I can be
elected president.
You feel like
you're alone, Will?
What?
Do you have a soul mate?
Do I have a...
Define that.
Somebody who challenges you.
Uh, Chuckie.
No, Chuckie's family.
He'd lie down
in fuckin' traffic for you.
I'm talking about someone
who opens up things for you,
touches your soul.
I got... I got...
Who?
I got plenty.
Well, name 'em.
Shakespeare, Nietzsche,
Frost, O'Connor,
Kant, Pope, Locke...
That's great.
They're all dead.
Not to me they're not.
You don't have
a lot of dialogue with them.
You can't give back
to them, Will.
Not without some serious
smelling salts and a heater.
That's what I'm saying.
You'll never have that kind
of relationship in a world
where you're always afraid
to take the first step,
because all you see
is every negative thing
10 miles down the road.
You gonna take the
professor's side on this?
Don't give me a line of shit.
No.
Look I didn't want
the job.
It's not about the job.
I don't care if you work
for the government.
But you can do
anything you want.
You are bound by nothing.
What are you
passionate about?
What do you want?
There are guys
who work their entire life
layin' brick,
so their kids have a chance
at the opportunities
you have here.
I didn't ask for this.
No.
You were born with it,
so don't cop out behind,
"I didn't ask for this."
What do you mean,
cop out? What's wrong
with layin' brick?
Nothing.
There's nothin' wrong.
That's somebody's home
I'm buildin'.
Right. My dad
laid brick, okay?
Busted his ass so
I could have an education.
Exactly. That's
an honorable profession.
What's wrong with
fixin' somebody's car?
Someone will get to work
the next day because of me.
There's honor in that.
Yeah, there is, Will.
There is honor in that.
And there's honor in,
you know, takin'
that 40-minute train ride,
so those college kids
could come in in the morning
and their floors are clean,
and their wastebaskets
are empty. That's real work.
That's right.
You're right,
and that's honorable.
I'm sure that's why
you took that job.
I mean, for the honor of it.
I just have a little
question here. You could be
a janitor anywhere.
Why did you work at the most
prestigious technical college
in the whole fuckin' world?
Why did you sneak
around at night and finish
other people's formulas,
that only one or two people
in the world could do,
and then lie about it?
'Cause I don't see
a lot of honor in that, Will.
So what do you
really wanna do?
I wanna be a shepherd.
Really?
I wanna move up to Nashua,
get a nice little spread,
get some sheep
and tend to them.
Maybe you should go do that.
What?
You know,
if you're gonna jerk off,
why don't you just
do it at home
with a moist towel?
You're chuckin' me?
Yeah, get the fuck outta here.
Hey, no, no, no,
time's not up yet.
Yeah, it is.
I'm not leavin'. No.
Listen, you're not gonna
answer my questions,
you're wastin'
my fuckin' time.
What? I thought
we were friends.
What you mean you...
Playtime's over, okay?
Why are you
kickin' me out, Sean?
I mean, what...
I mean...
You're lecturin' me on life?
Look at you,
you fuckin' burnout.
What winds your clock?
Workin' with you.
Where's your soul mate?
You wanna talk about
soul mates? Where is she?
Dead.
That's right.
She's fuckin' dead.
She fuckin' dies and
you just cash in your chips
and you walk away?
Hey, at least
I played a hand.
Oh, you played a hand
and you lost.
You lost a big fuckin' hand.
And some people will lose
a big hand like that
and have the sack
to ante up again.
Look at me.
What do you wanna do?
You and your bullshit.
You got a bullshit answer
for everybody.
But I ask you a very simple
question and you can't give me
a straight answer,
because you don't know.
See ya, Bo-Peep.
Fuck you.
You're the shepherd.
Shepherd.
(WHISPERS)
White little prick.
I just wanted to,
you know, um,
call you up,
uh, before you left, um...
I've been takin' all
these jobs interviews
and stuff,
so I'm not gonna be just
a construction worker.
Will, you know I never
really cared about that.
Yeah.
I love you.
Will?
You take care.
Someone's always
coming around here
Trailing some new kill
Bye.
Says, I seen your picture
on a
Hundred-dollar bill
What's a game of chance
to you
To him is one
Of real skill
So glad to meet you
Angeles
Picking up the ticket
Shows there's money
to be made
Go on, lose the gamble
That's the history
Of the trade
Did you add up
All the cards left to play
To zero
And sign up with evil
Angeles
Don't start with me
trying now
Will, come on. Will!
Will, that's it!
We're done!
I'm sitting in your office
and the boy isn't here.
Well, it's 10 past 5:00.
An hour and
10 minutes late.
Well, if he doesn't show up
and I file a report saying
he wasn't here
and he goes back to jail,
he won't be on
my conscience.
Okay. Fine.
What's up?
Thanks.
Ah!
Ah! Fuck, that's good.
(SNIFFLES)
So how's your lady?
Ah, she's gone.
Gone? Gone where?
Med school.
Medical school in California.
Really?
Yeah.
When was this?
It was, like, a week ago.
That sucks.
So, uh, when are you done
with those meetings?
I think the week
after I'm 21.
Yeah? They gonna hook ya up
with a job or what?
Yeah, fucking sit in a room
and do long division
for the next 50 years.
Nah, probably make
some nice bank though.
I'm gonna be
a fucking lab rat.
Better than this shit.
Way outta here.
What do I want a way
outta here for?
I mean, I'm gonna fucking
live here the rest of my life.
You know, be neighbors.
You know, have little kids.
Fucking take 'em
to Little League together
up Foley Field.
Look, you're my best
friend, so don't take
this the wrong way but...
In 20 years, if
you're still living here,
coming over to my house
to watch the Patriots games,
still working construction,
I'll fucking kill ya.
That's not a threat.
That's a fact.
I'll fucking kill ya.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
Look, you got something
none of us have.
Oh, come on!
Why is it always this?
I fucking owe it to myself
to do this or that.
What if I don't want to?
No, no, no. Fuck you.
You don't owe it to yourself.
You owe it to me,
'cause tomorrow I'm gonna
wake up and I'll be 50,
and I'll still
be doing this shit.
That's all right.
That's fine.
I mean, you're sitting on
a winning lottery ticket.
You're too much
of a pussy to cash it in,
and that's bullshit.
'Cause I'd do
fucking anything
to have what you got.
So would any of
these fucking guys.
Be an insult to us
if you're still
here in 20 years.
Hanging around here
is a fucking waste
of your time.
You don't know that.
I don't?
No. You don't know that.
Oh, I don't know that.
Let me tell you what
I do know.
Every day
I come by your house,
and I pick you up.
We go out and have
a few drinks and few
laughs, and it's great.
You know what the
best part of my day is?
It's for about 10 seconds,
from when I pull up
to the curb and when
I get to your door.
'Cause I think
maybe I'll get up there
and I'll knock on the door
and you won't be there.
No "good-bye,"
no "see ya later,"
no nothing. You just left.
I don't know much,
but I know that.
This is a disaster, Sean.
I brought you in here
because I wanted you
to help me with the boy,
not to run him out.
I know what
I'm doing with the boy.
I don't care if you have
a rapport with the boy!
I don't care if
you have a few laughs,
even at my expense.
But don't you dare undermine
what I'm trying to do here.
Undermine?
This boy is at
a fragile point right now.
I do understand.
He is at a fragile point,
okay? He's got problems.
What problems does he have,
Sean?
That he's better off as
a janitor, that he's
better off in jail?
Better hanging out with
a bunch of retarded gorillas?
Why do you think he does
that, Gerry? Do you have
any fucking clue why? Hmm?
He can handle the problems.
He can handle the work.
He obviously handled you.
Gerry, listen to me.
Why is he hiding?
Why doesn't
he trust anybody?
Because the first thing
that happened to him,
he was abandoned by
the people who were supposed
to love him the most.
Oh, come on, don't give me
that Freudian crap.
No, listen, Gerry, why does he
hang out with those retarded
gorillas, as you call them?
Because any one of them,
if he asked them to,
would take a fucking bat
to your head, okay?
That's called loyalty.
Yeah, that's very touching.
And who's he handling?
He pushes people away
before they have
a chance to leave him.
It's a defense
mechanism, all right?
And for 20 years, he's been
alone because of that.
And if you push him right now,
it's gonna be the same thing
all over again.
And I'm not gonna
let that happen to him.
Don't you do that Sean.
What, Gerry?
Don't you do that.
Don't infect him with the idea
that it's okay to quit, that
it's okay to be a failure.
Because it's not okay, Sean!
And if you're angry at me
for being successful,
for being what you
could have been, Sean...
I'm not angry at you, Gerry.
Oh, yes, you're angry
at me, Sean.
You resent me,
but I'm not gonna apologize
for any success I've had.
You're angry at me for doing
what you could have done!
But ask yourself, Sean,
ask yourself
if you want Will to feel
that way, if you want him
to feel like a failure?
You arrogant shit!
That's why I don't come
to the goddamn reunions,
'cause I can't
stand that look in your eye.
You know? That condescending,
embarrassed look.
Oh, come on, Sean.
You think I'm a failure.
I know who I am.
I'm proud of what I do.
It was a conscious choice.
I didn't fuck up!
And you and your cronies think
I'm some sort of pity case.
You and your kiss-ass chorus
following you around going,
"The Fields Medal!
The Fields Medal!"
Why are you still so
fucking afraid of failure?
It's about my medal, isn't it?
Oh, God, I could go
home and get it for you.
You can have it.
Oh, please don't.
You know what, Gerry,
shove the medal up your
fucking ass, all right?
'Cause I don't give
a shit about your medal,
because I knew you before
you were a mathematical god,
when you were pimple-faced
and homesick
and didn't know what side of
the bed to piss on.
Yeah, you were smarter
than me then and you're
smarter than me now.
So don't blame me for
how your life turned out.
It's not my fault.
I don't blame you!
It's not about you!
You mathematical dick!
It's about the boy!
He's a good kid! And I won't
see you fuck him up
like you're trying to fuck up
me right now.
I won't see you make him
feel like a failure, too!
He won't be a failure, Sean!
But if you push him, Gerry!
If you ride him!
Sean, I am what I am today
because I was pushed
and because I learned
to push myself.
He's not you!
You get that?
I can come back.
No, come in.
Uh, I was just leaving.
A lot of that stuff goes back
a long way between me and him.
You know. Not about you.
(PAPER RUSTLES)
What is that?
This is your file.
I have to send it back to
the judge for evaluation.
Oh.
Hey, you're not
gonna fail me, are you?
What's it say?
Wanna read it?
Why?
Have you had any, uh,
experience with that?
Twenty years of counseling.
Yeah, I've seen some
pretty awful shit.
WILL: I mean, have you had
any experience with that?
Personally?
Yeah.
Yeah, I have.
It sure ain't good.
My father was an alcoholic.
Mean fucking drunk.
He'd come home hammered,
looking to wail
on somebody.
So I'd provoke him so
he wouldn't go after my mother
and little brother.
Interesting nights
when he wore his rings.
He used to just
put a wrench,
a stick and a belt
on the table
and just say, "Choose."
Well, I gotta
go with the belt there, Vanna.
I used to go with the wrench.
Why the wrench?
'Cause fuck him, that's why.
Your foster father?
Yeah.
So, uh, what is it,
like, Will has
an attachment disorder?
Is it all that stuff?
Fear of abandonment?
Is that why I broke up
with Skylar?
I didn't know you had.
Yeah, I did.
You wanna talk about it?
No.
Hey, Will,
I don't know a lot.
You see this?
All this shit?
It's not your fault.
(WHISPERS)
Yeah, I know that.
Look at me, son.
It's not your fault.
I know.
No. It's not
your fault.
I know.
No, no, you don't.
It's not your fault.
Hmm?
I know.
It's not your fault.
All right.
(WHISPERS)
It's not your fault.
Don't fuck with me.
Don't fuck with me, all right?
Don't fuck with me, Sean,
not you.
It's not your fault.
(SOBS)
(WHISPERS)
It's not your fault.
(SOBS)
My God.
My God! I'm so sorry!
My God!
(SOBBING CONTINUES)
Fuck them, okay?
Can I help you?
Yeah, I'm Will Hunting.
I'm here about a position.
Could you just have
a seat for a moment?
MAN: Yes, there's a
Mr. Hunting in the lobby.
Which one did you take?
I was over at McNeil.
It's one of the jobs
the professor set me up with.
I haven't told him yet,
but I went down there
and talked to my boss.
My new boss.
He seemed like a good guy.
Is that what you want?
Yeah, you know, I think so.
Well, good for you.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Time's up.
So that's it?
So we're done?
Yeah, that's it.
You're done.
You're a free man.
Well, um, I just want you
to know, Sean, that...
You're welcome, Will.
So, you know, I hope
we keep in touch, you know.
Yeah, me, too.
I'll be traveling
around a bit. It'll be
a little hard,
but I've got an answering
machine at the college
I'll be checking in with.
So, here's the number.
You call that.
I'll get back
to you right away.
Yeah, you know,
I figured I'm just gonna
put my money back
on the table and see
what kind of cards I get.
You do what's in your heart,
son. You'll be fine.
Thank you, Sean.
Ah.
Thank you, Will.
Hey, does this violate the
patient-doctor relationship?
No. Only if you
grab my ass.
(BOTH CHUCKLES)
Take care.
You, too.
Yeah.
Hey.
Good luck, son.
MORGAN: Two beers.
What's up?
Did you guys go?
No. I had to talk him down.
Why didn't you yoke him?
Little Morgan's
got a lot of scrap to him.
People try to whip
his ass every week.
Fucking kid won't back down.
MORGAN: What are you
saying about me?
Was I talking to you?
None of your fucking business.
(DOOR OPENS)
CHUCKIE: Go get me a beer.
MORGAN: I ordered two beers!
Hey, asshole.
What, bitch?
Happy birthday.
Thought we forgot, huh, bitch?
Come on!
I'm going, I'm going.
All right. Who's first?
Come on, motherfucker!
Who's first?
Oh, Danny boy
Here's your present.
Come on, bro.
What?
Well, we knew you had to get
back and forth to Cambridge
for your new job.
I knew I wasn't gonna
fucking drive you
every day, so...
Morgan wanted
to get you a "T" pass.
That's not what I was saying!
But, uh, you're 21 now.
You're legally allowed to
drink, so we figured the best
thing for you, kid, was a car.
How do you like it?
This is like...
It's the ugliest fucking car
I've ever seen in my life.
Come on, brother.
How'd you guys do this?
You know, me and Bill
scraped together the parts,
and Morgan was out panhandling
for change every day.
I had the router to do
all the bodywork.
Yeah, I have a fucking job,
too, brother.
Guy's been up my ass for
two years about a job. I had
to let him help with the car.
So you finally got a job,
huh, Morgan?
Yeah, had one.
Now I'm fucked again.
So what is it?
A lawn mower?
What do ya got?
BILLY: It's a straight
fucking six.
MORGAN: Me and Bill rebuilt
this engine ourselves here.
It's a good car.
The engine's good.
Engine's good.
Happy 21, Will.
Happy 21, brother.
Hi.
Come on in.
Sean, I, um...
Me, too, Gerry.
Yeah. Good.
I heard you're
taking some time.
Yeah. Travel a little bit,
maybe write.
GERRY: So where are you going?
India and China
and Baltimore.
Oh.
You know when
you'll be back?
Oh.
I got this flyer
the other day.
It says, uh, class of '72
is having a reunion
in six months.
Yeah, I got
one of those, too.
Why don't you come?
I'll buy ya a drink.
The drinks at
those things are free.
I know, Gerry.
I was being ironical.
(LAUGHING)
Oh. How about
a drink right now?
Yeah. It's a good idea.
Come on.
This one's on me.
I got the winner
right here, pal.
Oh!
Yes, sir, this is the one.
This is my ticket
to paradise.
GERRY: Sean, do you know what
the odds are against
winning the lottery?
What? 4-1?
About 30 million to one.
I still have a shot, you know?
(LAUGHS)
GERRY: Yes.
Just about as big chance as
you being hit by lightning
here on the staircase
right now.
SEAN: It's a possibility, too.
I mean, 32 million.
If you look at the size...
GERRY: Sean.
(BELL TOLLING)
(HORN HONKS)
(KNOCKING)
Will!
Will?
(HORN HONKS)
He's not there.
I'll fake it
through the day
WILL: Sean, if the professor
calls about that job,
just tell him sorry,
I had to go see about a girl.
Will.
Son of a bitch.
He stole my line.
Two tickets torn in half
And a lot
Of nothing to do
Do you miss me
Miss Misery
Like you say you do
I know you'd rather
see me gone
Than to see me
The way
That I am
But I am
In your life anyway
Next door TV's flashing blue
Frames on the wall
It's a comedy
Of errors, you see
It's about taking a fall
To vanish into
Oblivion
It's easy to do
And I try to be
But you know me
I come back
When you want me to
Do you miss me
Miss Misery
Like you say you do
Gonna find my baby
Gonna hold her tight
Gonna grab
Some afternoon delight
My motto's always been
When it's right, it's right
Why wait until the middle
Of a cold, dark night
When everything's a little
clearer in the light of day
And we know the night is
always gonna be here anyway
Thinking of you
is working up an appetite
Looking forward to
A little afternoon delight
Rubbing sticks
and stones together
Make the sparks ignite
And the thought of loving
you is getting so exciting
Skyrockets in flight
Afternoon delight
Started out this morning
Feeling so polite
I always thought a fish
could not be caught
Who didn't bite
But you got
some bait a-waiting
And I think I might
Like nibbling a little
afternoon delight
Skyrockets in flight
Afternoon delight
Be waiting for me, baby
When I come around
We can make a lot of loving
'Fore the sun goes down
Thinking of you's
Working up an appetite
Looking forward to
A little afternoon delight
Rubbing sticks
and stones together
Make the sparks ignite
And the thought of loving
you is getting so exciting
Skyrockets in flight
Afternoon delight