[ Birds Twittering ]
[ Dog Barking
In The Distance ]
[ Airplane Flying Overhead ]
[ Murmuring ]
[ Bell Tolling ]
Mod f-x-square, d-x.
So please finish Percival
for next time.
I know many of you
had this as undergraduates,
but it won't hurt to brush up.
Thank you, Steven.
I also put
an advanced Fourier system
on the main hallway chalkboard.
I'm hoping that one of you
might prove it by the end
of the semester.
Now the person to do so will
not only be in my good graces,
but also go on
to fame and fortune...
by having their
accomplishment recorded
and their name printed...
in the auspicious M.I.T. Tech.
Former winners
include Nobel laureates,
Field's medal winners,
renowned astrophysicists
and lowly M.I.T. professors.
Well, that's all.
If you have any questions,
I'm sure that Tom
has the answers.
[ Applause ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Door Closes ]
♪♪ [ Country ]Hi, Will.
Kirsten, how you doing?I'm all right.
How are you?
Good.I didn't get on
Cathy last night.
No?No.
Why not?I don't know.
Cathy! What?
Why didn't you give me
none of that nasty
little hoochie-woochie...
you usually
throw at me? Oh, fuck you...
and your Irish curse,
Chuckie.
Like I'd waste my energy
spreadin' my legs for that
Tootsie Roll dick?
Go home
and give it a tug yourself. [ Boy ] Tootsie Roll!
T-Toots!
[ Chuckling ]
She's missin' a tooth,
Will.
She's got skin problems.
I don't--
Plus, it's like 5-to-2
Morgan ends up marryin' her,
you know what I mean?
There's only so many times
you can bang your friend's
future wife.
It's wrong.
Where you goin'?
- I'm gonna take off.
- Fuck you, you're takin' off.
It's, like, what, 10:00?
No, I'm tired.
Irish curse?
She don't know.
There ain't
no Irish curse.
[ Buffer Humming ]
[ Buffer Clicks ]
[ Chalk
Clicking Chalkboard ]
[ Chattering ]
Out! Stop
brushing me back.
Stop crowding the plate!
Which one will it be?
You're gonna get charged,
you know that?
You think I'm afraid of you,
you big fuck? You're crowdin'
the fuckin' plate.
Hey, uh, Casey's bouncin' up
a bar at Harvard next week.
We should go up there.
What are we gonna do
up there? I don't know.
We'll fuck up some smart kids.
Probably fit right in.
Ow! Fuckin' punk.
- Oh, what's up?
You still tough?
- Come on!
Come on. Come on.
That's it.
♪ I'd hold you forever
here ♪
♪ In my arms
Professor Lambeau?Yes?
I'm in your applied theories
class. We're all up at
the math and science building.
Come here.
It's Saturday.[ Chuckles ]
Unless you wanna have
a drink with me tonight.[ Chuckling ] Maybe.
We just couldn't wait
until Monday to find out.
Find out what?Who proved
the theorem.
This is correct.
Who did this?
Jack?It wasn't me.
- Nemesh?
- [ Chuckling ]
N-No way.
Come on, Joey, now!Billy, McNamara's up.
[ Chuckie ]
Come on, kid!
Joey, dig it out!
Dig it out!Son of a bitch!
Bring it down, Mac!
That's how to do it!
Attaboy! Take two, Mac.
Hey, Morgan, who's the girl
with the striped pants?
She's got a nice ass.
[ Morgan ]
Yeah, that's a real nice ass. Who's the guy she's with?
That fuckin' guinea.
I hate that little bitch.
Will knows him.
Yeah, I do.
Yeah, fuckin'
Carmine Scarpaglia.
That guy used to beat the shit
out of me in kindergarten.That guy?
Yeah.Mm-hmm.
Fuck this.
Let's get some food.
Oh, what, Morgan, you're not
gonna go talk to her?Fuck her. [ Burps ]
I could go
for a Whopper.Let's go to Kelly's.
Morgan, I'm not goin'
to Kelly's just 'cause
you like the take-out girl.
It's 15 minutes out of our way.What the fuck are we gonna do?
We can't spare 15 minutes?
[ Morgan ]
Double burger.
Chuck, I had
a double burger.
Would you shut the fuck up!
I know what you ordered.
I was there.
-So give me my fuckin' sandwich.
-What do you mean,
your sandwich? I bought it.
Morgan, how much money
you got on you?
I said I'd get change
when I get the snow cone.
I said that when we pulled up.
Give me my sandwich
and stop bein' a prick.
All right, well,
give me your fuckin' 16 cents
that you got on you now.
We'll put your fuckin' sandwich
on layaway. Here we go.
Keep it right up here for ya.
We'll put you on a program.
Every day you come in
with your six cents.
- At the end of the week,
you get your sandwich.
- Are you gonna be an asshole?
What am I, fuckin' sandwich
welfare? I think you should
establish a good line of credit.
Like how you bought
your couch-- payment plans.
Remember how your mother
brought in ten dollars
every day for a year.
She finally got her couch
Rent-A-Center style.
-Can I have my food, please?
- Here's your fuckin'
double burger.
- Whoa!
- Hey, hold up, Chuck.
- Slow it down.
- Who do we got?
I don't know yet.Hey, douche bag!
[ Glass Shattering ]Yeah, you, you skank face!
- Shut the fuck up.
- Get outta here.
- What are you worried about?
Why don't you lick
my love stick?
We seen the guy 15 minutes ago.
We should've fight him then.
We're eatin' our snacks now.
- Shut up, Morgan, you're goin'.
- I'm not goin'.
- So don't go.
- Fuckin' go, Morgan.
Let me tell you somethin'.
If you're not out there
in two fuckin' seconds,
when I'm done with them,
you're next.
Carmine, it's me, Will.
Remember, we went
to kindergarten together.
♪ Way down the street
there's a light in his place ♪
[ Birds Twittering ] ♪ He opens the door, he's
got that look on his face ♪♪
[ Bell Tolls ]
- Fuckin', let's go, man.
- Step on his fuckin' head.
Get his ass on the ground.
Stop that motherfucker.
Motherfucker, die!
Carter! Come on!
[ Groaning ]
[ Chuckie ]
Will! Will, come on!
Will, come on.
Let's go. Let's go.
Easy, brother, easy.
[ Chuckie ] Hey, fellas,
thanks for comin' out.Come here!
Whoa! Whoa!
[ Groans ]
[ Dispatcher On Walkie-talkie,
Indistinct ]
Ah. Fuck.
[ Students Chattering ]
Is it just my imagination,
or has my class
grown considerably?
Well, by no stretch
of my imagination...
do I believe
you've all come here
to hear me lecture.
Rather,
to ascertain the identity
of the mystery math magician.
So without further ado,
come forward, silent rogue,
and receive thy prize.
Well, I'm sorry to disappoint
my spectators, but...
it seems there will be
no unmasking here today.
However, uh, my colleagues and I
have conferred,
and there is a problem
on the board right now...
that took us
more than two years to prove.
So let this be said:
The gauntlet has been
thrown down,
but the faculty have answered
and answered with vigor.
[ Car Alarm Screeches ]
Hey, when's the arraignment?
Next week.
[ Chalk Clicking Chalkboard ]
[ Chattering ]
Sorry.
What are you doing?Sorry.
That's people's work.
You can't graffiti here.
Don't you walk away
from me!Hey, fuck you!
Oh, you're a clever one.
What's your name?
[ Door Closes ]
Oh, my God.
Looks right.
[ Cheering ]
Will, how retarded
do you gotta be to get
fired from that job?
I mean, how hard is it
to push a motherfuckin'
broom around?
Mitch, you got fired
from pushin' a fuckin' broom.
I got fired
'cause management
was restructuring.
Yeah, restructuring
the amount of retards
they had workin' for 'em.
Shut up. You get canned
more than tuna, bitch.
At least I got
a motherfuckin' job
right now, don't I?
Why'd you get fired, Will?
Come on.Management was restructuring.
- My uncle could probably
get you on a demo team.
- Can he do that?
You kiddin' me!
I asked you yesterday
if I could get a job.
And I told you "no"
yesterday.
- What's up, Casey?
- What's up, Case?
- What's up, Big Case?
♪♪ [ Rock ]
Let's sit over here.
All right. Let's go.
Oh, this is-- this is
a Harvard bar, huh?
I thought there'd be, like,
equations and shit on the wall.
I will take a pitcher
of the finest lager
in the house.
Time-out. I'm gonna have to bust
a little move on them Harvard
hotties down there at the bar.
Work some magic.Get some potion for us.
[ Giggling ]Oh, hello.
Oh, hello.
Hi. How are ya?Fine.
So, do you ladies, uh--Come here often?
Do I come here?
I come here a bit.
I'm here, you know,
from time to time.
Do you go
to school here?Yep.
Yeah, that's it. I think
I had a class with you.Oh, yeah. What class?
- History.
- Maybe.
Yes, I think
that's what it was.
You don't necessarily--
may not remember me.
You know, I like it here.
It doesn't mean 'cause
I go here, I'm a genius.
I am very smart.
Hey.
Hey, how's it goin'?
How are ya?Good. How ya doin'?
What class
did you say that was?
[ Together ]
History.Yeah.
Just history?
It must have been
a survey course then.
Yeah, it was.
It was surveys.Right.
You should check it out.
It's a good course.
It'd be a good class.
How'd you like
that course? You know, frankly,
I found that class, you know,
rather elementary.Elementary.
You know,
I don't doubt that it was.Yeah.
I, uh--
I remember that class.
It was, um--
It was just between
recess and lunch.
Clark, why don't you
go away?
- Why don't you relax?
- Why don't you go away?
I'm just havin' fun
with my new friend.Are we gonna have a problem?
No, no, no, no.
There's no problem here.
I was just hoping you might
give me some insight
into the evolution...
of the market economy
in the southern colonies.
My contention is that
prior to the Revolutionary War,
the economic modalities--
especially
in the southern colonies--
could most aptly
be characterized as...
agrarian
precapitalist.Let me tell you somethin'.
Of course that's
your contention. You're
a first-year grad student.
You just got finished readin'
some Marxian historian--
Pete Garrison, probably--
You're gonna be convinced
of that till next month
when you get to James Lemon.
Then you're gonna be talkin'
about how the economies
of Virginia and Pennsylvania...
were entrepreneurial
and capitalist way back in 1740.
That's gonna last until
next year. You're gonna be in
here regurgitatin' Gordon Wood,
talkin' about, you know,
the prerevolutionary utopia...
and the capital-forming effects
of military mobilization.
[ Scoffs ]
Well, as a matter of fact,
I won't,
because Wood
drastically underestimates
the impact of--
Wood drastically
underestimates the impact
of social distinctions...
predicated upon wealth,
especially inherited wealth.
You got that from Vickers'
Work in Essex County.
Page 98, right?
I read that too.
Were you gonna plagiarize
the whole thing for us?
Do you have any thoughts
of your own on this matter?
Or is that your thing?
You come into a bar.
You read some obscure passage.
Then pretend--
pawn it off as your own.
As your own idea
just to impress some girls?
Embarrass my friend?
See, the sad thing
about a guy like you is,
in 50 years,
you're gonna start doin'
some thinkin' on your own.
You're gonna come up
with the fact that there are
two certainties in life.
One: Don't do that.
And two: You dropped 150 grand
on a fuckin' education...
you could've got
for $1.50 in late charges
at the public library.
[ Chuckling ]
Yeah, but
I will have a degree,
and you'll be servin' my kids
fries at a drive through
on our way to a skiing trip.
Maybe, but at least
I won't be unoriginal.
If you have a problem with that,
we could step outside.
We could figure it out.
No, man, there's no problem.
It's cool.
It's cool?Yeah.
Cool.Damn right,
it's cool.
How do you like me now?
My boy's wicked smart.
I just spent three minutes
in this fuckin' place
and run into a barney, huh?
There it is.
Nice to meet you.They were fine, man.
I was gonna close the deal,
but then Chuck-- Billy
insulted one of 'em--
The heavyset girl said I had
a receding hairline, and I was
a few pounds overweight.
And I was, like,
"Go fuck yourself."
I swallowed a bug.
[ Chuckling ]
Hi.
You're an idiot. What?
You're an idiot.
I've been sitting
over there for 45 minutes...
waiting for you
to come and talk to me.
But I'm tired now,
and I have to go home.
I couldn't sit there anymore
waiting for you.
I'm Will.Skylar.
Skylar.Oh, and by the way,
that guy over there--
Michael Bolton clone--
He wasn't sitting with us,
so to speak.
I know. I kinda got
that impression.Good. Okay.
Well, I've got to go.
Gotta get up early
and waste some more money
on my overpriced education.
No, I didn't mean you.That's all right.
There's my number.
Maybe we can go out
for coffee sometime.
All right, yeah.
Maybe we can just get together
and eat a bunch of caramels.
What do you mean?When you think about it,
it's as arbitrary
as drinkin' coffee.Oh. Yeah. Okay.
Uh, right, then.
- Oh, come on. You're kidding.
- [ Giggling ]
Yo!
Fuck you, bitch!Fuck you.
There goes them fuckin' barneys
right now with his skiin' trip.Hold on.
We should've beat
that old bitch's ass.
Do you like apples?
Yeah.Yeah?
Well, I got her number!
How do you like
them apples?
[ Chuckling ]
♪ We arrived tonight
♪ The miles were over me
♪ I turned off the light
♪ So, come on, night
♪ Everyone who's gone
♪ Home to oblivion
♪ So come on home
♪ So come on by ♪
Come.
Excuse me?
Is this the Buildings
and Grounds office?
Yeah. What can I do
for you?
I just need the name
of a student who works here.
No students work for me. Could you please check?
I have this guy
who works in my building.
- He's about this high.
- Which one is your building?
- Two.
- Two. Building two.
Look, if anything was stolen,
I should know about it. No, it's nothing like that.
I just need his name.
I can't give you his name
unless you have a complaint.This is Professor Lambeau.
And this is
Professor Hayes.
Tom, please.
This is important.
Please.
Will didn't show
for work today.
[ Sighs ]
Got this job through his P.O.
You can call him.
- P.O.?
- Yeah. Parole officer.
Thank you.
Asshole.
[ Chuckling ]
[ Will ] There is a lengthy
legal precedent, Your Honor,
going back to 1789,
whereby a defendant
can claim self-defense against
an agent of the government...
if that act is deemed
a defense against tyranny,
a defense of liberty.
[ Clears Throat ]
Your Honor,
Henry Ward Beecher,
in Proverbs from the Plymouth
Pulpit,1887, said, quote-- 1887?
Excuse me. This is the 20th century.
- He's gonna make a mockery.
- I am afforded the right to
speak in my own defense, sir,
by the Constitution
of the United States.
Don't tell me
about the Constitution. This guarantees my liberty.
"Liberty,"
in case you've forgotten,
is a soul's right to breathe.
When it cannot
take a long breath,
laws are girded too tight.
- Without liberty,
man is a syncope.
- Man is a what?
Ibid., Your Honor.Son, my turn.
I've been sitting here
for 10 minutes now lookin' over
this rap sheet of yours.
I just can't believe it.
June '93, assault.
September '93, assault.
Grand theft auto,
February of '94.
Where, apparently,
you defended yourself and had
the case thrown out by citing...
"free property rights
of horse and carriage"
from 1798.
Joke. January '95,
impersonating an officer.
Mayhem, theft, resisting.
All overturned.
I'm also aware that you've been
through several foster homes.
The state removed you
from three because of
serious physical abuse.
You know, another judge
might care, but you hit a cop.
You're going in.
Motion to dismiss is denied.
$50,000 bail.
[ Gavel Pounds ]Thank you.
[ Woman ]
Rise.
[ Ringing ]
Hello?[ Will ]
Uh, Skylar?
Yep.Hey, uh, it's Will.
Who?It's Will.
You know, the really funny,
good-looking guy you met
at the bar the other night.
I don't recall meeting anyone
who matches that description.
I think I'd remember.
Oh, all right, you got me.
It's the ugly, obnoxious,
toothless loser...
who got hammered
and wouldn't leave you
alone all night.
Oh, Will!
I remember.[ Chuckling ]
How are you?
I was wondering
if you'd call me.
Yeah, look,
I was wondering--Yo, what's up, baby?
Hold on one second.What you doing?
Want some of my ass?
Herve, I remember you
from juvi. How you doing?What you doing?
Oh, yeah,
sorry about that.
I was wonderin' maybe
we could get together
sometime this week.
Sit out at a café.
Maybe have some caramels.Oh, that sounds wonderful.
Yeah?Yeah, sure.
Where are you?
Uh, well, actually,
this is just a shot
in the dark,
but, uh, there's no chance
that you're pre-law,
is there?
Have a seat.Thank you.
Nice talking to ya.
What the fuck
do you want?
I'm Gerald Lambeau.
Professor you told
to fuck himself.
Well, what the fuck
do you want?
I've spoken to the judge,
and he's agreed to release you
under my supervision.
Really?Yeah.
Under two conditions.What are those?
First condition is
that you meet with me
every week.
What for?Go over the proof
you're working on,
get into
some more advanced...
combinatorial mathematics,
finite math.
Sounds like a real hoot.
And the second condition
is that--
that you see a therapist.
I'm responsible
to submit reports
on those meetings.
If you fail to meet with
any of those conditions,
you will have to serve time.
All right. I'll do the math,
but I'm not gonna meet
with any fuckin' therapist.
It's better
than spending that time
in jail, isn't it?
[ Laughing ]
[ Clears Throat ]
[ Dog Barking ]
I read your book, and "Mike"
was havin' the same problems...
that "Chad," the stockbroker,
was havin'.
Absolutely right.
Right on the button.
Good for you, Will.
Very nice.Thank you.
Will, the pressures--
and I'm not judging them.
I'm not labeling them,
but they are destroying
your potential.
No more shenanigans.
No more tomfoolery.
No more ballyhoo.
You're right.
God, I know.
You're not gonna get off
that easily. Come on, Will.
A bit more.
- Well, I mean,
I do do things, you know?
- What-- What kind of things?
I do things that, you know,
I mean, I hide from people.
- You hide, do you?
- No, no. I mean, I like--
I go places. I interact.
Really?
What sort of places?Just certain clubs.
More. That's nice. Yes.
What sort of clubs?
Like, uh, like Fantasy.
Fantasy. That's nice.
A bit more.
It's something like
when you get in there,
the music, like, owns you.
It's like that house music.
It's like--
♪ Bom, bom, bom
♪ Bom-bom-bom
Boom, boom, boom, boom ♪♪
- You know, you start dancin'.
- Boom, boom, boom. Yeah.
It's just--
Yes.
[ Chuckling, Sighing ]
Do you find it hard to hide
the fact that you're gay?
[ Stammering ]
What are you talking about?
What?
Look, buddy, two seconds ago,
you were ready
to give me a jump.
A jump? Are you--
[ Laughing ]
I'm terribly sorry
to disappoint you.
Hey, I don't have a problem
with it. I don't care
if you putt from the rough.
What are you-- P-- Putting
from the rough? What on earth
are you talking about?
A difficult theorem
can be like a symphony.
It's very erotic.
[ Therapist ]
You go somewhere else.
I can't handle this.
Wow. [ Will ]
Thank you, Henry.
[ Grunting ]
Ah, Henry.Hi, Gerry.
You know something?
I can't do this
pro bono work anymore.
It's just not--
It's not worth it.What happened?
Well, I'm going on national
television next week.
I mean, I haven't got time
to tell you, much less talk to
that raving looney in there.
An absolute lunatic,
he is.
[ Lambeau ]
Henry.
[ Man ] Okay,
you are in your bed, Will.
Now, how old are you?
Seven.
What do you see?
Something's in my room.
What is it?
It's like a--
It's a figure.
It's hoverin' over me.
You are in a safe place,
Will.
It's t--
[ Sighs ]
It's touchin' me.
Where is it touching you?
It's touching me
down there,
and I'm nervous.
You don't have to be
nervous, Will.
We start dancin' and dancin'.
It's just beautiful,
'cause we can make...
a lot of love
before the sun goes down.
♪ Skyrockets
in flight ♪
♪ Afternoon delight
- ♪ Hey, hey, hey
Afternoon delight ♪
- Jesus.
♪ Skyrockets in flight
Da-da-da-da ♪
I'm sorry, Rich.I have better things to do
with my time.
♪ Hey, hey
Afternoon delight ♪♪
Come on! One dance!
You really hypnotized me,
you know?
For God's sake, Will.What? Oh, come on. He left.
You can't pin that on me.
I told you to cooperate
with these people.Look...
into my eyes.Get out, Will.
I don't need therapy.
That's enough.
Get out![ Imitating Spooky Sound ]
I called Mel Weintraub
this morning to see--Oh, what's the use?
What do you want to do?
[ Sighs ]
Well, there is someone.Who is he?
He used to be my, uh--
my roommate in college.
Trust. Very important
in a relationship.
It's also very important
in a clinical situation.
Why is trust
the most important thing...
in making a breakthrough
with a client?
Maureen,
stop the oral fixation
for a moment and join us.
- Vinnie.
- Um--
Because, uh--
Trust is, uh--
Trust is life.
Wow. That's very deep.
Thank you, Vinnie.
[ Professor ]
Next time, get the notes
from your brother.
If a patient doesn't feel
safe enough to trust you, then
they won't be honest with you.
Then there's really no point
for them being in therapy.
I mean, hey, if they don't
trust you, you're never gonna
get them to sleep with you.
That should be the goal
of any good therapist. Nail 'em
while they're vulnerable.
That's my motto.
Oh, good, everyone's back.
Welcome back, everybody.
Hello, Sean.Hey, Gerry.
Um, ladies and gentlemen,
we are in the presence
of greatness.
Professor Gerald Lambeau,
Field's medal winner for
combinatorial mathematics.
Hello. Anyone know what
the Field's medal is?
It's a really big deal.
It's like the Nobel prize
for math.
Except they only give it out
once every four years.
It's a great thing.
It's an amazing honor.
Okay, everybody,
that's it for today.
Thanks. We'll see you Monday.
We'll be talking about Freud.
Why he did enough cocaine
to kill a small horse.
Thank you.
How are you?It's good to see you.
Good to see you.
Sean, I think I got something
interesting for ya.Yeah?
What, you have to have
blood and urine?
What's up?
Why didn't you come
to the reunion?
You know, I'm--
I've been busy.
You were missed.Really?
So how long has it been
since we've seen each other?Before Nancy died.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I was in Paris.
It was that damn conference.
I got your card.
It was nice.
[ Grunting ]
Come here. Now that's a takedown.
Hey, what happened?
Did you get leniency or what?
I got, uh, probation
and then counseling
two days a week.
Joke. You're a smoothie.
Come on, Morgan!
Just submit!
[ Groaning ][ Chuckling ]
Hey, Bill,
just-just get off him.
We're gonna miss the game.
I've got a full schedule.
I'm very busy.Sean, Sean.
This-This boy is incredible.
I've never seen anything
like him.
What makes him
so incredible, Gerry?
You ever heard
of Ramanujan?Yeah, yeah. No.
It's a man.
He lived over 100 years ago.
He was Indian.
Dots, not feathers.Not feathers. Yeah.
He lived in this tiny hut
somewhere in India.
He had no formal education.
He had no access
to any scientific work. Coffee?
You, sir?Just a little.
But he came across
this old math book,
and from this simple text,
he was able to extrapolate
theories...
that had baffled
mathematicians for years.
Yes. Continued fractions.
He wrote, uh--
- Well, he mailed it
to Hardy at Cambridge.
- Yeah, Cambridge. Yeah.
And Hardy immediately recognized
the brilliance of his work...Mm-hmm.
and brought him over to England,
and then they worked together
for years,
creating some of the most
exciting math theory ever done.
This-This Ramanujan--
his-his genius
was unparalleled, Sean.
- Well, this boy's
just like that.
- Hmm.
- But he's--
he's a bit defensive.
- Hmm.
I need someone
who can get through to him.
Like me? Yeah, like you.
- Why?
- Well, because you have
the same kind of background.
What background? Well, you're from
the same neighborhood.
- He's from Southie?
- Yeah.
Boy genius from Southie.
- How many shrinks
you go to before me?
- Five.
Let me guess. Barry?
Henry? Not Rick? Yeah. Yeah.
Sean, please, just meet
with him once a week. Mm-hmm.
Please?
It's a poker game with this kid.
Don't let him know
what you've got.
He probably even read your book,
if he could find it.
It's gonna be hard
for him to find.
Hi, Will.Hi.
This is Sean Maguire.
Will Hunting.
How are ya?
Yeah.
Let's get started.Yeah, let's do it.
I'm pumped.
Let's let the healing begin.
Will you excuse us?Yeah, please, Tom.
You, too, Gerry.
Yeah, of course.
How are you? [ Door Closes ]
Where you from
in Southie?
I like what you've done
with the place.Oh, thanks.
Do you buy all these books
retail,
or do you send away for, like,
a "shrink kit" that comes with
all these volumes included?
Do you like books?Yeah.
Did you read
any of these books?I don't know.
- How about
any of these books?
- Probably not.
What about the ones
on the top shelf?
You read those?
Yeah, I read those. Good for you. What do you
think about 'em?
I'm not here for a fuckin' book
report. They're your books.
Why don't you read 'em?
I did. I had to.
Must've taken you
a long time. Yeah, it did.
United States of America:
A Complete History, Volume I.
Jesus.
If you wanna read
a real history book,
read Howard Zinn's
A People's History
of the United States.
That book'll fuckin'
knock you on your ass.
Better than Chomsky's
Manufacturing Consent?
Do you think
that's a good book?You fuckin' people baffle me.
You spend all your money on
these fuckin' fancy books. You
surround yourselves with 'em.
They're the wrong fuckin' books. What are the right
fuckin' books, Will?
- Whatever blows your hair back.
- Yeah. Haven't got
much hair left.
Hey, you know you'd be better
shoving that cigarette
up your ass.
It'd probably be healthier
for you.Yeah, I know.
It really gets in the way
of my yoga. You work out, huh?
What, you lift?Yeah.
Nautilus?No, free weights.
Oh, really?
Free weights, huh? Yeah. Yeah, big time.
Yeah? Just like that.
- What do you bench?
- 285. What do you bench?
You paint that?
Yeah.
Do you paint?Uh-uh.
- Do you sculpt?
- No.
Do you like art?
Do you like music?This is a real piece of shit.
Oh, tell me what
you really think.
Just the linear
and impressionistic mix makes
a very muddled composition.
It's also a Winslow Homer
rip-off, except you got
whitey rowin' the boat there.
Well, it's art, Monet.
It wasn't very good.
That's not really
what concerns me though.What concerns you?
Just the coloring.You know what the real bitch
of it is?
It's paint-by-number.
Is it color-by-number?
Because the colors
are fascinating to me.
Aren't they really?You bet.
I think you're about
one step away from cuttin'
your fuckin' ear off.
Really?Oh, yeah.
Think I should move
to the south of France,
change my name to "Vincent"?
You ever heard the sayin',
"any port in a storm"?Yeah.
Yeah, maybe that means you.In what way?
Maybe you're in the middle
of a storm, a big fuckin' storm.Yeah, maybe.
The sky's fallin' on your head.
The waves are crashin'
over your little boat.
The oars are about to snap.
[ Sniffling ]
You just piss in your pants.
You're cryin' for the harbor.
So maybe you do
what you gotta do to get out.
You know, maybe you became
a psychologist.
Bingo. That's it.
Let me do my job now.
You start with me. Come on.
Maybe you married
the wrong woman.
Maybe
you should watch your mouth!
Watch it right there, chief,
all right?
Ah.
That's it, isn't it?
You married
the wrong woman.
What happened?
What, did she leave you?
Was she, you know--
[ Whistling ]
banging some other guy?
If you ever
disrespect my wife again,
I will end you.
I will fuckin' end you.
Got that, chief?
Time's up.
Yeah.
At ease, gentlemen.
You okay?
Look, I'll understand
if you don't wanna meet
with him again.
Thursday, 4:00.
Make sure the kid's here.
Yeah.
Thanks.
[ Chattering ]
Well, you look lovely
in those glasses.
Thank you very much.They're just beautiful.
Yes, I always wanted
dark blue eye shadow.Wonderful.
Growing up in England,
you know, I went to
a very nice school.
You know, it was
kind of progressive, organic,
do-it-yourself, private school.
Then Harvard.
Hopefully med school.
You know, I figured out,
at the end,
my brain's gonna be worth
$250,000.
That sounded horrible,
didn't it?
[ Clacking ]Bring me another mai tai!
Nah, that's cool.
I mean, I bet your parents
were happy to pay.
No, I was happy to pay.
I inherited the money.
Wow. Is Harvard gettin'
all that money?
No, Stanford.
I'm going there in June
when I graduate.
All right, so you just wanted
to use this sailor
and then run away, huh?
I was gonna, you know,
experiment on you for
anatomy class first, obviously.
In that case, that's fine.
Hey, you wanna see
my magic tricks, Skylar? Of course.
All right.
Promise to--
This one's for you, Rudolph.Wait, wait.
You need my wand.
All right, give me a hit.
Thank you. All right.
I'm gonna make
all these caramels
disappear.
You ready?
Ready.
One, two, three.
[ Gasps ][ Chuckles ]
They're all gone.
That was my--
It works better
when I have my rabbit.
Well--
[ Clears Throat ]
I don't really date,
you know, that much.
How very unfortunate...
I think for me.
[ Chuckling ]
You know what I mean?
I know you've been
thinking about it.
Oh, no, I haven't.Yes, you have.
No, I really haven't.Yes, you have. You were hoping
to get a good night kiss.
No, you know, I tell ya,
I was hopin' to get
a good night lay.
[ Laughing ]
But I'll settle for,
like, a kiss, you know?
How very noble of you.Thank you.
Mm.No, I was-- I was
hopin' for a kiss.
Well, why don't we
just get it
out of the way now?
Right now?Yeah.
Come on.
[ Giggling ]
I think I got
some of your pickle.
You again, huh?
Come with me.
So what's this?
A Taster's Choice moment
between guys?
This is really nice.
You got a thing for swans?
Is this, like, a fetish?
Is it something, like, maybe
we need to devote some time to?
Thought about what you said
to me the other day.
About my painting.
Oh.
Stayed up half the night
thinking about it.
Something occurred to me.
I fell into a deep,
peaceful sleep and haven't
thought about you since.
You know
what occurred to me? No.
You're just a kid.
You don't have the faintest idea
what you're talking about.
Why, thank you.It's all right.
You've never been
out of Boston.
Nope.
So if I asked you about art,
you'd probably give me
the skinny...
on every art book
ever written.
Michelangelo?
You know a lot about him.
Life's work,
political aspirations.
Him and the pope.
Sexual orientation.
The whole works, right?
I'll bet you can't tell me
what it smells like
in the Sistine Chapel.
You never actually stood there
and looked up at
that beautiful ceiling.
Seeing that.
If I ask you about women,
you'll probably
give me a syllabus of
your personal favorites.
You may have even been laid
a few times.
But you can't tell me
what it feels like to wake up
next to a woman...
and feel truly happy.
You're a tough kid.
I ask you about war,
you'd probably throw Shakespeare
at me, right?
"Once more into the breach,
dear friends."
But you've never been near one.
You've never held
your best friend's head
in your lap...
and watch him gasp his last
breath lookin' to you for help.
If I asked you about love,
you'd probably quote me
a sonnet,
but you've never looked
at a woman and been
totally vulnerable.
Known someone that could
level you with her eyes.
Feelin' like God put
an angel on Earth just for you,
who could rescue you
from the depths of hell.
And you wouldn't know
what it's like to be her angel,
to have that love for her
be there forever.
Through anything.
Through cancer.
And you wouldn't know
about sleepin' sittin' up
in a hospital room...
for two months,
holding her hand,
because the doctors
could see in your eyes...
that the terms "visiting hours"
don't apply to you.
You don't know about real loss,
'cause that only occurs
when you love something more
than you love yourself.
I doubt you've ever dared
to love anybody that much.
I look at you,
I don't see an intelligent,
confident man.
I see a cocky,
scared shitless kid.
But you're a genius, Will.
No one denies that.
No one could possibly understand
the depths of you.
But you presume to know
everything about me because
you saw a painting of mine.
You ripped
my fuckin' life apart.
You're an orphan, right?
Do you think I'd know
the first thing about
how hard your life has been--
how you feel, who you are--
because I read Oliver Twist?
Does that encapsulate you?
Personally,
I don't give a shit
about all that, because--
You know what? I can't
learn anything from you...
I can't read
in some fuckin' book.
Unless you wanna talk
about you,
who you are.
And I'm fascinated.
I'm in.
But you don't wanna do that,
do you, sport?
You're terrified
of what you might say.
Your move, chief.
[ Chattering ]
[ Knocking ]
[ Machinery Humming ]
[ Ringing ]
Hello? Hello?
Hello?
Professor Valenti,
are you calling me again?
Freak.
Oh, fuck.Christ,
who did you call?
No one.
I forgot the number. You fuckin' retarded?
You went all the way out there
in the rain, and you didn't
bring the number.
No, it was
your mother's 900 number.
I just ran out of quarters.
Why don't we
get off on mothers?
I just got off yours.
[ Laughing ] [ Billy ] That's
pretty funny, Morgan.
That's a fuckin' nickel,
bitch.
Keep antagonizing me.
Watch what happens.All right, then, Morgan.
[ Morgan ]
Keep fuckin' with me.
No smoking.
What do you mean,
he didn't talk?
You were in there for an hour.
He just sat there
counting the seconds
until the session was over.
Pretty impressive,
actually.Why would he do that?
To prove to me
he doesn't have to talk to me
if he doesn't want to.
What is this? Some kind of
staring contest between two kids
from the old neighborhood?
Yeah, it is,
and I can't talk first.
We know your theory, Alexander,
but the boy's found
a simple geometrical picture.
A tree structure won't work. Look now.
He's joining the two vertices.
But I can do the sum.
It's how you group the terms,
Alexander. But, Gerry.
If we do the whole thing
this way, then--
Hey, look, look.
[ Will ]
I wrote it down.
It's simpler this way.
Sometimes
people get lucky.
You're a brilliant man.
[ Door Closes ]
♪♪ [ Whistling ]
You know,
I was on this plane once,
and I'm sittin' there, and...
the captain gets on,
he does his whole, you know,
"we'll be cruisin'
at 35,000 feet," but then
he puts the mike down.
He forgets to turn it off.Mm-hmm.
So he turns to the copilot.
He's, like,
"You know, all I could use
right now is a fuckin'
blow job and a cup of coffee."
So the stewardess fuckin' goes
bombin' up from the back
of the plane...
to tell him
the microphone's still on.
This guy in the back
of the plane's like, "Hey, hon,
don't forget the coffee."
[ Chuckling ]
You ever been on a plane?
No, but it's a fuckin' joke.
It works better if I tell it
in the first person.
Yeah, it does.
I have been laid,
you know?
Really? Good for you.
Big time, big time.Big time, huh?
I went on a date last week.
How'd it go?It was good.
Goin' out again?I don't know.
Why?Haven't called her.
Christ, you're an amateur.I know what I'm doin'.
Yeah. Don't worry about me.
I know what I'm doin'.
Yeah, but this girl was, like,
you know, beautiful.
She's smart. She's fun.
She's different from most
of the girls I've been with.
So call her up, Romeo.Why, so I can realize
she's not that smart?
That she's fuckin' boring?
You know, I mean, you don't--
This girl's, like,
fuckin' perfect right now.
I don't wanna ruin that.
Maybe you're perfect right now.
Maybe you don't wanna
ruin that.
But I think that's
a super philosophy, Will.
That way, you can go through
your entire life without ever
having to really know anybody.
My wife used to fart
when she was nervous.
She had all sorts
of wonderful idiosyncrasies.
You know, she used to fart
in her sleep.
Just thought I'd share that
with you.
One night it was so loud,
it woke the dog up.
[ Both Laughing ]
She woke up and gone, like,
"Was that you?"
I said, "Yeah."
I didn't have the heart
to tell her. Oh, God.
She woke herself up?
[ Laughing ]Yes.
Oh, Christ. But, Will,
she's been dead two years
and that's the shit I remember.
It's wonderful stuff, you know?
Little things like that.
Yeah, but those are the things
I miss the most.
Those little idiosyncrasies
that only I knew about.
That's what made her
my wife.
Boy, and she had the goods
on me too. She knew
all my little peccadillos.
People call these things
"imperfections,"
but they're not.
That's the good stuff.
And then we get
to choose who we let into
our weird little worlds.
You're not perfect, sport.
And let me save you
the suspense.
This girl you met,
she isn't perfect either.
But the question is
whether or not you're perfect
for each other.
That's the whole deal.
That's what intimacy
is all about.
Now you can know
everything in the world, sport,
but the only way
you're findin' out that one
is by givin' it a shot.
You certainly won't learn
from an old fucker like me.
Even if I did know,
I wouldn't tell a pissant
like you.
[ Chuckling ]
Yeah, why not?
You told me every other
fuckin' thing. Jesus Christ.
Fuckin' talk more than
any shrink I ever seen
in my life.
I teach the shit.
I didn't say I knew
how to do it.
Yeah.
[ Sighs ]
You ever think about
gettin' remarried?
My wife's dead.
Hence the word
"remarried."She's dead.
Yeah, well, I think
that's a super philosophy,
Sean.
I mean, that way, you can
actually go through the rest
of your life...
without ever really knowing
anybody.
Time's up.
Hold it open.Okay.
Thanks.[ Chattering ]
♪♪ [ Piano ]
♪♪
[ Woman ]
♪ I am happy with you
♪ I know I'm about
to love you ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah
You know him ♪
[ Knocking ]♪ Oh, my, you made me-- ♪
"G" minor seventh.
Saddest of all chords.
Hello.Hey.
Where have you been?I'm sorry. I've been, like--
I've been really busy, and--
[ Clears Throat ]
But, um--Mmm. Me too.
Yeah. I--
I thought you'd call.
Yeah, um--
I mean, we had
a really good time.I had a really good time too.
I mean, I just-- I--
I'm sorry, you know.
I blew it.
No. No, I mean,
you know, it's all right.
Yeah, um, so, I was
wonderin' if, uh,
if, you know, you'd give me
another crack at it.
You know, let me
take you out again.
I can't.All right.
Oh, no, I didn't--
I didn't mean
I can't, like, ever.
I just can't right now.
I've got to assign
the proton spectrum
for "ebogamine."
All that sounds really,
really interesting. It's
actually fantastically boring.
All right, um--Maybe some other time.
Like tomorrow?Um, yeah, all right.
Okay.Okay.
Bye. Bye.
[ Bell Tolling ]
[ Knocking ]What are you doing here?
I couldn't wait
till tomorrow.
Where the fuck
did you get this?
I had to sleep
with someone in your class.
Oh, I hope it was someone
with the open-toed sandals
and the really bad breath.
Come on. Let's go
have some fun.No, I've got to learn this.
Well, you're not going into
surgery tomorrow, are you?
No.Let's go.
[ Bell Rings ] [ Crowd Shouting ]
Oh, my God!
My dog is winning!
Come on, Misty!
Come on! Run!
Look at that!
Come on!
Look, there he goes.
Misty, run! Come on!
We won.
[ Laughs ]He totally won.
So did you grow up
around here then?
Not far.
South Boston.
Still glowing from my win.
Look at you.
You're so happy.
And what was
that like then?
It was normal, I guess.
Nothin' special.
Do you got lots of
brothers and sisters?
Do I have a lot of
brothers and sisters?That's what I said.
Well, Irish Catholic,
what do you think?Right. That's right.
How many?You wouldn't believe me
if I told you.
Why? Go on.
What? Five?No.
Seven? Eight?
How many?
I have 12 big brothers.You do not!
No, I swear to God.
I swear to God.
I'm lucky 13 right here.
Do you know
all their names?
Do I-- Yeah,
they're my brothers.
What are they called?
Marky, Ricky, Danny, Terry,
Mikey, Davey, Timmy, Tommy,
Joey, Robby, Johnny and Brian.
Say it again.
Marky, Ricky, Danny, Terry,
Mikey, Davey, Timmy, Tommy,
Joey, Robby, Johnny and Brian.
And Willy.
Willy?Yeah.
Will.Wow.
Do you still see all of them?Yeah, well,
they all live in Southie.
I'm livin' with
three of 'em right now.Oh, yeah?
Yeah.I'd like
to meet them.
Yeah, we'll do that.
Oh, you know,
I read your book last night.
Oh, so you're the one.[ Laughs ]
Do you still, uh--
Do you still counsel veterans?
No, I don't.
Why not?Well, I gave it up
when my wife got sick.
You ever wonder what your life
would be like if you, uh,
if you never met your wife?
What? Wonder if I'd be
better off without her?
No, no, no, I'm not saying,
like, better off.No.
I didn't mean it like that.It's all right.
It's an important question.
'Cause you'll have
bad times, but that'll
always wake you up...
to the good stuff
you weren't paying
attention to.
And you don't regret
meetin' your wife?
Why? 'Cause the pain
I feel now?
Oh, I got regrets, Will,
but I don't regret a single
day I spent with her.
So when did you know, like,
that she was the one for you?
October 21, 1975.
Jesus Christ.
You know the fuckin' day?
Oh, yeah, 'cause it was game six
of the World Series, biggest
game in Red Sox history.
- Yeah, sure.
- My friends and I had slept out
all night to get tickets.
You got tickets?Yep. Day of the game
I was sittin' in a bar,
waitin' for
the game to start
and in walks this girl.
It was an amazing game though.
You know, bottom of the eighth,
Carbo ties it up.
It was 6-6.
It went to 12.
Bottom of the 12th,
in stepped Carlton Fisk,
old Pudge.
Steps up to the plate.
You know, he's got
that weird stance.
- Yeah, yeah.
- And then-- Boom!
He clocks it, you know.
High fly ball
down the left field line!
35,000 people on their feet,
yellin' at the ball.
But that's nothin',
'cause Fisk, he's wavin'
at the ball like a madman.
Yeah, I've seen that."Get over! Get over!
Right.Get over!"
Then it hits the foul pole.
He goes ape-shit,
and 35,000 fans--
They charge the field,
you know.
Yeah, and he's
fuckin' blowin'
people outta the way.
"Get outta the way!
Get outta the way!"
I can't fuckin'
believe you had tickets
to that fuckin' game!
Did you rush the field?No, I didn't rush the
fuckin' field. I wasn't there.
What?No, I was in a bar, havin'
a drink with my future wife.
You missed Pudge Fisk's home run
to have a fuckin' drink
with some lady you never met?
Yeah, but you should have
seen her. She was a stunner.
I don't care if--Oh, no, no,
she lit up the room.
I don't care if Helen
of Troy walks into the room.Oh, Helen of Troy!
That's game six!
Oh, my God, and who were
these friends of yours?
They let you
get away with that?They had to.
What did you say to 'em?I just slid my ticket
across the table.
I said, "Sorry, guys.
I gotta see about a girl."
"I gotta go see
about a girl"?Yes!
That's what you said?
They let you get
away with that?
Oh, yeah. They saw it
in my eyes that I meant it.
You're kiddin' me?No, I'm not
kidding you, Will.
That's why I'm not talkin'
right now about some girl
I saw at a bar 20 years ago...
and how I always
regretted not goin' over
and talkin' to her.
I don't regret the 18 years
I was married to Nancy.
I don't regret the six years
I had to give up counseling
when she got sick,
and I don't regret
the last years when
she got really sick.
And I sure as hell don't
regret missin' a damn game.
That's regret.
Wow!
[ Sighs ]
Would have been nice
to catch that game though.
I didn't know Pudge
was gonna hit a home run.
[ Both Laughing ]
You know, I'm very, very
useful on the court.
I'm extremely tall.
You're not that tall.I dunk.
[ Rattling ]Will I ever play
in the N.B.A.?
"It is decidedly so."
Hmph.
Why do we always stay here?
'Cause it's nicer
than my place.
Yes, but I've never
seen your place.
I know.
[ Laughs ]
When am I gonna meet
your friends and your brothers?
Well, they don't really
come down here that much.
I think I can make it
to South Boston.
It's kind of a hike.
Is it me you're hiding from them
or the other way around?
All right, we'll go.When?
I don't know.
We'll go sometime next week.
What if I said I would not
sleep with you again until
you let me meet your friends?
[ Groans ]
I'd say it's, like,
4:30 in the mornin'.
They're probably up.
Oh, my God.
Men are shameless.
If you're not thinking
with your wiener, then you're
acting directly on its behalf.
You bet. And on behalf
of my wiener, can I get
an advance payment?
I don't know. Let's ask.
"Outlook does not look good."
[ Chuck On Phone ] What? Fuck the-- Hey, Chuck.
No. Nothing. Go back to sleep.
"Outlook"? That's the
same thing that told you
you was gonna play in the N.B.A.
Exactly, so look out.
You'd better start buying
some season tickets.
Mmm! I plan to. I'm tall.
I like wearing shorts.
Hook, hook. Dunk, dunk.
You're not that tall.Yes, I am.
Maybe I'm all
about three points.
I'm all about home runs.
[ Laughs ]
Stop mixing your
sporting metaphors.
[ Laughing ]
A leprechaun's got his dick
in the monkey's ass.
Morgan comes runnin' in,
goin', "I don't mind it.
I don't mind--"
[ Laughing ]
Well, I can't believe you
brought Skylar here when we're
fuckin' all bombed and drinkin'.
I know, Morgan.
It's a real rarity
we be all drinkin'.
My uncle Marty drinks.
He'll go on a bender
for six, eight months.
Did I ever tell ya what happened
to him when he was drivin'
up there and got pulled over?
I told you guys, right?Marty, yeah.
Let me tell ya what
happened to my uncle Marty,
because you oughta know this.
He's always tellin' stories.
Every time we come here
he's got another story.
But we all heard this one.
Go ahead. Say it anyway.
I will go ahead.
Thanks a lot.
Guess I have the floor now.
My uncle Marty's
drivin' home, right?
Bombed out of his tree, right?
Just hammered out of his gourd.
Just wrecked.
This state trooper
sees him, pulls him over.
So my uncle's fucked basically.
Got him out of the car,
tryin' to make him
walk the line.
He gets out of the car, pukes,
and the statie's pretty sure
he's over the legal limit.
So he's about to
throw the cuffs on him
and put him in jail.
All of a sudden,
50 yards down the road,
there's this huge fuckin' boom.
Statie gets real spooked.
He turns around--He got shot?
No. So-- So-- You
heard this story before.
Yeah, Morgan, stop.
Stop.
Some other guy's car
had hit a tree.
There was an accident.
[ Coughs ]
Anyway--
How could he hear--Shut the fuck up!
- You're drivin' him nuts.
- I'm gonna break your neck.
Shut up!
He told you the story
once before.
So he tells my uncle,
"Stay here. Don't move."
Statie goes runnin'
down the road to deal
with the other accident.
After a few minutes
of just lyin' in
his own piss and vomit,
my uncle starts wonderin'
what he's doin' there.
Gets up, gets in his car
and just drives home.
The next mornin'
my uncle's just passed out.
He hears this knockin'
at the door. [ Knocking ]
So he goes downstairs,
pulls the door open--
"What?"
It's the state trooper
that pulled him over.
Statie says,
"Fuck you mean, 'What?'
You know what.
I pulled you over last night
is what, and you took off."
He's like, "I never
seen you before in my life.
I've been home all night
with my kids. I don't know
who the fuck you are."
He's like, "You know who I am.
Let me get in your garage."
My uncle's like, "What?"
He said, "You heard me.
Let me get in your garage."
He was like, "All right.
Fine." Takes him out to
the garage, opens the door.
And there's--
The statie's police cruiser
is in my uncle's garage.
[ Morgan Laughing ]He was so fuckin'--
He was so fuckin' hammered
he drove the wrong car home.
The best part about it is,
the fuckin' state trooper...
was so embarrassed
he didn't do anything.
He'd been drivin' around all
night in my uncle's Chevelle,
lookin' for the house.
All right, Chuck,
what the fuck is the point
of your story?
He got away.
That's the point.
- Well, question--
- Come on. Stop.
I'm tryin' to
clarify somethin'.You're embarrassing him.
It doesn't make any sense.It does make sense,
if you listen to the story
and quit askin' questions.
Well, let's see if you can
get this one. I've got
a little story for you.
All right, there's
an old couple in bed,
Mary and Paddie.
They wake up on the morning
of their 50th anniversary.
Mary looks over and
gazes adoringly at Paddie.
She's like,
"Oh, Jesus, Paddie.
"You're such a good-looking
feller. I love ya.
"I want to give ya
a little present.
"Anything your
little heart desires,
I'm goin' to give it to ya.
What would ya like?"
Paddie's like, "Oh, gee, Mary.
That's a very sweet offer.
"Now, in 50 years,
there's one thing
that's been missing,
"and, uh, I would like you
to give me a blow job.
I would like for it."
Mary's like, "All right."
She takes her teeth out,
puts 'em in the glass.
She gives him a blow job.
Afterwards, Paddie's like,
"Yeah, geez, now that's
what I've been missin'.
"That was the most beautiful,
earth-shattering thing ever!
"Beautiful, Mary!
I love ya!
Is there anything
that I can do for you?"
Mary looks up to him
and she goes,
"Give us a kiss."
Oh! Oh, my God!
That's filthy. It's not that filthy.
I've heard filthier.
[ Laughing ]
Get off of me!All right.
See you guys later.
All right.
Take it easy, Bill.
So, Skylar,
thanks for comin' by.
Changed my opinion
of Harvard people.
You don't want to rush
to judgment on that one,
'cause they're not all like me.
Oh. I'm sure.
It was nice to meet ya.
Oh.Take it easy.
Slowly back away.
Oh, come on. Brother.I don't know
what you're doin', dude.
You're givin' us a ride.What the fuck
do I look like to you?
Come on, Chuck. You're walkin', bitch.
Will's takin' the car.
All right, thanks, sucker.
I appreciate it.
I don't know what you're
gettin' all serious about.
You're droppin'
me off first.It's really out of the way.
Oh, okay. Just 'cause you
don't have to sleep in your
one-room palace tonight...
don't start
thinkin' you're bad.
Hey, wait a minute.
You said we were
gonna see your place.
Not tonight.Oh, no, not tonight.
Not any other night.
He knows once you see
that shit-hole he's gettin'
dropped like a bad habit.
But I wanted to meet
your brothers.
We're gonna do that
another time.
All right.
Need them keys.
The stewardess hears this
and goes haulin' ass
down the aisle.
I yell,
"Don't forget the coffee."
No shit!
You didn't say that.
For Christ's sake, Marty,
it's a joke.
I know someone that
actually happened to, Marty.A joke.
Gerry.Hi.
Have trouble
findin' the place?No, I took a cab.
Timmy, this is Gerry.
We went to college together.
How you doin'?
Nice to meet ya.
Pleased to meet you.Can I get you a beer?
Um, no, just a Perrier.
That's French
for club soda.
Club soda, yeah.Couple of sandwiches too.
Sure.Put it on my tab.
You ever plannin'
on payin' your tab?
Yeah, chief, got the winning
lottery ticket right here.
What's the jackpot?Twelve million.
I don't think that'll cover it. It'll cover your
sex change operation.
Nuts?No, thank you.
So, you wanted
to talk about Will.
Well, it seems
to be going well.I think so.
Have you talked to him
at all about his future?
No, we haven't gotten
into that yet. We're still
bangin' away at the past.
Maybe you should.
My phone's been ringing
off the hook with job offers.
What kind? Cutting edge mathematics,
think tanks.
The kind of place
where a mind like Will's
is given free rein.
That's great that there are
offers, but I don't really
think he's ready for that.
I'm not sure
you understand, Sean.
What don't I understand?Here you go, guys.
Thanks, Tim.Yeah, thank you.
Just so you don't
get sticky fingers.
Tim, can you help us?
We're tryin'
to settle a bet.
Uh-oh.
- Ever heard of Jonas Salk?
- Sure. Cured polio.
-Ever heard of Albert Einstein?
-Hey.
[ Pool Balls Clattering ]
How about Gerald Lambeau?
Ever heard of him?
- No.
- Thank you, Tim.
So who won the bet?I did.
This isn't about me, Sean.
I'm nothing compared
to this young man.
You ever hear of
Gerald Lambeau?
In 1905 there were hundreds
of professors renowned for
their study of the universe.
But it was a 26-year-old
Swiss patent clerk,
doing physics in his spare time,
who changed the world.
Can you imagine if Einstein
would have given that up...
just to get drunk
with his buddies
in Vienna every night.
We all would have
lost something.
Tim would never
have heard of him.
Pretty dramatic, Gerry. No, it isn't, Sean.
This boy has that gift.
He just doesn't
got the direction,
but we can give that to him.
Hey, Gerry, in the 1960s,
there was a young man graduated
from University of Michigan.
Did some brilliant work
in mathematics.
Specifically,
bounded harmonic functions.
Then he went on to Berkeley.
He was assistant professor.
Showed amazing potential.
Then he moved to Montana, and
he blew the competition away.
- Yeah, so who was he?
- Ted Kaczynski.
Haven't heard of him.
Hey, Timmy! Yo!
Who's Ted Kaczynski? Unabomber.
That's exactly
what I'm talking about.
We gotta give
this kid direction. Yeah--
He can contribute to the world,
and we can help him do that.
Direction's one thing.
Manipulation's another.
- Sean--
- We have to let him find--
I'm not sitting at home
every night twisting my mustache
and hatching a plan...
to ruin this boy's life!
I was doing advanced mathematics
when I was 18,
and it still took me
over 20 years to do something
worthy of a Field's medal.
Maybe he doesn't want
what you want.
There's more to life
than a fuckin'
Field's medal.
This is too important, Sean,
and it's above personal rivalry.
Wait a minute.
Let's talk about the boy.
Why don't we give him time
to figure out what he wants?
That's a wonderful theory,
Sean. It worked wonders
for you, didn't it?
Yeah, it did,
you arrogant fuckin' prick!
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry
that I came here today.
I came here out of courtesy.
I wanted to keep you
in the loop.
Nice to be in the loop.
The boy's in a meeting
right now I set up for him
over at McNeil.
Well, Will, I'm not exactly sure
what you mean.
We've already
offered you a position.
Nobody in this town works
without a retainer, guys.
You think you can
find somebody who does,
you have my blessin'.
But I think we all know
that person is not gonna
represent you as well as I can.
Will, our offer
is $84,000 a year.
Retainer!
Retainer.
You want us to give you
cash right now?
Whoa-ho-ho. Easy--
Now, I didn't say that.
Allegedly,
your situation, for you,
would be concurrently
improved if I had...
$200 in my back pocket
right now.
[ Clears Throat ]
I don't think I can--
Larry?
I've got $73.Will you take a check?
Let me tell you somethin'.
You're suspect.
Yeah, you. I don't know
what your reputation is
in this town,
but after the shit
you tried to pull today,
you can bet
I'll be lookin' into you.
Now, any business
we have heretofore,
you can speak with
my aforementioned attorney.
Good day, gentlemen.
And until that day comes,
keep your ear
to the grindstone.
[ Chattering ]
How's it goin'?Fine.
Yeah.
Good.
Want some help?No!
Come on. Give me
one little peek, and we'll
go to the batting cages.
No.
It is actually important
that I learn this.
It's really important...
to me, okay?All right.
Why don't we just
hang out here all day?Yes, why don't we?
All right, Mr. Nosey Parker.[ Chuckles ]
Seeing as you're intent
on breaking my balls,
let me ask you a question. All right.
Do you have
a photographic memory?
I don't know. I just kind
of remember. I mean, how do you
remember your phone number?
You just do.
Have you studied
organic chemistry? A little bit.
Oh, just for fun? Yeah, for kicks.
Yeah, it's so much fun
studying organic chemistry.
Are you mad?[ Laughs ]
Have you completely
lost your mind?
Nobody studies it for fun.
It's not a necessity,
especially for someone like you.
Someone like me? Yeah.
Someone who divides
their time, fairly evenly,
between batting cages and bars.
I would hardly say
it was a necessity.Oh.
You know, there are very
smart people here at Harvard.
Even they have to study,
because this is really hard.
And yet...
you do it so easily.
I don't understand.
I don't understand
how your mind works.
Did you play the piano?I want to talk about this.
No, I'm trying
to explain it to you.
Do you play the piano?
Yeah, a bit.So when you look at
a piano, you see Mozart.
I see "Chopsticks."All right, well,
Beethoven, okay?
He looked at a piano,
and it just made sense
to him. He could just play.
So what are you saying?
You play the piano?Not a lick.
I look at a piano, I see
a bunch of keys, three pedals
and a box of wood.
But Beethoven, Mozart--
They saw it.
They could just play.
I couldn't paint you a picture.
I probably can't hit the ball
out of Fenway.
And I can't play the piano.But you can do my
O-chem paper in under an hour.
Right. Well, I mean, when
it came to stuff like that,
I could always just play.
That's the best
I can explain it.
Come here. I have
to tell you something.Huh?
I have to tell you
something.Oh.
Well--
It's not fair.What's not fair? What?
I've been here for four years,
and I've only just found you.
Well, you found me.
Are you awake?No.
Yes, you are.
Will, come to
California with me.
What?
I want you to come
to California with me.
You sure about that?Oh, yeah.
Yeah, but how do you know?
I don't know.
I just know.
Yeah, but how do you know?
I know because I feel it.
Because that's a really
serious thing you're saying.I know.
You could be in California
next week...
and you might find out
something about me
you don't like.
Maybe you wish
you hadn't said that,
but you know it's
such a serious thing
you can't take it back.
Now I'm stuck in California
with someone that doesn't
really want to be with me,
just wish they
had a take-back.A what? What's a take-back?
I don't want a take-back.
I just want you to come
to California with me.
Well, I can't go to
California with you, so--
Why not?
Well, one, because
I got a job here.
And, two,
because I live here.
Look, um,
if you don't love me,
you should just tell me.
I'm not sayin'
I don't love you.
Then why?
Why won't you come?
What are you so scared of?
What am Iso scared of?
Well, what aren't
you scared of?
You live in this safe
little world where
no one challenges you--
Don't tell me about my world.
You just want to have
your little fling with the guy
from the other side of town.
Then you're gonna go off
to Stanford. You're gonna
marry some rich prick...
who your parents
will approve of...
and just sit around with
the other trust fund babies...
and talk about how you
went slummin', too, once.
Why are you saying this?
What is your obsession
with this money?
My father died when I was 13,
and I inherited this money.
You don't think every day
I wake up, and I wish
I could give it back.
That I would give it back
in a second if it meant I could
have one more day with him.
But I can't, and that's
my life, and I deal with it.
So don't put your shit on me
when you're the one
that's afraid.
I'm afraid?
What am I afraid of?
What the fuck am I afraid of?
You're afraid of me.
You're afraid that
I won't love you back.
You know what?
I'm afraid too.
But fuck it, I want to
give it a shot. At least
I'm honest with you.
I'm not honest with you?No, what about
your 12 brothers?
- All right.
- [ Belt Buckle Jingles ]
No, you're not going.
You're not leaving.
What do you want to know?
That I don't have 12 brothers?
That I'm a fuckin' orphan?
You don't want
to hear that.I didn't know that.
You don't want to hear
I got fuckin' cigarettes
put out on me when I was little.
I didn't know that.That this isn't
fuckin' surgery.
The motherfucker stabbed me.
You don't want to hear
that shit, Skylar!
I do want to hear that.Don't tell me you want
to hear that shit!
I want to help you.Help me? What the fuck?
What do I got,
a fuckin' sign on my back
that says, "Save me"?
No.Do I look like
I need that?
No, I just want to be
with you--Don't bullshit me!
I love you.Don't bullshit me!
Don't you fuckin' bullshit me!
I love you.
I want to hear you say
that you don't love me.
Because if you say that...
then I won't call you...
and I won't be in your life.
[ Sobs ]I don't love you.
[ Giggling ]
Most people never get to see
how brilliant they can be.
They don't find teachers
that believe in them.
They get convinced
they're stupid.
I hope you appreciate
what he's doing,
because I've seen how much
he enjoys working with you,
not against you.
Hello, Will.
Tom, can you get us
some coffee?
Sure.
Now, let's see.
[ Clears Throat ]
Good. This is correct.
I see you used Maclaurin here.
Yeah, I don't know what
you call it, but--
This can't be right.
This would be
very embarrassing.
Did you ever consider-- I'm pretty sure
it's right.
Hey, look, can we
do this at Sean's office
from now on?
Because I got to knock off
work to come here and
the commute is killin' me.
Yeah, sure. Did you
think of the possibility-- That's right.
It's right.
Just take it home with you.
What happened
at the McNeil meeting?
I couldn't go.
I had a date.
So I sent my
chief negotiator.
On your own time, you can do
whatever you like, Will.
But when I set up a meeting
with my associates,
and you don't show up,
it reflects poorly on me.
Then don't set up
any more meetings. I won't.
I'll cancel 'em.
I'll give you a job myself.
I just wanted you to see
what was out there.
Maybe I don't want to spend
the rest of my fuckin' life
explainin' shit to people.
I think you could show me
some appreciation.
A little appreciation?
Do you know how easy
this is for me?
Do you have any fuckin' idea
how easy this is?
This is a fuckin' joke.
I'm sorry you can't do this--
I really am--
Because I wouldn't have to
fuckin' sit here and watch you
fumble around and fuck it up.
Then you'd have more time
to sit around and get drunk
instead, wouldn't you?
You're right. This is probably
a total waste of my time.
You're right, Will.
I can't do this proof,
but you can.
And when it comes to that,
it's only about just a handful
of people in the world...
who can tell the difference
between you and me.
But I'm one of them.Sorry.
Yeah, so am I.
Most days I wish
I never met you,
because then I could
sleep at night.
I didn't have to walk around
with the knowledge that there
was someone like you out there.
[ Door Closes ]
I didn't have to watch you
throw it all away.
[ Dog Barking ]
♪♪ [ Plunking Notes ]
Bill, hold it.
Did you hear that? [ Man Moaning ]
Morgan!
If you're watchin' pornos in
my mom's room again, I'm gonna
give you a fuckin' beatin'!
[ Door Closes ]
[ Footsteps Running
Downstairs ]
[ Panting ]
What's up, fellas?
Morgan, why don't you jerk off
in your own fuckin' house.
That's fuckin' filthy.
I don't have a V.C.R.
in my house.
Come on. Not in my glove.
I didn't use the glove.
That's my
Little League glove.
What do you want me
to do?
I mean, what's wrong
with you?
You'll hump
a baseball glove?
I-I just used it
for cleanup.
[ Laughing ]Stop jerkin' off
in my mother's room.
Is there another
V.C.R. in the house?It's just sad, bro.
So why do you think
I should work for the
National Security Agency?
Well, you'd be working
on the cutting edge.
You'd be exposed to
the kind of technology
you wouldn't see anywhere else,
because we've classified it.
Superstring theory,
chaos math, advanced algorithms.
Code breaking.
That's one aspect
of what we do.
Oh, come on.
That is what you do.
You guys handle 80% of
the intelligence workload.
You're seven times
the size of the C.I.A.
We don't like to brag
about that, Will,
but you're exactly right.
So the way I see it,
the question isn't:
"Why should you work
for the N.S.A.?"
The question is:
"Why shouldn't you?"
Why shouldn't
I work for the N.S.A.?
That's a tough one,
but I'll take a shot.
Say I'm workin' at the N.S.A.
and somebody puts
a code on my desk.
Something no one else
can break.
Maybe I take a shot at it
and maybe I break it.
I'm real happy with myself
because I did my job well.
But maybe that code was
the location of some rebel army
in North Africa or Middle East.
Once they have that location,
they bomb the village where
the rebels are hidin'.
Fifteen hundred people
that I never met, never had
no problem with, get killed.
Now the politicians are saying,
"Send in the Marines
to secure the area,"
'cause they don't give a shit.
It won't be their kid
over there gettin' shot,
just like it wasn't them when
their number got called 'cause
they were in the National Guard.
It'll be some kid from Southie
over there takin' shrapnel
in the ass.
He comes back to find the plant
he used to work at...
got exported to the country
he got back from,
and the guy who put
the shrapnel in his ass
got his old job...
'cause he'll work for 15 cents
a day and no bathroom breaks.
Meanwhile, he realizes the
only reason he was over there
in the first place...
was so we could install
a government that would
sell us oil at a good price.
Of course, the oil companies
used a skirmish over there
to scare up domestic oil prices.
A cute little ancillary benefit
for them, but it ain't helpin'
my buddy at 2.50 a gallon.
They're takin' their sweet time
bringin' the oil, of course.
Maybe they even took
the liberty to hire
an alcoholic skipper,
who likes to drink martinis
and fuckin' play slalom
with the icebergs.
It ain't too long till
he hits one, spills the oil...
and kills all the sea life
in the North Atlantic.
So now my buddy's out of work,
he can't afford to drive,
so he's walkin' to
the fuckin' job interviews...
which sucks because
the shrapnel in his ass is
givin' him chronic hemorrhoids.
Meanwhile, he's starvin',
'cause every time he tries
to get a bite to eat,
the only blue plate special
they're servin'...
is North Atlantic scrod
with Quaker State.
So what did I think?
I'm holdin' out
for somethin' better.
I figure, fuck it.
While I'm at it, why not
just shoot my buddy,
take his job,
give it to his sworn enemy,
hike up gas prices, bomb
a village, club a baby seal,
hit the hash pipe
and join the National Guard?
I can be
elected president.
- You feel like you're alone?
- What?
Do you have a soul mate?
Do I have a--
Define that.
Somebody who challenges you.
Uh, Chuckie. No, Chuckie's family. He'd lie
down in fuckin' traffic for you.
I'm talking about someone
who opens up things for you,
touches your soul.
I got-- I got-- Who?
I got plenty. Well, name 'em.
Shakespeare, Nietzsche,
Frost, O'Connor,
Kant, Pope, Locke--
That's great.
They're all dead.
Not to me they're not.You don't have
a lot of dialogue with them.
You can't give back
to them, Will.
Not without some serious
smelling salts and a heater. That's what I'm saying.
You'll never have that kind
of relationship in a world...
where you're always afraid
to take the first step,
because all you see
is every negative thing
10 miles down the road.
You gonna take the
professor's side on this?Don't give me a line of shit.
No.I didn't want the job.
It's not about the job.
I don't care if you work
for the government.
But you can do
anything you want.
You are bound by nothing.
What are you
passionate about?
What do you want?
There are guys
who work their entire life
layin' brick...
so their kids have a chance
at the opportunities
you have here.
I didn't ask for this. No.
You were born with it,
so don't cop out behind:
"I didn't ask for this."
What do you mean, cop out?
What's wrong with layin' brick? Nothing.
There's nothin' wrong.
That's somebody's home
I'm buildin'.
Right. My dad
laid brick, okay?
Busted his ass so
I could have an education.
Exactly. That's
an honorable profession.
What's wrong with
fixin' somebody's car?
Someone will get to work
the next day because of me.
That's honor in that.
Yeah, there is, Will.
There is honor in that.
There's honor in takin'
that 40-minute train ride...
so those college kids
could come in in the morning
and their floors are clean.
And their wastebaskets
are empty. That's real work.That's right.
And that's honorable.
I'm sure that's why
you took that job.
I mean, for the honorof it.
I just have a little
question here. You could be
a janitor anywhere.
Why did you work at the most
prestigious technical college
in the whole fuckin' world?
Why did you sneak
around at night and finish
other people's formulas...
that only one or two people
in the world could do
and then lie about it?
'Cause I don't see
a lot of honor in that, Will.
So what do you
really wanna do?
I wanna be a shepherd.
Really?
I wanna move up to Nashua,
get a nice little spread,
get some sheep and tend to them.
- Maybe you should go do that.
- What?
You know, if you're gonna
jerk off, why don't you just do
it at home with a moist towel?
You're chuckin' me?Yeah, get the fuck outta here.
No, no, no,
time's not up yet.Yeah, it is.
I'm not leavin'. No.You're not gonna answer,
you're wastin' my time.
I thought we were friends.
- Playtime's over, okay?
- Why are you kickin' me out?
You're lecturin' me on life?
Look at you,
you fuckin' burnout.
What winds your clock?Workin' with you.
Where's your soul mate?
You wanna talk about
soul mates? Where is she?
Dead. That's right.
She's fuckin' dead.
She fuckin' dies and
you just cash in your chips
and you walk away?
At least I played a hand. You played a hand and you lost.
You lost a big fuckin' hand.
Some people will lose a big hand
like that and have the sack
to ante up again.
Look at me.
What do you wanna do?
You and your bullshit.
You got a bullshit answer
for everybody.
But I ask you a very simple
question and you can't give me
a straight answer,
because you don't know.
I'll see ya, Bo-peep.
Fuck you.You're the shepherd.
Shepherd.
[ Whispers ]
White little prick.
I just wanted to,
you know, um,
call you up,
uh, before you left, um--
I've been takin' all these
jobs interviews and stuff,
so I'm not gonna be just
a construction worker.
Well, you know, I never
really cared about that.
Yeah.
I love you.
Will?
You take care.
♪ Someone's always
comin' around here ♪
♪ Trailin' some new kill Bye.
♪ Says, I seen your picture
on a ♪
♪ Hundred-dollar bill
♪ What's a game of chance
to you ♪
♪ In this world
♪ Of real skill
♪ So glad to meet ya
♪ Angeles
♪ Pickin' up the ticket
shows there's money
to be made ♪
♪ Go on, lose the gamble
♪ That's the history
of the trade ♪
♪ Did you add up
all the cards left to play ♪
♪ To zero
♪ And sign up with people
♪ Angeles
♪ Don't start with me
tryin' ♪
Will, come on.
Will!
Will, that's it!
We're done!
I'm sitting in your office
and the boy isn't here.
Well, it's 10 past 5:00.
An hourand
10 minutes late.
♪ I can make you satisfied
in everything ♪
Well, if he doesn't show up
and I file a report saying
he wasn't here...
and he goes back to jail,
it won't be on
my conscience.
♪ Now be coming true ♪
Okay. Fine.
What's up?
Thanks.
Ah! Fuck, that's good.
So how's your lady?
Ah, she's gone.
Gone? Gone where?
Med school.
Medical school in California.
Really?Yeah.
When was this?It was, like, a week ago.
That sucks.
So, uh, when are you done
with those meetings?
I think the week
after I'm 21.
They gonna hook ya up
with a job or what?
Yeah, fuckin' sit in a room
and do long division
for the next 50 years.
Nah, probably make
some nice bank though.
I'm gonna be
a fuckin' lab rat.
Better than this shit.
Way outta here.
What do I want a way
outta here for?
I mean, I'm gonna fuckin'
live here the rest of my life.
You know, be neighbors.
You know, have little kids.
Fuckin' take 'em
to Little League together
up Foley Field.
Look, you're my best
friend, so don't take
this the wrong way.
But in 20 years if
you're still livin' here,
comin' over to my house
to watch the Patriots games,
still workin' construction,
I'll fuckin' kill ya.
That's not a threat.
That's a fact.
I'll fuckin' kill ya.
What the fuck
are you talkin' about?
Look, you got something
none of us have.Oh, come on!
Why is it always this?
I fuckin' owe it to myself
to do this or that.
What if I don't want to?No, no, no. Fuck you.
You don't owe it to yourself.
You owe it to me,
'cause tomorrow I'm gonna
wake up and I'll be 50,
and I'll still
be doin' this shit.
That's all right.
That's fine.
I mean, you're sittin' on
a winnin' lottery ticket.
You're too much
of a pussy to cash it in,
and that's bullshit.
'Cause I'd do
fuckin' anything
to have what you got.
So would any of
these fuckin' guys.
Be an insult to us
if you're still
here in 20 years.
Hangin' around here
is a fuckin' waste
of your time.
You don't know that.I don't?
No. You don't know that.Oh, I don't know that.
Let me tell you what I do know.
Every day
I come by your house,
and I pick you up.
We go out and have
a few drinks and few laughs,
and it's great.
You know what the
best part of my day is?
It's for about 10 seconds:
from when I pull up to the curb
and when I get to your door.
'Cause I think maybe I'll
get up there and I'll knock on
the door and you won't be there.
No "good-bye,"
no "see ya later."
No nothing. You just left.
I don't know much,
but I know that.
[ Mutters ]
This is a disaster, Sean.
I brought you in here
because I wanted you
to help me with the boy,
not to run him out.I know what
I'm doing with the boy.
I don't care if you have
a rapport with the boy!
I don't care if
you have a few laughs,
even at my expense.
- But don't you dare undermine
what I'm trying to do here.
- Undermine?
This boy is at
a fragile point right now.
I do understand.
He is at a fragile point.
He's got problems.
What problems does he have?
That he's better off
as a janitor, in jail?
Better hanging out with
a bunch of retarded gorillas?
Why do you think he does that?
You have any fuckin' clue why?
He can handle the problems.
He can handle the work.
He obviously handled you.
Listen to me.
Why is he hiding?
Why doesn't
he trust anybody?
Because the first thing
that happened to him,
he was abandoned by
the people who were supposed
to love him the most.
Don't give me
that Freudian crap.
Why does he hang out with
those retarded gorillas,
as you call them?
Because any one of them,
if he asked them to, would
take a bat to your head.
- That's called loyalty.
- Yeah, that's very touching.
Who's he handling?
He pushes people away before
they have a chance to leave him.
It's a defense mechanism,
all right?
For 20 years, he's been
alone because of that.
If you push him right now,
it's gonna be the same thing
all over again.
I'm not gonna
let that happen to him.
Don't you do that. What?
Don't infect him with the idea
that it's okay to quit, that
it's okay to be a failure.
Because it's not okay, Sean!
And if you're angry at me
for being successful, for
being what you could have been--
- I'm not angry at you.
- Oh, yes, you're angry at me.
You resent me, but
I'm not gonna apologize
for any success I've had.
You're angry at me for doing
what you could have done!
But ask yourself, Sean--
Ask yourself...
if you want Will to feel
that way-- if you want him
to feel like a failure?
You arrogant shit!
That's why I don't come to the
goddamn reunions, 'cause I can't
stand that look in your eye.
That condescending,
embarrassed look.Oh, come on, Sean.
You think I'm a failure.
I know who I am.
I'm proud of what I do.
It was a conscious choice.
I didn't fuck up!
And you and your cronies think
I'm some sort of pity case.
You and your kiss-ass chorus
following you around going,
"The Field's medal!"
Why are you still so
fuckin' afraid of failure?
It's about my medal, isn't it?
Oh, God, I could go home and get
it for you. You can have it.
Shove the medal up
your fuckin' ass, all right?
'Cause I don't give
a shit about your medal,
because I knew you before
you were a mathematical god,
when you were pimple-faced
and homesick and didn't know
what side of the bed to piss on.
Yeah, you were smarter
than me then and you're
smarter than me now.
So don't blame me for
how your life turned out.
I don't blame you!
It's not about you!
You mathematical dick!
It's about the boy!
He's a good kid! And I won't
see you fuck him up like you're
tryin' to fuck up me right now.
I won't see you make him
feel like a failure too!
He won't be a failure!But if you push him!
If you ride him!
I am what I am today
because I was pushed and because
I learned to push myself.
He's not you!
You get that!
I can come back.
No, come in.
Uh, I was just leaving.
A lot of that stuff goes back
a long way between me and him.
You know. Not about you.
[ Paper Rustles ] What is that?
This is your file.
I have to send it back to
the judge for evaluation.
Oh. Hey, you're not
gonna fail me, are you?
What's it say?
Wanna read it?Why?
Have you had any, uh,
experience with that?
Twenty years of counseling.
Yeah, I've seen some
pretty awful shit.
I mean, have you had
any experience with that?
Personally?Yeah.
Yeah, I have.
It sure ain't good.
My father was an alcoholic.
Mean fuckin' drunk.
He'd come home hammered,
lookin' to whale
on somebody.
So I'd provoke him so
he wouldn't go after my mother
and little brother.
Interesting nights
when he wore his rings.
He used to just
put a wrench,
a stick and a belt
on the table.
Just say, "Choose."Well, I gotta
go with the belt there.
I used to go with the wrench.
Why the wrench?
'Cause fuck him, that's why.
Your foster father?Yeah.
So, uh, what is it,
like, Will has
an attachment disorder?
Is it all that stuff?
Fear of abandonment?
Is that why I broke up
with Skylar?
I didn't know you had.Yeah, I did.
You wanna talk about it?No.
Hey, Will,
I don't know a lot.
You see this?
All this shit?
It's not your fault.
[ Whispers ]
Yeah, I know that.
Look at me, son.
It's not your fault.I know.
No. It's not
your fault.
I know.
No, no, you don't.
It's not your fault.
Hmm?I know.
It's not your fault.All right.
It's not your fault.
[ Whispers ]
It's not your fault.Don't fuck with me.
It's not your fault.
Don't fuck with me, all right?
Don't fuck with me, Sean,
not you.
It's not your fault.
[ Sobs ]
[ Sobs ][ Whispers ]
It's not your fault.
My God--
My God! I'm so sorry!
My God!
[ Sobbing Continues ]
Fuck them, okay?
[ Barking ]
[ Elevator Bell Dings ]
[ Chattering ]
Can I help you?Yeah, I'm Will Hunting.
I'm here about a position.
Could you just have
a seat for a moment?
[ Man ]
Yes, there's a Mr. Hunting
in the lobby.
Which one did you take?
I was over at McNeil.
It's one of the jobs
the professor set me up with.
I haven't told him yet,
but I went down there
and talked to my boss--
My new boss.
He seemed like a good guy.
Is that what you want?Yeah, you know,
I think so.
Well, good for you.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Time's up.
So that's--
So that's it?
So we're done?
Yeah, that's it.
You're done.
You're a free man.
Well, um, I just want you
to know, Sean, that--
You're welcome, Will.
So, you know, I hope
we keep in touch, you know.
Yeah, me too.
I'll be travelin'
around a bit. It'll be
a little hard, but, uh--
I've got an answering
machine at the college
I'll be checking in with.
So, here's the number.
You call that.
I'll get back
to you right away.
Yeah, you know,
I figured I'm just gonna...
put my money back
on the table and see
what kind of cards I get.
You do what's in your heart,
son. You'll be fine.
Thank you, Sean.Uh--
Thank you, Will.
Hey, does this violate
the patient-doctor
relationship?
Naw. Only if you
grab my ass.
Take care.You too.
Yeah.
Hey.
Good luck, son.
[ Morgan ]
Two beers.
What's up?
Did you guys go?
No. I had to talk him down.
Why didn't you yoke him?Little Morgan's
got a lot of scrap to him.
People try to whip
his ass every week.
Fuckin' kid won't back down. What are you sayin' about me?
Was I talkin' to you?
Then mind your fuckin' business. [ Door Opens ]
[ Chuckie ]
Go get me a beer. I ordered two beers!
Hey, asshole.What, bitch?
-Happy birthday.
-Thought we forgot, huh, bitch?
- Come on!
- I'm goin'. I'm goin'.
All right. Who's first?
Come on,
motherfucker!Who's first?
♪ Oh, Danny boy ♪
Here's your present.
Come on, bro.What?
Well, we knew you had to get
back and forth to Cambridge
for your new job.
I knew I wasn't gonna
fuckin' drive you
every day, so--
Morgan wanted
to get you a "T" pass.That's not what I was sayin'!
But, uh, you're 21 now.
You're legally allowed
to drink, so we figured
the best thing for ya was a car.
How do you like it?This is like--
It's the ugliest fuckin' car
I've ever seen in my life.
Come on, brother.How'd you guys do this?
You know, me and Bill
scraped together the parts,
and Morgan was out panhandlin'
for change every day.
I had the router to do
all the bodywork.
Yeah, I have a fuckin' job,
too, brother.
Guy's been up my ass for
two years about a job. I had
to let him help with the car.
So you finally got a job,
huh, Morgan?
Yeah, had one.
Now I'm fucked again.So what is it?
A lawn mower?
What do ya got? It's a straight fuckin' six.
Me and Bill rebuilt
this engine ourselves here.
It's a good car.
The engine's good.
Engine's good.
Happy 21, Will.Happy 21, brother.
Hi.
Come on in.
Sean, I, um--
Me too, Gerry.
Yeah. Good.
I heard you're
takin' some time.
Yeah. Travel a little bit,
maybe write.
So where are you going?
India and China
and Baltimore.
Oh.
You know when
you'll be back?
Oh. I got this flyer
the other day.
It says, uh, class of '72
is having a reunion
in six months.
Yeah, I got
one of those too.
Why don't you come?
I'll buy ya a drink.
The drinks at
those things are free.
I know, Gerry.
I was being ironical.
Oh.How about a drink
right now?
Yeah. It's a good idea.
Come on.
This one's on me.
I got the winner
right here, pal.Oh!
Yes, sir, this is the one.
This is my ticket
to paradise.
Do you know what the odds
are against winning
the lottery?
What? Four to one?About 30 million to one.
I still have a shot,
you know?[ Laughs ]
Yes, just about as big chance
as you being hit by lightning
here on the staircase right now.
It's a possibility too.
I mean, 32 million.
If you look at the size--
[ Bell Tolling ]
[ Horn Honks ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
Will!
[ Knocking ]
Will?
[ Horn Honks ]
He's not there.
♪ I'll fake it
through the day ♪
[ Will's Voice ]
Sean, if the professor
calls about that job,
just tell him sorry,
I had to go see about a girl.
Will.
Son of a bitch.
He stole my line.
♪ To take its toll
and in having a lot ♪
♪ Of nothin' to do
♪ Do you miss me
♪ Miss misery
♪ Like you say you do
♪ I know you'd rather
see me gone ♪
♪ Than to see me
♪ The way
♪ That I am, when I am
♪ In the life anyway
♪ Next door TV's
flashing through ♪
♪ Frames on the wall
♪ It's a comedy
♪ Of errors, you see
♪ It's about
takin' a fall ♪
♪ To vanish into
♪ Oblivion
♪ It's easy to do
♪ And I try to be
♪ But you know me
I come back ♪
♪ When you want me to
♪ Do you miss me
♪ Miss misery
♪ Like you say you do ♪
♪ Gonna find my baby
Gonna hold her tight ♪
♪ Gonna grab
some afternoon delight ♪
♪ My motto's always been
When it's right, it's right ♪
♪ Why wait until the middle
of a cold, dark night ♪
♪ When everything's a little
clearer in the light of day ♪
♪ And we know the night is
always gonna be here anyway ♪
♪ Thinkin' of you
is workin' up an appetite ♪
♪ Lookin' forward to
a little afternoon delight ♪
♪ Rubbin' sticks and stones
together make the sparks
ignite ♪
♪ And the thought of rubbin' you
is gettin' so excitin' ♪
♪ Skyrockets in flight
♪ Afternoon delight
♪ Started out this mornin'
feelin' so polite ♪
♪ I always thought a fish
could not be caught
who didn't bite ♪
♪ But you got
some bait a-waitin'
and I think I might ♪
♪ Like nibblin' a little
afternoon delight ♪
♪ Skyrockets in flight
♪ Afternoon delight
♪ Be waitin' for me, baby
when I come around ♪
♪ We can make a lot of lovin'
before the sun go down ♪
♪ Thinkin' of you
is workin' up an appetite ♪
♪ Lookin' forward to
a little afternoon delight ♪
♪ Rubbin' sticks and stones
together make the sparks
ignite ♪
♪ And the thought of rubbin' you
is gettin' so excitin' ♪
♪ Skyrockets in flight
♪ Afternoon delight
♪ Aft
♪ Afternoon delight ♪