Previously onGotham...
- Is it loaded?
- Ain't no point in unloaded gun.
It's Kristen Kringle's
final pay cheques.
She never picked them up.
I don't like it.
Possible you are making progress.
By the laws of Gotham City
is hereby declared sane.
You are a free man.
I was wondering if you'd heard
from Kristen Kringle lately.
Do you think that something bad
has happened?
We have no idea
when she might wake up.
- Bitch.
- So that's the game,
is it, Jimbo?
You're gonna try to outsmart me?
- I don't think so.
- We've met before?
Yes. You killed my parents.
- Who hired you?
- You'll never know their name.
I'm a monster. You need to kill me.
You're just a man.
- Bruce.
- He's in there.
Alfred, I've left home for a while
to live on the street with Selina.
Trust me and honor my wishes,
don't try to bring me back.
Welcome to
the Gotham Museum of Art.
The museum offers hundreds
of new events
and programmes each month,
including lectures,
performances, tours,
family activities and more.
The Gotham Museum Cafe
and Gift Shop is located on the...
Keep moving.
Solo robber hit the museum
about an hour ago.
Scared people away with a bomb
that never went off.
- Anybody hurt?
- No.
Why us, then?
Isn't it a Robbery Squad case?
Bomb threats are you guys.
Whether the bomb goes off or not.
So get on it.
Gordon, you stay.
Internal Affairs is re-opening
the file on Galavan's murder.
Why?
Anonymous tip.
Someone called in,
claims they saw you,
not Penguin, kill Galavan
that night on the docks.
I.A. gets a dozen crank calls a week.
They're probably just bored.
This tip came with a detail
we didn't put out to the public.
The umbrella.
So someone in the GCPD
is trying to make trouble for me,
by spreading lies.
- Been known to happen.
- Lies?
Tell me the truth again.
I didn't kill Galavan.
I wasn't there.
- What was that about?
- Later.
- Detective Gordon.
- Hey, Ed.
- I'm ready for our sit down.
- Our what?
You wanted to interview me
about Ms. Kringle leaving town
- with Officer Dougherty?
- Right, yeah.
Sorry, rain check.
We gotta get to Gotham Museum.
The art heist.
Yes, I heard about this. Very bold.
Yes, rain check.
Tally ho, chaps. Go get that bad guy.
We'll talk later this afternoon.
And, Ed, don't worry.
I'll find out what happened
to Ms. Kringle.
I have the utmost faith in your
abilities, Detective Gordon.
Believe me.
Boss...
You'll never guess
who just knocked on the door.
If I'm never guessing,
why not just tell me, jackass?
If you say I have three guesses,
well, then that's a game.
It's an annoying and stupid game,
but at least it makes sense.
Son of a...
Hi.
Well, well, well.
I heard they let you out of Arkham.
Yes.
Happy day.
I'm sane.
I have a certificate...
But, I hope I'm not intruding.
I just got back in town.
I thought it would be rude
not to say hello to an old friend.
- An old friend?
- Well, yes.
I mean, we had our ups and downs,
but on the whole,
I thought we were friends.
Weren't we?
That's what I recall anyhow.
You want cupcake?
You killed my brother.
You messed with his mind
and made him your slave.
Hello?
I guess I was pretty terrible?
I want to apologize sincerely.
I wasn't thinking straight.
Apology accepted.
- Let's kill him.
- Wait, what?
Butch, listen, I've changed.
You have no reason to fear me. I'm...
I'm a good person now.
I was thinking about visiting
your mother's grave.
Miss the old bird.
Her sobs would often lull me
to sleep at night.
"Oswald, Oswald, save me."
That does sound like her.
You know, I think he's for real.
The loony bin doctors must have
really done a number on him.
I'm actually kind of sad.
Let him go.
What?
You heard me.
Look at him, he's a pathetic loser.
He doesn't pose a threat to anyone.
Are you serious?
No way. He has to die.
Who's the boss here?
I believe in an eye for an eye.
We've all lost something
including him.
We square. You and me.
- Understand?
- Completely.
Fine. You know, I didn't realize
you were so sentimental.
He's not leaving without some
kind of punishment.
- He's not.
- Okay.
What do you have in mind?
Your little private,
inside voice is screaming.
Wanna tell me what that pow wow
with Barnes is all about?
I.A. is re-opening the investigation
into the murder of Theo Galavan.
Anonymous person called
in saying they saw me kill him.
That old chestnut?
Is there something I can do?
You still friendly
with your gal over in I.A.?
Ginny?
Our paths have been known to cross.
Can they cross again soon?
I need to know what they have.
Sure.
Mr. Thatch.
Detective Gordon.
This is Detective Bullock.
What can you tell us about
the painting that was stolen?
The painting is entitled
Mad Grey Dawn.
Depicted a railway explosion
of the tunnel at the center.
A minor work compared
to much of the collection.
Strangely, he simply deface
too much more valuable paintings
in another section of the gallery.
A Marche and a LaRue.
Follow me.
Priceless.
What kind of art thief would take
time to defile such masterpieces?
- An ignorant one?
- No.
He has took a lot of time and effort.
He knows what he's doing.
He's not interested in profit.
He's trying to send a message.
Which is what?
No idea.
What about the painters themselves?
What about them?
The question marks are directly
over their signatures on the canvas.
There's entire books
written on each of them.
- I'm sorry...
- Hey, we wanna keep it simple.
What about their names?
Marche means Market
and LaRue is the road, yes?
- Yes?
- Or the street.
Market Street.
Painting he stole...
Depicted a railway explosion?
- Yes?
- Yes.
A bombing actually.
It was known as Bloody Monday.
Today is Monday.
And Union Railway Station
is on Market Street.
Attention, please evacuate
the train station in an orderly...
Please find the nearest exit
and evacuate the train station...
- What are we looking for?
- I have no idea.
Get these people out of here. Go! Go!
- Get out of here! Go!
- Move!
Move!
- Bullock.
That's enough!
The device is inside the lockers!
Hey, can you get these people
out of here.
- Get them out of here.
- Outside, now.
Get them out of here! Go! Go!
- Move it!
- Straight ahead here.
Move!
How much time
until the bomb squad gets here?
Too long.
- Get back.
- Back, back, back.
- Go! Go! Go!
- Get them out of here!
- Go! Go!
Get a medic!
- Hey, Ivy.
- Hey, Cat.
Hey, Billionaire Boy.
What is he doing here?
They're right upstairs.
- He's staying with me for a while.
- Don't touch anything.
What is this place?
Ivy works for a gang that runs
the magic mushroom trade.
- What's a magic mushroom?
- Some give you visions.
Some give you energy.
Some help you to sleep.
I've cultivated over a dozen kinds.
What are we doing here?
The gang is run
by Gilzean's nephew, Sonny,
and his merry band of losers.
- So, these mushrooms are illegal?
- Yes, very illegal.
Which means there's always
a ton of cash around.
You're going to rob them?
Yeah?
Okay.
How do we do it?
We don't.
You have money, remember?
- A lot of it.
- Selina, I told you.
I wanna survive on my own.
Find out who I am without my money,
without being Bruce Wayne.
Besides...
I don't mind stealing
if it's from criminals.
What's the plan?
Meet Psilocybe Arkrescens.
Also known as the blue devil.
She slipped a few of them
into the gang's lunch today,
so all we have to do now is wait.
- What will they do?
- Instant death.
Kidding.
They'll be in a state
of relaxed bliss.
Like a dream.
Trust me. It's great.
How long until they're out?
Mad thief and mad bomber
in the same day.
- What the hell is next?
- I don't know.
But he wanted us to find it.
I think that was the heist was about.
He's playing a game.
Great.
That's exactly what this city needs.
Did you find any other brain-teasers
that might indicate his next piece
- of performance art?
- No,
either he's decided to keep it
a surprise,
- or he's taking a break.
- I doubt we're that lucky.
I want every available resource
on this thing.
You got it.
Excuse me.
Officer Pinkney,
can I get your signature
- on this chain of custody form?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
- Pinkney.
Detective Gordon.
We're working together
for over a year, Ed.
You can call me, Jim.
Jim. I heard you were able
to save the day.
- I got lucky.
- I don't believe in luck.
You saw a problem,
and you solved it. Bravo.
Hey, I want you to oversee
forensics on this one.
Maybe our luck will hold,
and we'll get something
on the bomb's signature
or trace elements.
- No other leads, yet?
- No.
I have no idea what this guy wants
or what he's after.
Which makes him dangerous.
Well, don't you worry.
I'm on the case.
All right.
Be quiet.
Someone might still be awake.
- Wait.
- Hey.
Hey. Hey.
We're no one.
You're dreaming.
- Pretty cool, right?
- Totally.
Yeah.
Listen, if you give us
the coffee can...
And close your eyes,
you'll be able to fly.
Sweet.
Run.
Where are you going?
Hey, Cat.
Hey, Sonny.
You lose weight?
Keep cracking wise, Selina.
You ain't gonna be smiling
when my uncle gets to you.
See how many lives
you really have left.
- Hi.
- Penguin?
- Hi. Hi.
- Hi.
I am sorry to intrude.
I'm a bit of a mess.
I was just passing by and... and...
May I...
Can I come in for a moment?
These feathers aren't as warm
as they look.
Of course. Where are my manners?
It's so good to see you.
So, how have you been, old friend?
Well, I hope.
Yeah. Well.
I have been busy.
Have been really busy.
And what about you?
I hear that you've been released.
What... What? What happened?
Well, just good old Butch
and Tabitha having fun.
They talked about killing me, so...
This was actually pretty nice
of them, considering.
Pretty nice of them?
They did a pretty good job on you
in Arkham?
I'm here to tell you, Ed,
as a friend,
violence and anger are not
the answer.
I'm a changed man. Better.
You can change too.
Cool.
Tempting offer.
The thing is...
The me I am right now is just
kind of hating my stride.
And I'm really grateful
for all that you've taught me.
And that bad stuff you told me
about Jim Gordon
is really paying off.
- Is it?
- It is. It's helped me
to create the perfect puzzle
to get rid of my Jim Gordon dilemma.
Normally, I would love to share,
but to be honest,
this new you is kind of
freaking me out.
- I'm just really busy right now.
- Well, I'll be on my way.
Thank you for coming by.
So I spoke with my gal in I.A.
The snitch said Penguin
was beating Galavan to death
when you stepped in
and put a bullet in his chest.
Someone else was there that night.
Either that or Penguin talked.
He did just get out of Arkham.
How the hell he did?
I'll never know,
but let's not forget, he was in there
for a murder you committed.
A grudge is not beyond the realm
of possibility.
He could've talked
when he was arrested.
Used it to cut a deal but he didn't.
Did you I.A. contact
gave you anything else?
The witness has agreed
to swear out a statement.
I.A. has officially reopened
the investigation.
You're now the primary suspect
in the murder of Theo Galavan.
Well, tell my uncle to call me.
Look, I know you think
he's got a soft spot for you,
but I'm pretty sure
that's gonna change
when he finds out
you tried to rob him.
My guess is he's not gonna be
too happy with you, either,
when I tell him I just waltzed
in here and grabbed the cash.
So...
Maybe you let us go,
and we call it even?
What kind of message
would that send?
No. The Gilzeans are all about
consequences.
More like all about pizza.
- You ever tried our product, Selina?
- Stop!
Aren't you being rather cowardly?
Assaulting a girl?
No, he's right.
You know, when you're right...
Knock it off, Sonny.
You made your point.
Stay out of this, Selina.
Call me a coward again.
You're a coward.
An ignorant, brutal...
Stop!
While you're down there kid,
lick my boot.
Strength causes wind.
Now, if you're gonna be a big man,
all you have to do is outlast him.
Stop!
I actually think he wants a beating.
Is that your thing, kid?
You like pain?
An ignorant, brutish, cowardly clown.
Yes. He likes it, all right.
Your mum and dad
must have been real freaks,
bringing up a weird kid like you.
Enough!
Let's go! Let's go!
Hello, mother.
What a lovely spot.
I'm so sorry
I couldn't be here for the funeral.
But I think you'd be proud of me.
I'm a changed man.
Or...
At least, I'm trying to be.
To be honest...
I don't know
if I'm gonna make it without you.
Hello.
I'm terribly sorry,
I don't mean to interrupt.
Not at all.
- Lilies.
- Her favorite, if memory serves.
Yes, they were.
Did you know her?
A long time ago.
I found her again only in death,
I'm afraid.
I'm Elijah Van Dahl.
Oswald Cobblepot.
Cobblepot?
You're related to Gertrud?
My mother.
Mother?
You're Gertrud's son?
Yes.
I'm sorry, I... How did you know
my mother, exactly?
- How old are you?
- Excuse me?
How old are you?
- Gertrud left...
- I am 31.
31 years ago, yes. That's right.
Oh, my god, she...
She never told me.
Told you what?
That I had a son.
Any word at the bomber?
Bullock is waiting on forensics.
I just wish
I knew what his end game was.
Feels like I'm missing something.
Is that why you're not eating?
Yeah, I guess.
No.
I.A is re-opening the investigation
into Galavan's murder.
- Why?
- An eye-witness came forward.
You told me it was over, Jim,
you swore to me.
I'm sorry.
I knew in my heart that it wasn't
but I let you lie to me.
I didn't, I wasn't.
We should have left
when we had the chance.
Go to somewhere new,
somewhere better,
- somewhere fit to raise our child.
- You knew I couldn't do that.
I can fix this.
How?
You did it, you killed Galavan.
I'll find a way. I have to.
What if you can't?
Hello, Officer Pinkney.
I'm so sorry to bother you at home.
Can I come in?
Sure.
Make it quick, the ballgame is on.
What's this about?
Detective Gordon, he'll explain.
He's just behind me.
Oh, okay.
Hey, Pinkney.
What do you call
a tavern of blackbirds?
A crowbar.
You get it? A crowbar.
I know it's kind of lame.
I just came up with it on the spot.
Come on!
Gertrud came to work
as a cook for my parents.
She was so young and beautiful.
So full of life.
So beautiful.
I was young then too, a boy, really.
A foolish romantic boy.
When my parents found out...
They forbade us from being together.
I was the heir to a great fortune,
they said.
And she was just a cook.
I threatened to run away with her.
Turn my back on my family name
and my inheritance.
It was the first and only time
I ever stood up to them.
They must have known
my words were just that.
A spoiled child making idle threats.
The next day, Gertrud was gone.
My parents told me only that
they had come to an arrangement.
She would be taken care of,
and I must never make
an attempt to find her.
And to my shame, I didn't.
I let them separate us.
I had no idea.
She never told me she was pregnant.
She didn't told me about you.
- If she did...
- She...
Told me that my father had died
when I was still a baby.
Easier than the truth, I suppose.
That your father was a coward,
who wouldn't stand up to his parents.
She must have figured
that the two of you would be
better off making your own way,
which in fact,
was probably the truth.
Look at you.
A strong young man.
She did a good job, didn't she?
She tried.
We both miss her terribly.
My poor boy.
You've been all alone in the world.
Yes, I have.
No longer.
You have a home...
And a father...
And a family.
- A family?
- A big, happy family.
They're going to be
so thrilled to meet you.
Sir, please...
Tell me truthfully, is this a dream?
It's not a dream, my boy.
You're home.
- Yeah.
- Forensics just landed.
The timer on the bomb
was activated remotely by phone,
which is smart.
Gave him time to plant it in advance
and set it off when he wanted.
- We get a number?
- Yeah.
The call came from a payphone
inside 17 West Dewy Avenue.
Just a few blocks from Union Station.
A payphone?
All right, I'll go over there
and check it out.
- See you tomorrow.
- It's probably long gone by now.
- I can't sleep anyhow.
- Yeah.
Hello?
Pinkney.
Gordon?
What the hell are you doing here?
Put your gun down, now!
Place your gun on the floor.
I won't say it again.
Okay.
Listen to me.
I was just following up a lead
on the bomber investigation.
You were following a lead
in Pinkney's apartment?
No.
I didn't know that this was
Pinkney's apartment building.
Why are you here?
Pinkney send me a message.
He wanted to talk outside of work.
About what?
You.
I have to take you down
to the precinct.
There's been a mistake.
I hope so, son.
I hope so.
Almost done.
I've never seen someone
take a beating like that before.
I think Sonny is right,
you do like pain.
When it was happening...
It was like nothing else existed.
Everything...
I've been struggling with,
the emptiness...
And confusion...
It just vanished.
And for the first time...
In a long time...
I knew I was going to be okay.
I knew that whatever Sonny did to me.
I could take it.
That he couldn't break me.
That no one can.
Nobody is unbreakable, Bruce.
You want your rep here?
I didn't do this. Somebody set me up.
Cause of death,
blunt force trauma to the head.
Captain, listen to me...
Murder weapon was a crowbar.
We found it under the couch.
Your fingerprints were on it.
At Union Station, I used
a crowbar to open up the locker.
Somebody must have picked it up.
And that someone
just happened to know
that you'd be paying
Officer Pinkney a visit tonight?
I told you, I didn't know
that he lived there.
Forensics traced the bomber's call
to a payphone in the building.
- Bullock will back me up.
- He did.
But when I asked for the report,
it had nothing to do with a
remote timer or any traced call.
I know how this looks...
But Pinkney was one of us.
Why would I kill him?
Because he was the anonymous
witness that fingered you.
We found this.
Internal Affairs form
at Pinkney's place.
It's the exact same statement
that the anonymous witness made.
Only Pinkney has signed this
with his own name.
I guess he got cold feet about
putting himself on the line.
So he sent in
the anonymous tip instead.
He must have figured you'd get nasty.
I don't know how you figured it out.
But you found out he was the witness.
- No.
- Maybe,
you went over to his place
to talk him out of it?
I told you,
I didn't know it was his place!
Or maybe you had
no intention of talking
and you just killed him.
You know, me.
I know that something went down
between you and Galavan that night!
I saw it in your eyes
when I.A. was grilling you.
And now, the one person
who was about to shine light
on this whole thing,
is found beaten to death
with you standing over the body!
- What am I missing?
- I was set up!
Jim!
How many lying son-of-a-bitch,
low-life weasels have you heard
used that same line?
Somebody set you up?
That's what you're going with?
And the least you can do
is admit what you did.
Be a man!
Pinkney was one of us.
He deserves that.
I deserve that!
The least you can do
is look me in the eye
and remind me that you were
a good cop once.
That you still know right from wrong.
Jim!
I wanna talk to my rep.
You're a disgrace to the badge.
I trusted you!
And you broke my heart.
You, take him to County.
I don't want him here.
- Jim?
- Harvey.
The bomber, Harvey.
Everything that happened today
was set up to trap me!
The bomber, Harvey!
The four-week murder trial
of Detective Gordon
concluded just minutes ago,
with the jury returning
the unanimous verdict of guilty.
The judge handed down
the maximum sentence of 40 years
to be served
at Blackgate Penitentiary.
The jury was unanimous
in its decision
after deliberating
less than 24 hours.
District Attorney Harvey Dent
was not available for comment...
Are you okay?
This isn't right.
This can't be right.
Tell me something that is.
Just hours ago, the murder trial
of Detective James Gordon
concluded with the jury returning
a unanimous verdict of guilty.
The judge handed down
the maximum sentence of 40 years
to be served
at Blackgate Penitentiary.
The jury was unanimous
in its decision...
My, awake at last!
District Attorney Harvey Dent
was not available for comment...
Well, hello, dear.
Someone call Professor Strange!
We're gonna fight this.
- Okay.
- Did you hear me?
No matter what it takes,
we're gonna fight this.
The evidence isn't gonna change.
You're innocent.
I'm far from this, we both know that.
So, what, we just give up?
We move on.
Move on?
Move on to what?
You mean, me? You mean, I move on?
I've thought long and hard
about this.
- No.
- You have to listen to me.
I'm tired of listening,
this is unfair!
How can you not be with us?
Birthdays.
And first steps.
And skinned knees.
I never think...
What? Visits through bars and...
And not knowing
when the phone is gonna ring
in the middle of the night
and tell me when you're...
I don't want that for either of you.
You still have a chance at happiness.
- No.
- You need to go somewhere.
Far away from here.
Somewhere fit to raise our child.
And start a new life.
Forget I exist.
The only way
either one of us survive...
No, Jim.
Don't try to contact me again.
- I won't reply.
- No.
Don't do this.
I'm sorry, Lee.
- Jim, don't do this. I love you.
- I'm so, so sorry.
Jim!
A toast.
I wanna thank you all
for your generosity.
You have welcomed Oswald
into our family
with open arms and open hearts.
And for that,
I am truly blessed.
To the family...
You guys have made me
the happiest man on the planet.
I...
I'm so grateful.
I love you all.
Family.
- To the family.
- Brother.
- Yes, yes.
Yes.
Main door at the prison transfer,
open gate.
I'm gonna find who set you up.
This ain't over.
Yeah.
You were a good partner, Harvey.
Still, I am.