JIM: Previously on Gotham...
We're onto you, Professor Strange.
Bad guys come in and monsters come out.
I am Firefly.
Selina. Hugo Strange has Selina.
Do you remember your name?
My name is Fish Mooney.
Make me a grilled cheese sandwich.
You made me a sandwich? Why?
I don't know.
And how exactly do you plan on getting
into Arkham?
I'll ask for a tour.
From the man that ordered
the assassination of your father?
He'll wanna find out what we know.
And he won't see me
and Lucius as a threat.
I call Bullock,
he comes busting in with a hundred cops.
Take them.
Move everything you can
to the facility upstate.
You have an explosive device. Use it.
Destroy Indian Hill.
Basil is a chameleon of sorts.
Would you like to see?
You son of a bitch!
I'm Jim Gordon.
Right. Go get our guys.
(SIRENS BLARING)
(GUNS COCKING)
No sign of Gordon.
How long do you want us to wait?
Give him 10 seconds.
If you don't see Jim,
bust that joint open and find him.
Ready, entry team. We go on one!
- Go!
(RAPID BEEPING)
(BEEPING)
Go. Go!
Four, three, two--
(GATE CREAKING)
JIM: Stand down.
- Stand down, officers.
- Hold. Hold.
Stand down.
- All clear.
- OFFICER: Stand down. Stand down.
All clear?
Sorry to waste your time, hoss.
How about a ride to HQ?
Sure thing, Jim. You okay?
You look kinda hinky.
Never better.
JIM: Strange! Strange!
Strange! Strange, you son of a bitch.
Come back here!
- So, you're really doing this?
- Not my call.
Prepare the patients for transport
to the upstate facility.
If even one of your patients
were to escape--
They won't.
The police won't be delayed much longer.
Prepare the patients and move fast.
As soon as we're done
with Gordon and Wayne,
we will detonate the bomb.
Yes, sir.
Uh...
Okay, quiz kids.
Who's ready to play, "Life or Death"?
Sir, Mr. Nygma. You are Nygma, aren't you?
This is absurd. The police know
we're here, you can't kill us.
Are you ready to play?
Yes.
Good.
You have one guess,
five minutes to talk it over.
- Who runs Indian Hill?
- (CLICKING)
Who runs Indian Hill? You have one guess.
Think carefully, fellas.
Answer correctly,
or die.
- Strange.
- (DOOR OPENING)
- Strange?
- Hi.
What is that?
Honesty serum.
- I need to know what you know.
- Wait. Wait.
So, how do you feel now?
Not good.
Can you be more specific?
I feel vulnerable.
Naked.
Your feelings are entirely
natural and normal.
There is nothing to be ashamed of.
You are in a helpless situation.
There is nothing you can do.
Do you understand that?
Yes.
- No.
- No?
What can you do?
James, what can you do?
- Made a plan.
- Tell me your plan.
If I don't check in with the GCPD by noon,
tell them I'm safe,
they'll come after you.
Yes.
Yes, I know.
You did check in with the GCPD.
Nobody's coming.
You can relax.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Jim! Jim!
- Harv.
- Strange is clean?
What the hell happened?
- Dead end.
- "Dead end"?
What are you talking about? Dead end?
- He's connected.
- So is my mechanic. Who isn't?
- Connected to people we can't cross.
- What people?
You don't wanna know.
Trust me.
You feelin' all right?
You look like a sack of fish.
A little flu, maybe.
Oh. Keep your distance.
I'm getting laid this weekend.
Fingers crossed.
(BULLOCK LAUGHING)
ED: You have 60 seconds left.
Who runs Indian Hill?
I say, Hugo Strange.
Wayne Enterprises.
Wayne Enterprises runs Indian Hill.
That's surmised.
Why would he ask that question
if the answer was obvious?
He wants to know what we know.
- What we think we know.
- Which is Wayne Enterprises.
Is that your answer?
Running out of time here.
Yes.
Correct!
- Wayne Enterprises runs Indian Hill.
- (FANFARE PLAYING)
Bravo, Brucey.
You're almost safe.
Just one more question.
- You ready?
- Yes.
You have five minutes, quiz kids.
Answer correctly or die.
Wayne Enterprises runs Indian Hill,
but who runs Wayne Enterprises?
(ROARING AND SCREECHING)
Move 'em out in order of security grades.
Lowest risk, first.
Tranq 'em, immobilize them,
and put them on the bus.
And do it fast, but very, very carefully.
Security is our number-one priority.
MAN: Yes, ma'am.
(GRUNTS)
- Hey, lady.
- MS. PEABODY: Busy day, busy day.
We'll get to you, number 13.
Your mama may be number 13,
but I'm a human being.
Fish Mooney, bitch.
Here,
you're reanimant test case number 13.
And I'm Ms. Peabody.
And you best not talk about my mama.
Ms. Peabody,
I apologize.
I'm a bit stressed.
I don't like being locked up.
It's against my nature.
I understand, I do.
But you are a priceless,
scientific miracle.
You are history.
Seclusion is regrettable but inevitable.
Look, I've been here before.
All you mad scientists
say the same kind of stuff.
I don't care.
Let me go.
Sorry, 13.
Let's go.
You're messing with the wrong woman.
You hear me? The wrong woman.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(RADIO TUNING)
(OPERA MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
Here?
A little too central, maybe?
You don't want one piece
to overpower the room.
Try over there.
You're absolutely right.
See, I told you she'd be useful.
Isn't that better?
Interior design ain't my thing.
NEWSCASTER ON RADIO:
News on the hour with WTGC.
Police sources say that reports of
an impending raid on Arkham Insane Asylum
and its controversial chief,
Professor Hugo Strange, are inaccurate.
Despite the disclaimers,
flurries of police activity around
the troubled facility have fueled...
Hugo Strange.
How interesting.
HUGO: Answer quickly, please, Jim,
without thinking.
Who did you love more,
your mother or your father?
- Mother.
- Why?
I resented my father's strength.
- I see, yes. And when he died...
- Yes.
...how did you feel?
- Guilty.
- For a car crash?
Why? It was not your fault.
I imagined he was gone and then he was.
- You lost a child recently.
- Yes.
How does that make you feel?
Guilty.
Guilt, again. You blame yourself?
It was my fault.
Oh, I see, I didn't know that.
And what happened to the mother?
Lee, was it?
She's down south somewhere.
- You still love her?
- Yes.
- You want to be with her?
Why aren't you with her?
I've put her through enough pain.
Jim, I need you to relax.
Close your eyes.
Imagine that I am God.
All powerful.
I am God,
and I absolve you of all of your guilt.
I put that guilt on you. And now...
I take it away.
It's gone. Your burdens are gone.
So, how do you feel?
(SOFTLY) Good. Better.
Good.
Good. Good.
Jim,
now that we're relaxed
and speaking honestly, tell me,
what do you know about
our work here at Indian Hill?
You're building monsters for military use.
Oh, we're doing much more than that.
But for who?
Who owns Indian Hill?
Wayne Enterprises.
And who controls Wayne Enterprises
behind the scenes?
Who controls everything in Gotham?
Behind the scenes.
I don't know.
- The rich.
- Well, they are rich, I'm sure.
But can you be more specific?
Who controls Gotham, Jim?
You've never heard of a...
Secret council?
No.
Excellent.
Excellent. Thank you.
That's what I needed to know.
Professor Strange?
- Yes, Jim?
- What you said about Lee,
I should've gone after her?
Oh, no doubt.
Guilt has compelled you to sacrifice
your heart to your conscience,
but guilt is useless.
Love, Jim.
Love is our guide.
(WATCH BEEPING)
Time's up, I'm afraid.
In the spirit of intimacy and honesty,
I have been speaking about your life
as if it had a future,
and that is not so.
You have a few hours.
You have 30 seconds left.
Who runs Wayne Enterprises?
(STAMMERS) The Devil, maybe.
Is that the deal?
Communists? Witches?
No, there's some trick
behind his question. Some big secret.
I've worked for Wayne Enterprises
for 10 years.
There is no big secret.
The board of directors
runs Wayne Enterprises.
Fifteen seconds.
That can't be the answer, Lucius!
- Ten seconds.
- Give us more time!
- Five seconds!
- The board of directors.
(SIGHS)
(CLICKS)
Incorrect.
Oh, what a shame.
The correct answer is...
(MAKES HISSING SOUND)
Sorry, fellas. You lose.
And what happens to losers?
(EXCLAIMS) Yowza!
- Death by poison gas.
- (GAS HISSING)
- (ALARM BLARING)
- (ED LAUGHING)
(LAUGHTER CONTINUES)
(COUGHS)
(BODY THUDS)
(GASPING)
(GUN COCKING)
(GUNSHOT)
(LUCIUS GROANING)
(EXHALES)
Jim. Jim.
- Hi.
Are we alive?
So far, so good.
Had to be sure. Thought we were dead.
(GRUNTS)
Wow. That was unpleasant.
How are things going for you?
We've had a hell of a time.
Same.
- You okay?
- A little groggy.
He drugged me. Made me talk.
- About Wayne Enterprises, right?
- About everything.
Bruce,
I never should have made that oath to you.
- That's not really--
- I was arrogant and naive,
and I'm sorry.
I've tried to do the right thing, but...
What a fool I've been.
Uh...
What kinda drugs did they give you?
Oh, well done, Ed. I'm impressed.
- You're a shaman of sorts, a witch doctor.
- (LAUGHS)
So, just between us,
who does run Wayne Enterprises?
I could tell you,
but then I would have to lobotomize you.
Gotcha.
So, moving forward, sir,
I would be more than happy to help you
with any of your other cases.
You would be a wonderful addition
to my staff, Ed.
A wonderful addition,
if you were only sane.
- No, seriously.
- Yes, seriously.
You have been very useful,
and we arrogant physicians
have much to learn
from a mad man like you.
But not that much.
No, no, no. No!
You will not turn me into a crazy person!
No!
Madam, I bring good news.
Gordon and Wayne and Fox
know nothing but mundanities.
They have told no one the truth
because they have none of the truth.
(INDISTINCT TALKING)
Our secret is safe.
Kill them all.
Then continue with the evacuation
of your test subjects.
Yes, madam.
The destruction of Indian Hill
will proceed as scheduled.
Releasing Galavan
was a grave error on your part.
No more of your patients will see
the light of day under any circumstances,
at any cost.
I understand, madam.
(SLURPING)
These people to whom Strange is connected,
they must be pretty heavy
to make you back off.
Oh, they're heavy.
I don't want anything dangerous,
I just like being titillated.
Seriously, you don't wanna know.
Remember the time
you called me from the hospital
when you had Falcone on the gurney,
and the whole town and their uncle
were looking to kill you both?
- How could I forget?
- Remember what I said to you on the phone?
Remember what I said?
I forget.
- That's funny.
- ALFRED: Gordon, you're back.
What happened? Where's Master Bruce?
Where's Lucius?
Where are they? Have you seen them?
- Hey, Alfred, take it easy.
- Where are they?
Alfred. Alfred, relax.
Master Bruce and Lucius are, uh,
headed back to Wayne Manor.
Yeah, well, that's a load of old tosh,
for starters, innit?
I've just come back from there.
What can I tell you?
Maybe they stopped to get a snack.
- So? What about Strange?
- It's complicated.
Well, go on, then. What?
Complicated police business!
He's got a touch of the flu.
(CROWS CAWING)
(DOOR BUZZING)
(GUNS COCKING)
You.
- How you doing?
- Middling.
- What's your deal?
- Chillin'.
They're gonna blow this dump sky-high,
and the whole circus is moving upstate.
- When?
- Soon.
Like, an hour.
- Can you escape?
- Of course.
Firefly thinks I'm her sidekick,
so I got a trustee status.
Then please do so.
- Get out of here and call the police.
- I'll do what I like.
I led you into this mess,
I was self-righteous and arrogant
and manipulative.
- I used you, and I'm sorry.
- Like you can use me.
I got you wrapped around my pinkie.
Always have.
Be that as it may...
If you can escape, do it.
(SCOFFS) "Manipulative."
As if.
(DOOR OPENING)
What'd she say?
She'll do what she likes.
(DOOR CLOSING)
And there's a bomb.
(DOOR BUZZING)
(PATIENT GROWLING)
(SNARLING)
(PATIENT COUGHING)
(GASPING)
(DOOR OPENS)
Hello, number 13.
Stay calm.
No one's going to hurt you.
It's time to go on a trip.
Give me your right arm.
Say my name.
Fish Mooney.
That's right.
- What's your name?
- Ethel Peabody.
Ethel, you seem sad
and anxious.
(SIGHS) You got that right.
You let me out of here,
and I'll be your friend.
(ALARM BUZZING)
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh. Interesting.
Ms. Peabody, what are you doing?
- What she says.
- Why?
I don't know.
Ms. Mooney, you have special talents.
Some form of psychotropic chemical agent
on your skin, I imagine.
You are marvelous. Yes, truly marvelous.
- Always was.
- Indeed.
Would love to chat about me,
but we have a bus to catch.
Ah, no, Ms. Mooney,
if you and the others on that bus
were to appear in public,
you would cause a revolution.
An apocalypse.
I simply can't allow you
to just walk out of here.
- Watch me.
- No, please don't go.
Please, you're breaking my heart.
I love you like my own daughter.
No one could love you more,
but I will have to kill you
before I let you go.
Please choose life.
You would have made a great pimp.
No, no, no. No!
Bring him back.
MS. PEABODY:
Hugo, I order you to stop. Now.
Stop, now!
You hear me? (GROANS)
(BEEPING)
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
(KEYPAD BEEPING)
COMPUTER: Security systems activated.
Security systems activated.
(DOOR BUZZING)
No!
(SCREAMING)
I tried calling about 1,000 times.
Still no answer.
Strange has them, I'm positive.
Holy crap, are you still here?
I told you 1,000 times, Strange is clean.
You in charge of that, are you?
That's strange though, isn't it?
I mean, strange they're MIA.
Ah! That's funny.
- "Strange."
- "Funny"?
You know, maybe I should send
the Strike Force back into Arkham,
- to have a little look-see.
- No, no, no. You don't wanna do that.
Bad idea.
Trust me, that's a terrible idea.
How long you known me?
All right, if you're good,
I guess I'm good.
I don't know what's got to you, Gordon,
but you're just...
Weird.
Hey, Alfred.
- Miss Kean.
- How's the butlering business?
- To what do we owe the--
- Jimmy, my love.
I'm sure you're ever so busy,
but could we have a word in private?
You bet.
Well, you look terrible.
Hey, thanks, Barbara,
you look pretty good.
Shucks.
Question, what the hell's going on
down at Arkham?
Two questions back at you, gorgeous.
Why you askin', and what's in it for me?
I'm askin' because a dear friend of mine
wants to know the answer.
And what would you like
to be in it for you?
Hey, spring is here, baby.
- So, now you like me again?
- What's not to like?
- So, you've forgotten about Lee?
- "Lee"?
Lee Thompkins.
(SCOFFS) Screw that hoe.
Water under the bridge.
You're not Jim.
- Say what now?
- You're not Jim.
Whoa, whoa. Hold on there, woman.
- Holy mother of saints!
- MAN: Holy cow!
(GASPS)
Kill the captives. We have to go.
Whoa, whoa. Where are we going?
- What's the hurry?
- Silence.
Freeze, get it done.
- Jeez. Relax. What's with him?
- Quiet.
Quiet, yourself.
Why do you have to kill them?
Why are you so mean?
I knew I shouldn't have spared you.
Freeze.
Kill her.
- Wait a minute.
- I'm sorry, Firefly.
I told you she was an experiment.
But she is my friend, I need her.
We don't have time for this.
Please don't let him hurt me, Firefly.
Please help me.
Don't you dare.
Out of the way, Sparky.
- Make me.
- HUGO: Firefly, no!
No!
- What now?
- (ALARM BLARING)
Sounds like warfare.
What's going on?
Simple psychology.
Been waiting for the right moment.
You coming or what?
COMPUTER: Fifteen minutes to detonation.
Fifteen minutes to detonation.
(HUGO GROANING)
JIM: Strange.
Strange!
Wake up. Strange.
Strange.
(BEEPING)
Alpha and Charlie squads to Arkham.
Bravo and Delta to Indian Hill.
Move!
Hey, Penguin,
so it turns out
our Mr. Strange is a very bad man.
The police are on to him now.
They figure he's planning to run,
but he won't, thanks to me.
Thank you, Barbara. You have pleased me.
(PHONE CLICKS)
Saddle up, Butch.
We've got an old friend to catch.
(GRUNTS)
Wake up, Strange. I know you're in there.
Wake up.
Oh, Gordon.
I surmise my plan must have gone awry.
You could say.
I'm gonna stand you up now,
and you're gonna give us
a tour of your secret lab.
- No.
- You don't have a choice.
- It's this way, right?
- Jim, we can't go down there.
I set a bomb, the lab is going to blow up.
We have to get out of here!
In 10 minutes, everything within
a quarter-mile radius will be dust.
That's madness.
If you want to live, which I do, frankly,
we had better leave.
We detected radioactive material
down there.
- You got it out first, right?
- There wasn't enough time.
They forced my hand.
But I calculated the chances
of a radioactive cloud as fairly low.
If you're wrong,
thousands of people could die.
Yes, yes, yes.
But paying that price will be better.
Releasing what's down there...
How do we shut it down?
The security walls are up,
the lab is sealed.
- There must be some way in.
- We have to go.
We have to leave now.
You tell me how to get that bomb
and shut it off,
or I'll batter you to death right here!
HUGO: In which case, young man,
I suppose I will just have to die.
Wait, Nygma knows the way down there.
- Could use some help.
- Yep.
You two, you've got nine minutes.
Get as far away from here as you can.
- No.
- Go, go!
Lucius, this way.
Yes, of course I know how,
but what is with all the hoo-ha?
What is the rush here?
Just do it.
What do I get if I do it?
You get to live.
Fair enough.
COMPUTER: Security systems deactivated.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
Security systems deactivated.
You any good at defusing bombs?
I don't know yet. You?
(SCOFFS)
COMPUTER: Two minutes to detonation.
- (ENGINE STARTS)
- Two minutes to detonation.
(BOMB BEEPING)
Oh, my...
Got any ideas?
You got a knife?
No.
BULLOCK: (ON RADIO) We're on approach
to Arkham for patient evacuation.
We need that Bomb Squad ASAP.
(SIRENS WAILING)
What now?
You're asking me?
How about we just pull all this stuff off
and see what happens?
There's no cutoff, bro, maybe.
Maybe, there's no tamper-proofing program.
Yeah.
No.
Water.
- Need water.
- BOTH: Water.
What's going on? Hello!
LUCIUS: Twenty-five seconds.
Fifteen seconds.
(CRACKLING)
(BOMB DIFFUSES)
(SIGHS)
Please, I need water.
Water.
I need water.
(SIREN WAILING)
ED: Hello!
- Hello!
- (CLATTERING)
Hello! Guys!
What's going on?
Hello!
Where are my people? Where are my people?
You don't understand.
We have to find my people.
There'll be... There'll be consequences.
(LAUGHS)
You heroic son of a bitch!
A nuclear bomb? Huh?
- You'll never guess what took us so long.
- Problem.
Whatever was down there,
whoever was down there in Indian Hill,
they're not there anymore.
Couple of squad cars
are in pursuit of a bus
that left the Indian Hill's compound.
- That's got to be them!
- That bus cannot get away.
COP: Unit 12 in pursuit of Arkham bus
heading south along the D line.
Come in, Unit 12.
(SIREN WAILING)
...squad, get ready!
Can't make any mistakes here.
Civilian traffic ahead. It's blocked in.
Hold them at the cross street.
COP 2: Nothing. I'll check up ahead.
Car 32 to Captain Bullock,
heading east towards...
- JIM: Damn, damn!
- What's on that bus, Jim?
- Tell me, what's on the bus?
- Monsters.
Come on. Monsters?
Hugo Strange would rather destroy
half the city than let them out.
And now, they're out.
Code Red, Code Red. All units,
to Penford Highway!
BULLOCK: All units be on the lookout for
the Indian Hill bus on Penford Highway.
COP: Captain Bullock,
I got eyes on the bus.
Under the South Burnside Expressway.
BULLOCK: Well, then stop the damn thing!
Don't let it get away!
(ENGINE REVVING)
Come to mama!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SCREAMING)
Professor Strange!
Come out.
Strange, we need to talk.
You did a very bad thing to me.
And now, you're going to pay!
(BLOWS)
(GASPS)
Impossible.
(TUTTING)
Nothing is impossible.
Holy...
- MAN: Bitch...
- No.
Hmm.
This city's in deep trouble
if we don't find that bus.
- So let's find it.
- COPS: Yes, sir.
I want squadrons at 20,
in these quadrants here.
I want choppers in the air.
I want TAC units on all...
Bruce.
I have to go.
I might not see you for a while,
but I'll try to stay in touch.
Where are you going?
I have to find Lee.
Right move, mate.
(INHALES) Do me a favor.
Say goodbye to Bullock for me.
I don't really want
the whole Celtic farewell.
He's gonna have his hands full,
but I think he can handle it.
Will do.
SELINA: Chocolates!
Girls like chocolates.
I'll keep that in mind.
Well, there's a man who's
got his priorities straight.
The love of a good woman and all that.
Well, I hope you learned
your lesson, Master Bruce.
And that's the end of your adventures
with the police, eh?
There's a secret council, Alfred.
A secret council that
runs everything in Gotham.
Oh, bloody hell.
It's them that wanted me dead.
We're so close, Alfred.
We're so close to the ultimate truth.
- Oh, bloody hell.
- Hey, don't look at me.
Right.
BULLOCK: Jim, hey!
Hey, where you going?
Hey.
We got monsters to find.
And you'll find 'em. I have to go.
But the city's in danger!
You got this, I know you do.
And I have more important things to do.
- And Harvey--
- Yeah?
You're the boss now.
Maybe get a haircut?
(SIGHS)
That's my car.
That's my car!
Hey! Jim!
(INDISTINCT CLAMORING)
MAN: Help.
Help.
Oh, those poor souls.
(STAMMERS) Hello? Hello?
- (WOMAN GASPING)
- (GROANING)
(CREATURE GROWLING)
Oh!
(SNARLING AND HISSING)
(SINISTER LAUGH)
Thank you.
English - SDH