Previously on Gotham...
We could've had a good thing,
you and I.
- You?
- Yeah.
Me.
When I get out of here,
I'm gonna confess.
My connections to Sofia, all of it.
No.
You wanna pay your debt?
You live with it.
it's what the city needs.
When I brought you back to life
I ask you to be
my eyes and ears in Gotham,
you became so much more.
- Let her go now.
- No!
- I'll never go with you!
You killed her!
So, now you're going to return it?
What am I supposed to say?
I stole your jewelry, sorry.
- Sometimes that's enough.
- Can you do it?
Migraine still? It's like I've been
hit in the head with a brick.
You could escape anytime.
You're planning something.
Something spectacular.
But when we're done,
the world out there,
that will be the asylum.
Get back in your front, Tetch.
Don't even try hypnotizing me,
I can't hear a word you're saying.
I'm not talking to you!
I'm talking to him.
Geez. Tortuga.
You almost gave me
a heart attack.
Wait,
where the hell are your headphones?
Did I do it right?
Why does it rain
in the plain in Spain?
Knock-knock call the cock.
Time to rise and wield your size.
I fear I will require
a moment more, Mr. Tetch.
Our moment is fleeting,
my dear Mr. Crane. It's wens.
Desperately beating.
And now...
scarcely a drop's build.
Shall we, Mr. Tetch?
Let us be the pains, Mr. Crane.
When I say three hairs
past the freckle, gentlemen,
I do not mean five hairs past.
Let's do better next time.
Mind both P's and Q's, Velaska.
We're not your militia
to be backed and come.
I dread to think
where you'd be without us.
Boys, boys, let's not squabble
too early in our partnership.
There'll be plenty of time
to stab each other
in the backs later. But for now,
stick to Jerome's plan
and everyone will get what they want.
Unearthly, Kingdom of Terror.
Piece of Gotham pie,
both sky and high.
That's the spirit, boys, think big...
and kinky.
And lose the weirdo.
She's getting me the heebie-jeebies.
Your work is done, my dear.
You race, I'll run.
Glad to be a cop.
Much better. Now...
to free the rest of our cronies
and blow this pop stand.
Forward march!
Are you sure you're up for this,
Captain Gordon?
I'll manage.
Picked the hell of the night
to come back on the job.
- How many got out?
- Eighty-seven.
The entire violent ward.
Yeah, we rounded up
most of the serious nutjob
so the guys, they think
they're walruses and whatnot.
From snow child murderer,
Daedalus Bache mutilator, Erasmus
reign cult-killer, all at large.
Surviving guards think your buddy,
Tetch, was behind it.
No.
This big.
That's insane Jerome Valeska
put this together.
And there'll be more to come.
Got a lot of nerves
with the cops out here tonight.
We're thinking along the same lines.
And I know what you're thinking.
Why not tell him the truth?
About Sofia and the Pyg,
get it all out in the open.
I kept my mouth shut
like you told me to.
Good. I'm telling you again,
don't slip.
Go over there
and be Big Jim Gordon, hero cop.
It's what they need.
Even if it is a lie.
- You're back.
- Nice to see you, sir.
Back up there, back up there.
Hey, back at it. All right.
- Hey.
- Jimmy boss.
All right, listen up.
If I had known I'd be seeing
your ugly mugs tonight,
I'd have stayed in the hospital.
Jervis Tetch, Jonathan Crane,
Jerome Valeska.
Each of these madmen
has wreaked a different
kind of havoc in our city.
Now, they're on the loose,
and presumably working together.
Along with several dozen other
garden-variety psychopaths.
Know their MOs, their associates,
their home turf.
Gotham needs you tonight.
Have each other's backs
and we'll get through this.
- Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
- Captain Gordon.
- Jim, Jim, Jim.
Why so grim, Jim?
Tetch.
What do you want?
I'm not playing any of your games.
No games this time. Just some maims.
And your own share of blames
if you don't do what I tell you.
Do it, James.
Find your way
to which street James went.
Do it! Or I'm gonna kill someone!
In case you had any doubts.
- This is a set-up.
- That's our sort
of chance to catch him.
If we can get Tetch,
he can lead us to Valeska.
I'll put a squad together,
they can...
- come up behind...
- No. The force is spread too thin
looking for the escapees.
Let's go.
Sure.
You said we had to have each
other's backs this time, right?
I'm following your orders, Captain.
- I'd have thought.
- I'll alert the press.
What if we're hypnotized?
What?
Stick with me here.
We both listened to Tetch
on the phone.
What if he hypnotized us
and we're coming down here alone?
That would be pretty stupid,
wouldn't it?
So, what, we're either idiots
or hypnotized?
Good choices.
You did a good job
with the troops back there.
Thanks.
This is where the straight lines up.
What the hell?
We gotta get them out of there.
All right, don't shoot,
they're hypnotized.
- They're hypnotized, don't shoot.
- Let go!
All right, buddy, come on.
Hey.
Lo and behold.
The bold Captain Jim Gordon
and his rusty caboose in tow.
You have us, Tetch, let them go.
Do you recall
when I first came
to this fair city gym,
a bawling mess?
When nothing more
than to address the safety
of my dear sister Alice.
What's the choice this time, Tetch?
How do I save them?
Just tell me what you want?
What I want is my sister wreak!
But you kept me from saving her...
you gave me no choice!
So no more choices to you either.
No more saving.
No!
Soon the bells will toll, Jim.
How many more will go cold, Jim?
Like your soul, Jim.
How many would be flyers,
would-be dyers, splatter
like my force spitted Alice,
when the Gotham bells told them
full roll!
So do you mean it helping,
you don't say.
Let me think about walking
straight to the G.C.P.D.
You wanna bail out now?
No, I just wanna make sure
there's no...
jewelry death.
There's no death.
I'll help you to get the jewelry
back because I wanna help.
Nobody does anything just to help.
Fine. Once this is over,
there'll be nothing left
to set up between us. Can you do it?
Okay.
Okay, got it. Which file?
Jerome Valeska,
there'll be a red Arkham stamp on it.
Valeska, what do you want
with that night?
He broke out the Arkham tonight.
Yeah,
what's that have to do with you?
Can you just get the file
before someone sees us.
The largest single breach
of security
and the trouble history
of Arkham Asylum
has led to a city wile curfew
as many of the worst criminals
who have ever play Gotham
on the streets.
Twenty-seven deaths
have been attributed
to the escapees...
The whole city is going crazy-pants.
Can you turn that thing off.
We could be out there
making a killing
while the cops are running up
all these nut jobs.
I am gonna go nuts,
if you don't turn
that damn thing off!
Beware that these escapees
are extremely dan...
Another migraine?
I think a little self-medication
will fix.
And your hand...
got a pill for that?
I'll fix it.
I've been reading ancient history,
mysticism, philosophy,
anything that might reference
Ra's al Goul.
I'm sick of hearing
that charlatan's name.
He brought me back to life.
We'd never even met.
Why choose me...
For all you know he lied to you.
Maybe he just told you you were dead.
When you came,
you don't remember what happened.
It hurts to remember.
What?
The attacks I'm having...
is like memories are trying
to push their way
into my brain,
but when I go to touch them,
it's just the searing pain.
You have to let them in.
It hurts too much.
Listen to you,
whining like a little baby.
- What?
- You have been hiding here
for weeks reading these books.
And now, you're telling me
you might have all the answers
in your head,
but you don't wanna get them
because it hurts too much.
You have no idea
what you are talking about.
No, I have no idea
who I'm talking to.
The Barbara I know
wouldn't let anything
that she is afraid of stand
in the way of what she wants.
Not cops, not criminals, not blood,
and not pain.
I remember when it all went dark.
This is...
blinding electric light and then...
nothing.
But then, I remember...
I remember...
I know. I hear you.
The world and its cruelties,
how unfair it's being to you.
I can hear you cursed me.
What a vital,
poisonous little mind you have.
And yet,
everybody hates you for it,
don't they?
Yes.
Everybody hates me.
You don't know why?
I understand that
feeling very well, Barbara.
You...
are just the one
I have been looking for.
And I have a present for you,
but it's a secret.
You shall become The Demon's Head,
the league of shadows
will be yours to command.
Army of assassins.
The world is weak, Barbara.
And you are strong.
Use the league
to make the world long light.
- You...
- Barbara.
Barbara.
I'm okay.
Ra's just really...
understood me.
Say, you remember something?
Yeah.
It's a beacon. Calling them here.
And they're coming.
Who?
The League of Shadows.
All right. Hey!
Same story all around.
Last thing they remember
is they were driving,
then they were here, then it was
cluck, cluck here chick, their chick.
Any luck?
Something bad is gonna happen.
And there's a time limit.
That's the Gotham bell's full roll.
Midnight, right?
That's less than an hour.
What's the bad thing
that's gonna happen?
I don't know.
He's gonna hypnotize more people.
To do what?
"Splatted like my spitted Alice."
Her sister Alice jumped, was impaled.
"Flyers will become dyers
they'll be splatted."
- No.
- Yeah, yeah, come on.
Bruce Wayne? What are you doing here?
Detective Harper,
where is Captain Gordon?
- I need to see him.
- He's out on the Arkham Break.
What do you need?
I need protection.
Last year, I captured Jerome Valeska.
He's clearly escaped
so I didn't get his revenge on me.
Okay,
I think, a little bit more than that.
I'm very close friends
with Captain Gordon.
I'm sure he wants me
to be well protected but...
this is a matter of payment.
What do you... put that away.
What do you want? A bribery charge?
I... I just...
I'm sorry.
I'm just really scared.
I know Valeska wants me dead.
I just know.
Take it easy, Wayne.
All right, you can stay here.
You'll be perfectly safe.
Okay.
All right, Wayne.
I'll find you a seat.
Hold on, we're gonna get you down.
Tetch has a booby trap.
If we get too close, they'll jump.
But if we do nothing
they jump at midnight.
How did he get all of them?
The drivers,
how did he hypnotize all of them?
What's that matter?
We gotta help these people.
We're gonna put a net around
the building.
That won't work, Harvey.
Do you know this diner? Zack's?
No, why?
Look, Valeska's uncle owns it.
He might know
where Jerome would go after escaping.
Still sounds like a cop's job to me.
I could've killed Jerome
after he kidnapped me,
and I didn't.
Any harm he does now,
I share a part of it.
Either way,
I'm responsible for his life now.
I can't just wait to see
what the cops will do.
I... I have to get him back
to Arkham.
What?
Your ego, Bruce...
It's huge.
What?
Not everything is your fault
or your responsibility.
Get over yourself.
Make you a little easier
to be around.
Thanks for the advice.
You sure you don't need
my help anymore?
We're even?
You don't owe me anything,
Selina.
You never did.
And you're sure you haven't heard
from your nephew, Mr. Trumble?
That monster killed my sister.
I ever see him, his screams
are what you'll be hearing.
Just maybe give us a call
before things go that far.
Jeez, there's a lot of gum
under here.
You're lucky those flatfoots
didn't check under the table,
Uncle Zach.
I mean,
that'll be some kind of health
code violation or something.
Jim,
it's happening all over the city.
Thousands are climbing up
on roofs, more every minute.
Drivers, people at work,
in the streets, at home.
How's he getting to them?
Radio. He's broadcasting on radio.
He must have taken over
our radio station.
Which one? We don't have time
to hit them all.
Drivers who grabbed us.
They were listening
to the same station.
XDJ in here.
WYED!
WEPV.
They're all on different stations.
He must've commanded
on the change of stations
so we couldn't find him.
There's only one way to know
which one he's using.
What are you doing?
No, no, no. Harvey.
- Harvey.
- Hey
- Hey.
- Hey!
- WYED, clear!
- Harvey, no, let me go.
- Big B Radio.
That toilet paper jingle
I hate so much.
No, I got Tetch out of my head
once before.
- I could do it again.
- XDNJ.
- It's that song I hate.
- Come on.
Too cold.
Too hot.
Just right.
You always could cook up a storm,
unck.
I remember back in the circus,
we used to dare each other to sneak
into the chuck wagon.
Steal one of your cookies or two.
That reminds me of my favorite meal
you ever cooked.
You remember that time
you caught me trying to snag
a snickerdoodle?
That soup you made that day,
mamma mia.
What was the special
ingredient again?
Right.
It was my hand.
The one you dipped in a boiling pot
of chicken stock!
That smell...
it was...
mouthwatering.
Almost as good as this.
That's a good story, nephew.
Well, aren't you curious
about the soup?
Don't tell me there's poison in it.
Not at all.
You got me worried
there for a second, unck.
I set out three bowls of soup,
nephew,
so I'd have enough
for all my guests.
You remember Love Kid
from his strongman days
at the circus?
The minute I heard you broke out,
I knew you'd be headed here.
So I invited good old Love
for some supper.
But just right, soup is for him.
The cold is for me.
I always love gazpacho!
The too hot, that's for you, nephew.
I'm just saying how could there be
a global army of assassins
we'd never heard of?
What part of League of Shadows
do you not understand?
- And they're coming here?
- To me.
They're coming to me.
Well, hello, Barb,
shouldn't you be getting ready
for them or something?
I'm ready.
Soon as they wanna show themselves.
What?
You can stop hiding.
I know you're there.
We're here for the Demon's Head.
Where is he?
She...
is right here.
Harvey!
WZPZ.
Top of every tower.
- Jim, WZPZ.
- When the clock strikes 12...
- Hell no!
- Stop listening.
That's an order, you hear me?
Stop listening.
- WZPZ.
- Change the station.
Come on, Harvey, change the station!
Sorry, pal,
there's something I gotta do.
Hickory dickory dock,
the copper went up the clock.
The clock struck 12,
he felt pelt melon,
and that was it for the cop.
- Gotham Central.
- Harper, it's Gordon.
Cap, it is crazy here.
I got seven cops ready to jump.
I got calls coming in
from everywhere.
It's Tetch. He's broadcasting
for the WZPZ station.
- Okay, I'll re-direct units.
- No.
I want all cars on the street
ready to amplify
the emergency G911 band.
Ready our teams
on as many roads as possible.
- And then what?
- Wait for my signal.
What, wait, wait, wait.
No!
Hey, there, nephew,
have a taste
of one of my three soups.
No, no, no.
My sister had the wrong idea
with you keeping you around.
She should've put you in a sack
with some rocks,
and dropped you in the river.
Put this creep out of our misery.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Get out of here, kid.
No.
Look, kid, I appreciate
a concerned citizen and all,
but this is Jerome Valeska.
The psycho
who broke out of Arkham tonight.
And what we're doing is giving him
what he deserves.
No one deserves that.
You tell them that.
- Shut up.
- Stop.
Call the police,
and they'll come for him.
Jeez.
Let him go.
And get rid of the kid.
Look what we left lying around.
Enough re-living old memories,
Uncle Zach.
Tell me what I wanna know.
You know, why I'm here.
I don't know anything.
It's too bad we're out of soup.
I wonder what else is on the menu.
She's got the mark
of the Demon's Head.
Ra's chose her.
She doesn't even know what it is.
I know it means
I'm your new damn leader.
Is that all you think it is?
Ra's didn't explain everything.
Look at the mess he's left us with.
You have the mark
of the Demon's Head,
but no woman
has ever been allowed
to lead the League of Shadows.
- I'm sorry, you just said what?
- Women serve in the League,
but they do not lead.
That's not our law,
just a stupid tradition.
Ra's chose her.
We need to honor his choice.
That's true.
As long as you have
the Demon's Head,
the League must follow you.
Now, we're back on track.
So I guess I'll have to...
Cut the Demon's Head from you.
Anyone else want a shot at the title?
Here comes your plane.
No, no, no.
I'll tell you, I'll tell you,
I'll tell you. Look, look.
She picks St. Ignatius.
The school is St. Ignatius.
Got it. Lost it. Write it down.
Thanks. It's been great
catching up, Uncle Zach.
You really brought back
the utter helplessness
of childhood.
Well, see you around.
I mean, except the opposite.
Boy billionaire, Bruce Wayne,
my savior!
I did not see that one coming.
No.
With Uncle Zach,
the beatings just never stopped.
They went on and on, yet,
nobody ever help me...
Ever.
And it makes a man wonder.
What the hell is wrong with you?
The only thing funnier
than you saving my life...
Will be if I saved yours.
No!
No, wait.
What would be funnier is
if you are choked to death
by the guy
that you saved me from.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
we'll do that instead.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, do your thing.
Almost magic hour, Gothamites.
Time to climb to the tippy top
of every tower.
When the bell strikes 12,
throw yourselves,
pommel over the edge
onto your heads!
Shut up, Tetch.
This is Captain Gordon
of the G.C.P.D.,
am I coming through?
You're coming through.
We can hear you all over the city.
All right, Tetch.
You're gonna tell those people to
set back from the ledge, no tricks.
You go off script,
and I'll shoot pieces of you.
So you do what I say.
I would love to do
as you command, Jim.
But sadly, I've tied my own hands.
Your hands.
I can't stop them.
If anyone tells them
to save themselves, they'll jump.
But you're more than welcome
to try, Jim.
I'm playing the next voice,
you hear!
Tell them anything!
It will not matter
when the bell start to ring.
Your, so callous caused
the death of my darling, Alice, Jim.
Try it and they die.
Stand by and they all try to fly.
Captain?
Captain, what do we do?
How do we save them?
Yeah, I can watch this all night,
Bruce.
Hands off big boy.
Still don't need my help, Bruce?
Selina.
Selina?
Wasn't that a nice name?
- Selina?
- No, no, no.
She's not that kind of girl.
- Wrong answer freak.
- That's funny because...
All right.
See you crazy kids later. Ciao!
You should've let me shoot him.
It would've been over by now.
Selina, I told you
I'm responsible for him.
I can't just let him be shot
Selina, I can't.
I'm not taking
responsibility for this mess.
So let's get out of here
before the cops show up.
Yeah?
Come on.
It's not over yet.
Suit yourself.
Just don't take...
so much responsibility that,
you get yourself killed.
Some legacy
your dead boyfriend left you.
No.
Ra's chose me for a reason.
I know it.
You're weak.
You're also damn weak.
That's it.
That is why Ra's chose me.
Because he knew I would see
how pitiful you all are.
Afraid of change.
Afraid to take orders from a woman.
Well, listen up!
I am the demon's head!
So you sons of bitches better
start vowing down right now!
Or it's gonna get ugly up in here.
You're right.
They were weak.
And the mission
of the League of Shadows
is to call weakness.
They were unfit and needed to die.
But the Sisters of the League
are yours to command.
Well, so much of a league now,
is it?
We're the point of the spear,
Barbara.
Hundreds will follow you.
What the hell?
You have no idea
what they expect from you.
This is mine, Tabitha.
And I'm taking it.
Tell me what I need to know.
Hey, Cap, what do we do?
I can't save you.
Save each other.
It worked.
They're stepping away.
- No.
- What?
- What happened?
- I got you. I got you.
Thank you.
Yes.
Heard we got nothing
from Tetch about Valeska's plans.
Not a word the whole time the medics
were patching him up.
Still, 40 escapees back in the can
and a lot of people with their feet
safely on the ground.
You need a drink.
I don't keep it around.
Squirrels hide nuts for the winner.
I...
got this for whenever.
I don't belong here.
I don't deserve to be here.
Not in this office,
not in this building.
By rights, I should be in jail.
No argument from me.
Let's say you were in jail
sucking on your own misery,
where would the thousands of people
you saved tonight be?
Where would I be?
What you did tonight was heroic.
You could've done what I did.
Anyone could have.
You know, what I was thinking
when I jumped in that car
and I was flicking
through those channels?
I was thinking,
"I can do this crazy thing
because if it goes sideways,
Jim Gordon will save me."
And here we are.
Who I am?
What I've always say I believe in...
it's like it's a lie now, Harvey.
A feet of clay are heavy
to carry around,
that's what the whiskey is for.
I judged you...
for a long time.
I shouldn't have done that.
What you know about me, Jim,
is just the tip of the iceberg.
There are no heroes here.
No heroes here.
Yes?
I got the Wayne kid on line three,
something about Valeska.
Bruce, you okay?
I saw Jerome Valeska tonight.
- He killed his uncle.
- What?
He was looking the name
of a school, St. Ignatius.
- Why?
- I'm on my way to find out.
No. Wherever you are, stay put.
Valeska is my problem
as much as anyone's.
- I'm going after him.
- Damn it, Bruce.
Stay the hell away
from that mad man.
I'll see you at St. Ignatius, Jim.
- You can deal with me there.
- Bruce...
Kid in trouble again?
More than he can handle.
Let's go.
How do you like the new threads?
Speechless. I know.
You look affright, Mr. Tetch.
This is what, lame,
my dear Mr. Crane.
But I do confess,
pure joy investing Jimmy Boy
with our ploy.
Yeah, yeah, you did a great job
keeping Gordon occupied.
Meanwhile, Crane got his fear gas,
I got my information,
everything is going
according to my plan.
But no time to pull average of a man.
We have fish to fry.
And by fish, I mean faces, or feet.
Something fun to fry.
Buckle up.
All aboard!
I'm coming.