NARRATOR:
Previously on Gotham:
You haven't by chance
seen Officer Daugherty?
[GRUNTS]
Supposed to have dinner last night
and he didn't show. No surprise.
- Um, but I haven't seen him today.
- Me neither.
Barbara, we're doing this for you.
[GASPS THEN SCREAMS]
- He's dead?
- Yeah. He's dead. It's gonna be okay.
Bruce, your father was a true stoic.
He kept his best self hidden.
- Your father was a good man.
- But even good men have secrets.
You have a hard head, James,
just like your father.
Gotham is on a knife edge. But I won't
let it fall apart without a fight.
ESSEN: Just got wind of three attacks
on Falcone businesses...
in different parts of town.
It's Maroni. We're in a shooting war.
[WOOD CREAKING]
Whoa.
Good morning, child.
We ain't children.
And it ain't morning.
Oh, it will be soon.
A brand-new day.
NEWSMAN [ON TV]: The gang war
rages on here in Gotham.
No one knows what set this turf war off...
but it is commonly believed to be the
result of the longtime power struggle...
between Salvatore Maroni
and Carmine Falcone.
Longtime enemies, these men
have often come to blows...
[NEWSMAN CONTINUES
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
ALFRED:
Still looking for secrets, are we, sir?
Or just breaking stuff?
Secrets.
ALFRED:
Why don't l...?
Whole city's going doolally around us.
I mean, there's a bloody
war on the streets...
and you're here worrying
about your poor dad.
Yes, I am.
If your father had a secret life,
which I hasten to add he didn't...
I'd know about it, wouldn't I?
A sober, diligent man, he was.
Never out gallivanting.
Home every night like clockwork,
working in this very room.
Yes, I remember.
I wasn't allowed to disturb him
while he was working.
- Nobody was.
- Classical music, he would play, for hours.
That's right.
Mom and I would read books
or play board games until he was done.
I remember.
I tried to sneak in to see him,
but the door was locked.
- Was the door always locked, Alfred?
- Yeah, I suppose so, when he was working.
Why, though?
- Why lock the door?
- That's what doors are for, isn't it?
It's in here. It's in this room.
My father's secret. It's in this room.
I know it. I know it.
Uh... Oh.
[CHICKENS CLUCKING]
[CHATTERING]
Hello, young lady. I like your style.
COP 1: Put Falcone's guys in one cell
and Maroni's in another.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING AND GRUNTING]
COP 2:
Shut up.
Get in there.
More where that came from.
Officer Katz, right?
- Yes, sir. Katz, Griffin.
- Word of advice, Katz.
I'm a dead duck around here.
Brass are gonna fire me
as soon as this gang war cools off.
So don't salute me.
Makes you look like a rube.
- Hi.
LESLIE: Detective.
- Dr. Thompkins.
- Jim.
Thanks for coming to see me.
It's good to see you looking so well.
I am well. Much better.
Yes, you are. This is your last checkup.
You are all healed, physically.
But you need to get
some trauma counseling.
Doc, I'm happy. I am happy to be alive.
Which is why, Jim, I didn't wanna leave
without saying thank you properly.
Thank you for saving my life.
I was glad to do it.
LESLIE:
Ms. Kean.
Trauma counseling, like, yesterday.
I have several recommendations for you.
- Really, doc, I'm fine.
- You're not fine.
After what you've been through,
nobody would be fine.
Fine. If you will be my counselor.
And we do it at my place.
No. I have some trauma training,
but it's not my area of focus.
I like you. Okay? I can talk to you.
Please.
Okay.
- Deal.
- Thank you.
Hmm?
COP: All right, last warning to all of you:
don't be that guy.
Hey, Jim, did you hear the news?
Don Falcone just got hit. Jim.
- What?
- Falcone got hit. Twenty minutes ago.
Maroni's boys blew up his car.
- Wait, he's dead?
- No. He's at the hospital.
But he'll be dead soon enough.
Essen said City Hall
and the bigwigs okayed the hit.
They switched their support to Maroni.
Maroni? That hothead?
They think he can run this city?
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Someone had to go.
This war has been bad for business.
Hello?
[GRUNTING]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
Good morning, good morning.
Oh, Penguin. Thank God. Get me out of here.
Maroni's men will be here any minute.
Yes, I imagine so. Heh.
Mustn't stay long.
I knew I'd regret it
if I didn't say goodbye to you in person.
It was me, old friend.
I did this to you.
I started the war.
From the day I met you,
I was planning your end.
I'm sorry it has to be in this...
squalid little corner, but...
[SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
Why?
Nothing personal, I assure you, sir.
You have been a wise mentor
and a good friend.
But business must come first.
I'm gonna take your place, old man.
I'm gonna be the king of Gotham.
[CHUCKLING]
You?
Never.
You're going to burn in hell.
I do worry about that.
But you first, old friend.
You first.
Nobody move.
[GRUNTS]
- Walk away.
- Shut up.
You're both under arrest
for attempted murder.
Didn't you hear? Falcone is out.
By official decree. Everyone agreed.
I heard.
So release me, Jim.
Get on the winning side.
Winning side, my ass.
Maroni's a fool. He can't replace me.
A thousand rivals will jump up
to challenge him.
There'll be civil war.
If I die now, Gotham falls apart.
I agree. But can you turn things around?
Can you take back control?
Of course.
Two days at my safe house.
I need two days to make some moves.
Then I'll skin Maroni
and those disloyal scum like rabbits.
OSWALD:
Wake up, Napoleon.
Maroni's louts are minutes away
from coming here and cutting your throat.
And the thing is, Jim,
they aren't very fond of me either.
So seriously, you need to uncuff me. Jim?
- Jim, where the hell did you run off to?
- Harv, I'm in the hospital with Falcone.
- There's nobody here.
- No kidding. What are you doing there?
You gotta get out.
They'll be coming back to finish him off.
Yeah. Any moment now.
- Unless I get him out of here.
- Jim, Jim, Jim.
- I could use some help.
- No way. Are you nuts?
He's a bad man,
but he's the best bad man we got.
If Falcone loses control,
Maroni's too wild to run Gotham.
- There'll be anarchy.
- Yeah, probably.
- But Falcone already lost control.
- And he'll get it back.
Listen, you're all twisted
over what happened to Barbara.
- You're not thinking straight.
- Yeah. Maybe.
But I'm done in this town anyhow.
What do I have to lose?
Your life.
Huh? How about your life?
What the hell are you doing here?
I thought the fix was in with you guys.
[CHUCKLES]
- Can you walk?
- If I have to.
Let's get you out.
I'll take you to your safe house.
My friend, you are making
a terrible mistake.
I'm doing this for the city, not you.
You're the least worst option.
If I didn't think you could take
back control, I'd let you die.
- Just so we're clear.
- We're clear.
You can't leave me here.
Maroni's men will kill me.
- Possible.
- No. No, you arrested us.
We are in your custody.
- That's true.
- You owe me a favor, Jim. You owe me.
- Damn it.
LOEB: James Gordon?
Detective Gordon?
Don't kill them.
Morning, fellas. What can I help you with?
Yes, Gordon.
As usual, wrong place, wrong time.
Go. Now.
Why? So these men
can kill Carmine Falcone?
I have no knowledge of that.
Go. That's an order.
You're a disgrace, Loeb.
I hope to see you behind bars very soon
or dead.
- Whichever.
- Hope?
It's for losers, Jim.
He's all yours.
[GRUNTS]
Jim, Jim, don't shoot. It's me. We gotta
go. There are ambulances in the basement.
Where's your man?
Uh...
About that.
- We gotta take Penguin and Gilzean too.
- Penguin and Gilzean?
I arrested them for attempted murder.
They're in my custody.
Ugh! I don't even wanna argue with you.
Come on, let's go. Go.
Tommy?
[TIRES SCREECHING]
MAN:
Boss! Boss, look out!
Get down.
Damn it.
What exactly are we looking for,
Master Bruce?
When I find it, I'll know.
Nobody knows about this place, right?
Nobody?
Nobody. Anybody who did is dead.
We'll be safe here.
Hello.
What's up?
[GARAGE DOOR OPENS]
FISH:
I know, I know.
It's astonishing.
Sometimes I astonish myself.
I feel like, uh, this is all a dream.
I'm gonna wake up soon.
Barbara, you were abducted.
Your parents were killed in front of you.
Yeah. Yeah, that's real.
I'm talking about this, now. This...
This is the dream.
I'm gonna wake up, and he's still alive.
And he's coming for me.
FISH: I thought for sure you were dead.
Let me look at you.
Fish?
Is it real...? Is it really you?
It's me, Butch. I'm home.
My poor baby. What did they do to you?
Nothing good.
It's him, boss.
Don Maroni.
[CHUCKLES]
Yes, alive and well.
Well, that's a long story.
We need to talk.
I have something you want.
[GRUNTING]
They didn't find my knife.
Ah. So we're saved, then.
It's in my sock.
If you get the chance,
take some of them with us.
I'll try.
- Hey, you.
- Selina, what are you doing here?
- Chilling. How about you?
- Kind ofjammed up.
Yeah.
That's too bad.
Oh. That's mime for "Help us out here,"
and totally blow the coolest gig ever.
Just because we kind of
sort of know each other? Right?
[SIGHS]
Hello, fellas. Hmm.
Carmine.
Penguin? Nothing to share?
Well, I have a little something.
I just made a sweet deal with Maroni.
He just told me
I could have all my territories back...
and all I have to do in return...
is give him Carmine's head.
Uh, Fish, I need to go lie down.
What did you do to that poor soul,
you sadist?
I assure you...
You will die a slow, painful death
on account of Butch.
You too, Carmine.
You.
We'll keep it simple.
And you?
We're cool. Any questions?
How you gonna kill them?
I love this girl.
[FISH LAUGHS]
BARBARA:
Jason saw right through me.
He knew me instantly. Like I was naked.
(Scar)'-
But thrilling.
And aren't all the best
guys a little scary?
I was way more scared of Jim Gordon,
first date we went on.
So butch and stern.
That type, they often have a bad temper.
Hmm. But Jim was a sweetie.
Never laid a finger on me.
It's kind of surprising.
Does he ever hit you?
Me? No. Why?
Why would he hit anyone? Any woman?
You know, out of passion.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to pry.
Only, I heard you and Jim were dating.
No.
Uh, yes. We've been on a few dates.
I'm sorry. I didn't think that you knew.
If that makes you uncomfortable
in any way...
No, don't be silly.
I, uh... I'm happy for you.
He's one of the good guys.
Yeah, he is.
Hey, you hungry?
FISH:
So there he is.
Fish, you mysterious, crazy,
gorgeous killer, you.
I love you.
[FISH CHUCKLES]
This...
This is delicious. Finally.
- You're hard to kill, old man.
- No. Your people are second-rate.
[SCOFFS]
Ms. Mooney, if I may, a brief word.
I know my life is forfeit.
I speak not for my sake but yours.
Because after all,
I still love and respect you.
Kill me if you must,
but keep Falcone alive.
As soon as he's dead,
Maroni has no use for you.
You are simply a threat. He will kill you.
Oh!
You think?
OSWALD:
Why would he need another boss in town?
- Another rival?
- That's where you're wrong, smart guy.
A, she's not a rival,
because she's not a boss.
She's an underboss.
An underboss takes orders.
I don't take orders.
I know that. We're cool. Relax.
- I'm relaxed.
- I don't think you are, babes.
Please don't call me "babes."
You see? Not relaxed.
Babes? Really? It's a term of endearment.
It means I like you.
Fine, I misspoke.
You're not an underboss and you're not
a babe. You tell me what you are.
What we are, Sal...
are partners.
Whatever you want. Partners.
I'm Partner Number 1,
and you're Partner Number 2.
That's the deal, right?
I'm number one, and you are...?
- Number two.
MARONI: There you go. Simple math.
One, two, babes. Oops.
Sorry. That's the last time, I swear.
Guys, can you feel the buzz in the air?
That's victory.
Redemption. Power.
When this old man dies, a new day begins.
We will rule Gotham.
We're building a dynasty.
We will whip this town like a rented mule.
Right, babes?
[MEN CHUCKLING]
[CHUCKLES]
All right, relax. I'm kidding you.
Guys, no, seriously.
Don't call her "babes."
Or "toots" or what have you.
It's a women's-lib thing.
I am relaxed.
[GUNFIRE]
Come on!
[ALL GRUNTING AND SHOUTING]
GORDON:
Let's go.
We've been circling around the subject...
but haven't talked
about what actually happened to you.
What was done to you.
Lee, you're a nice lady.
I could go there, but I'm not sure
you wanna go there with me.
Don't worry about me.
Has Jim told you he loves you?
- Barbara...
- Fair is fair.
And I'm telling you all my little secrets.
No, he hasn't.
But he will, though, won't he?
You can feel it coming.
Come on, look at you.
You're gorgeous and smart.
Of course he loves you.
Do you love him?
Barbara.
Tell me what happened.
[GUNFIRE AND SHOUTING NEARBY]
If we can get to Seventh without being
spotted by Fish's people, we're home free.
- Then what?
- We find a safe place, regroup.
Maroni's death is a lucky break for you.
Spoken like a true mafioso.
You're the least worst option. Like you
said, without you, the city falls apart.
Yes, I said that. And it might be true.
But this has been a long day...
and I've had a long time
to look at this world I've created.
I'm done with this business. I'm out.
I've got a place down south I can go to.
- I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
I know, I'm letting you down.
I'm letting the city down. I know.
[DOOR OPENS NEARBY]
[MEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
MAN 1:
Think I heard something.
MAN 2:
Yeah, flash this way.
Down here, down here.
Okay, plan B.
So you got a place down south, huh?
Nice? On the water?
- Yes.
- Any work for beat-up old cops?
Sure.
How's that sound, Jim?
Beaches, sunshine, fishing...
Yeah. Tempting.
Hello again.
Cat got your tongue?
Yes.
Selina. Boys.
- Bless you.
- Gotta hand it to you, Fish.
You really know how to stop a show.
I couldn't help myself, Harvey.
The man vexed me.
Crazy move. Possibly a good move too.
We'll see.
The battlefield is in flux.
You could be looking
at the new queen of Gotham.
Congratulations, my dear.
- I'm quitting, Fish. I'm out.
- Does this mean I don't have to kill you?
You're going to retire someplace warm,
lay back, read your little funny papers?
- That was the thought.
- Yeah, nice thought.
[GUNFIRE]
Please, no...
Fish! Where are you?
Go.
Then he left me for a long time.
Alone.
And I slept.
I don't know for how long.
And then he woke me up.
Road trip, he said.
We were halfway there when I realized...
we were going to my parents' house.
Go on.
Well, then he tied them up to a chair.
And, uh, he told me to talk to them...
about my childhood issues.
So I did.
I just told them
whatever came into my head.
And what came into your head?
You know, just stupid kid stuff, I guess.
Like...
My mom used to call me her little piggy
when I was little.
They threw away my posters.
Never nurtured my self-esteem.
Just slowly, steadily...
grinding away at my soul.
Trying to make me disappear.
That's not kid stuff.
To be fair to them...
they simply never understood me.
They have no clue who I am.
Even when I was killing them,
they just gaped at me like fools.
No understanding.
Barbara, Jason Lennon killed your parents.
You didn't kill them.
Yes, I did.
I stabbed them several times.
And then I slit their throats.
- I'd like to leave now, please.
- You uncomfortable?
How about now?
[DOOR OPENS]
[LOCK CLICKS]
[BARBARA GRUNTING]
[BANGING ON DOOR]
[BUSY SIGNAL ON PHONE]
[ELEVATOR BELL DINGS]
[DOG WHIMPERING]
[GRUNTS]
[YELLS]
[BOTH YELLING AND GRUNTING]
[BARBARA GROWLING WILDLY]
Lee'?
She just... She just went crazy.
I told him that woman was trouble.
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
[FISH YELLS]
[BOTH YELL]
Butch. About time.
- Shoot her, Butch.
- Oh, really?
Do as I say, Butch. Shoot her.
What are you doing? Drop him.
My friend, remember your training.
I order you to shoot her.
Butch, don't listen to him.
He did something to your mind.
I'm your girl. Remember, I'm your girl.
Kill her now!
[BOTH YELL]
[GROANING]
FISH:
Butch.
Oh, my God, what did I do?
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I would never hurt you. I love you, Fish.
It's okay. It's not your fault.
I love you too.
He messed with your mind.
It's not your fault.
I'm gonna be fine. You know me.
[OSWALD YELLS THEN BUTCH GRUNTS]
[G ROWLS]
Goodbye, Fish.
It's all good.
[BOTH YELL]
No!
[FISH SCREAMS]
[WATER SPLASHES]
I'm the king of Gotham.
[LAUGHING]
I'm the king of Gotham!
Mr. Nygma.
Ms. Kringle.
I just noticed something really weird.
Oh?
This note Officer Dougherty left for me...
The first letter of every line
spells out your name.
You see?
N-Y-G-M-A.
Yes.
How... How odd.
What an amazing coincidence.
- Coincidence?
- What else could it be?
- So you know nothing about this?
- I? Me? No. No.
No.
Huh.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[LAUGHING]
DOUGHERTY:
You're the guy that likes riddles.
Why laugh? It's not funny.
DOUGHERTY: What a creep.
She'll keep digging-
Why did you have to leave a clue?
Why?
Relax.
What can she find? What can she prove?
Nothing. There's no body. Stop worrying.
She looked so sad and angry.
I hate it when she's that way.
KRINGLE: Menacing and weird.
- Please.
Like it matters.
Like you stand a chance with her.
She knows how you feel about her,
and she treats you like dirt.
[SIGHS]
I don't care. I still love her. Ugh!
Listen to yourself. Be a man!
KRINGLE:
You're an odd man, Mr. Nygma.
You'll do better
if she's a little scared of you.
- Stop talking like that.
DOUGHERTY: No riddles.
KRINGLE: Formal complaints about you.
- Just keeping it real.
What's black and white and red all over?
Stop it!
DOUGHERTY:
I wouldn't quit your day job if I were you.
[LAUGHING]
KRINGLE:
He is so weird.
Beautiful, huh? I'm gonna miss this town.
You won't change your mind?
Town needs you.
No. Gotham needs a lawman now,
not a criminal like me.
A strong lawman.
You looking at me?
Someone needs to grab this city
by the neck and shake it hard.
That's you, Jim. I know it in my bones.
There's a lot of powerful men
who would disagree with you on that.
FALCONE:
Nice knife, huh?
That was your father's.
He gave it to me a long time ago.
A spur-of-the-moment birthday gift.
I said no.
Such a beautiful knife,
and I have men with guns to protect me.
He said, "Take it.
A knife is a good friend
when you have no other."
You were that close?
At one time.
Point of the story, Jim...
your father was the most honest man
I ever met.
But he carried a knife.
ALFRED: Enough searching, Master B.
There's nothing here.
Now, your father was a good man.
A flawed man like anyone else.
- Doesn't mean he had a secret life.
- My intuition is nearly always correct.
Yeah, well...
It's a common delusion, I find.
Arkham's full of men
whose intuitions were always correct.
There are none so blind.
None so blind.
- Marcus Aurelius. Marcus Aurelius.
- What about him?
- He was a Roman emperor.
- Yes, I'm fully aware of that, Master Bruce.
And a stoic.
I think I remember he was a stoic,
like my father.
Lucius Fox called my father a stoic.
Lots of people are called stoic.
It means a hard nut who doesn't say much.
Doesn't mean it's a clue.
It's a philosophy, Alfred.
It's a way of life.
Maybe... Maybe that as
well, I suppose, but...
- Ah!
- Uh-oh.
- What is it, do you think?
- I don't know and I don't care.
- Don't you dare press that button.
- Why not?
It could be a bomb.
Alfred, that seems improbable.
[PROKOFIEV'S "DANCE OF THE KNIGHTS"
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
It's a stereo.
[BRICKS GRINDING]
[English - US - SDH]