Previously on Gotham...
You haven't by chance seen
Officer Dougherty?
We're supposed
to have dinner last night,
he didn't show, no surprise.
But I haven't seen him today.
Me neither.
Barbara, we're doing this
for you.
- He's dead.
- Yeah, he's dead.
It's gonna be okay.
Bruce, your father
was a true stoic.
He kept his best self-hidden.
Your father was a good man.
But even good man have secrets.
You have a hard head, James,
just like your father.
Gotham is on the knife edge.
But I won't let it fall apart
without a fight.
Just got wind of three
separate attacks
on Falcone businesses
in different parts of town.
It's Maroni.
We're in a shooting war.
Good morning, child.
We ain't children.
And it ain't morning.
Oh, it will be soon.
A brand new day.
Still looking for secrets,
are we, Sir?
Or just breaking stuff?
Secrets.
I don't know.
The whole city
is going doolally around us.
I mean, there's civil bloody war
on the streets.
And you were there
worrying about your poor old dad.
Yes, I am.
If your father had a secret life,
which I hate to say to you
that he didn't,
I'd know about it, wouldn't I?
A sober, diligent man he was.
Never out gallivanting.
Home every night like clockwork,
working in this very room.
Yes, I remember.
I wasn't allowed to disturb him
while he was working.
- Nobody was.
- Classical music.
- He would play for hours.
- That's right.
Mum and I would read books
or play board games
until he was done.
I remember...
I've tried to sneak in
to see him.
But the door was locked.
Was the door always locked,
Alfred?
Yeah, well, I suppose so,
when he was working.
Why though?
Why lock the door?
That's what doors are for,
isn't it?
It's in here. It's in this room.
My father's secret,
it's in this room!
I know it. I know it!
Hello, young lady.
I like your style.
Move Falcone's guy on one cell
and Maroni's on another.
Officer Katz, right?
Yes, Sir, Katz, Griffin.
Word of advice, Katz.
I'm a dead duck around here.
The brass are gonna fire me
just as soon
as this gang war cools off.
So, don't salute me.
Makes you look like a robot.
- Hi.
- Detective.
- Dr. Thompkins.
- Jim.
Thanks for coming to see me.
It's good to see you
looking so well.
I am well.
Much better.
Yes, you are.
This is your last check-up.
You are all healed physically.
But you need to get
some trauma counseling.
Doc, I'm happy.
I am happy to be alive.
Which is why...
Jim, I didn't wanna leave
without saying
thank you properly.
Thank you, for saving my life.
I was glad to do it.
Ms. Kean, trauma counseling.
Like yesterday.
I have several recommendations
for you.
- Really, Doc, I'm fine.
- You're not fine.
After what you've been through,
nobody would be fine.
Fine.
If you will be my counselor.
And we do it at my place.
No, I have some trauma training,
but it's not my area focus.
I like you.
I mean, I can talk to you. Please?
Okay.
Deal.
Hey, Jim, did you hear the news?
Don Falcone just got hit.
- Jim.
- What?
Falcone got hit 20 minutes ago.
Maroni's boys blew up his car.
- What do you mean, he's dead?
- No, he's at the hospital.
But he will be dead soon enough.
Listen, Essen said City Hall
and the big wigs okayed the hit.
They switched their support
to Maroni.
Maroni? That hooligan?
He think he can run the city?
Someone had to go.
This war has been bad
for business.
Hello? Hello?
Good morning, good morning.
Oh, Penguin, thank God,
get me out of here.
Maroni's men will be here
any minute.
Yes, I imagine so.
Mustn't stay long.
I knew I'd regret it if I didn't
say goodbye to you in person.
It was me, old friend.
I did this to you.
I started the war.
From the day I met you,
I was planning your end.
I'm sorry it has to be in this...
Squalid little corner.
C'est la vie.
Why?
Nothing personal, I assure you, Sir.
You have been a wise mentor
and a good friend.
But...
Business must come first.
I'm gonna take your place, old man.
I'm gonna be the King of Gotham.
You?
Never.
You're going to burn in hell.
I do worry about that.
But you first, old friend.
You first.
Nobody move.
- Walk away.
- Shut up.
You're both under arrest
for attempted murder.
Didn't you hear?
Falcone is out, by official decree.
Everyone agreed.
I heard.
So, release me, Jim.
Get on the winning side.
Winning side, my ass.
Maroni is a fool.
He can't replace me.
A thousand rivals will jump up
to challenge him.
There will be civil war.
- If I die now, Gotham falls apart.
- I agree.
But can you turn things around?
Can you take back control?
Of course.
Two days at my safe house.
I need two days to make some moves,
and I'll skin Maroni
and those disloyal scum.
Like rabbits.
Wake up, Napoleon.
Maroni's louts are minutes away
from coming here
to cut your throat.
And the thing is, Jim,
they aren't very fond of me either.
So, seriously,
you need to uncuff me. Jim?
Jim, where the hell
did you run off to?
Harv, I'm in the hospital
with Falcone.
There's nobody here.
No kidding, what the hell
are you doing there?
You got to get out now,
they'll be coming back
to finish him off.
Yeah, any moment now.
Unless I get him out of here.
- Jim, Jim, Jim.
- I could use some help.
No way, are you nuts?
He's a bad man, but he's
the best bad man we've got.
If Falcone loses control,
Maroni is too wild to run Gotham.
There'll be anarchy.
Yeah, probably.
But Falcone already lost control.
And he'll get it back.
Listen, you're all twisted
over what happened to Barbara.
You're not thinking straight.
Yeah, maybe.
But I'm done on this town anyhow.
What do I have to lose?
Your life.
How about your life?
What the hell are you doing here?
I thought the fix was in
with you guys.
- Can you walk?
- If I have to.
Let's get you out of here.
I'll take you to your safe house.
Jim, my friend.
You are making a terrible mistake.
I'm doing this for the city not you.
You're the least worst option.
If I didn't think
you could take back control,
I'd let you die.
Just so we're clear.
We're clear.
Well, you can't leave me here!
Maroni's men will kill me!
Possible.
No, you arrested us,
we are in your custody.
That's true.
You owe me a favor, Jim! You owe me!
Dammit.
James Gordon!
Detective Gordon!
Don't kill him.
Good morning, fellas.
What can I help you with?
James Gordon, as usual,
wrong place, wrong time.
Go. Now.
Why?
So, these men
can kill Carmine Falcone?
I have no knowledge of that.
Go. That's an order.
You're a disgrace, Loeb.
I hope to see you
behind bars very soon.
Or dead. Whichever.
Hope...
It's for losers, Jim.
He is all yours!
Jim, Jim, don't shoot, it's me.
We got to go, their ambulance
is in the basement.
Where is your man?
About that...
We got to take Penguin
and Gilzean too.
Penguin and Gilzean?
I arrested them for attempted murder,
- they're in my custody.
- I didn't even
wanna argue with you,
Come on, let's go! Go!
Tommy? Tommy?
Dammit.
What exactly are you looking for,
Master Bruce?
Will I find it or not?
Nobody knows
about this place, right?
- Nobody?
- Nobody.
Anyone who did is dead.
We'll be safe here.
Hello.
What's up?
I know, I know.
It's astonishing.
Sometimes I astonish myself.
I feel like this is all a dream.
And I'm gonna wake up soon.
Barbara, you were abducted.
Your parents were killed
in front of you.
Yeah, yeah, that's real.
I'm talking about this now, this...
This is the dream.
I'm gonna wake up.
And he's still alive.
And he's coming for me.
I thought for sure you were dead.
Let me look at you.
Fish?
It's really you.
It's me, Butch, I'm home.
My poor baby.
What did they do to you?
Nothing good.
It's him, boss.
Don Maroni.
Yes, alive and well.
That's a long story.
We need to talk.
I have something you want.
They didn't find my knife.
So, we're saved then.
It's in my sock.
If you get the chance,
- take some of them with us.
- I'll try.
Hey, you.
Selina, what are you doing here?
Chilling. How about you?
Kind a jammed up.
Yeah. That's too bad.
That's mime for help us out her.
And totally blow
the coolest gig ever.
Just because
we kinda sorta known each other.
Right?
Hello, fellas.
Carmine?
Penguin?
Nothing to share?
Well, I have a little something.
I just made a sweet deal with Maroni.
He just told me I could have
all my territories back.
And all I have to do in return...
Is give him Carmine's head.
Fish, I need to go lie down.
What did you do
to that poor soul, you sadists?
I assure you...
You'll die...
A slow and painful death
on account of Butch.
You too, Carmine.
And you.
We'll keep it simple.
And you...
We're cool.
Any questions?
How you gonna kill them?
I love this girl.
Jason saw right through me.
He knew me instantly.
Like I was naked.
It's scary.
But thrilling.
And aren't...
all the best guys a little scary?
I was way more scared of Jim Gordon
the first date we went on.
So, butch and stern.
That type, they often have
a bad temper.
But Jim was a sweetie.
He never laid a finger on me.
It's kind of surprising.
Does he ever hit you?
Me? No. Why?
Why would he hit anyone? Any woman?
You know,
out of passion.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to pry.
Only I heard you and Jim were dating.
No.
Yes, we've been on a few dates.
I'm sorry,
I didn't think that you knew.
If that makes you uncomfortable
in any way.
No, don't be silly.
I, I'm happy for you.
He's one of the good guys.
Yeah, he is.
Hey, are you hungry?
So, there he is.
Fish,
you mysterious,
crazy, gorgeous, killer you.
I love you.
This...
This is delicious.
Finally.
You're hard to kill, old man.
No.
Your people are second-rate.
Ms. Mooney, if I may, brief word.
I know my life is forfeit.
I speak not for my sake, but yours.
Because after all,
I still love and respect you.
Kill me if you must,
but keep Falcone alive.
As soon as he's dead,
Maroni has no use for you.
You are simply a threat.
He will kill you.
You think?
Why would he need
another boss in town?
Another rival?
That's where you're wrong, smart guy.
A, she's not a rival,
because she's not a boss.
She's an underboss.
And underboss takes orders.
I don't take orders.
I know that. We're cool. Relax.
I'm relaxed.
I don't think you are, babes.
Please don't call me babes.
You See? Not relaxed.
Babes?
Really? It's a term of endearment.
Means I like you.
Fine, I misspoke.
You're not an underboss
and you're not a babe.
You tell me what you are.
What we are, Sal...
Are partners.
Whatever you want.
Partners.
I'm partner number one
and you're partner number two.
That's the deal, right?
I'm number one, and you are?
Number two.
There you go.
Simple math, one, two, babes.
Sorry.
That's the last time, I swear.
Guys, can you feel
the buzz in the air?
As victory.
Redemption.
Power.
When this old man dies,
a new day begins.
We will rule Gotham.
We are building a dynasty.
We will whip this town
like a rented mule.
Right, babes?
Oh, relax. I'm kidding you.
Guys, don't, seriously...
Don't call her babes or toots
or what have you.
It's a women's lib thing.
I am relaxed.
Let's go!
Barbara, we've been circling
around the subject,
but haven't talked about
what actually happened to you.
What was done to you.
Lee, you're a nice lady.
I could go there.
But I'm not sure
you wanna go there with me.
Don't worry about me.
Has Jim told you he loves you?
- Barbara...
- Fair's fair.
And I'm telling you
all my little secrets.
No, he hasn't.
But he will though, won't he?
You can feel it coming.
I mean, come on, look at you,
you're so gorgeous and smart,
of course, he loves you.
Do you love him?
Barbara...
Tell me what happened.
If we can get to 7th Avenue
without being spotted by
Fish's people, we're home free.
Then what?
We find a safe place, regroup.
Maroni's death
is a lucky break for you.
- Spoken like a true Mafioso.
- Yeah.
The least worst option,
like you said.
Without you, the city falls apart.
Yes, I said that.
And it might be true.
But this has been a long day.
And I've had a long time to
look at this world I've created.
I'm done with this business. I'm out.
I've got a place down south
I could go to.
I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
- I know.
I'm letting you down.
I'm letting the city down, I know.
Okay. Plan B.
So, you got a place down south.
Nice? On the water?
Yes.
Any work for beat-up old cops?
Sure.
How's that sound, Jim?
Beaches, sunshine, fishing.
Yeah, tempting.
Hello again.
Cat got your tongue?
Selina.
Boys.
Bless you.
I'm gonna hand it to you, Fish.
You really know how to stop a show.
I couldn't help myself, Harvey.
The man vexed me.
Crazy move,
possibly a good move too.
We'll see.
The battlefield is in flux.
You could be looking at
the new Queen of Gotham.
Congratulations, my dear.
I'm quitting, Fish. I'm out.
Does this mean,
I don't have to kill you?
You're gonna retire some place warm?
Lay back,
read your little funny papers?
That was the thought.
Yeah, a nice thought.
Please no.
Fish! Where are you?
Then he left me...
For a long time.
Alone.
And I slept...
I don't know for how long.
And then he woke me up.
Road trip, he said.
We were halfway there when...
I realized...
We're going to my parent's house.
Go on.
Well, then, he tied them up to chair.
And...
He told me to talk to them
about my childhood issues.
So, I did.
I just told them
whatever came into my head.
And what came into your head?
You know...
Just stupid kid stuff,
I guess, like...
My mum used to call me her
little piggy when I was little.
They threw away my posters.
Never nurtured my self-esteem.
Just slowly...
Steadily...
Grinding away at my soul.
Trying to make me disappear.
That's not kid stuff.
To be fair to them...
They simply never understood me.
They have no clue...
Who I am.
Even when I was killing them,
they just gaped at me like fools.
No understanding.
Barbara...
Jason Lennon killed your parents.
You didn't kill them.
Yes, I did.
I stabbed them several times.
And then I slit their throats.
I have to leave now, please.
Are you uncomfortable?
How about now?
Lee?
She just... She just went crazy.
I told them that woman was trouble.
Butch, about time.
- Shoot her, Butch.
- Really?
Do as I say, Butch. Shoot her!
What are you doing? Drop him!
My friend, remember your training.
I order you to shoot her.
Butch, don't listen to him.
He did something to your mind.
I'm your girl.
Remember, I'm your girl.
Kill her now!
Oh, my God. What did I do?
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, I would never hurt you.
I love you, Fish.
It's okay.
It's not your fault. I love you too.
He messed with your mind.
It's not your fault.
And you're gonna be fine.
You know me.
Goodbye, Fish.
It's all good.
No!
I'm the King of Gotham.
I'm the King of Gotham!
Mr. Nygma.
Ms. Kringle.
I just noticed
something really weird.
This note Officer
Dougherty left for me...
The first letter of every lines
spells out your name.
You see?
N.Y.G.M.A.
Yes.
How odd.
What an amazing coincidence.
Coincidence?
What else could it be?
So, you know nothing about this?
I... Me? No, no.
No.
Why are you laughing, you fool?
It's not funny.
She'll keep digging.
Why did you have to leave a clue?
Why?
Relax.
What can she find?
What can she prove?
Nothing. There's no body.
Stop worrying.
But she looked so sad and angry.
I hate it when she looks at me
that way.
Like it matters,
like you stand a chance with her.
She knows how you feel about her
and she treats you like dirt.
I don't care, I still love her.
Listen to yourself. Be a man!
You'll do better way with that one
if she's a little scared of you.
Stop talking.
Hey! Just keeping it real.
What's black and white
and red all over?
Stop it!
This is so weird.
Beautiful.
I'm gonna miss this town.
You won't change your mind?
The town needs you.
No.
Gotham needs a lawman now.
Not a criminal like me.
A strong lawman.
You're looking at me?
Someone needs to grab this city
by the neck and shake it hard.
That's you, Jim.
I know it in my bones.
There's a lot of powerful men who
would disagree with you on that.
Nice knife.
That was your father's.
He gave it to me a long time ago.
A spur of the moment birthday gift.
I said, "No."
Such a beautiful knife
and I have men with guns
to protect me.
He said, "Take it."
"A knife is a good friend
when you have no other."
You were that close.
At one time.
The point of the story, Jim...
Your father was
the most honest man I ever met.
But he carried a knife.
Enough searching.
There's nothing here.
Your father was a good man,
a flawed man, like anyone else,
but it doesn't mean he had
a secret life.
My intuitions
are nearly always correct.
Well...
It's a common delusion I find.
Arkham is full of men whose
intuitions are always correct.
There are none so blind.
None so blind.
Marcus Aurelius. Marcus Aurelius!
What about him?
He was a Roman emperor.
Yes, I'm fully aware of that,
Master Bruce.
And a stoic.
I think I remember
he was a stoic like my father.
Lucius Fox called my father
a stoic.
Lots of people are called stoic.
Does not mean
a hard nut doesn't say much.
Doesn't mean
it's a bloody clue, does it?
It's a philosophy, Alfred.
It's a way of life.
Maybe that as well, I supposed but...
What is it, do you think?
I don't know and I don't care.
And don't you dare
press that bloody button.
- Why not?
- It could be a bomb.
Alfred, that seems improbable.
It's a stereo.