GORDON: Previously on Gotham...
SOFIA: Harvey is weak,
and how many more cops need to die
because of his incompetence?
As of this moment, I'm assuming
the Captaincy of Gotham Central.
Nothing in Gotham is free.
You wanted a gangster to help you
get rid of Penguin.
This is what that help looks like.
The whole town has gone
hog wild for the Pyg. (SNORTS)
GORDON: Turns out the Pygk real name
is Lazlo Valentine.
And he just escaped.
LEE: I haven't been looking
for a cure for your brain, Ed.
Because I was afraid
that if I told you the truth,
you would go back to being
who you were before.
And I like who you've become.
BRUCE: I'm not the hero Gotham needs.
- I took the dark path.
- ALFRED: Yes, you did.
And it's gonna be a long,
bumpy journey back.
- What...
- Hello, Victor.
- Where's the boy?
- SOFIA: Alive, for now.
If Oswald wants to keep it that way,
he will meet me under
the Crown Point Bridge...
You wanted a war, you've got one!
We will wait for Mr. Cobblepot
to send instructions.
Åhh!
(ALL GRUNTING)
Hello.
Where is Penguin, little man?
This is Gordon.
I need forensics in West End Alley.
A black-market doc. Pyg was here.
Looks like he got a new face.
(CHOKING)
(MR. PENN SCREAMING)
So, Penguin's out building
support amongst the gangs.
Pretty soon every criminal in Gotham
is gonna be hunting us.
He's out building support
because we made him look weak.
We kill him, and all the gangs
will support me.
- I'm still a Falcone.
- Yeah, you mentioned that.
- About a billion times.
- (DOOR OPENS)
(EXHALES) He doesn't know
where Penguin is.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATES)
(SIGHS) What?
I'II be right there.
Is that about Penguin?
No.
Harper.
We were an hour outside of Gotham
when I got waylaid by Victor Zsasz.
He took Sofia. Gave me this.
Iwoke up in Virginia.
Damn it. I had a deal with Penguin.
There's more.
We're getting word Penguin had some
meeting under the Crown Point Bridge
late last night.
Gunfire. A car blown up.
Sofia Falcone was there.
AII right, we have
to find Penguin. Harper?
- I'm good, Cap.
- Put out a citywide BOLO.
- L'll find Sofia.
- HARPER: What about the Pyg?
- I heard he escaped from Arkham.
- Tracked him to a black market surgeon.
He's already got a new
face. Lazlo Valentine is gone.
- But if we don't find him...
- Focus on the bigger problem.
We've got a war to stop, people.
So, you're gonna tell us
why we're at your dad's house?
Why do you think?
Sofia.
You look tired.
Ms. Kean, it's good to see you again.
Likewise. So this is weird.
Why are you here, Father?
What did I tell you when you
asked to return to Gotham?
- I know...
- (LOUDLY) What did I tell you?
- That I wasn't ready.
- Exactly.
And you came back anyway.
Perhaps I should've acted then.
But I was indulgent.
Curious.
Who is this daughter I raised?
Father, Penguin is weak.
If you help me, we can end this.
I don't want Gotham.
I don't believe that.
You love this city.
I used to, yes.
But I'm dying, Sofia.
Someone else can have Gotham.
What I care about now is my family.
And I'm your family. And I want this.
I deserve this. Gotham belongs to me.
Your actions
have disgraced our family.
Tell me how sleeping with Jim Gordon,
the man who killed your brother,
helped reclaim Gotham.
I'm sorry, what?
I have done many things
Iwill have to answer for.
But I always knew
the meaning of honor.
You have proven that you do not.
Children... (CHUCKLES)
- They can be such disappointments.
- (SELINA GASPS)
I kill him, and this is over. Please.
You know why I came
when Penguin called?
It's because you were going to lose.
If you were anyone but my daughter.
You'd be dead right now.
Oh. Morning.
In there.
ALFRED: Dear, oh, dear.
Oh. Good morning, Officer.
My name is Alfred Pennyworth.
Neighbors called in
a noise complaint.
- He's all yours.
- Thank you.
Right.
(SCOFFS)
(ALL GASPING)
- Good morning, Master Bruce.
- WOMAN: Oh, my God!
Ido believe the party
is well and truly over.
Morning, miss. Good morning, miss.
GCPD.
- I'm looking...
- For my daughter.
You can stop. She's with me.
GORDON: Carmine.
I didn't expect to see you.
I imagine not.
I arrived this morning.
- You heard Sofia is in danger.
- Was in danger.
I made a deal with Cobblepot.
I take her out of Gotham today
and she lives.
I made the same deal,
he didn't keep it.
He will with me.
I'm glad I never killed you.
Thanks.
Don't thank me. Killing you
would have been a kindness.
You have no idea what you've brought
to your city.
I imagine when you find out
the truth, it will destroy you.
That's a comfort.
Another day. Another man
sending me out of Gotham.
We're both just trying
to keep you alive.
Tell yourself that.
But what I know is that neither
of you believed in me.
Could have been s0 different.
Goodbye, James Gordon.
I doubt we'II see each other again.
The sun never shines here.
Everything I did, I did for your love.
That doesn't matter, does it?
What matters is that after
everything you've done,
I still consider you my daughter.
That's enough.
Mother planted those roses,
she loved them.
I wanna take one with me.
Get down!
(GASPS)
(INAUDIBLE)
Gotham is still reeling
from the violent death
of Carmine Falcone three days ago.
Falcone ruled the Gotham underworld
for nearly 30 years.
No arrests have been made
and a strange quiet...
Pleasant night, Master Bruce?
There's a mess in the Rolls.
You'll need a bucket.
MALE NEWSCASTER: which many have
atlributed to the Pax Penguina.
Indeed, the Don 's claim
to the throne of Gotham...
He shouldn't have come back.
More recent years
by a new breed of criminal...
Leaving some to ask, does Gotham...
Yes, Victor?
You would've told me, right?
If you were gonna ice the old man.
(SCOFFS) Obviously!
Victor, I did not kill Don Falcone.
Well, everyone on the street
thinks you did.
So let 'em.
My hands are clean. You have my word.
MALE NEWSCASTER:
With Don Falcone's passing,
it is unknown how or indeed when
the void of power
at the center of the city's
Underworld will be filled.
(CHOIR SINGING)
GORDON: Sofia.
- I came to the hospital.
- I told them not to admit you.
- I am truly sorry about your father.
- You know it was Penguin.
And if I had evidence supporting
that, I'd arrest him.
He is over there, waiting to see
my face and gloat.
He is a liar.
And a murderer many times over.
But you need evidence.
I have to bury my father.
Excuse us.
(GASPS)
Victor!
- (SIGHS) Harvey.
- Jim.
Your leave is almost up.
- Be good to have you back.
- We'II see.
S0 why haven't you arrested
the little weasel?
Penguin still owns the judges.
If I arrest him,
and it's not rock solid, he'll walk.
So him whacking Falcone
and you sitting on your hands,
what good does that do?
It was Sofia who paid off the Mayor
to make me Captain.
I didn't ask her to.
Well, well.
She's been pressing me
to move on Penguin. Even before this.
I told you, didn't I?
That bill would come due.
I can't allow her to turn the GCPD
into her own private army.
We've come too far.
This has to be by the book.
Then forget Falcone.
Penguin's too smart
to get nailed for that anyway.
What do you mean?
Get him to do something
you can really bust him for.
And then yank his ass off the street
once and for all.
- You're saying start a war.
- I'm saying get him to start one.
You know he's gonna come for her.
I don't give a tinker's damn
about Sofia.
Way I see it,
everything that's happened.
Down to Don Falcone
lying in that box,
comes from you deciding months ago
to go after Penguin.
This is all on you.
S0 finish what you started.
PENGUIN: Goodbye, old friend.
I will not forget
all that you taught me.
I had great respect for your father.
But once he's in the ground,
you are...
- Excuse me.
- (BREATHES HEAVILY)
Not here.
What're you doing, Jim?
Finishing what I started.
(INDISTINCT CHATFERING)
Testing, testing, one, two, three.
James Gordon.
GORDON: What do you want, Oswald?
You know what I want. Where is she?
No.
You're seriously going
to go to war for her?
I'm upholding the law.
No one gets to decide
who lives or dies in Gotham.
Can you not see, Jim?
She's manipulated you and lied...
The law is the law.
Now either get over it
or face the consequences.
(MICROPHONE FEEDBACK)
Let's try it this way.
Sofia Falcone is in this building,
whoever brings her to me
will be richly rewarded.
I'm going to count to five.
Count as much as you want, twerp.
Yeah, we don't work for you.
This man is asking you to risk
your lives to protect a gangster!
I am offering you money. Huh?
And bonus, no one gets killed. (LAUGHS)
Hey, Captain, can we?
Sure.
Get off me.
Blood will run, Jim.
Mark my words! Blood will run!
It will be on your hands!
(PENGUIN YELLING)
(OFFICERS JEERING)
From the first day
I put on the badge,
I was told things could never change.
Gotham was corrupt. GCPD was corrupt.
Criminals and lowlifes ran things.
You just showed me different.
Penguin will be coming.
It's time we showed Gotham
who we are.
Suit up.
(GUNS cocxme)
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Just let us go.
You've obviously got your hands full.
- Shut up!
- Whateven
They'II all be dead in a few minutes.
Listen, you stupid" (GROANS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON LOUDSPEAKER)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
More left.
She means your left.
Then say that.
Your left! Your left! Your left!
- Hmm.
- (SIGHS)
Yay. Teamwork!
(INDISTINCT CHATFERING)
- SOFIA: You're winning.
- So far.
But every gang in Gotham
owes Penguin allegiance.
I can't arrest them all.
So arrest Penguin,
wasn't that the point?
As long as he's using proxies,
he's protected.
I have to keep pressing him.
When his back is against the wall,
he'll do something
he can't take back or explain.
And then I'II have him.
So, you're baiting him into
committing a public atrocity.
What if he already has?
There's this boy from my orphanage.
Martin. Oswald cared for him.
I hid him away for his safety.
But Oswald forced me into telling him
where Martin was,
and then put him in a car,
and blew it up.
Why didn't you tell me this before?
Because I'm his enemy.
Who's going to believe me?
Also, I didn't see him
plant the bomb.
- So you have nothing?
- I didn't say that.
Oswald never understood the way
people cared for my father.
And one of those people
just called me.
How is Jim Gordon beating us?
Well, every cop in Gotham
is behind him.
I'm guessing he has
great leadership skills.
Victor, when this is said and done,
you and I need to have a frank
discussion about chain of command.
But now, go do something horrific!
Show the GCPD exactly...
GORDON: Oswald Cobblepot,
you're under arrest.
Have you completely lost your mind?
Nobody has to die.
We only want Cobblepot!
Well, see, Jim, that's a problem,
as they work for me.
Butjust s0 I know,
what's the charge?
Murder.
Enough! Enough!
I did not kill Don Falcone!
And I dare you to prove otherwise.
GORDON: It's not for Falcone.
I'm arresting you for the murder
of the boy you blew up
under the Crown Point Bridge.
(SNICKERING)
What's so funny?
Nothing. Well, everything,
actually, 'cause you see,
he's not dead. (LAUGHS)
I only faked his death
so that Sofia Falcone
couldn't use him against me.
She's the one who told you
I killed him, isn't she?
Then where is he?
(STAMMERS) I don't know. Victor took him
out of Gotham, tell him.
ZSASZ: What's to tell?
You blew that kid sky-high.
PENGUIN: What?
You sent that pipsqueak
to kingdom come.
No! That's not true!
And I'II testify to that.
What?
Look, I ain't taking the rap
for no kid murder.
- (YELLS)
- GORDON: Get him out of here!
You are lying!
You are a lying traitor!
Victor Zsasz is a liar!
No! I will kill you!
Traitor!
GORDON: This doesn't give you
a free pass, you know.
Jim...
Not now.
You did it, Cap. You won.
(CHEERING)
S0 I'm guessing Gordon doesn't know
the kid's actually alive.
Jim Gordon played his part.
He showed the underworld
that Penguin was weak.
That he did. End of the day...
He's a Cobblepot.
You are a Falcone.
Smile, ladies. It's a new day.
So, Sofia was as good as her word.
We got our club back.
Yippee. We get to serve drinks again.
It's just a base of operations.
But I am meeting with the designer
later to make it less Penguiny.
Have fun.
Music to soothe the savage beast?
Something like that.
Alfred?
Oh, the front page is up?
Didn't expect you to brave the light
of the day for couple more hours.
Master B.
Tommy wanted to go to
the horse races. What's all this?
It's a little project of mine.
I like to call it, Operation
Save Bruce Wayne.
(SCOFFS)
Switzerland.
Few months up in the Alps,
you'll be tickety-boo.
Are you going to kidnap me?
No, I'm going to appeal
to your better angels.
And if that doesn't work,
I shall beg.
Please, Master Bruce.
If for no other reason, do it for me.
These past weeks, you know how much
I've thought about Ra's al Ghul?
About my parents? Not at all, Alfred.
- AII you're offering me is pain.
- Well, there is no life without pain.
There's no love, there is nojoy.
Idon't know about that.
I am having a fair amount of joy.
You're bloody miserable
is what you are, mate. I can see it.
Alfred, I know you care about me.
But I am asking you to stop
what you are doing.
I'm not who you thought I was.
I'm not who my parents
mighfve wanted me to be.
- And I'm okay with that.
- But I'm not okay with it.
- And I don't believe it.
- And that's your problem.
Now, I'm gonna go meet Tommy.
Can't let you do that, Master Bruce.
(SIGHS)
You gonna stop me?
- If need be, yes.
- (SCOFFS)
You really think you can?
Oh, I know I can.
I just don't want you to make me try.
Well...
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(OBJECTS CLA1'I'ERING)
Don't do this, Master Bruce.
No, Alfred, we're doing this.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Getting slayed, Master Bruce.
Haven't been training, have you, son?
- Got a bit of ring rust.
- Really?
Because you're the only one
breathing hard, old man.
(GROANS)
- Stop it, will ya? Stop it! Stop!
- Fine! Fine.
Oh, no. Master Bruce, I'm so sorry.
I don't know what came over me...
(nooa CLOSES)
I am in control.
(LAUGHS)
I am in control. Me. Ed Nygma.
But why would you want that?
You don't understand.
We had so much fun
when we were me.
Oh, no.
Tell me it's not that.
Not what?
I leave when spurned. I give all.
I take nothing. I can raise you to
a king, or make you to a beggar.
What am I?
I'm just gonna tell you
'cause you're not going to get it.
- Love.
- I am in control!
You're in love with Lee Thompkins,
you pathetic loser.
Shut up!
Ed angry at mirror?
No, Grundy.
I am not angry at the mirror.
- Ed angry at Ed?
- That is...
Surprisingly perceptive.
(SIGHS) I need some air.
(nooa CLOSES)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON GRAMOPHONE)
This was the end of Solomon Grundy
Huh?
(GROANS)
This was the end of Solomon Grundy
(GRUNTING)
- Where is Grundy?
- I kidnapped you.
For the record, you're not light.
What pretty lady want?
When we were fighting,
you called me "Tabby," remember?
- Grundy want to go back to friend Ed.
- Ed...
Right, your friend.
Well, your best friend Ed
tied you and me to chairs.
Electrocuted you,
and cut off my hand.
Look at the scar. Ring a bell?
(EXHALES)
Remember me, Butch. I'm Tabby.
I'm your Tabby.
Grundy sorry.
Yeah. I'm sorry too.
Before, when you said my name.
I'd just hit you in the head.
Maybe that's the only way.
So you're gonna remember me, Butch...
Or I'm gonna beat your head in.
- Pretty lady...
- (GRUNTS)
When I called,
I wasn't sure you would come.
I was going to anyway.
We need to talk.
I agree.
I'm going to ask you not to do
what you're about to do.
Which is?
Unify the gar195-
Put the Falcones back
in charge of the underworld.
But wasn't that our deal?
I'd replace Penguin.
You'd be the law, I'd be the order?
No. And if you try and take over,
l'll have to come after you.
James.
You're nothing if not predictable.
(CLICKS TONGUE) Now, I think it's time
you heard my proposal.
- I'm not interested.
- I think you are.
MAN: Surprise.
(GUN COCKS)
I know, you thought I'd have
a different face
because I killed that doctor.
But that was just to throw you
off the scent.
That's not why he's surprised, Lazlo.
THE PYG: Can I tell him?
You came to this beautiful woman
because you had a problem.
A Penguin problem.
Pax Penguina was gonna last.
But Sofia had an idea.
I'd heard of a contract killer that
was impersonating serial killers, so.
What if there was a killer,
a real vicious son of a bitch,
hunting the police, all slice and dice.
SOFIA: I needed the police
to turn on Penguin.
I knew a few cops would have to die.
So you sent this monster to my city?
I let him improvise.
I'II admit, got a little carried away
with the whole (CHUCKLES)
"cooking folks" routine.
I really got in the role.
You know, only hiccup was that mess
with her daddy.
That was you.
I gave him a chance, Jim.
And if he would've shown
one iota of appreciation
for everything
I have done for this family,
for him... He would be alive.
GORDON: But I saw you shot.
There was another shooter there.
SOFIA: I had to do something
to throw off suspicion.
THE PYG: Well, she wasn't about
to get herself
plugged by a bunch
of yahoos in a car.
It was some pretty shooting,
if I do say so.
I missed all her vital parts.
I'm putting you in jail.
And this time it's Blackgate.
- You are gonna rot in there.
- Jim...
(eunsnor)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
That's done now.
(CLATTERS)
My father had his moment of truth.
This is yours.
How many cops died under
the Pax Penguina? Not one.
It was you who couldn't stomach it.
It was you who came
to the Falcones for help.
There is a direct line
from your decision
to a dozen police officers
who have been brutally murdered.
You are insane.
Why notjust kill me?
Because, Jim...
I need you at the head of the GCPD.
- I need...
- Someone you can control.
You've been planning this
since the day we first met.
This isn't about Gotham.
This is revenge.
For me killing Mario.
(GUN THUDS)
You want
to arrest me, arrest me.
But I will talk.
And the cops that died,
the friend that you betrayed,
will all have been for nothing.
The GCPD will crumble.
Penguin, or someone worse,
will take over
and you will lose Gotham forever.
Or, take on the sin as your own.
Keep the GCPD.
Let them think you're a hero.
But live knowing who you are.
What you've done.
That's my revenge.
(PHONE BEEPS)
FEMALE OFFICER: GCPD.
GCPD, how can I help you?
Hello? Anyone there? Anybody?
This is Gordon.
I'm at Sofia Falcone's...
Ijust shot and killed the Pyg.
Oh, thank Christ. You're safe.
Master Bruce, listen,
I don't want to fight anymore.
You win.
If this is how you want to deal
with what you've been going through,
then so be it.
I'm not gonna try and stop you.
Butjust knowthis...
You will remember who you are,
and when you do,
Iwill be right here...
No. you won't be.
I went to my lawyer and had him
draw up emancipation papers.
You're no longer my legal guardian.
I won't sign them.
You don't have to. Now I'm going out.
If you're still here when I get back,
I'II go to the police
and show them my face.
- Master Bruce, please...
- Alfred, you're fired.
Now get the hell out of my house.
(nooa CLOSES)
(PANTING)
Butch! Say something!
Say something.
(PIPE CLATTERS)
(GROANS)
I'm sorry.
I tried.
(LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATFERING)
Harvey.
I wasjust, uh, dropping something off.
Oh, I heard you got the Pyg.
- And Penguin.
- Yeah.
So everything turned out well.
- You didn't even need me...
- You got a second? Could we, uh...
They, uh, believe in you.
Don't let them down.
What the hell happened to me?
PENGUIN: Traitors.
Every single one of them.
I'II kill her! I will flay her alive!
Her and Gordon and Zsasz and...
(BANGING)
- MAN: Hey, buddy...
- (GASPS)
- Do not talk to me.
- I get it, pal...
This place is full of loonies.
I just thought,
we could help each other out.
And how can you help me? (CHUCKLES)
Well, not to toot my own horn,
but I'm a very resourceful fellow.
So, toot. Toot, toot!
(MAN CACKLES)
(GASPS)
I know that laugh.
What do you say, pal?
L'II be your best friend.
(GASPS)
Give me a smile...
(LAUGHS)
English - SDH