BARBARA: Previously on Gotham...
Oh, no. Help me! Help me! Somebody help!
COBBLEPOT: They think she might have
fallen asleep at the wheel.
ED: Her brake lines were cut.
Which leaves one conclusion. Murder.
And I know who did it.
Hold on, Butch.
IVY: I might be in trouble.
I stole a necklace.
BRUCE: Why is this necklace
so important?
What makes someone kill for it?
- What is it?
- A key.
SELINA: We need to go somewhere.
BRUCE: We'll go to my house.
You two are a couple now?
- No.
- Yes.
My engagement announcement is
coming out in the Gazette tomorrow.
And it will feature Mario's name.
His family name.
JIM: You mean Falcone?
Such a beautiful space
for a rehearsal dinner.
We can't thank you enough.
And did Roberto's food
live up to all my hype?
Are you kidding?
(SIGHS) Any more burrata,
and I wouldn't fit into my wedding dress.
(CHUCKLES)
I can't believe we're getting married
in two days.
Have you two settled
on a honeymoon destination?
Uh, no, but Lee finally agreed
to take some time off of work.
With everything going on,
I didn't wanna leave anybody in the lurch.
I was very sorry
to hear about Captain Barnes.
He's a good man.
What he did was due entirely to the virus.
What's truly frightening is that
nobody knew. Nobody could see it.
There aren't any symptoms?
Well, looking back now, there were signs.
Increased strength, emotional instability.
Nothing he couldn't hide.
DR. THOMPKINS: The lab
analyzing Alice Tetch's blood
has developed a test
to see if someone's infected.
- You're kidding. When?
- They just finished.
It's a step toward finding a cure.
How are we? Good?
Wonderful, Roberto.
We can't wait for tomorrow night.
Oh! Your rehearsal dinner's
gonna be fantastico.
We're gonna take care of everything.
It's a privilege to serve you again,
Don Falcone.
Don Falcone, please,
we'll pull your car around.
Yeah, okay.
- Wonderful evening, Roberto.
- You're welcome.
- I love you.
- (SOFT CHUCKLE) I love you, too.
(BOTH GRUNT)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
MALE WAITER 1: You don't
understand anything, okay?
My friend just got blown up.
Now, I wanna know what happened?
Can you explain that to me?
We need to talk.
Is everyone okay?
A few first degree burns, but that's it.
They were lucky.
Any idea who might have done this?
I've made my share of enemies
over the years. Could be anyone.
Why come after you now?
My oldest son is getting married.
When better to settle an old score
and hurt me and my family?
Maybe.
Or maybe someone thinks
you're coming out of retirement?
- I'm not.
- Good.
Doesn't mean I'm gonna stand by
after something like this.
The Captain of Police was just indicted
for murder and sent to Arkham.
The last thing I need is you and your men
tearing up Gotham, looking for revenge.
I didn't start this.
I'll get to the bottom of it.
You have my word.
I'll give you one day.
COBBLEPOT: As members
of the five families, you are well aware
that with the tragic downfall
of Captain Barnes,
people are frightened.
They will be looking to us for stability,
to feel safe.
So,
how does a 50% increase
on protection fees sound?
- (LAUGHTER)
- BARBARA: Sounds a little steep to me.
What do we have here?
A little family reunion?
My invitation get lost in the mail?
No, this meeting is for grown-ups,
so I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
Hmm.
Quick question.
(GUNS COCKING)
Is it, "How do I commit suicide?"
Because that answer is coming.
Tabitha and Butch are missing.
Where are they?
I have no idea.
I have not seen Butch since his little
summer stock revival of the Red Hood Gang.
Let's cut the crap. Shall we?
Tabitha has been helping Butch hide
since your little victory celebration.
They're an item now, barf...
She's supposed to check in every night,
and she hasn't.
She's not answering her phone,
and no one has seen her.
And you think I took them?
Obviously.
(MUFFLED LAUGHTER)
How about this, you lower your gun
and beg my forgiveness
for this gross insubordination,
and I might let you walk
out of here alive.
(SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
MY apologies.
They must have run off somewhere
without telling me.
Love makes people
do crazy things, doesn't it?
We have a history, you and I.
But if you ever point a gun at me again,
Olga will be cleaning your brains
off the floor.
She's a real wiz with stains.
Bye, Pengy.
Everyone out, now!
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Are you checking up on me?
What? No.
Barbara Kean was just here.
She's looking for them.
- So'?
- So, are you finished yet?
We've talked about this.
I need to work through my grief my way.
COBBLEPOT: Of course, and I support you.
Any chance you could work through it
a smidge faster?
I am swamped today.
(DIAL TONE)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Sorry you had to hear that.
He can just be so self-centered.
- What were we talking about?
- I’m gonna kill you!
On! Right, how I found you. (LAUGHING)
Well, it wasn't hard.
The next time you wanna disappear,
consider taking a sabbatical
from your favorite restaurant.
Your love of Gusto's Eggplant Parmesan
isn't exactly a state secret.
- (MUFFLED GROANS)
- Come here.
That, with a healthy amount of Midazolam
in your food to knock you out.
A hundred bucks to your delivery boy,
who, by the way,
I get the feeling
hasn't been being tipped very well, Butch.
(MUFFLED SPEECH)
I'm sorry. What was that?
(MUFFLED) You're gonna regret this!
You're gonna regret this.
If you touch one hair on her head,
I swear I'll kill you.
Save your strength, big guy.
You're gonna need it.
And you tell Penguin he's a coward.
If he wants me dead,
- he should come here and do it like a man.
- (DEVICE POWERING UP)
This has nothing to do with Penguin.
And you are the coward.
Killing an innocent woman.
What? Who?
Isabella.
She was my everything,
and you took her from me!
What in the hell are you talkin' about?
I was hoping you'd be difficult.
- (ELECTRICITY ZAPPING)
- (GROANING)
(LAUGHING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey. You okay?
Stomach.
Being acting captain is such a strain,
why do it?
I'm the senior guy around here.
- What about Tuttle?
- Tuttle?
Guy shot a cat last week.
- On purpose?
- Does it matter?
Look, I might not have always
seen eye-to-eye with Barnes,
but he was a good captain.
Least I can do is keep his seat warm
until they find some kind of cure
for this virus.
Detective Gordon,
car bomb used a mercury switch
with military grade plastic.
That's kind of high end for a mob hit.
That's not all.
The explosive was laced
with some sort of accelerant.
Made the explosion burn at 10 times
the heat of standard C-4.
Whoever set this bomb
didn't want anything left behind.
Only one guy I know
with that level of expertise.
Ex-military nutjob,
goes by the name of "Fuse."
(SIRENS WAILING)
This is our guy.
Not for nothing, ensuring Don Falcone's
safety is not why I wear the badge.
- It's not just about him.
- You mean Lee?
If you're worried, you could tell her not
to marry the son of a former crime boss.
GCPD!
Dead, but still warm.
Whoever did this must've just left.
So, whoever hired Fuse to plant the bomb
doesn't want any loose ends?
Looks like he was on his way out of town.
Must have figured
his employers weren't that forgiving.
- Guy can pack, I'll give him that much.
- Once a soldier, always a soldier.
Bed sheets aren't tucked in.
Times, locations, surveillance photos.
- This doesn't make any sense.
- What?
Carmine's not the target.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(MOTORCYCLE REVVING)
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
(TIRES SCREECH)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
- Down!
- (GUNSHOTS)
What the hell's going on?
Carmine's not the target. You are.
Et, euh, voila.
Thank you very much, Master Bruce.
What is this?
That is a Pennyworth signature frittata.
It's a crustless quiche.
It's eggs, miss. Just eat it, will you?
Where's your mate, anyway?
Conservatory. Girl loves it there.
Well, she's hardly what you call
"a girl," is she?
Yeah. Well, thanks for
the crustless egg thing.
But I got errands to run.
Uh, no, sorry, miss.
No one is to leave the house
until we find
exactly who is following you.
It's been days. I can't take it anymore.
I'm sorry.
What is it exactly that you object to?
Is it the gourmet food, or the king-size
double-bed with the Egyptian linen?
Would you tell the help here that
I can come and go as I please? Please?
Alfred's right. It's not safe for you
to be in Gotham alone.
(SCOFFS)
I've been in Gotham alone my whole life.
I can take care of myself.
Nothing's changed.
Yeah, you've made that clear.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Nothing.
Those men were willing to kill
for this key, we need to know why.
I'll be in the study.
There's more books I haven't gone through.
There has to be a reference
to the key somewhere.
And have you stopped to consider
that maybe it's just an old key?
No.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACH)
I'll get you some breakfast, miss.
You know, some of these plants would do
much better in direct sunlight.
Could you turn off the alarm,
so I can put them outside?
Well, maybe later. I'd rather not you be
walking around the grounds on your own.
Can you smell this?
Beg your pardon?
Right here.
(EXHALES DEEPLY) What is that?
Just a mix of clove, fenugreek,
and yarrow root oils.
It's lovely.
- It is, isn't it?
- Yeah.
Now, I need you
to tell me something, okay?
Anything.
How do you turn off the alarm?
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
This doesn't make any sense.
Do you know anyone
who might want you dead?
- You can't be serious.
- Everyone has enemies.
No, Detective. They don't.
Regardless, you need
to limit your exposure.
Lay low for a while
until I can find out who's behind this.
How do you propose I do that?
I'm picking up our wedding rings
this afternoon.
Lee and I are getting married tomorrow.
Oh.
You want me to cancel the wedding.
- I just wanna keep you safe.
- I’d bet you'd love that.
I run home to Lee.
Tell her we need to hide until
Detective Gordon can save the day?
- This is not a time for ego.
- Are you talking to me about ego?
How do I even know
you're gonna be able to find him?
- Or that you'll even try?
- You need to trust me.
Whoever is behind this is gonna
keep coming until they get the job done.
If that's true, it doesn't matter
where we go, or what we do.
As long as I got a target on my back,
Lee isn't safe.
- Hey.
- Yeah.
Keep an eye on Mario, don't let him leave.
What are you doing?
- I'm keeping an eye on Mario.
- Don't look at him.
What the hell's going on?
I don't know. Something doesn't fit.
I need to talk to Carmine.
Maybe once he knows Mario's the target,
something will jog his memory.
Just keep it...
I got it. I got it.
(DOOR LOCK OPENS)
Hello, Comrade.
Comrade is not Russian word.
- Oh, shut up. Of course, it is.
- You shouldn't be here.
Relax.
I know Penguin's out for a few hours.
I just wanna talk.
I don't know anything.
Listen. I grew up in a place like this.
A large staff of people
always coming and going.
Listening. You can't help
but overhear things.
Is handsome ring.
(GASPS) It is. And very expensive.
I bet it would look just fabulous on you.
(CHUCKLING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Mr. Penguin, he treat me nice.
I have warm feeling for him.
But the other one...
Nygma?
I don't know why
Mr. Penguin likes him so much.
He could do better.
Wait. You mean likes, likes?
Wow. Okay, we should definitely
revisit that another time.
But what about Nygma? Did he say
anything about my missing friend?
I don't know.
But I hear Mr. Nygma
talking about special delivery.
But nothing come to the house, but bill.
"Stocks & Bondage?"
- (ELECTRICITY ZAPPING)
- (LAUGHING)
(GROANING)
(MUFFLED GRUNTS)
BUTCH: How many times
do I have to tell you?
I have never even heard of this woman.
- (ELECTRICITY ZAPS)
- (GRUNTS)
Well, then I suppose
I should put my attention elsewhere.
BUTCH: No! No!
- Leave her out of this!
- ED: Afraid I can't do that.
She is an integral part of your penance.
It was such a pleasant surprise
when I discovered
that the two of you were together.
(LAUGHING)
You know, after the initial gag reflex.
You know,
I bet this girl doesn't even exist.
I mean, come on, who would fall in love
with a freak show like you?
(CHUCKLING) Oh, wait, let me guess,
I bet she's got a certificate, too, huh?
- ED: Mmm-hmm.
- (LAUGHING)
- (ELECTRICITY ZAPS)
- (GROANING)
(MUFFLED) What do you want?
Tell me what you want?
Tell me what you want.
I wanna break Butch's heart
before I end his life.
You know, kind of an eye-for-an-eye thing.
But in this case,
I'll take a hand.
(DOOR OPENS)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Is that vinegar?
Vinegar and baking soda.
Takes tarnish off anything.
Selina, that key is hundreds of years old!
I'm not an idiot, you know?
Maybe there's something on the key
that you can't see,
because 100 years of crap
is covering it up?
Why did you tell Ivy we weren't a couple?
- Why did you tell her we were?
- Is that a trick question?
Why can't we just be us?
Can you take that key out now?
It's making me nervous.
(SOFT CHUCKLE)
SELINA: Mmm.
There's an engraving on it.
Like a bird, or something.
Not just a bird. An owl.
- Uh... And'?
- BRUCE: Alfred!
If you're right, merely possessing
this key could be seen as breaking
your agreement with the people that
the woman in the owl mask represents.
Which is why we need to contact them.
They have to understand
Ivy didn't know what she was stealing.
Wait. Where is she anyhow?
Oh, bloody hell. She's gone.
How did she disable the alarm?
Don't worry about that now, all right?
What's the big deal?
She'll be back when she's hungry.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Wayne Manor.
VOLK: You have the necklace,
we have your friend.
We make exchange, no?
Where and when?
We're supposed to go down the manhole?
That's what they said. All right,
give me the key. I'll sort it out.
No. I need to speak with them personally.
Make sure they understand
this was a mistake.
Very well, Master Bruce.
There's no way of asking you to stay here
that doesn't end with you yelling at me,
is there?
No.
BRUCE: Over there.
- SELINA: Ivy?
- It's about time.
My name is Bruce Wayne.
I need to speak with Kathryn.
She needs to understand
I've honored our deal.
Hand over the necklace, and you
get your friend back. That's the deal.
You mean the key, don't you?
You're not getting it back until
I talk to the people you work for.
Maybe we just kill you and take it?
You think we're stupid enough
to bring it with us?
You really want it back,
I'd listen to him.
Put the tools down. All right? Eh?
I need reassurances my friends
are no longer in any danger.
I need to speak to the woman in the mask.
Any assurances that woman
gives you are lies.
How do you know?
Because the people you are talking about
have no honor.
And they will betray you,
as they betrayed us.
Wait. You don't work for them?
No. We work to destroy them.
Who are they?
They call themselves "The Court of Owls."
(SIRENS WAILING)
- They're after Mario?
- Yes.
- Where is he?
- GCPD. He's safe. For now.
But I can't help him
if you don't tell me what's going on.
You think I'm holding something back?
Military grade explosion? The clean-up?
A sword-wielding assassin
in broad daylight.
This doesn't feel like a mob grudge.
What else is there?
Could Mario be mixed up in something?
- Is that what you came to ask me?
- I’m working the evidence I have.
I understand why you'd want to believe
the man who's marrying Lee
must be mixed up in something.
My son is the most decent person
I've ever known.
He's not like us.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
That just tells me
there's something you don't know.
BULLOCK: Jim, Mario's gone.
You were supposed to keep him there.
I know, I tried,
but he said he didn't trust you
or the GCPD to take care of this.
So, he was going to.
Whatever the hell that means.
What is it?
Mario just walked out of the GCPD.
Think he's gonna try
to finish this himself.
How?
I have a pretty good idea.
- Can I help you?
- BARBARA: I hope so.
I had something
that was supposed to be delivered to me?
Could you check your records?
Sure. Let me check the safe.
Uh, what was the last name?
"Nygma."
Oh. That item was already delivered.
Great.
Well, I guess as long as I'm already here
I should pick up something
for the weekend. Right?
(SOFTLY) Mmm.
Well, this looks fun.
Could I ask a favor of you?
- Uh, Todd.
- Todd.
Could you show me how this works?
(SIGHS)
We're not really supposed to...
(CLEARS THROAT)
I won't tell if you don't.
It's pretty basic, really.
Um, you just put your arms through here,
and then your head through here,
and then you bring it up.
And then... Oh!
Do you like role play, Todd?
Good.
I will play the beautiful,
coquettish bank robber
who needs to get into that safe,
and you get to play
the lucky, young shopkeeper
who gives her the combination, okay?
My friend was taken by this man, Nygma.
I need to know where she is.
If I find her, I could come back here
and personally thank you.
(WHIMPERING)
Give Mommy the combination.
(STAMMERING) Nine, 25, 72.
Good.
(SIGHS)
Nygma, you sick bastard.
(STAMMERING)
Hey? You can’t just leave me here!
Hello?
(GASPS) Oh, goodie! You're finally awake.
The show continues.
(MIMICKING DRUMROLL)
Ta-da!
I designed it myself.
You wanna see how it works? Okay!
I love a captive audience.
So, we'll set the timer for,
say, 55 seconds.
Now, when the timer hits zero,
the spring-loaded blade is released.
- (TIMER TICKING)
- Simple. Now, for the fun part.
You can stop the blade from being
released, if you click this little button.
But if you do,
it will send a fatal jolt of electricity
to zap Butch.
It's a simple test, really.
Stop the blade from falling
and kill Butch, or...
(TIMER tunes)
Mmm!
The choice...
(GRUNTS)
...my dear, is yours.
Will we hear the zap of heartbreak,
or the sound of one-hand clapping.
(LAUGHING)
(METAL CHAINS CLINKING)
My name is Volk.
(CUFFS CLICK)
My brother, Jacob, and that's Dmitry.
What's with the stupid mask?
I like you.
You remind me of my sister in Kiev.
Dmitry is an initiate.
The mask ensures his silence
until he proves himself
and becomes a full member.
Of what? Who are you?
We are called "the Whisper Gang."
Gotham's most notorious smugglers.
We used to number in the hundreds
until the Court saw our growing strength
and they offered us a partnership,
only to betray us.
Many escaped back to Ukraine,
but a few of us stayed back,
hoping to find a way to enact revenge.
- And we did.
- The key?
But what does it open?
A safe.
It is in
one of the Court's buildings, here.
Inside, there is a device
that we believe can destroy them.
What? Like some kind of weapon?
Oh, honestly, we don't know.
We captured a member.
But even he didn't know
what's inside the safe.
Only that the Court fears it
falling into the hands of their enemies.
Wait, wouldn't they know you stole it?
They're probably waiting for you
to show up there.
No. Because, originally,
the safe had two keys.
The Court still has one of them.
And the second one was thought lost.
Until we found it.
You mean, we did?
The Court of Owls killed my parents.
I stood down because I thought
there was no way to defeat them.
What are you proposing?
If what you're saying is true,
and there is something in that safe,
then that's no longer the case.
(DOOR OPENS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
JIM: Mario?
You really think this is a good idea?
Using yourself as bait?
If those guys are out there,
Lee isn't safe.
They're pros. You're gonna get killed.
What do you care?
- Why would someone wanna kill you?
- I have no idea.
Because it seems to me
an operation like this
doesn't happen for no reason.
And putting yourself in the cross hairs
feels a lot like
someone protecting a secret.
I wanna protect Lee. That's it.
We're sitting ducks in here.
We need to get away from bystanders.
- They're here.
- What?
Get down!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
WOMAN: No! No!
(GROANS)
(MEN GRUNTING)
(MARIO STRAINING)
(SCREAMING)
You could have killed her! Who sent you?
Why are you coming after me?
(CHOKING) You know why.
(GRUNTS)
- (SIRENS WAILING)
- (HANDCUFFS CLICKING)
(BUTCH AND TABITHA GRUNTING)
Hey, Ed, come on.
Come on, let's talk about this, huh?
Come on, Ed. You don't have to do this.
Come on, let's talk about this.
Come on! Listen!
I told you, I've never heard
of anyone named Isabelle.
Isabella! Why is that so difficult?
Also, I'm not the one
you should be pleading with.
Your life is in her hand.
What difference does it make?
You're gonna kill me one way,
or the other, right?
Good point. (CHUCKLES)
New deal.
If she loves you enough
to sacrifice her hand. Twinsies.
In exchange for your life.
I swear on the memory
of my beloved Isabella,
I will set you both free.
(CLICKING)
(TIMER TICKING)
Tabby, baby, you don't wanna...
- We can get out of here. We can...
- I like you, Butch. I really do.
But to be completely honest,
I'm not exactly in a love place right now.
(LAUGHS)
Sorry, big fella.
I wish I could say that I was surprised,
but I knew that she was going to say that.
(WHISPERS) It's why I made the offer.
Any final words? I would keep it brief.
BUTCH: Tabby, baby,
the last few weeks
have been the best of my life.
And it's okay you don't love me.
'Cause I love you.
And for a guy like me, that's enough.
And, you, you're damn right I killed her.
I killed the woman you loved.
You know what she said to me
right before I put a bullet in her brain?
You know what she told me?
She said she wished
she would've been with a real man.
Hey, Butch?
Yeah?
You're sweet.
No! No!
(GASPS)
Untie me!
Please untie me!
She's gotta get to a hospital! Quick!
You said
that you put a bullet in her head.
Isabella died in a car crash.
The break lines were cut.
I don't care!
I told you I never heard of her.
You really didn't kill her?
No! Untie me!
She's gotta get to a hospital! Come on!
(GUN COCKS)
I'd put that hand on some ice.
(HORNS BLARING)
Neither of you recognize him?
No.
Has he said anything?
Not a pee-P-
Hey. I ran your guy's prints.
They're not in the system.
Which, considering he's a pro,
wasn't that hard to believe.
I know. Still. Now, that we have him,
we should work him.
Find out who's behind this.
You better act quick. Call came in.
They're transferring him
to a Federal facility upstate.
What! No, no, no.
We can't let this guy leave!
What can I do? My hands were tied.
The Feds want him, they get him.
Question is why.
Maybe somebody wants him
out of this precinct.
Away from us.
I don't know anyone
with that kind of pull. Do you?
JIM: The other assassin.
You wanna tell me
what happened in the store?
There's nothing to tell. He came after me,
I did what I needed to do.
You called her?
She deserves to know what's going on.
Either you tell her, or I will.
(DOOR CLOSES)
FALCONE: I think I know who sent you,
but I need to know for sure.
And we both know
that you're not going to tell me.
So...
So, how does it feel?
BULLOCK: I don't know.
Maybe I could be Captain?
Yell at people for not having proof,
or at one of my detectives
for going after a pair of assassins
all by his lonesome!
- Not bad.
- Right?
Very interesting play, by the way.
It's not every day that you get to save
the man who's marrying the woman you love.
Yeah. I'm really something.
It's not too late, Jim.
Lee deserves to know how you feel.
God knows I know
that life gives us enough regret.
There's no need adding to it.
- Oh, crap.
- I know it's hard.
It's just, it's something you have to...
Falcone!
(ASSASSIN SCREAMING)
(CONTINUES SCREAMING)
(COUGHING)
(BLOOD SPUTTERING)
(ASSASSIN SPITS)
(DOOR OPENS)
Falcone, up against the wall.
- What're you doing?
- Just having a chat.
Turns out our friend here works
for a former associate of mine.
So, now that I know who's behind this,
I can take care of it.
My way. It's over.
You think you're gonna walk away?
You just assaulted a suspect
in police custody.
He won't be pressing charges.
I'm gonna find out what happened today.
Who's pulling the strings.
And how Mario's involved. Trust me.
If I were you, I'd let it go.
VOLK: Gather the men.
Tell them
we're joining forces with the boy.
I will brief them tomorrow night myself.
TALON: Volk!
Dmitry, eyes!
(CHOKES)
We know you've been searching
for the second key.
Have you found it?
(BOTH GRUNTING)
I'll ask you again.
Have you found the second key?
(GROWLING)
Why don't you ask Dmitry? Huh?
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS AND GROANS)
(BLOOD DRIPPING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
You think she'll be okay?
Think they can reattach the hand?
Please. She's tough as nails.
She'll be fine.
BUTCH: You know this is war, right?
Nygma, Penguin, anyone
who stands with them, they're all dead.
This woman, Isabella.
Nygma said she was a librarian, right?
Well, who kills a librarian?
I mean, what's the motive?
I don't know.
Maybe someone had an overdue book
and things got out of hand.
Excuse me, but you just can't walk...
Come on! Come on! I got it.
NURSE: We got a hand here, people! Hand!
You cut someone's break lines,
you know where they're going and when.
You know...
You know them.
(LAUGHS)
I know who did it.
I know who killed the librarian.
Who?
The same person who's in love with Nygma,
and doesn't wanna share him. (GIGGLING)
Okay. One woman in love
with that psychotic bean pole
defies explanation, but two?
Who said anything about a woman?
(BARBARA CHUCKLES)
I am tired of sitting at the kids table.
If I'm right,
we can have way more than vengeance.
We can have it all.
We don't need to go to war.
All we need to do is start one.
(BARBARA GIGGLING)
There must've been some mistake.
We don't make mistakes.
I've always done
whatever the Court has asked of me.
Even against my own interest.
I got you Indian Hill
when Maroni refused to sell.
No one is questioning your loyalty.
If this isn't about me,
then why are you trying to kill my son?
There are things you're not privy to.
That's not an answer!
It will have to do.
We both know the level of disruption
I can cause.
You think we're scared of you?
The car bomb was designed
to look like a mob hit.
You didn't want me to find out it was you.
I have.
I don't care about your reasons.
If my son is harmed in any way,
I will come after you
with everything I have.
You won't win.
If my son is dead,
winning won't be the point.
Gotham will burn.
This city is on the brink of chaos.
Only we can save it.
We will expect your assistance
when called on.
Until then, your son is safe.
At least from us.
What aren't you telling me?
A great many things.
Enjoy your dinner.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
Hey.
Is everything okay?
I was on my way to the rehearsal dinner,
then I heard myself
telling the cab driver your address.
Mario told me everything about today.
How you risked your own life
to make sure...
I didn't do it for him.
I know.
He's a good man.
Uh-huh.
Tell me.
What?
What you have to tell me.
I missed my chance
to give you the life you deserve.
To make you happy.
But I do want that for you.
More than anything.
Why does it feel like
we keep saying goodbye?
Maybe it's all we have left.
Or we just haven't done it properly yet.
Goodbye, James Gordon.
(DOOR OPENS)
MAN: Yo, Peeping Tom! You lost?
Lucky for you, we sell directions!
Price, everything you've got.
MARIO: She loves him.
She loves him. She loves him.
You deaf?
MARIO: She loves him.
- I said...
- MARIO: She loves him.
Hey, man! What...
(MAN GROANING)
- (CHOKING)
- She loves me! And I won't let her go!
She loves me!
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English - SDH