Previously onGotham...
Oh no.
Help me! Help me! Somebody help!
They think she might have fallen
asleep at the wheel.
Her brake lines were cut!
Which leaves one conclusion. Murder.
And I know who did it.
Hold on, Butch.
I might be in trouble.
I stole a necklace.
Why is this necklace so important?
What makes someone kill for it?
- What is it?
- A key.
We need to go somewhere.
We'll go to my house.
You two are a couple now?
- No.
- Yes.
My engagement announcement is
coming out in the Gazette tomorrow.
And it will feature Mario's name.
His family name.
You mean Falcone?
Such a beautiful space
for a rehearsal dinner.
We can't thank you enough.
And did Roberto's food live
up to all my hype?
Are you kidding?
Any more Burrata, and I wouldn't fit
into my wedding dress.
I can't believe we're getting married
in two days!
Have you two settled on a,
honeymoon destination?
No. But Lee finally agreed
to take some time off of work.
With everything going on, I didn't
wanna leave anybody in the lurch.
I was very sorry
to hear about Captain Barnes.
He's a good man.
What he did was due entirely
to the virus.
What's truly frightening
is that nobody knew.
Nobody could see it.
There aren't any symptoms?
Well looking back
now there were signs,
increased strength,
emotional instability...
Nothing he couldn't hide.
The lab analyzing Alice Tetch's blood
has developed a test
to see if someone's infected.
- You're kidding. When?
- They just finished.
It's a step toward finding a cure.
- How are we? Good?
- Wonderful, Roberto.
We can't wait for tomorrow night.
Your rehearsal dinner's
gonna be fantastico.
We're gonna take care of everything.
It's a privilege to serve you again,
Don Falcone.
Don Falcone. Please.
We'll pull your car around.
Okay.
Wonderful evening, Roberto.
Appreciate...
I love you.
I love you, too.
You don't understand anything, okay?
My friend just got blown up.
Now, I wanna know what happened?
We need to talk.
Is everyone okay?
A few first degree burns
but that's it.
They were lucky.
Any idea who might have done this?
I've made my share of enemies
over the years. Could be anyone.
Why come after you now?
My oldest son is getting married.
When better to settle an old score
and hurt me and my family?
Maybe.
Or maybe someone thinks
you're coming out of retirement?
- I'm not.
- Good.
Doesn't mean I'm gonna stand by
after something like this.
The Captain of Police
was just indicted for murder
and sent to Arkham.
The last thing I need
is you and your men
tearing up Gotham
looking for revenge.
I didn't start this.
I'll get to the bottom of it.
You have my word.
I'll give you one day.
As members of the five families
you are well aware,
that with the tragic downfall
of Captain Barnes,
people are frightened.
They will be looking to us
for stability.
To feel safe.
So, how does a 50 percent increase
on protection fees sound!
Sounds a little steep to me.
What do we have here?
A little family reunion?
Did my invitation get lost
in the mail?
No. This meeting is for grown-ups,
so I'm gonna have to ask you
to leave.
Quick question.
Is it, "How do I commit suicide?"
Because that answer is coming.
Tabitha and Butch are missing.
Where are they?
I have no idea.
I have not seen Butch
since his little summer stock
revival of the Red Hood Gang.
Let's cut the crap, shall we?
Tabitha has been helping Butch hide
since your little
victory celebration.
They're an item now. Barf.
She's supposed to check
in every night, and she hasn't.
She's not answering her phone
and no one has seen her.
- And you think I took them?
- Obviously.
How about this, you lower your gun,
and beg my forgiveness
for this gross insubordination,
and I might let you walk out
of here alive.
Damn it.
My apologies.
They must have run off somewhere
without telling me.
Love.
It makes people do crazy things,
doesn't it?
We have a history, you and I.
But, if you ever point a gun
at me again,
Olga will be cleaning your brains
off the floor.
She's a real whiz with stains.
Bye, Pengy.
Everyone out, now!
Are you checking up on me?
What? No.
Barbara Kean was just here.
She's looking for them.
- So?
- So, are you finished yet?
We've talked about this.
I need to work through my grief
my way.
Of course, and I support you.
Any chance you could work through it
a smidge faster?
I am swamped today.
Sorry you had to hear that.
He can just be so self-centered.
- What were we talking about?
- I'm gonna kill you!
Right, how I found you.
Well...
...it wasn't hard.
The next time you wanna disappear,
consider taking a sabbatical
from your favorite restaurant.
Your love
of Gusto's Eggplant Parmesan
isn't exactly a state secret.
Come here.
That, with a healthy amount
of Midazolam
in your food to knock you out.
A hundred bucks to your delivery boy,
who by the way,
I get the feeling hasn't been being
tipped very well, Butch.
I'm sorry. What was that?
You're gonna regret this!
You're gonna regret this.
If you touch one hair on her head,
I swear I'll kill you.
Save your strength, big guy.
You're gonna need it.
And you tell Penguin he's a coward!
If he wants me dead, he should
come here and do it like a man!
This has nothing
to do with Penguin...
...and you are the coward.
Killing an innocent woman.
What? Who?
Isabella.
She was my everything,
and you took her from me!
What in the hell
are you talkin' about?
I was hoping you'd be difficult.
Hey.
You okay?
Stomach.
Being acting captain
is such a strain, why do it?
I'm the senior guy around here.
- What about Tuttle?
- Tuttle?
Guy shot a cat last week.
- On purpose?
- Does it matter?
Look, I might not have always seen
eye-to-eye with Barnes,
but he was a good captain.
Least I can do is keep his seat warm
until they find some kind of cure
for this virus.
Detective Gordon...
Car bomb used a mercury switch
with military-grade plastic.
That's kinda high-end for a mob hit.
That's not all.
The explosive was laced
with some sort of accelerant.
Made the explosion burn at 10 times
the heat of standard C-4.
Whoever set this bomb
didn't want anything left behind.
Only one guy I know
with that level of expertise.
Ex-military nut job
goes by the name of "Fuse."
This is our guy.
Not for nothing,
ensuring Don Falcone's safety
is not why I wear the badge.
- It's not just about him.
- You mean Lee.
If you're worried,
you could tell her not to marry
the son of a former crime boss.
GCPD!
Dead but still warm.
Whoever did this must've just left.
So whoever hired Fuse to plant
the bomb doesn't want any loose ends?
Looks like he was on his way
out of town.
Must have figured his employers
weren't that forgivin'.
Guy can pack,
I'll give him that much.
Once a soldier, always a soldier.
Bed sheets aren't tucked in.
Times, locations,
surveillance photos.
This doesn't make any sense.
What?
Carmine's not the target.
Down!
What the hell's going on?
Carmine's not the target.
You are.
Voila.
Thank you very much, Master Bruce.
What is this?
That is a Pennyworth signature
Frittata.
It's a crustless quiche.
It's eggs, Miss.
Just, just eat it, will ya?
Where's your mate, anyway?
Conservatory.
Girl loves it there.
Well, she's hardly,
what you call, a girl, is she?
Yeah. Well, thanks for the crustless
egg thing, but I got errands to run.
No, sorry, miss.
No one is to leave the house,
until we find exactly
who is following you.
It's been days.
I can't take it anymore!
I'm sorry. What is it exactly
that you object to?
Is it the gourmet food
or the king-size double-bed
with the Egyptian linen?
Would you tell the help here
that I can come and go as I please?
- Please.
- Alfred's right.
It's not safe for you to be
in Gotham alone.
I've been in Gotham alone
my whole life.
I can take care of myself.
Nothing's changed.
Yeah.
You've made that clear.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Nothing.
Those men were willing
to kill for this key.
We need to know why.
I'll be in the study.
There's more books
I haven't gone through.
There has to be a reference
to the key somewhere.
And have you stopped to consider
that maybe it's just an old key?
No.
I'll get you some breakfast, miss.
You know? Some of these plants
would do much better
in direct sunlight.
Could you turn off the alarm
so I can put them outside?
Well, maybe later.
I'd rather not you be walking around
the grounds on your own.
Can you smell this.
Beg your pardon?
Right here.
What is that?
Just a mix of clove, fenugreek,
and yarrow root oils.
It's lovely.
- It is, isn't it?
- Yeah.
Now, I need you to tell me something,
okay?
Anything.
How do you turn off the alarm?
This doesn't make any sense.
Do you know anyone
who might want you dead?
You can't be serious.
- Everyone has enemies.
- No, Detective. They don't.
Regardless.
You need to limit your exposure.
Lay low for a while until I can
find out who's behind this.
How do you propose I do that?
I'm picking up our wedding rings
this afternoon.
Lee and I are getting married
tomorrow.
You want me to cancel the wedding.
- I just wanna keep you safe.
- I'd bet you'd love that.
I run home to Lee.
Tell her we need to hide until
Detective Gordon can save the day?
This is not a time for ego.
Oh, you're talking to me about ego?
How do I even know
you're gonna be able to find him?
Or that you'll even try?
You need to trust me.
Whoever is behind this is gonna keep
coming until they get the job done.
If that's true...
...it doesn't matter where we go
or what we do.
As long as I got a target on my back,
Lee isn't safe.
- Hey.
- Yeah.
Keep an eye on Mario.
Don't let him leave.
- What are you doing?
- I'm keeping an eye on Mario.
Don't look at him.
- What the hell's going on?
- I don't know.
Something doesn't fit.
I need to talk to Carmine.
Maybe once he knows Mario's the
target something will jog his memory.
- Just, just keep it...
- I got it. I got it.
Hello, Comrade.
Comrade is not Russian word.
Oh, shut up. Of course it is.
- You shouldn't be here.
- Relax.
I know Penguin's out for a few hours.
I just wanna talk.
I don't know anything.
Listen, I grew up in a place
like this.
A large staff of people always coming
and going.
Listening.
You can't help but overhear things.
- Is handsome ring.
- It is.
And very expensive.
I bet it would look just fabulous
on you.
Mr. Penguin, he treat me nice.
I have warm feeling for him.
- But the other one...
- Nygma?
I don't know why Mr. Penguin
likes him so much.
He could do better.
Wait.
You mean likes, likes?
Wow.
Okay, we should definitely revisit
that another time.
But what about Nygma?
Did he say anything
about my missing friend?
I don't know, but I hear
Mr. Nygma talking about
special delivery but nothing come
to the house but bill.
"Stocks & Bondage?"
How many times
do I have to tell you?
I have never
even heard of this woman.
Well, then I suppose I should put
my attention elsewhere.
No! No!
- Leave her out of this!
- Afraid I can't do that.
She is an integral part
of your penance.
It was such a pleasant surprise
when I discovered that the two
of you were together.
You know,
after the initial gag reflex.
I bet this gal doesn't even exist.
I mean, come on.
Who would fall in love
with a freak show like you?
Oh, wait.
Let me guess.
I bet she's got a certificate, too,
huh?
What do you want?
Tell me what you want.
I want to break Butch's heart
before I end his life.
You know, kind of a
eye-for-an-eye thing.
But in this case...
...I'll take a hand.
Is that vinegar?
Vinegar and baking soda.
Takes tarnish off anything.
Selina, that key
is hundreds of years old!
I'm not an idiot, you know.
Maybe there's something on the key
that you can't see,
because a hundred years of crap
is covering it up?
Why did you tell Ivy
we weren't a couple?
- Why did you tell her we were?
- Is that a trick question?
Why can't we just be us?
Can you take that key out now?
It's making me nervous.
There's an engraving on it.
Like a bird or something.
Not just a bird.
An owl.
- And?
- Alfred!
If you're right, merely possessing
this key could be seen
as breaking your agreement
with the people
that the woman
in the owl mask represents.
Which is why we need to contact them.
They have to understand Ivy didn't
know what she was stealing.
Wait, where is she anyhow?
Oh, bloody hell. She's gone.
How did she disable the alarm?
Don't worry about that now,
all right?
What's the big deal?
She'll be back when she's hungry.
Wayne Manor.
You have the necklace.
We have your friend.
We'll make exchange, no?
Where and when?
We're supposed to go down
the manhole?
That's what they said.
All right, give me the key.
I'll sort it out.
No.
I need to speak with them personally.
Make sure they understand
this was a mistake.
Very well, Master Bruce.
There's no way of asking you
to stay here
that doesn't end with you
yelling at me, is there?
No.
Over there.
Ivy?
It's about time!
My name is Bruce Wayne.
I need to speak with Kathryn.
She needs to understand
I've honored our deal.
Hand over the necklace
and you get your friend back.
That's the deal.
You mean the key, don't you?
You're not getting it back until
I talk to the people you work for.
Maybe we just kill you and take it?
You think we're stupid
enough to bring it with us?
You really want it back?
I'd listen to him.
Put the tools down, lads, aye?
I need reassurances my friends
are no longer in any danger.
I need to speak to the woman
in the mask.
Any assurances
that woman gives you are lies.
How do you know?
Because the people
you are talking about have no honor.
And they will betray you
as they betrayed us.
Wait. You, you don't work for them?
No, we work to destroy them.
Who are they?
They call themselves
the Court of Owls.
- They're after Mario?
- Yes.
- Where is he?
- GCPD. He's safe for now.
But I can't help him
if you don't tell me what's going on.
You think I'm holding something back?
A military grade explosion.
The clean up.
A sword-wielding assassin
in broad daylight.
This doesn't feel like a mob grudge.
What else is there?
Could Mario be mixed up in something?
Is that what you came to ask me?
I'm working the evidence I have.
I understand why
you'd want to believe
the man who's marrying Lee
must be mixed up in something.
But my son is the most
decent person I've ever known.
He's not like us.
That just tells me
there's something you don't know.
Jim, Mario's gone.
You were supposed to keep him there.
I know, I tried, but he said
he didn't trust you or the GCPD.
to take care of this,
so he was going to.
Whatever the hell that means.
What is it?
Mario just walked out of the GCPD.
I think he's gonna try
to finish this himself.
How?
I have a pretty good idea.
- Can I help you?
- I hope so.
I had something that was supposed
to be delivered to me.
Could you check your records?
Sure. Let me check the safe.
What was the last name?
- Nygma.
- Oh!
That item was already delivered.
Great.
Well, I guess as long
as I'm already here,
I should pick up
something for the weekend.
Right?
Well, this looks fun.
Could I ask a favor of you...
- Todd.
Could you show me how this works?
We're not really supposed to...
I won't tell if you don't.
It's pretty basic, really.
You just put your arms through here,
and then your head through here.
And you bring it up...
And then... Oh! Hey!
Do you like role-play, Todd?
Good.
I will play the beautiful,
coquettish bank robber
who needs to get into that safe,
and you...
...get to play the lucky
young shopkeeper
who gives her the combination.
Okay?
My friend was taken by this man,
Nygma.
I need to know where she is.
If I find her, I could come back here
and personally thank you.
Give Mommy the combination.
Nine to twenty five, seventy two.
Good.
Nygma, you sick bastard.
Hey!
You can't just leave me here!
Hello?
Oh, goodie.
You're finally awake.
The show continues.
Ta-da!
I designed it myself.
You want to see how it works? Okay!
I love a captive audience.
So, we'll set the timer for,
say, 55 seconds.
Now, when the timer hits zero,
the spring-loaded blade is released.
Simple. Now.
For the fun part.
You can stop the blade
from being released
if you click this little button.
But if you do,
it will send a fatal jolt
of electricity to zap Butch.
It's a simple test, really.
Stop the blade from falling
and kill Butch, or...
The choice...
...my dear, is yours.
Will we hear the zap of heartbreak?
Or the sound of one hand clapping?
My name is Volk.
My brother, Jacob,
and that's Dmitry.
What's with the stupid mask?
I like you.
You remind me of my sister in Kiev.
Dmitry is an initiate.
The mask ensures his silence
until he proves himself
and becomes a full member.
Of what? Who are you?
We are called the Whisper Gang.
Gotham's most notorious smugglers.
We used to number in the hundreds
until the Court saw
our growing strength,
and they offered us a partnership,
only to betray us.
Many escaped back to Ukraine
but a few of us stayed back,
hoping to find a way
to enact revenge.
And we did.
The key.
Well, what does it open?
A safe.
It is in one of the Court's
buildings...
...here.
Inside, there is a, a device,
that we believe
can destroy them.
What, like, some kind of weapon?
Well, honestly, we don't know.
We captured a member,
but even he didn't know
what's inside the safe,
only that the Court fears it falling
into the hands of their enemies.
Wait, wouldn't they know
you stole it?
They're probably waiting for you
to show up there.
No. Because originally,
the safe had two keys.
The Court still has one of them,
and the second was thought lost.
Until I found it.
You mean we did.
The Court of Owls killed my parents.
I stood down because I thought
there was no way to defeat them.
What are you proposing?
If what you're saying is true,
and there is something
in that safe...
...then that's no longer the case.
Mario?
You really think this is a good idea?
Using yourself as bait?
If those guys are out there,
Lee isn't safe.
They're pros.
You're gonna get killed.
What do you care?
- Why would someone want to kill you?
- I have no idea.
Because it seems to me,
an operation like this
doesn't happen for no reason,
and putting yourself
in the crosshairs feels a lot like
someone protecting a secret.
I want to protect Lee.
That's it.
We're sitting ducks in here.
We need to get away from bystanders.
- They're here.
- What?
Get down!
No, no!
No! No, please!
You could've killed her.
Who sent you?
Why are you coming after me?
You know why.
Ed, come on.
Come on, let's talk about this, huh?
Come on, Ed.
You don't have to do this.
Come on, let's talk about this.
Come on! Listen!
I told you, I've never heard
of anyone named Isabelle!
Isabella!
Why is that so difficult?
Also, I'm not the one
you should be pleading with.
Your life is in her...
...hand.
What difference does it make?
You're gonna kill me
one way or the other, right?
Good point.
New deal.
If she loves you enough
to sacrifice her hand.
Twinsies.
In exchange for your life.
I swear on the memory
of my beloved Isabella,
I will set you both free.
Tabby.
Baby, come on.
We can get out of here, we can...
I like you, Butch. I really do.
But to be completely honest,
I'm not exactly in a "love"
place right now.
Sorry, big fella.
I wish I could say
that I was surprised,
but I knew that she was going
to say that.
It's why I made the offer.
Any final words?
I would keep it brief.
Tabby.
Baby.
The last few weeks
have been the best of my life.
And it's okay you don't love me.
'Cause I love you.
And for a guy like me?
That's, that's enough.
And you.
You're damn right I killed her.
I killed the woman you loved.
You know what she said to me?
Right before I put a bullet
in her brain?
You know what she told me?
She said she wished
she would have been with a real man.
Hey, Butch.
Yeah?
You're sweet.
No!
Untie me!
Please, untie me!
She's got to get to a hospital!
Quick!
You said that you put
a bullet in her head.
Isabella died in a car crash.
- The brake lines were cut.
- I don't care!
I told you I never heard of her!
You, you really didn't kill her?
No! Untie me!
She's got to get to a hospital,
come on!
I'd put that hand on some ice.
Neither of you recognize him?
No.
Has he said anything?
Not a peep.
Hey, I ran your guy's prints.
They're not in the system,
which, considering he's a pro,
wasn't that hard to believe.
Yeah, still, now that we have him,
we should work him,
find out who's behind this.
You better act quick. Call came in.
They're transferring him
to a federal facility upstate.
What? No, no, no, no.
We can't let this guy leave.
What can I do? My hands are tied.
The Feds want him, they get him.
The question is why?
Maybe somebody wants him
out of this precinct.
Away from us.
I don't know anyone
with that kind of pull.
Do you?
The other assassin.
You want to tell me
what happened in the store?
There's nothing to tell.
He came after me,
I did what I needed to do.
You called her?
She deserves to know what's going on.
Either you tell her or I will.
Come on.
I think I know who sent you.
But I need to know for sure.
And we both know
that you're not going to tell me.
So...
So, how does it feel?
I don't know,
maybe I could be captain.
Yell at people for not having proof,
or, at one of my detectives
for going after a pair of assassins
all by his lonesome.
- Not bad.
- Right?
Very interesting play, by the way.
It's not every day that you get
to save the man
who's marrying the woman you love.
Yeah, I'm really something.
It's not too late, Jim.
Lee deserves to know how you feel.
God knows, I know,
that life gives us enough regret.
There's no need adding to it.
- Oh, crap.
- I know it's hard.
It's just, it's something
you have to...
Falcone.
Falcone, up against the wall!
What are you doing?
Just having a chat.
Turns out our friend here
works for a former associate of mine.
So now that I know who's behind this,
I can take care of it, my way.
- It's over.
- You think you're gonna walk away?
You just assaulted a suspect
in police custody.
He won't be pressing charges.
I'm gonna find out
what happened today.
Who's pulling the strings,
and how Mario's involved.
Trust me.
If I were you, I'd let it go.
Gather the men.
Tell them we are joining forces
with the boy.
I will brief them tomorrow night
myself.
Volk!
Dmitry, eyes.
We know you've been
searching for the second key.
Have you found it?
I'll ask you again.
Have you found the second key?
Why don't you ask Dmitry, huh?
Think she'll be okay?
- Think they can re-attach the hand?
- Please, she's tough as nails.
She'll be fine.
You know this is war, right?
Nygma, Penguin,
anyone who stands with them...
- They're all dead.
- This woman Isabella,
Nygma said she was a librarian,
right?
Well, who kills a librarian?
I mean, what's the motive?
I don't know.
Maybe someone had an overdue book,
and things got out of hand.
Excuse me, but you just can't walk...
Come on! Come on!
We got a hand here, people. Hand!
You cut someone's brake lines.
You know where they're going
and when.
You'd know...
You know them.
I know who did it.
I know who killed the librarian.
Who?
The same person who's in love
with Nygma
and doesn't want to share him.
Okay. One woman in love
with that psychotic bean pole
defies explanation, but two?
Who said anything about a woman?
I am tired of sitting
at the kids' table.
If I'm right, we can have
way more than vengeance.
We can have it all.
We don't need to go to war.
All we need to do is start one.
There must have been some mistake.
We don't make mistakes.
I've always done whatever
the Court has asked of me.
Even against my own interest.
I got you Indian Hill
when Maroni refused to sell.
No one is questioning your loyalty.
If this isn't about me,
then why are you trying to kill
my son?
There are things you're not privy to.
That's not an answer.
It will have to do.
We both know the level
of destruction I can cause.
You think we're scared of you?
The car bomb was designed
to look like a mob hit.
You didn't want me
to find out it was you.
I have.
I don't care about your reasons.
If my son is harmed in any way,
I will come after you
with everything I have.
You won't win.
If my son is dead,
winning won't be the point.
Gotham will burn.
This city is on the brink of chaos.
Only we can save it.
We will expect your assistance
when called on.
Until then, your son is safe.
At least from us.
What aren't you telling me?
A great many things.
Enjoy your dinner.
Hey.
Is everything okay?
I was on my way
to the rehearsal dinner.
Then I heard myself telling
the cab driver your address.
Mario told me everything.
About today.
How you risked your own
life to make sure...
I didn't do it for him.
I know.
- He's a good man.
- Uh-huh.
Tell me.
What?
What you have to tell me.
I missed my chance
to give you the life you deserve.
To make you happy.
But I do want that for you.
More than anything.
Why does it feel like
we keep saying good-bye?
Maybe it's all we have left.
Or we just haven't done it
properly yet.
Good-bye, James Gordon.
Yo, Peeping Tom
You lost?
Lucky for you, we sell directions.
The price, everything you've got.
She loves him. She loves him.
- She loves him...
- You deaf?
- She loves him, she loves him!
- I said...
Hey, man...
She loves me!
And I won't let her go.