Previously on Gotham...
THEO:
Monsters are coming, Mr. Mayor,
who will cleanse this city.
If you sell me
your company,
I will give you
the name of the man
who killed your parents.
Who the hell
are you?
I'm Bruce's friend.
And you're a piece
of gutter trash.
You think that
little minx is
gonna tell you
something, do you?
Getting information
out of a girl
like that requires
a level of deception
that you do not yet possess.
GORDON:
You're under arrest.
May I ask what
the charge is?
The kidnapping and torture
of Aubrey James.
These were Ms. Kringle's.
A man with nothing
to love is free.
Hey, Parks,
you did good today.
THOMPKINS: Eduardo Flamingo
killed Officer Parks
before they could get him
into lockup.
Bruce Wayne will die,
and his company
will be ours.
Everything is ready.
The brothers' arrival
is imminent.
CREEL: Gotham will be redeemed
in blood.
(whimpering)
(man grunts)
(thunder rumbling)
Please don't
hurt me!
Shut up.
(grunts)
(whimpering)
♪ ♪
Ah.
(thunder rumbling)
(sighs)
Forget your umbrella?
Thought visiting hours
were over.
What are rules
to the man
who arrested
the mayor of Gotham?
(sighs)
Any chance
you're gonna tell me
what this little visit
is about?
Tomorrow's hearing,
perhaps?
You're here to gloat.
Does the name Katherine Parks
mean anything to you?
No, can't say it does.
I'm gonna be there tomorrow.
I'm gonna watch them
put you away.
(chuckles softly)
Always a pleasure, Detective.
(door buzzes, opens)
Hey.
(thunder rumbling)
You're soaking wet.
Do you want to talk about it?
Katherine Parks was 23.
On the force a year.
And today we put her
in the ground
because when I had the chance,
I didn't do
the only sensible thing.
Jim...
An assassin kills four cops...
dares me to pull the trigger,
and I don't.
Explain that to me.
That man was your prisoner;
you didn't have a choice.
I had a choice.
Yes, to uphold the law
or to become a murderer.
You made the right one.
You think Katherine Parks
feels the same way?
What about
her family?
(sighs)
I went to see Galavan today.
And?
You're asking
did I get the guards to
turn the cameras off? No.
But they would have.
Galavan as good as killed Parks,
Essen and a dozen other cops,
and yet he sits there,
smiling, breathing.
And tomorrow, Aubrey James is
going in front of the grand jury
and telling them
that he was kidnapped
and tortured by Galavan.
He's gonna be put away
for a long time.
Maybe.
Just the way he acted.
It wasn't a man
looking at a decade in prison.
I have a bad feeling.
Jim, it's over.
You did good.
Now, come to bed.
Doctor's orders.
♪ ♪
(coughs, grunts)
MAN:
Where am I?
Who are you?
The day of reckoning is at hand.
And the blood
of the nine
shall wash away the sin.
(gasping)
(panting):
Please!
And Gotham will be cleansed.
(choking, gurgling)
(bell tolling)
This isn't gonna work.
This girl is a world-class liar
from a family
of world-class liars.
She'll see through you.
Or her uncle will.
Well, that's very possible.
And?
Bruce,
they're playing nice with you
because they think
you trust them.
Once they see you don't,
it'll get ugly fast.
Your logic is flawless, Selina.
It's not too late...
If there's even a chance
Galavan knows
who killed my parents,
I have to take it.
I told Alfred I have
fencing practice after school
to buy us some time
if we need it.
Hey.
The best liars
always tell the truth.
Something to remember.
Thank you.
That's her car. You'd b...
(car door closes)
Alvarez, call the morgue.
See if any bodies turned up
matching Gertrude Cobblepot.
She didn't just vanish;
Galavan killed her.
Did that yesterday.
And you're gonna
do it again today.
I got my own cases, Gordon.
Turn up anything on that symbol
we found in the penthouse?
No. I'm waiting for Father Mike
up at St. Bart's.
Sent him a picture
of the cassock, too.
He's up on all that
religious mumbo-jumbo.
What exactly
are we after here?
Something tying Galavan
to the murders of Essen,
Parks, any of the
people he killed.
Not to state the obvious, Jim,
but the guy's going to jail.
I went to see him last night.
Yeah?
Get the guards
to turn off the camera?
The look on his
face, Harvey...
I don't know, I
can't describe it.
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
God...
Guy gets stabbed;
I thought we'd have
at least a week of peace.
Hey, Cap!
How you doing?
Did you get my flowers?
(panting)
Captain, how
you feeling?
Eh, five-by-five.
Damn doc would've had me in bed
a week if I'd have let him.
Got something for you.
Munis found a dead body
down by the port,
throat cut from ear to ear.
The vic's a career dirtbag,
but the work's the same.
Uh, sir, if it's all the same,
I'd like to stay on Galavan.
It isn't.
Galavan's cooked,
so you're back
in the rotation. What?
I just feel like
we're missing something, sir.
There's some piece of
the puzzle that's gonna
come back and bite us.
Just give me a few more days.
Answer's no.
Be pissed, but it's
for your own good.
Oh, and, uh...
I'm sorry about Parks.
She deserved better.
BULLOCK:
Yo, Jim!
Message from Father Mike.
That symbol
is from something
called the Order of St. Dumas.
They used to have
an abbey downtown.
Barnes just told me
to lay off of Galavan.
Oh. Well, then
you probably don't care
that the mayor's office tried
to buy the abbey last week.
Galavan tried to buy it?
Yeah.
Some urban development nonsense.
New owners said no.
It's a Chinese
slap-slap joint now.
Hell with it.
You got the address?
Yep. Let's go get lucky.
(knocking)
♪ ♪
Your uncle made me an offer:
the name of my parents' killer
in exchange for selling him
my shares in Wayne Enterprises.
I said no.
But circumstances
have changed.
You're going to sell?
No.
Then...
Your uncle
was arrested,
and his assets are frozen.
Tell him I'll pay for
his defense; in exchange,
he gives me the name.
You're taking
advantage of him.
I have something
he needs, he has something
I need, that's all.
Do you believe what people
are saying about him?
I don't care what people say.
My father was investigating
Wayne Enterprises,
then he and my mother
were killed.
Last year, I investigated
Wayne Enterprises,
and someone tried
to kill Alfred.
Either I find out
who killed my parents
and stop whatever's happening
in my company, or I'm dead.
I need that name.
The grand jury
hearing is today.
He's going to
be cleared.
What if he's not?
What then?
Silver, get him
to tell you the name,
and I will make
sure he has
the best defense money
can buy, I promise.
You think he's guilty.
Why would you believe
anything he says?
Because it would come from you.
If you bring me the name,
I'll know it's real.
(whispering)
Do you mean that?
I'll call you
after I talk to him.
(bell tolling in distance)
Still got to get the name.
I will. I'm late for school.
(crow cawing in distance)
Not yet.
You sure about this?
Doesn't look much like
a massage parlor.
Maybe there's
another entrance.
(women screaming)
GORDON:
Get these girls out of here.
Come on, come on. Come on.
GCPD!
(weak groaning)
Sir?
(sighs)
(grunting)
(bones crack)
(grunts)
(panting)
Stop!
Drop the knife.
The day of reckoning
is at hand,
and the blood of nine
shall wash away the sin.
Uh-huh.
Who are you?
What's your connection
to Galavan?
And Gotham shall be cleansed.
Hey.
(truck horn blaring)
Hey!
GORDON:
The girls at the parlor
say they saw
at least six monks.
Uh-huh.
They have to be a part
of this same order of St. Dumas.
Bullock's contact says
they're penitents.
Yeah, I forgot my
dictionary in my purse.
They believed in
purification through pain.
Blood.
They were big
in the old days in Gotham.
Then about a hundred years ago,
vanished.
It was their crest we found
in Galavan's penthouse.
And now they're back
and they're pissed off
that their home is
a high-end rub-and-tug joint.
Fine.
Gather what you have
and give it to Alvarez.
Captain, these monks
could be the key
to whatever Galavan is planning.
As I recall, Detective,
I already gave you a case.
And I expressly
told you
to move away from Galavan.
The dead guy at the ports--
he attacked a woman
across town yesterday.
In her statement, she said
her attacker was pulled off
by a man dressed like a monk.
Does the universe normally
like you this much, Detective?
First time.
All right, say they're
the same monks.
Why would they kill
a bunch of bankers and some...
nobody street thug?
The monk said,
"The blood of the nine
shall wash away the sin."
It's obviously
some sort of ritual.
And if Galavan
is connected,
what does he stand to gain?
I don't know.
We have to find a monk
and get him to talk.
Well, considering
what this last one did,
that might not be so easy.
Captain, it's no coincidence
that this is happening
just as Galavan's
about to stand trial.
Whatever it is,
it's going down today.
"The blood of the nine."
Five are
already dead.
Okay.
But I still want you
at the grand jury to
hear James' testimony.
And, Gordon,
whatever this is,
stop it.
(school bell rings,
phone line beeps)
SILVER (recorded):
Bruce, it's Silver.
I just saw my uncle.
He agreed to your deal.
Everything you asked.
He... he told me
the name, Bruce.
Meet me across the way
after school.
(line beeps)
(tires screech)
(muffled sobbing)
MAN:
Shh.
Don't scream. Don't run.
Just get in.
Or we kill the girl.
(muffled shout)
MAN:
Go.
The scar tissue's old.
See how the wounds wrap
over his shoulder?
It was definitely
self-inflicted.
I stabbed him,
he didn't flinch.
And there are thick scars
on the palms.
He cut himself there repeatedly.
Father Mike said
the leaders cut themselves
and then mark the followers
with the blood, like a blessing.
Charming.
Dug up two more bodies
from the past three days.
Career hoods.
Killed somewhere, then dumped--
both their throats cut.
GORDON:
Seven down,
two to go.
It's weird.
How has nobody seen
these monks till now?
A, they're killing people
and carrying them across town,
and B, they're monks.
The woman who was attacked
yesterday,
she said the monk vanished
with the
attacker, but...
that alley was a dead end.
The sewers.
Oh, no.
(rats squeaking)
So, the monk
drags the woman's attacker
into the alley
above us.
Next thing,
he's food for seagulls.
Ports are this way.
Again?
Did you try
jiggling the handle?
Well, what did
you put down it?
Dr. Thompkins,
can I help you?
Hi, Ed. This is the
autopsy on the dead monk.
Jim wants you
to run toxicology.
Fascinating.
The need to inflict that
kind of pain on oneself.
Is there anything else?
No.
Yes.
Was that Kristen
you were just talking to?
What?
Oh, sorry. It sounded
like you were talking
to somebody in your apartment,
and who besides...
I was talking to my plumber.
Oh.
Well, have you heard
from Kristen?
I know she said she was sick.
I was thinking of stopping by...
As it happens,
she's not sick.
She lied.
To all of us.
I just found out,
Miss Kringle left town
with Officer Dougherty.
She left Gotham
with Dougherty?
Mm-hmm.
But he was abusive.
(chuckles softly)
Love.
Wow.
I-I'm... I'm stunned.
(phone vibrating,
ringtone playing)
♪ Who's sorry now? ♪
Do you need to get that?
No. I don't think so.
♪ Whose heart... ♪
(phone continues vibrating)
(sobbing)
Oh, Ed...
you must be devastated.
Right now, I'm just trying
to focus on the job.
Well, let me know
if you ever want to talk.
Thank you. That means a lot.
(phone vibrating,
ringtone playing)
♪ Who's sorry now? ♪
Yes?
OSWALD:
Where is the spicy mustard?
You better not have finished...
Ah. Never mind.
(line clicks)
(wood creaking)
(quiet sobbing)
Silver, are you okay?
What happened?
(door creaking)
(man sighs loudly)
You have one chance.
You let us go...
(sobbing)
You talk...
when I tell you to.
Understand?
Now...
so you know,
we are outside of the city,
and there is absolutely no one
to hear you scream,
except me.
You work for the people
inside Wayne Enterprises.
Whoever's paying you...
(grunts)
Again...
you talk when
I tell you to.
Now, my employers have heard
that you are thinking of
selling your company shares
to the uncle of this one?
That's not good.
But not why we're here.
The issue is:
someone's been nosing
into the deaths...
of Thomas...
and poor Martha Wayne.
And I wonder who.
Mmm.
Kidding.
We know it was blondie's uncle.
So...
I've been tasked to find out
what dear old
uncle told little Bruce Wayne.
Nothing.
Galavan didn't
tell me anything.
You think
that I won't hurt you
because you're a kid?
Or because you're you?
How'd that work out for
your mummy and daddy?
There are billions
at stake here.
And that's with a B.
Do what you want to me.
I don't know anything.
Okay,
so we start with Goldilocks.
You touch her, and I swear...
Yeah?
I've been threatened by
the best, kid, and you...
not exactly terrifying.
Now, let me tell you
how this is going to go.
(blade clinks)
In a minute,
I'm gonna take one of you
into the back
and start cutting off
your fingers.
(sobs softly)
And you're gonna talk.
I've been doing this
a very, very long time,
and everyone talks.
(sobs)
So... unless you're
really into wearing mittens,
this is your last chance.
What does Theo Galavan know?
Okey-dokey.
Let's go.
No, no, no, no, no!
BRUCE: No, wait, stop!
Stop, stop, stop!
No!
Silver, you have
to tell him.
I'll hold my side of the
deal, I promise. Please.
Please. I promise.
But my uncle
didn't tell me anything.
But you left me a message.
I was supposed to keep you busy
till this evening.
He's sure
he's going to be freed.
Then he'll convince you
to sell your company.
(gasps)
I'm sorry, Bruce.
I don't know anything.
Really?
I don't!
That's a pity.
No.
No!
Kid.
No! Please.
You really need
better taste in women.
No!
(screaming)
(screaming) Stop! Bruce!
No!
(water dripping)
BULLOCK: Just when you think
Gotham's shown her last jewel,
she reveals herself
like a flower.
You're mixing
metaphors.
I'm in a freakin' sewer.
(indistinct, distant shouting)
You hear something?
A voice.
(man screams in distance)
I know this bum.
Muscle for hire.
Check out the finger painting
on the forehead.
Victim at the port
had the same thing.
Like a blessing.
Whoever did this
can't be too far away.
We should...
Harvey!
(grunting)
Oh, no, no, no, no, no...
Please, please, don't. Hold.
He needs an ambulance.
Boo-hoo. We got to wake
him up, make him talk.
Religious fanatic who doesn't
feel pain? What's our angle?
These nut-jobs have killed eight
people. Whatever their plan is,
whatever Galavan's up to,
it is happening now.
We make him talk.
What are we gonna do,
torture him?
Threaten to let him die?
He wouldn't care.
There's no signal
down here.
I'll call in, but
I got to go up.
Thank you.
God!
(weakly):
The day...
...of reckoning.
The day... of
reckoning, brother.
Bruce?
(door opens)
(man whoops)
Well, if nothing else,
today has given me a newfound
respect for boy billionaires.
Kid's tougher
than he looks.
Didn't know
a damn thing.
Did you kill him?
No, not yet.
But the rest is
kind of up to you.
I told you...
my uncle didn't
tell me anything.
Are you gonna stick
to that story?
It's the truth.
Bruce, I'm sorry!
I don't know anything!
You know what?
I don't like you.
The Wayne kid--
he's got some sap in him.
But you...
You know when you meet someone,
and you just don't click?
That's the way
I feel about you.
That's why this is
gonna be so much easier.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna make sure
that you are telling the truth.
Touch me, and my uncle
will have you gutted.
Every person you love
will die screaming.
I've had enough of this.
Let me go. Now!
Well, hello!
Nice to meet ya!
I knew there was
someone hiding in there.
Are you deaf as well as ugly?
I said... let me go!
I heard you, princess.
What are you doing?
(knife slices)
Stop!
Malone! It's Malone!
What's that?
Malone. That's the name.
The man who killed
Bruce Wayne's parents.
So your uncle did tell you.
Not today. Before.
When he first found out.
Malone's a very common name.
His first name begins with "M."
That's all I know.
Mm...
Stop!
You know what?
I believe you.
(shouting):
Are we good?
Yes.
We're good.
Hey.
Remember me?
The gutter trash?
Bruce... what's happening?
What does it look like, dummy?
We tricked you.
Though, if it
was up to me,
you would've lost
a few fingers.
Going soft, Tom?
Cat.
BRUCE:
Thank you.
Thank you, Mr. Wayne.
Pleasure doing business.
Sorry about the slaps.
Now are you two
gonna be okay
with this one,
or would you like me to, uh...?
(knife scrapes)
SELINA: Nah.
We're cool.
Mr. Wayne. Boys.
(whistles)
You're probably
very confused right now.
Probably have
a million questions
going through
your head.
Bruce, please...
Be quiet!
I trusted you, Silver.
Even after
your uncle was arrested,
I still believed
you were my friend.
It was finally Selina
who convinced me otherwise.
I never bought your stupid act.
BRUCE: She broke
into your apartment,
found the file
you had on me.
It was clear that
you'd been sent
to push me to
sell my company,
that your entire family
was corrupt, but I still
had to find out what your uncle
knew about my parents' murder.
Now I do.
Thank you.
Bruce! Wait.
That name wasn't real.
It was just something
I made up to stop him.
SELINA:
That's funny.
You only made it up
when you were
under the knife,
not when Bruce was
getting tortured.
(chuckles)
You little bitch, I'll...
Please.
Try it.
You're right
about my uncle.
He's everything everyone says.
Worse.
When he finds out
what I told you,
he'll kill me.
You pretended to be my friend.
Good-bye, Silver.
Bruce.
The things you told me today.
I believed you.
Yes. That was the point.
SILVER:
Bruce, you can't
do this.
It isn't you.
That's what you think.
But you're wrong.
Bruce...
(door opens)
Bruce!
(water dripping)
The ambulance is...
Drink...
brother.
(monk coughs)
Can't... see.
You're hurt.
Lie still.
The police?
Dead. We got here
just in time.
The blood of the nine...
BOTH:
Shall wash away the sin.
MONK:
I fulfilled
my task, brother.
All that remains
is the son.
Yes. The son.
MONK:
Give me your blessing,
brother.
Please.
(sighs)
The Son of Gotham
shall die,
and the city
shall be cleansed.
WOMAN:
Detective, where is the...?
What?
(blindfold rips)
(panting rapidly)
Who are you?!
GCPD. You're under arrest.
Take him to the hospital, see if
you can get anything from him.
I got to see Barnes.
ALFRED:
Bruce?
Bruce, you in here?
Master Bruce?
Master B, you here?
You're trespassing.
I'm looking
for Bruce Wayne.
Now, he's not answering
his phone.
He's not home,
he's not at school.
My guess, he's with that snotty
little niece of yours.
Sorry.
Now, I suggest
you leave
while you still can.
I see you're a bit
of a player, are you?
As it were then,
Tabby.
Big bad Galavan barks the
orders, and you scamper around,
bringing home dead rabbits,
so you might get
a little pat on the head?
I wonder what he'd do
if I just disappeared you.
Honestly,
I don't think he'd care.
If I learn anything has happened
to that little boy,
we'll find out, won't we?
(both grunting)
(shouts)
Stop it!
(panting)
For the record,
I was telling the truth.
I have no idea
where Bruce Wayne is.
But I'll tell him
you were asking.
(elevator bell dings)
(thumping)
(groaning softly)
(grunts)
(engine revving)
(gavel banging)
WOMAN:
Mr. Dent,
your witness.
So, Mayor James...
Excuse me,
Mr. Dent.
I think you mean
former mayor.
I'm just a citizen of Gotham...
here to tell the truth.
Mr. James...
...if you could begin
by telling us
where you spent the month
of October this year.
(quietly):
Where the hell have you been?
Bullock and I captured
one of the monks.
I was right.
They're completing
some sort of ritual
to cleanse the city of sin.
They have one
victim left.
They're calling him
the Son of Gotham.
Did they say anything
about Galavan?
JAMES: I was not
kidnapped by Theo Galavan.
They didn't, did they?
(gallery gasping, murmuring)
Quiet!
Mr. James,
please repeat what you said.
Theo Galavan did not kidnap me.
(gallery murmuring)
Your Honor, the witness
has suffered...
Please explain yourself, sir.
Why did you lie?
Who held you captive?
Oswald Cobblepot, the Penguin.
He hates Theo Galavan.
He tried to kill
him multiple times.
He told me what to say.
He threatened me with
terrible things.
He's lying!
BARNES: Gordon! Gordon!
JUDGE:
Detective Gordon, silence!
Gordon!
MAN:
Your Honor,
I move my client
be released at once.
Your Honor, the State
requests a recess to further...
Quiet. Mr. James,
you do realize you are
under oath?
Oswald Cobblepot...
tortured me,
put my head in a box.
He made me lie.
I'm so very, very sorry.
JUDGE:
In light of
Mr. James' testimony
and the complete
absence of any other
evidence provided
by the State,
I hereby order
Theo Galavan released
and the case
against him dismissed.
Your Honor!
No, Jim.
There's nothing
we can do.
Your Honor,
may I say a few words?
I think that's only fair.
I'd just like to state that...
I harbor no ill will toward
Detective Gordon
and the GCPD.
They did their jobs.
They're still my heroes.
What do you say,
Detective Gordon?
Can we move forward
together to fix
this broken,
beautiful city?
(clamoring)
You son of a bitch!
You're a son of a bitch!
I'm gonna get you!
JUDGE:
Get him out of here!
Ah, come on,
get your hands off of me!
Relax. We're not
arresting you.
(Taser crackles, Gordon groans)
(door creaks)
Alfred?
He's probably out
looking for me.
Thank you, Selina.
I couldn't have done
this without you.
I was just glad to see
the two-faced bitch get served.
What are you gonna do now?
You gonna tell the cops or look
for this Malone guy yourself?
Honestly, I haven't thought
that far ahead.
So, when you whispered to her
b-before
she went to her uncle,
what did you say?
You want to know what I said.
Hey, if you don't want
to tell me, then I can leave.
I told her
I've never met
anyone like her.
I told her
I trusted her with my life.
And that...
I felt tied to her
in a way that I...
couldn't explain,
but wouldn't change.
Ever.
The best liars
always tell the truth.
That was true?
Yes.
Just not about her.
(chuckles softly)
Um...
I'm...
I'm gonna steal
one of your cars to...
take to the city. Cool?
Sure.
It's good you're changing.
Just...
don't change too much.
(window opens, closes)
Why did you keep her glasses
to begin with?
I told y...
I loved Miss Kringle.
Just get rid of them.
Dr. Thompkins is suspicious.
(phone beeps)
Amateurs.
(pounding on door)
Gabe, when I gave you
this address,
I was not inviting pop-ins.
Galavan's been let go.
(glasses crackling)
Where is he?
(ship horn blows in distance)
(groans)
THEO:
My, my.
What a difference
a day brings.
Here, you're the
prisoner and I'm free.
Fortune's wheel.
Turn, turn.
These cops?
Good men who can tell which
way the wind's blowing.
Now, we have
a very small window.
I have places to be,
you have to die, but I know
you must have
questions, so...
The monks.
They... work for you?
For centuries,
the Order of St. Dumas
has protected my family.
They have been a light
in a dark world.
Shall I tell you a secret?
Theo Galavan
is a mask.
My name is Dumas,
and my family built this city
out of nothing.
But we were
betrayed,
driven out, erased.
So that's all
this is about?
Revenge?
No.
This is about atonement.
The ground that
Gotham is built on
is poisoned by the wrongs
done to my forefathers.
I will change that.
By killing
nine random people?
You're insane.
(laughs)
I can see why you'd think so.
Ritual blood
sacrifices,
bunch of guys in robes
(laughs):
chanting prophesies.
It's a bit too...
But belief itself--
that's what matters, Detective.
Belief gives strength,
purpose.
And not all the victims
are random.
The Son of Gotham.
Good-bye, James.
I couldn't have
done it without you.
Ah, what the hell.
I have a few minutes.
Cut him loose.
(chuckles)
All right, Jim, give
it your best shot.
Save Gotham.
(grunts)
(groans)
(shouts)
(panting)
(sniffles, sighs)
Kill him.
Don't make it quick.
(footsteps approaching)
Alfred? Is that you?
(door opens)
You won't believe
what I learned...
Sorry.
Not Alfred.
(grunting)
(gunshots)
(Gordon groaning)
(grunts)
Hello, Jim.
Lucky for you, Gabe had people
following Galavan.
Now...
where is he?
Where's Galavan?!
Tell me!
Where is Galavan?!
(grunting)
(yells)
You've shown mettle
and ingenuity,
my boy.
But that's all done with.
What do you want?
Why, your life, of course.