Told you. Easy as pie.
Sorry, Frankie.
You're under arrest for the murder
of Leon Winkler.
- You think these guys are gonna let you?
- Shut up, Flass.
Penguin, you're a smart monkey.
And I'm the zookeeper.
FALCONE:
I didn't think it was going to be you.
You can come out now.
Right as usual, my friend.
We gotta g0!
FISH: I swear, Butch,
I'm gonna come back and kill Penguin.
You sure now? Fish Mooney is done?
She tried to bring down Falcone.
She failed.
Last I saw her,
Victor Zsasz had her cornered.
We can assume she's either dead
or extremely unwell.
Well, then: salud.
Mm. You know, this creates
some intriguing opportunities.
Falcone will struggle to hold on
to her territory. If we move quickly...
My thinking exactly.
In fact, I took the liberty of claiming
her nightclub. In your name, of course.
You did, huh?
- Good thinking.
- Heh.
A bird in the hand is
nine-tenths of the law.
Yeah. Ha, ha.
Phone for you, boss.
- Speak.
FISH [OVER PHONE]: Hello, Sal.
MARON I:
Hey.
You sound surprised. Let me guess,
your friend Penguin told you I was dead.
- As good as.
- Mm.
I'm just on a vacation for a while.
- Huh.
- I'm not going to lie.
I thought I was gonna end up on top.
Instead, I got played.
Turns out Penguin has been
Falcone's man the whole time.
They played us both for suckers.
- Is that right?
- Ah. Indeed.
He told me himself
right before I was about to gut him.
You understand why I might be skeptical,
considering it's you telling me this.
Oh, wake up, dummy.
You mean to tell me this whole time,
you haven't suspected anything?
That he hasn't made one slip
that he's had to explain away?
Or maybe you wanted to believe his lies.
But it still gnaws at you, doesn't it?
The doubt.
It's right there. A smudge.
Don't let it happen again.
- Maybe a couple of times.
- Time to get your house in order, Salvatore.
And remember who put you wise.
[PHONE CLICKS]
- Not bad news, I hope.
- No.
I gotta go upstate. See
a guy about a thing.
Come with me.
We can talk about opportunities.
Sure. Heh.
- Just, uh, let me run home and...
- Ah-ah. We gotta go now. Right now.
Super. Ha, ha.
I love a road trip. Yay. Heh.
(Ya)'-
Harvey.
- Captain.
- What have we got?
Last night, Mr. Lucky there
got tied to that chair.
A noose over his neck.
He was heaved over the side.
Some suits this morning found him.
- How'd he get back up to the roof?
- See that pulley?
My guess, it was the killer.
Guy went to a lot of trouble to get him
back up. Why not leave him hanging?
- Morning, captain.
- Good morning, Ed.
The more you cut me,
the bigger I grow. What am I?
We're on a rooftop. Don't tempt me.
- A hole. I'm a hole.
- Okay. Relevance?
There's a hole, a surgical incision,
in our victim's abdomen.
Certainly postmortem.
Killer was looking for something.
- I'll examine the body at the lab.
- You mean the medical examiner.
- Well, but...
- You handle forensics, Ed.
The bodies belong to Dr. Guerra.
And he's made formal complaints.
I can't cover for you anymore.
I read you, ma'am. Loud and clear.
- So where's Gordon?
- Personal stuff. He'll be in soon.
ESSEN: Don't stand so near the edge.
- You worried about me, captain?
- I don't start drinking until noon.
- I gotta spell it out?
Detective Flass had a lot of friends.
And your partner arrested him for murder.
Accidents happen.
- You put the cuffs on him.
- So we should all be careful.
To hell with them.
Barbara?
- Hi.
- Let go of me.
- How long you been here?
- Just last night.
And a couple times before.
I knew your girlfriend was gone.
You got sent to guard that loony bin,
so better here than sleeping on the street.
- Have you seen Barbara?
- No.
Oh. So things are over
between you two, huh?
Sure you should be here?
Maybe you're the one breaking in.
- I came to drop off keys. Get your stuff.
- Where are you taking me?
Well, you're not staying here.
I'll find you someplace safe.
Mm. Safe.
Safe like Wayne Manor?
- That was your last great idea.
- So someplace else.
You're still my only witness
to the Wayne murders.
Hmm.
- Talked to Bruce since you got back?
- No. Why?
Because I told him already.
I didn't see anything. I lied.
Sucks about your girlfriend.
She's got some really nice stuff.
Hey, wait.
Stop.
Detective James Gordon to see you,
Master Bruce.
- Detective.
- Bruce.
How are you?
I'm fine, thank you.
I would've come by earlier,
but things were a little crazy.
You were gone for a while.
- Switzerland.
- Probably wise.
I saw Selina Kyle.
She told me she lied. She saw nothing.
Yes. That's what she told me.
She made up the story to get out ofjuvie.
She could be saying this
because she's scared.
It would be understandable
after what happened.
No.
She doesn't scare easily.
I believe her. She didn't see the killer.
Look, this is unfortunate.
It doesn't mean we're back to square one.
Someone sent assassins after her.
Only a guilty person would do that.
Yes.
A lot of bloody assassins to the manor.
Thank you very much.
Anyway, you need no longer
concern yourself with the case.
- Bruce, this isn't the time to give up.
- I'm not giving up.
I don't understand.
You promised you'd find
who killed my parents.
You've managed to find one witness
who turned out to be a liar.
- An investigation like this takes time.
- I understand.
But I don't want you to feel bound
by an oath you can't fulfill.
I'm releasing you from your promise.
I'll pursue the matter on my own.
- Bruce...
- L really wouldn't bother, actually, mate.
Once Master Bruce makes up his mind,
there's no arguing with him.
He can't pursue this case on his own.
It's too dangerous.
Then I'll have to look after him.
Can I show you the door?
MARONI:
Hey, sleepyhead. We're here.
You smell that air?
That's country air.
Let's get some chow.
Chow.
Excellent.
- So where's the guy?
- Which guy?
- The guy with the thing?
- Oh. He'll be around.
- You don't like the coffee?
- I like the coffee.
How about the oatmeal?
Also delicious.
It's good to get out of the city, huh?
Away from the fumes, the noise.
I can finally hear myself think.
It's all so simple, and clean,
and honest out here.
Fresh air, oatmeal, good friends.
How true.
In Gotham, you never have
any time to connect, to reflect.
- You feel that?
- Absolutely.
MARONI:
Mm.
This guy with the thing...
- Heh. What is the thing?
- Stop worrying about that guy.
You know what I was thinking about?
This is crazy.
Indian Hill.
You know, that dump in Arkham that
I traded to Falcone for your neck.
How could I forget? I'm eternally grateful.
You suggested it. Whispered it in my ear.
- It's worthless land.
- But was it so worthless?
I mean, Falcone snapped it up pretty quick.
It was a token.
He simply needed to save face.
After Nikolai died...
Ah, see, you wouldn't believe it. That's
the other thing I was thinking about.
The fight with Nikolai when Frankie was
killed. What was he, stabbed, like, 1O times?
- I don't recall the exact number.
- Only it was a gunfight.
How'd Frankie get killed with a knife?
Always kind of bugged me.
Honestly, I'm not much use
when things get physical.
- I'm sorry I couldn't save him.
- I was just reminiscing.
Don't beat yourself up about it.
We all got our talents, right?
Yes, we do.
Me?
I'm deceptively quick for a big guy.
Yes, you are.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm gonna go get some air.
Wait for the guy with the thing, hmm?
The guy. Right.
BULLOCK: How about getting
it right the first time...
so we don't have to keep doing this?
- Detective Bullock?
- That's my name. Don't wear it out.
I'm Scottie Mullens.
You called me about Adam Jodowsky?
Oh, Ms. Mullens, yes.
Thank you for stopping by. Miss? Mrs.?
- Miss.
- Good. Good. Please.
So...
how did you know Mr. Jodowsky?
I was his sponsor, sort of.
We're in a support group together.
- He's dead, isn't he?
- Why would you say that?
This is a Homicide Division.
You're a homicide detective.
We found his body this morning.
Your number was in his pocket.
I'd just given it to him.
I'd recently started being his sponsor.
So, uh, what kind of group is this?
Booze? Pills?
- It's for people suffering from phobias.
- You're joking.
Fear can be debilitating.
It helps to talk to someone about it.
Don't be an ass.
- Excuse me?
- You're about to make fun.
Don't be an ass.
You're right. I'm sorry, I was.
No fun-making. Please.
Um...
What was Mr. Jodowsky's phobia?
Heights.
Hmm. So if he was found dangling
from the top of a tall building...
Oh, my God. Is that how he...?
I'm gonna need names of all the people
in the support group.
It's anonymous.
Adam was the only one I knew personally.
You think someone from the group
did this?
Could be. Killer certainly seemed
to know of his phobia.
Are you Irish?
You seem like you could be Irish.
- What's it to you?
- I'm just curious.
- When's the next meeting?
- Tonight, 6:00.
And these things, they usually run,
what, an hour?
Mm-hm.
So you could maybe
go to dinner afterwards.
Hypothetically.
- Hypothetically.
- Okay. Well, I'll keep working the case.
And I'm gonna call you
if I feel the need to go to this meeting.
We're gonna find who did this.
I promise, Ms. Mullens.
Okay.
So I went through the materials
from the scene.
Ropes and pulleys
can be bought anywhere.
For what it's worth, I, uh,
traced the chair the victim was tied to...
Yeah. I'm listening.
Banker's chair. Wooden.
Made by some company in the Narrows.
Closed for years.
- Great, let's go.
- You sure? That's a pretty thin lead, Harv.
Since when have you been
scared of a little work, huh?
[MAN GASPS]
[PIGLET SQUEALING]
[WHIMPERING]
[TASER CRACKLING]
[MAN YELLS]
[TIRES SCREECH]
What was he after?
Well, now.
[DOOR OPENS]
There. See? I told you.
Oh. Oh, dear.
Get your hand out of that corpse now.
I was just passing by
and I, um, was just curious.
Ha, ha. What was I thinking?
Sorry. Won't happen again. Promise.
Do something about this
or I'm going over your head.
I'm the medical examiner,
not this gibbering loon.
I'm sorry, Ed.
- Until further notice, you're suspended.
GUERRA: Finally.
But I found something.
BULLOCK: So word around the house
is that you and Doc Caliente have a thing.
GORDON:
Thompkins? Yeah, kind of, I guess.
- So you and Barbara are finally finito?
- Yeah.
Dropped the keys
off at her apartment today.
BULLOCK:
Get any of that righteous break-up sex?
She wasn't there. You notice
I don't ask you about your love life.
My love life is an open book,
a short and nasty one.
But I'm working the Vic's friend
in the phobia group.
Unless she's the killer,
I think I'm in there.
You see why I don't ask.
Don't screw it up with the doctor.
- I'll try not to.
- Seriously.
Been willing to forgive you
on account of your not getting laid.
But this whole time you've been
raising hell, you've had a woman?
The thought of what you would do
if alone is truly terrifying.
[MAN SCREAMS NEARBY]
- G.C.P.D.
- Drop the knife.
[YELLS]
What the hell?
[PIGS GRUNTING AND SNORTING]
Thin lead, huh?
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Come in.
I hope everything
is to your satisfaction, ma'am.
It is. Thank you, captain.
You can see Gotham on the horizon
if you want to say goodbye.
No need. I'll be back soon enough.
Well, if you need anything,
just let me know.
I Will.
This fella and the previous victim are both
part of the same phobia support group.
Pigs. Go figure. How is he?
He's at Gotham General scared
half to death. Medics had to sedate him.
The man you shot, he in this group?
Nope. No ID as of yet.
We're running his prints.
Are we still looking for someone else?
- Hard to say.
BULLOCK: He's our man.
These wackos work alone. I'm gonna run by
the support group. Tell them it's settled.
- Hey, we don't know that yet.
- You need to be more optimistic.
You do. You need to be more optimistic.
We have a perp.
The postmortem incision
on the first victim is weird.
The killer was after something.
I wanna know what. I'm gonna ask Nygma.
No. He's been suspended.
You got the report from the M.E.
Who said my last witness stabbed himself
to death in the back with an ice pick?
No, no thanks. Nygma...
Is not the medical examiner.
I like him too.
But there's nothing I can do,
not with the way things are.
- What do you mean?
- Look, I'm glad we took down Flass.
But there are people you go after
and people you don't.
So now everything we do is being watched.
You got the bad guy. Let it go.
- I'm sorry you got dragged into it.
- Don't be.
It felt good.
It did, didn't it?
[KRINGLE SOBBING]
Ms. Kringle, I came to tell you that I...
- Have you been crying?
- No. No, I'm fine.
But I can see tears on your face.
Is it because your friend
Flass was arrested?
- What do you need, Mr. Nygma?
- Yes.
I've been suspended
and won't be seeing you anymore.
So I wanted to return this pencil.
I took it from your office some time ago.
I kept meaning to return it.
It used to be longer.
You're an odd man, Mr. Nygma.
But I'm sorry that you've been suspended.
I wish something could be done.
Have a seat. We gotta talk.
I feel the time has come in our relationship
when we should have trust with each other.
Real trust.
Total honesty between us.
No secrets.
I 100 percent agree.
So here's a secret to start off.
There is no guy with a thing. I lied.
I was beginning to wonder about him.
- Now you.
- Me?
We're being honest.
You have to tell me a secret in return.
Secrets from you, Don Maroni?
I have none.
Please.
Um, honestly, I don't really like oatmeal.
Good to know. See, I like this game.
I'll tell you another secret.
Fish Mooney's alive. I spoke to her.
Good secret, huh?
- What did Fish say?
- Oh, no.
You have to tell me a secret first.
That's how it works.
I don't much like coffee either.
Fair enough.
What did Fish say? Said you and Falcone
have been working together all this time.
She said you've been playing me
for a chump since the first day I met you.
She would say that, wouldn't she?
The bitch.
You don't believe her, do you?
It did put some incidents in a different
and troubling light, I must say.
- Huh. That's too bad.
- Your turn.
Tell me another secret.
A good one this time.
I took your gun.
I have it right here.
That's a good secret.
I took it because I figured
Mooney had called you somehow.
I knew you might believe her.
- It doesn't mean she's telling the truth.
- Is she?
Have you been playing me
for a chump, Penguin?
- I think it's your turn to tell a secret.
- You little dirt bag.
- I treated you like a friend.
- Like a monkey friend.
You're the Zookeeper, remember?
Tell me a secret now.
Just one more, then. I'm
tired of this game.
That gun is loaded with blanks.
Liar.
- You...
- Yeah.
Good secret, huh?
[PANTING]
Hi.
- Thank you for coming.
- I was glad to get your call.
How are things at Arkham?
A little less interesting since you left.
- Oh.
- How are things at the precinct?
Uh, well, that was what I was hoping
you could help me with. Uh...
We've got this case and I can't understand
what exactly our perp was doing.
And our medical examiner
is kind of a clown.
- Uh, something wrong?
- No. Not at all.
Only, last time we met,
you were very passionate.
So when you called me, I thought...
Well, whatever, I put on lipstick.
And you want forensic advice.
You're very confusing.
I don't mean to be. Uh...
- The case is a pretext. I wanted to see you.
- Well, why didn't you just say that?
I should have. I haven't done this
in a while. I'm a little rusty.
- Heh.
- Sorry.
All right. Good.
I don't like to put on lipstick by mistake.
So, what's the issue?
No, forget the case. Don't worry.
Please. I'm interested.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Uh...
Excuse me.
Gordon.
When?
Uh, yeah. Okay.
Take his statement. I'll be right there.
- I'm sorry. I have to go.
- I'm fine.
- You sure?
- Yes. I'll bring this back to you.
BULLOCK: It's Harvey.
- Harvey, the second victim woke up.
Says he was abducted by two men.
There's someone still out there.
It's kind to come here
and tell us what happened.
No problem. I just didn't want
you worrying, that's all.
To be honest, you don't strike me
as the fraidy-cat type.
Phobics are not fraidy-cats.
I know, it's just you seem
like a strong lady, is all.
I am strong. I just happen to be
terrified of swimming pools.
- You're kidding.
- Heh.
I can see how that might be a thing.
Nearly everyone has a thing.
I'm sure that you, if you dig deep enough,
would have issues you need to confront.
I'm a cop. The only thing
I'm scared of is decaf coffee.
Really? I've always found that
the best and bravest people...
are the ones that willingly
acknowledge their fears.
Maybe you've been hanging out with
too many timid and whiny people.
You are so bad.
I'm scared all the time.
And it's something I'd be willing to share
with the group if you think it'll be helpful.
Yes. Yes, thank you. I think it would.
- First time?
- Yeah. You?
No. I'm a regular.
MARONI: So here's the deal. You go in the
car. The car's already in the crusher.
You get squeezed to death.
It takes a couple minutes to die.
Whatever comes out, I send to Falcone.
Maybe he uses it as a coffee table.
- Don Maroni, please listen to me...
- Oh, this is the begging part?
Because this is my favorite part.
Go ahead and beg for your miserable life.
Just allow me to
suggest some options here.
- Mm-hm.
- Dead, I'm worthless.
Factoring in Falcone's inevitable retaliation,
killing me will be a net loss for you.
This is not a business issue.
Me and Frankie Carbone go back 2O years.
You hurt me, Penguin.
You were right about Indian Hill. There's
more to it. Falcone knows something.
- I don't know what, but I can find out...
- Stop it. You're making me sad.
How did I ever fall for your crap?
No. No. Please. Please.
No.
[OSWALD GRUNTING]
Hey-
Say hi to Frankie for me.
I'm afraid every day.
I'm afraid I'm gonna die in an alley...
bleeding out while some scumbag
goes through my pockets and laughs at me.
And I try to speak, but nothing comes out.
And I just lie there...
staring at a small space of sky
between the buildings.
And then I die.
Alone.
I don't want to die alone in some gutter.
I wanna die in a warm, cozy bed
in the arms of a beautiful woman.
Thank you for sharing, Harvey.
Would anyone else like to share?
[TOD CLEARS THROAT]
Tod, go ahead.
My name is Tod
and I've never spoken here before...
but I have a horrible terror of failure.
I torment myself and those around me.
I'd crawl on broken glass
to avoid failing about anything.
I inherited this illness
from my father...
but I'm afraid I'm passing it on
to my son.
We're here for you, Tod.
When I came home from work yesterday,
my precious son was crying.
And he said to me that he...
[TOD SOBBING]
- I'm sorry. I can't speak. I'm so sorry.
- Tod.
Tod.
[GRUNTING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Oh, you gotta be kidding me. What?
- Don Maroni, you have to listen.
- Actually, no.
This is how this began,
me listening to you.
I was telling the truth
about Indian Hill and Arkham.
Whoever controls Arkham
will control Gotham...
Would you shut up and take it like a man?
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
OSWALD: Hello, is this Mr. Duffy?
- Uh-huh.
Listen to me very carefully.
I'm the man in the car
in this ferocious machine of yours.
My name is Oswald Cobblepot and I work for
Don Carmine Falcone of Gotham City.
- Do you know who Don Falcone is?
- Uh-huh.
Good. I just called Don Falcone.
And I told him exactly where I am
and what's happening.
So, Duffy, you better stop this machine
right now because if I die...
Don Falcone is gonna send a team up here to
skin you alive and slaughter your family.
- But Don Maroni said...
- Don Falcone runs Gotham.
And you're about to murder
his right-hand man.
What the hell?
Hey. Get back here.
Son of a bitch.
Is it just me or have those two
been gone a while?
This has been real and fun,
but I gotta go.
[WHISTLING]
[SHRIEKS]
[PANTING]
Oh, my God.
This isn't what it looks like.
Our abductor's been coming
the last month.
Said his name was Tod, but group protocol
requires they remain anonymous.
So no real ID.
- The guy with the pigs?
- Prints came back. Career criminal.
Just the muscle.
The other guy was in charge.
He knew there was a cop at the meeting and
he still took her. That's cold or crazy.
He's almost sure
to follow the same MO.
He'll confront Ms. Mullens
with her greatest fear.
- Which is drowning.
- Specifically in a pool.
- There's hundreds of pools in Gotham. We...
- That was her mother.
When she was 7, Scottie almost drowned
on Lemmars Park pool uptown.
- It's a start, I guess.
- That's where he took her. I can feel it.
- Boss?
- Uh, not now, Joe.
Wait.
Tell me that's not what it looks like.
You're brave.
I'd say you're an eight on the Crane Scale.
Profound fear.
Twelve is top:
abject heart-stopping terror.
I'm surprised you're only an eight.
You do understand
that this is really happening?
I'm going to drown you.
[SHRIEKS]
Right now.
There. That's a 10.
Dad.
- Help.
- Jonathan, I said to wait in the van.
Parking meter ran out.
[WHIMPERING]
Look, son, I know this is hard,
but we've talked about it.
It's for the common good, for humanity.
I know. I just... I think...
This will be over soon. Here.
Go and feed the meter. Go on. Go.
[SOBBING]
Now, my dear, don't think badly of me.
[SCREAMING]
- G.C.P.D.
- Don't move.
I'm on him. You get her.
[GRUNTS]
[GASPING]
[SOBBING]
He's alive.
I told you he was alive. Praise the Lord.
What happened to you, boy?
Like the prodigal son,
ma'am, I have fallen.
Like Job, I've been tested in the deepest
pits of the devil's perfidy and survived.
[CHUCKLES]
Lord have mercy.
Are you headed to Gotham City
by any chance?
Sure. Come on.
[WOMEN SINGING]
Trouble in my way
- I got to cry sometimes
- l got to cry sometimes
- I lay awake at night
- l lay awake at night
- But that's all right, it's all right
- That's all right
- For Jesus will fix it
- Jesus will fix it
- After a while
- After
The case files you gave me about that man
thrown from the roof. You catch his killer?
Uh, no, he's still out there. Hi.
- I had a quick look at his corpse.
- A quick look at his corpse?
It's downstairs at the morgue.
So the killer removed his adrenal glands.
Strange. They have no value
on the black market, do they?
No. Kidneys and livers, yes.
Adrenal glands, no.
It produces cortisol, the hormone that gives
us that adrenalized fight-or-flight reaction.
Essentially, it's the fear gland.
And our man wants to take it from the
victim when he's most fearful. Why do that?
All I can think of
is at the moment of death...
the victim's adrenals would produce a
massive, highly elevated form of cortisol.
Fascinating, huh?
This is one weird dude.
A doctor or a nurse, most likely.
Takes skill to remove the adrenals
as cleanly as they did.
- You really like this kind of work, huh?
- I do.
Good. Maybe there will be more for you.
Full time job, even. Our M.E. has been fired
for stealing body parts. You believe that?
Only in Gotham.
So, what do you say we discuss
this potential job over dinner?
- Nice segue, Mr. Smooth.
- Thank you.
Dinner sounds good.
You gonna bring your case files?
Go ahead, mock my crude dating skills.
I'm doing my best.
You're doing fine.
I have a powerful urge
to kiss you right now.
Why don't you?
Because I'm on-duty and, uh...
there's about 50 people watching.
- Scaredy cat.
- Damn straight. I have an image to keep up.
- The heartless, by-the-book hard man.
- Kind of.
On count of three,
I'm gonna lean in so that it's subtle.
And you're gonna kiss me
on the cheek or no dinner.
- Come on.
- I'm serious.
One.
Two.
Three.
I'm not leaving after all.
What?
The medical examiner is leaving,
so Captain Essen decided to reinstate me.
Oh. Okay. Good.
Mr. Nygma.
You owe me a new pencil.
- What? What's happening?
- I can hide you.
Quickly.