NARRATOR:
Previously on Gotham:
I had a meeting with Wayne Enterprises...
to tell them I was investigating them,
they sent someone we trust to spy on us.
Alfred was stabbed.
It was a friend of his from the Army.
- What was he looking for?
BRUCE: Some of my files.
I could find out who hired him.
He's the key to everything.
I have a plan.
I promise you
I will get some of us out of here alive.
- Who are you?
- Dr. Francis Dulmacher.
The people in the basement trust me.
Put me in charge and I promise you
a dependable flow of healthy product.
- And if I fail?
DULMACHER: Those who fail me...
still have their uses.
- What are they doing?
- I'm sorry, honey, you're on the list.
Half the cops on the G.C.P.D.
have a Cobblepot...
and Loeb has the goods on all of them.
- That is what Loeb does.
- Well, it ends now.
So, what do you want?
With the coming election for president
of the Policeman's Union...
there's no man I'd rather support.
It's a new day in the G.C.P.D.
- Mm, looking good, Ms. Cavanaugh.
CAVANAUGH: Thank you.
- How's that swelling?
CAVANAUGH: Fine.
If you need more ice packs,
I'll let Denise know.
Mr. Douglas,
I know you don't like your view...
and as soon as a recovery suite is open,
I'm going to move you.
[DOUGLAS SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
[ALARM SOUNDS]
Is there a problem?
- You're outside.
- You're observant.
I'm the new assistant for the doctor.
I'm Fish. And you are?
Inside, you're free to roam,
that's Dr. Dulmacher's prerogative.
But once you step outside,
you're in my world.
I'm the man who catches the poor souls
brave enough to try to escape.
Ah, you're the catcher.
- I've heard a lot about you.
- Heh.
So have there been many?
Poor souls, I mean.
No.
The water does most of the work...
but every so often someone gets stupid
and gives it a go.
I didn't know
I wasn't supposed to be outside.
My mistake.
Make that mistake again,
and it'll be your last.
BRUCE:
I saw the papers the other day.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
So, what does president
of the Policeman's Union do exactly?
Depends on the president.
- I see.
- How's Alfred?
- Whinier than I thought.
- Mm.
BRUCE:
No, he's getting better.
GORDON:
Glad to hear it.
You two lied about who stabbed him,
didn't you?
That's why you're here?
Is it?
Yes.
Did you?
Lie to me?
No.
If we don't have a description of
the culprit, we won't find him.
I wish I could help you, detective.
Alfred wants to go after him on his own,
that's why you lied to me.
No.
Bruce, look at me.
Whatever Alfred is up to,
you have to stay out of it.
It's dangerous.
And it's not your fight.
I cut this bread way too thick, didn't I?
Bruce...
I understand what you're saying.
Okay, then.
[GORDON SIGHS]
Detective Gordon.
- Len Moore.
- Officer. What can I help you with?
- You're a man with a reputation.
- Oh, yeah?
A Gotham detective
who actually closes cases.
I try.
MOORE: Uh, that's actually why I'm here.
- Oh, yeah?
A few weeks ago,
I was the first responder to a homicide.
Victim's name was Grace Fairchild.
They found her body stabbed to death.
The detectives who caught the case,
they got nowhere with it and moved on.
I'm sorry to hear that, but it happens.
I was wondering if you'd pick up
where they left off.
- You want me to take over the case?
- Yeah.
Look, Len, I got a full boat here.
This victim's family, they deserve justice.
- Yeah.
- Her killer deserves to pay for what he did.
This was a nasty one.
They're all nasty.
What's your angle on this?
There's no angle. It's just...
A few of us younger guys, we've been
watching what you've been doing...
to clean up Gotham and the G.C.P.D.,
and I wanna be a part of it.
And bringing you this case
is my way of trying to do that.
I'll look into it.
GORDON:
Ready to go?
Ready? I have been dreaming
about the carbonara at Luccio's all day.
New case?
Uh, sort of. It's an unsolved homicide
a uni asked me to look into.
- It's an odd one.
- Ooh, how so?
Thought you were hungry.
What can I say?
You had me at "homicide."
[GORDON CHUCKLES]
GORDON: The victim, Grace Fairchild,
was found two weeks ago.
But she was reported missing
four months earlier.
The last anyone heard,
she called her mother...
said she was having a drink at a bar
in the South Village.
That's my neighborhood. What bar?
Detectives canvassed the area,
nobody knows.
No leads, no tips. I'm starting to see
why the case was dropped.
God, we were almost the same age.
We could've been friends.
You know, they have a few speakeasies
in the South Village.
It's a new thing. You walk in through a dry
cleaner's or a shoe store to get inside.
- Easy to miss if you're not in the know.
- Thanks. I'll check it out.
LESLIE:
Good. I'm glad you're looking into this.
Whoever did this, he's a monster.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
[KELLY WHEEZING]
Kelly.
[KELLY GRUNTING AND MUTTERING]
Shh, Shh, shh.
KELLY: God.
- Shh, shh.
Still bad.
What do you want?
I have a plan, but I need your help.
What plan?
We're going to escape.
I'm getting off of this
hell of an island...
or I'm gonna die trying.
Alfred?
- Where are you going?
- Lnto the city, Master Bruce.
If I know Reggie, he's probably
drunk himself half to death by now...
and is moving swiftly
onto the harder stuff.
I'll probably find him...
holed up in a shooting gallery,
totally off his maracas.
Alfred, you can't go.
- You're not well.
- No choice, Master Bruce.
He'll only be here for a few days.
Enough time to get his fix,
then he'll be off.
Well, then we'd better get going.
If you think I'm gonna take you, Master...
[ALFRED GRUNTS]
Oh, dear.
Good day, Lidia.
Have you thought about my offer?
I told you already,
my place is not for sale.
Please. I beg of you, think again.
I will serve strictly as a silent partner.
You will continue
to run the day-to-day operations...
[SPEAKS IN ITALIAN]
I told you already!
Madam, please, I meant no harm.
Okay, Mama. You made your point.
COBBLEPOT:
Madam, I assure you...
I have a sincere interest
in your establishment.
If money is not what you seek...
surely there is something you want.
My granddaughter, Antonia...
she's beautiful...
virtuous...
an angel.
And she has been seduced
by a silver-tongued guitar player.
Lucifer himself.
A tragedy.
You make her come home...
leave this baboon...
then I'll consider your offer.
Madam...
she'll be home for Sunday Mass.
You have my word.
This place is a dump.
Real nickel-and-dime.
It's worth far more than that, Gabe.
You just don't see it yet.
- No.
GORDON: I'm not saying...
we officially take
over the investigation.
- Just help me look into it.
- No.
Harvey, the victim deserves justice.
And I deserve a mute supermodel who likes
pasty Irish guys and loves to cook.
It's not happening.
Besides, we both know that justice
isn't the real reason you want this one.
- Hello, detectives.
BULLOCK: Ed, question.
Would you rather work more or less?
- Is this a riddle?
- Exactly.
You're helping. What's up?
Uh, list of establishments in
the South Village with a liquor license.
- Including speakeasies?
- Yes, sirree.
Four of which, you'll be pleased to know,
were missed by the original detectives.
That's great, Ed. Thanks. One more thing.
I was going through the crime scene
evidence from the Fairchild murder...
and, uh, there's
a piece of evidence missing.
- Any idea what it is?
- No, but it's labeled "SA."
- Think you can find it?
- Detective, I will solve this puzzle.
You coming?
Let me say it in Spanish: No.
Okay, look, you're right. I'm ambitious.
I wanna show people around here
that things are gonna change.
But, Harvey,
I can't do that without your help.
Look, I know you're riding high,
what with getting over on Loeb and all...
but there's one thing
you should always remember.
Fly too close to the sun,
you're gonna get burned.
- You done?
- Yeah.
Good. Then get your ass up.
[GRUNTS]
FISH:
So that's it.
So you're trying to tell me
you actually think we can get out of here?
That's What I said, didn't I?
- How?
- With cunning and guile.
But it won't work without your help.
Why us?
Why not your friends?
There's no telling how this is all going
to go down during the breakout.
Just in case it goes south...
I need some stone-cold killers by
my side not some whipped-ass victims.
CLINT:
That's fair.
What's the plan?
Outside, there's a boat
down by the shore...
big enough to carry the six of us
off of this island.
A boat?
You have a better idea?
I heard a chopper land the other day.
Thumped like a son of a bitch.
Why don't we fly out of here?
Do any of you know
how to fly a helicopter?
Mm-hm. That's why.
All right, this boat.
You got the keys to it?
No. Not yet, but I Will.
So are you in or out?
We're oh for 3 and my dogs are barking.
I'm hardly one to complain about going
to a bar, but this is getting ridiculous.
It's grunt work, just like any other case.
Except it's not just like any other case,
it's a hobby.
Everybody needs a hobby.
G.C.P.D. Homicide.
WOMAN:
Yeah, she was in here.
A while ago, maybe three or four months.
GORDON:
You remember her?
Yeah, she mentioned she went
to a rival college of mine.
- Plus...
- Plus what?
To be honest with you, her date was hot.
Her date?
Remember what he looked like?
Just that he was good-looking,
but classy, you know?
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYS OVER SPEAKERS
AND PEOPLE CHATTERING]
FAIRCHILD:
Okay, your turn.
How is a successful, funny...
mildly good-looking guy like you
still single?
- Mildly?
- Maybe a little bit more than that.
Come on.
Something has to be wrong with you.
LENNON:
Maybe you're right.
I've, uh...
I've had plenty of relationships...
but in the end...
they never seem to work out.
Why not?
I think what I'm looking for
frightens people.
Uh, okay.
No, it's... Heh, heh. It's nothing weird.
What, then?
It's gonna sound cheesy.
I won't laugh. I promise.
What I'm looking for...
is unconditional love.
Unconditional, real...
intense love.
[CHUCKLES]
Cheesy, right?
Totally.
[DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
FAIRCHILD:
Wow.
- You like it?
- It'll do.
There's some wine in the kitchen.
Open anything you like.
May I take your jacket?
This place must work well.
What do you mean?
The women that you bring back here.
Heh. Actually...
it's been a while
since I've had anyone over.
Hmm.
- Lucky me.
- I'm the lucky one.
Thank you for taking a chance on me.
Heh. Are you kidding me?
Look at this place.
I could definitely stay here.
For a night.
Look, if he, uh...
comes back in or you think of
anything else, give me a call.
Sure.
He was right here, Harvey.
Yeah.
You're not dropping this one, are you?
Not a chance.
[DOORBELL BUZZES]
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
[MAN WHIMPERING]
So...
are we in agreement?
Not quite.
Pagliacci says he still loves the girl.
He won't leave her.
Antonia and I are destined to be together.
And nothing you can do...
will make me stop loving her.
See what I mean? True love.
You want me to put a slug in him?
- See if that loosens him up?
- No.
He's a guitar player.
Lose the fingers.
- You want me to shoot his fingers?
- Don't shoot them.
Lose them.
[MAN SCREAMS]
[DOOR OPENS]
Just the man I wanted to see.
Oh, don't say that.
You're gonna make Jim jealous.
I finished the Fairchild autopsy
and the results are strange.
GORDON:
Strange how?
LESLIE: Grace Fairchild was missing
for over four months.
Usually with these kind of abductions...
there's a lot of trauma and abuse
to the body, not this time.
Other than the stab wounds to her heart and
her throat, her body was mostly pristine.
That doesn't add up.
Unless...
- Unless what?
- You ever consider she ran off on her own?
That her going missing has nothing to do
with her murder?
The findings would certainly
support that.
Maybe.
No.
No, Fairchild had a good job, a mortgage.
Hell, she called her mother
the night she went missing.
No, she didn't run away. She was taken.
And whoever took her
kept her locked away...
till he was good and ready...
and then he killed her.
I know it.
Morning.
How'd you sleep?
Like a baby.
So I thought after breakfast,
we could go to the Palick exhibit.
- He's only in town another week.
- Oh.
I would love to, really,
but I am already late...
and I've got a morning meeting
and a work lunch.
- So reschedule it.
- I can't.
I had a really good time
with you last night.
And I hope that I get to see you again.
At least, uh, have some breakfast.
Oh, I still have to go home and change,
and I'm so late.
Next time.
Call me tonight.
I can come over after work...
if you want.
Jason, please, I really have to go.
[FAIRCHILD GRUNTS]
No...
you don't.
[DOOR KNOB RATTLING]
Ms. Mooney.
What a surprise.
Is there something I can do for you?
Well, supplies were running low
for the inmates.
Those are in the storage room.
But then, of course,
you already knew that.
The one thing I won't tolerate...
is dishonesty.
- You were trying to escape, weren't you?
- No.
DULMACHER:
I'll tell you what.
I'm gonna shoot you in the stomach.
You'll feel pressure at first.
Then you'll feel an intense burning
like you've never felt in your life.
Maybe that will properly motivate you
to be honest with me.
I ask you again.
Were you trying to escape?
No.
How disappointing.
Wait. Stop. Wait, wait.
I was lying, but I...
But I wasn't trying to escape.
You were going to kill me?
Slit my throat, perhaps?
No, I swear.
Not yours.
Every night when I close my eyes,
I pray to God...
that nightmare doesn't come.
That"
living, breathing man
stitched together with...
arms and legs that weren't his.
That nightmare you created.
I've faced dangerous men...
but none like you...
Dollmaker.
So you'd rather take your own life
than end up one of my creations?
Yes.
Well, Miss Mooney...
try anything like this again
and your nightmare will come true.
I will bring you back from the dead
if I have to...
and make you into something
the world has never seen.
Was there something else?
No.
[DANCE MUSIC
PLAYS OVER SPEAKERS]
[METAL CLANGING]
Could've smashed your head with a brick,
you know.
Why would you do that?
Why'd you even say that?
Just thought you should know.
What's up? Why are you looking for me?
Reggie Payne, the man who stabbed Alfred,
he's in Gotham.
And you need my help to find him. Okay.
BRUCE: Alfred said he'd be at a gun range
for a few days.
But I checked every one in the city.
Nothing.
Who stays at a gun range for a few days?
Doesn't make any sense.
That's what he said.
He said Reggie would be
at a shooting gallery.
That's not the same as a gun range, silly.
You really need to get out more.
[SOBBING]
All right, all right, all right.
[ANTONIA GASPS]
Go get yourself cleaned up.
[BELL JINGLES]
I'll be back in a minute.
So shall we discuss terms?
So, what is it?
This isn't an actual piece of crime scene
evidence. It's gone, as far as I can tell.
What I was able to find is a photocopy
buried deep in a logbook.
It's a broken heart. Hand-painted, I guess.
This was at the crime scene?
You sure?
Well, not this, exactly.
You see, a photocopy is a replica...
Damn it, no, Ed, not now.
- What's wrong?
BULLOCK: I warned you...
but, no, you had to go
and get both of us burned.
- What are you talking about?
BULLOCK: This guy you're after...
this is not his first rodeo.
He's a serial killer.
This looks delicious.
Thank you.
I, uh...
I think I might have overcooked the lamb
a little bit.
But I... I...
I'm sure it's fine.
[CLASSICAL MUSIC
PLAYS OVER SPEAKERS]
How was your day?
Wonderful, darling.
And how was yours?
Good.
Thank you for asking.
Hmm.
I think you might have been right...
about the lamb.
I am so sorry.
It's fine.
I checked it twice
when it was in the oven...
and I think it might be hotter
than it says that it is.
[WHIMPERING]
You know...
[INHALES DEEPLY THEN EXHALES]
I don't think this is working out.
[SOBBING]
It's not you.
It's me.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS]
[FAIRCHILD GASPING]
We could've had something special.
FAIRCHILD:
Please. Please, don't hurt me.
LENNON: You know,
I really thought you were the one.
[FAIRCHILD WHIMPERING]
Please.
Don't worry, sooner or later...
I'll find her.
GABE:
I still don't get it.
Why all that trouble
for this pile of bricks?
This was never about money, Gabe.
Not about money? What else is there?
All kinds of things motivate people.
Lust, ambition, envy.
Okay, what motivated you?
Why do you want this place so bad?
It's simple.
This is where I'm gonna kill Don Maroni.
It's time. Are you ready?
Let's go.
Now, as soon as this door opens...
an alarm will go off
and we will not have much time.
- What about the gate?
- Unlocked last night.
Take these.
Get the boat started
as soon as you get there.
You're not coming?
I'm coming. I'll be right back.
I need to get Kelly.
He can barely walk. Let's go.
Call me sentimental,
but I cannot leave him here.
[ALARM SOUNDS]
And you better not leave me.
You lied to me, Fish.
[BATON WHIRRING]
I warned you what would happen
if you lied to me.
Oh, what wonders I'm going to make
of your parts.
[DULMACHER GRUNTING]
See you around, doc.
Leave him there.
We don't have much time. Let's go.
MAN:
Go.
This way.
They're headed for the boat.
- What are you doing? Open up the gate.
- I can't. It's locked.
What? Fish said she unlocked it.
- That bitch.
- What?
Fish. She set us up.
[KELLY GRUNTS]
[INMATES GRUNTING]
- Kelly, other side.
- Over here, come on.
HurW, hurry-
- You told them you couldn't fly, didn't you?
- I lied.
[HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING]
The chopper.
Hold on.
- Aah!
- Fish.
[GASPS]
He abducts young, single, attractive women
and he keeps them...
sometimes for a week,
sometimes for months.
Then he dumps their bodies
around Gotham.
- How many has he killed?
BULLOCK: A dozen. Maybe more.
Every time he makes a kill,
he leaves one of these at the crime scene.
It's his calling card.
So who is he?
No one knows.
Thinking is he's educated, decent-looking,
rich, but that's just a profile.
Some of the guys call him
the Don Juan Killer.
Most call him the Ogre.
So why haven't I heard
about this guy before?
Why hasn't the public?
- It's the G.C.P.D.'s...
COP: Fellas.
Dirty little secret.
Only a handful of senior detectives
know anything...
and they sure ain't leaking
it to the press. - Why not?
Because the Ogre retaliates
against any cop who investigates him.
He kills the people they love.
That's why this lunatic
hasn't been caught yet, Jim...
because no one's been stupid enough
to investigate.
Until I came along.
Which makes me wonder,
how did you catch this?
I told you, a fellow officer
asked me to look into it.
Who?
Which one?
[PEOPLE CHATTERING AND COUGHING]
BRUCE:
Cat.
MAN:
Other side.
That's him.
WOMAN:
Give me some of that stuff.
[SIREN WAILS]
[REGGIE YELLS]
[REGGIE YELLING]
Relax, old man. We're not gonna rob you.
- What are you doing here?
- We came to talk to you.
- Who's she?
BRUCE: Never mind.
Who sent you to my house?
Who sent me to...?
Just go home. Go home, Bruce.
You'll be in more trouble
than you are already.
Hey! That's my medicine. Give me that.
My friend just asked you a question.
I said, give me that.
Or you'll what? Huh?
- Hey! Don't!
- Answer the question.
I didn't mean any harm.
I was just supposed to
take some documents.
But Alfred walked in...
Is he all right?
Is he?
You stabbed him.
What do you care?
I care. He's all right, isn't he?
Who sent you?
Throw them out.
- No!
- Tell me who sent you.
Who sent you?
You shouldn't be doing this, Bruce.
Only Alfie can deal with these people.
What people?
There's a woman named Mathis
and a guy called Bunderslaw.
Sid Bunderslaw. He's the guy I dealt with.
But you've go...
You've got to let Alfie take care of this.
Not you, Bruce.
It's no business for a child.
This man, Bunderslaw...
what did he want?
Just to know what you knew.
To see how far
your investigation had gone.
But he was scared.
And that's why he sent me.
Now, can I have my bag back, please?
Please?
Give it back to him.
You.
You're a sick man, Mr. Payne.
You need help.
Don't you patronize me.
I may have vices, yeah,
but I'm a professional.
Do you want me to tell Bunderslaw
that you're onto him?
Because he'll come after you.
And there's nothing that you can do
to stop him.
You're just silly little children.
I'm going to tell on you.
[REGGIE GRUNTING]
No, you won't.
[REGGIE SCREAMING]
[CRASH]
It was... It wasn't my idea. I swear.
I was ordered to get you to take the case.
- Ordered by who?
- Loeb.
It was Commissioner Loeb.
He told me to tell you that...
I looked up to you,
that you inspired me.
I mean, he told me to say that I wanted
to help clean up Gotham and the G.C.P.D...
and that this case...
This case was part of that.
He knew you couldn't say no.
So you followed orders
like a good soldier.
I didn't have a choice.
I mean, you know what Loeb can do.
All too well.
Jim, listen, you're still
in the clear on this.
- In the clear? He could come after Lee.
- Only if he thinks you're investigating him.
Think about it.
It's not on your docket. There's been
no press linking you to this case.
All we've done is ask questions,
so you gotta drop it now.
This is no time to be a hero.
If I drop it,
I'm letting a serial killer go free.
The blood of his next victim
is on my hands.
If you don't drop it,
that blood could be Lee's.
[LINE RINGS]
LESLIE [ON RECORDING]:
Hi, you've reached Lee.
Go ahead and leave a message.
Lee, call me as soon as you can.
It's very impor...
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
YOu!
- You son of a bitch.
LOEB: Excuse me?
You set me up.
- Detective, I don't know what...
- Don't talk. Listen.
- Hey.
GORDON: Back off.
COP:
Don't you...
GORDON:
I tried to work with you.
But now you crossed a line.
You come after the one I love?
From here on, we're playing my way.
No more games, no more deals.
I'm gonna find the Ogre,
and I'm gonna put him behind bars.
And when I've done that,
I'm coming after you.
I'm coming after you, commissioner.
You're done.
[MURMURING]
[English - US - SDH]