GORDON: Previously on Gotham...
- The Doc? You know him?
- I know the Doc.
LEE: sometimes we search
for things we don't wish to find.
I enjoy being the queen of Gotham.
Glad we understand each other.
There are other ways
for me to hurt you.
HARVEY: Something's eating at you, Jim.
And you're not gonna feel clean
till you get it off your chest.
That's done now.
I'm at Sofia Falcone's.
Ijust shot and killed the Pyg.
Isee Arkham's treating you well.
Goodbye. Oswald.
PENGUIN: "I am held captive.
AII my brilliance locked away.”
- You're still there.
- (LAUGHING)
And you're gonna help me
find a way out of here.
I need a name.
- Ivy Pepper.
- I know Ivy.
SELINA: No, Gordon, she's changed.
Like a lot.
Called Lazarus Water.
LUCIUS: Whatare you going
to do with it?
IW: I'm going to make miracles happen.
You'll reel it in a little,
or should I call your keeper?
- Alfred? He won't answer.
- SELINA: Why?
BRUCE: 'Cause I fired him.
Where's the other guy who works here?
You mean, Harvey?
He's out sick.
You wanna leave a message?
(CHOMPING)
(SMACKING)
- I do.
- (BURPS)
AII right.
What should I say?
Nothing.
Because all of you,
with your blood and your flesh.
And what you will become...
You are the message.
He was a good man.
Doesn't matter that Maria's gone,
you'll always be my sister.
For Falcones, it's all about family.
I appreciate that.
So, sister to sister...
We're not really here
to look at photographs.
There's only one neighborhood
in Gotham that hasn't bent the knee.
The Narrows has never submitted
to an outside boss.
There's never been someone
like me ruling Gotham.
Okay.
What do you want?
A tax.
Thirty percent on all income coming
from The Narrows, legal and illegal.
Every family there lives
hand to mouth. They'II starve.
We all have to make sacrifices.
I'll need an answer
by the end of the day.
You want me to kiss the ring?
I'II do it.
To keep the peace. But what you're
asking for is impossible.
You'll find a way.
Thought it was all about family.
Never said it was a happy family.
(DOOR opens)
Thank you.
Thank you for meeting me.
My parents' foundation is having
their annual dinner tonight.
I thought we could go.
Somehow. I don't think you got me
all the way down here
to talk about a fundraiser, did you?
Bruce, what exactly is it that
you want from me?
Help.
Figuring this out.
I can't do it alone, I...
Alfred, I need your help.
No.
What?
Listen, you can't just waltz back
in here and expect me to go
and clean your smalls and cock
your tea. After what you've done.
Alfred, I'm not asking for that.
I've changed.
You have. have you?
It's one thing saying
that you've changed.
And another actually changing.
So show me. Show me how you've
changed, and I might reconsider.
Show you how?
That's for you to figure out, innit?
I'm asking as a friend.
I'm not yourfriend.
I was your butler.
And you fired me.
He'II pay for the tea, miss.
Sure hope Lee is gonna
figure something out with Sofia.
Lee being the love
of your life and all.
We're friends.
You know, those koo-koo pills
aren't gonna make me go away.
Well, they have stopped you
from getting out
and trying to kill Lee again.
So works for me.
Mail arrived.
Oh, who's it from?
Oswald.
"I want to apologize...
Can we be friends againT'
What? I'm never gonna forgive him.
I think it's a nice letter.
- Shut up!
- Hey, Ed.
What has two eyes but can't see?
What has two...
(LAUGHING)
Good lord.
This is new. More aggressive.
The plants are literally bursting
through their flesh.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
You! Get away from that! Now!
Now.
Same flower growing out
of these bodies.
That's a weapon?
Gordon, this must be what Ivy
did with the Lazarus Water.
Used it to increase
the potency of a toxic plant.
- The seeds made it airborne...
- GORDON: Where's Bullock?
- What?
- He works here.
Harvey killed Ivy's father.
Too late.
No, we're not.
Hey.
Hey!
Damn it, Jim!
Jim, what the hell?
Hey, someone's paying for that door!
'Vy Pepper.
- Who?
- Mario Pepper's kid.
She's been working on some biotech.
She attacked your bar.
It's bad.
Donnie, the bartender...
I'm sorry.
Oh, God!
Look, I gotta think
that you were the target.
Jim, I only shot Ivy Pepper's dad
because I was saving your stupid eye.
You can't put this on me.
- I'm not putting it on you.
- ALVAREZ: Guys.
We have decided to share the footage.
So in a moment the video
we are about to show you
is from a tape received this morning.
And again, let me warn you.
It is very disturbing.
Plants love us.
They give us food, shelter,
the very air we breathe.
But what do we do in return?
Kill them. Because that's our nature.
We cause pain.
Everyone I've known
has only hurt or betrayed me.
Maybe I've always known in my heart
what I needed to do.
But I finally
have the power to do so.
I'm giving your city
back to the plants.
Starting with the people who hurt me.
So if that's you,
your time is coming.
- Guess we know what she's up to.
- Yeah.
She's gonna kill everyone in Gotham.
Starting with me.
WOMAN: Preliminary reports indicate
that similar tapes have been delivered
to multiple news organizations.
Wait a minute.
What's that there?
HARVEY: Sully's Eatery.
That's in Ives Square.
House must be right across.
You should go to the precinct.
Hey, I'm not hiding
like some freaking coward. AII right?
Four people are dead
because she wanted me.
Okay. then we'II work on it together.
You can wear the badge.
Get this straight, Jim.
I ain't working for you now or ever.
I got more contacts in The Narrows
than any of you.
I'm gonna find her. Alone.
Once I find my pants.
LEE: Doesn't make any sense.
There's no money here.
Okay. so it's about power.
I offered to bend the knee.
She's asking for something
she knew I couldn't give.
She wants...
She wants to punish me.
For what?
Idon't know.
But you can't fight an enemy
whose motivations
you don't understand. Lee.
You are the greatest spies
in all of Gotham.
You have eyes and ears everywhere.
The survival of The Narrows
depends upon you.
Whoever learns why Sofia Falcone
wants to destroy Lee Thompkins
will receive
a complete set of encyclopedias.
Minus the T.
Plus 20 bucks.
- Yes!
- Yeah!
Go get 'em.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
OFFICER: We're moving, clear.
She wasn't bluffing.
With this many plants, she could kill
hundreds if not thousands of people.
Search the other room for any signs
of where she's heading.
What are you gonna do to her?
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
Ijust saw the news.
She killed four more people today.
You knew where she was staying.
If you had told me,
- we could've saved lives.
- Or not.
I mean, you couldn't even stop her
from hypnotizing your own cops.
S0 why did you come here?
To try to reason with her.
Have you heard a word she said?
She's a fanatic.
She's my friend.
What do you expect me to do?
She contacts you again, call me.
I'II try and find her,
and bring her in quietly.
Otherwise, stay out of her way.
Harvey?
Hey, I got a lead.
Great.
HARVEY: I knocked some heads.
Heard a hot redhead was poking around
in that dive bar next door.
That is the place in The Narrows
for low-end muscle.
So I figured,
if she was planning something big.
She mighfve gone there to recruit.
That's the back entrance.
That's where my contact said that...
(DOOR opens)
Hello, Detective Gordon.
On the ground. Now.
Harvey, call it in.
She's beautiful,
don't you think, Jim?
Drop your weapon.
(WHISTLES)
You don't look good.
I think you might be exceeding
your recommended dosage.
Are you experiencing
"trembling extremities"?
Check. "Cognitive impairment"?
Definite check.
Though to be fair,
how would you know?
Shut up!
Take all the pills you want, Ed.
I'm only getting stronger.
Soon I'm gonna be out,
and the fun begins.
No. I won't let you.
'Cause I know what you'll do.
Oh, you mean kill Lee?
Yeah, I guess I will do that.
And you can't stop me.
There are things that I can do.
Like what? You need to face it, pal.
The only way you'll get
rid of me is to kill yourself.
I guess you are smarter than me.
- You wouldn't actually...
- Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I said drop the gun, Jim.
Do you believe in fate.
Detective Gordon?
I went out today to test my plants
on the man who shot my father.
He wasn't there.
That's disappointing.
Then he found me.
And I realized I could make him
deliver his partner as well.
Fate.
Stay strong, Harvey.
She's controlling you.
I kinda like it, Jim.
Sweet surrender.
GORDON: You need help, Ivy.
Let me find Selina.
She wants to help.
Quiet.
I have to go.
Big plans tonight.
Lots of people to kill.
- Detective Bullock?
- Ma'am.
After you kill your partner, be sure
to shoot yourself in the head, okay?
Copy that.
(IW HUMMING)
(nooa CLOSES)
Harvey..
Don't even try
and talk your way out of this.
I wouldn't. But. quick question.
Is lvy's hair more auburn or scarlet?
I, uh...
That's a good..
(GUNSHOTS)
(GUN CLICKING)
You think I didn't come prepared, huh?
You always underestimate me.
That's not why I'm shooting you.
Ijust think
we should, uh, clear the air.
What do you wanna talk about?
I'm all ears.
How you stole myjob for starters.
GORDON: Was it really yourjob, though?
I mean. you only got it
'cause one captain died
and the other one went nuts.
Like hell!
I paid my dues! I earned that job,
and you took it!
You mean like the time
you gut-shot Officer Patel?
That was a mistake.
GORDON: Hey, give yourself some credit.
You did shoot her
from across the room.
Although you couldn't
face her later, remember?
You didn't have the courage to
meet her the next day, did you?
- You coward.
- Screw you!
(GUNSHOTS)
- We're not open.
- I wanted to see you.
Why? Because you weren't big enough
of an ass the last time I saw you?
- Selina...
- I don't have time for this, Bruce.
Something happened.
- I need to talk to someone.
- 0kay, then go find Alfred.
Oh...
You did, and he wanted nothing
to do with you.
Smart guy, Alfred.
- Can you at least hear me out?
- No, Bruce.
Because Ivy's out there
killing people
and I need to find her and stop her.
So whatever problem
you have going on right now,
you need to figure it out.
I mean, say sorry to Alfred.
'Cause I'm sure whatever happened
was your fault.
According to my spies.
Sofia and Jim
were carrying out an affair
till Jim ended it.
So, technically.
Your ex has been sleeping with your
dead husband's mafiosa Sister...
Okay, I get it.
If Sofia was sleeping
with the captain of the GCPD,
it was a power play. And it failed.
I'm her next step.
Why don't Ijust give her
what she wants?
Power over Jim Gordon.
You would do that?
I'm not trying to get back at Jim,
though he deserves it.
Myjob is to make sure that
the people of The Narrows are safe.
And Iwill do everything
in my power to ensure that.
What?
Lee, I...
I...
I have to leave.
- Harvey. Harvey, come on, buddy.
- Where am I?
You were hypnotized.
I need you to focus.
Did Ivy give you any clue
about who she's targeting next?
I can't believe I let her get to me.
Hey, you wanna help? Here's how.
Did she say anything?
Something about,
"They get rich by murdering plants."
So she's targeting
a group of rich people.
At her place, she was trying on
fancy clothes, fancy shoes.
A party?
She said she had big plans.
Couldn't be late.
- Yeah, black tie.
- No, no, no, come on.
Fancy schmancy, like a charity
for hobos or something.
Wayne Foundation's
annual dinner is tonight
over at Gotham Square.
AII right. Get the strike force.
Iwant full body armor,
gas masks, nonlethal rounds.
To fight plants?
When Ivy got me, she was hypnotizing
a bunch of low-end muscle.
Go.
We could really use you there, Harv.
Jim, she got in my head.
I really...
I just don't trust myself right now.
AII right, you can help out here.
Man the phones.
Hey, Jim.
I spent too long
putting this all on you.
What happened between us.
The fact is I only got
myself to blame.
I'Il call.
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
And now, ladies and gentleman.
Please welcome to the stage
our host Bruce Wayne.
(APPLAUSE)
Good evening.
Welcome to the third annual dinner
for the Thomas and
Martha Wayne Foundation.
This year we disbursed $4 million...
Um...
We disbursed $4 million and, uh...
My parents spent their
lives helping people.
I was so proud of them, and I always
wanted them to be proud of me.
And then I saw them get murdered.
I survived because someone in
my life kept me going.
He's been everything to me.
A teacher,
a protector.
He's been a father to me.
I hope...
I hope he can see that.
And give me another chance.
Thank you.
(APPLAUDING)
That meant a great deal.
But I can't help you.
Not until you accept
who you really are.
I know who I am,
I've seen what's inside of me.
Darkness and anger?
But what's beneath that?
It's a heart that feels pain.
Your heart is what makes you
want to help other people.
Your heart is your strength.
Deny the darkness and you deny that.
But accepting that is something that
you must do on your own.
Do you understand me?
I was stupid for reaching out.
WOMAN: That was quite a speech.
Hello all.
I'm Ivy Pepper.
- (CROWD GASPS)
- No, no, no, please.
Stay seated.
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
RIDDLER: Can I just say?
This is crazy!
Well, this whole thing
was your idea.
And you're the smart one,
as you always tell me.
Veryfunny.
Okay, fine! Fine!
You win!
- What?
- You win.
You beat me.
Is that what you wanna hear?
That is very nice.
But I still have to do it.
Wait! Wait!
Wait! What if there's a way
to do this where nobody gets hurt?
I don't believe you.
S0 you're just going to kill yourself
without hearing me out?
I'm telling you, Ed.
There is a way to save Lee
without killing yourself.
Or killing us.
I'm listening.
Aren't these crimson flowers lovely?
You're a handsome man.
But you want more from life.
I can feel it.
(CHOKING)
Bruce, is Ivy Pepper in there?
BRUCE: Ivy?
No, I didn't see her.
(WOMEN SCREAMING)
Get out of here.
Let's
GORDON: Breach that door.
We
Are going to turn this room
into the most gorgeous garden
the world has ever seen.
AII you have to do
is take a deep breath.
Oh,
a volunteer.
- (CURTAINS RUSTLING)
- (GRUNTS)
GCPD!
Drop your guns. On the ground, now!
Kill everyone.
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (SCREAMING)
You got this, I'm going after Ivy.
(ELECTRICAL BUZZING)
(GRUNTING)
I'm getting you out of here.
Come on, let's go.
Listen, listen.
People need your help.
This is who you are.
MAN: Watch the door.
I'm gonna go look for him.
Where'd you go, punk?
You can run, but you can't hide.
(GRUNTING)
GORDON: Hey! Hey!
'°'°n it!
'Nol
(GASPING)
Hey. HBV-
(SIREN WAILING)
(HELICOPTER HOVERING)
SELINA: You hear the news?
"Crazy Ivy Pepper attacks
the Wayne Foundation dinner."
I'II be honest. The evening didn't
turn out quite the way I'd hoped.
(SCOFFS)
You mean you didn't
get to kill everyone in there?
Something like that.
You got out.
Made it back here.
You always were the survivor.
No, you taught me that, Selina.
What's in the bag, Ivy?
It's the last of the Lazarus Water
I stole from Wayne Enterprises.
So you can go
and make more plants to kill people?
Yeah, that ain't gonna happen.
Are you gonna stop me, Selina?
You're gonna remind me
of the old days?
- Tell me I'm not this person?
- (CHUCKLES)
No, I think we're past words now.
(GROANS)
Well,
Selina Kyle
turns out to be the hero.
I'm no hero.
(GRUNTING)
One scratch is all it takes, Selina.
And there's no antidote this time.
And there's no more
jumping across rooftops
for little dead Selina.
I'II keep that in mind.
You're gonna
have to fight me, Selina.
You can't run forever.
I wasn't running. (PANTING)
I was getting this.
This is what you're gonna use
to make all your little plants?
So, I guess it's safe to say
that I shouldn't drop it.
Stop, Selina.
I will let you leave.
Let me?
(SNORTS)
You're not gonna turn me. into
some geranium-type thing?
That's so generous.
No!
How can you side with them?
AII the people who hurt us.
You think they're innocent?
They're gUiW-
Every person in this city,
they spew out poison.
How are you not choking on it?
The only thing that I'm choking on,
Ivy, is your insanity.
(GRUNTS)
You shouldn't have done that.
Now, you're gonna die.
Ivy, look down.
- Well?
- Yeah.
S0, what happens now?
We kill each other?
That's an option.
You always did think
you were better than me.
That's not true. Iwas your friend.
We were friends, Ivy.
You said so yourself.
That was a long time ago.
I'm a different person now.
This isn't what I want.
Don't get in my way again.
MAN: Lift your hands up.
Got any weapons?
I'd almost think this wasn't
going to be a friendly conversation.
Just being careful.
- They're clean.
- 0kay.
Smart lady.
So, you said you wanted 30% of
everything in The Narrows?
What if I told you I had something
more valuable to offer?
Such as?
Jim Gordon.
I know crimes he's committed
no one else does.
It would give you control over him.
Surely that's worth more
than 30% of this.
I have my own dirt on Jim Gordon.
But you can't use it.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be sitting
there threatening me,
would you?
Soña?
Take my deal.
I have a better way to
bring Gordon around.
'(GROANS)
- No! No!
Stay with me, stay with me.
(SCREAMS)
You're never gonna
get out of here alive.
My people are going to kill you.
Your people?
Who do you think planted these guns?
You can come out.
How you doing, Doc?
(SAMPSON LAUGHS)
I'm having Sampson run The Narrows.
You should have killed me
when you had the chance.
The fact that you didn't told me
everything I needed to know.
(LEE GRUNTING)
Since we're family, I'm only
going to do one hand.
(SCREAMS VIOLENTLY)
SOFIA: Throw her on the streets.
(HAMMER CLATTERING)
Let The Narrows see their queen.
(LEE WHIMPERING)
REPORTER: The scene here remains
Iargely under control,
but Ivy Pepper remains at large.
Now inside we have
a team of investigators...
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Yeah.
What?
Where is she?
Sir?
Excuse me?
Are you family?
I'm a cop.
She wouldn't tell us who did it.
She doesn't have to.
(ALARM BUZZING)
Arkham doesn't get many volunteers.
You do know who I am, right?
Criminally insane
pretty much covers it.
Read.
And sign.
I'II be back.
I hate that you were
right about this.
But it'll keep her safe.
Hey. Ed?
What has two eyes but can't see?
(SIGHS) This again.
Two needles.
Half of Mississippi, who cares?
You should, Ed.
(DOOR BUZZING AND OPENING)
I knew you'd come.
I knew you'd understand my letter.
How did you know I'd be...
What are you talking about?
I'm not talking to you, Ed.
I'm talking to him.
(LAUGHS)
He read my letter.
Read the first word of each sentence.
"Please bring Ed to Arkham,
so I can set you free."
What has two eyes.
But can't see what's
happening in front of him.
- Ed Nygma!
- No.
I came here to save Lee.
He read my letter.
You...
Yo u', e wrqng'
lam Ed!
Edward Nygma, that is it!
Lee believes in me.
She sees me for who I am.
But I see him,
- Ed.
- No.
Lee Thompkins may have made
Ed strong,
but I see the other you.
One whose name I wouldn't speak.
But because he has earned it
and because I need him,
- I'm saying now.
- No!
- Please. please don't.
- I need you.
Please...
Riddler.
(GASPING)
Shall we get to work?
(BOTH LAUGHING)
So?
How'd you make it off the roof then?
Afire escape on the next building.
Why'd you run from Gordon?
I mean, you could've told him,
it was you.
I don't know.
I just couldn't.
I'm going to help people, Alfred.
[And if that means accepting
even] part of myself, good and bad,
then I will.
Ido.
It's what my parents would've wanted.
Your parents would've
been very proud of you.
I'm proud of you.
Alfred?
If y0u'd
need a ride back to Gotham,
I can drive you.
I'm not going anywhere, sir.
I'm home.
Congratulations.
I heard you saved the day.
Good job.
There's a reason you're
captain and I'm a
50-year-old screwup,
pouring shots for barflies.
There's a reason, all right,
but it's not what you think.
I screwed up, Harv.
I screwed up bad.
And I'm gonna need your
help to make it right.
Sofia hired the Pyg.
And I knew.
I knew...
And I covered it up.
And now, I'm gonna take her down.