GORDON: Previously on Gotham...
The infected are being killed
all over the city.
RA'S: I'm the one you seek.
I am Ra's al Ghul.
This man is your past...
Now, embrace your future.
(YELLING)
RA'S: Use the waters, Bruce.
(COUGHS)
PENGUIN: You were the one time
I let love weaken me.
I want you around as a constant reminder
to never make that mistake again.
(SCREAMS)
I heard about Alfred.
Is he gonna be okay?
You don't give a damn about Alfred, and
you sure as hell don't care about me.
I know you better than that.
I thought you did.
GORDON: Jonathan Crane's father
made a toxin
from the adrenal glands of his victims
while they experienced terror.
(SCREAMING)
- What do you want?
- I'm tired of just surviving.
I want more.
(GLASS SHATTERS)
I'm sorry, Alfred.
I've been trying to find
who I am for so long.
Who am I supposed to be?
Money! Now!
ALFRED: You need to find your true north
and let that guide you.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Money! Now!
(WOMAN EXCLAIMS)
Hurry up. All of it! Give me the ring.
BRUCE: You have one chance. Walk away.
Who's this?
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
License. I got a license.
(SINGING)
Never gonna give you up
Never gonna let you down
Never gonna run around and
desert you
Never gonna make you cry
Never gonna say goodbye
(CROWD CHEERING)
(CROWD GASPING)
Nobody move!
Jewelry, watches, wallets!
MAN: You know the drill. Let's go.
- We want it all.
- MAN: Let's go.
- Hey, you.
- Come on. Nice. Thank you.
Ah.
- Jackpot.
- Let me see that.
MAN: All the money.
(SCOFFS)
Cheapskate, huh?
(WHISTLES)
Come on.
Excuse me.
Hi.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
That's Victor Zsasz.
I know who it is.
What do you want?
Oh, I was just passing by,
heard the ruckus.
You know you can't
commit a crime in Gotham now
without a license from Penguin, right?
Is that right?
Well, we just started it
so word's still getting out.
We ain't kicking half our take
to that little creep.
Well, that's a problem.
Maybe you ain't noticed,
but there's, uh, four of us
and only one of you.
- (CROWD GASPS)
- My finger!
(MAN GROANING)
No license, no crime.
Now, drop the loot, and blow.
You tell Penguin
he hasn't heard the last of this.
GUEST: And stay out.
(CROWD MURMURING)
I can't thank you enough.
Don't bother because,
you see, those guys...
They do have a license.
Mazel tov.
(CROWD SCREAMING)
Seriously?
Best wedding ever.
You know, we appreciate all you've done.
Do you?
Three months ago,
following the Tetch incident,
this city was in flames.
I came to you and offered
to cut crime in half,
and I delivered.
Violent crime is down 57%.
But now you want to, uh, literally
unionize crime.
- But we can't possibly...
- Quiet!
(EXHALES)
I remember when I sat there
in the mayor's chair.
I do not envy you.
Nor you.
Commissioner of Police
in a city notorious for crime.
That's why I wanna help.
But...
We are fully aware of all you've done.
Are you?
What do you think really happened
to those hordes of criminals
who once prowled our streets?
- I'll tell you. I hunted them down...
- No, no, no...
I made Gotham safe.
Me.
But this is Gotham City,
there will always be crime.
What I'm offering is crime
in the hands of professionals
and held to agreed-upon terms...
From which you'll profit.
God bless America.
You have a choice.
An era of calm, prosperity,
or a return to the good old days.
And they will return
with a vengeance.
We deny everything to the press.
Mmm.
What you need to worry about
is the GCPD.
When one of your officers
finds someone committing a crime,
if that person has a license,
they walk away.
Three percent each, uh, from the take.
Two to split between you.
- Two and a half.
- One!
- You...
- Yes, fine. Done.
Excellent.
Well, if you'll excuse me,
I have to go prepare
for the grand opening
of my new club, the Iceberg Lounge.
Good luck.
Smile, gentlemen, it's a new day.
(DOOR CREAKS)
- Hi, Frank.
- Good morning, Jim.
I'll get your coffee in a second.
Sure.
- Mornin'.
- Good morning.
Everything okay, Frank?
Everything's fine, copper.
I got a license.
Penguin-approved.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
(GRUNTS)
I'll take that coffee to go.
Come on, man.
Hey, what the hell are you doing?
I got... I got a license!
Yeah, and unless you shut up,
you're also gonna get a fat lip.
We got a problem?
HARVEY: Penguin guarantees
these numbers?
PENN: Mr. Cobblepot has negotiated them
with the Mayor and Commissioner.
These are damn good numbers.
But I already heard
from the Commissioner.
We have to play ball.
What the hell are you doing here?
Compliance with the licenses is key.
Mr. Cobblepot worries
about Detective Gordon.
- He has a history.
- My men
will honor the licenses.
You let me worry about Gordon.
Now get the hell out of my office.
(SCOFFS)
- Who was that?
- A, uh, dung beetle.
What's up?
I pulled this off of some guy
robbing my corner bar.
You're a homicide detective.
Isn't a stick-up a little JV?
I'm a cop. I see a crime, I stop it.
This is the second one of these
I've come across,
- and I'm not the only one.
- Yeah.
Harvey.
Harvey, we cannot let this slide.
Word's come down from the Commissioner,
you find someone with one of those,
they walk.
And before you get on your high horse,
three months ago,
this city was in a tailspin.
We survived because Penguin
took control of the underworld.
I'm not giving this city over
to Penguin.
I don't care what the Commissioner says.
What about your fellow cops, huh?
The past month, how many have been shot?
None.
I know the stats.
Jim, we will bust Penguin one day,
I promise you.
But this city has to get back
on her feet, please?
Harvey, I get that,
but every day the citizens
of Gotham look to Penguin
and not the GCPD to keep them safe,
the harder it's gonna be
to win them back.
You want people to trust cops,
there are better ways of doing it
than spitting in Penguin's eyes.
You see one of these,
you walk.
ALFRED: Bloody Penguin.
There must be some way
we can turn this against him.
Just stop. Stop, right there.
How does this fit into what we're doing?
What was the initial reason
that you popped on that mask,
and you went out there?
We agreed that I have to be ready
for when Ra's al Ghul returns.
You yourself said there's no substitute
for real world encounters.
But my point is, if that is our mission,
we must hold to it.
My finger was on the button
that released the virus.
- Oh, I see.
- I know I didn't press it,
but I feel responsible
for what happened.
And more than that, I can make
a difference in Gotham, Alfred.
- I know I can.
- And that is what we call
"mission creep," Master Bruce.
You're trying to achieve not one
but two objectives.
So, go on then,
which one is your priority?
It's messy, sir.
It's dangerous.
I hear you, Alfred,
but I can prepare myself for Ra's,
and make Gotham safer.
You have to trust me.
(DOOR CLOSES)
MAN: (OVER P.A.)
All inmates, this is your last call.
In five minutes, be sure
to make your way to your door.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
This way.
Hey, Warden Reed.
Warden Reed's the boss here.
(HUMMING OFF-KEY)
(INMATE WHISTLING)
(LAUGHS MANIACALLY)
(SCREECHING)
- Where is he?
- This way.
(MAN GRUNTING)
Back when I was an orderly in here,
he'd always talk about his dad,
and this formula he'd made.
Some sort of scare juice.
Made you see your greatest fear.
When we get a hold of that,
we don't got to worry
about Zsasz or Penguin,
or nobody.
What's wrong with him, anyway?
The toxin his father injected him with
overloaded Jonathan's fear response.
His mind created a sort of
bogeyman figure
and now it haunts him.
I find it very useful
for controlling him.
Jonathan, you're going with these men.
- What? Wait, where are you taking me?
- Just wanna give someone a little scare.
Excellent.
(BIRD SQUAWKING)
(PANTING) Yeah,
that's all my dad's stuff.
But, look, I can't be here
after dark, please.
I really... I cannot be here after...
You were your daddy's
little assistant, weren't you?
You helped with the experiments.
Some, but I don't know everything.
Now you're gonna
take your daddy's notebooks,
and make as much of that
fear juice as I say.
And so you don't get lonely,
the boys here brought you a friend.
CRANE: No.
(SCREAMS) No! Stop!
No, you don't understand! Stop!
No, you don't understand!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Good morning, ladies and gentlemen.
May I have your attention, please?
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
All the money, now!
Give it to me! All of it!
Hey, you have a license?
(SCREAMS)
Look at me.
(ROARING)
(SIREN WAILS)
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
MAN: Fiery demons. Demons.
Fiery demons, demons.
Demons, yeah. We'll catch 'em.
- Get him out of here. Go, go, go.
- Fiery demon.
Hey.
Did Penguin issue a license for this?
Why are you asking me?
Best of my knowledge, no.
Then why do something so public
unless you're trying
to send Penguin a message?
I hope the message was, "Please send
Victor Zsasz down here to kill me."
Because that's exactly
what's gonna happen.
- Not if I find them first.
- Hey.
You asked me to stop
busting crooks with licenses.
This gang didn't have a license.
And you're gonna find them before Zsasz
just to prove that GCPD still matters?
That's not thumbing your nose
at Penguin?
- Fire me.
- Hey, don't tempt me.
You got a lead?
The victims, the way they're acting,
their terror reminds me
of Crane's formula.
You think someone's using
the fear juice?
It ain't him, he's dead, remember,
not that that matters much
in this town anymore.
He's dead, his son isn't.
REED: Jonathan Crane's
condition is fragile.
I'm afraid he can't see anyone,
certainly not the two men
who killed his father.
Yeah, so, uh, how many loonies you got
in this joint?
Four hundred and thirty-six total.
We mustn't call them loonies.
Of course not.
(DOOR BUZZES)
How about staff
that had access to Crane?
Any of them not show up for work?
All present and accounted for.
- You don't wanna check?
- I don't need to.
See, that's impressive,
'cause I run a precinct
and if half of my cops didn't show up,
I'd be none the wiser.
- It's true. He wouldn't.
- Clearly we have
different professional standards.
(EXHALES SOFTLY)
Jonathan Crane's father created a toxin
that makes people see their
greatest fear.
This morning, it was used to rob a bank.
How is that my problem?
HARVEY: Let me explain it to you.
See, whoever robbed the bank,
they challenged Penguin,
and all we have to do is tell Penguin
that you're involved,
and he'll send Victor Zsasz
down here to talk to you.
Jim, how would you describe Victor?
Victor Zsasz...
A homicidal maniac and sadist.
A homicidal maniac and sadist
of the highest professional standards.
So you can talk with us here and now
or you can talk to Victor.
They threatened me. I had no choice.
We want a name, putz.
HARVEY: I knew it rang a bell.
Grady Harris.
Ran a crew a few years back.
Him and his cousin Merton.
Couple of cowboys from the sticks.
Grady!
GCPD!
(GORDON GROANS)
(HARVEY GROANS)
Well, well.
Look at what we got here.
What's wrong with you pigs?
Harassing honest fellows like us,
when there's real criminals out there.
You robbed a bank in broad daylight.
That don't make you a criminal?
I'm an outlaw. Outlaws have a code.
(GRUNTS)
Criminals, they'll take everything.
They'll take a man's livelihood.
Like the Penguin and his licenses.
But we're gonna show him, you'll see.
Penguin wouldn't give you a license
if you begged him
till the cows came home,
you stupid hick.
You're lucky I'm not the Penguin.
He'd gut you right here.
We're better than them!
Take care.
Pigs.
(CHUCKLES)
(LOCK CLICKS)
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey, check it out.
MAN: Babe, lost?
Ooh.
Looking for company?
(MEN MURMURING)
She all by herself.
Just let me go, okay?
Not a chance.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
- (WHIP CRACKS)
- (MEN GRUNTING)
(GRUNTING)
Don't turn your back on a guy
unless you're sure he's down.
(PANTING)
Otherwise, not bad.
Does this mean we can get pizza?
(GRUNTS)
I'm just saying,
you steal my pepperoni again,
- I'll break your fingers.
- So you're saying,
do steal your pepperoni again.
I come in peace.
You ladies were not easy to track down.
Then again, I can see
why you don't advertise.
Didn't you used to be rich?
That was before your boss stole my club.
Well, you murdered his mom
and tried to kill him.
So, call it even?
Is there a reason you're here?
Know about these?
The boss can't have you
operating on your own.
Now, he could just kill you,
but he figures it's time
to let bygones be bygones.
How big of him.
Tomorrow night's the opening
of his club,
come by, kiss the ring,
get your license.
Is that pepperoni?
Goes without saying,
this is one of those
"or else" kinda deals.
Later.
- We got to find a new place.
- Why?
If we join Penguin,
we can at least get work.
I came to you
because I wanted to move up.
And look around,
we're barely making it.
I'm not working for him.
Now, pack.
BRUCE: Detective Gordon.
Bruce.
I didn't hear you.
What happened?
Ah. Nothing. Harvey and I
were tracking a gang.
We let ourselves get surprised.
What brings you down here?
I found this when I was in the city.
Wasn't sure what to do with it.
One of Penguin's licenses.
Apparently, crime is legal now.
And you're going along with that?
Not really.
There's a number on the license.
I was thinking Penguin must have
some sort of master list.
Connecting the crime and the criminal
to the license issue.
List like that would tell you
not only who committed that crime,
but crimes that haven't even
happened yet.
Unfortunately, the judges
are going along with the licenses,
and trying to track down
who in Penguin's organization
keeps the list
would set off too many alarms.
I see.
But you haven't given up.
You just said
you were out tracking a gang.
It's different.
This gang isn't licensed.
But Penguin will come after them,
if he hasn't already,
and when he catches them,
it'll be more proof
that Gotham doesn't need the GCPD.
Sorry, it's been a long day.
So, why not use Penguin
to lead you to them?
If I could figure out
how to do that, I would.
It was good to see you, Detective.
You should come by the house for dinner.
Yes.
I'd like that.
How about we grab a bite...
Tonight.
Exclusive but welcoming.
Urbane and edgy.
Tonight's opening
will establish the Iceberg Lounge
as Gotham's newest place to see,
and be seen.
And you say you acquired the club
from Barbara Kean?
Is that a question?
It's just no one's seen her
for months, and...
Barbara Kean's whereabouts
are not my concern.
This was The Sirens club.
It is now mine.
MAN: Mr. Cobblepot,
there's a rumor going around
about criminals being given licenses.
The rumor is you're issuing them.
Tell me, what is the crime rate
in Gotham?
We're at historic lows.
Historic lows...
You know, Augustus Caesar once presided
over the longest period of peace
and prosperity the world has ever known.
It was called the Pax Romana.
Perhaps one day, this will be known
as the Pax Penguina.
That's not a denial.
We're here to talk about my club.
Your readers will find this interesting.
Ivy?
(REMOTE BEEPS)
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
That's Edward Nygma.
Turns out, Ed had
a very rare brain disease,
and there was only one option,
to freeze him and wait for the cure.
In his final lucid moments,
he begged me,
"Oswald, do not hide me away.
"Put me out with the people."
It was the least I could do.
Anyone tell him he was being frozen?
I have affidavits from his doctor
if you would like to see them.
No, thanks.
Well, Jim.
I'm rather busy,
so whatever your business is...
I came to tell you you're a fraud.
The gang that has Crane's fear toxin,
they're not afraid of you.
Others will find out.
That's how it begins.
You've had a nice run, Oswald,
but it's over.
Oh, Jim, it's so hard to admit
when you've become irrelevant.
Let me tell you what's gonna happen.
I'm going to find this gang
and I'm going to crush them.
And everyone will see
that it is Oswald Cobblepot,
the Penguin, who keeps Gotham safe.
Always good to see you, old friend.
As he prepares for the opening
of the Iceberg Lounge,
Oswald Cobblepot announced
that he would destroy the gang
that attacked
Gotham First National Bank yesterday.
He described them as
cowards and pond scum.
(SIGHS)
Penguin's goin' down tonight.
- You finish that new batch yet?
- Yes.
Now, can you please...
Can you please get rid of that, please?
- What, you and him ain't gettin' along?
- Please, just get rid of it.
Listen, I got to do some things tonight,
but I think you guys should
spend some time together. Huh?
We all have our fears to face.
(WHIMPERING)
Stop! Stop! Please, stop!
Please! No!
Stop!
(BANGING ON DOOR)
Let me out!
Remember how you accused me
of being a slave to my emotions?
No more.
I have banished those feelings.
And look how I have risen.
But at what cost?
I wonder which of us is frozen.
Him.
He's, like, totally frozen.
Ivy, go somewhere else.
All right,
I want two unmarked units
at street level
and another two teams with me and Harvey
watching the entrances to the club.
The moment that gang arrives, we move.
You heard the man! Suit up, let's go!
Can we count on them?
Let's see. You tricked Penguin
into baiting the gang to attack his club
hoping to arrest them
before they cause mass panic
only so you could embarrass Penguin.
So I would say, yeah, they're about as
dependable as any other part
of this cockamamie plan.
Thanks, I'll get the gas masks.
Please, let me out!
SCARECROW: Jonathan.
Let me out!
SCARECROW: Jonathan!
(ROARING)
- So, you guys work for Penguin, huh?
- It ain't like that.
- Sure.
- Come on, Gordon.
Since Penguin's been cracking down,
life's been good.
Why you gotta rock the boat?
What happens when he starts giving out
licenses for murders?
Huh? What then?
- I'm wasting my breath, aren't I?
- Pretty much.
All right, then.
Who wants it first?
(JAZZY MUSIC PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Mr. Wayne. Mr. Pennyworth.
- I am so glad you could make it.
- It's our pleasure.
Congratulations.
We were just admiring your frozen mate.
Is he still alive in there?
I fear we may never know.
But you'll know when
you finally thaw him out,
when they discover
a cure for his disease.
Oh, yes, then, of course.
I wanted to personally thank you
for everything you've done
for this city.
Thank you, Mr. Wayne.
So...
Can I ask about the licenses?
A little discretion, if you would,
Master Bruce?
Everybody's talking about it, Alfred,
I just want to know how it works.
So, does someone come to you and say,
"I want to rob a bank"?
Now, Bruce, if I didn't know any better,
I would think
that you wanted me to implicate myself.
Anything you say stays between us.
First, let me ask,
you would be agreeable
to the idea of licensed crime?
If crime had been licensed
and controlled three years ago,
my parents would still be alive.
Exactly so.
Well, between us,
I have nothing to do
with the licenses directly.
I provide the guidelines while Mr. Penn
handles all of the details.
Now, would you excuse me?
- Well done, sir.
- Thank you.
Now we know who has the list.
The next step is...
Selina.
Where's your babysitter?
It's kind of a package deal.
Yeah, well, he's got me.
Is that good enough or not?
Actually, we're both in.
- I should pat you down for weapons.
- Sure.
- If you wanna lose a hand.
- It was worth a shot.
I'll tell the boss.
See ya.
You were worried about me.
(DOOR OPENS)
Hey, man,
I've been looking all over for you.
Ooh, ouch.
Think we can forget about backup.
I see you talked to some of your
fellow officers.
- Probably not a bad thing.
- How's that?
Guys get to let off steam,
resentments don't fester.
Next time, you can get punched
in the face.
This beautiful mug, no one would dare.
Let's go.
All right, once inside,
get Zsasz and Penguin first,
and then go crazy.
I still don't see Penguin.
PENGUIN: Hello!
I'm guessing that gas isn't faster
than a bullet, what do you think?
Jim Gordon
and his ham-fisted manipulation.
He thought he fooled me.
You wanna do 'em here or downstairs?
- Might be a little loud in here.
- Neither.
I have something special planned
for them.
What do you want, Bruce?
You knew I'd follow you.
Just like I knew you'd come up here.
You don't know anything about me.
I wanted to apologize
for what I said at the hospital
when you came to visit Alfred.
You were making a kind gesture.
You wanna talk to me, come up here.
My point is, I'm sorry.
Yeah, you were a jerk.
I saw you arrive with Tabitha Galavan.
I'm not sure I'd choose her as a mentor.
Wow.
That means absolutely nothing to me.
Selina...
Oh?
You wanna say something?
It's a lovely dress
you're wearing tonight.
(APPROACHING FOOTSTEPS)
Honestly, you two,
why can't you just go to the cinema
like normal teenagers?
And, Master Bruce, we got
a bit of a situation downstairs, sir.
What sort of situation?
Ms. Kyle.
PENGUIN: For the past three months,
I have given this city
a tranquility it has never known.
Now, I would like to ensure that peace
for the future.
In the weeks to come,
you will hear whispers
about what's happening
on the streets of Gotham.
All you need to know is
without me, this is what you get.
Men who want to bring fear
back to our city.
Who promise a return to the old days.
So, tell your families,
tell your friends,
it is Oswald Cobblepot
who keeps them safe.
Not the GCPD.
You're welcome.
I have my things in the car,
we can stop them in the parking garage.
Absolutely not, Master Bruce.
Alfred, Penguin's gonna take
those men out and kill them.
Undoubtedly so.
But, as you said before,
you can make a difference.
There is time for masks,
and there is a time for Bruce Wayne.
PENGUIN: Do you know
what's going to be done to you?
Wait!
I want to know what
you're gonna do with those men.
You need not concern yourself with that.
Are those men going to be turned over
to the police?
(CHUCKLES)
Earlier tonight, you thanked me
for making the city safer.
Now, how do you think that happened?
I do the dirty work no one else will.
I understand.
But I'm asking you,
turn those men over to the police.
You're young.
You have a good heart.
No.
Enjoy your party, Penguin.
You little twerp.
(PEOPLE GASPING)
- (GUN COCKING)
- (GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
(GASPING)
(DISTORTED) What's wrong?
You scared?
(SCREAMING)
(DISTORTED LAUGHTER)
(GRUNTING)
No!
(LAUGHING)
GORDON: Hey!
(THUDS)
You're under arrest.
By order of the Gotham City
Police Department. Cuff him.
(PENGUIN GASPS)
(GASPING)
Help me. Help me.
(SOBBING)
HARVEY: Penguin
ain't gonna be too happy.
Screw him.
I'm just worried
about finding Jonathan Crane.
If he's out there
with access to his father's formula...
Relax, we'll find him.
Wouldn't expect too much help
from these parts, though.
There's good cops out there.
They just need reminding.
(CARS HONKING)
BRUCE: You have a list
of all the licenses you've given.
I want it.
I... I can't.
Penguin, he'll...
(GASPS)
(EXHALES SHAKILY)
(GLASS SHATTERS IN DISTANCE)
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(ALARM RINGING)
MAN 1: What about the alarm?
MAN 2: Forget it.
We got a license, remember?
(GLASS SHATTERS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(GLASS CRACKLING)
Oh, no.
What the...
(DOOR CRASHES)
OFFICER: GCPD.
Gotham Police, you're under arrest.
Crane, you got to make more
of that fear gas.
We got to get Merton out of jail.
Crane!
Crane?
(DISTORTED) Jonathan Crane
isn't here anymore.
(GROWLS SOFTLY)
It's just the Scarecrow.
(SCREAMING)
(ROARING)