NARRATOR: Previously on Gotham:
- Listen.
- There are things I need to do.
- If you stay, I stay.
VICTOR:
My name is Victor Zsasz.
I'm here for Jim Gordon.
Everybody out.
There's not a single cop in the city
who'll help you. I won't help you.
I'm not leaving.
You don't have to join me.
I'm doomed anyhow.
I might as well join the good guys.
FISH: I ain't looking for no girl.
I'm looking for a weapon.
Excuse me.
You want to start a war over this punk?
The little guy amuses me.
FALCONE:
Why go to war over trifles?
We'll let you have him. Our gift to you.
[PANTING]
Oh, God.
[GRUNTING]
Ripped By mstoll
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
BULLOCK:
Ugh. Hell of a way to start the day.
- I mean, I just cleaned this.
- Harvey.
Hey. Uniforms found the body.
No wallet, no ID, no watch.
He got beaten up pretty good.
I'm guessing the cause of death is that
gigantic gash on the side of his neck.
- You think? What's all the black on him?
- Ink? Paint?
- Mm. Good morning, Ed.
- Detective.
Going by overall coagulation,
I'd say time of death is midnight.
But he's only been here
for a couple hours.
Rats have just started on his ears.
Sneaky little buggers.
So not a mugging.
Muggers don't move the body.
Abrasions on his knuckles?
Put up a fight.
Yeah. Look at his suspenders.
I'm guessing some kind of finance guy.
Maybe it was an abduction-ransom thing
gone wrong.
He resists, ka-chunk! You wanna talk
to the uniforms who found the body?
Ah, you do it.
We should canvass the area.
A lot of homeless around here.
- I'll get some unis on it.
- I'll handle it myself.
- Hey, Joe. Go smoke somewhere else, huh?
BULLOCK: Come on.
Jim, that's what we got uniforms for.
Let them do it.
- And I'd rather handle it myself.
NYGMA: Detectives.
I'm guessing I should run all the prints.
Yeah, Ed, run the prints.
This one too?
Yeah, Ed. That one too.
It wasn't even a proper yacht.
It was more like a dinghy.
Can I help you?
What a lovely brooch.
Thank you.
May I have it? Heh.
I have a friend who would love that.
Excuse me?
[OSWALD CHUCKLES]
I'm sorry.
May I please have it?
You shouldn't have.
OSWALD:
I wanted to make a gesture.
I hope in time...
...we can be friends.
Friends? Hmm.
Sure.
Why not? What's done is done.
I'm so glad you feel that way.
Don Maroni wants us
to clarify terms.
Well, it's business as usual.
Maroni still has his drugs, his unions.
He pays tariff for the ports.
If he needs favors
from the cops or the mayor...
...Don Falcone will consider it.
And of course the families
still share Arkham.
And there's to be no blood spilled
on either side.
Not a drop.
Mm. Maybe just a drop.
[CHUCKLING]
Tsk-tsk-tsk.
[CHUCKLES]
Look at you.
Timothy...
...do you know this fellow
used to have your job?
Carried my umbrella
and thought it an honor.
Now look at him.
Has a seat at the table.
Things change, eh?
I've been blessed.
Perhaps I should open your gift.
[GASPS]
My goodness.
That is beautiful.
Now I feel awful.
- I didn't get you anything.
- No.
Thank you.
Mm.
- Sweet.
- That was uncalled for.
I brought you into my family
and I treated you like a son.
- And you betrayed me.
- For which I suffered.
Not enough. When I order some fool
killed, I expect him to stay that way.
- Your boss, Don Falcone, expressly said--
- Yeah, yeah.
He wants peace. He's the only reason
why your ass is still alive.
And if I were you, I would pray...
...for his good health.
[CHUCKLING]
Oh, I do.
I do.
Good.
Because remember...
...things change.
Convey my respects to your don.
Likewise.
Peace...
...friend.
[BELL RINGING]
ALFRED:
Come now, Master Bruce.
Had to happen sooner or later.
Is this really necessary?
Homeschooling is just as effective.
I can show you the data.
You need to be around children
your own age.
Why?
- Because you do.
- You know I despise that sort of answer.
Don't you miss your mates?
Not really.
I've always found them kind of childish.
That's what they're meant to be,
aren't they? It's what they do.
Don't you wanna be like a normal kid?
I'm not sure.
Define normal
and make a good case for it.
You're going to bloody school.
Now, start walking.
Good luck, lad.
GORDON:
Very sorry for your loss, ma'am.
Can you think of anyone
who'd wanna hurt your son, Coleman?
No, sir. Nobody.
He was a good boy.
Yes, ma'am. I can see that.
No arrests, an honest young man.
- What did he do for a living?
- He worked in a coffee shop.
When we found him, he was in a suit.
- Suspenders.
- He was looking for a job in finance.
He was very ambitious.
First in our family to go to college.
- Who would do this, sir? Why?
- We'll do our best to find out, ma'am.
Gordon's finishing up with the mother.
Nothing off the severed thumb.
None of the city's ERs have seen...
...any thumb-less guys.
- He went black market?
That's next on my list.
- How's Gordon?
- Angry.
How would you feel if every cop
in the building ran out on you?
Now they treat him
like he's got the plague.
Seeing him reminds them
of what cowards they are.
I'm sorry, cap. I didn't mean you.
Nope. You're right.
But he's gotta get over that.
Can't do this job alone.
Lucky he's got you.
Yeah.
[WOMAN GASPS]
So beautiful.
As soon as I saw it, I thought of you.
Such a good son.
Put it on, put it on.
Ah! What happened? Who did this?
Nobody. It's just a scratch.
Is your mother a fool? No.
Someone is being mean to my boy.
It's a tough business.
The restaurant business
is so tough these days.
- Why is that?
- My success makes people envious.
So tell the boss on these people.
This person isn't scared of the boss.
Not like they should be.
I don't know why.
I know.
When I was in school...
...Magda Himmelfarb
was so mean to me...
...and teacher did nothing.
Why?
Because such a good dancer, I was.
And Magda, with her nice hair
and her big bosoms...
...a cart horse!
I meant...
...why did the teacher do nothing?
Why you think?
Private lessons, they said.
I put stop to that.
You told on them.
Oh, no. I denounced Magda's father...
...to secret police.
[TRAP CLICKS THEN RAT SQUEAKING]
Ah!
Three weeks he's been turning
up his nose at my traps.
And now, now today,
a smidge of camembert...
...and Mr. Rat, he cannot resist.
No. Oh, can you?
Can you, my little greedy baby?
I found out your secret.
Yes.
Everybody has a secret.
[YELLING]
Morphine! Morphine!
- They teach you that in med school?
- Ugh.
Bullock.
Is that Kenny Suffield?
Smash-and-grab guy. Also a real hound
with the ladies. Who shot him?
I don't ask.
Me and my partner are doing all the
rounds of you black-market sawbones.
Guy we're looking for would've come in
early this morning, missing a thumb.
- Sorry.
- You'd tell us if you knew, wouldn't you?
I mean, that's the deal, right?
You give us info,
we let you keep operating.
That's a pun. Operating.
Bullock, black ink?
Just like on the victim?
Oh, doc...
Fine.
He came in about 3 this morning.
Didn't give a name
but this dropped out of his pocket.
- Sionis Investments.
- What did he look like?
Mid-20s, suit, suspenders.
Just like our dead guy.
Sorry, doc. This is Gordon.
I need an ambulance and
a black-and-white at 1856 Wilton--
Wait. Just a second.
Just get me Alvarez, will you?
Bullock. Bullock, what the hell, man?
I got a deal with that guy.
- Deal's off.
- But I told you everything.
- Yeah, after we caught you in a lie.
- He always lies.
You just squeeze him.
- You're screwing the rest of us.
- Yeah?
- How's that feel? You like it?
- Hey, enough! Enough!
I get it, I get it, huh?
Sons of bitches didn't have your back
when it mattered. Where was I?
I was there, remember? With Falcone
and the mayor, blaze of glory?
- Be nice for my sake.
- I am being nice.
Haven't you learned your lesson?
We're only alive
because Falcone let us live.
- You gotta go along to get along, Jim.
- No, I don't.
You think locking up Doc Scumbag there
is gonna make a difference?
I'm on your side, I proved that.
- Yeah, you did.
- So I'm asking you, please...
...let the doc out, and tomorrow...
...you and I will go check out
this Sionis Investments together.
All right, partner?
Sorry, Harv.
- This ain't right, Harvey.
- Alvarez, put a zipper on it!
[GUN COCKS]
- Jim.
- Barbara, what are you--?
I heard someone come in.
You didn't turn on the lights.
- You got out my spare?
- You were late. I got nervous.
Not the best idea to be handling a firearm
when you've been drinking.
I'm sorry.
Look...
...you've been through a lot.
It's over now.
I am scared, Jim.
Everywhere I go, I can...
I can feel that monster Zsasz
stalking me, and I...
He's not a monster.
He's just a man.
I won't let anyone hurt you.
How can you promise me that?
Tell me it'll be okay.
[SIGHS]
Tell me there really aren't any monsters.
Or just lie, if you have to.
There aren't any monsters.
When are we gonna get out of here?
That's up to you.
Morning.
Hi.
I didn't think you were up.
That last night was just nerves...
...and way too much to drink.
I said I wanted half your life,
and I've got it.
Leave the gun.
I wish it wasn't like this.
Do you really?
Ignore me. I'm just tired.
Go. Catch some bad guys.
Go get them.
Forensic examination by Edward Nygma.
8:42 a.m. G.C.P.D. morgue.
The room
is approximately 19 degrees Celsius.
I ate half a cranberry muffin earlier,
saving the rest for later.
What do a dead man, a cruise ship,
and an emu have in common?
Correct. Nothing.
Ever more curious.
MAN:
He what?
How many times have I told you
to stay the hell out of here?
But I discovered something--
You'll discover your butt on the
street if you keep doing this. Out.
Your loss.
You sloppy ignoramus.
Hi, Bruce.
Hi.
Brucey, how you doing?
Tommy, hey. I'm well. How are you?
You know, chilling.
So your mom and dad got killed, huh?
- Yes.
- Did you see the whole thing?
The blood and everything?
- Rather not talk about that.
- Just interested.
Never seen a real dead body.
Was there guts?
I'll be going to class now.
Forgive me, Mother, for I have sinned.
FISH:
Funny.
Feels weird meeting here.
You don't want anyone to see us together.
Falcone has his eyes everywhere.
So where are we?
I cook for him.
I sing to him. We go on walks.
I don't know whether I'm his maid,
his lover, or his mother.
Or all three. He cares about you.
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
Been inside his private office?
Yeah, a few times.
Inside the right bottom desk drawer
is a ledger.
Copy the last two pages.
It'll be locked.
You'll need a key off of his key ring.
Heh. How do I get that?
Behind you is a vial. Give it to him.
He'll sleep like the dead for two hours.
- It won't kill him, will it?
- Mm.
[CHUCKLES]
Liza, you haven't got feelings
for the old man, have you?
Not at all.
No, it won't kill him.
Killing him now would only create chaos.
I need to siphon his strength.
So when the time is right...
...taking over his organization
will be like slipping on a glove.
What if one of his men
catches me snooping?
Then you're probably dead.
You leave first.
[CHATTERING AND PHONES RINGING]
Something tells me
we came to the right place.
- You think?
- Mr. Sionis will see you now.
Ah.
Richard Sionis.
James Gordon.
This is my partner, Harvey Bullock.
How can I help you, detectives?
I don't have much time.
You know this man? Coleman Lawson?
He might have interviewed for a job.
Sorry.
Any of your employees
miss work yesterday?
Any of them show up
today with an injured right hand?
I don't take roll call, detective.
GORDON:
You mind if we check?
Perhaps you can tell me
what this is about.
Coleman Lawson was killed
two nights ago.
The man who did it
had your firm's card in his pocket.
There's a thousand ways
he could have gotten that.
What's with all the warrior baloney?
It inspires me.
High finance is a tough business.
In order to succeed,
you have to be a warrior.
No, you don't.
You have to be a good businessman.
Warriors fight wars. It's different.
So you fancy yourself a killer.
Have you killed people, Mr. Sionis?
- Only metaphorically.
- So all this is just juvenile play-acting.
Exactly. Thus speaks
a man who's seen actual combat.
You've killed people for real, haven't you?
True killers are easy to spot.
Yes, they are.
Why all the masks? A shrink
would say you're hiding something.
To the contrary.
A mask hides the face, but frees the soul.
A mask speaks the truth.
Deep. How come so many of your
employees have scars and injuries?
Our touch football games get very rough.
You're a liar, Mr. Sionis.
Such fire.
You must miss the battlefield
desperately.
I imagine killing gets quite addictive.
You murdered Coleman Lawson,
didn't you?
Prove it.
We will.
I'd give you a "good cop" routine,
but it's not in my tool kit.
G.C.P.D. Turn around slowly.
Let me see those hands.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Don't move.
[GRUNTING]
Should have waited for me.
[BELL RINGING]
Hey, Brucey.
It's Bruce. No Y.
No parents either,
so I can call you what I like.
Please get out of my way.
Snobby little jerk, isn't he?
For an orphan.
You're being very unkind.
I don't understand why.
Heh, boy, you're a weirdo.
Your mother must have--
Don't talk about my mother.
Oh, really?
Oh, is that Timothy?
We met at Fish Mooney's. Hmm?
I'm the fellow
who used to have your job.
I was hoping
to ask you a few questions.
- I don't know anything--
- Shh.
There'll be time for that.
First things first.
[THUDDING AND MAN GRUNTING]
BULLOCK: Most killers leave their prints
at the crime scene. Not you.
You left your whole thumb in the dead
guy's mouth. You got style. I like you, kid.
This is your last chance.
Once we walk out that door, it's over.
It was self-defense.
Course it was. Wasn't that what I said, Jim?
Didn't I say it was probably self-defense?
Talk.
Gordon's getting the rest of his statement.
Apparently it was part of the hiring process.
Sionis told the top
three candidates to fight it out.
They weren't supposed to fight
to the death--
This is unbelievable.
They signed confidentiality agreements.
They're accomplices to whatever happens.
- Do we know where the fight was?
- Some old office building.
He was taken there blindfolded.
Yes, Ed.
- Printer toner.
- Do you know what he's talking about?
The medical examiner's
report said it was black ink...
...but I did my own
exam and it was printer toner.
Also I pulled staples
from his shoulders...
...and found graphite chips
between his ribs.
He was killed in an office.
Yeah, we're kind of past that, Ed.
But thanks.
Is there something else?
Yes, it made me think of a case
from a year ago.
Young man, business suit.
Esophagus lacerated
from index cards shoved down his throat.
So I did some digging.
How many were killed
with office supplies?
Four. In the last three years.
Get that man to sign a confession.
Now.
I think we have a problem.
As counsel to Mr. Adams,
I advised him against speaking further.
Any statements he has made
will be considered...
...having been made under duress.
Uh-huh. How much is Sionis
paying him to take the fall?
Good day.
He showed up before
Adams could sign his statement.
Gotta figure out where
Sionis is staging fights.
I'll run all the buildings
he or his company owns.
- This make any sense to you?
- No.
But how is it any worse than the Goat
or Balloon Man?
When did this become normal
for this city? What changed?
Maybe nothing. It was always just below
the surface, only needed a spark.
What? Thomas
and Martha Wayne being killed?
I'm not blind, Gordon.
I know you're still looking into it.
But how could
their deaths have caused all this?
Why were they so important?
I think it's what they represented.
A different Gotham.
Decent. Hopeful.
Whatever it was, it's gone now.
When Zsasz came for you,
I should have stayed.
I told you to go.
That doesn't matter.
I should have stayed.
Let's get this guy.
Yeah.
[DOOR OPENS]
Tad late, Master Bruce. Oi.
- What happened?
- I'm fine.
What happened?
Someone spoke
disrespectfully about my mother.
Oh, did they, now?
I hope you broke
their bastard teeth for them.
No.
He's much bigger than me, and I'm
not good at fighting. Didn't hurt him at all.
Not at all.
Don't tell the school.
Not bloody likely.
BULLOCK:
Look at this. Sionis owns half of Gotham.
We'll split up. Focus on the buildings
that are abandoned or under construction.
This son of a bitch
is not getting away.
I'll say one thing. He has your number.
- What are you talking about?
- Sionis.
You may not have put down Cobblepot,
but you've got a demon in you.
You can call yourself a soldier...
...but all this fighting Falcone,
fighting other cops, you love it.
So when you find something
that seems remotely possible, call me.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Barbara. Everything all right?
Fine. I just, uh-- I wanted to check in.
Can we talk later?
In the middle of something.
Of course. I love--
[DIAL TONE]
[OPERA MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
MAN:
Hey.
Boss wants his tea.
It's almost ready.
[CLANGING]
G.C.P.D.
Anybody else here?
[TASER CRACKLING]
That would be a yes.
[CHATTERING]
Hey.
Ah.
Hi.
Girl's gotta shop.
ALFRED:
This is your father's watch.
Don't you lose it, now.
Tommy Elliot's house.
Don't you be scared.
I'm not.
I'm visualizing what I'm going to do.
Because if you don't want to do this,
there's no shame in it.
There would be immense shame in it.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
- What the hell are you doing here?
- We have unfinished business.
Listen, if you think you're--
- Are you crazy?
- Don't talk about my mother.
- Unh!
- Master Bruce!
Point well made, I think.
You all right, mate?
Any broken bones?
- He tried to kill me.
- That's right.
He did. He tried to kill you.
Just you remember that
next time you see him.
And you remember that I let him try.
Now, let's get some ice
on those knuckles.
What do you fancy for your dinner?
- Pizza.
- Pizza?
Superb choice, Master Bruce.
Jim, where the hell are you?
My list crapped out. Call me.
- Nygma, Gordon hasn't called in, has he?
- No.
But if the detective becomes the mystery,
then...
SIONIS [OVER SPEAKER]:
Wake up.
Detective Gordon. Wake up!
So, three of you
applied for a position at my firm.
I explained then,
you can use anything here as a weapon.
The last man standing gets the job.
However, tonight is special.
You see the man without the mask?
Whoever kills him is the victor.
Listen to me. I'm a cop.
So far none of you
have broken any laws.
SIONIS:
Let the games begin.
[BELL RINGS]
One last chance. Nobody move.
MAN: Oh, and I'll throw
in a million dollar signing bonus.
Oh, crap.
[GRUNTING]
Alvarez, I need help checking these
addresses. Gordon might be in trouble.
- Busy.
- I'll remember that next time...
...your wife calls,
asking where you are, you putz.
Collins, listen up, man.
Can I have some help?
Now listen up, you sons of bitches!
So you don't like Gordon. Fine.
He can be a total ass hat,
but he is still a cop.
And not one of you, not one,
stood up when he needed it.
That ain't happening twice.
I need help checking these addresses.
Now.
Give me a couple.
- Okay. You'd cover with my wife, right?
- Yeah.
[GRUNTING]
[ALL CHEERING]
[SWORD UNSHEATHS]
I knew you had a killer in you.
So where are your brother police?
Did they abandon you?
I don't need them.
[ALL CHEERING]
Seems like I'll have to
give myself the million dollars.
ESSEN:
Jim? Jim?
Jim!
Thanks.
You're welcome.
[SINGING]
If I die and my soul be lost
Ain't nobody's fault but mine
You better have
a good reason for being here.
Did you get what I asked for?
I want out.
No.
He's gonna find out.
Maybe not today, but soon.
Is it worth it?
You are rich. People are afraid of you.
Is that not enough?
No. It's not.
I grew up not too far from here.
One bedroom,
cold water, just me and my mama.
I used to sleep in a bed
behind a curtain.
It's where I would hide
when she entertained men.
And that's where I was
when he killed her.
One of Falcone's men.
They didn't like the service.
I hid there, silent, until morning.
With my mama two feet away from me.
That night I made a promise.
To get revenge.
To never again be powerless.
To never let any man...
...any man be over me.
This is about keeping
that promise to that little girl.
So, what's this about?
[SIGHS THEN CHUCKLES]
This is a thread.
I pull this and Falcone comes undone.
You're scared.
But I won't let anything happen to you,
and that's a promise.
I want you to say,
"I believe you, Mama."
I believe you, Mama.
That's my girl.
OSWALD:
The thing is, when I had your job...
...had someone asked me
what is Ms. Mooney's secret...
...I could have answered.
Ooh.
[CHUCKLES]
Timothy.
I think you're holding back on me.
Okay. I--
I might have heard her with Butch.
Talking about what? Whom?
Fal-- Falcone.
She said--
"Our friend with Falcone." That's it.
She was whispering. Please--
She has someone close to Falcone.
Of course.
Thank you.
No one can find the body.
TIMOTHY: No.
- We are at peace after all.
No. No, please. No, no!
[SCREAMING]
BULLOCK: Alvarez and Collins
are bringing in Sionis' minions.
Pansies tried to rabbit when they
saw you cuffing their boss. You okay?
Essen told me you made a speech.
- I wouldn't call it a speech.
- She said you called me an ass hat.
I did call you that.
Thank you.
For having my back.
Now and before.
Just try not to be
such a pain in the neck.
Makes my day harder.
You know, you were wrong.
What you said earlier.
It's not that I love fighting,
but I'm not afraid to either.
And if we don't fight for this city,
who will?
I'm not gonna stop, Harvey.
Falcone, the mayor,
every cop I know that's dirty...
...I'm gonna get them.
You should know that.
Go home, Jim.
You were listening tonight,
weren't you?
You gonna get in trouble, old woman.
Heard you telling that girl stories.
A lie with a heart of truth
is a powerful thing.
Go on. It's late.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hey, it's me. I'm coming home soon.
Everything's gonna be better.
I promise. I love you.
Hey, Gordon. You got a minute?
Can it wait? I'm on my way out of here.
Some uni's brought in a perp.
Claims to know you.
- Oh, yeah? What's the charge?
- B & E. Some fancy store uptown.
Pretty professional job.
Kid didn't even trip the alarm.
Kid? A boy or a girl?
Girl. Said to ask
if you'd been down any sewers lately.
Hey, detective.
Miss me?
I enjoyed it.
I enjoyed hurting him.
Of course you did.
He deserved it.
I'm so angry all the time.
Will it ever go away?
That I don't know.
Alfred...
...can you teach me how to fight?
Yes...
...Master Bruce.
Yes, I can.
Ripped By mstoll