Previously on Gotham...
- Hello.
- What's wrong with you?
I let him out of his cage,
and he helped me get out of mine.
You're him. The Riddler.
Hi, Lee.
Butch?
- You're alive.
- Huh?
Oh, Butch. I tried.
Tabby, I'm gonna find a way
to get back to the old me.
I promise.
Tell me about your mother, Jerome?
- Did she have any enemies?
- No.
And do you have any other family?
The circus is my family.
Now, to free the rest of our
cronies and blow this pop stand.
I could have killed Jerome
after he kidnapped me, and I didn't.
Any harm he does now,
I share a part of it.
I saw Jerome tonight.
He was looking for the name
of a school, St. Ignatius.
Stay the hell away from that madman.
I'll see you at St. Ignatius, Jim.
Sir.
Sir?
Can I help you?
My name is Bruce Wayne.
I'm looking for Jerome Valeska.
Has he been here?
I didn't have the pleasure
of meeting Mr. Valeska.
However, I did speak with his friend,
the one with the top hat.
- Jervis Tetch.
- Yes.
That's the fellow.
He was very polite.
What did he want?
The name of a student
who graduated St. Ignatius 10 years ago.
Xander Wilde.
Fine young boy. Very bright.
Did Tetch tell you
why Jerome was looking for him?
No.
But he did have a message
for you.
Listen to me. You're being hypnotized
by Jervis Tetch.
You don't wanna press that button.
But I have to.
- He's depending on me.
- Bruce!
Step away from him.
Please.
- Hand me the detonator.
- I want to.
But I can't.
Captain Gordon, look.
He's under Jervis' spell.
Oh!
Get down!
Hear ye, hear ye!
I'd like to officially
welcome you all to our first ever
Mandatory Brunch Meeting.
Now, I know what you're all thinking.
Why have I gathered
this legion of horribles?
That has a nice ring to it.
Write that down, will ya?
Well, back when I was in Arkham,
I came up with a plan
to turn this city into a madhouse.
Now I am on the cusp
of making that happen,
but I need help from all of...
Put all questions on ice until the end.
Danke schön.
Mr. Oswald.
Thank you for doing your part
in hosting us today.
Anything for an old friend.
Crane.
Where are we at with the...
You know what.
It's coming along dreadfully.
Oh, Pun-worthy. Excellent.
Freeze, Ice Man, you're our science guy.
We're gonna need a lab.
A big one.
Easy enough.
Mmm. Now, all we need
is Mr. Tetch to return
with some very important information.
Use the tongs, Carl.
You still haven't told us
how you're going to take over
the underworld.
Who says I wanna do that?
I'm an artist.
I just wanna paint the town crazy.
Once that happens, I could care less
how you horribles rip the city apart.
I'm in. Let's do this.
Well, not yet.
Nothing can happen until we have
our one last essential ingredient.
The one thing
that'll tie it all together.
Who is Xander Wilde?
I don't know.
Did Jerome say anything
at his uncle's diner?
Anything that could tell us
why he's going after him?
If I knew that, Captain,
I would tell you.
Would you?
How can I trust anything you say?
I told you not to come here
and you did anyway.
Damn it, you could have been killed.
All right, Captain,
I think you've made your point.
And you?
Did you know he was going after Jerome?
Indeed, I did, yes.
If he gets involved in this case again,
I'll press charges. We clear?
Come on, son.
Yo!
I just talked to an administrator.
Xander Wilde
was some kind of child prodigy.
Now he's a hotshot structural
engineer at Meyer and Hayes.
What does Jerome want with an engineer?
Maybe he wants him
to build him something.
Let's go.
I used to be a great whistler.
Mmm-hmm.
Um, yeah, hi.
I'm here to see Xander Wilde. And, no...
I don't have an appointment.
Don't bother going to security.
They're all...
Headless.
All right. If you would all
please look at the rendering,
you'll notice that there are several
interesting engineering problems
that present themselves. Mostly...
Oh, don't get up.
I won't waste too much of your time.
I've got a business proposition.
Tell me what I want to know
and you don't get turned inside out.
Please, don't... Don't hurt anyone.
Where is Xander Wilde?
- He's... He's not here.
- Yeah.
I'm not blind. Maybe you are.
Um, you know? Hmm?
No one does. He's never
set foot in this office.
Okay.
Oh, God!
We've never met.
I've only ever
communicated with him
through a proxy.
- Proxy?
- Yeah.
That slippery little sucker
thinks he can get away from me.
Where can I find this proxy, pray tell?
I'll tell you. I'll tell you.
Don't take the elevator!
Jimbo!
Old buddy, old pal,
it's great to see ya!
Drop the gun.
You are such a stick in the mud.
Give it up, clown boy!
Hey.
Knock, knock.
You were supposed to say, "Who's there?"
- Thank you, Francis.
- Take down their statements.
Hey, Jim. Same story all around.
No one knows Xander.
No one even met him.
Apparently, he had a proxy
who handled his dealings
with the company.
Hayes was the only one
who knew their identity,
but obviously, he's not talking.
So, we have to figure out
another way to find Xander.
I'm ahead of you. We looked into it.
No driver's license. No known
addresses. Guy's a ghost.
Everything that's happened
in the last 24 hours,
the breakout, Tetch,
it's all been about
Jerome finding this guy.
I don't think it has anything to do
with him being an engineer.
- This seems personal.
- Makes sense.
I mean, Jerome went to his uncle
to look for him.
Yeah, so how are they connected?
What's up?
Is that Wayne Plaza?
Take a look
at the initials of the engineer.
- "X.W." Xander Wilde.
- Uh-huh.
Looks like we're gonna have to go
talk to the kid.
He's gonna be thrilled to see you.
What time is it?
Riddle time!
That's right! It's riddle time
- at the Riddle Factory!
- The Riddle Factory!
Our first contestant is...
Lars.
From the now-defunct biker gang,
The Street Demonz.
It's been a rough go
of it lately, huh, Lars?
I've fallen on hard times.
But I'm damn happy
to be here with you, Riddler.
That's the narrow spirit I love.
Now, you know the rules.
I ask a riddle, you answer correctly,
you ask me one.
You win 'em both,
and you're walking out of here
with cold hard cash!
Lila.
Prepare the timer.
I am heavy forward, but backward
I am not. What am I?
Okay. I'm heavy forward...
But backward I'm not.
Okay, wait... Wait a minute.
No, no, I know this.
It's...
No, no, I know this. Um...
Wait, wait, wait.
It's the hour glass.
The answer is, "Ton." T-O-N.
Backwards I am, "Not."
Sorry, Lars.
Spin the wheel!
You hear them, Lars.
It's time to spin
the wheel of misfortune!
Spin the wheel!
Lila, please.
My personal favorite.
Rabid sack of rats.
Yeah!
All right, that's enough. Enough!
Doc Thompkins.
What brings Your Majesty
down to our rabble?
How are you doing, Ed?
Haven't seen you
since we put Oswald on ice.
Well, I'm doing far better
than Sofia Falcone,
from what I understand.
Whatever the hell this is, it's over.
I don't think so.
Ladies and gentlemen,
our queen has just informed me
she wants to shut us down.
How do you feel about that?
You hear that?
That's the sound of democracy.
The people have spoken.
And my name is The Riddler.
Okay.
You wanna be entertained?
Hold this, will you?
- Then I'll beat him.
- Oh!
You can't be serious.
You realize what happens when you lose.
I know. I spin the wheel.
But if I win, you shut this place down.
We have our next contestant!
Got any ice cream in there?
I've always had a soft spot
for Chunky Monkey.
I was wondering when you would come.
Me? That's very flattering.
So, tell me, Little Miss Proxy,
where is he?
I'll never tell you.
Hmm,
I don't know.
See...
I can be very persuasive.
See that?
Yeah. I was wondering about that.
You got, like, a big dog or something?
No.
That's how I'm going to transport you.
Hmm?
I've got him.
Butch?
I had heard you were different.
But I will be honest...
I like it.
What do you want?
I assume you've heard
about the Arkham breakout.
Well, I just came from brunch
with Jerome Valeska,
and let's just say
that he has plans for Gotham.
What kind of plans?
That part wasn't entirely clear.
Seemed to involve a great deal of paint.
No matter.
I have seen his kind come and go.
Jerome Valeska will flame out.
And in the rubble,
I will reclaim the underworld.
I could use a good man
like you by my side.
You must be all out of allies
to come looking for me.
Don't be modest.
With your brute strength and my brains,
we will be unstoppable.
I did that job.
I'm my own man now.
Really?
Because from where I am,
you look like a man who has nothing.
You'd be wise to watch
what you say to me.
- I'm not the same man you remember.
- And neither am I.
Look at the two of us.
We used to run this town. Together.
We were friends.
Look, you want your old life back,
so do I.
- We are the same.
- Wrong!
You can have your old life back.
I can't. Look at me.
Tabitha will never love me again.
Slaughter Swamp
turned me into a monster!
Now get out of here.
If I ever see you again,
I'll pop your head off like a flower.
Let me get this straight.
You tell us to stay out
of your investigation
and now you want our help?
- Subtle.
- We have reason to believe
your father met with Xander Wilde.
Well, if he did, he certainly
would have made a note of it.
What was the name
of that building again?
Wayne Plaza.
He was a meticulous note taker, Thomas.
He organized everything by project.
Let's see. Wayne Gardens...
Wayne Hospital...
Aha, here we go, Wayne Plaza.
All right.
Why, you're bang on the money
there, Captain.
Xander Wilde. Says he went
to meet him to finalize the plans.
No address, just the name
of the street, Ainslie Drive.
It's out past Buxton
by the old rock quarry.
This man
must've been very important
if my father went out of his way
to meet him alone.
I'm starting to think he isn't just
some recluse hiding from the world.
He's hiding from Jerome.
How interesting.
Oh! Oh,
you are incorrigible.
And then again,
you always were.
Wait. Or was that me?
Sometimes I get so confused, I...
I can't remember.
You didn't have to run away like that.
You see,
I would never hurt you,
Xander.
I love you.
I can't wait to see you.
Did you think about me?
I know that you did.
I'm gonna squeeze you until you pop.
Where the hell is the house?
James Gordon.
Here to see Xander Wilde.
So this whole joint's underground?
Mr. Wilde values his privacy.
How long has he lived here?
He finished construction six years ago.
- Echo, 496.
- Welcome, Miss Echo.
He'll see you now.
Thank you for seeing us, Mr. Wilde.
I expected you might come, Captain.
My God.
There's two of them.
May I put my hands down now, gentlemen?
Please?
Apologies, Mr. Wilde,
you took us by surprise.
It's understandable.
You can call me Jeremiah.
That's name my mother gave me.
You solved her murder,
and Captain Gordon, I owe you
a debt of gratitude for that,
and for putting Jerome in Arkham,
where he belongs.
He never mentioned you before.
No, I suppose you wouldn't know
from the letters my mother sent me,
he never spoke of me after I left.
Left where?
The Circus.
They hid me away to protect me from him.
See, we are always different,
Jerome and I.
From an early age, I showed
a proficiency for maths and design
and Jerome, mainly the mutilation
of alley cats.
On my 10th birthday,
he held a cake knife to my throat.
A few weeks later,
he lit my bed on fire.
It was like living in a nightmare.
My mother knew, eventually,
one day he would succeed, so...
One night, my uncle came to my room
while Jerome slept
and told me that he was taking me away.
I had no idea where,
but I kissed my mother goodbye,
told her I love her,
and I never saw her again.
He took you to St. Ignatius.
Got a new name, new life, where I was
finally able to live without fear.
But in my heart,
I knew one day Jerome would come for me.
Well, that day is today, pops.
We have reason to believe
Jerome knows where you are.
We need to move you to a safe location
until we can apprehend him.
That won't be necessary, gentlemen.
I've spent the bulk of my life
preparing for this eventuality.
I am safest here in my home.
Not anymore.
Jerome knows the name of your proxy.
He got it from your boss
just before he executed him.
I heard about Jerome
visiting Alan Hayes.
It's tragic.
But the proxy's name
I gave to Alan was a fake.
You're lying.
I beg your pardon?
There's something about this guy
that's fishy.
Security cameras outside were turned on,
so why are the monitors in here off?
I don't see why
that is any of your concern.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm a very busy man.
Yeah, I'm sure that you are.
Please don't touch that.
That's very sensitive equipment.
Oh, yeah. I'd say
that's pretty damn sensitive.
Ladies and gentlemen, a gauntlet
has been laid at the Riddler's feet.
Our leader, Doc Thompkins,
she thinks that she knows
what's good for you.
She thinks stapling a live barracuda
to someone's face
isn't damn good entertainment.
Just get on with the show, Ed.
Okay, enough! What time is it?
Riddle time!
What time is it?
Lila!
Prepare the timer.
I can be broken
without being held.
Given, and then taken away.
Some people use me to deceive,
but when delivered,
I am the greatest gift of all.
What am I?
You stumped?
Of course I am. You're the Riddler.
So, you give up?
No.
You're gonna give me the answer.
Really? How's that?
Because deep down, you want to.
So, that's your plan.
To appeal to the inner Ed.
You played the wrong hand, Doc.
Ed is gone,
and I will not be manipulated by you
the way that dope was.
I didn't manipulate him, I helped him.
No. No, you lied to him.
You promised to fix him.
And that pathetic dust mite
believed you,
causing me to be locked
inside of his feeble mind.
Okay, you have 10 seconds left
to find your answer!
So, prepare to lose.
But I know the answer now.
You just gave it to me.
What are you talking about?
You're right. I told Ed
I would fix him, and I didn't.
I broke my promise.
And that, Riddler,
is the answer.
A promise.
Well played.
We're only halfway through.
And I assure you, you will not stump me.
Boo.
You need to take us to your brother.
I can't do that.
What if he's nuttier than the other one?
I'm nothing like Jerome!
Do you want me to put you
in a cell next to his?
Because that is where this is heading.
And then what, Captain Gordon?
You couldn't hold him,
Arkham couldn't, I can.
And I will make sure
Jerome never escapes again.
No, no, no. Jerome comes with us.
And if you wanna
make this easier on yourself,
I suggest you stay the hell
out of the way.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
The loonies are outside.
No, no.
How'd they find me?
Must've followed Jerome.
We need to move. Now.
This is not good.
Is there another way out of here?
Yes, but I'm not leaving Echo.
The loonies will use her against us.
She's devoted her life to me.
We get you out first
and we can come back for her.
Deal?
As a child,
I was obsessed with labyrinths,
so I designed my house like one.
- You mean this place is a maze?
- Easy enough to get in.
I'm the only one who knows the way out.
Stay close to me.
The maze is built on a hundred acres.
There are 73 dead ends.
I once invited the top maze designers
in the country to try to solve it.
One did. It took him three days.
And how much further?
Not far. We just passed
the final switchback point.
If I knew
this thing was a hundred acres,
I would have stopped
and got a sandwich before we came.
Echo.
- Thank God you're okay.
- Hey, hey, hey. She's hypnotized.
Echo. It's me.
It's me. Ow!
Gordon! Help!
Gordon!
She's a pistol.
Come on.
Echo, please. Where are you taking me?
- I'm taking you to Jerome.
- No.
He'll do horrible things to me. Echo!
Stop!
Let him go.
Thanks.
- He went that way.
- All right.
Jeremiah?
Let's try this way.
Hello, brother.
So, how you been? Oh, you look great.
To think I used to be
the handsome one, right?
How'd you find your way
through the maze?
Oh, bro, we might not
look the same anymore,
but we still think the same.
Plus, you used to draw those
stupid things all the time as a kid.
I paid attention.
Hey, Hat Head,
take Crane, find Jimbo
and his bearded sidekick. Kill them.
I've been waiting for this moment
for 15 years,
ever since you ran away in the middle
of the night like a coward.
- You're insane.
- Yeah.
And I tried telling Mom,
but she didn't want to listen to me.
You blame me for everything
that's gone wrong in your life,
but the truth is, Jerome,
you were born bad.
Born bad, huh?
So, that's why you made her think
that I tried to kill you, right?
- Yeah, we both...
- What was it again? What was it?
I put a blade to your throat.
No, no, no.
- I tried to light you on fire.
- We both know you wanted to.
Yeah, that was a funny story, wasn't it?
Okay, maybe it didn't happen
exactly like that,
but I didn't have a choice
and I was right.
Huh?
You killed our mother.
She did deserve it though.
After that whore hid you away,
she gave up on me,
poisoned by your stories.
You turned everyone
I ever loved against me.
My own flesh and blood!
I guess it's like what they say,
"We all could go insane
with just one bad day."
I guess with you
it's more like one bad spray.
You'll see.
- Listen to what I have to say.
- Oh, hell no!
You are not hypnotizing me again!
That's one way to do it.
Must go! Must go!
What are you gonna do to me, Jerome?
Come on. I'm gonna kill you, of course.
But first...
I'm gonna drive you mad.
But don't worry, you won't be alone.
All of Gotham will be joining you, too.
Must go! Must go!
They're after me and the Scarecrow!
These guys just don't give up, huh?
Get any closer, and I splatter him!
I'm gonna splatter broski.
No, you won't. If you wanted him dead
you would've killed him already.
He's right. I'll see you soon.
Mwah.
Okay, Doc.
You've had enough time
to think of a riddle.
I hope you've come up with a good one.
I have.
Then ask away.
What three words are said too much,
meant by few, but wanted by all?
That's your riddle?
You're kidding, right?
What's the answer?
Easy. I love...
The answer is, I love...
I love what, Ed?
- That's not my name.
- Then what's the answer?
You tricked me.
You're trying to awaken a love
that isn't there.
If it isn't there, then say the words.
I won't say it.
Come on.
Say it.
Time's up.
Thank you.
What did I say?
I can help you get Tabitha back!
I know how to reverse your condition.
Talk.
This barrel is from Slaughter Swamp.
It turned you into what you are.
Talk.
Professor Hugo Strange is the one man
who can cure you.
Join me, and we will find him.
I thought I was going to be
stuck like this forever.
You don't have to be, friend.
Okay. I'll join you.
But you'd better deliver.
And I'm not your friend.
I can live with those terms.
Why did you open your club
in The Narrows?
You could've set up shop
anywhere in Gotham.
You wanted my attention.
I came back here
because the people love me.
People didn't come here
because they love you, Ed,
they came for the money.
But I can give them what they want.
I just need your help.
Why would I help you?
Because I know what you really want.
You love me.
You've loved me all along.
You're wrong.
That was Ed.
Okay.
So, do it.
Kill me.
What's your record for how many banks
you've robbed in one day?
Three. Why?
I think you can do better.
You're playing a dangerous game, Lee.
I know.
It's all right. Come on.
- Captain.
- It's okay.
This is Jeremiah Valeska,
Jerome's twin brother.
We need to put him
into protective custody.
Okay. Follow me.
Thank you.
Captain Gordon, I wouldn't be alive
if it weren't for you.
Hell of a day.
What are you thinking?
Jerome told his brother
his plan was to turn Gotham mad.
How the hell
is he going to do that, Harvey?
I don't know. I thought it already was.
Damn.
Doesn't even make me feel better at all.
Jerome.
The test subject has arrived.
Hmm.
A little large for a test subject,
don't you think?
He is not your test subject.
This is Grundy.
He will make a welcome addition
to the team.
Mmm-hmm. Mmm-hmm.
I like him. He's scary.
Good thinking, Mr. Oswald.
Nice to meet you, big fellow.
Ow!
Ah!
- Test subject?
- Here to test your plan,
an unwilling businessman.
No, no, no! Please, please.
Please don't hurt me.
Oh, this won't hurt a bit.
Oh, we're gonna need a lot more of this!