This is Reginald Payne.
We served together, sir.
Feel free to stay with us
a few days.
ALFRED:
You're stealing from us?
Arnold Flass, you're under arrest
for the murder of Leon Winkler.
IA ruled it a suicide.
- Arnold Flass, you're under arrest.
- I'm protected.
So you're the one causing all of the fuss.
You will take nothing from me.
- Really?
MAN: Unh!
Stop" No!
PAYNE:
He has nothing concrete.
Now is the time to make a move on the kid.
Slim pickings at the food court.
- Brought you a bagel.
- Thanks.
But nothing for the invalid?
Sorry. Hospital food only. Doctor's orders.
- How you feeling?
- All right.
Slight puncture, leaked a bit.
So I know last night must be kind of a blur,
but do you have any idea who did this?
- It... It was...
ALFRED: Dark. It was very dark.
I saw a shadow, then my savior,
Master Bruce, was leaning over me.
- Did you get a look at the guy?
- No.
- Sorry, my captain keeps calling.
ALFRED: It's fine, detective.
- Just... Just go.
- No, I can stay.
I appreciate
you sitting with Master Bruce...
but as you can see, I'm completely fine.
Go.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
All right. I'll try and stop by later.
Thank you again for coming, detective.
Why not tell him the truth?
Well, believe it or not, Master Bruce,
Reggie is a mate.
You don't set coppers on your mates,
do you?
- But he nearly killed you.
- I served with that bastard.
Anyone sorts him out, it's me,
nobody else. It wouldn't be right.
- Why would he stab you?
- Now, that's a bloody good question.
And one I mean to find out.
[MACHINE BEEPING]
Because as long as that bloody lunatic's
out on the loose...
[ALFRED GRUNTS]
the harder it's gonna be to find him.
Now, you just...
Get back in bed, Alfred.
- Just pass me my robe.
- Get back in bed.
That's an order.
[GASPS]
MAN:
You're awake.
Wonderful.
- Mm. How long have I been...?
- Asleep?
Just since last night.
How do you feel?
- My head hurts.
- To be expected.
May I?
Who are you?
Doctor Francis Dulmacher.
Founder of this facility.
A pleasure.
[CHUCKLING]
I've gone to great lengths
to meet you, doctor.
Indeed you have.
I must say
you have a remarkable constitution.
I wish I could say the same
of all my patients.
Oh. So I'm a patient now,
no longer a prisoner.
I confess I don't know what you are.
You seize control of the basement...
take one of my guards hostage...
then scoop out your own eye.
What am I to do with you?
Simple. Make me your right hand.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm glad to see you've retained
your sense of humor.
I'm not joking.
For the past 10 years, I have been
Carmine Falcone's top lieutenant.
I'm afraid the name means nothing to me.
I woke up hungry and alone
in an underground cell.
In less than a week,
I brought this place to a standstill.
Now, you've had me as your enemy.
Wouldn't you rather have me
as your friend?
Such vim, such panache.
Bravo.
And now you should eat.
I'll have a nurse come in with some food.
We'll talk more later.
Tricky things, eyes.
Our stock is frightfully low at the moment.
Oh, and apologies,
we couldn't match your original color.
We'll talk soon.
[DOOR OPENS, THEN CLOSES]
[MACHINE BEEPING]
[GASPING]
GORDON:
This can't be true.
I was prepping the case for the DA
when word came down this morning.
Press got it last night, of course.
We had the murder weapon.
With Flass' prints.
There's no way.
The defense dug up a witness,
cleared Flass of all charges.
- What witness?
DENT: No idea.
Only the judge and the lead attorneys
were privy...
and our honorable DA is staying mum.
- What about a subpoena?
- We don't have sufficient grounds.
But I did a little snooping around.
- And?
DENT: The mystery witness...
was provided by Commissioner Loeb.
Let me guess, L0eb's reinstating Flass
as head of Narco.
Worse.
He announced he's backing Flass...
for president of the Policemen's Union
in the upcoming election.
You're telling me a man we know
is a drug dealer and a murderer...
is gonna hold a major position
in the G.C.P.D.?
Clearly Loeb's sending a message.
- This is not gonna stand.
- I'm just as upset about this as you are.
- But it's the commissioner.
- Which is what makes it worse.
ESSEN:
Jim. Jim!
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Jimbo.
You heard the good news?
Hey, the boys are throwing me
a welcome-back down at O'Donnelly's.
Figure you'd wanna stop by...
show support
for your soon-to-be new president.
I wouldn't celebrate just yet.
You just don't learn.
You still wanna take me down.
I'm like the phoenix.
I'll just rise again and again and again.
WOMAN:
Excuse me, you can't go in...
Ah, Detective Gordon.
I had a presentiment I might be seeing you.
Arnold Flass is a murderer.
He belongs in jail.
Detective Flass was legally exonerated.
The judge heard testimony.
The case is closed.
You used your connections
to orchestrate his release.
You perverted the system.
Petulance and naiveté
are a bad combination.
Know when you're beaten.
I was knee-deep in the Flass investigation.
There is no one with enough credibility
to trump our evidence.
I do enjoy when unwavering certainty
is undermined by the truth.
WOMAN: Look into the camera,
state your name and why you're here.
BULLOCK:
My name is Detective Harvey Bullock...
and I presented false evidence
against my fellow G.C.P.D. detective...
Arnold Flass.
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
BULLOCK:
Hey, there you are.
Dude, I feel like a herd of cattle
had a dance party in my head last night.
- What's up?
- Why would you lie to exonerate Flass?
Don't deny it, I saw the tape.
I'm not denying anything.
I did what I had to do.
If I didn't do what Loeb told me to do,
I would have lost my job.
Probably gone to prison.
What does he have on you?
- Harvey.
- Think you're the only one who had orders...
to take a punk down to the end of a pier
and put a bullet in his head? Huh?
The difference is
my Cobblepot didn't come back.
Who'd you kill?
Some scumbag mobster.
Caught him coming out of a club.
My sergeant put a gun in my hand...
held another to my head and said,
"Make a choice."
I decided to keep breathing.
Damn it, Harvey.
So, what...?
What are you gonna do, arrest me?
Go ahead, arrest me, but don't stop there.
Half the cops on the G.C.P.D.
have a Cobblepot...
and Loeb has the goods on all of them.
That is what Loeb does.
Well, it ends now.
Jim, hey.
Going after Flass was bad enough.
- Going after Loeb is suicide, simple.
- So, what...
I'm supposed to stay quiet?
Fall in line like the rest of you?
That would be a good idea.
The day I do that is the day
I quit being a cop.
Oh, my.
Fun fact. Heh-heh.
The human species attracts
the opposite sex via pheromones...
secreted through saliva,
sweat and urine. - Gross.
But one can't always trust
such an animalistic method...
to find a suitable partner.
What are you trying to tell me?
Arnold Flass was released.
I know that you two were dating, and if
the attraction wasn't intellectual...
How could it be with that gorilla?
Then it must be physical.
He's just... He's such a bad, bad, bad...
I appreciate your concern...
but it won't be necessary.
I've realized there are far better men
in the world than Arnold Flass.
DENT: So Loeb's been collecting dirt
on cops for years...
and using it to control the department.
I doubt it stops there.
He's probably got leverage
on businessmen, politicians.
He's got nothing on me.
Just checking.
Anyway, yeah,
that's the source of all his power.
And you wanna steal the dragon's gold.
If we find his cache of evidence
and destroy it, he'll be toothless.
Well, I know Loeb.
He won't keep it anywhere obvious.
- We could watch him, hope he leads us to it.
- We don't have that kind of time.
Isn't there someone
Loeb might have trusted?
Ex-friends, an estranged wife.
No. Well, he was married.
She died 2O years ago.
Fell down the stairs.
There were rumors Loeb killed her,
but nothing ever happened with it.
I still can't believe about your partner.
Why'd he do it?
What's Loeb have on him?
I don't know.
Well, it's gotta be rough.
I know how it is
with cops and their partners.
[SIGHS]
What is it?
MAN: What's the matter, Dent?
I thought that lambaster case was settled.
- And why the hell are we meeting here?
- You'll see.
You know Jim Gordon.
What the hell's going on?
Have a seat.
DENT:
Back before Loeb was commissioner...
when he was a lowly Homicide dick,
you were his partner.
Yeah. That was 2O years ago.
But I always hear that cop partnerships
are like marriages.
You know each other better
than your wives.
Isn't that right, Jim?
That's right.
You digging up that old story
about Loeb killing his wife?
He was with me when she died.
We know about the secret files.
- What secret files?
DENT: Oh, that was good.
- I almost believed him. What about you, Jim?
- No.
You're out of your depth, kid. Both of you.
Swim back to shore.
He's got something on you too,
doesn't he?
He got you to do something for him.
What was it?
Robbery? Coercion?
Murder?
And all this time, he's been using it
to keep you under his thumb.
DENT:
This is your chance to breathe easy again.
Take it, Griggs.
I don't know
what you two are talking about.
If I did, I'd Say talk t0 Xi Lu.
Chinese bookkeeper on Huron Street.
Loeb always said,
"You wanna keep something safe...
you give it to Xi Lu."
You wanna bring in Bullock?
We might need him.
No.
- Thanks, Joe.
JOE: Yeah.
[CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYS
OVER SPEAKERS]
I mean it.
- I like the blue.
- I'm so pleased.
Happy patient, happy doctor.
Ah, Mrs. Harris.
HARRIS: Ah, doctor.
- Don't forget, jazz at 6 on the veranda...
but no martinis
until the bandages come off, yes?
- You're no fun.
DULMACHER: Good girl.
Kidney transplant.
We threw in a new face for free.
And none too soon.
But you need a steady supply of organs?
Yes. Which is suddenly
something of a problem, thanks to you.
But I'm also a solution.
The people in the basement trust me.
Put me in charge and I promise you
a dependable flow of healthy product.
Or I could save myself the trouble...
and kill you and everyone downstairs.
- Tsk, tsk.
Now, if that were an option,
you would have done it already.
And you surely wouldn't have wasted
this beautiful eye on little old me.
I'd like to show you something.
People view themselves
as unique, self-contained systems...
but we are merely a collection of parts.
What happens when I replace your eyes,
your face, your heart?
When do you stop being you
and become something new?
That's what fascinates me.
Nice talk.
Do we have a deal?
Conditionally.
I will send you back to the basement.
You will retrieve my guard...
and then prove to me
that you can provide me with the bodies.
[MACHINE BEEPING]
A test?
And if I fail?
Oh, those who fail me
still have their uses.
You may remember
my former officer manager.
[OFFICE MANAGER GASPING]
[GRUNTING AND COUGHING]
[SCREAMS]
OFFICE MANAGER:
No!
Amusing, no?
OFFICE MANAGER:
No!
[MACHINE BEEPS RAPIDLY,
THEN OFFICE MANAGER SCREAMS]
BRUCE: "And then I looked at the stars
and considered how awful it would be...
for a man to turn his face up to them
as he froze to death...
and see no help or pity
in the glittering multitude.
SELINA: Ha. Ha.
- Here come..."
That's cheerful.
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY OVER PA]
What are you doing here?
Ivy sneaks in a few times a week.
Steals food from the sickies.
She spotted you.
He okay?
[WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER PA]
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Alfred was stabbed.
It was a friend of his from the army.
Well, that sucks.
I think he was there because of me.
What are you talking about?
I had a meeting with the board
of Wayne Enterprises...
to tell them I was investigating them.
- So they sent someone we trust to spy on us.
- What was he looking for?
Some of my files are missing. I think
the other things he stole were just cover.
If I find him...
I could find out who hired him.
He's the key to everything.
You're gonna track him down?
Really? You?
I have to.
- This... This is my fault.
- Kid, you're out of your mind.
Look at him.
Is that how you wanna end up?
I don't expect you to understand.
- I'll help.
- No.
I can't risk anybody else getting hurt
on account of me.
You know how to find me.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
[CLATTERING]
Xi Lu.
Detective Gordon, G.C.P.D.
We have a few questions we'd like to ask you.
Is there somewhere we could talk in private?
Ask your questions, detective.
It's about Commissioner Loeb.
We understand
you two have a business relationship.
- I do not know Commissioner Loeb.
- Listen, old man...
we can have a dozen ADAs and cops here
in 10 minutes.
They'll confiscate every dollar
in this place...
and you will go to jail.
[CELL PHONE BUZZING]
XI LU:
Hm.
[XI LU CHUCKLING]
Your name is Gordon?
That's right.
And you are Dent.
Yes.
Wait here.
[SPEAKS IN CHINESE]
[KNIVES CLANGING]
- Okay, not good.
- GORDON: G.C.P.D. Drop your weapons now.
- Gordon.
- Yeah, run.
[MEN YELLING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
Get in!
[YELLING]
We gotta go back there. Call backup.
- Place will be cleaned out.
- Thanks for stopping by.
I got enough on my conscience.
Griggs set us up. Now Loeb knows
we're after his evidence cache.
Griggs sent you? The guy would turn
on anyone to save his own skin.
- You gotta scare him enough.
- We tried.
Let me. Counselor, trust me,
you're gonna wanna sit this one out.
BULLOCK:
I want a name!
Falcone.
- What?
- The only person who knows...
where Loeb keeps his stash.
Falcone.
The two of them are in it together.
Loeb and Falcone.
You two are dead men. You're going
against Loeb and Falcone, you're dead.
Go! Before I lose my good cheer. Go!
He has a point.
GORDON:
Yeah.
BULLOCK:
So, what next?
Assume Loeb and Falcone are
the only ones who know where the stash is.
We need someone close to them.
Someone who'll talk.
That person doesn't exist.
Yeah, he does.
Mm. Oh, yes. Hm.
[DOOR OPENS]
Gentlemen.
So nice to see you.
What can I do for you?
You do realize
what you're asking me to do?
If Don Falcone is working
with Commissioner Loeb...
to keep this trove of secrets hidden...
and I help you uncover them...
I'd be betraying my patron.
- That's right.
COBBLEPOT: If he found out, he'd...
Well, heh, he'd be very angry.
To say the least.
BULLOCK:
Enough with the hemming and hawing.
Are you gonna help us or not?
Let's say for argument's sake
I could help you, what's in it for me?
I'll owe you a favor.
No questions asked?
Jim.
Yes.
Do you know what this is?
Madre de Dios.
A hundred bottles made once a year
by monks in the Italian countryside.
It's Don Maroni's favorite.
What's your point?
Oh, it's just a piece of information
that might be useful one day.
I like information.
If I help you find
where Loeb keeps his files...
you give me 10 minutes alone with them.
I take what I want.
- This is not a good idea.
- Five minutes.
And you don't touch anything
that has to do with cops.
Five minutes with the files
and a favor from Jim Gordon?
Done.
[CHUCKLES]
So who's up for a road trip?
KELLY:
We have to give Fish more time.
She'll get us out of here, she promised.
Can't you see she abandoned us?
Got herself out and left us here to rot.
I say we kill this one.
Let them know we're serious.
KELLY: Fish Said...
MAN: Fish, Fish, Fish.
Where's Fish now?
Yoo-hoo.
I'm disappointed.
I told you I was coming back.
What, you didn't believe me?
Family is built on trust,
and that's what we are.
A family.
Fish, I tried. I did.
I know you did.
MAN:
So where's everything you promised?
- When do we get out?
- First things first.
I spoke to the man upstairs about our
demands for better conditions, better food.
He asked for a show of good faith.
We're gonna return his guard.
[PEOPLE MURMURING,
THEN MAN SIGHS]
Let him go.
Now.
[GUARD PANTING]
Next.
[WOMAN WHIMPERING]
- What?
WOMAN: Aah! Aah! No!
- What are they doing?
- I'm sorry, honey, you're on the list.
- Doctor's orders.
- Fish.
- Fish!
MAN: I told you, didn't I?
- She's working for them now.
- I warned you not everyone would live.
Their sacrifice means your survival.
And my promise remains the same.
BULLOCK:
You sure about this, Penguin?
You're telling me this is where Loeb
keeps 2O years of dirty secrets?
- It doesn't feel right.
- Maybe that's the point.
- No one would suspect it.
- What would you prefer, Detective Bullock?
A sign saying
"super-secret blackmail hoard"?
You know, the last time the three of us took a
ride, you were in the trunk. I like that better.
I told you, I overheard Falcone
on the phone to Loeb.
He said the farm was safe.
Now, I'll wait here, and
when you're done...
flash the lights or something.
- Uh-uh.
You're coming along.
But if whoever is inside sees me
and reports back to Falcone...
Then you'll be in some really deep doo.
What'd you think? Huh?
We were gonna go do your dirty work...
then you were just gonna waltz in and pick
through the leavings? Have some respect.
[GASPS]
- You fellows lost?
- Good evening, sir.
We were sent by Commissioner Loeb.
Might we have a word?
Out of the cold? Heh.
Well, Marge is putting on some tea.
[CHUCKLES]
[OLD-TIMEY MUSIC PLAYS
OVER SPEAKERS]
- I love your house. So cozy.
- Thank you.
How long have you two been here?
Oh, well, about 20 years.
Ever since Mr. Loeb bought the place.
Hard to believe, time, boy.
You should have seen Margie back then.
Hot to trot.
[ALL CHUCKLING]
- What were you doing before that?
- Oh, nothing much.
Margie was a nurse over at Arkham,
and I was working on the railroad.
- Whoo-whoo!
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
Why are you men here?
Oh, uh, inspection.
Commissioner Loeb has some concerns
about security.
We didn't hear nothing about it.
- You didn't get a letter?
- No.
That's odd. You should
have gotten a letter.
You got ID?
- Well, I don't know that that's necessary.
- No, no. It's fine.
Jim Gordon, G.C.P.D.
This is Detective Bullock. We're on
the commissioner's personal detail.
He don't look like a cop.
I'm undercover.
[THUDDING]
JUDE:
Damn raccoons.
Jim, what do you say
we get on with our inspection?
Mm. Perhaps you wouldn't mind
showing us around.
Oh, absolutely.
Marge, would you mind fetching my keys?
Sure.
Now, listen, before you go...
you fellows have got to get a piece
of Marge's cake.
She makes it with sour cream.
Tastes like a warm Sunday morning.
[THUDDING]
- That's one hell of a big raccoon.
- Maybe we should start upstairs.
Oh, just wait a lick for the keys.
- Margie pie, that was quick.
- Ma'am, put down the...
[GASPING]
Aah!
Freeze!
[MARGE GROANING]
Thanks, Jim.
- You saved my life.
- Watch them.
You're lucky I have a soft spot
for old ladies.
[WOMAN SINGING INDISTINCTLY]
[OLD-TIMEY MUSIC PLAYS
OVER SPEAKERS]
[MUSIC STOPS]
Oh.
Uh...
it... It's so quiet downstairs.
Is the party over?
I prepared a song.
It... It includes a dance and everything.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Miriam Loeb.
Did my father send you?
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Miss Kringle. Ahem.
Oh, Mr. Nygma.
Miss Kringle, I was wondering
if you had plans this evening.
Oh, um...
Actually, I do.
With Tom.
Have you met Tom?
You're the guy that likes riddles. Hey.
What has hands but can't clap?
- A clock.
TOM: Correct.
He's good. You're good.
Am I correct to assume that
this is your...? Uh...
Your new boyfriend?
- Yeah... Yes, I guess so.
- You betcha.
Oh.
Congratulations, sir.
Thank you.
- Well, we should probably get going.
- Okay.
TOM:
It's nice to meet you.
Riddle man,
next time I'm gonna stump you.
Yes. Next time.
BULLOCK:
So, Miriam...
you live up here all the time?
MIRIAM: Always.
Ever since...
I, uh...
I'm not alone though. Heh.
Father comes to visit on Sundays and we
listen to the radio and play checkers.
He always lets me win.
My dad used to do the same thing.
Oh. Really?
- Fathers are funny like that, aren't they?
- Your dad's a real hoot.
Does he keep other stuff up here?
Like important papers or files
or maybe rooms full of boxes?
No.
Why would he do that?
This is a waste of time.
GORDON:
Miriam...
what happened to your mother?
She died.
I, um... I've started a new hobby.
- Would you like to see?
- Sure.
Oh, great.
What are you doing?
Loeb's wife died 20 years ago.
Skull fracture from a fall down the stairs.
Miriam would have been a teenager.
Think Loeb killed her? She was the witness?
That's why he keeps her cooped up here?
You said I wasn't the only one
with a Cobblepot.
Maybe this is his.
I started making jewelry.
What's it made of?
Bones.
Starlings.
They, uh... They land on my windowsill...
and you can catch them
if you're really silent and still.
And I can be really silent and still.
Silent as a mouse.
Then what do you do?
I crush the back of their heads.
I just press down with my thumb.
It makes like a... A popping noise.
Popping-
Miriam...
can you tell us
about your mother's death?
I'm a good person.
Sometimes good people make mistakes.
That's what Father said.
Did you make a mistake with your mother?
Is it like what happens with the birds?
No.
Not like with the birds, no.
Silly.
I had to use a candlestick on her.
She wouldn't stop singing either.
She knew that it was my night.
I was supposed to perform at dinner...
not her.
So you hit her and she stopped.
And your dad covered it up.
He knew that it was my night.
[GUNSHOT]
I'm sorry, Jim.
They came at me. I tried...
[CAR ENGINE STARTS]
Did you find what Loeb's hiding?
Is it here?
Yes.
Well, a deal is a deal.
You have to let me in there.
MIRIAM:
Who's he?
He looks just like a bird.
Oh, I love birds.
I see you still haven't learned
the art of knocking, Detective Gordon.
Miriam is sick.
She didn't mean to hurt her mother.
She just...
has these urges. If you want
to expose what she did, go ahead.
- You think I can't weather the scandal?
- I'm sure you could.
But that's not why you kept her locked away
for 20 years.
Do enlighten me.
I think you love her.
I think you've done everything you can
to keep her out of Arkham.
And you'll keep doing it.
You're willing to hold my daughter hostage
to achieve your ends?
You're much colder than I thought.
So it seems.
I'll hand in my resignation today.
Just keep Miriam out of it.
No, you're not resigning.
You step down,
I'll have someone else to deal with.
And chances are he'll be Falcone's lap dog,
same as you.
With you, I have leverage.
So, what do you want?
Flass is tried.
Fairly.
And I want all the evidence you have
on Bullock...
and every other cop in the G.C.P.D.
sent to Harvey Dent.
- He'll decide who to prosecute.
- No.
I do that, I'm a dead man.
I love Miriam, but I love living too.
You can have Bullock's
file, but not the rest.
Fine.
And Miriam stays where she is.
Is that all?
There's one more thing.
It's become something of a habit
to stand up here with Detective Gordon.
But with the coming election
for president of the P0licemen's Union...
there's no man I'd rather support.
Thank you, Commissioner Loeb.
It's a new day in the G.C.P.D.
Sorry I missed your big moment.
I figured I'd catch the next one.
Your file.
It's everything Loeb has on you.
Always hated that picture.
You know, you tell yourself:
"I'll just do this one bad thing...
but all the good things I'll do later
will make up for it."
But they don't.
There's still that bad thing.
Penguin's gonna come asking
for that favor.
Be careful.
I know we had a deal.
I let you go
and you escape the inevitable punishment...
that will descend on your heads when
Commissioner Loeb hears of your failure.
Unfortunately, I was only able
to acquire one ticket to Arizona.
So who's it gonna be?
Marge and I have been
together for 20 years.
We're not splitting up.
Life can be cruel sometimes.
How do we decide who goes?
I leave that in your hands.
JUDE:
Wait a minute.
Margie. Margie.
Whoa. Whoa.
MARGE:
Here we... Here we go.
What time is the train?
Oh, there's no train.
- I just needed your help.
- What?
I was down to one shell.
I've been thinking
of introducing salsa night.
You think our guests would like that?
No.
Honest. Good.
But I like salsa.
Tuesday it is.
So you've completed your task and the
lines of supply are open once again.
I am duly impressed.
Hope is a carrot, easily dangled
in front of the desperate, doctor.
And you have earned your carrot.
Welcome to upper management.
I think you'll find the view better
than in the basement.
In fact...
You see why I can trust you?
Why I'm not worried
about you betraying me and escaping?
Yes, I see.