OSWALD:
There's a war coming.
A terrible war.
There will be chaos...
...rivers of blood in the streets,
I know it.
I can see it coming.
It's time. Somebody has to
take over, it might as well be me.
[GUNSHOT, THEN THOMAS GRUNTS
AND BRUCE SCREAMS]
My name's James Gordon. Detective.
I will find the man who did this.
Pepper was framed
by Fish Mooney and the cops.
James Gordon is not a good guy.
You deserve better.
GORDON:
Don't ever come back to Gotham.
FALCONE:
I spoke with Cobblepot before he died.
Men who are about to die are very honest.
FISH:
I am gonna kill that old man.
I just wish Penguin was still alive.
I've been watching you.
I saw who really killed the Waynes.
[CHATTERING]
Excuse me! Unh.
MAN 1:
Hey, yo!
MAN 2:
Come on!
MAN 3:
Come on, move your car!
- Thank you.
- Hey, somebody took--!
Stop him!
You need something?
Home.
MAN 4 [ON TV]:
Let's go live for some breaking news.
I'm coming to you
with the latest wrinkle in a story...
...that sent shockwaves
through the financial world of Gotham.
I'm standing before the home
of Ronald Danzer...
...the man who bilked investors out
of a reported...
...half billion dollars
in a vast Ponzi scheme.
Danzer is currently out on bail
awaiting trial.
All of them. The judge, the jury, the DA.
Pay them whatever it takes.
I am not going to prison just because a few
dumb bus drivers and stupid old ladies...
...lost their damn pensions.
Ugh. I gotta sneak out.
Villagers are here with pitchforks.
You're my lawyer.
Fix this.
MAN:
Balloons.
Balloons?
Air balloons.
- Want a balloon?
- What? No. No, thank you. No.
Ronald Danzer?
Who are you?
[DANZER SCREAMING]
Help me!
That's Ronald Danzer. Roll the camera.
Roll the camera!
Help me!
In a bizarre turn of events,
a man appearing to be Ronald Danzer...
...is rising into the air above Gotham...
...attached to a weather balloon.
[SCREAMING]
Ripped By mstoll
The cart was loaded
with bricks for ballast.
Ronald Danzer cheats half of Gotham
out of their savings...
...but before he can stand in trial,
a man clips him to a balloon?
No body?
- We're calling this a murder?
- Call it a public service.
Danzer was a bum.
He got what he deserved.
I'm gonna go get a Danish.
It's what I deserve.
CRANSTON:
Damn it!
Somebody find me O'Brian.
- Get me some ice.
MAN 1: Yes, sir, lieutenant.
Who the hell are you?
Jim Gordon.
Bullock's new partner, right?
Yeah.
Lieutenant Bill Cranston.
Bullock tells me you're a real boy scout.
Don't think we should be
roughing up the skells?
They do have their rights.
We'll have to remember that.
Maybe I'll get that tattooed on my ass.
[CRANSTON CHUCKLES]
Let me show you something, Gordon.
This was a gift from the
Gotham Chamber of Commerce...
...for years of service.
I call him O'Brian.
He also just happens to be
the best interrogator on the force.
Nice meeting you, Gordon.
Oh, Luke! Say hello to Sergeant O'Brian.
MAN 2:
No. No.
[MAN 2 SCREAMING]
I just met Lieutenant Cranston.
- The man, the myth, the legend.
- He's a thug.
So no fingerprints.
Those carts are too easy to buy or steal
to trace.
- How you coming on the death threats?
- I thought we talked about this.
Danzer was murdered.
It's our job to catch murderers.
- Guy was a crook.
- Who had not been convicted of any crime.
Tell that to the guys who killed themselves
because he lost their savings.
This guy was living high
while the city kissed his ass...
...and gave him awards
for being a philanthropist.
- So we let his killer go free?
- Guy walks in here, holds out his hands...
...I’ll arrest him.
Otherwise, I'm content justice was served.
- Like with the Waynes? That what you mean?
- Mario Pepper killed the Waynes.
We killed Pepper. That case is closed.
Detective Gordon?
Davis Lamond from Juvenile Services,
you asked to see Selina Kyle.
Sign for custody.
When you finish,
bring her to our facility on Water Street.
She's scheduled to be transferred upstate
tomorrow.
Yeah, that's gonna be delayed.
She has information about an investigation.
Would you mind stepping back...
...a bit, please?
Wait a minute.
Is that one of the kids that was snatched?
Another closed case.
What is it about the word "closed"
you don't understand?
This is something else.
Just read the letters, track the balloons.
I'll be back in an hour.
Yeah, boss. Get right on it.
Where's my pen?
So why do you care
who really killed the Waynes?
Because I wanna see the person responsible
brought to justice.
Did you read that in a book
or something?
And...
...I made a promise to the boy.
So?
The killer came from there.
Took the man's wallet
and the woman's necklace...
...then shot them both.
He left the boy alive.
I was up there.
Everybody knows that much.
Plus, the killer's face was covered.
Not at first. He pulled up his scarf
when he walked toward them.
- I saw him for a second.
- You saw him? Here? In the dark?
I can see in the dark.
You don't believe me?
There's the question
of whether you're lying...
...and whether you were even here.
You're not giving me proof.
I told you, I stole some chump's wallet
before it happened.
That was two blocks from here.
Didn't he report it?
Yes, a man did report his wallet stolen
by a thief that matches your description.
Yes, the timing does work out
to just before the Waynes' murder.
- But that does not place you here.
- I dumped the wallet.
There.
A sewer. Great.
It's not that I don't trust you
not to run away, but, well...
...I don't.
You find the wallet, you let me go?
That's the deal?
No.
I find the wallet, that places you here.
- I still have to find the guy.
- That's bull.
That's the deal.
Great.
Son of a bitch. She was telling the truth.
SELENA:
Oh, detective.
You're gonna need these.
Hey! Hey, wait a minute!
[GORDON GROANS]
Lazlo, honey...
...take a rest.
Poor thing.
Well, well, well.
Detectives Montoya and Allen.
To what do I owe this honor?
Thought we'd pay our respects.
Maybe ask if you've seen
your friend Cobblepot around.
Oswald. Hmm.
Now that you mention it,
I haven't seen him.
Isn't that funny?
Almost as funny as two detectives
from Major Crimes...
...looking for a nobody like Oswald.
Can we stop the dance?
He's dead. Isn't he?
Killed because he told us about Pepper
being framed for the Wayne murders.
He's dead.
But I didn't kill the little Snitch.
Word is...
...Jim Gordon pulled the trigger.
You have proof?
What do I look like? A cop?
I only heard that James Gordon
splattered poor Oswald's brains...
...all over Gotham River.
Why would Gordon
wanna murder Cobblepot?
Just to keep him quiet about the frame?
Wrong question, gorgeous.
Jim Gordon pulled the trigger,
but who gave the order?
Who can make a cop commit
cold-blooded murder?
Falcone.
Your deductive powers astonish me.
Honestly, I just got a chill.
There's a rumor going around...
...that Falcone gave your latest boy-toy
a nasty beating.
You wouldn't be looking for revenge,
would you?
I just want justice for little Oswald.
MAN:
Hey, Cobblepot.
You're supposed to be dead.
[IN RUSSIAN ACCENT] I'm afraid
you have me confused. My name is Dimitri.
No, I heard you got whacked for ratting.
Fish is gonna pay some serious cash
for your skinny ass.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
No. Please. Please, she'll kill me!
Why'd you even come back, huh?
I could not stay away.
Gotham is my home.
It's my destiny.
You don't see what's coming. I do.
Gotham needs me. I'm its future.
If you're its future,
then Gotham is in trouble.
Yes. Yes, it is.
[MAN GRUNTING]
OSWALD:
Can I have a tuna sandwich, please?
BRUCE: Alfred, I don't wanna do this.
ALFRED: What?
- Stop, I don't wanna do this.
- Come on, swat.
En garde.
Here we go, son.
- What? What? Shall we go?
- I don't want to do this.
What?
There she blows.
Eye of the tiger through the wind
in your nostrils, Sir Bruce.
The blood in his veins.
Sink. Mind your head. Dive!
Oh, I do beg your pardon, sir, I--
[GRUNTING]
That's gotta hurt. No, not really.
I said, stop!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Stop. Down swords. I surrender.
See? A nice...
...swordfight...
...gets our blood up, doesn't it?
Better than reading these dusty old files.
What is this, anyway?
Police file.
Your mom and dad.
How did you get these?
It wasn't hard.
Why would you wanna look at these?
They're horrible.
They're gonna give you nightmares.
I have those anyway and...
...I'm looking for clues.
So you're a detective now?
- If I find a clue, I am.
- Have you found a clue?
- Not yet.
Detective Gordon has promised you...
...that he will find the person that killed--
- You really believe he will?
He will try.
Of that I'm certain.
Yeah, Detective James Gordon.
One of your counselors brought me
a girl this morning and I signed for custody.
That's what I'm saying,
I can't bring her back, she got away.
Yeah? Well, I'm not happy about it, either.
On edge, Gordon?
I'm fine. How can I help you?
We were just, uh, wondering...
...when you shot Cobblepot in the head
and dumped his body in the river...
...did Falcone pay?
Or was that more of a
"favor to the don" type thing?
Whatever you heard, it's not true.
Oh, so you mean
you didn't kill Cobblepot?
Or you didn't do it for Falcone?
MONTOYA: We thought we'd give you
a chance to tell us the truth. Cop to cop.
You're not listening. I didn't kill him.
Okay, so where were you
on the night of September the 17th?
Are you really asking me this?
Since when did Major Crimes
become IA?
When cops started doing hits
for the mob.
Yeah? Then come back to me
when you have actual proof.
Until then, don't waste my time.
Hey, Gordon, piece of advice.
Take a shower.
Because you stink like a sewer.
- Any job at all, even dishwasher.
- We're staffed up.
I only ask a chance to prove myself.
- You ever work in a restaurant?
- Not exactly.
Here, you're on your feet all day.
You don't even have the right shoes.
There you are. We got the owner
of a balloon factory downstairs.
- Says he's got something for us.
- Montoya and Allen came by.
- They accused me of killing Cobblepot.
- Damn.
- Somebody must've talked.
- Doesn't matter.
The fact they're here means they got nothing
and they're gonna get nothing.
End of the day,
no one cares about Cobblepot.
- Because he deserved it? Like Danzer?
- Don't make this into something bigger.
You did what you had to do,
and he did deserve it, he worked for Fish.
She doesn't employ altar boys.
What about Mario Pepper?
He deserve what he got?
Hell, yes.
He was a dirtbag for trying to shoot you.
Remember?
I thought we were done talking about this.
We're done talking about this...
...when the person who actually murdered
Thomas and Martha Wayne is in jail.
Not the person we killed for it.
For the last time, Gordon...
...let it go.
- Or what?
Am I gonna be the next person taken
out to the pier to get a bullet in the head?
The interview's waiting.
OSWALD:
Pardon me.
You work at that Italian restaurant,
don't you?
Yeah.
And what size are your shoes?
Uh, nines.
What a coincidence!
[CHUCKLES]
When I saw that balloon go up on TV,
I knew it was mine.
I said to myself, "Jimmy boy,
you better call the cops right away.
Or they'll try and pin this on you."
So it was you who called us?
I thought my partner had gone
to the trouble of tracking you down.
How exactly was your balloon
used to kill Ronald Danzer?
It was stolen
by my bum of an ex-employee a month ago.
Carl Smikers.
That's what I get for hiring a kid.
- Did he ever mention Danzer?
- Hell, no.
I'm surprised
if he even knew who Danzer was.
We ain't talking about one of those
intellectually superior types here.
- You got an address?
- Yeah, you find him...
...see you can get back the others.
- The other what?
The other balloons.
A grand a pop those things are.
He stole four.
[GRUNTS]
Forty-seven dollars?
Frankie, I'm coming back next week,
try to show some initiative, all right?
Okay, Bill.
You're a disgrace to drug dealers.
- Hot dog?
- Get lost.
- I said, get lost!
Lieutenant Cranston?
[GRUNTING]
All right.
Let's see.
Let's see what we got here.
What the hell?
Who are you?
Oh, no.
[CRANSTON GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
Right.
So no breakfast then.
And no dinner last night.
What's the new program?
You wanna see how long we can go
without eating anything?
Well, if that's the case,
I should save myself the trouble...
...of making it.
Have you seen this?
Oh, yeah, nuts are going around
offing people with balloons.
Can think of easier ways to kill someone.
Master Bruce, forgive me for...
...uttering the tired old words
"in times like these."
But in times like these...
...you really need to keep
your strength up.
I'm just not hungry.
Morning.
Hi.
Thank you.
- I tried not to wake you.
- It's fine. I have a meeting.
You Okay?
You hardly slept last night.
- It's just work.
- This Balloonman thing?
That's what the paper's calling him.
And it says he killed a cop.
You're not in danger, are you?
You don't have to worry about me.
Well, what is it then?
I can see somethings bothering you.
Yesterday...
...our first victim, Ronald Danzer...
...he was a con man. Nobody cared.
Now that a cop's been targeted...
...the investigation
will get all the support it needs.
It's not right.
Everyone has to matter
or nobody matters.
Otherwise people lose faith...
...and that's when you get vigilantes.
But that isn't your fault.
I mean, if anything,
you're giving people faith.
Am I? How?
Your first case,
you caught the Wayne killer.
Do you have any idea what that meant
for the city?
You're a hero.
I gotta go.
Don't matter if you a cop, you dirty,
The Balloonman gonna get you.
It's time the people of Gotham realize
that they have to stand up for themselves.
Hey, Balloonman ought to get
to my landlord next.
He's a crook.
And his name is Harold--
This is wonderful. This is like my dream
of how today was gonna go.
Besides the black eye to the department,
now we have a vigilante who kills bad cops.
- Cranston wasn't that bad.
- But whatever he was or wasn't guilty of...
...Cranston was a lieutenant
in the G.C.P.D.
You don't get to go around killing cops.
Where are you on this
in the Danzer murder?
We're looking for a man
named Carl Smikers.
He was an employee at the factory
where the balloons were stolen.
We have uniforms staking out his apartment,
but he hasn't been back there.
- And you like him for this?
- Oh, he's guilty.
Leave me in a room with him,
he'll be guilty.
He's connected,
but I'm not sure he's the one.
He had weather balloons.
Cranston and Danzer were killed
with weather balloons. He's the guy.
Smikers never graduated high school.
He's never held a job for more than a year.
He's got busts for soliciting.
Possession.
- Tell her about the other balloons.
- What other balloons?
Smikers' boss mentioned...
...that four balloons are missing.
There are two of them still out there.
So two more targets?
We have any sense who they might be?
Danzer and Cranston were both known
figures, and known to be dirty.
Killer didn't need any special knowledge
to target them.
So it's likely the next target
is public and known to be corrupt.
Basically every elected official in Gotham
should stay indoors.
Find him.
- Now.
- We will.
We Will?
What happened to
the killer doing the city a favor?
You're gonna make me think
you actually care.
You wanna kill a crook-financier,
be my guest.
You kill a cop, it's a job safety issue.
We need a plan.
Relax, one thing I do know
is how to find someone.
[GRUNTING]
Beautiful, baby.
Hey.
Hey. Yo.
What did he tell you?
Nothing. I was just hungry. Mm. Mm.
Here's the deal: You wash dishes,
mop the floor, take out the trash.
Otherwise...
...you're deaf, dumb and blind.
- I understand--
- No. You don't. But you will.
This ain't like other places,
and you'll either get it...
Or I'll be fired?
You could say that.
Oh, you have nothing to worry about.
I know that this is a great opportunity--
Don Maroni.
Good to see you.
Great opportunity indeed.
Our suspect had a prior for soliciting
two years ago, right?
One of my girls said he looked familiar,
remembered he liked big, brawny types.
She pointed me to that pimp,
that guy who specialized in that.
- He remembered...
- After you roughed him up a little.
...that he used to do deliveries
for this, uh, dry cleaner, Mr. Chang...
...he remembered the guy
was a mahjong nut.
He was into these Chinese bookies
for five grand.
And they sent you here?
By way of bike messengers, a guy that
runs some pickpockets on the south side...
...and a pot sticker joint
the guy apparently loves.
Dragon Palace.
- We didn't order any--
- Carl Smikers?
Run!
G.C.P.D! You're under arrest!
[GRUNTING]
Don't move!
Don't move.
Jim, a little help!
Put it down!
Put it down now!
[WOMAN GRUNTS]
LAZLO: You put the MCU on
to that cop killing Oswald.
Falcone finds out it came from you,
I-- I mean...
...I don't mind what he did to me.
It's, uh--
Lazlo, honey...
...you're worried about me, aren't you?
But you must remember...
...it wasn't you Falcone wanted to hurt...
...it was me.
Understand?
Good.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
The boy has lost his spine.
Not everyone is built
for a beating like that.
What's that new piece
that the Roman has been seeing?
What's her name? Natalia? Nadia?
- Mm-hm.
- Yeah.
Tell Butch
she's going to have an accident.
Such a shame.
She was a pretty girl.
And get rid of Lazlo while you're at it.
He's bringing down the mood.
With pleasure.
- My God.
MONTOYA: Sorry.
- I knocked but I could hear someone--
- How did you get in?
- I still have a key, remember?
- And you just let yourself in?
Give it to me.
I could have you arrested.
Or I could arrest you.
Anyway, it's kind of early to get high,
isn't it?
It's been a stressful day.
- Is that all you're doing?
- I'm afraid so.
Disappointed?
Don't play with me, Barbara.
I was there, remember?
- Through all of it.
- You mean you're part of it?
Fine.
- Answer the question.
- Yes.
This is it.
Now that you've broken into my home...
...and accused me of being a drug addict,
you can leave.
Not until we talk about Gordon.
- He's killed a man.
- You told me. It's not true.
Not Mario Pepper.
Another man.
And he killed him on the orders
of Carmine Falcone...
...biggest crime boss in Gotham.
You're lying.
But you know,
I guess I should be used to that.
True.
When we were together,
I did lie to you.
A lot.
But you always knew.
You looked in my eyes...
...and you knew when I was lying to you.
Am I lying now?
Is this just because I love him?
Is that why you are so determined
to destroy him?
I've been sober for a year and I know
that doesn't erase the things that I did...
...but I still care about you.
I can't stand you being with this man.
You deserve better.
Leave.
Now.
Ask him where he was the night
that Oswald Cobblepot disappeared.
That's the name of the man he killed.
I'm telling the truth. I didn't kill those guys.
I mean, a cop? Why would I kill a cop?
Maybe because you're a thieving,
cop-murdering pile of crap.
But mind you, that's just a theory.
- You admit stealing the balloons?
- Yeah, but I owed these loan sharks.
And if I didn't pay them,
they were gonna cut off stuff.
If you didn't kill Danzer and Cranston,
who did?
- Who did you sell the balloons to?
- I never saw his face.
We had a drop off point
to exchange the balloons and money.
You know what we got here, Jim?
We got us a criminal mastermind.
Not only is the murder weapon
in the stratosphere...
...but so are the bodies.
It's the perfect crime.
The bodies will come back.
What are you talking about?
You guys not know
how weather balloons work?
Tell us, genius.
Or I'll beat it out of you.
Wait-- Okay, they rise up...
...and it gets colder and colder,
and the balloon gets brittle...
...and the helium expands.
Then what?
It pops.
[DOG BARKS]
BULLOCK:
I'm really starting to dislike this case.
Where do you think
they find shovels that big, huh?
We only have to worry about
one more balloon.
- Who?
- Quinn. He's meditating in his garden.
Alvarez is on his way to the scene.
We're gonna have the church
on our back.
Great. Forget the fact...
...that Quinn was known
as "the diddling priest."
Here's what we found in Cranston's pockets.
What wasn't smashed to bits.
Why is your name on this, Jim?
I know who the Balloonman is.
MARONI: You see,
Falcone is only the boss of Gotham...
...because people believe he's the boss.
That's what this Arkham thing
is gonna change.
People are gonna see
that the emperor's got no clothes.
I'm wasting my breath.
You're an idiot. Get out of here.
Who the hell are you?
I-- I'm sorry, sir. I am--
Hold on. Put that down.
You were listening, huh?
You're new.
What's your name?
Paolo, sir.
Italian? You don't look Italian.
On my mother's side.
It's the side that I claim.
A boy who loves his mother.
Here. Take it.
I was a lot like you.
Started from nothing.
But I kept my head down, I worked hard,
now look at me.
Gotham is the city of opportunity.
Yes, sir. I believe that too.
You hear what I was saying back there?
Those names? Falcone. Arkham.
They mean anything to you?
Honestly, sir,
I didn't hear anything at all.
Attaboy.
The Balloonman has struck once again.
Cardinal Quinn, accused of multiple accounts
of sexual abuse...
...is the latest victim of the vigilante.
See this? This is not good.
You can't go around killing priests.
At least not in public.
Go take care of your mother, Paolo.
GORDON:
His name is Davis Lamond, 48.
He's worked at Juvenile Services
for 15 years.
No priors.
He didn't show up at work today.
And he hasn't been back to his apartment.
- We have uniforms in both.
- You're positive he's the killer?
We found a form on Cranston's body
that I've given Lamond yesterday morning.
Also, keys that opened
Lamond's apartment.
I'm guessing they had a scuffle.
Cranston went through his pockets...
...but Lamond managed
to attach him to the balloon.
What caused Lamond to snap?
GORDON:
Not sure.
Lamond's coworkers describe him
as thoughtful, dedicated, sweet.
A few said that.
Great, one of those
sweet cop-killing vigilantes.
- What about his last target?
- Same profile as all the rest.
Well-known. Seemingly respectable.
Actually corrupt.
This is Gotham.
That doesn't exactly narrow it down.
Meanwhile,
I have the mayor, city council...
...half the city's judges
and clergy hiding indoors...
...screaming at the commissioner
to find the guy.
Guess who he screams at?
We've got his photo out there.
It's just a matter of time.
- Nothing.
- Really?
Your network of Chinese loan sharks
and hookers came up empty?
Gloat later. Just think about it.
He had to store the balloons, the helium
canisters, the carts he was using...
Maybe a storage facility, a warehouse?
Or an abandoned building.
That's it? How'd you come up with that?
It's the same thing I just said.
What made you figure this place?
The girl yesterday, Selina,
she told me she was in a new juvie building.
Lamond, the counselor, said the same thing.
So I'm thinking:
What happened to the old juvie building?
Turns out,
the city's getting ready to demo it.
Even if he was here,
he's probably long gone.
He's only got one balloon left.
He knows we're closing in...
Or that's him right there.
Bullock!
Drop the gun now!
- I can't do that, detective, I'm not done yet.
- One more time, drop it.
- You should be helping me.
- You're wasting your breath.
My partner thinks
you're as bad as the scum you kill.
Me, I can see how you're doing us a favor,
so don't shoot me, all right?
You believe as I do.
You're the one
who caught those child snatchers.
- You risked your life.
- So did I.
You wanna protect the innocent?
Yes, we have laws for that.
And what good are laws...
...when they require men like your
Lieutenant Cranston to implement them?
And Ronald Danzer? You think he would
have seen the inside of a jail?
Or that priest?
Why didn't the law punish him?
I have given my life...
...to the lost children of Gotham
because I wanted to make a difference.
You know what kind of difference I made?
None.
Because the people running this city
feed off the weak, and the law protects them.
When your mayor rounded up all those
children to send off to that prison upstate...
...I decided no more.
I would teach them
there are consequences.
So why don't you ask yourself, detective.
Who are you fighting for?
A mayor in the mob's pocket,
cops on the take...
...or for the weak and the innocent?
Who are you finally?
Forget it.
[GRUNTING]
LAMOND:
No, no! Aah!
- What are you doing?
- How do you like that?
- Grab him!
- How does it feel...
...you're hoisted by your own petard?
No, Jim!
Jim, what are you doing?
Jim, let go!
GORDON: Shoot it! Shoot the balloon!
- Jim!
- Let go!
GORDON: Shoot it!
Just let go!
GORDON:
Shoot it now!
[LAMOND GRUNTS]
FISH:
Carmine.
What a lovely surprise.
We're not quite open.
But for you...
Hello, Fish.
Just stopped by on my way to dinner.
I wanted to make sure
there were no hard feelings.
Never.
That's my girl.
Speaking of your girl, that'd better be
the reason why you're ditching me tonight.
What's her name again? Nadia?
Natalia.
And no.
She had an accident.
I hope nothing serious.
A mugging.
Mugging?
Ever since the Waynes were killed,
the city has gone crazy.
I hope the punk who did it
paid with his life.
He will, when we find him.
Along with anyone who helped him.
Are you hearing any rumblings
from Maroni's camp?
You don't actually believe that Maroni
had something to do with it, do you?
Like you say...
...people are acting crazy...
...and crazy is bad for business.
Especially with everything
on the horizon.
You're talking about Arkham.
I thought you had that locked up.
Keep your eyes open.
Hold on.
Give me a second.
There will be more like me, detective.
You know that, don't you?
Not if we do our job.
And We Will. I Will.
You had your chance.
All of you.
Who was your last target?
The crusade of the vigilante known
as The Balloonman ended...
...when he was apprehended by police.
He was the man who stood up to the
corruption eating at the heart of Gotham...
...willing to break the law
in order to save it.
I'd imagine the criminals of Gotham
are sleeping well tonight.
He killed people.
That made him a criminal too.
That's very true.
Can I get you anything else?
No, thank you, Alfred.
Right, well, you know...
Do try and eat a bit, won't you?
Be a shame to have you floating away.
WOMAN [ON TV]: G.C.P.D. claims a win,
but this journalist is left to wonder...
...now that The Balloonman is gone,
who will defend the people of Gotham?
This is Channel 7 at 7 reporting live...
...from the former Gotham
Juvenile Facility Center in downtown...
...with your minute-to-minute update.
Back to the newsroom, John.
BARBARA:
You're okay.
Are you okay?
Yeah. I fell, that's all. I'm fine.
What's wrong?
I want you to know
that you can tell me anything.
The city is sick.
Sick in a way I hadn't realized.
When they were taking him away,
this Balloonman killer...
...I asked who his last target was.
You know what he said?
"Doesn't matter."
He meant the mayor, judges,
anyone in a position of power...
...they're all guilty.
But that's not true.
That's how he feels.
That's how they all feel. Everyone.
That's why the city embraced him.
Because we let them down.
But if people take the law
into their own hands...
...then there is no law.
And we're lost.
There are cops who do it.
Same thing he did.
But you never would.
Do you think I could?
[SIGHS]
No.
I know you...
...Jim Gordon.
And I love you.
And now I'm gonna get you a drink.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
I'll get it.
Jim?
Hello, James...
...old friend.
Ripped By mstoll