Previously on Gotham...
Father Creel.
You have
the Wayne boy?
Not yet.
There are some
practical matters
that have to be resolved first.
Whoa!
(gasping)
Mr. Penguin?
Help me.
THEO:
This is the name
of the man
who killed your parents.
Sell me your company.
I will give you this
as a signing gift.
I've been a very bad girl.
GORDON: You're a good woman.
You're just sick.
(gasps)
I knew you still had
feelings for me.
I want to
show you something.
GORDON:
You're under arrest!
May I ask what
the charge is?
The kidnapping and torture
of Aubrey James.
No! Tell me who killed them!
Can you believe it still fits?
Don't make me
kill you.
Do it, Jim. Do me.
Kill him!
GORDON:
It's over.
Not yet.
Hold on.
I love you, baby.
No!
(siren wailing in distance)
(thunder rumbling softly)
MAN:
Here you go!
(talking quietly)
(doorbells jingle)
Morning.
Help you?
I was told to order
a Highsmith Royale.
Bit early, don't you think?
I said Highsmith Royale.
No ice.
(lively chatter, music playing)
There you go, man.
(man speaking indistinctly
over phone)
How may I help you?
I need somebody killed
and I heard
that you employ the best.
Oh, yes, I know you.
Our illustrious
mayor's sister.
Or should I say "ex-mayor"?
Word is,
you're quite
the deadeye yourself.
Why come to us?
Had an accident. My aim is off.
Hmm.
Is this business, personal...?
What's it matter to you?
Personal costs extra.
There's always complications.
It's business.
A cop.
Seems personal to me.
Anyhow, cops also cost extra.
Fine.
I want it done today.
What kind of guarantee do I get?
I accept the job,
the job gets done. Period.
You see, I believe in the
beauty of extreme measures.
So who's the lucky fellow?
DOCTOR: Ms. Kean has yet
to regain consciousness.
With this kind of trauma,
we have no idea
when she might wake up.
If ever.
But the medical
wing at Arkham
is fully equipped
to handle her condition.
Will you be riding
over with her?
No.
Hello, sleepyhead.
(panting)
Where am I?
Rapid movement
and elevated heart rate
are counterproductive
to the healing process.
No! No! Don't kill me!
Apologies in advance.
Rest up, my feathered friend.
We have a big night ahead of us.
Looking for this?
Thank you.
You left before I woke up.
I know. Couldn't sleep.
Was I snoring?
No.
Are you sure?
My big, loud, rumbling,
barnyard snore?
I've heard complaints--
neighbors,
airplanes...
You don't snore.
Look,
I'm glad Galavan's
been arrested,
but he should pay
for everything he's done.
I'm on my way to meet Barnes
at Galavan's penthouse.
Hopefully, we can
find some evidence
to corroborate
Aubrey James' testimony.
I got a call.
They're transferring
Barbara to Arkham.
I know. I stopped by
Gotham General.
You went to see her?
She's a witness
against Galavan.
I wanted to check
on her condition.
Her condition is
she's in a coma.
We never talked about
what happened
with you and Barbara
in that interrogation room.
I know. Tonight?
Sure, tonight.
Or right now.
Lee, I went over to see her
as a part of
the case against Galavan,
that is it.
This isn't jealousy.
That woman is...
How do I put this?
She's the devil.
No, she is.
Lee...
you think I wanted things
to go the way they did?
I had to play her game.
I know.
Uh, forget
about Barbara.
Most people fight
their dark side.
Lately, you find ways
to give in to it.
That's a problem.
For you and for us.
I know.
I hear you.
Can we please just not
talk about this right now?
I'm late to meet Barnes.
I'll be fine.
I wasn't sure you'd ever
want to see me again.
When you called...
You don't believe what
they're saying about my uncle...
do you?
No.
Of course not.
Silver, I asked you here
because I need your help.
Anything.
Before he was arrested,
your uncle made me an offer.
I want...
ALFRED:
Right, Master Bruce!
On your feet.
Bought us a lovely
couple of rakes
from the ironmonger's.
I suggest we get
outside and get...
Hello, Ms. St. Cloud.
Did not expect to see you here.
Hello, Alfred.
That must have been
your car I saw,
idling on the main road.
Now, in light of
recent events, I suggest
you get in it and you leave.
Immediately.
I invited her,
and I want her to stay.
And I'm ordering her to leave.
And it's my house,
and I give the orders.
Oh, is that so?
It's okay.
I don't want to cause
any trouble.
Smart girl.
Off you pop.
(whispers):
I'm at the Kane Hotel.
You had no right to do that.
I had every right.
What were you thinking,
asking her up here?
(door closes in distance)
Oh, wait, you...
think she was gonna
tell you something.
If Galavan really has the name
of my parents' killer
in that envelope,
it's worth a shot.
Well, my guess is
there was absolutely nothing
in that envelope.
It was just a ruse to get you
to sign away the company.
Galavan is smart.
He wouldn't enter
a multibillion-dollar offer
without his end of the bargain.
He has the name.
And you think that little minx
is gonna tell you something,
do you?
We're friends.
No, you're not.
Getting information
out of a girl like that
requires a level of deception
that you do not yet possess,
Master Bruce.
It is too dangerous.
It's worth the risk.
No.
You will not see
Ms. St. Cloud again
or pursue Galavan's
wild claims.
You have no right
to make that decision for me.
Well, someone has to.
If you force me
to be your jailer...
then that is who I will be.
(elevator bell dings)
(sighs)
Excuse me. Thank you.
(elevator bell dings)
Press 56, please?
(muzak playing)
You live here?
No.
Me neither.
Lady's baby grand
is flat, so...
I don't mind
making house calls.
I like my work.
You like your work?
Yeah. I do.
I guess we're lucky.
Caramel?
No, I'm good.
You're missing out;
they're good.
(grunting)
Where the hell is Gordon?
(elevator bell dings,
grunting continues)
(elevator bell dings)
(panting)
(grunting)
Who is that?
No idea.
But he just tried to kill me.
He tell you why?
Wasn't random.
Piano wire.
Guy's a pro.
(phone ringing)
(ringing continues)
No, wait, wait.
(phone beeps)
(Gordon breathing)
You feeling lucky, Ned?
(blows)
MAN:
You got this!
(crowd gasps)
THE LADY:
Listen up.
Who wants a shot
at eighty-sixing
one of Gotham's finest?
I'm waiving
any collateral fines.
Just do what you have to do,
but Jim Gordon doesn't see
the sun... rise.
(footsteps approaching)
(car passing outside)
(gasping softly)
You drugged me.
That was for your own benefit,
Mr. Penguin.
You have extensive injuries.
I know you.
Ed.
Nygma.
We met once before,
at the GCPD.
You're not a cop.
Oh, no, no, no.
(laughs)
No, I'm in forensics.
Do you believe in fate?
Where are my clothes?
Oh, I threw them away.
They smelled.
Oh, no. Oh, my.
Uh, I'm afraid, sir,
that you can't leave.
You sedate me again,
and I swear, I will...
Sir!
You are a wanted man.
You can try and run,
but with your condition,
you'll get about three blocks.
I'm afraid that you're
stuck here until you recover.
(pants softly)
Now, drink up.
It's just water.
Dehydration is common after
prolonged outdoor exposure.
What do you want from me?
Remember I had mentioned fate?
(chuckles)
Recently,
I've been going through
a sort of change.
"What kind of change?" you ask.
I didn't.
I've started murdering people.
(laughs)
Wow!
That is thrilling
to say out loud.
(laughs)
How many people?
Three in total.
(scoffs, chuckles)
Two of them
I didn't really care for.
But one was my girlfriend,
Ms. Kringle.
She was the love of my life.
If you're planning on
killing me,
could you get
on with it?
At this point, it would
come as a welcome relief.
Oh, heavens.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I have no ill intentions
toward you.
Then what are your intentions?
I need advice,
Mr. Penguin.
These murders...
changed me.
And like the butterfly,
I've come to realize
that I cannot be a caterpillar
once again.
And you're one of
the city's
most notorious killers.
I brought you here, in part,
because I was hoping you could
guide me on this new path.
(laughs)
Listen, friend...
Ed.
Whatever.
(helicopter passing in distance)
My empire is in ruins.
I'm a wanted man
with no friends.
And my mother...
the one person
I swore to protect is dead
because of my weakness.
(inhales sharply)
Believe me when I tell you
that this path you're on
leads to nothing
but destruction and pain.
So...
wanted or not...
I'm leaving.
(gasps)
Oh, my.
Rise and shine.
Hell with this.
(grunts)
Who sent you? Huh?
Who sent you?!
Your mother.
(laughs)
That's what I was hoping
you would say.
No! Don't!
(screaming)
Talk!
Detective Gordon, stand down!
(screaming)
Stand down right now!
Parks, watch the perp.
Cortez, you shut
the window.
Come over here!
You know damn well I don't
tolerate that type of behavior,
and yet you pull that crap
right in front of me?
GORDON:
I'm sorry, sir.
BARNES: Are you
losing it, Gordon?
Has that church incident
messed with your mind?
No, sir.
BARNES: 'Cause if I
remember correctly,
you disobeying
my orders
is what landed you there
in the first place.
I ordered you to turn
that car around,
and you ignored me and drove
straight into an ambush.
And ended the day
putting Galavan behind bars.
We need to push the boundaries.
PARKS:
Captain!
(laughing)
My employer has
a strict protocol.
(laughs)
If the first guy
doesn't succeed,
keep sending men
till the job is done.
None of you is making it
out of here alive.
(laughing)
BARNES: When you get
here, move carefully.
We don't know how many
active skells
we're dealing with.
All right.
Two units on
the way here.
We just have to hold out
till they get here.
Hey, Cortez,
kill the lights.
Sir, I'm forensics.
I don't have a gun.
Grab something
you can use as a weapon,
and stay behind us
as best you can, all right?
Parks, take cover
behind the desk.
Hey. Remember your training.
Aim for center mass.
Right. Center mass.
And don't stop firing
until you're sure.
And, Parks...
Yes, sir?
Breathe.
(exhales)
(knocking)
(door handle rattling)
(quiet creak)
(grunts)
CORTEZ:
Help me!
Drop the knife!
(grunting)
(gunfire)
I'm leaving.
Not gonna happen.
Try to stop me.
I'll lop off her
pretty little head.
You know what I like
about those glasses?
(shell casing clatters on floor)
They look like bull's-eyes.
Are you okay?
I am.
Okay!
We're not gonna
hang around for round two.
Everybody load up,
and let's get
the hell out of here.
I'm not leaving.
That wasn't a request.
This place is still our best bet
for evidence against Galavan.
We leave, they'll destroy it.
Now you're just
looking for a fight.
Parks, make sure
the staircase is clear.
I've got a civilian who's dead
and a rookie who's scared
half out of her mind.
You think we're gonna
survive the next attack
with just a few handguns?
We have to get
out of here.
(quiet clatter)
Wait.
A monk's cassock?
What the hell
is this about?
BARNES:
I don't know,
but we have to get out of here.
Let's go!
Captain...
Captain!
This could be exactly
what we're looking for.
Knife!
(grunts)
(screams)
Captain!
You okay?
It's just a scratch.
Let's get out of here.
No, no.
(groans)
The knife punctured
an artery.
You move,
it could tear.
What are you, a doctor now?
I can move.
(groans)
You stand up,
you'll bleed out in
a matter of minutes.
(muffled grunting)
(muffled whimpering)
Ta-da!
(laughs)
Who is that?
This is Mr. Leonard.
You were talking
in your sleep last night
about Galavan
killing your mother.
I was?
Yes.
Mr. Leonard...
(Leonard whimpers)
...works for Galavan.
Well, before he was
arrested, of course.
Arrested?
Detective Gordon
arrested Galavan
for kidnapping
Mayor James.
He's in Blackgate!
(laughing)
Huh.
(chuckles)
Oh, I thought you'd be pleased.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Why is he here?
He was a gift for you.
And what exactly am I supposed
to do with a Leonard?
Kill him.
(muffled grunting)
I thought it might be nice
to get some retribution
for your mother's death.
That it might
cheer you up a little.
No?
(muffled whimpering)
I'm done.
I need some rest.
And then I'm leaving
Gotham forever.
I really thought
he would like you.
(muffled grunt)
What to do now?
(muffled whimpering)
(Oswald humming a tune)
(muffled screaming)
MAN:
Please! Please!
Not my...!
(blade slices, man screaming)
EDUARDO: Why just smell
the fear on your victim
when you can
taste it, right?
(phone ringing,
man continues screaming)
(panting)
Help me!
Help! Help!
(screaming)
Hola.
Hola, Eduardo.
Long time.
Yes.
(screaming)
Just a moment, please.
Help! Help!
(chuckles) Are you on a job?
It's not a job
if you love what you do.
Oh, fair enough.
Listen, um, I'm in a bit
of a pinch over here.
I thought my membership
was revoked.
Bygones, darling.
Live and let live.
So you eat people.
Who am I to judge?
The target is
a Detective Gordon.
I'll make it worth your while.
Send me the address.
(phone beeps)
(groans loudly)
Death squads have
softer touches than you.
(grunting)
At least Galavan
goes top shelf.
The EMTs should
be on their way.
Yeah, sure.
They'll be here about
the same time as our backup.
So you want to tell me what
the hell's going on with you?
In the church that day,
Barbara accused me
of having a monster inside me.
And?
Lee seems to agree.
She thinks I'm ready
and willing to give in to it.
What do you think?
There was a moment.
When I had the shotgun
on Barbara.
She was taunting me
to pull the trigger.
If Galavan's people
hadn't busted in...
...I don't know.
But they did bust in.
I nearly crossed the line.
"The line."
Let me tell you something
about the line.
My third tour, we were
stationed in the desert.
We captured three insurgents,
when this sandstorm kicks up.
Zero visibility.
Then we start taking fire.
We're getting lit up.
Suddenly, I'm alone.
I come across
one of our prisoners.
He's a kid.
His hands are zip-tied.
But he figures, what the hell,
he's gonna use the sandstorm
to try to escape.
So I jump him.
And I take my gun
and I jam it in his mouth.
I figured
it was just a threat.
Show him who's boss,
you know?
Next thing I know...
...I just pulled the trigger.
Blew his head off.
(panting)
That kid woke me up
every night for years.
Until I made my peace with him.
See, I come to find out
I'm just a man.
And at the right moment,
a man might do anything.
Any man.
There is no line.
There's just the law.
That's what separates us
from the animals.
There is no line.
Alfred?
I thought about what you said.
And you're right.
Pursuing Galavan on my own
is too risky.
Well, you don't say.
Best course of action
is call Detective Gordon
in the morning.
Enlist his help.
At last, some sense.
You're thinking of retiring,
are you, sir?
Yeah, yeah. Very tired.
Right, can I get you anything
to eat before you go to bed?
No.
No, thank you, Alfred.
Right, well, sleep well.
Oh, and, uh, Master Bruce?
I sent that car off that's
parked at the end of the lane.
You know, the taxi.
Don't worry, I gave
him a right good tip.
I mean, after all, he did drive
all the way up here, didn't he?
I didn't call a taxi.
You really are the most...
terrible liar, aren't
you, Master Bruce?
I will not stop
pursuing this, Alfred.
I'm never
going to give up.
And nor will I.
Good night, sir.
(groans)
WOMAN (over recording):
♪ The fire has gone out ♪
♪ Wet from snow above ♪
NYGMA (singing along): ♪ But
nothing will warm me more ♪
♪ Than my, my mother's love ♪
♪ I light another candle ♪
♪ To dry the tears
from my face... ♪
Why are you
playing this song?
(woman continues singing
over recording)
I can bring tears
to your eyes
and resurrect the dead.
I form in an instant
and last a lifetime.
What am I?
A memory.
So what?
You were humming this
under your covers.
I figure it has meaning for you.
(chuckles softly)
(sniffles)
Every night when I was young,
my mother would sing
that song to me
when I was
going to bed.
And every time,
she would tell me...
(music fades,
helicopter passing in distance)
"Oswald...
"...don't listen
to the other children.
"You're handsome and clever.
And some day,
you will be a great man."
(both chuckle softly)
She said that every time.
(sniffles)
That's all I
have left now.
Memories.
And they're like
daggers in my heart.
Not forever.
These were Ms. Kringle's.
It's all I have left
to remember her by.
But when I look at these,
I don't feel sadness anymore.
I feel gratitude.
And do you know why?
No. And I don't care.
This little
visit is over.
I will just
simply bid you
adieu.
Mr. Penguin.
For some men, love is
a source of strength.
But for you and I,
it will always be
our most crippling weakness.
Move aside, Ed!
We are better off unencumbered.
What did you say?
You said it yourself.
Your mother is dead
because of your weakness.
But what you need to realize
is that your weakness
was her.
(grunts)
My mother was a saint!
The only person who
truly cared about me,
and now she's gone!
And I have nothing left!
A man with nothing
that he loves...
...is a man
who cannot be bargained.
A man that cannot be
betrayed.
A man who answers to no one...
but himself.
And that is the man
that I see before me.
A free man.
(sirens wailing)
GORDON (over radio):
Are the EMTs with you?
Captain Barnes needs
immediate attention.
Ambulance is
still inbound.
We'll secure the perimeter...
Wait, wait, hold on!
OFFICER 2:
Behind you!
(gunfire over phone)
Officer?
(shouting)
Officer?!
(gunfire, screaming)
EDUARDO:
Hola.
Detective Gordon, I presume?
Who is this?
This is Eduardo Flamingo.
Is that name supposed to mean
something to me?
Not yet.
But it will.
I'll be upstairs
in a few minutes.
I'm going to feast
on your friends first.
Save you for dessert.
You try to run,
I will find you.
I won't.
In fact, I'm coming down.
What the hell
is going on down there?
We've got another hit man.
He's just taken out
all of our backup.
I'm going down to end this.
You... He just killed four cops!
You're not going
anywhere on your own.
He's right.
I'm coming with you.
No, you're staying here.
You need to make sure
he doesn't bleed out.
I just said you're not
going down there solo.
We'll make them
come to us.
We stay here,
we're sitting ducks.
He's after me, boss.
Go.
(elevator bell dings)
(elevator whirring)
(phone ringing)
(indistinct
police radio chatter)
(grunts)
(both grunting)
♪ ♪
(laughing)
(panting)
(Gordon yells)
Oh, baby.
You disappoint me.
You have the right
to remain silent.
I suggest you use it.
(sirens approaching)
I'll make sure he gets
processed and put in lockup.
Thanks.
And, Parks...
you did good today.
OSWALD and NYGMA:
♪ For my mother looks over me. ♪
And again!
♪ The fire has gone out ♪
♪ Wet snow from above ♪
♪ But nothing will
warm me more ♪
♪ Than my, my
mother's love. ♪
What happened to that gentleman
you had tied up earlier?
Galavan's lackey?
Why do you ask?
(muffled whimpering)
My mother always said
a party is not a party
without entertainment.
(Leonard grunts)
(muffled screaming)
♪ ♪
Sneaking out to see
your girlfriend, huh?
Selina, what are you
doing here?
Saving your ass
from making a big mistake.
Silver is bad news, Bruce.
You've said that before.
This time,
I have proof.
You interested?
You're going away for a
long time, Mr. Flamingo.
(groaning)
Get up!
I said get up!
(screaming)
(officers shouting)
(screaming continues)
Lee...
Hold still.
Thank you.
I almost crossed
the line tonight.
No kidding.
How out of character.
Scared me a little.
Welcome to my world.
Why the hell are you with me?
Beats me.
Just tell me the truth.
Always.
I promise.
(phone ringing)
Uh-uh.
Detective James Gordon's phone.
This is Lee Thompkins speaking.
Hi, Alvarez.
I'll tell him.
Eduardo Flamingo
killed Officer Parks
before they could
get him into lockup.
Hit men?
You sent hit men
after Jim Gordon,
after I expressly
told you to do nothing
until I gave you orders?
Nothing.
Tell me this isn't
about Barbara.
He hurt her.
I'm disappointed
that you let
a woman like that
get in your head.
If you're feeling upset,
find yourself a nice librarian
to torture.
That always
cheers you up.
Everything is ready.
The brothers' arrival
is imminent.
Bruce Wayne will die,
and his company
and this city will be mine.
Ours.
Everything
that we have
worked for for so long
will be ours.
Endanger that prize again,
and though it breaks my heart,
I will cut your throat.
Welcome, brothers.
Welcome.
Hey!
(indistinct
police radio chatter)
Docks are closed.
I need to see some I.D.
Wait...
No! (grunting)
(blades stabbing)
(officer gasping)