Previously onGotham...
You're the brother I never had.
We will create a legacy in this city.
Gotham falls, we rise together.
Poor Jim. All alone again.
- I told you to leave.
- I heard you.
So many things I wish I could change.
Things I have done.
We're here now.
We'll try to put the pieces
back together again.
Jim, I'm pregnant.
- This isn't you.
- We are not the same.
That night when your parents
were murdered,
I didn't do anything
because I didn't care.
Everyone, let's dig a little deeper.
'Cause that's the only way
you're all making it out
of this hole.
Deep enough?
You're leaving Gotham.
There's nothing left for me here
anymore.
- I've done all I can.
- I want in.
I love family reunions.
Don't you?
- Go!
Go!
Hurry!
- Which way?
- Wait.
General, you were the ones
who let Walker operate,
right under your noses.
Now you're telling me
she evaded capture?
I understand your frustration.
Have you at least determined
why she did what she did?
Not yet.
Look, bottom line, Walker
and Dorrance are out of the picture.
What else is standing in the way
of reunification?
Nothing. I'm recommending
we begin the process immediately.
There have been a lot of promises
from across the river.
But unlike Walker or whoever she is,
I have the authority to take action.
Unless something happens
to destabilize Gotham again,
this nightmare is about to end.
Think he's for real?
I'll believe it when it happens.
I take it your search party
didn't find Alfred.
Neither hide nor hair.
Pennyworth vanished five days ago.
It ain't looking good.
How's Bruce?
He's been pulling double shifts
on the search parties.
Kid's dead on his feet.
I want to search this area next.
There are whole blocks
of abandoned buildings.
I'll get a squad right on it.
Just give me five minutes,
I'll be ready.
- You're not going out.
- No, Jim!
You need your rest.
I'm not cutting you out.
But I need you sharp,
not a liability.
I just don't understand
what could've happened.
Neither do I.
But I know that Alfred Pennyworth
can take care of himself.
I'll send for you if I hear anything.
- Kid's tough.
- Yeah.
In other goodish news, Harper
radioed, squad found something.
What?
It's weird.
Four men.
Looks like they breathed
in some sort of chemical agent.
I'm thinking airborne.
And the Z's on their bodies?
Carved into them before
the time of death.
Check out the mustache.
Fake.
It seems that they escaped from here.
- A film set?
- I said it was weird.
The Z's on their chests,
think it could be Zsasz?
No, chemicals aren't really his M.O..
Plus, I never figured Zsasz
for much of a cinephile.
But whoever it is,
if they have more of these chemicals,
- and the will to use them.
- It's, It's bye-bye reunification.
We gotta stop him before news
reaches the mainland.
The Chessmen.
It's a gang that operates
out of the Narrows.
What the hell is a Narrows gang
doing way up here?
I think we both know
someone we can ask.
Can you check on the fever
in bed twelve?
What's up, Doc?
Heard you were working here.
Interesting.
It's what I do, help people.
Speaking of which, I've got patients.
Oh, you wouldn't kick Jim's baby
momma to the curb now, would you?
Whatever happened between you
and Jim, it's none of my concern.
- So, if you're here to gloat...
- I'm here for medical assistance.
For my little nugget.
- What do you say? Be my OB?
- You can't be serious.
I know you we've had our differences.
You tried to kill me, Barbara.
Twice.
That was years ago.
- There are other doctors here.
- Not as good as you.
Look, whatever you think of me,
my child is innocent,
and I want the best for it.
And in this place that means you.
- Does Jim know you're here?
- This is none of his business.
Lee?
Jim.
- Barbara.
- You're interrupting.
Doctor patient. Blow.
- I'm sorry, you're her doctor?
- No.
I don't know. Maybe.
What are you doing here?
Some bodies turned up.
There might have been Narrows
connection.
- I wouldn't have come but...
- It's important. Right.
You two need to talk.
- I'll be outside.
- I'd rather not.
If you want me to be your doctor,
you will talk to the baby's father.
Your first appointment is next week.
The nurse will give you
all your vitamins when you leave.
Deal?
Is she really the only one
you could find?
She's the best doctor
in this hellhole of a city.
- Not everything is about Jim Gordon.
- Pretty sure this one is.
Because we slept together, yeah.
I only told you because
I felt you had a right to know.
But your involvement in this ended
the moment you put your pants
back on.
Or what?
You don't think
I'm fit to be a mother?
What do you think?
Barbara.
Who are you?
- Well, look who decided to join us.
- Hello, Champ.
Master Bruce!
- Alfred. How did you...
- Look at the state of you.
What have I told you about
rolling around in the muck?
Alfred, what's going on?
Who are these people?
Whatever do you mean, Bruce?
We're your parents.
Right.
Well, let's get you spruced up.
After all, we have a guest.
Welcome home, Bruce.
Jeremiah.
You're alive.
Well, you didn't think Selina
could kill me so easily, did you?
I just had to put you off my scent
until I could finalize my project.
Manners, Master Bruce!
Let's not be rude to our guest.
Especially, when I come
bearing gifts.
Oh, Mr. Jeremiah. A cake!
How exceedingly kind of you.
Is it Italian meringue?
- Sure.
- Oh.
Now, now, Bruce.
You come any closer,
and I blow up Wayne Manor
with all of us inside of it.
I have a dozen more of these,
Italian meringues,
sprinkled all throughout the house.
What did you do to Alfred?
And who are these people?
Ah, glad you asked.
Hmm, come. Come, come.
Mommy and Daddy dearest...
Were just an innocent couple
I kidnapped
based on bone structure and...
build.
Just a touch of plastic surgery
and voilà, Waynes.
Alfred, I nabbed in the Green Zone.
They're hypnotized.
Well, I'm afraid there's no room
for improv in our script.
Today is a very important day, Bruce.
Just look at the way they're dressed.
It's the night my parents
were killed.
And I'm giving you the chance
to experience it all over again.
Why?
Isn't it obvious?
Bruce...
this, this was the most
important day of your life.
And I didn't get to be a part of it.
Well, we need to rectify that.
Alfred, it's time for dinner.
Chop-chop!
We're on a very tight schedule.
Of course, Mr. Jeremiah.
That's zero for three.
Yes.
Seems the government was quite
thorough when they mined the river.
You didn't have a plan
to get off this rock
before you stole everyone's crap?
I was working on a plan.
The river is mined.
Everything that flies out
gets blown from the sky.
What?
Jeremiah was digging a tunnel
under the river.
A tunnel?
- Really?
- Do you have any better ideas?
Didn't think so.
It's in the Dark Zone.
We should wait until night
to check it out.
Well, I was running out of guinea
pigs anyway.
Oh, look, he's swimming ashore.
Are you sure you should be
out in the Narrows alone?
When the bridges fell,
this place descended into chaos.
Figure our best bet of getting out
in one piece
is to keep a low profile.
So, all the work I did to make
the Narrows better was for nothing.
It's the Leopards.
Rivals of the Chessmen.
The freak is dead.
- About this Barbara thing...
- Jim, just don't.
No, it's important to me
that you understand.
Okay. So, what're you gonna do?
I don't know but it's my child, too.
Barbara seems to have a difference
in opinion.
But hey, people change.
- You don't know her like I do.
- You can say that again.
Look.
We're clear.
The Chessmen moved around.
They used these as signals
for their members.
The rook's a compass needle.
North-northeast. Let's go.
Alfred told me such great tidbits
about your childhood.
How you used to eat here
in the kitchen when it was just you
and the family.
My, how homey and intimate.
The grilled cheese and Branston
pickle sandwich, Mr. Jeremiah.
Master Bruce's favorite.
My influence though Thomas did
add a dash of aioli for extra flair.
Oh, come on, Bruce.
That's a weird favorite food
for a twelve year old.
I'm playing your game.
Now, let Alfred and these people go.
They're innocent.
I'm sorry, Bruce.
It's just, it's very important to me
that I get every detail
exactly right.
Speaking of which, the final touch.
What was it like...
losing your parents that night?
I lost my family too, Bruce.
The wound still hasn't healed.
I think about it often.
None of this is real.
You're trying to manipulate me.
It will never be real.
But you are thinking about
that night.
And that's all I need.
I just wanna be connected to you.
I offered for you
to be my best friend!
But I realized
if we can't be friends,
then we can be connected
in other ways.
How?
You'll see.
In time.
I'm sorry to cut the night short,
but your parents and I
have a very important date.
- Jeremiah!
- With destiny.
Jeremiah!
You might want to find
your faithful butler and leave.
Quickly.
Alfred!
The signs lead this way.
Look at the smoke.
Someone restarted production.
Oh, my God, Jim.
Look at all of this.
Come on.
Who's in charge here?
Tick tock, the chemical stock
shall give our Gotham an aftershock.
- Tick tock.
The chemical stock
shall give our Gotham an aftershock.
- They've been hypnotized.
- It was Tetch.
Tick tock, the chemical stock
shall give our Gotham an aftershock.
My, my, what a thrill.
Jim Gordon and the woman
he told me to kill.
Brings back memories.
That tea party, so long ago.
But now, to order these men
to attack my foe!
All for one, and one for all.
Isn't this a grand old ball!
Yoo-hoo!
- Jim!
- Ain't this some
game.
Give it to me again?
Penguin has been stealing everything
in the City that's not nailed down
and now he needs a way
of getting it off the island.
- And you're helping him.
- Well, that's what he thinks.
Barbara, Tabitha was my friend, too.
If anything, I wanna gut the twerp
and take his loot.
Except you don't actually
have a way out of Gotham.
I'll find one tonight.
I'll still need your help
moving the stuff.
We can get out of here together.
Away from Jim Gordon.
Rich as Midas.
Penguin dead in a ditch.
Well, aren't we just
two single ladies and a baby,
about to kill
our sworn enemy together.
What?
It's just you're pregnant.
Don't even start.
Alfred!
Alfred, we need to get out of here.
Ah, Master Bruce, I was just taking
a quiet moment to tidy up.
We need to go. The bombs.
- What bombs?
- These bombs!
No need for rough housing, sir.
There has to be a way.
Alfred, you'd do anything to protect
me, right?
Absolutely, sir.
There's a gas leak. In the kitchen.
It's only a matter of time
before this whole place goes up.
A gas leak?
Where're your parents?
Where's our guest?
I've already warned them.
I know a way out. Come on!
Alfred!
Alfred.
- Oh, bloody hell.
- Don't move.
Do you...
Oh, yeah. I remember everything.
Clear as day.
Let me tell you if ever I see that
Jervis Tetch character again,
I'll stick that watch so far up his,
his nose.
How about you?
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm all right.
The Manor.
Don't you worry about that now, son.
Come on, help me up.
Oh, your leg's hurt.
Yeah, it's all right.
It's not broken.
I thought I lost you.
Me?
Never, Master Bruce.
Go on.
You know where he's gonna be at.
Go.
If you're here,
Jeremiah must still alive.
And if you're here, I'm guessing
you found our test subjects,
all boiled and bubbled.
What's he planning?
It's a surprise, don't you know?
A real killer.
Shall I hypnotize our friends here,
and have them slit each other's
necks?
Nix.
Better check with the boss.
He might have other ideas.
I'm sorry I got you involved in this.
Don't be. I knew
what I was getting myself into.
I know but, Lee...
Jim, whatever you wanna tell me,
save it till we're out of here.
Fair enough.
We need to find out
what Valeska's planning.
Hey, Tetch.
You know, it's funny.
I never figured you
for Jeremiah's errand boy.
Oh, Captain.
No errands do I run.
This is simply a way for me
to have some fun.
Tell yourself that.
What are you, when you would take
away your games and your rhymes?
Nothing but a second-rater
with that really silly hat.
Shut up.
Beautiful.
Lee Thompkins,
you do intrigue me so.
First, you were a doctor.
Then, the Narrows Queen.
Tell me, please do.
Are you running from your past,
when you become someone new?
When I found Jeremiah,
he had a bunch of crazies
digging this tunnel for him.
Well, that certainly fills me
with confidence.
You hear that?
- Alfred?
- Selina?
What are you doing here?
And with that?
I should ask you the same thing.
What's down that tunnel?
Well, it was Wayne Manor
till Jeremiah blew it up.
He sealed the only way out of Gotham.
No, Jeremiah is not alive.
I... I saw him die, right here.
Yeah, well, you're wrong.
We all were.
And now he's embarked
on some mad cap scheme,
where he's reenacting the night
Bruce's parents were killed.
- Where's Bruce?
- He's gone after Jeremiah.
He could use your help.
- Wait...
- Don't.
You think, that because
I did not kill Jeremiah
does not mean that I won't kill you.
- Selina.
- You killed my friend, Tabitha.
- You deserve to die.
- Selina.
Just put the knife down.
Bruce needs you.
I suppose I should thank you.
Or you could help me
to the Green Zone.
Of course. It's that way.
Jeremiah!
Show yourself!
Olle!
Hola, Bruce.
Well, here we are.
The theater where your Mummy
and Daddy took you to see
The Mark of Zorro.
I had heard you were obsessed
with this man as a child.
I wonder what it was
that intrigued you so.
Was it the fact that he struck
fear into the heart of his enemy?
En guarde!
Take that, villain!
Vagabond!
You know what?
Perhaps, the movie
was a bit too effective.
Isn't this the part
where you became frightened?
When you asked your parents to leave?
I wonder what would've happened
if you hadn't done that.
If you had conquered your fear.
Maybe your parents
would still be alive.
Well, on to the last and final stop
down memory lane.
Stop!
That's far enough, Bruce.
Jeremiah,
you don't have to do this!
But I, I do.
You see, I came to this realization,
I realized that no matter
what I did to bond us,
some random gunman in an alley
would be the man
who you were tied to the most.
The man you saw
when you closed your eyes.
I want to be the star of the show.
So, if I can't have you
as a brother bonded by love,
then we'll just have to be
bonded by hatred.
And you think killing two people that
look like my parents will do that?
It won't.
Then it's a good thing
I already put a bullet
in both of their fraudulent skulls.
Oh, you're confused.
You're wondering if I already shot
them, then who is this lovely couple.
Thomas, Martha.
Why don't you turn around?
Jim!
I know.
See, over the course
of our little adventure,
fate brought to me
James Gordon and Leslie Thompkins.
and I thought to myself...
why not?
Why not kill the man who you think
of as your second father figure?
And your dear, dear,
dear friend, Lee Thompkins.
And when I do,
finally you and I
will be bound together.
'Cause you see...
Reunification with the mainland
hangs on by a thread.
Those fireworks go off, and toxic
chemicals rain down onto the city,
and the government cuts
us adrift for good.
Jeremiah,
don't.
le pièce de résistance.
One last thing,
I had Jervis Tetch hypnotize them
so that they'll wake up
the moment these
beautiful pearls hit the ground.
I want you to see them realize
what I've done to them
as the life drains from their bodies.
Never forget,
this is all for you, Bruce.
No!
Selina, the pearls!
Ecco! Now!
We need to stop the fireworks.
They're gonna...
I know. You go after Jeremiah
and Ecco! I'll take the truck!
There's no way to stop them all.
Get to Harvey.
Warn the people in the Green Zone
to get to cover.
What are you...
Jim!
Jeremiah!
Face me!
Here, Bruce!
Jeremiah!
This ends, tonight.
No.
No, Bruce. Now, it begins.
Yes.
You feel it,
the connection between us?
You do.
Don't you?
Oh, Bruce, you feel it?
Tell me you feel this.
You mean nothing to me.
Why don't you understand?
You need me!
I'm the answer
to your life's question.
Without me, you're just a joke...
without a punch line.
After all this time,
you've come to me for help?
After allowing Strange
to put a chip into my brain?
Attempting to sell me out to Gordon?
And after naming..
a dog after me?
First of all,
I am very fond of that dog.
Secondly, I had Hugo Strange
save your life.
Thirdly, do you really think
I didn't have plans
to save you from Jim Gordon?
You always have an answer
for everything, don't you Oswald?
We have been through
all of this before.
I've tried to kill you,
you've tried to kill me.
But here we are, in this room.
Together.
It means fate has different plans
for us.
What are these plans?
Haven't you realized
what Gotham is yet?
It is no longer a city.
It is a prison.
And I think it's time we escaped.
You heard the news?
Everybody is talking about it.
Reunification isn't happening.
Word of the chemical spill
reached the mainland.
No action until the government
can determine if Gotham is safe.
I figure at least a couple of months.
You don't sound surprised.
Guess I'm not.
Could've been much worse.
You stopped that.
Every time I think
we're turning things around,
I look up, right back
where we started.
What were you about to say to me,
when, Tetch had us?
I don't know.
I guess I, would've said...
would've said the last time
we saw each other...
I wish I could go back.
Do things differently.
Better.
- That feels like a long time ago.
- Nothing's changed.
But it has, Jim.
- That was a mistake.
- Mistake?
Put yourself in my shoes.
After everything you said,
suddenly you're having a baby
with Barbara, of all people.
But it's not just that.
You talk about doing things
differently and I keep thinking...
what if we hadn't lost ours.
What're you doing here, Lee?
I don't know.
I know you've taken on so much and...
and I want to be understanding.
But...
You let me down, Jim.
I'm sorry.
What does that mean?
For us?
I don't know.
You can't change the past so,
I guess we just have to live with it.
No, please.
I can't believe he's still alive.
They've been doing scans,
and he has no brain activity.
He's no longer a threat.
To either of us.
Thank you for coming to help me.
The night your parents were killed.
I should have done something.
Selina, you've done enough.
It's not much but it's home.
I've been looking
through your treasure trove.
You've been a very naughty boy.
Barbara? How did you...
- Selina.
- Hmm.
She and I were gonna go
murder-halvsies
to get you back for Tabitha.
But it seems I will have to do
the dirty work myself.
- As usual.
- Oh, my God!
You're pregnant!
How could you possibly know that?
Look at you! She's glowing.
You're glowing!
How very observant of you.
- Adieu, Oswald.
- Wait!
Come with us!
- What?
- Yes,
I killed Tabitha.
You are angry. You want revenge.
But do you really wanna raise
your child in a toxic waste war zone?
Come with us.
Are you telling me you found a way
out of Gotham?
Ed did.
- It's a submarine.
- A submarine?
It can track mines in the river
using sonar.
So, where's this submarine?
- We have to build it.
- Yeah, I'm gonna shoot you.
God!
What is happening to me?
- Perhaps...
- Shut up!
That was a rhetorical question.
Fine.
I won't shoot you.
For the sake of my child.
But I will never forgive you.
Of course.
I understand.
Call me when it's done.
- So, who's the lucky father?
- Shut up!