GORDON:
Previously on Gotham...
My forefathers were betrayed,
their legacy erased,
and I am here to punish
those who wronged us.
We have a deal?
We do.
I'll do whatever it takes.
I'll train every day.
Yeah.
Well, you said
that before, didn't you?
I'll even go back to school.
(screams)
I saved your life.
You wanted to do it, too,
you just didn't have the guts.
Selena, I miss you.
THEO: This is not
what we rehearsed.
I'm so sorry, Jerome.
Enter the hero.
(clamoring)
(gunshot)
OSWALD:
Gentlemen!
Ladies! Others!
Let us discuss the future with
a little civility, shall we?
So...
not one of you knows
who orchestrated
and/or executed
the Arkham breakout?
I find that hard to believe.
I mean, the cops' only lead
is an old blind man,
for God's sake.
A blind man!
Then who here is to be trusted?
Because someone knows.
Uh...
we thought it was you.
Why would I do that?
We've never had it better.
I gave you all of
the freedom in the world
and business boomed.
For all of us.
A new generation.
Then that ginger maniac
had to spoil everything.
Even now he's dead,
the public is still terrified,
business is in the can
and what are we doing?
Fighting among
ourselves.
Is this how any of us
want to live?
Squabbling, brawling,
running, hiding?
This city belongs to us now.
But kids,
that brings responsibilities.
We need to restore
confidence in our brand,
if you will.
We need discipline
and unity, yes?
There will be no more chaos.
No more gang wars.
No more blood
in the streets,
scaring decent folk.
From now on,
if you want to kill someone,
blackmail, steal
or kidnap anyone,
I need to hear about it first.
Understand?
Yeah, got it.
Yeah.
Fine.
(all murmuring, grumbling)
(whispering):
Boss, there's somebody...
(continues indistinctly)
Bravo.
Quite the King Solomon.
You had them
nicely in line.
Who are you?
My brother would very much like
to talk to you.
Alone.
Why you looking at me like that?
You don't know me.
Relax, Butch.
He has issues.
Bipolar.
She don't know me,
I'm just saying.
(sighs)
Your brother?
Theodore Galavan.
There's a car waiting
for you outside.
I'm sick and tired of your
holier-than-thou crap, Gordon!
Yeah? Then do some
police work.
Last arrest you made
was your bookie.
My name is Nathaniel Barnes.
Captain Nathaniel Barnes.
That's right.
I'm your new boss.
Ten-hut!
BARNES:
You.
Clean that up.
You know
when this place was built?
Over 100 years ago.
Can you imagine how many perps
have been booked in here
since that time?
All the murderers, rapists,
thieves that have been
locked up?
They don't make 'em
like this anymore--
strong, sturdy.
And yet...
just days ago,
an escaped convict
just strolls in here,
into our house-- our house--
and murders your commissioner
and nine of
your fellow comrades.
I wasn't even here
and I'm ashamed.
Are you all ashamed?
I hope so.
Anyone that's here
that's not ashamed,
and angry,
should resign.
Right now.
Huh.
Some of you are lying
to yourselves.
I've got your files here.
I've read them all.
Step forward
if you hear your name called.
Pollard.
Guthrie.
Coulson.
Dowler.
Brooks.
Perez.
Hightower.
You aren't ashamed.
You have no shame.
You're not police,
you're low-life criminals.
Bribery,
drug abuse,
extortion,
racketeering...
Sons of bitches!
You're all fired!
Drop off your badges
and your guns
with the desk sergeant
on your way out.
PEREZ:
Hey.
You can do this!
We got rights!
Yes, you're right.
You do have rights.
You have the right
to remain silent.
to an attorney.
Take him.
From now on...
any officer,
detective, rookie or clerk
who breaks the law
will not just
lose their job,
they will go to jail.
If you turn a blind eye
to crime,
I will bust you.
If you fail to help
a fellow officer
because of cowardice or apathy,
I will bust you!
What the hell
are you still doing here?
Don't make me mad.
Anyone who didn't hear
their name called,
get back to work.
I'd like to see you
in my office, please.
Well, what do you think
about what I said out there?
I agree with
every word, sir.
Every word, huh?
You a sycophant, Gordon?
No, sir.
"No, sir."
I've read all your files.
Army, Academy, GCPD.
You're a troublemaker.
A fighter.
Is that an accurate
assessment?
Yes, sir.
Good.
You're my second in command.
Starting now, Jim,
we're gonna fix this department
and bring respect for
law and order back to this city.
Yes, sir.
We're, uh...
kind of shorthanded.
What, you think I cut too deep?
You could have thrown out
20 more guys and not hit bottom.
Fixing this department's
gonna be tough.
Maybe tougher than you think...
sir.
Welcome to my unit,
you sad-ass Army hump.
Tough is what we eat
for breakfast.
(laughs quietly)
A jarhead, huh?
Who would've guessed?
Sir.
I hope you just told him
he made a huge mistake.
I don't think he did.
Come on, Jim, we've seen
his type come and go.
Idealists, always looking
to walk the straight line--
Gotham doesn't have
straight lines, it's got twists
and turns and dead ends.
Yeah. But it doesn't
have to be that way.
With Mayor James still missing
and the deputy mayor
recently murdered,
the need for leadership
at City Hall
is of paramount concern
to Gotham's citizens.
Today, two more
hopeful candidates
have thrown their hats
into the ring.
Janice Caulfield
is a city councillor
who began
her political career
as an environmental activist.
Randall Hobbs-- the
longest-serving teamster boss
in Gotham's history,
is another candidate
with a strong base.
In the latest polls, though,
a surprise surge
for a man who has not even
declared his candidacy--
Theo Galavan.
The dashing
billionaire businessman
has not ruled out a bid
for the mayor's job,
but he is considering
his options,
according to a spokesman.
(turns TV off)
(chuckles): Mr. Cobblepot,
finally we meet.
Call me Penguin.
I thought I heard
you hated that name.
It grew on me.
Penguin, it is.
Please, sit.
How's your head?
Oh, healing,
thank you.
(chuckles) Gave me
quite a scare.
You were lucky to get out
of there with your life.
Wasn't I just.
(chuckles quietly)
Was it luck?
You are a clever man.
Perfect timing, dear.
Do you two know
each other?
We've met.
Oh, my.
The Arkham breakout,
the GCPD massacre,
Jerome and the Maniax.
All you.
(chuckles)
Of course.
Guilty.
It was foolish of me
to think I could trick
the "The King of Gotham."
BARBARA:
Here.
You need this more than me.
I'll make another.
My sister tells me
you're doing
a stellar job
of organizing your new empire.
I try.
You're not "The King of Gotham."
You're "The King of Garbage."
A year ago,
I held Fish Mooney's umbrella.
Now she's dead
by my hand.
Along with Maroni.
Falcone is in hiding,
and all of their
businesses are mine.
They all underestimated me.
I suggest you not make
the same mistake.
My sister is too blunt.
But she is honest.
The foundations
of this great city were laid
200 years ago,
by some very dedicated people.
Now it's an old
crumbling pigsty,
full of human waste.
It's time to move
into the future.
A cleaner, brighter...
...future.
Uh...
those are all
residential areas,
so thousands of homes would have
to be destroyed, wouldn't they?
Yeah. So?
Here's the rub:
In order to rebuild,
I need first to destroy,
but I can't do that.
I mean, watch the news,
I'm a hero.
But you have a certain flair
for such a task.
You, Penguin...
you will be my destroyer.
(chuckles)
Truly, I'm flattered.
Thank you so much for
thinking of me, but...
my dear sir,
you have me all wrong.
I have no flair for destruction.
I'm a builder, a problem solver.
Besides, such a huge project
would need the support
of hundreds of
city officials.
Yes, only the highest authority
could see it through correctly.
Say, a mayor
with a landslide mandate.
But you're not a candidate.
Oh, I will be.
By popular demand.
Alas, some
of my fellow candidates
actually stand
a chance of winning,
so they'll have to go.
(scoffs)
Go?
And I'm gonna need you
to take a crack at me also.
And miss, of course.
Don't want anyone
to think that...
I had anything to do with
my fellow candidates' demise.
That's smart thinking.
However, with all due
respect, Mr. Galavan,
I'm not your man.
You need an assassin.
This is Gotham, you can
find them in the phone book.
Under "A."
One moment, Mr. Penguin.
I'm sorry, I took you
for a man of vision.
Tabitha, you want to
get the remote, dear?
Yay.
THEO:
Before you leave,
my sister would
love to show you
her favorite reality show.
She's addicted.
(chuckles)
Mmm, she's being kind
of dull right now,
but sometimes she cries
and bangs on the door.
Please.
OSWALD: Mother.
(over TV): I swear, I swear,
I don't know about this.
You'll pay for this.
(chuckles)
That's the spirit.
They die,
your mother lives.
Simple.
(Gertrude pleads
indistinctly over TV)
(over TV):
Please!
I swear, I swear,
I don't know nothing...
(Theo laughs)
(phone rings)
(Thompkins groans)
Thompkins.
BARNES:
Good morning, Dr. Thompkins.
Captain Barnes, GCPD.
Captain Barnes.
Hi.
I hear great things
about you, Doc.
Get ready to get real busy.
We're gonna be sending you
a whole lot of dead bad guys.
Oh, uh, okay-okay.
May I speak to Jim?
He wants
to talk to you.
This is Gordon.
Meet me at the police
academy at 0700.
The academy, yes, sir.
If you don't mind
me asking, sir...
Everybody knows
you're banging the M.E.
See you in an hour.
BARNES:
Oldest in your class.
Not the strongest
or the fastest
or even the most
academically gifted either,
and yet... you finished
at the top of your class.
Now how did you do that?
I'll tell you how.
You were a soldier.
You saw combat
while your classmates were
still playing with themselves
in their parents' basements.
You got blood on your face.
You could say that.
You're a warrior, Jim.
So am I.
But you can't carry on
the way you've been,
going after everyone
on your own.
You need help
that you can rely on.
With all due respect, sir...
What if there were
a team of young cops
who haven't been
bought yet?
Not jaded,
not corrupted.
Still filled with hope
and faith in the system.
Cadets.
This is the greatest
academy in the country.
Graduation
is next week.
We could grab a group
of their finest
before some precinct
kills their spirit.
Wouldn't hurt to look
into it, right?
(whistle blowing,
jump rope whipping)
GUS: Don't want anybody
getting shot...
BARNES:
Gus.
Captain Barnes.
This is Gordon.
Sure, I remember
this guy.
He argued a lot.
I'd like to think
I was raising questions.
(Gus chuckles)
What do you got for us?
This way.
(whistle blows)
(grunts)
Keep your eye
on the little one.
The one getting her
ass handed to her?
Wait.
(chuckles)
(whistle blows)
Patience.
Not your strong virtue,
if I remember right,
Gordon.
BARNES:
State wrestling champ,
academy running back.
Why this place and not
a sports scholarship?
People from my neighborhood
don't get scholarships.
They join gangs, sell drugs.
I needed to change the direction
my life was going.
Mr. Martinez...
says here you're
the best shot
this school's
ever seen.
Where'd you
learn to shoot?
Gotham gun range.
One of my mother's
three jobs was cleaning it.
When she died, the owner
let me go there after hours
and practice,
until I worked out my anger.
I still go there.
You're way too smart
to be here, Garrett.
Don't tell me--
your father's a cop.
Negative.
My father's family business
was destroyed by armed thugs
who demanded he pay them
protection money.
When he refused,
they beat him half to death.
I'm here to make sure
that doesn't ever happen again.
Garrett!
Pinkney!
Josie!
Martinez!
You swear to honor
that badge with your life?
CADETS:
Yes, sir.
Congratulations.
You are now Unit Alpha
of the GCPD Strike Force
under the command
of Detective James Gordon.
You answer only to him,
and him only to me.
Dismissed.
Strike force?
Got a nice ring to it,
doesn't it?
They're good kids.
But facing what's out there
at their age?
That's a big risk, sir.
True.
What do we got to lose?
Yes, sir.
For your acts of courage
in the face
of overwhelming uncertainty,
the city of Gotham
would like to give you
this token of appreciation.
The Medal of Valor
and Bravery.
(applause)
(clears throat)
Mr. Galavan.
Uh, please-- Theo.
Theo, for Pete's sake,
why aren't you
running for mayor?
(car tires screeching)
Get down!
(group screaming, groaning)
OFFICER:
Everybody stay where you are!
THEO:
Everyone okay?
Everyone?
(sirens wailing
in distance)
(sighs heavily)
You know what?
Gothamites don't buckle
under pressure,
and neither will I.
We will not be intimidated
by the scum
that seek to reduce
this great city of
Gotham to ruins.
If the bad guys
want to stop me running,
well, then I guess
I got no choice.
I will run for mayor.
(all cheering,
speaking affirmatively)
MAN: Yes!
WOMAN:
Hello, Caulfield for Mayor.
Yes, uh... will do!
Excuse me,
you can't go in there.
Miss Caulfield,
what a pleasure.
Allow me
to introduce myself.
I can see what you are.
How did you get in?
I know it's late,
but I'm afraid
there's no time for delay.
Someone tried to kill
Theo Galavan this morning.
Are you here to kill me?
Actually, yes.
Please, no.
I'm a mother.
Wait!
I have a mother, too.
(muffled shrieking)
Steady now, folks.
Just think of blue skies
and cornfields.
That's what I do.
Why are you doing this?
Darling,
I got no freaking idea.
We've been doing
crazy stuff all day long.
Well, we're away then.
Sorry to ruin your evening.
Now, remember...
Yeah.
I got your names and addresses.
So think about your families
and keep mum, eh?
(copy machine clicks, stops)
(boys conversing
indistinctly)
(hands gripping, feet landing)
Are you waiting for someone?
No.
That's your job.
That's for Reggie.
I know you killed him.
Now, I don't know
what you want
with Master Bruce,
but I'm certain
that his life's gonna be a damn
sight better without you in it.
So you do yourself
a favor, treacle,
and jog on.
(sniffles)
All good.
Oh, Master Bruce.
You know, I could always pull
out front, if you want.
No, uh,
Alfred, I don't want
the other kids to see...
To see that you've got a butler.
Yeah, I completely
understand that.
I made dinner reservations,
as requested,
for tomorrow night.
Mr. Galavan suggested
the Regal Hotel.
It's very posh.
You're gonna be
forking out serious dosh
for that, I'll tell you.
He saved my life.
Dinner's the least I can do
to repay him.
Uh, Master Bruce,
where are you going?
Now, I clocked Wayne Manor
at exactly six and a half miles.
It should take 90 minutes
to two hours,
depending on how many times
you stop, of course.
Now, you said
you wanted to train.
To prepare.
Well, this is it.
Wait, you...
you expect me to-to walk?
No, Master Bruce.
I expect you to run.
(car door shuts)
(engine starts)
(engine revs)
(siren wailing in distance)
Miss Kringle,
ever since
I first laid eyes on you,
I've felt this deep connection.
(clears throat)
Perhaps you've felt it, too?
Ugh. How cheesy.
Miss Kringle,
you've perhaps felt
my affections from afar.
"Afar"? Really? Oh, God.
Miss Kringle...
(wry laugh)
Be quiet.
I don't need your opinion.
What you need is
to stop mumbling
and fumbling
and tell her what's up.
Well, she's been bullied and
taken for granted for too long.
And I want her
to understand...
You saved her life!
For God's sake!
She owes you.
Take what you deserve.
KRINGLE:
Guys... (chuckles)
Miss Kringle.
Dinner, tonight.
Um...
Chez Moi. 8:00.
Okay.
I'd like that.
You will.
A wise cop once said,
if you catch a kid smashing
a window,
even a small one, bust him.
You let it slide,
and he'll smash another one.
Then he'll tag a wall,
steal a bike,
rob a store,
maybe hold someone up.
Crime unpunished
is a crime in itself.
This city is bleeding to death
from the amount of
free passes we hand out.
Time to put a tourniquet
over that wound.
From now on...
no one gets a free pass.
What is this strike force for?
To send a message that
this epidemic of lawlessness
will no longer be treated
but extinguished.
With extreme prejudice.
Gentlemen, lady,
your new uniforms.
Sir, got a caller.
Says Councillor Caulfield
has been attacked.
Says she's dead.
(indistinct chatter,
siren wailing in distance)
No security cameras.
Galavan and now her.
Looks like a damn pattern.
Only she's dead.
Come on, people!
Who knows what?
Just give us
a name, a description.
You will not have to testify.
They have our names
and addresses.
WOMAN: All right, Hanson,
can you show me...
(continues indistinctly)
Ms. Caulfield
was stabbed repeatedly.
Probably drowned
in her own blood.
Forget it, Jim.
The man with the knife
was short,
fancy clothes.
Walked funny.
Ah, Mr. Galavan.
Thank you for meeting me.
It's an honor.
The pleasure's all mine.
I'll meet you in the
lobby, Master Bruce.
Oh, why not dine with us?
That's very kind
of you, sir,
but I don't think
it's appropriate.
And I know that Master
Bruce wants to speak to you
on his own.
Sir.
Thanks, Alfred.
Enjoy.
(Theo sighs deeply)
You like this place?
I've never been here
before.
To be honest, I don't...
go out much.
Well, I hope
I can change that.
There's always
some tedious function
I could drag you to.
I just...
I wanted this opportunity
to thank you,
in person, for saving my life.
Oh, you're very kind.
The truth is,
I don't know what came over me.
I-I don't think
I was in complete control
of my faculties.
I also wanted to speak with you
face-to-face.
It's regarding
your parents' passing.
I find it astonishing
that the police have failed
to produce any evidence
or any real suspect
in all this time.
It is disappointing.
Even your father's own company,
(young woman laughs)
Wayne Enterprises,
has failed
(whoops gently)
to advance the
investigation in any way.
It's shocking.
Yes, Mr. Galavan,
it's-it's very disappointing.
(young woman chuckles)
That's Silver.
Uh, I'm sorry?
Silver St. Cloud.
Her father was my stepbrother.
He passed, sadly.
She's my ward now.
Would you like to meet her?
Yes.
Hello, my dear.
(chuckles)
Uncle.
I'd like to introduce you
to Bruce Wayne.
Nice to meet you, Bruce.
Hello.
(chuckles)
I was early, so I came out here.
It's such a warm day.
Do you know,
I do believe
that you two will be sharing
a school soon.
Anders Prep,
yes?
Silver just got back
to, uh, Gotham after
two years abroad.
Switzerland.
Geneva. Ugh.
Yes. We have a house there.
So, what's it like?
Switzerland?
No. Prep, silly.
I think it's fine.
I've been homeschooling
for quite a while now,
so I'm virtually
a new boy, too.
Then we shall brave it together.
(wry chuckle)
♪ I'm just a gigolo ♪
♪ Gigolo ♪
♪ And everywhere I go ♪
♪ Gigolo, gigolo ♪
♪ People know the part
I'm playing ♪
♪ Gigolo ♪
♪ Gigolo, gigolo,
gigolo, gigolo ♪
♪ Paid for every dance ♪
♪ gigolo... ♪
♪ Selling each romance ♪
♪ gigolo ♪
♪ Oh, what they're saying ♪
♪ Gigolo, gigolo ♪
♪ Gigolo, gigolo,
gigolo, gigolo ♪
♪ There will come a day
when youth will pass away ♪
♪ Oop, what will
they say about me? ♪
♪ When the end comes,
I know... ♪
♪ Life goes on without me... ♪
I was kind of expecting
a restaurant.
Miss Kringle, I'm so sorry.
I-I'm sorry.
I should have been more clear.
Uh, I like
to cook.
(chuckles)
I'm a good cook. Is that okay?
It is. It is. Um, and...
perhaps you should call me
Kristen.
♪ When the end comes, I know ♪
♪ They'll say just a gigolo ♪
♪ Life goes on without me. ♪
(door clangs shut,
thunder rumbles)
Hobbs' campaign office is
the entire second floor.
You sure about this?
Don't worry.
I've got it under control.
Okay, you gotta tell me
what the hell's going on.
I know I gotta do
whatever you say,
but at least tell me why
the hell we're doing it.
They have my mother, Butch.
Who?
Galavan and his sister.
They have her.
They're making me do this.
Holy smokes.
We gotta find your mom.
If they find out we're looking,
they'll hurt her.
(pats leg)
Don't worry.
We'll find her.
(vehicle approaching)
(sniffles)
(brakes squeaking)
He's here.
(clears his throat)
Let's go.
Got it. Thanks.
(thunder rumbling)
I still think we should move you
somewhere a little more secure.
Forget it. Anyone has the guts
to come after me--
they'll find out real soon
who they're messin' with.
(conversation continues
indistinctly in distance)
BODYGUARD:
Whoa-ho-ho...
Who the hell are you?
Oh.
(clears his throat)
I came here to volunteer.
(scoffs)
Well, run back
to whoever hired you.
Tell them I'm not
going anywhere.
This city needs me.
Oh...!
Cool pins.
Count, idiot.
There's five of us.
I know.
Hardly seems fair.
BODYGUARD: Move, move,
move, move, move! Go!
Aah!
(bodyguard groans)
(horn honks, siren blares)
Keep going!
There you go.
Right there!
Go!
(gunshot)
(groans)
GORDON:
GCPD! Put down your weapons!
(whimpers)
Fan out! Flank him
from both sides,
catch him in
our crossfire.
Yeah, do that.
I'll cover you. Go!
(gunfire blasting)
BULLOCK:
Okay.
So they move well.
Aah!
(groans)
Unexpected.
Move! Move, move, move!
(Josie gasping in pain)
(groans)
Let's go!
(Josie gasping)
Shooter got away, sir.
(panting)
You just met Victor Zsasz.
Works for Penguin
these days.
What the hell
is Penguin playing at?
(thunder rumbling)
♪ I love how
your eyes close... ♪
(laughter)
Not, but I... I feel like,
um, I owe you an apology.
I feel as though I have been
nothing but mean to you.
No, I don't think that's fair.
I feel like all I've ever done
is... is annoy you.
(laughs)
I've been consistently
inappropriate.
No. No, no, no, no, it's me.
You have been nothing but sweet,
and I ignored your card
and your... your gift.
Miss Kringle,
I can honestly say
that our interactions are always
the highlight of my day.
Please. Uh... Kristen.
Oh, my, God,
I even accused you
of writing Dougherty's
good-bye note.
Right. (laughs)
Crazy.
I mean, oh...
who knows what that jerk
was thinking?
Jerk.
How I ever
let him lay a hand on me,
I'll never know.
I'm glad he's dead.
♪ If I've been told... ♪
(phonograph needle scratches,
music stops)
Well, he's...
he just left town.
He's not... dead.
Right, yeah, I know.
Figure of speech.
He's dead to you.
Out of your life.
Not dead, dead.
Oh...
Um... (clears her throat)
I'm gonna use the restroom.
You blew it, dummy. Nice work.
Leave me alone!
Are you talking to me?
No.
Honestly, Kristen,
I wasn't talking to you.
Who else is there?
I talk...
to myself.
It's crazy, I know.
I just, I have this, um...
I have this voice
inside my head,
a sort of stronger
version of me,
that keeps this me in line,
because I'm such a klutz.
I can understand that.
I think that we all
have a voice like that.
You think?
What was
your inner voice saying?
He was mad at me for
spoiling the mood.
Mm-hmm.
It was...
it was a really nice mood.
But my...
inner voice is telling me that
I think maybe
we can get back there.
(laughs)
(giggling)
(thunder rumbling)
(door opens)
(door creaks shut)
You killed Caulfield.
We have a witness.
And the attempt on
Galavan-- was that you, too?
Not now.
And Hobbs.
You sent Zsasz there?
It's complicated, okay?
What does it profit you
to mess with the election?
You have your own sordid
empire to rule over.
Walk away, Jim.
Let me be.
The GCPD has new leadership.
No more deals,
no more favors.
If they find out
you're behind these attacks,
we will come after you
with every...
Rousing speech!
Really!
Goosebumps.
But you came here alone, Jim,
with no warrant, no cuffs,
no backup, and why?
Because you would hate
for your new captain to find out
about how you gunned down
Ogden Barker in cold blood.
Over a debt.
(laughs)
A debt to me.
He was trying to kill me.
Where are your witnesses?
And just that day before,
I suppose
you did not ask me to run
Commissioner Loeb out of town
so that you could
get your old job back?
I'll face
whatever's coming to me.
As will I.
Good-bye, Jim.
JOSIE: Obviously.
MARTINEZ:
I don't think so.
I'm serious.
Singed for a second.
Hey, you shouldn't be joking
about near misses.
Next bullet might get stuck
right in your eye.
Yes, sir.
No joking.
BARNES:
All right, gather round.
Today, I'm giving the strike
force its first real mission.
Build a case to put away
Gotham's Enemy Number One.
Time to take down The Penguin.
(students conversing
indistinctly)
Bruce?
YOUNG WOMAN: Hey, Selina,
come on, let's go.
ALFRED: I don't know what
you want with Master Bruce,
but I'm certain
that his life's gonna be
a damn sight better
without you in it.
So, what do you think? Red?
Or blue?
Red.
Blue.
Blue it is.
I want some fun.
I'm sick
of staying indoors.
Patience, Barbara.
Your time will come.
The wheel is turning.
While the GCPD
chase The Penguin,
I'll steal the mayor's office
right from under their noses.
Did you find her?
(door closes)
(moaning)
(yelling)