There you are.
I've been all round the bloody house
looking for you.
- What're you doing?
- Nothing.
You, my old son, are a terrible liar.
What have you got there?
Come on, show me.
Oh, you stupid little boy!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
It's gonna be all right.
Hi! I'm Patti.
This is Doug.
We're with the Mayor's Homeless
Outreach Project.
We have some sandwiches
and some soup.
We got cookies. We got candy.
Who here likes chocolate?
Ain't you hungry, Cat?
Yeah, dig in. Take a sandwich.
- This is what I need.
- Sure. Go ahead.
Plenty for everyone.
Yeah, sure. Take two.
- Hey!
- Hey, lady.
- Fudge!
- Don't worry. I'll go.
Slow down there, buckaroo.
I got you one, but I dropped it.
Yeah, thanks.
- Where is everybody?
- I don't know.
What do you think?
I think it's been a long shift.
We give this bum three hours,
then we knock off.
He was a vet.
I salute his service.
Now he's a dead bum.
People are shooting bums
all the time.
We might as well be looking
for the tooth fairy.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, Bo.
How come you weren't here?
Good morning to you, too.
Where were you?
I was at the restaurant down
the street here. Chezz Vowse.
They had some homeless junkie kid
fell through their front window
last night.
I've been taking care of that.
This is a potential murder.
You're first responder.
You're supposed to preserve
the integrity of the crime scene.
He's got a point.
The restaurant that pays me
50 a month to look after them.
So I'm gonna babysit a dead wino?
I got a family.
He's got a point.
Why the kid jump through the window?
Who knows? He was high.
- Did you ask him?
- Why am I the bad guy here?
I'm asking about the kid because
maybe he's related to the victim.
You're not a bad guy.
You're just a bad cop.
Oh, who are you talking to?
- I know where you hide him.
- Come on! Come on!
You want it? Any day.
Hey!
Zeb and Smoke went right down,
and that's when that wacky dude
just shot Soldier,
and that's when I realized
I needed to get out of there.
So I ran and I ran,
and that's how I end up
on the floor of that restaurant.
- She used a pin.
- I swear!
A big pin.
But listen,
this is not the first time.
Street kids have been disappearing
for weeks now.
By a dozen. No one knows why.
First, we've heard of it.
Why would you?
Nobody gives a crap about us.
- I mean, look! That is...
- Proof! Proof!
That's a scab. Now listen, Mackey.
We're grown-ups.
We're smarter than you.
- Man, whatever.
- You're gonna tell me the truth!
It was you, wasn't it?
It was you that killed
that poor old man.
It was you!
Now you got to tell me the truth
or I swear to God
I'm gonna beat it out of you!
That old man was a war veteran!
Listen, Cat was there.
Cat saw the whole thing.
- Ask Cat.
- Relax, Mackey, relax.
No one's gonna beat you. Who's Cat?
What do you mean
no one's gonna beat him?
Isn't that what I just said
I was gonna do right now?
- Just now, I was gonna beat him.
- Come here! Come here.
He is 16.
Yeah, and six-foot, 220?
He can take a punch.
Look, I wasn't going to beat him.
I just wanted to scare him.
But if I did want to beat him,
I could.
- It would be my prerogative.
- It's illegal.
How now so righteous?
Not long since you put a man
in the river.
You want to say that a little louder?
Not everybody heard.
Ever since that, you've been
a royal pain in the ass.
You think I or anybody around here
gives a crap
about a dead snitch
or your guilty conscience?
We got our own problems.
Guilty conscience,
call it what you want.
I'm going to do what's right.
You are beginning to irritate me.
Get your hands off me!
Hey!
Watch the shoes, clown.
Shift's over.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, seriously.
Thank you so much, guys, truly.
I'm very grateful.
I've been waiting for hours.
No kidding.
Look like you crawled
out of a cemetery.
Smell like it too.
Open the window back there.
- There you go.
- Yes, thank you.
Forgive me, I am somewhat disheveled.
A temporary setback, I assure you.
Oh, thank you so much.
What the hell happened to you anyhow?
It was my own fault.
Foolish arrogance led me astray.
But I've learned my lessons.
I'll be back.
Stronger and smarter than ever.
Good luck with that, bro.
Here I am riding
about a lovely truck,
sharing an ice cold beer
with my new friends.
My luck has already turned, right?
Dude, anyone ever tell you,
when you walk?
You look just like a Penguin.
No.
Nobody's ever told me that.
He's saying he has a right
to stop me from beating on a mope.
Damn right I do.
How am I supposed to work with that?
Look it, Jim, it's not like I can
order you to break the law.
But this is Gotham.
- You don't bend, you'll get broke.
- I understand.
I thought you were with the program.
- He is.
- Well, let's get back to work.
Where are you at?
If the boy we have
is telling the truth,
there's a couple of kidnappers
out there
abducting homeless children
in numbers.
They lure them clothes
with the food truck
from the Mayor's Homeless
Outreach Project,
and they drug them with a jab
from a big pin.
Why would anyone wanna abduct
scraggy-ass orphans in bulk?
I mean, where's the market?
They're out on the street
because no one wants them anyway.
If they said they were snatching
cute girls, I'll believe them.
But why would anyone want
with a lard-ass like Mackey?
What is it, Ed?
Guess what I found?
I did a blood test on him
and he has high levels of ATP.
What's ATP?
It's a fast acting knock out drug.
They used to use it
at the old Arkham Asylum
to bring down troublesome patients.
It's hard to get.
No recreational use.
Okay.
- That's interesting.
- Anything else?
Thank you, Ed.
Get to work.
And keep this quiet. No press.
Not a word.
Shouldn't we tell the public
what's going on?
- Warn them?
- Department policy.
We don't advertise
this kind of stuff.
Causes panic.
The headlines will read
"Gotham Kids Snatched."
- Which would be true.
- No press. That's an order.
Follow-up on the drug, the ATP,
and the Arkham connection.
Arkham's been closed
for like 10 years
Yeah, 15.
Their drug suppliers
might still be in business.
This happened on Fish Mooney's turf.
Do you wanna see if it's safe for us
to go back there
or is she still mad at us?
It's a good question.
Bravo!
Don Falcone.
What a wonderful surprise.
Welcome.
Thank you my dear.
- Can we talk?
- Of course.
Give me a moment to clear the place.
No, no. No need to spoil the fun.
Men who are about to die
are very honest.
It pays to listen to them.
That's some toast.
I spoke with your man, Cobblepot,
before he died.
Odd little fella. Perceptive.
He told me the death of the Waynes
would bring troubled times
for our family and Gotham.
What did he know?
Business is good as ever.
No, he was right.
The Waynes and the Falcones
were pillars of the same house.
We understood each other.
Now that they're gone,
everything is out of balance,
and the Wayne Empire is in flux.
Who knows who'll end up in control?
The Maroni family senses weakness.
They'll start making moves
and every criminal in the city
will start making moves.
Please, don't lose
any sleep over Maroni.
He's number two for a reason.
I never lose sleep over my enemies.
It's my friends that keep me awake.
Cobblepot told me you say I'm old
and soft and ready to be taken out.
And you're the one to take me.
Don Falcone,
I would never ever say that.
I only have deep love
and respect for you.
You have been like a father to me.
I was so happy to hear that.
Let's forget all about it then.
The babbling of a condemned man.
Enough business.
How have you been, my dear?
- Thriving I hope?
- Yes.
Good. I'm good.
Which of these is your lover?
Please, my heart has been broken
far too many times for that nonsense.
I heard you had a lover.
Well, if you are referring to the boy
that I keep around for exercise,
my lover he is not.
- What's your name?
- Lazlo, sir.
Lazlo, be good to this woman.
She's very precious to me.
If you break her heart,
you break my heart.
Yes sir.
Give me your hand.
Thank you for being honest.
It means a lot to me.
It shows wisdom and humility.
Out!
Everyone out!
Never, never in his life my son
is away this long.
Nightclubs is his business.
Such hours.
But always, he comes home
to his mother.
His clothes are here.
My son would never leave his clothes.
Oh, so elegant he is.
Yes, I show you.
Damn. Mooney and the cops
must have had him killed.
Looks like. Snitches get bumped.
That's life.
They're not gonna get away with it,
not as easy as they think.
You take things too personal,
you know that?
Yeah, I do.
That was a good snitch.
- What are we...
- Nothing.
- Mrs. Cobblepot...
- Kapelput.
Mrs. Kapelput.
Do you know anyone
who might wanna do your son harm?
Harm?
No. I would feel it.
A mother feels these things.
It's a woman.
Some painted slut has him
in her clutch.
- A woman, you think?
- I'm sure.
So handsome he is.
And so naive.
Who are you again?
Detectives
with Major Crimes Unit, ma'am.
- Oh, G.C.P.D.
- Like that.
But honest.
Boss, don't get mad at me.
But I know that look.
Now is too early to make a move
on Falcone.
I know.
Not yet.
I need more money, more men,
more territory, I know.
I'll play this being loyal
and bide my time.
But I swear, Butch...
on my sainted mother's grave,
someday soon I'm gonna kill
that old man
with my bare hands and my teeth.
I'll be holding your shoes.
I just wish that Penguin
was still alive.
I didn't make that little punk suffer
near badly enough.
Excuse me, sir.
I couldn't help but notice
the sign on your trailer.
Is it still for rent?
Hundred bucks a week.
It ain't much, but...
I'll take it.
- You don't want to look at it first?
- No, I'm not fussy.
It's all yours.
The key?
A sweet truck.
You got that big hemi in there?
Yes. Yup.
That big hemi is in there.
Somewhere.
Sir, the key?
It's in the door.
Okay.
What's up, player?
- You got any smokes?
- No.
Where are we?
Damn if I know.
I think we're dead.
Harvey, Jim, how marvelous.
Are you still mad at us?
No, please.
I'm quite fond of you
and you intrigue me
I knew I'd regret killing you
as soon as I gave the word.
But you know me.
I'm feisty.
What do you know
about a man and woman
abducting street kids on your turf?
No foreplay with you, huh?
Figures.
But you got with the program.
Killed Penguin your own bad self.
I was surprised.
Straight arrow like you.
I guess you misjudged me.
I guess I did.
You are just a little sinner
like the rest of us.
I'm almost kind of sad about that.
We're looking for a man
and a woman...
middle-aged, white,
targeting children under 16.
They use a poison pin,
if you can believe it.
Used to be there was only a market
for nice looking girls.
That's what I said.
But now there's a new buyer overseas
that will take anyone young
and healthy.
- Overseas where? Who's they?
- Nobody knows.
- What do they want them for?
And no one cares to know.
Ta-da, moo shu.
Sorry, go on.
They drug them with a big pin?
That is so creepy.
No. You don't want to hear
those stuff. It's depressing.
What do they use them for?
The children.
Nobody seems to know.
We can't say a damn thing
to the press.
Bad PR.
I can't believe the system
is so corrupt.
You have no idea.
What do you mean?
No.
Figure of speech, I guess.
Did something happen
that you're not telling me about?
These last couple of weeks
you've been different.
Troubled.
No.
I'm having trouble sleeping, I guess.
The newspapers must get anonymous
tips all the time.
Sure. Yeah.
You mean, call it in myself?
No, I can't do that.
- Gotham Gazette, the newsroom.
- Wait. No.
Hi. Listen. I can't talk long.
Somebody is abducting homeless
children off the streets
and the cops
are trying to keep quiet.
Go talk to Captain Sarah Essen
of the G.C.P.D.
She has a kid in custody
who can tell you the whole story.
- End the call.
- I got to go.
Listen to me, Barbara.
When I tell you stuff,
that's just between us.
You can't do that what you just did.
- But it was the right thing to do.
- That's not the point.
What is the point?
You're right.
It was the right thing to do.
- Don't do it again, okay?
- Yes, boss.
Gotham Spirals Ever Downward.
Mayor James under attack,
vows swift action,
points finger at Police Department's
sluggish response, etcetera.
It's just ink.
- Did you give them this?
- Me?
You've done it before.
On my own case? Never.
It would be a very stupid thing
to do.
Jim?
I didn't call it in.
I swear.
Another mystery.
We have a thin lead on the case,
if you'd like to hear it, ma'am.
There's only three companies
in Gotham that stock this ATP stuff,
and you need a special license
to buy it.
Chances are,
one of the three is crooked.
We're looking to lean hard
on all three,
like they are crooked
and see which one pops.
That was sneaky good.
Almost couldn't tell you were lying.
I wasn't lying.
Good morning, Judge Baker.
Thank you, sir. Yes, all three.
Wellzyme, Dracotech,
and Quillan Pharma.
You guys have screwed me.
Against my better judgment,
I sell you the juice.
I let you, guys, use my storage space
because no problem you said.
And now look.
Heat.
- White hot heat!
- No problems, my friend.
We're here to take the merch away.
You'll be clean as a whistle.
Merch?
They're children, dammit.
They're human beings.
Didn't I tell you to check on them
10 minutes ago?
I want another five large.
But we have a deal already.
I got to stand up
for what is right here.
Be fair, sir.
We don't have that kind of cash
on hand.
That's your problem.
I can wait.
I thought you were worried
about the heat.
If heat arrives. In the meantime,
I can get rid of the evidence
very quickly.
We have an obligation to deliver.
The Doll-maker
doesn't tolerate failure.
- We need those children.
- Well, that's also your problem.
No. Hey!
This is totally inappropriate!
I mean, we were having
a business discussion here.
You weren't being fair.
Oh, gosh.
Cops.
You didn't call the Gazette,
but did your girl call the Gazette?
Yeah.
- I knew it.
- I didn't know
she was going to call them.
Seriously, you got to learn
to control your woman.
I kind of like her the way she is.
These high-class temperamental bras,
they need firm handling, trust me.
Trust you? On women?
Damn right. All varieties.
From hausfraus to movie stars.
I love them all.
Now you, let me guess.
High school sweetheart,
and a bunch of hos overseas
only made you sad,
and then there's Barbara.
Pretty much.
You, my friend, are a monkey riding
a racehorse.
Good evening. May I help you?
Detectives Gordon and Bullock.
We need to speak whoever's in charge
here, ma'am.
Of course. Mr. Quillan,
detectives are here to see you.
Wow.
Detectives. Hey. What's up?
Nothing serious I hope.
Cut the crap.
We have a warrant
to search the premises.
We know what you're doing.
Well, then, you know
some boring stuff then.
What are you talking about?
You're peddling ATP
to those kids' snatchers.
Oh, my gosh, no.
I mean, we used to stock ATP, but
not since the Arkham Asylum closed.
I heard that the Wayne Foundation
is planning on reopening
the old place again.
But now that the Waynes are dead,
I guess everything's up in the air.
What a world, eh?
Nobody's safe.
- Jim!
- Go, go!
Where the hell were you?
Get rid of them now.
Then hose down the room.
Zeb.
Freeze!
On behalf of all the citizens
of Gotham,
I wanna thank the brave gentlemen
from the bottom of my heart,
and I wanna promise, you kids,
we will take care of you
as if you were our own children.
But here's the thing.
The people who victimized these kids
are still out there,
and hundreds of vulnerable youngsters
are still living rough
on our streets, alone, unprotected.
And let's face it,
that's the real crime here.
So what are we going to do
to help these kids?
Yesterday, I made a phone call
to Juvenile Services
and the G.C.P.D. to initiate a humane
but tough love program,
to get these kids off the streets
and into the loving arms
of Juvenile Services.
- I think that went very well.
- I think so.
A small toast, Your Honor?
You read my mind.
Mr. Mayor.
Where are you sending
all the children that get rounded up?
Foster homes
for the cute undamaged ones.
Upstate for the rest.
Upstate?
The Alpena Youth
Corrections Facility.
A fine institute.
Prison in other words.
Forgive me, Your Honor.
Detective Gordon
is our house firebrand.
No, no, no, that's okay.
Jim. Can I call you Jim?
Half the petty crime in the city
is homeless kids.
They need structure.
People who care about them,
for the greater good of Gotham
and for the children, you see?
I see you're using
the child snatchers as a pretext
to lock up children without a trial.
Thank you, my friend.
Valuable input.
Most refreshing.
L'chaim.
Yo, Gordon.
Man's been waiting for you upstairs.
Mr. Pennyworth.
Alfred, please.
It's bedlam, innit.
Rough job you do.
Best job in the world.
I wonder if it might be convenient
for you to visit us tomorrow?
Of course.
- Why? Is something wrong?
- I don't know.
I never had a child before.
Nor me.
The boy respects you.
Teatime should we say?
Teatime.
- Name.
- Ma'am, there's been a mistake.
I'm not meant to go upstate.
I need to talk to James Gordon.
He's a cop.
You'll be allowed a phone call
when you get upstate.
- Name.
- I need to talk to him now.
- He'll thank you for it.
- Not happening.
- Name.
- Bite me, Pigarina.
Jane Doe.
Hey.
Relax kid.
Juvie's not so bad.
First week, whatever you do,
don't make friends
with anyone that's friendly.
When you get into a fight,
go for their eyes.
Hi, kids!
How you doing?
Are you ready to go
on a big adventure?
Sit down, young lady.
I said sit down!
Like now!
Okay.
Next naughty child to stand up
gets a black mark right here.
One or two or three.
I can explain that.
But a bus load, a whole bus load
of the little bastards?
What am I supposed to say?
Oops? Just tell me it's wasn't them.
I'm begging you.
Just tell me it wasn't
"The Snatchers."
Bus driver was a man,
guard was a woman.
- It could be them.
- You're killing me.
- You're killing me!
- We're working it, Your Honor.
I told you everything I know.
I told you.
Now you see that man there?
He doesn't like it
when I beat people.
But for you, he's got no objection.
Why is that?
Math. The lives of 30 children
versus one scumbag.
So I can beat you like a bongo drum
and Saint Jim here won't intervene.
Give us something.
Okay, okay!
The truck, when they came to pick up
the last bunch of kids,
on the side of it,
there was a picture.
Like a logo.
I didn't want to say before because
it would give a bad impression
- that doesn't reflect really...
- What was it?
There's a blue plate
and a silver fork.
A plate and a fork.
Yeah, you know like...
- Like a catering company? Like food.
- Like that.
I mean, you know... But, I mean,
that doesn't mean, you know.
Doesn't mean what?
Look, I don't know
what they do with them.
Hey! Hey.
All right, draw the logo.
Uncuff him.
There you go, kids.
Don't worry.
Everything's going to be all right.
That's right. That's right. Come on.
- Come on, come on, come on.
- Come on.
Go.
Funny thing, by my count,
according to the sheet they gave us,
- we're one short.
- Me too.
Maybe there's one on the bus.
Nope. Weird?
Must be a miscount some place.
Never mind.
We've got more than enough.
- We did good.
- Indeed we did.
The Doll-maker
will be so pleased with us.
All right, thanks.
Nothing. You?
Apparently, there are no companies
in Gotham
with trucks with a plate
and fork as their logo.
Selling children for food.
Is such a thing even possible?
We've got officers searching all the
trucks on every bridge and tunnel.
But they had a three-hour window.
We can only pray they stayed
in the city.
If not, they can be any place
on Earth by nightfall.
You scum sucking toads,
where are they?
It's not a blue plate.
It's not a fork either.
It's a trident.
When you stow this on the ship,
make sure there's plenty of room
for the doors to open.
- The ship's crew has to...
- Let me out!
Quiet in there!
Hush. Hush.
My eyes! She scratched me.
Come on, follow me.
Let me look.
It's nothing. It's a scratch.
We'll get you to a doctor,
you'll be right as rain in no time.
You sure?
- What was that?
- Hang on.
Well...
You are a very naughty little girl.
Hi.
- What's your name?
- Why is that your business?
Jim!
Where are the kids?
Where are they?
He's not been sleeping.
And when he does,
he has these nightmares.
Now he's hurting himself.
Burning himself.
He's cutting.
- Is he getting professional help?
- You mean psychiatrists.
No, no. He won't have them.
No psychiatrists. That's a rule.
You make the rules, don't you?
You're his guardian.
Bruce's father gave me very firm
orders was him and his missus to die.
I'll raise the boy the way his father
told me to raise him.
Which is how?
Trust him to choose his own course.
He's after all a Wayne.
Sounds like a recipe for disaster.
What do you want me to do?
He wants you to talk some sense
into me.
Haven't I told you to stop creeping
up on people like that,
for it's bloody rude.
All right, then, Bruce, talk to me.
I'm perfectly fine.
Alfred is a worrywart.
What did you do to your hand?
I burned it.
Listen to me, Bruce.
You've been through
a terrible experience.
Talking to someone
can be very helpful.
You must have seen terrible things
in the war.
Does it help you to talk about
what you saw?
Yes, a little.
You're not a very good liar.
- Bruce, you're hurting yourself.
- I'm testing myself.
Different.
But I appreciate your concern.
I've been following your adventures
in the newspapers.
I feel very sorry
for all those poor children.
Me too.
I'll give you some money
to give to them.
I'm afraid it doesn't work that way,
Bruce.
What way does it work?
Those children need someone
who cares for them.
Like you have right here.
Money won't buy that.
There must be something I can do.
What about clothes?
They all looked awfully ragged.
They did, didn't they?
After all this?
You're sending us upstate?
- Selina...
- Cat.
Cat, even if you didn't have
outstanding warrants, you're 13.
- No parents or guardians.
- That's not true. I have a mom.
- It says here she's deceased.
- That's not true.
She's alive.
- Someplace.
- Be that as it may,
we're not allowed to put you back
on the street.
For your own well-being.
Have you been there? Upstate?
- Yes.
- Then you know!
You know.
Go get Detective James Gordon.
He works here.
Cat.
- The police are very busy people.
- Go get him.
Or I'll say you touched me.
Excuse me?
James Gordon.
I'm going to scream
in about three seconds.
Hello.
Yes, this is he.
Well, I'm looking at your son
right now.
He doesn't look good.
Madame, I assure you,
your son is not trying to trick you.
Well, he will die a horrible death
unless he...
No, no, no.
Really truly, he isn't joking.
I'm not joking.
I will poke his eyeballs out and...
How can you say that?
You saw the video I sent.
I'm not lying.
Madame, Madame, calm yourself.
If 10,000 is too much,
I'm sure we can...
Hello?
Well, that's disappointing.
She didn't believe me.
You must be quite the scamp.
I got it.
Hello again, young lady.
- How can I help you?
- We need to talk.
So now you wanna talk, huh? Okay.
It's all right.
- Selina is it?
- Cat.
Cat.
You're Mackey's friend.
Yeah, I know Mackey.
Those bastards nearly got you twice,
huh?
You're quite a survivor.
You have no idea.
Suppose I had something
you really, really wanted.
If I gave it to you,
could you get me out of here?
What do you got?
I've been watching you.
You're a friend of the boy.
You're not like the rest
of these crooks.
The boy?
Bruce?
What do you mean
you've been watching me?
That Mario Pepper guy
was a patsy, huh?
- What make you say that?
- Could you?
Could you get me out?
It's possible.
I saw who really killed the Waynes.
Saw him clear as day.