Previously onGotham...
- I set a bomb.
- Thousands of people could die.
Yes, but paying that price
will be better
than releasing what's down there.
Are you ready to play?
Wayne Enterprises runs Indian Hill,
but who runs Wayne Enterprises?
There's a secret council in Gotham.
It's them that wanted me dead.
We're so close to the ultimate truth.
Strange, you did
a very bad thing to me
and now you're going to...
Impossible.
Nothing is impossible.
Thank you.
Bruce, I might not see you
for a while.
- Where you going?
- I have to find Lee.
Hello?
We're closed.
If you leave now,
I won't call the cops.
Hey.
Any chance you wanna come quietly?
At 8.15 this evening
an individual robbed a pharmacy
and attacked its owner.
But we don't have an ID as yet.
We believe that this individual
is another escapee from Indian Hill.
Captain Barnes, can you clarify...?
Captain Barnes. Captain Barnes!
Valerie Vale, Gotham Gazette.
Why can't we see the escapee?
Because crews are still
picking up the pieces.
This isn't the first time
that a bounty hunter
has apprehended an escapee.
Is the G.C.P.D. incapable
of handling this threat themselves?
Only a handful of escapees have been
brought in by bounty hunters.
The vast majority
were apprehended by.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
I take issue with the word "threat."
These escapees are themselves
victims of Hugo Strange.
Now, if any ordinary,
hard-working citizen
wants to help these poor souls
off the street
so that they may receive
the proper treatment
well, these citizens should be lauded
and rewarded financially.
Mr. James, before they were taken
to Indian Hill
these poor souls
were all criminally insane inmates
at Arkham Asylum, were they not?
Next question.
- Hear that? You should be lauded.
- I'll settle for the cash.
How many escapees
you've brought in now? Six?
Five grand a pop, that's not too bad.
What happens
when there aren't any more?
Don't think Gotham's running out
of monsters any time soon.
I really can't get you
to come back, huh?
Look, whatever happened
when you went to see Lee, and...
- You know I don't like to pry.
- Sure, you do.
That's because you won't tell me
anything.
The point is man is not supposed
to be alone.
- You have a family here.
- Can't do it, Harv.
But you've got no problem
chasing down Strange's freaks?
Yeah, it pays the rent.
You are a cop in everything but name.
Yeah. Except I don't have to
listen to Barnes.
I get to go home when I want,
get drunk when I want.
And at end of the day
I sleep because saving Gotham's
not my job anymore.
Jim, I love you like a brother
but you've gotta stop blaming the job
for what happened
between you and Lee.
And do you really think
I don't get drunk when I want?
Detective Bullock, I looked
into the drug the escapee was after.
It's a powerful immune suppressant.
Gordon.
See, look at Lucius here,
our new resident expert
on all things scientific.
He said sayonara
to the Wayne Enterprises robots.
And he loves it here.
Wayne Enterprises revealed itself
as morally corrupt.
Here,
despite the primitive facilities
casual violence,
fascistic meathead culture...
Lucius.
I love it.
Anyway, that drug is only sold
at three pharmacies in the city.
And the other two pharmacies
were both robbed in the last month.
The question is: why are Indian Hill
escapees now robbing pharmacies?
Good question.
So, what do you say,
just like the old days
you and me run it together,
huh, partner?
You get a hard lead on an escapee
and the price is right,
I'll bring him in.
Thanks for the drink.
Lucius.
"Fascistic meathead culture"?
I mean, you couldn't try to be
just a little bit more positive?
I was very positive.
Why is Hugo Strange the only one
that's been arrested?
- The situation...
- And what about the rumors
that Indian Hill
is a Wayne Enterprise facility?
And how many more escapees
are at large?
Are we talking 20? 30?
Well, just give me a blink
if I'm close.
The situation is firmly in hand.
Liar!
Oh, no.
My name is Oswald Cobblepot...
We know who you are, Penguin.
What do you want?
What do I want?
I want you to tell the truth
to the people of Gotham.
They would have us believe
that there is no danger.
But I was there the night those
creatures broke out of Indian Hill.
I saw them.
And I saw who's leading them.
Are you saying the escapees
are organized?
Hello. That is what I am saying.
There is absolutely nothing
to support that.
I told the police who to look for.
I begged them. Time and again.
And they have done nothing.
So I am here to speak directly
to the good people of Gotham.
The enemy's name is Fish Mooney.
Fish Mooney?
She hasn't been spotted
for over six months.
She's either long gone or she's dead.
I wish I shared your simple belief.
She is a criminal.
She is a murderer.
And now God knows
what kind of monster
Hugo Strange has turned her into.
I implore every citizen of Gotham
if you love your family,
if you love your children
find Fish Mooney.
Until then, no one is safe.
Hello, Jim.
Oswald.
I'm surprised
you haven't found Mooney.
I hear you're quite the bounty hunter
these days.
You haven't made it worth my while.
- Tough guy now.
- But he makes a point.
I know what boys like
I know what guys want
I've got what boys like
I know what boys like
I know what guys want
Boys like me
Ozzie.
Butch.
What a nice surprise.
Forgive me for not coming sooner.
The place looks marvelous.
- Wouldn't you say so, Butch?
- Yeah. Place looks great.
I imagine you're here
about your offer.
To let us shelter
under your umbrella?
I only want what's best for you.
Appreciate the thought.
But we're big girls.
We can handle ourselves.
Can't we?
Sure we can.
Hey, Butch.
Hey. Hi, how... How you doing?
You taking care of yourself?
Yeah... Yeah. Yeah.
So... So, you, how you doing?
You already asked her that.
Listen, you guys should take him up
on his offer.
Gotham's full of rough characters.
You look great, by the way.
Wait over there, please.
Poor bunny. Breakups are hard.
I offered to kill you.
I thought it would raise his spirits.
It would be my pleasure
seeing as how you murdered my mother.
But he is nursing some foolish hope
that you two will get back together.
Love.
You can take your offer
and stick it...
We'll think about it, Ozzie.
Fine.
But that's not the only reason
I'm here.
Spread the word. I want Fish Mooney.
And I will give a million dollars
to whoever can bring her to me.
Dead or alive,
or chopped into pieces.
I want her.
Are you okay, Butch?
- World getting you down?
- I'm fine, kid.
And you're too young to be in here.
Scram.
Jeez, just trying to be nice.
Just seeing her kills me, you know?
Get over it.
And that child
just stole your wallet.
Hey. Barbara and that whip lady
are gonna get angry,
you're stealing from their customers.
Let them. I got other things going.
- Like what?
- Top secret.
Let's eat. I'm starving.
Hey, kid. Take it.
It's yours.
Keep feeding strays,
one's gonna follow you home.
Like you?
Come on.
Well, that should be the last of it.
I'll put the kettle on.
There is nothing
like a sweet cup of tea
to make home feel like home
after a long trip away.
Eh, Master Bruce?
You all right?
Were we right to leave, Alfred?
To stay away all this time?
Well, considering the appalling state
of the topiary
I should say absolutely bloody not.
Alfred, you know what I mean.
I know you know why we left.
We had to leave.
You're nervous about tomorrow,
aren't you?
Yes.
Well, you wouldn't be human
if you weren't.
So why don't you go through there
and take a pew, put your feet up
and I'll see
about that lovely cup of tea?
All right?
You saving that for someone special?
Coffee, please.
"Search continues for new
Arkham Asylum director." Great.
Good luck finding anyone
to take that job.
I'm Valerie Vale,
reporter for the Gazette.
I know who you are.
And you're James Gordon,
son of a respected Gotham DA
former war hero,
former white knight cop,
now bounty hunter.
You know, someone should do a story
on you.
Not interested.
Yeah, me neither, actually.
You were there that night,
in Indian Hill.
I got nothing to say.
What about the fact that besides
Hugo Strange and his assistant
no one else has been arrested?
Or that despite everything
pointing to Wayne Enterprises
there seems to be zero investigation.
You're new to Gotham, aren't you?
Okay, this is where you tell me
things work differently here?
I'm not from Gotham
but my dad's a cop.
My brothers are cops.
And things work the same everywhere.
I was going to say it's hard to find
a quiet bar in this city.
I like coming here.
Please don't make me find another.
Now, do you think Cobblepot's right?
That Fish Mooney's organizing
the escapees?
Penguin is a liar and a murderer.
But...
But based on the escapees
and knowing Fish...
I hope not.
Well, he's offering a million dollars
to whoever brings her in.
You're welcome.
It's a puzzle.
The trick is opening it.
The man at the store said it's one
of the most difficult ever made.
People pass it down unsolved
for generations.
A mathematician once went mad
trying to...
Yes.
Well, there you go.
It was a lovely thought.
And did you get the biscuits?
And the sweater?
I know how drafty these rooms are.
- Mr. Penguin...
- Oswald.
When I think of how I treated you,
and...
Stop.
Why are you being so kind?
Talking to you these past months
I don't know
how I would have gotten by otherwise.
With Fish out there
planning who knows what
and me being surrounded
by morons and lunatics.
I know the feeling.
Why didn't she kill me
when she had the chance?
I was powerless.
She must have a larger goal.
I... I need to know
what she is doing.
Do you?
When Alexander encountered
the Gordian knot
a knot so complex that no one
had ever been able to untangle it
he just removed his sword
and cut it in two.
Details can be distracting.
Sometimes...
a simple solution is best.
So no matter what she's planning,
just remember...
penguins eat...
fish.
You know why we're here.
What are you doing here?
Stop. Stop...
So, what are we after?
It's not like they keep cash around.
- For now, survival.
- Don't move!
Hands.
Of course.
Drop the gun.
Now, knock yourself out.
That was awesome.
How did you...?
Whoa, Fish.
I'm fine. Watch the door.
Yeah. And that's the only company
that makes the drug.
Cray Pharma. They've actually have
a warehouse here in Gotham.
You think they could be a target?
Yeah. They're the only pharmacy
that carries the drug.
If somebody wants it,
they'll have to go to the source.
- Let me find the address.
- That's all right.
- James Gordon.
- Hands where I can see them.
So, what, you're here to collect the
bounty that Penguin has over my head?
What is it? A million dollars?
And to think I let that punk live.
Well, then
I think you'd better cuff me.
Cuff yourself.
- How many others you have with you?
- They're all with me.
Every wretched soul
that Hugo Strange experimented on.
But tonight, just him.
Did you hear them rats last night
scurrying around in the attic?
Drove me bloody bonkers.
Now, may I ask you, what's the point
of having a caretaker
if they can't take care
of nothing, eh?
You all right, Master B?
Hungry.
I should have eaten.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
I do this, there's no turning back.
No.
You say your piece.
We'll see about getting you
a proper breakfast, all right?
I'd like to thank the board
for giving me this time.
It will come as no surprise
I'd like to talk about Indian Hill.
I know preliminary investigations
have concluded
Hugo Strange acted alone.
I reject this conclusion.
While trapped in Indian Hill,
I was led to believe an unnamed group
had taken control of my company
and it was they
who hired Hugo Strange.
I left Gotham both for my own safety
and so that I might have the time
to discover hard evidence
of their existence.
A conspiracy theory?
That's why we're all here?
Excuse me, Master Bruce.
Pardon me, sir.
Might I have your name, please?
- What?
- Your name, please, sir.
- Crowley.
- Mr. Crowley
did you parents ever teach you
any manners?
- I don't have to listen to this.
- Oh, but you do, sir.
That is precisely the point
that I am making.
I know how it sounds.
But I now have proof they exist.
And I can tell you that they're here.
In this room.
I wanna talk face-to-face.
You have 24 hours to contact me
or the information that I've gathered
will be sent
to every newspaper
and television station in Gotham.
Thank you for your time.
Pancakes?
Pancakes.
And how did the board react?
Then he leaves us no choice.
Bruce Wayne.
Do it quietly.
- You Barbara Kean?
- We're closed.
What?
You built this club on our territory.
We let you because we heard
Penguin had your back.
And now we hear that ain't so.
Bad for you, good for us.
Get the hell out.
This place is ours now.
Do you understand?
You can't just come in...
Don't hit me, okay? Please.
- Hey.
You still paying for stuff
about the Indian Hill freaks?
It depends. If it's good.
Is Fish Mooney good?
I guess I'm finding a new bar.
I heard you ran
into Fish Mooney yesterday.
- So?
- So...
are you still interested
in finding her?
Every cop in the city
is looking for her now.
But I know where she's gonna be next.
And why are you telling me?
You see, I need something
from the cops.
They're not gonna tell me.
- But Bullock still trusts you.
- And you want me to lie to him.
A million dollars
covers a lot of sins.
And obviously, I get to come along.
Don't tell me you have a conscience.
Yeah, all right.
- Jimmy.
- Hey.
So after your run-in with Fish,
Barnes had us up all night
rousting her old hideouts.
Yeah. You find anything?
Nada.
But I did get what you asked for.
You wanna tell me what this is about?
Just a hunch. Probably nothing.
Look, if you've got a hot lead
you don't wanna share
so you can collect Penguin's million,
I got no problem with that.
Just don't get yourself killed
or me fired, okay?
I'll do my best.
Hey, get some rest, huh?
Hey.
- When did you get back?
- Couple of days ago.
- I tried to find you before I left.
- No worries.
You remember what I discovered
that night in Indian Hill
that there was a secret group
that infiltrated my company?
I wasn't paying attention.
I needed time to research them.
- I couldn't do it here
- Okay.
I have a plan,
but these people are powerful.
We need to assume
they know you and I are friends.
- You need to be careful.
- Got it.
- I'm serious.
- I can see that.
I'm sorry I was gone for so long.
Don't apologize.
Shoot, if I could fly to Italy
and eat pizza all day, I would too.
- It's Switzerland.
- Italy's better.
- Selina...
- Bruce, seriously.
Don't sweat it.
I gotta go.
I'll see you around.
Good to see you, Selina.
- Hey, did you get it?
- Yeah.
She's under guard in a building
on Douglas and 80th.
There's one thing, though.
Hey. Hey!
What the hell are you doing?
You're a hundred yards
from a police station.
- I'll be back in an hour or two.
- We had a deal.
If there's a story,
I'll make sure you get it.
Oh, you're a son of a bitch.
Also, you could scream
but then you'd have to tell the cops
everything
then you'd lose the story entirely.
Gordon.
Gordon!
Son of a bitch.
- 47, this is dispatch.
- This is 47.
Report to Captain Barnes immediately.
Relief team will take your place.
Over and out.
You've got it. We're out of here.
- I knocked.
- I didn't answer.
- You alone?
- All day, every day.
I wasn't expecting Jim Gordon
to stop by.
You aren't supposed to be here,
are you?
How come you're not in jail?
I agreed to testify
against Professor Strange.
In case you're about to ask
I don't know who really ran
Indian Hill.
I don't care who ran Indian Hill.
Then why are you here?
Fish Mooney.
And why would I know
how to find Fish Mooney?
No reason you would.
But it's clear
whatever you and Strange did to her
is making her sick.
Her people are stealing drugs.
But I don't think they're working.
She's gonna come after you.
Or her goons will
and they'll lead me to her.
And how will they find me?
Only the police are supposed to know.
My guess, she'll have someone
get the information for her.
Someone who wouldn't suspect
being used.
Maybe a reporter.
She'll follow that person
or whoever she goes to for help
in this case, a bounty hunter
right to you.
You led them to me on purpose.
You're using me as bait.
I don't like being played.
Plus, she's worth a million dollars.
Gordon, help. Somebody help!
I don't know which one of you
I wanna bat over the head
with this cane more.
I get it.
Life disappointed you.
So what? Does that make you special?
I'm done with you.
You cross me again
I will have you skinned alive
and your head put on a pike.
And you.
When I came back, I saw the way
you handled things while I was away.
I swear,
I had this feeling right here.
I thought
I was having a heart attack.
But it was pride, Bullock. In you.
The next time I have that feeling
I'll know it was just gas.
You both better pray
that we find her.
Get out of my sight.
I'd say that went well.
He was right, though.
About me being captain.
- I did a good job. I even liked it.
- Yeah.
Hey, look. I'm sorry, Harvey.
I'll do my best to find Peabody.
Honestly, Jim, for the time of being
it might be better if you just...
stayed away.
Hey. Hey.
- Just tell me, did you know?
- That I know what?
That Mooney was using us
to find Peabody.
You mean using you?
Yeah, it's her kind of play.
- You should have told me.
- Sure.
Why don't you tell me
who your source was?
That's it? You're not gonna
try and find Mooney?
Barnes is on it. I've had a long day.
I'm gonna get a drink.
Gordon.
Nothing.
- Come on.
- I said no.
- Who are they?
- Just people.
- They need me to do things for them.
- Well, I can do stuff.
These are scary people, okay?
It's for your own good.
- You just don't wanna share.
- Just stay here, all right?
Hello.
What do you want?
I want to talk to her.
I was following her.
She was kind to me.
But then she met him. That boy.
What happened to you?
- You know me?
- Yeah. I know Bruce Wayne.
Who is he? Who is he?
What's wrong with you? Let go of me.
Bruce Wayne! Bruce Wayne!
Who is he?
I really do not have time for this.
- He started it.
- It's a lie.
- The cwub is in our territory.
- "Cwub"?
What's a "cwub"?
- Cwub.
- What's a "cwub"?
I mean, can anyone understand him?
Do you know what a "cwub" is?
- Cwub.
- Enough.
We will work something out.
Now, this is his territory.
What are you willing to give him?
That is not helpful.
Are you telling me
you don't see what's going on here?
He is behind this.
What are you talking about?
He sent this ding-dong to squeeze us
hoping it would send us back to you
so that he could lord it over Tabby.
Ain't that right?
That's... That's just...
That's crazy. She's crazy.
- She was in Arkham, hello.
- Hello, so was I.
Is that true, Butch?
Unbelievable.
Fine. Run your club.
Just so we're clear
the only reason
you are alive is Butch.
The moment he gives me
the word, you're mine.
Hello again.
I know why you brought me here.
Your body is beginning to reject
the changes we made to your DNA.
You feel it every time you use
your ability.
How do I fix it?
Stop using the power.
Every time you use it,
new cells are activated
and your body rejects them.
Stop and you will recover.
It's that simple?
It's just, I like the new me.
I can't fix you.
I can't reorder your DNA...
There's always a way.
Strange. He can.
He's the only one.
- Where is Strange?
- I don't know.
They've hidden him somewhere secret.
Him fixing me
is just the beginning.
I want an army.
I want an army like me.
And he is going to give it to me.
- He can't...
- Oh, he will.
Or he will die.
You remember Marv.
He's one of yours.
Sort of the fountain of youth
in reverse.
Good night, Ethel.
We caught a spy.
- Ivy?
- Selina, tell this creep
to let go off me.
She's my friend.
- I don't like spies.
- She's not a spy.
Ivy, what are you doing here?
I followed you the other day
so I knew where you went.
Bruce Wayne came looking for you
but he was acting weird.
Who else have you told about us?
- No one.
- I asked her.
- Selina?
- Ivy, shut up.
They're those monsters everyone's
talking about, aren't they?
You better tell your friend
to be careful
who she calls a monster.
You'd better stay away from me.
All of you. I'll tell.
Marv.
No.
Leave her alone.
Stay away from me!
Ivy. Ivy!
Ivy!
Watch out!
Help!
Ivy?
Right. Once this alarm is set,
Master Bruce
no coming downstairs
till the morning.
Is that clear?
Yes. But was a new alarm system
really necessary?
I don't know. Was it really necessary
offering a challenge
to a shadowy cabal?
Yes, it was necessary, Master Bruce.
Alfred!
Al...
Alfred, wake up. Alfred!