♪ Oh, Penguin ♪
♪ Our hero ♪
♪ He knows ♪
♪ No fear-o ♪
♪ He brings us joy ♪
♪ And cheer-o ♪
♪ Oh, Penguin ♪
♪ Our king ♪
♪ Our Penguin ♪
♪ He's brave and clever ♪
♪ And kind ♪
♪ With a strong ♪
♪ Resourceful mind ♪
♪ He rules our land all day ♪
♪ In the most magnificent way ♪
♪ Oh, Penguin ♪
♪ Oh, Penguin, oh, Penguin ♪
♪ Our king, oh, Penguin, our king ♪
♪ Oh, Penguin... ♪
Production is steady, Mr. Cobblepot.
Our stores contain 512 loaves of bread,
2,001 liters of filtered water,
400,232 bullets,
and...
Penn, why is my countertenor out cold?
I-I'm sorry, Mr. Cobblepot.
Uh... everyone was working
through the night
in the bullet factory.
We've been, uh, shorthanded,
since people started defecting.
Defecting?
You've been holding out on me, Penn.
A thousand apologies.
I-I simply couldn't stand
seeing you upset while
you were recovering.
Just tell me everything!
Rumor is they've fled to a place
called Haven,
in Jim Gordon's sector.
My subjects are fleeing to Jim Gordon?
After he shot me?!
What about the bounty on Gordon's head?
We've had trouble finding takers.
The gangs are too disorganized,
and-and ordinary people, well...
they love him, sir.
They should love me.
Without me,
this entire island
would sink into chaos!
It's not just us.
People from every territory
are fleeing to Haven.
Finally. Breakfast.
Ha!
The Street Demonz!
To what do I owe this honor?
You hit our stronghold
and killed our men.
Not just us.
You hit the Lo Boyz and the Undead, too.
Did I, now?
You tagged the scenes with graffiti
that said "Penguin was here."
You dolt.
If I wanted to start a gang war,
you'd all be dead.
I wouldn't leave a few and sign my name.
Someone wanted you to attack me.
- That's a good point.
- Mm-hmm.
We didn't really think this through.
No. Well, there will be
plenty of time for thinking
when my men are ripping
out your fingernails.
Chain him up.
Wait! No!
Tighten our borders.
No one in or out, or it's your head.
That's right, Edward.
It's Mr. Penn's head!
It's his head!
You're a good dog, aren't you?
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
Word of this place is spreading
like a bad case of the
clap. We got refugees
coming in from every
territory in Gotham.
Can you blame 'em?
You saw what it was like out there.
People being starved and terrorized,
used by the gangs as slave labor.
You think those same gangs
aren't gonna want 'em back?
Sooner or later, they're
gonna come looking for us.
Let 'em.
Hey, I get it,
but after our excursion through
nightmareville last week,
we hardly have any ammo left... sorry...
and we barely have any food.
Okay, all right.
This is the only safe
place left in Gotham.
I'm not turning people away.
I was afraid you were gonna say that.
- Hey, how you feeling? How, is uh...
- I'm fine.
You getting any sleep?
You've been going full tilt for months,
carrying the weight of everyone.
Share the load. We can't
have you fall apart.
Thanks. I'm okay.
Please tell me some good news.
Water purification system repurposed
from Wayne Enterprises tech.
I know it's a drop in the
bucket, but every bit helps.
That's the last can of beans!
- I ain't had my rations yet!
- Think I have?
Hey, break it up. Break it up!
Break it up.
For all the new people here...
everyone is welcome in
Haven, but there are rules.
And one of them is we leave
the fighting outside.
Government already thinks
we don't deserve help.
We have to show otherwise.
Gangs want to tear
themselves apart outside,
that's their business.
In here, in Haven...
... we help each other survive.
Your speech worked.
For now.
What happens when they find out
the government abandoned them?
Sorry.
For what?
Jim, you're holding this place together.
You're giving these people hope.
Hope can only go so far.
Not to put more on your plate,
but the kid whose friends you
saved from the slavers...
his bunkmates say he's
been having nightmares.
Last night he fell off his bed
half-asleep, broke his arm.
Maybe you can talk to him.
Hey.
You don't feel like
joining the other kids?
We can't even begin to imagine
what you've been through.
But it's over. You're safe now.
I promise I will never let
anyone hurt you ever again.
Okay?
I got something for you.
From my rations.
Little pineapple.
Hang in there.
I'll come check on you later, okay?
Selina?
One second.
What are you doing out of bed?
The doctor said you need rest.
Does it look like I need rest?
No, but...
Look, whatever Ivy's root did to me...
I've never felt better.
So now I have to find
the freak who shot me.
I've been looking for Jeremiah
since the bridges blew.
I haven't found a thing.
Right, but there have
never been refugees
in the Green Zone before.
These people come from
all over Gotham, Bruce.
Someone has to know something.
I want to find Jeremiah
just as much as you do.
But even if we find him, he's
had months to fortify himself.
We can't go after him alone.
You scared, Bruce?
Of course I'm scared.
Jeremiah shot you to get to me.
He almost killed you.
I won't lose you.
I'm not yours to lose.
You can't stop me from
going after Jeremiah.
But I am asking you for help.
We take him down, we do it right.
We bring him back here,
and he stands trial for turning
Gotham into a madhouse.
What?
I was hoping I could count on you.
I heard rumors about
Jeremiah in the Dark Zone,
but who knows if they're true.
The Dark Zone?
On the other end of the island.
It's chaos,
ruled by those who've lost their minds
since the bridges went down.
They said Jeremiah is there,
gathering followers.
Sounds like a lead.
No. You can't go there.
You'll die.
We fought Jeremiah before.
You don't understand.
If you go to the Dark Zone,
Jeremiah is the least of your worries.
Everyone there is insane.
Look at what they did to my friend.
_
Penn, where the...
♪ Penguin, my hero ♪
♪ He having no fear-o... ♪
- Stop.
- ♪ He bringing joy and cheer-o. ♪
Stop!
Where is my staff? Where is Mr. Penn?
Um, they're having to, um...
defected to Haven.
And my guards didn't stop them?
My guards, too?
Edward?
Edward! Edward!
They took my dog?
Rumors say pup went willingly.
Lies!
You're in luck, my friend.
Jim Gordon is luring people
from every territory in Gotham
including yours.
As our interests are now aligned,
I have decided that you may live.
He's been dead since yesterday.
Contact the Lo Boyz and the Undead.
You have men, vehicles and gas.
I have the bullets.
It's time we paid a
visit to this Haven...
right after I put on some clothes.
Jim! Border guards just radioed.
Penguin broke through the barricades.
Street Demonz, other
gangs rolling with him.
They're heading for Haven.
We can beat them there. Load up!
What the hell are we gonna do?
We don't have more than a
dozen bullets between us.
You're right.
We get in a firefight and we're dead.
Okay, I'm gonna need you
to go get some help.
I'm not sure we got any friends left.
I'm hoping we still have one.
So, this is the Dark Zone.
They should call it the Dull Zone.
Place is dead.
What?
You seem yourself again.
I'm glad.
Wait, I know this block.
Used to be the posh part of town.
Everyone with money got out.
You didn't.
I had a reason to stay.
Oh, God!
Help me, please.
- Wait. Wait, wait.
- Come on.
Oh, God.
Get down.
Now we know who carved "kill"
into that guy's chest.
Do you think they know
anything about Jeremiah?
Let's find someone else to ask.
Let's go before they see us.
Kill!
We're not here for you.
We're looking for Jeremiah Valeska.
Kill you. Kill Jeremiah.
I don't think this guy is
much of a talker, Bruce.
What do you want to do?
Easy.
Find the schoolyard's biggest bully...
... and kick his teeth in.
The chicky-chick is mine.
Selina.
♪ Mine eyes have seen the glory ♪
♪ Of the coming of the Lord ♪
♪ He is trampling out the vintage ♪
♪ Where the grapes of
wrath are stored... ♪
Everyone inside. Inside.
Let's go. Get inside.
What's going on, Captain Gordon?
Inside, go.
Hold your fire.
Well, if it isn't my old friend Mr. Penn
and the Gertrud Kapelput Memorial Choir.
Oh, it is so nice to see
some familiar faces!
You shouldn't have come here, Oswald.
Oh, well, perhaps you shouldn't
have stolen my people
or my dog.
Every refugee is here
of their own free will
and under the protection of the GCPD.
Edward!
Come here!
Right now!
I will make this very simple, Jim.
You return our people and
Edward and an apology
or we will destroy this
little commune of yours
and salt the earth on which it stands.
The answer is no.
Now turn around unless
you want a bloodbath.
Let me explain something, Jim.
I heard about your little excursion
through the territories.
So, whatever ammo you stole from me,
I'm betting you used it up,
which means you're bluffing.
You want to test us, Oswald?
I'm sure my men could use
the target practice.
Slice and dice, little chicky.
You look soft.
You look like 300 pounds of ugly.
Kill and kill.
Where's Jeremiah?
- Where is Jeremiah?
- Jeremiah?
Tell me where Jeremiah is or my face
is going to be the last
thing you ever see.
Old Town North, okay?
We don't mess with him.
Old Town North?
You wouldn't lie to me, would you?
It's the truth.
Selina, he's had enough.
He's had enough
when I say he's had enough.
What the hell?
You won.
It's over.
Old Town North. See?
That was easy.
What are we waiting for?
You said they'll be out of bullets.
He's bluffing, you idiot.
How do you know?
I know Jim Gordon.
But if you require a demonstration,
three of you, march.
But, uh, they have guns.
So do I
and mine is most certainly loaded.
On my mark.
Make them count.
Ah.
Well, Jim,
it seems you are out of ammo, after all.
Now, if you don't want your men
to die in a hail of bullets,
you know what to do.
Fine. On the count of three.
- One, two...
- All right.
All right. Put them down.
Put them down.
Selina, what was that back there?
They had to know I was serious.
You didn't have to hurt him like that.
He was trying to kill me, Bruce,
just like Jeremiah tried to kill me.
So as far as I'm concerned...
he got off easy.
Whose side are you on, Bruce?
Yours. Always.
Then let's do what we came here to do.
Looks like we're close.
When I see him,
I'm gonna tear his throat out.
Selina.
Welcome, pilgrims,
to The Church of Jeremiah Valeska.
The only place where
you faithful pilgrims
can become your very best selves.
Who the hell is that?
I don't know.
I bet she knows where
Jeremiah is, though.
Stay here. I'm gonna get a closer look.
No. We do this together, Selina.
That was the deal.
Funny, I don't remember saying that.
Now, I know you've
come from far and wide
to meet the man himself.
But first, he requires a show of faith.
Don't be shy.
Jeremiah awaits.
Who is ready?
Lovely.
Jeremiah will be so happy.
But remember:
he wants only the most
faithful followers.
And you all have a chance
to prove yourself,
right up those stairs.
And the rest of you, get out!
Selina.
Wait.
I want to meet Jeremiah.
You don't look like one
of Jeremiah's worshipers.
I have witnessed his work firsthand.
I will never forget it.
Then right this way.
You're gonna regret this.
Strong words,
for someone who is out of options.
First, I'm gonna make you
watch while I destroy Haven.
Then, I'm gonna shoot you
and leave you for dead,
just like you did to me.
Sound fair?
If the government liberates the
city and finds out about this,
you'll be at the top of their list.
Wake up, Jim.
The government has abandoned us.
The only law in Gotham is power,
and that power belongs to me.
We have children here. Families.
What happens when the gangs take them?
Hmm.
They probably go back to
being slaves, I guess.
My people, on the other hand,
will go back to their regular lives,
with their bellies full of
gruel and their heads full
of wonderful thoughts about
their grand protector, me.
If this is about revenge
against me, do your worst.
But leave the refugees out of it.
So heroic.
Almost tempting.
But I think I'm gonna stick
to my original plan.
Uh, Jim's gonna die, isn't he, boy?
Oh, you're a good dog, yes, you are.
Mr. Cobblepot.
Stop. That one belongs to me.
No can do.
You sacrificed one of my guys
calling the cop's bluff.
So what?
I said he's mine.
Oh, thank you, Mr. Cobblepot.
Then how about we take your territory?
And your bullet factory.
Penn! Penn!
I'm sorry, Mr. Cobblepot.
You fool!
This never would have happened
if you stayed with me.
Why did you leave?
Everyone hated you.
You will pay for this!
Hey, Penguin, you got
something on your face.
Let me go! We had a deal!
Shut your mouth...
... or the next thing that comes
out your mouth is a bullet.
Man, you are on fire!
I take it that didn't work
out the way you'd hoped.
Barbara?
Hey, you in here?
You've gotten good at that.
Haven't you heard, Harvey?
No men in the Sirens past midnight.
Sorry to bust up ladies' night,
but Jim Gordon needs your help.
Oh, perhaps it's time Golden
Boy learned to save himself.
And aren't you tired
of playing sidekick?
See, I don't see it that way.
Me and Jim are friends.
We're fighting for the same thing.
It seemed like you got that.
You know, I remember when
you first partnered up.
He, the idealistic rookie.
You, the cynical veteran.
You were sane.
Now you carry his laundry.
Do you ever wonder what your life
might've been like if you'd
never met Jim Gordon?
I'd be dead, or wishing I was.
You're delusional, Harvey.
Just like all the sad saps
who think the government
is just gonna sail in and save them.
Maybe. And look,
I know you've had your
differences with Jim,
but if you don't help him now,
- Penguin and the other gangs...
- Penguin?
You should've opened with that.
Let's move!
It's not working.
We need to find a way
to cut these bindings.
Well, I'm not helping you, Jim.
You are the reason I'm
in this predicament.
You have taken everything from me.
Keep your voice down.
I kept people safe. I
protected them from chaos.
They should have loved me.
Instead, they came here, to this pigsty,
to be covered in fleas and filth.
Why? What makes this place so special?
Well, for one thing,
it's far away from you.
Oh, that's rich, Jim.
You should be proud of
yourself for that one.
Quiet.
I think I saw someone place a stash...
there.
- Who is that?
- A friend.
Just act normal.
I know it's a stretch.
Hey.
Bingo.
I'm gonna get out of here, Jim.
And I'm gonna watch these animals
tear this place to the ground.
So you make your way back to
your territory. Then what?
Hmm? You don't think that eventually,
these gangs are gonna come after you?
We need to take them out.
Right here, right now.
Now, how do we pick it up?
I'll have to have a word
with the cleaning lady.
Mind your step, pilgrims.
But first,
the main attraction.
Six-shooters.
Bang, bang.
Each of you get one gun.
And one bullet.
What is this?
Like I said, a show of faith.
But if you're ch-ch-ch-chicken...
Try me.
Oh, my little pilgrims.
This will make Jeremiah so happy.
Now,
on the count of three.
One...
Two...
Chicken poo.
Just seeing if y'all were listening.
Three!
Well, well, well.
You disappoint me, curls.
I had such high hopes for you.
What, with that
cocky little swagger and all.
I'm just not a mindless idiot
who's willing to get shot
in the head for nothing.
Hear that?
Curls is here to judge all of us,
to judge Jeremiah and his methods.
What a fitting reminder.
To outsiders,
Jeremiah's methods may
look like madness,
but we believers know:
his methods will be our salvation.
Now,
I need to have a word with our friend.
The rest of you
get straight A's.
Please proceed
and be reborn.
What's the matter?
Don't you want to meet Jeremiah?
I do.
I'm just not willing to play
your little psychotic game.
But, baby, it's so fun.
If it's so fun,
why don't you play?
Don't you get it?
I have.
The bullet's still inside.
Rattling around this old noggin of mine.
Ping. Ping.
Ping.
Boy, do I feel it when
the nights get cold.
You're insane.
No.
I was willing to look death in the face,
to allow the old me to die.
It's the gift Jeremiah's
brother Jerome gave him.
And the gift he wants
for all his followers.
Don't you want to experience
this gift for yourself?
I know I want you to.
Selina.
You know me.
There isn't a single part
of Bruce Wayne's life
that we don't know about.
His joys, his disappointments,
his desires.
But just like Bruce wasn't ready
to embrace his true self,
looks like you aren't either.
Maybe.
But one thing
Jeremiah did teach me is I...
hate
having a gun pointed at my face.
Oh, puddin', aren't you delicious.
Don't call me puddin'.
There you go, Selina.
I knew you had it in you.
All it took was a little
kick in the pants.
Where's Jeremiah?
Selina, drop the gun.
Oh-oh, your boyfriend's worried.
But I still don't think
you have what it takes.
Yeah?
Well, let's see what happens
when someone deserves
to get shot in the head.
Selina, stop!
Wait. You're bleeding.
If you know what's good for you,
you will let me go.
We need to get you patched up.
What are you doing?
I have been doing it your way.
I'm gonna do it my way.
Selina!
Ha, ha, look at those biceps.
Whoa, I need him to build barricades.
Nah, homie.
This guy's got cage match
written all over him.
I'll give you two of mine in exchange.
How about this.
Drop your guns, and I won't shoot you.
How the hell did he get free?
Don't matter. He's bluffing again.
I'm afraid he's not.
Neither am I.
Come on out, boys.
Yes, Edward, I killed the bad men.
Penguin shot the gang leader.
Penguin! Penguin! Penguin!
Penguin! Penguin!
You'd said we'd be safe here.
We were better off where we came from.
Give it a rest, he saved us!
All right, listen up.
- Listen to me.
- For what?
Listen to me!
I know today was a hard day.
And I can't say there won't be others.
But we won.
We got Penguin's guns, his ammunition.
We survived.
And as long as we survive,
hope survives in Gotham.
I think that's worth fighting for.
So do I.
There's work to be done,
wounded to be cared for,
food, water to be doled out.
Tomorrow's another day.
Go to.
Captain, we've got Penguin outside.
All right, give me a minute.
Hey.
That was a brave thing you did there.
We wouldn't have escaped without you.
You saved me and my friends.
I wanted to help.
I can't be everywhere at once.
I'm gonna need people I can
trust watching over this place.
Maybe...
you could be my deputy here in Haven.
Thanks.
Because, honestly, I'm
allergic to pineapple.
Go get 'em, Deputy.
Jim, is this really necessary?
I did just save, I don't
know, hundreds of people.
After endangering them to begin with.
Forgive me if I wanted to play it safe.
Still, I do hope that there
are no hard feelings.
You did the right thing today, Oswald.
You're free to go, just
don't make me regret it.
Jim!
Harvey.
- Hi, Pengy.
- Jim!
- Hold your fire.
- Bye, Pengy.
- Barbara, no. No.
- Get out of the way! Now!
Outside of the Green Zone,
he's fair game, but not here.
Last chance.
Move now or you get my first bullet.
I'm not moving.
- Synced & Corrected By NaShWaN AL-YeMeN 2019 -
-- treestand_2002@yahoo.co.uk --