GORDON:
Previously on Gotham...
I have walked this earth for centuries.
Only you can kill me
and only with that dagger.
(GROANS)
- What did I say?
- I can help you get Tabitha back.
Professor Hugo Strange is the one man
who can cure you.
Join me, and we will find him.
(GASPING)
Okay. But you'd better deliver.
Why would I help you?
You love me. You've loved me all along.
What's your record for how many banks
you've robbed in one day?
You're playing a dangerous game, Lee.
LELIA: Ra's al Ghul chose you
to pass on his spirit.
We have much more to show you.
BARBARA: All my life, I have known
that I was meant for more.
This isn't you.
I'm not gonna let your jealousy
distract me.
Ladies, escort Ms. Galavan
to the street.
MAN: We serve the one and only
true master, Ra's al Ghul.
- But he's dead.
- Death is only an illusion.
(SWISHES)
(GRUNTING)
(KNIVES SWISHING)
(BARBARA PANTING)
(SHOUTING) What the hell?
- You didn't sense our approach?
- No, you're ninjas.
The Demon's Head gives its bearer power
to see past, present, future as one.
You should have anticipated our attack.
So this was a test?
I'm The Demon's Head.
My hand is a fricking light bulb.
That is only its mark.
You have yet to access its real powers.
You're questioning whether I'm worthy?
I'm sick of this.
The men from the League,
Tabitha, and now you?
You misunderstand.
How do you think Ra's al Ghul became
the world's most fearsome warrior
and ruled empires?
He saw the future.
So, attacking me was what,
a way to jump-start it, like,
"Hey, Demon's Head, snap to it?"
The powers of The Demon's Head
are triggered by intense emotions.
All right. So next time,
don't go so easy on me.
And take that knife out of my face.
(CAR ENGINE REVVING)
(DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING)
You don't have a covert mode
on this thing?
(ENGINE REVVING STOPS)
(SCOFFS)
Show-off.
So, you're gonna tell me
what Tabitha needs us for?
All I know is it's about Barbara,
and it's important.
- So, what's the emergency?
- Inside.
You coming?
Tabitha, what am I doing here?
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
(BRUCE GASPS)
- What the heck?
- Wait.
What the hell? What is this?
I don't know.
She didn't tell me this part.
Barbara needs our help.
She's gonna get herself killed.
She has this thing
called The Demon's Head.
- This is about Ra's al Ghul?
- He's the one who gave it to her.
These guys are gonna
help us take it back.
Okay, so why do you need Bruce?
You're gonna bring him back.
You can't do this. Ra's wanted to die.
He wanted me to kill him.
And now we need him alive.
No, no, no!
(BRUCE STRAINING)
No, no!
Bone, flesh, breath.
Come back to us, our leader.
Now we close the circle.
We give you the blood
of the one who slew you.
(TENSE MUSIC PLAYING)
No.
You have no idea
what you've done!
(OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING)
Five banks in one night? You're joking.
I wish. These guys were slick.
Banks didn't even know
they were hit till they opened.
One of the banks, the thieves came
in on boats through the sewer.
Tunneled up into the vaults.
All branches of Gotham Savings
and Loan. Why the same bank?
Maybe a leak in security,
maybe a grudge.
Five banks in one night.
It's like someone was trying
to make a point.
Prove how smart he is.
- Ed Nygma?
- The bowler fits.
Should I put out a BOLO on him?
Sure. In the meantime,
there's someone else I can talk to.
Say hey to Lee for me, won't you?
Tell her, nice shooting Sofia.
What, I can't make a joke?
That's what that was?
Why don't you go
put that BOLO out?
(PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
- Here you go. No problem.
- Thanks.
Look at them.
We did good.
Oh, yeah.
My brilliance allowed us to rob
five banks in one night.
Now these fine folks of The Narrows
are gonna be drowning in booze
and smokes for years to come.
So inspiring.
They're also gonna
use the money to buy food
and clothing and medicine.
What's wrong?
What am I to you?
A friend. A partner.
Are you always this amorous
with your friends?
I mean, I know that only happened once.
- Ed.
- Don't call me Ed.
Hey, I care about you.
I depend on you.
You know what we've got planned.
Other things are just
gonna have to wait.
You're not stringing me along,
are you, Lee?
Don't you wanna find out?
The answer to the riddle?
Maybe I do.
Are we good for tomorrow night?
Yeah. We just have a few last details.
And trust me,
this is gonna be a work of art.
That sounds promising.
Oh, what the hell, count us in.
You could've told me.
- You wouldn't have brought him.
- Yeah, because he's my friend.
And what is Barbara? What am I?
Pick a side and stick to it.
RA'S AL GHUL:
Do you know what you've done?
The years I spent planning my death.
- Now you've ruined it!
- Master.
The woman you gave The Demon's Head to,
she started a war.
I started that war!
The League of Shadows was rotten
and only through violence
could it be reborn.
Master, our lives are yours to take.
But this woman
does not serve the League.
Her goals are limited. Selfish.
That's Barbara all right.
Whatever faith you had
in her was misplaced.
If she keeps The Demon's Head,
the League shall die.
Wait, what do you mean,
"if she keeps The Demon's Head"?
I thought you were supposed to get it
the second you...
Came back.
No. Barbara must give it to me.
She'll never do that.
Then I'll kill her
and rip it from her corpse.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
PENGUIN: You owe us.
(NYGMA LAUGHS)
NYGMA: I'm sorry.
We owe you how?
Because we made you.
Both of you. Without me, you would
still be trapped inside Ed.
And you would still be stitching up
busted lips ringside.
I need money to buy back Sofia's capos.
Butch is saving
for future medical expenses.
(SCOFFS)
What'd you make last night?
Three, four million?
Say we go halfsies.
I've heard your offer.
And here's my counter. Bite me.
I don't like people coming into my club,
telling me what to do.
And I don't like threats,
implicit or otherwise,
and I really don't like
people telling me they made me.
NYGMA: Well said, Lee.
(NYGMA CLAPPING)
- Oh, God. Are you kidding me?
- What?
Okay, we're done.
I thought you got past all that
when you became the Riddler.
Past what?
Ed's pathetic adoration of her.
But, no, clearly,
he passed it all into you,
like a virus.
She knows it and she's using you.
Shame on you,
stringing along this troubled man.
- Get out!
- I don't think so.
We did not come here for violence.
We came here hoping our friends
would honor their debts.
Let us hope they come to their senses.
A little advice.
Be sure to skim some off the top
when she tosses you aside.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Kind of defeats the purpose
if I can hear you.
Hello, Barbara.
- Ra's.
- (GLASS BREAKING)
Don't be afraid.
(STUTTERING) What happened?
How are you even...
It's a long story.
But tell me,
what have you done with my gift?
Well, you might have left a how-to.
Plus, a heads-up
to your League of Shadows cronies.
Turns out the old boys' club don't
appreciate a woman calling the shots.
But you have plans
on rebuilding the League of Shadows?
You've read
the histories that I left for you?
I've read them.
But I need to do my own thing.
Your "own thing"?
With the power you gave me,
I can rule Gotham
like no one ever has before.
The people will worship me like a queen.
How disappointing.
You're right.
They should worship me like a god.
Enough. Give me your hand
so that I can take it back.
No. It is mine. You promised me!
I was mistaken in you, Barbara.
"Mistaken"?
Tell that to her.
You think that is you.
(RA'S LAUGHS)
She was just a whore.
I killed her out of pity.
You're lying.
The Demon's Head is my destiny.
Then why have you
not unlocked its secrets?
You sad, deluded woman.
You thought you were
a reincarnated queen.
But in truth, you're just
an unstable nightclub owner,
whose greatest accomplishment
was the murder of her own parents.
You are nothing.
Now, give me your hand.
Or I will kill you
and take The Demon's Head by force.
Try it, zombie boy.
(GRUNTING)
(BARBARA GROANS)
(NECK SNAPS)
(GRUNTING)
(BARBARA YELLING)
Get her out of here. Go!
(PANTING)
I'm fine.
(GRUNTS)
(CAR SPEEDING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Get in!
(ENGINE REVVING)
MAN:
All right, you know the rules.
Hands only, no drinking water.
I want a good, clean eat.
Ready? Ready?
- (CROWD CHEERING)
- (CHOMPING)
- Come on, eat it.
- Come, come, come on.
I'm looking for Lee Thompkins.
The Doc.
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
Lee.
(MAN VOMITING)
The winner!
Jim, you don't look like
a guy who got shot four times.
Because you were able to keep me alive.
Thanks.
I'd just shot Sofia Falcone in the head.
I was in a good mood.
I'm looking for Ed Nygma.
Five banks were robbed last night.
It has all the hallmarks
of a Nygma special.
I haven't seen Ed in weeks.
I know you feel loyalty towards him,
but you of all people should know
he's sick. He's a psychopath.
We all have our flaws.
(GORDON SIGHS)
Lee.
I can understand why you're here,
but there are other ways
of finding absolution.
You can't take ownership
of everyone's problems.
This is The Narrows.
Nobody owns anything down here
but the slumlords.
Why don't you try
going after the real criminals?
The people making money
off the backs of the poor.
You mean like Gotham Savings and Loan?
None of the guards were killed.
The more I think about it,
doesn't exactly feel like Ed Nygma.
- Or not just him.
- If we're done here...
Whatever's happened,
you can always call me. I can help.
You really don't get it, do you, Jim?
It's good to see you.
Ra's just tried to kill me
because of you.
You could have just given him
The Demon's Paw.
"Head"!
It's "The Demon's Head" and it is mine!
You betrayed me.
I was trying to save you from yourself.
Also, the other day, you actually
told your thugs to kill me.
It was a spanking.
- If I wanted you dead, I would've...
- Oh, shut up, both of you!
We're wasting time,
Ra's could be on his way right now.
Which wouldn't be a problem
if Barbara would
just give him what he wants.
Never gonna happen.
Okay, so what are we gonna do, Barbara?
We're just gonna walk around
with targets on our backs?
No, we're gonna kill the son of a bitch.
The kid did it before, right?
Yeah, but that was different.
We had, like, a special knife.
Yeah, that one you got from auction.
Where is it?
We gave it back
to the Nanda Parbat embassy.
Great, so we'll just do
a little smash-and-grab
and then I'll fillet the zombie.
I have to be the one holding the knife.
It's part of the ritual, like the blood.
I have to kill him again.
Even if that's the case, Master Bruce,
I can't allow you to do it. Not again.
We might not get another chance, Alfred.
This is the only way.
Says you, the mystical knife expert.
I've got The Demon's Head.
I bet if I'm holding it in my hand...
What if killing Ra's unlocks my powers?
Yeah, and what if you fail
and Ra's gets the knife back?
We'll worry about who kills him later.
Right now, we have to get
the knife before Ra's does.
TABITHA: Embassies are heavily guarded.
And we can't wait till night.
We're gonna need guns,
smoke grenades to cause a diversion.
If I may, there may be another option.
But you got to guarantee
not to stab us in the back.
Again.
So, in short, we'd like to thank you
very much.
Both of us would like to
thank you for taking such good...
Such good care of her.
But now we'd like to
take the knife home. Please.
It was never yours
to begin with, Mr. Pennyworth.
It belongs to my people.
When Mr. Bruce Wayne
purchased it at auction,
he was rescuing a looted
historical treasure.
That's why you returned it to us.
Yeah. But it was a loan,
wasn't it, mate?
It was never meant as a keepsie.
This knife is worth millions
and you just gave it away?
- You idiot!
- Easy, muffin.
Look, you look like you've got
a stable head on your shoulders.
Why don't I make a little donation,
and you give us the knife,
and we walk away?
Does Bruce Wayne even know about this?
(SCOFFS) Whatever your agenda is,
I believe that you and your chippie
should leave.
A chippie? Did you just call
my missus a chippie?
What is that...
What... A "chippie,"
is that a new term or something...
Something...
(COUGHING)
(STUTTERING) What? What's happening?
I can't breathe.
Oh, my God. I think
he's having a heart attack.
- I can't breathe.
- He's having a heart attack.
(ALARM RINGING)
- Look what you did.
- Tell the security
it's a false alarm.
I can't breathe.
I can't breathe. I can't breathe.
Give me your jacket.
Put your jacket under his head.
- Put your jacket.
- (ALFRED GROANING)
It really hurts. It really...
It really hurts.
(ALFRED GROANING)
TABITHA: All right,
you're gonna be just fine.
It really hurts.
(GRUNTS)
Stay with me.
Ooh, I feel much better now.
(ALARM RINGING CONTINUES)
Sorry about the fuss, fellas.
"Chippie!"
(DOOR OPENS)
Oh!
PENGUIN: She's using you.
Shame on you,
stringing along this troubled man.
(SIGHS) This troubled man.
Oh, can't argue with that.
Oh, no!
Sorry. Just because you're in charge,
doesn't mean I disappear.
That's because you're too stupid
to know when you've lost.
Have I? "Lee, what am I to you?"
Does that sound like you to you?
Because to me, that sounds like me.
I'm not proud of that phrasing.
I'm inside you, buddy. Like a virus,
infecting your thoughts.
Oh, please.
You couldn't even begin
to comprehend my thoughts,
much less influence them.
What about your feelings?
How else would you explain
those desperate attempts
to gain her approval?
No. No, if anything, she's the one who...
You gave money away to the poor.
- That was part of a larger plan.
- Yeah.
Her plan. What did you ever care
about The Narrows?
I don't.
Every person here could drown
in a stew of their own filth,
and I wouldn't lose a wink of sleep.
Oh, I know.
Because all you care about is her.
(ECHOING) Just like I did.
So keep that up, buddy.
'Cause soon, there will be no telling
where you end and I begin.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CREAKS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
That's not gonna happen.
Well done. Now, knife, please.
Selina, it has to be me.
Selina, give me the knife.
And you better scram
while you still can.
I'm taking the knife!
Oh, you do not want to
make me angry, kid.
Sorry, "muffin",
I'm gonna need you to step back.
Don't you even go there, love.
Selina, don't give her the knife.
(SCOFFS) Screw this.
Your arrogance is gonna get
someone killed, you know.
- Or just you.
- Stop!
Thank you.
Now... Get in!
Selina, let's go.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(ENGINE STARTS)
Nice doing business with you, boys.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
You were right.
She's using me.
Finally.
So much for you being smart, now.
Yeah. The most brilliant minds
are often blind
to the most obvious truths.
Finally.
- And you came to me...
- Because that lovestruck moron, Ed,
is floating down a river of dopamine,
deep within the primitive
reward circuit of my brain,
and I need you to help me drown him.
For good.
Did you bring the half-share
of profits we asked for?
That money is gone.
Distributed among
the riffraff of The Narrows. But...
Those five banks were merely
the first stage
of a very sophisticated plan.
And the coup de grâce is tonight.
I knew you were scheming something.
That's why we were
gonna rob you afterward.
But I prefer this way.
There better be enough in there
to get me fixed.
- Don't forget our deal.
- I won't.
Thank you so much.
And how big is the score?
About $100 million.
Apiece.
And you help me
deal with Lee Thompkins.
(DOOR OPENS)
Thank you for coming back.
We serve The Demon's Head, Barbara.
So, what's the play?
Simple. I do the flashlight
hand thingy, summon Ra's,
little stabby-stab with the knife,
send him back to hell.
Think I can remember that.
You can't be serious.
That's your plan?
How do you expect to get the drop
on someone who's studied
kung fu for 2,000 years,
and is a zombie?
Not feeling a whole lot
of faith here, kitty-cat.
Maybe I'd have a little more if you
knew how to use your demon head
for something
other than a flashlight.
You're gonna get us killed.
You got any useful suggestions?
- Maybe call backup.
- I did.
- Here they are.
- What if Bruce is right?
Let him use the knife. At least
we know that it worked before.
You just took the knife from him.
Because you told me to pick a side.
I thought you had some other plan
other than
"Let's stab the immortal undead guy
and hope for the best."
Listen, Selina, we're strongest
when we're together.
Now, are you in or are you out?
If it's suicide by Ra's, I'm out.
Fine, then go.
What if she's right?
I can't control The Demon's Head.
Maybe it's like Ra's said. Maybe...
I am just a nightclub owner.
I should have never
trusted those men.
I didn't want you to have
The Demon's Head.
Not even sure I want it now.
Three years we've been together,
on and off.
And I've never seen you
doubt yourself.
So, however you
wanna play this, I'm in.
But if you're saying
you're not worthy,
that's where I jump ship.
Let's do this.
I suppose on the bright side,
you won't have to kill him.
Again.
- Except, I'm the only one who can.
- Well, so said Ra's.
I mean, no disrespect to your
magical daggers and all of that,
but I'd love to see what would happen
if I pulled his head off
his bloody shoulders.
I can't believe
Selina gave Barbara the knife.
(SCOFFS)
Yeah, well, at least
we know where she stands.
That's what you think.
Oh, you got a bloody cheek
turning up here.
I gave Barbara the knife
because if there was a chance
she could use it, I wanted her to.
That way,
Bruce didn't have to kill him.
I would've done what I had to do.
And you would've gone straight back
to being the douchebag
you've been the last few months.
So, no, thank you.
She's got a point there,
Master Bruce.
Thanks for the explanation.
You can leave now.
- Bruce...
- You sided with them.
(SIGHS) Why does it have
to be about sides?
There is somebody,
something out there
that needs to be stopped.
So why can't we focus on that?
Another good point.
Barbara and Tabitha
are gonna get themselves killed.
And I don't want that to happen.
GORDON: There were easier banks to hit.
- Why yours?
- I keep telling you.
I have no idea.
I'm the victim.
You're treating me like a criminal.
Yeah, I wonder
where we'd get that from.
- Excuse me?
- We did some digging,
and your bank has been
investigated for redlining,
usury, illegal foreclosures.
And cleared on all counts.
You have good lawyers.
So we deserve to be robbed?
I'm done here.
Ma'am, can you just
give us a second, please?
(DOOR OPENS)
- What the hell are you doing?
- She's a crook.
A bigger crook
than whoever ripped her off.
You mean like Lee?
Look, brother,
I know what this is about.
You went down to The Narrows
and came back all fired up, okay?
But alienating her
is not gonna help us.
If Lee's involved with Nygma,
we got to stop it before it goes bad.
Which of your branches
are the most vulnerable?
As of this afternoon, none of them.
We have a security protocol.
After the Arkham breakout
and the robberies...
You moved your assets
to a secure location.
Yes, of course.
All 45 branches, this morning.
It's totally safe.
Fortified and heavily guarded.
Where is it?
- Pistol would've been more fun.
- You indulge me.
Breaking open the vault
is the last detail.
Big detail. How did you solve it?
A little help from some friends.
I'm the revealer of masks.
When I appear,
friend becomes foe,
and the one that you love,
becomes the one that you hate.
What am I?
Betrayal.
Hello, Lee.
(GASPS)
Yeah, it's not a dart gun. Let's go.
(SWORD SWISHING)
(ELECTRICITY BUZZING)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
- Nice entrance.
- I do hope you've reconsidered,
and are planning to give me
what I want.
I've thought about it. A lot.
And about us.
We had something, didn't we?
Back when you were less dug up-y.
I do not have time for this.
I will give you what you want, Ra's.
But I want you to admit
we had a connection.
And that those things you said to me
were just mind games
to make me lose my nerve.
You want me to tell you
that you're special?
Would that be so hard?
No.
And moreover,
it's true. You are special.
I'm just sorry
it had to come to this, Barbara.
Me, too.
But thank you for saying that.
(GASPS)
Ouch.
She must do this by herself.
(BARBARA SCREAMS)
(GRUNTING)
(BARBARA CHOKING)
(STRAINING)
Barbara, fight.
(GRUNTS)
But this is Barbara's fight.
(PANTING)
(GASPING)
But this is Barbara's fight.
Well, now. Look at you.
Yeah. Look at me.
You wanna give it another shot?
(GRUNTS)
She's mastered The Demon's Head.
Wow!
I can see why he likes this thing.
That's enough.
Give me what I want
or your friend dies.
I thought this was between us.
Choose now.
Tabby, I...
I can't give this up.
(GASPS)
No!
That's enough.
Choose now.
You win.
Just don't hurt her.
(PANTS)
Barbara Kean,
you surprise me yet again.
Maybe I wasn't mistaken
in you after all.
(RA'S GRUNTING)
(EXHALES HEAVILY)
Give me the knife, Ra's.
Let me kill you.
Today is not the day that I die.
NYGMA: This is the price for
taking advantage of me, Lee.
You're wrong, Ed. I wasn't using you.
Again, don't call me "Ed."
And I'm not wrong about you.
Truck is almost full. We should go.
Tell the ogre,
have him leave the property deeds.
They all belong to The Narrows.
Worthless.
(CHUCKLES)
And so ends the tale
of the Queen of The Narrows.
Hmm?
Goodbye, Lee. (LAUGHING)
What are you doing?
How did that go again?
"And the revealer of masks,
when I appear, friend becomes foe."
- Betrayal.
- Exactly.
(ALARM RINGING)
What the hell are you doing?
Just burning
The Narrows' property deeds.
Not that.
He's proving his love
by betraying us.
These bars can't hold me.
When I get out...
We'll be gone.
I just wanted you to hear something.
Oswald, we've been
through thick and thin.
And I hold no grudge on you.
But you come against Lee,
and you come against me.
I'm gonna dismember you, you twerp!
Yep, not even gonna try with you.
Let's go, Lee.
It won't make any difference.
She's still using you.
You are not the Riddler,
you are a fool!
God...
(STRAINING)
Why do that?
Why bring Penguin and Grundy if
you're just gonna lock them inside?
I needed Grundy to open the vault.
And Oswald was gonna rob us anyway,
so, just kept an eye on him.
He'll get over it, or he won't.
So you don't think I'm using you?
No, I know you are.
Then why would you
betray your friends for me?
Is this...
- Are you Ed?
- No, I'm me.
- How can you be sure?
- Because Ed didn't understand you.
He didn't see how deeply
you had changed. I do.
I know that that virus
woke up something deep inside you.
And you let that something loose
when you shot Sofia.
And you love it.
And I love it, too.
And I know that
you don't feel same way about me.
But you will.
And when you do, I will be here.
Ed Nygma,
you are a riddle.
That's the nicest thing
someone's said to me.
(SIRENS WAILING)
- That's Jim.
- This alarm just went off.
He was on to us.
- We can just go out the back.
- No, they'll see the truck.
One of us needs to distract them.
Done.
No!
I can handle Jim Gordon.
You take the money to The Narrows.
- You trust me?
- I do.
Go.
GORDON: GCPD.
Nygma, we know you're in there.
Come out with your hands up.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Sweet merciful mother.
You know your rights.
(SIGHS)
You'd have done the same for me.
Ladies, I hope
this isn't one of those
"kill the old queen" situations.
We discussed things.
Demon's Head or not, you fought.
Not for yourself,
but those alongside you.
You are worthy, Barbara Kean.
We follow you
to our deaths and beyond.
We can find from Barbara where
the League hides temples, safe houses.
He'll be in one of them.
Meanwhile,
we'll try to fix the knife.
Yeah, we'll just take it to
the magic knife shop, no problem.
- Selina, be serious.
- I am.
If Ra's wanted you dead,
you would be.
He obviously likes you.
- It's not about me.
- I know it's not about you.
(SELINA SIGHS)
Gotham has managed
a long time without you.
It can manage a little longer,
if you have one night off.
(SIGHS)
You did good today.
So did you.
RA'S: Ahem.
Poor timing. Apologies.
I only want to talk. Alone, please.
I'm staying.
Very well.
She's right, you know, Bruce.
I do like you.
Respect you.
Respect you for what you'll become.
You have no idea what I'll become.
Of course, I do.
At least, who you could become.
- Why are you here?
- I felt I owed you an explanation
as to why I chose to live.
When I took back The Demon's Head,
I saw a vision
of a cataclysmic event
soon to befall this city.
What event?
A cleansing fire that will destroy,
purify,
create. Create you, Bruce.
Because I will use it as a mighty forge,
molding you into
a dark knight of Gotham.
(SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING)
If it doesn't kill you, that is.