Previously onGotham...
Oh, crud.
He killed my mother, Jim.
He had her murdered in front of me.
I am going to kill you.
Think I found something.
The week of his murder,
he was supposed to meet
a woman named Karen Jennings
about something
called Pinewood Farms.
Pinewood Farms was a bio-engineering
program at Wayne Enterprises.
It started up again, didn't it?
That's why my father came to see you
after all those years.
Karen Jennings is gonna be dead
the minute she hits Blackgate prison.
That's why we're gonna break her out.
The man who contracted Matches
Malone to kill your parents
called himself "The Philosopher."
And I'd be willing to bet that this
is the man who's behind Pinewood.
"Hugo Strange, The Philosopher."
He runs Arkham now.
We brought someone back.
Azrael!
We actually did it.
Rally to me. Rally...
St. Dumas will deliver us.
Dumas will deliver us.
Rally. Heathens.
And Dumas will protect us.
Heathens, idolaters,
Spawn of Satan, prepare to die!
No, no. No, don't. Please.
Sister, speak to me, please.
Please, speak to me.
Who are you, huh?
Who are you?
Has there been any improvement
since he woke up yesterday?
No.
But he is wonderful, isn't he?
Who are you?
Strong as an ox, fast as a snake.
Mad as a hatter.
There's not much use bringing back
the dead if they come back crazy.
Oh, he's not crazy.
He just doesn't know who he is.
His psyche can't reconcile
being brought back from the dead.
It's fractured,
grasping at fragmented memories.
The text that he has written
on the walls
are all verses from this book.
The Will and Order of St. Dumas.
The Galavan family
is proudly descended
from 12th-century crusading knights.
This is their sacred text.
Evidently, our patient has memorized
the whole book.
His brain is struggling
to rebuild a coherent self,
but he's using the wrong parts.
So, what's the cure?
Good question.
What is it?
Mr. Gordon.
Professor Strange.
Sorry to drop by unexpected.
Oh, not at all. Please, have a seat.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
I've been hired by a client
to look into something.
I was hoping
you could help me with it.
Of course.
This is Karen Jennings.
She was murdered last night.
Oh, how tragic.
She was a test subject
in an old Wayne Enterprises program
called Pinewood Farms.
Before she passed, Karen mentioned
you were involved with the program.
That was a long time ago.
Try and remember.
If you can.
Pinewood Farms was started
by Thomas Wayne
in an attempt to cure
humanity's greatest ailments
on the genetic level:
old age, disease, even death.
But that's not what happened, is it?
Karen said the program
tried to play God,
and you ended up creating monsters.
I was just a researcher
with no knowledge of that
until it was too late.
A man of your skill and expertise
a lowly researcher?
Find that hard to believe.
But it's true.
Mr. Wayne excelled
at compartmentalizing
every aspect of his life.
Within Pinewood,
the left hand often didn't know
what the right was doing.
He lied to us all.
Not many people would see you
as the victim here.
I was one of the ones
who forced Thomas Wayne
to shut down the program,
but by then...
so many people had been hurt.
I have a theory.
I believe you ran Pinewood Farms.
I believe you've restarted the
program and I would like to know...
Why are you really here, Mr. Gordon?
Excuse me?
This whole city
has turned its back on you,
despite you risking your life
to save it over and over again.
I'm not here for a therapy session,
Professor.
No. It's more like an interrogation
by a man who's no longer
a police officer.
Who no longer has the right
to demand answers.
The only reason you're sitting
in that chair is because I allow it.
So let me ask you, why are you here?
Like I said, I have a client.
Bruce Wayne, I suppose.
So it's a job?
You're here to pay the rent?
Surely not.
All that's happened to you
this last year...
Hero cop found guilty of murder,
sentenced unjustly to Blackgate,
and now you return to what?
You've lost everything.
You're trying to make up
for the sins of your past,
and you believe that this case
will somehow bring about
- your own personal redemption.
- No.
You're not doing this
for your client.
You're doing this for yourself.
You're wrong.
You just exhibited several tells.
Facial tics, expressions
and eye movements
that people involuntarily
betray themselves with when they lie.
Let's talk about Victor Fries.
Victor Fries is dead, Mr. Gordon.
Really? I saw him last night.
That's impossible.
This is a court order
signed by District Attorney Dent
to exhume Fries' body.
Where is it buried?
He was cremated.
Thank you.
For what?
I can read tells, too.
You're lying.
I needed to be sure
you were behind all this,
and now I am.
Don't lie! I heard you!
Don't. Please.
- There you go.
- Don't.
Please do! Squeeze the life from him!
Kill him! Kill him now!
- Are you two fighting again?
- He called me fat!
I didn't do anything! It wasn't me!
It, it was Lucy.
The fifth personality again.
Such a nasty attitude.
See, this gets complicated.
See, Lucy is in his head,
because Rudy has what's called
multiple personality...
In his head?
- Then I'll pull her out!
- No... no!
She's... she's a... she's a ghost.
- A ghost...
- Yes.
And she makes Rudy say things
that he doesn't wanna say.
I can see her.
Lucy?
You've got some nerve,
making old Rudy say things like that.
You know that Helzinger is not fat.
In fact, you said that Helzinger
was handsome.
Don't you shove me!
She slapped me.
Now I'll tell you something, Lucy.
You will leave Rudy alone,
and if you come back here again,
you'll have to deal with me.
Thank you, Lucy.
She really made you say all that?
Yeah.
Wasn't me.
Sorry.
Hey!
Lucy thinks I'm handsome?
Is that right, Lu...
What is he doing here?
Hello, Jimmy.
Go to hell, Ed.
Oh, you've already put me there.
Here.
But not for long, my friend.
I'll find my way out.
Because this place
is just one big puzzle,
and puzzles are my forte.
Nobody beats me.
I did.
See you never, Ed.
That's what you think.
I have the feeling he's going to be
more than a simple nuisance.
Not the type to be bribed,
nor distracted easily.
Indeed.
Very interesting.
What has no hands
but might knock on your door,
and you better open up if it does?
Mr. Gordon's continued interference
threatens to slow us down
when we're about to reach
our finest moment.
He'll do more than that.
Mr. Nygma.
Eavesdropping is rude and unwise.
Eavesdropping implies intent,
and I mostly accidentally overheard.
Overheard what?
Jim Gordon, the word nuisance.
Sounds familiar.
Probably has something to do
with your releasing Penguin
and Gordon's ex-fiancee.
Probably.
I can help you...
take him down.
I know everything about Jim Gordon.
If you let me out of here,
we could probably just sit down
- in your office...
- Mr. Nygma, you can't help me.
I'm here to help you.
Those are the roles
that were defined for the two of us.
Now, there's another pressing matter.
No. Listen. I, I...
I can manipulate people.
I did it to Gordon once,
and I can do it again,
because peoples' brains
are just a mystery,
and once you figure it out...
Look. Helzinger?
Can't stand criticism
because of an overbearing mother.
Wants love and approval.
Gets mad when he doesn't get it,
so I give it.
Oh, thank you!
Sharon.
Kleptomaniacal due
to obsessive-compulsive disorder.
Just give her something
to concentrate on.
And...
And Norton, serious boundary issues.
Prone to torture,
violence and cannibalism.
Unless he thinks he's your friend!
Oh. For me?
My point is, everyone has a story,
and they just wanna be listened to.
My God! I should be the shrink!
- What did you say?
- I'm sorry. Was that too far?
Everybody has a story.
That's it. Mr. Nygma,
you've actually been very helpful.
I have it, Peabody.
I have the cure
for our prize patient.
Do tell.
What is an identity?
What is a sense of self?
It is a story
that we humans tell ourselves.
We have got to give him
a great, heroic story.
We need to give him
a good heroic dose of Thorazine,
but you're the boss.
Perfect.
Perfect!
Sir?
Sir? Stop!
He's dangerous!
Hello?
I need all available security
to the reanimation lab now!
No! Do not let them in!
Do not interfere!
My son. My son, please stop.
Why have you forsaken me?
Have you forgotten the code?
Who are you?
My poor, dear son.
Who do you think I am?
Your son?
You're my father?
Who else?
Don't you feel a father's love
when I look into your eyes?
Where am I?
What has happened to me?
What happened to me?
Why don't I know my name?
My son...
Calm your heart.
Demons took you to the land
of death and bewitched your soul,
but I brought you back to life.
You are the redeemed one.
What is my name?
You know your name.
No. No. There is another life.
There is a sister, a high tower.
No... no. Bewitchment.
False memories put into your head.
I am your father and your lord.
And he who has another birth,
brought forth
from the cold grasp of death
shall rise again and serve my Order.
I say this, and it becomes.
And I will give him the name of...
Azrael!
Yes!
I am Azrael!
My lord Dumas.
Command me.
This man ordered my parents' death?
You're sure?
I know he was part of the reason
they were killed.
Why is he not under arrest?
It's not so simple, hoss.
The evidence we have
is far too tenuous for a warrant.
It's ancient hearsay,
no fingerprints.
Only witness is dead.
Barnes wouldn't even say no.
He would just look at me
like I was nuts.
I'm sick of this.
We know where Strange is,
we know he's hurting people
right now,
and you two are talking
about politics with your boss
and then getting
a piece of paper signed.
- This is the way it works, Bruce.
- Why?
You're not a cop anymore.
Give us a sec?
Bruce, I know you're frustrated,
but we need to do this the right way.
The right way?
And how many times did that fail
with Galavan?
- It's not the same.
- He bent and broke the law
over and over again,
and Strange is doing the same thing.
This man killed Karen,
maybe my parents.
Look, I, I appreciate
everything that you've done for me.
But I fear we're going down
the same path as before,
- and we won't get justice unless...
- Unless what?
What you did to Galavan.
What you knew you had to do,
because of the bureaucracy
and the red tape.
What I had to do?
I chose to kill a man in cold blood,
and it was the wrong choice,
crossing that line.
You'll pay for it...
over and over again,
like I have been.
Like I still am.
And it will make you more
like the evil you're trying to fight.
You need to be better.
Do you understand me?
Just hold out a little bit longer.
We'll work on Barnes,
get him to sign off on a warrant
and put Strange away for good.
The right way.
Fearing the knights had become soft
and weak from lack of leadership,
Lord Dumas split from among them
and formed a new faction.
He named this new sect after himself,
calling it The Order of St. Dumas.
- Okay. Impressive.
- Yes.
His psyche couldn't reconcile
death and rebirth
until we gave it a grander context.
...the epic corner of the land...
A story.
He's Azrael now.
A fabled 12th-century knight
who died for the cause
of his feudal lord Adam Dumas.
This Dumas character
was made a saint,
performed a lot of miracles
and so forth.
And one of those miracles
was bringing Azrael back to life.
I still prefer Thorazine.
You need to learn to work
with what you have, Ms. Peabody.
- Okay.
- Our creations need new personas
to equal and embody
what they've become,
to give their minds focus.
Perhaps, this was Mr. Galavan's
destiny all along.
How do you even know
if the persona will hold?
There's only one way to find out.
We send our beautiful monster
out into the wild
with a simple task to perform.
He's going to need something to wear.
"Mr. Nygma, you have been,
you've actually been helpful.
Mr. Nygma,
you have actually been helpful."
Dismissal. The complete arrogance.
"Mr. Nygma. Mr. Nygma,
you have actually been helpful."
Inmate Helzinger.
Come with me.
Yes, ma'am.
Why do they keep disappearing
down that hallway?
Strange is hiding something.
Where are you taking me?
Where are we going?
How interesting.
Move!
Hey, I know you.
I have a gift for you, my son.
I'm crafting your armor as we speak.
But first,
your skills must be tested.
I got it.
You're the mayor.
What is this place?
What's going...?
That is a demon.
What's going on in here?
- He lives in fire.
- I wanna get out of here!
That case will give you everything
you need to destroy him!
Let me get out of here!
Let me out of here! Let me out!
I wanna get out of here! I wanna...
Not exactly what I had in mind,
but good enough.
Try opening the chest, my son.
The Sword of Sin.
Your ally and instrument of justice,
a vanquisher of evil for generations.
She thirsts for blood.
Generations?
That sword was made yesterday.
It doesn't matter.
Our replica is central to his
acceptance of his new identity.
An awe-inspiring signature weapon.
What must I do?
A murderer walks the streets
of this city a free man.
For his sins, by your blade,
he must be destroyed.
Tell me his name.
James Gordon.
My lord, I am the Angel of Death.
James Gordon dies...
tonight.
My officers responded
to an anonymous tip
and arrived here
earlier this evening.
Upon entering the construction site,
my men discovered the bodies
of four male victims.
It'll be some time
before we have any information
about their identities.
That's all I have for you
at this time.
Excuse me.
No, that's it.
Hey, Cap, look who I found.
Shut it, Bullock.
- You have one hell of a nerve.
- Listen...
You think I don't know it was you
that busted out Karen Jennings?
- Tell me it wasn't you.
- Captain...
I don't wanna hear it.
How do I keep falling for your games?
Really, it's a mystery to me.
Every time you come back,
I truly believe that you've changed.
You're like an optical illusion.
Listen, I just need
five minutes of your time.
Hargrove! Snead!
Escort Mr. Gordon off my crime scene
immediately.
You, we're gonna have
a little discussion
about this tomorrow morning.
Captain Barnes, please. Hear him out.
Listen, kid...
Mr. Wayne, I don't care how much
money or pull you have in this town.
I'm through talking to him.
Are you through
listening to the truth?
Oh, come on. Give me a break.
All right, five minutes.
No, three minutes.
Okay. Bobby pins?
Only one?
- It's all I could steal.
- It'll have to do.
- Rudy, did you get the ammonia?
- Here.
Perfect.
Okay, now we just need
the bug zapper.
- What is this?
- It's a fly swatter.
I can see that it's a fly swatter.
I didn't ask for a fly swatter.
I asked for the bug zapper
in the kitchen.
What's the difference?
The difference is that one
has a black light
that emits ultraviolet energy
and this is leather on a stick.
They both kill flies.
I don't need to kill flies.
I need you to go back to the kitchen
and get the bug zapper.
What are you gonna do
with all this stuff, anyway?
I think Professor Strange
is hiding something.
And I think that something
is a secret way out of this dump.
So I'm gonna use this stuff
to find it.
So, in a nutshell,
Hugo Strange is making monsters
out of dead people in his spare time,
and he had Karen Jennings
killed by Victor Fries,
who's been dead for three months.
I know it sounds far-fetched.
Far-fetched? No. It sounds insane!
But it's true. Trust me.
How can I trust you
when you're talking crazy?
How can I trust you when you've lied
to me so many times? Monsters?
I lied to you because it's hard
to tell you the truth.
You're stubborn and you're angry,
and the GCPD has paid a price for it!
Really? You self-righteous punk.
You think you have all the answers?
Maybe you should run it yourself!
Maybe I will one day.
In your dreams.
Who's there?
I said, who's out there?
What the hell?
James Gordon.
The time for your penance has come.
You know this guy?
Who are you?
I am Azrael,
righteous scourge of sinners,
and I have come to kill you,
James Gordon.
Put down that weapon!
Put the weapon down!
Put it down right now, or I'll shoot!
Captain!
Jim!
I need information now.
What do we know about this guy?
Just what you saw.
Calls himself Azrael.
Wants to kill me.
We know Hugo Strange is responsible.
Told you so, did he?
Who else could it be?
I have no idea.
I have to find out the facts.
Fun part about being
a police detective,
instead of a loose cannon vigilante.
Excuse me, Captain.
I find your flippant attitude
to be inappropriate.
I find you to be kind
of a pain in the ass.
- What's he even doing here?
- I'm a concerned citizen.
I wanna know what you're doing
about all of this.
You...
Well, I'm gonna assemble
the Strike Force,
call in all off-duty personnel.
We're gonna dragnet the living
daylights out of this wacko.
A knight from outer space
shouldn't be too hard to find, right?
Okay?
That's what we're gonna do.
What you're gonna do is go home
and stop inserting yourself
into police business.
- Captain...
- That's the final word.
He's right. It's time you went home.
Leave the rest of this to the police,
and to me.
This is not just police business.
This is my business, too.
I can't make the moves I need to make
if I'm worrying about you.
You need to be at home,
where Alfred can look after you.
Hello, Grace.
How are you today?
Incredibly, the attacker
fled the crime scene by,
for all intents and purposes,
scaling the side of the structure,
literally disappearing into thin air.
In all my years, Ken, I must say,
I've never seen anything
quite like it.
That a human being
should be capable of such feats.
It just astounds the mind.
Theo Galavan,
the new mayor of Gotham!
Oh, brother, like I don't know you
from way back.
Remember.
He calls himself Azrael.
He's armed, dangerous,
and has exhibited some extraordinary
physical abilities.
But no one, and I mean no one,
comes into our city
and tries to carve up my officers.
We're gonna go out tonight,
and we're gonna comb
each and every block
until we find this masked freak
and put him behind bars
where he belongs.
- Any questions?
- No, sir!
Good. Now get out there and get him.
- What are you doing?
- I'm going out there.
- The hell you are.
- Excuse me?
You're staying here
for your own protection.
That's an order.
I'm not a cop anymore, remember?
I don't need to follow your orders.
You're absolutely right.
You two,
put Mr. Gordon here in lockup.
- What?
- I'm holding you
on suspicion of breaking
Karen Jennings out of GCPD custody.
- Don't do this!
- I've already done it.
So many stories to choose from.
I feel like a child
on Christmas morning.
- You wanted to see me?
- Yes.
I want to install personas
into more subjects immediately.
Everything we've worked for
is finally within reach.
"But I don't want to go among
mad people," Alice remarked.
"Oh, you can't help that,"
said the cat, "We're all mad here."
Oh, yes.
Yes, that will do nicely.
No news from the search.
Let me out of here.
This is for your own good.
Trust me, you've broken enough laws
for one day.
There are times when breaking the law
is the right thing to do.
And who gets to decide that, you?
Yeah. Someone has to.
No, Jim, you're wrong.
Look where Gotham's going.
Maniacs, perverts, freaks,
crawling out of every hole.
It's like a sea of evil
flooding the city.
If a man doesn't cling on to the law,
he'll lose his bearings, drown.
What gives with the lights?
- Everything's down.
- Come on, check the back.
- Blackout?
- I don't think so.
Where's a flashlight
when you need one?
Yeah, me neither.
James Gordon.
Back up against the cell!
Move!
This is Captain Barnes of the GCPD!
Whoever you are, step into the light
or we will take you out!
But I am the light,
tasked with vanquishing
the evil in that cell.
You can die trying!
You lead these men,
so I will parley with you.
Parley?
Order them to stand aside
and allow the sinner, James Gordon,
to be punished.
Do this, and I will spare them all.
Decline,
and they will face my judgment.
Their lives now rest in your hands.
How many will die?
All? Or one?
Decide, Captain.
You can go to hell.
I've been there.
You go.
Over there!
Do you see him?
Where did he go?
I don't know. You got eyes on him?
Get him out of there!
Such an amazing tool of destruction.
Vile sorcery.
We need a bigger gun.
Yeah.
I'm gonna lure the freak
up the stairs,
then you show up with something
that'll tear a hole in this bastard.
- You got it.
- Let's get to the roof right now!
You...
you will show me to him.
You will tell me where he is.
And then what?
You'll spare my life?
It's too late for that.
The most I can offer you
is a painless death.
Let's dance.
That, that is not possible.
You?
You're dead.
Not anymore.
Finally.
Come to me...
and I will show you the way to hell.
I know the way.
For those just joining us,
we're coming to you live
from outside of the Gotham
City Police Department...
Oh, my God.
There been a major impact behind me.
The vehicle,
it appears a body has fallen...
- Theo Galavan.
- It's really him.
- It's him!
- Theo Galavan wearing...
- Oh, my God.
Galavan. He looks like he has...
Right. Once again, we are confirming
that the former mayor of Gotham City,
Theo Galavan, is alive
and dressed in a bizarre costume.
Boss.
Boss. Boss.
It's getting crazy in this town,
huh, Jim?
Don't talk. Just breathe.
I'm trying.
- You're gonna be okay.
- Sure, I am.
You're a pain in the ass,
you know that?
That makes two of us.
Boss, breathe! Come on, Captain.
Hold on. Stay with me.
Boss...
BP is falling fast. We gotta go now.
Radio Gotham General.
Let them know we're coming in hot!
Jim! Jim! What the hell happened?
- You okay?
- Yeah.
It was Galavan.
You sure?
I know it's hard to believe.
But Azrael is Galavan.
Barb.
That's a little irritating.
Sorry.
Hey.
Babes.
Relax.
Yeah.
No, I...
You guys have been so good to me.
That's okay. Don't worry.
Cocktails.
I make great cocktails.
Sure. That would be nice.
What do you want?
Bourbon on...
- Gimlets!
- Rocks.
- Actually, bourbon sounds...
- I'm making gimlets.
Okay, she scares me.
Don't be a baby. She's harmless.
Honey, I know you like her,
but that woman is mad
as a bag of squirrels.
She said she's cured.
That's what an insane person
would say.
Do we have any limes?
No.
- Oh, my God.
- That's right, Don.
The masked assassin that attacked
the GCPD earlier tonight
has been identified
as former mayor Theo Galavan.
- Now, there were reports earlier...
- Theo? It can't be.
Holy moly.
The assassin was forced off the roof,
then fell right over there,
then stood up in front of all of us.
And it was him, Theo Galavan, alive.
And from what we know,
he's responsible
for three officer fatalities.
We also learned that...
Hello, old friend.
...still at large and is considered
extremely dangerous.
Well, he must never have been dead.
I mean, that's the only possibility.
I mean, no one dies and comes back
to life again, do they?
No one.
But he did.
Strange.
Strange must be behind this.
What the hell
is happening to our city?
Nothing good.
No, no, I don't wanna go.
We're just going to see...
Oh, my.