Previously on Gotham...
Oh, crud.
He killed my mother, Jim.
He had her murdered in front of me.
I am going to kill you.
I think I found something.
The week of his murder, he was supposed to
meet a woman named Karen Jennings
about something called Pinewood Farms.
Pinewood Farms was a bioengineering
program at Wayne Enterprises.
It started up again, didn't it?
That's why my father came to see you
after all those years.
Karen Jennings is gonna be dead
the minute she hits Blackgate Prison.
That's why we're gonna break her out.
The man who contracted Matches Malone
to kill your parents
called himself The Philosopher.
And I'd be willing to bet that this
is the man who is behind Pinewood.
"Hugo Strange, The Philosopher."
He runs Arkham now.
We brought someone back.
Azrael!
We actually did it.
Rally to me.
St. Dumas will deliver us.
St. Dumas will protect us.
Heathens!
Idolaters!
Spawn of Satan. Prepare to die.
Don't, don't. No, don't. Please.
Sister, speak to me, please.
Please, speak to me.
Who are you? Huh? Who are you?
Has there been any improvement
since he woke up yesterday?
No.
But he is wonderful, isn't he?
- Who are you? Who are you?
- Strong as an ox, fast as a snake.
And mad as a hatter.
There's not much use bringing back
the dead if they come back crazy.
Oh, he's not crazy.
He just doesn't know who he is.
His psyche can't reconcile
being brought back from the dead.
It's fractured,
grasping at fragmented memories.
The texts that he has written on the walls
are all verses from this book.
"The Will and Order of St. Dumas"?
The Galavan family is proudly descended
from 12th century crusading knights.
This is their secret text.
Evidently, our patient has memorized
the whole book.
His brain is struggling to rebuild
a coherent self.
- But he's using the wrong parts.
- So, what's the cure?
Good question.
What is it?
Mr. Gordon.
Professor Strange.
Sorry to drop by unexpected.
Oh, not at all. Please, have a seat.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
I've been hired by a client
to look into something.
- I was hoping you could help me with it.
- Of course.
This is Karen Jennings.
She was murdered last night.
- Oh, how tragic.
- She was a test subject
in an old Wayne Enterprises program
called Pinewood Farms.
Before she passed, Karen mentioned
you were involved with the program.
- That was a long time ago.
- Try and remember...
If you can.
Pinewood Farms was started by Thomas Wayne
in an attempt to cure
humanity's greatest ailments
on the genetic level.
- Old age, disease, even death.
- But that's not what happened, is it?
Karen said the program tried to play God,
and you ended up creating monsters.
I was just a researcher,
with no knowledge of that
until it was too late.
A man of your skill and expertise,
a lowly researcher?
I find that hard to believe.
But it's true.
Mr. Wayne excelled at compartmentalizing
every aspect of his life.
Within Pinewood, the left hand often
didn't know what the right was doing.
He lied to us all.
Not many people
would see you as the victim here.
I was one of the ones who forced
Thomas Wayne to shut down the program.
But by then, so many people had been hurt.
- I have a theory.
- Hmm?
I believe you ran Pinewood Farms.
I believe you've restarted the program.
- And I would like to know--
- Why are you really here, Mr. Gordon?
Excuse me?
This whole city
has turned its back on you,
despite you risking your life to save it
over and over again.
I'm not here
for a therapy session, Professor.
No, it's more like an interrogation
by a man who is no longer
a police officer,
who no longer has the right
to demand answers.
The only reason you're sitting
in that chair is because I allow it.
So let me ask you, why are you here?
Like I said, I have a client.
Bruce Wayne, I suppose.
So it's a job.
You're here to pay the rent? Surely not.
All that's happened to you,
this last year...
Hero cop found guilty of murder,
sentenced unjustly to Blackgate,
and now you returned to what?
You've lost everything.
You're trying to make up
for the sins of your past
and you believe
that this case will somehow
bring about your own personal redemption.
- No.
- You're not doing this for your client.
- You're doing this for yourself.
- You're wrong.
You just exhibited several tells.
Facial tics, expressions,
and eye movements
that people involuntarily
betray themselves with when they lie.
- Let's talk about Victor Fries.
- Victor Fries is dead, Mr. Gordon.
Really?
I saw him last night.
That's impossible.
This is a court order signed
by District Attorney Dent
to exhume Fries' body.
Where's it buried?
He was cremated.
Thank you.
For what?
I can read tells, too.
You're lying. I needed to be sure
you were behind all this.
And now I am.
Don't lie! I heard you!
- Please... Don't.
- Please do.
Squeeze the life from him. Kill him.
- Kill him now.
- Are you two fighting again?
- He called me fat.
- I didn't do anything, it wasn't me.
It was Lucy.
The fifth personality again.
Such a nasty attitude.
See, this gets complicated.
See, Lucy is in his head 'cause Rudy has
what's called multiple personality--
In his head?
- Then I'll pull her out.
- No, no, no.
- She's a ghost.
- A ghost?
Yes.
And she makes Rudy say things
that he doesn't wanna say.
I can see her.
Lucy,
you've got some nerves,
making old Rudy say things like that.
You know that Helzinger is not fat.
In fact, you said
that Helzinger was handsome.
Don't you shove me.
Oh! She slapped me.
Now I'll tell you something, Lucy.
You will leave Rudy alone
and if you come back here again,
you'll have to deal with me.
Thank you, Lucy.
She really made you say all that?
Yeah.
Wasn't me.
- Sorry.
- Hey!
- Lucy thinks I'm handsome?
- Mmm-hmm.
Isn't that right...
What is he doing here?
Hello, Jimmy.
- Go to hell, Ed.
- You've already put me there. Here.
But not for long, my friend.
I'll find my way out.
'Cause this place is just one big puzzle,
and puzzles are my forte.
Nobody beats me.
I did. See you never, Ed.
That's what you think.
I have
a feeling he is going to be
more than a simple nuisance.
Not the type to be bribed,
nor distracted easily.
- Indeed. If only we...
- Very interesting.
What has no hands,
but might knock on your door
and you better open up if it does?
Mr. Gordon's continued interference
threatens to slow us down
when we're about to reach
our finest moment.
He'll do more than that.
Mr. Nygma.
Eavesdropping is rude and unwise.
Eavesdropping implies intent,
and I mostly...
- Accidentally overheard.
- Overheard what?
Jim Gordon, the word nuisance.
Sounds familiar.
Probably has something to do with your
releasing Penguin and Gordon's ex-fiancée.
Probably.
I can help you take him down.
I know everything about Jim Gordon.
If you let me out of here we could
probably just sit down in your office--
Mr. Nygma, you can't help me.
I'm here to help you.
Those are the roles that were defined
for the two of us.
- Now, there's another pressing matter.
- No, listen, I...
I can manipulate people.
I did it to Gordon once,
and I can do it again.
See, people's brains are just a mystery.
And once you figure it out...
Look, Helzinger.
Can't stand criticism
because of an overbearing mother.
Wants love and approval.
Gets mad when he doesn't get it.
So I give it.
Oh, thank you.
Sharon. Kleptomaniacal due to
obsessive compulsive disorder.
Just give her something to concentrate on.
And--
And Norton, serious boundary issues.
Prone to torture, violence
and cannibalism.
Unless he thinks he's your friend.
- For me?
- Mmm-hmm.
My point is, everyone has a story.
And they just wanna be listened to.
My God. I should be the shrink.
What did you say?
I'm sorry. Was that too far?
Everybody has a story.
That's it. Mr. Nygma,
you've actually been very helpful.
I have it, Peabody.
I have the cure for our prized patient.
- Do tell.
- What is an identity?
What is a sense of self?
It is a story
that we humans tell ourselves.
We have got to give him
a great heroic story.
We need to give him
a good heroic dose of Thorazine.
But you're the boss.
Perfect. Perfect.
Sir? Sir.
Stop! He's dangerous.
Hello?
I need all available security
to the reanimation lab now.
No! Do not let them in. Do not interfere.
My son.
My son, please stop.
Why have you forsaken me?
Have you forgotten the code?
Who are you?
My poor, dear, son.
Who do you think I am?
Your son?
You're my father?
Who else?
Don't you feel a father's love
when I look into your eyes?
Where am I?
What is happening to me?
What happened to me?
Shh. Shh.
Why don't I know my name?
My son.
Calm your heart.
Demons took you to the Land of Death
and bewitched your soul.
But I brought you back to life.
You are the redeemed one.
What is my name?
You know your name.
No, no. There is another life.
There is a sister, a high tower--
No, no, no. Bewitchment.
False memories put into your head.
I am your father and your lord.
"And he who has another birth,
brought forth from the cold grasp of death
"shall rise again and serve my order.
"I say this and it becomes.
"And I will give him the name of..."
- Azrael.
- Yes.
I am Azrael.
My Lord Dumas...
Command me.
This man ordered my parents' death.
You're sure?
I know he was part of the reason
they were killed.
Why is he not under arrest?
It's not so simple, hoss.
The evidence we have is far too tenuous
for a warrant.
It's ancient hearsay, not fingerprints.
Only witness is dead.
Barnes wouldn't even say no.
He would just look at me like I was nuts.
I'm sick of this.
We know where Strange is.
We know he's hurting people right now,
and you two are talking about politics
with your boss and
getting a piece of paper signed.
- This is the way it works, Bruce.
- Why?
You're not a cop anymore.
Give us a second?
Bruce, I know you're frustrated.
But we need to do this the right way.
The right way? And how many times
did that fail with Galavan?
- It's not the same.
- He bent and broke the law
over and over again,
and Strange is doing the same thing.
This man killed Karen, maybe my parents.
Look, I appreciate everything
that you've done for me.
But I fear we're going down
the same path as before,
- and we won't get justice unless--
- Unless what?
What you did to Galavan.
What you knew you had to do, because
of the bureaucracy and the red tape--
What I had to do?
I chose to kill a man in cold blood.
And it was the wrong choice,
crossing that line.
You'll pay for it.
Over and over again, like I have been.
Like I still am.
And it will make you
more like the evil you're trying to fight.
You need to be better.
Do you understand me?
Just hold out a little bit longer.
We'll work on Barnes.
Get him to sign off on a warrant.
And put Strange away for good.
The right way.
Fearing
the knights had become soft and weak
from lack of leadership,
Lord Dumas split and divided them,
and formed a new faction.
He named this new sect after himself,
calling it the Order of St. Dumas.
Okay. Impressive.
Yes.
His psyche
couldn't reconcile death and rebirth
until we gave it a grander context.
- A story.
- He's Azrael now.
A fabled 12th century knight who died for
the cause of his feudal lord, Adam Dumas.
This Dumas character was made a saint,
performed a lot of miracles and so forth
and one of those miracles
was bringing Azrael back to life.
I still prefer Thorazine.
You need to learn to work
with what you have, Ms. Peabody.
Okay.
Our creations need new personas to equal
and embody what they have become,
to give their minds focus.
Perhaps this was Mr. Galavan's destiny
all along.
How do you even know
if the persona will hold?
There's only one way to find out.
We send our beautiful monster out in
the wild with a simple task to perform.
He's going to need something to wear.
"Mr. Nygma,
you have actually been helpful.
you have actually been helpful."
This imbecile. The complete arrogance.
Inmate Helzinger. Come with me.
Yes, ma'am.
Why do they keep disappearing
down that hallway?
Strange is hiding something.
Where are you taking me?
Where are we going?
How interesting.
Move.
Hey, I know you.
I have a gift for you, my son.
I'm crafting your armor as we speak.
But first, your skills must be tested.
I got it.
You're the mayor.
What is this place? What is going on?
- That is a demon.
- What is going on in here?
- He lives in fire.
- I wanna get out of here.
That case will give you
everything you need to destroy him.
I wanna get out of here!
Let me out of here. Let me out.
I wanna get out of here. I wanna--
Not exactly what I had in mind,
but good enough.
Try opening the chest, my son.
The Sword of Sin.
Your ally and instrument of justice.
A vanquisher of evil for generations.
She thirsts for blood.
Generations? That sword
was made yesterday.
It doesn't matter.
Our replica is central to his acceptance
of his new identity.
An awe-inspiring signature weapon.
What must I do?
A murderer walks the streets of the city
a free man.
For his sin, by your blade,
he must be destroyed.
- Tell me his name.
- James Gordon.
My Lord, I am the Angel of Death.
James Gordon dies...
Tonight.
My officers responded
to an anonymous tip
and arrived here earlier this evening.
Upon entering the construction site,
my men discovered the bodies
of four male victims.
It will be some time before we have
any information about their identities.
Uh. Uh...
That's all I have for you at this time.
Excuse me.
No, that's it.
- Hey, Cap. Look who I found.
- Shut it, Bullock.
- You have one hell of a nerve.
- Listen.
You think I don't know it was you
that busted out Karen Jennings?
- Tell me it wasn't you.
- Captain--
No. I don't wanna hear it.
How do I keep falling for your games?
Really, it's a mystery to me.
Every time you come back,
I truly believe that you've changed.
You're like an optical illusion.
Listen, I just need
five minutes of your time.
Hargrove, Snead, escort Mr. Gordon
off my crime scene immediately.
You. We're gonna have a little discussion
about this tomorrow morning.
Captain Barnes, please. Hear him out.
Listen, kid...
Mr. Wayne.
I don't care how much money
or pull you have in this town.
- I'm through talking to him.
- Are you through listening to the truth?
Oh, come on. Give me a break.
All right, five minutes.
No, three minutes.
Okay, bobby pins?
- Only one?
- It's all I could steal.
It'll have to do.
Rudy, did you get the ammonia?
Here.
- Perfect.
- Okay. Now we just need the bug zapper.
- What is this?
- It's a fly swatter.
I can see that it's a fly swatter.
I didn't ask for a fly swatter.
I asked for the bug zapper in the kitchen.
What's the difference?
The difference is that
one has a black light
that emits ultraviolet energy,
and this is leather on a stick.
They both kill flies.
I don't need to kill flies.
I need you to go back to the kitchen
and get the bug zapper.
What are you gonna do
with all this stuff anyway?
I think Professor Strange
is hiding something.
And I think that something
is a secret way out of this dump.
So I'm gonna use this stuff to find it.
So, in a nutshell,
Hugo Strange is making monsters
out of dead people in his spare time.
And he had Karen Jennings
killed by Victor Fries,
- who's been dead for three months.
- I know it sounds far-fetched.
Far-fetched? No. It sounds insane.
But it's true. Trust me.
How can I trust you
when you're talking crazy?
How can I trust you when you've lied to me
so many times? Monsters?
I lied to you because it's hard
to tell you the truth.
You're stubborn and you're angry and
the GCPD has paid a price for it.
Really? You self-righteous punk.
You think you have all the answers?
Maybe you should run it yourself.
- Maybe I will one day.
- In your dreams.
Who's there?
- I said who's out there?
- What the hell?
James Gordon.
The time for your penance has come.
You know this guy?
Who are you?
I am Azrael,
righteous scourge of sins,
and I have come to kill you, James Gordon.
Put down that weapon.
Put the weapon down.
Put it down right now or I'll shoot.
Captain!
Jim!
I need information now.
What do we know about this guy?
Just what you saw. Calls himself Azrael.
Wants to kill me.
We know Hugo Strange is responsible.
- Told you so, did he?
- Who else could it be?
I have no idea.
I have to find out the facts.
Fun part of being a police detective.
- Instead of a loose cannon vigilante--
- Excuse me, Captain.
I find your flippant attitude
to be inappropriate.
I find you to be
kind of a pain in the ass.
- What's he even doing here?
- I'm a concerned citizen.
I wanna know
what you're doing about all of this.
You...
Oh, uh...
I'm gonna assemble a strike force.
Call in all off-duty personnel.
We're gonna dragnet the living daylights
out of this whacko.
A knight from outer space
shouldn't be hard to find, right?
Okay?
That's what we're gonna do.
What you're gonna do is go home and stop
inserting yourself into police business.
- Captain--
- That's the final word.
He's right.
It's time you went home.
Leave the rest of this to the police...
- And to me.
- This is not just police business.
This is my business, too.
I can't make the moves I need to make
if I'm worrying about you.
You need to be at home,
where Alfred can look after you.
Hello, Grace. How are you today?
Incredibly, the attacker
fled the crime scene by,
for all intents and purposes,
scaling the side of the structure,
literally disappearing into thin air.
In all my years, Ken, I must say,
I've never seen anything quite like it.
That a human being
should be capable of such feats.
It just astounds the mind.
Theo Galavan,
the new Mayor of Gotham.
Oh, brother, like I don't
know you from way back.
Remember.
He calls himself Azrael.
He's armed, dangerous, and has exhibited
some extraordinary physical abilities.
But no one, and I mean no one,
comes into our city
and tries to carve up my officers.
We're gonna go out tonight
and we're gonna comb each and every block
until we find this masked freak
and put him behind bars where he belongs.
- Any questions?
- No, sir.
Good. Now get out there and get him.
What are you doing?
- I'm going out there.
- The hell you are.
Excuse me?
You're staying here
for your own protection.
That's an order.
I'm not a cop anymore, remember?
I don't need to follow your orders.
You're absolutely right.
You two. Put Mr. Gordon, here, in lockup.
- What?
- I'm holding you on suspicion
of breaking Karen Jennings
out of GCPD custody.
- Don't do this.
- I've already done it.
So many stories to choose from.
I feel like a child on Christmas morning.
- You wanted to see me?
- Yes.
I want to install personas
into more subjects immediately.
Everything we've worked for
is finally within reach.
'"But I don't want to go among
mad people,' Alice remarked.
'"Oh, you can't help that,' said the cat.
""We're all mad here.""
Oh, yes. Yes. That will do nicely.
No news from the search.
- Let me out of here.
- This is for your own good.
Trust me.
You've broken enough laws for one day.
There are times when breaking the law
is the right thing to do.
- And who gets to decide that. You?
- Yeah. Someone has to.
No, Jim. You're wrong.
Look where Gotham's going.
Maniacs, perverts and freaks
crawling out of every hole.
It's like a sea of evil flooding the city.
If a man doesn't cling onto the law,
he'll lose his bearings. Drowned.
- Blackout?
- I don't think so.
Yeah, me neither.
James Gordon.
Back up against the cell. Move.
This is Captain Barnes of the GCPD.
Whoever you are, step into the light,
or we will take you out.
But I am the light.
Tasked with vanquishing the evil
in that cell.
You can die trying.
You lead these men,
so I will parlay with you.
- Parlay?
- Order them to stand aside,
and allow the sinner, James Gordon,
to be punished.
Do this and I will spare them all.
Decline, and they will face my judgment.
Their lives now rest in your hands.
How many will die?
All? Or one?
Decide, Captain.
- You can go to hell.
- I've been there.
You go.
Over there. You see him?
Where'd he go?
I don't know.
You got eyes on him?
Get him out of there!
Such an amazing tool of destruction.
Vile sorcery.
We need a bigger gun.
Yeah.
I'm gonna lure the freak up the stairs.
And you show up with something
that will tear a hole in this bastard.
- You got it.
- Let's get to the roof right now.
You.
You will show me to him.
You will tell me where he is.
And then what?
You'll spare my life?
It's too late for that.
The most I can offer you
is a painless death.
Let's dance.
That is not possible.
You?
You're dead.
Not anymore.
Finally.
Come to me.
And I will show you the way to hell.
I know the way.
For those just joining us,
we're coming to you live
from outside of the
Gotham City Police Department.
There's been a major impact
on the vehicle.
It appears a body has fallen...
- It's Theo Galavan...
- Theo Galavan...
- Theo Galavan wearing a...
- Oh, my God.
- Looks like he has...
- Right...
Once again, we are confirming that
the former Mayor of Gotham city,
Theo Galavan, is alive and
dressed in a bizarre costume.
Boss?
Boss? Boss?
It's getting crazy in this town, huh, Jim?
Don't talk, just breathe.
- I've tried.
- You're gonna be okay.
Sure, I am.
You're a pain in the ass, you know that?
That makes two of us.
Boss, breathe. Come on, Captain.
Hold on, stay with me. Boss.
BP's falling fast. We got to go now.
Radio Gotham General.
Let them know we're coming in hot.
Jim? Jim, what the hell happened?
You okay?
Yeah.
It was Galavan.
- You sure?
- I know it's hard to believe.
But Azrael is Galavan.
Barb.
It's a little irritating.
Oh.
Sorry.
Hey.
Babes.
Relax.
Yeah.
No, I...
You guys have been so good to me.
That's okay. Don't worry.
Cocktails.
I make great cocktails.
- Sure. That'd be nice.
- What do you want?
- Uh, bourbon--
- Gimlets.
- Actually, bourbon sounds--
- I'm making gimlets.
Okay. She scares me.
Don't be a baby. She's harmless.
Honey, I know you like her,
but that woman's mad
as a bag of squirrels.
- She said she's cured.
- That's what an insane person would say.
Do we have any limes?
No.
Oh, my God.
That's right, Don.
The masked assassin that attacked the GCPD
earlier tonight has been identified
as former Mayor, Theo Galavan.
Theo? It can't be.
Holy moly.
The assassin was forced
off the roof,
then fell right over there,
then stood up in front of all of us.
And it was him, Theo Galavan, alive.
And from what we know, responsible for
three officers fatalities.
Hello, old friend.
...is still at large
and is considered extremely dangerous.
Well...
He must have never have been dead.
I mean, that's the only possibility.
I mean, no one dies and
comes back to life again, do they?
No one.
But he did.
Strange.
Strange must be behind this.
What the hell is happening to our city?
Nothing good.
- Oh, no. I don't wanna go.
- You're just going to...
Ah!
Oh, my.
English - SDH