- Previously on Gotham...
- Where's Jeremiah?
(gasping)
BRUCE: Selina,
she's not herself, Alfred.
She's desperate for revenge.
You can't save her from herself.
NYGMA: This time,
woke up on a rooftop.
No idea how I got there
or what happened
during the preceding hours.
GORDON: In Haven,
as long as we survive,
hope survives in Gotham.
You've been promising me
help for weeks.
WALKER: I'm working
on getting you help.
GORDON:
I promise I won't stop
until I find those responsible.
I've got a lead
on a guy selling RPGs.
Oh, oh, please don't hurt me.
I just want to know
what you saw.
You had some kind of a rocket.
And you shot it
at that building.
(film projector clicking)
Raise your hands, Mr. Gordon.
I'm sorry, Steve,
they made me do it.
All right, be quiet, you.
Miss Zant, we're sorry
to interrupt your breakfast,
but you'll come with us,
quickly.
You may lower your hands now,
Mr. Gordon.
Turn around.
There a problem, Officer?
We know you sold the RPG
that took out Haven.
So?
So I want to know
who bought it.
Or what? You gonna arrest me?
Who said anything
about arresting you?
I want a name.
What do you say, boys?
(guns cocking)
Should we show this lawman how
we feel about uninvited guests?
Now, who told you
I sold that RPG?
(grunting)
(gunshot)
Eduardo?
Nice shot, right?
SOLDIER:
Lower your weapon now.
EDUARDO:
Delta Force,
stand down.
What are you doing here?
Come on.
The last time I saw you,
you were running
through sniper fire,
plucking my sorry ass
from a burning truck.
Least I could do
was pay you back.
I had that guy
right where I wanted him.
I'm glad you're here.
Yeah, me, too.
♪♪
We hated each other in boot.
Jim disapproved
of my ops tempo.
(chuckles): Yeah, 'cause you
only had one speed: too fast.
Took me a while to
realize he wasn't afraid
to get his hands dirty.
Just being careful.
- Yeah.
- Well, Jim's taught me a thing or two
- about being careful.
- (laughs softly)
So what's the mission plan?
Well, we are the help
Secretary Walker promised.
Our goal is to make this
hellhole safe again.
So it took the murder of
hundreds of innocent civilians
to get the government to act?
We're here to eliminate
all criminal threats.
We're gonna blanket the city
with flash sweeps.
Well, what about the people
that are still trapped here?
- They need relief now.
- Hey, I'm with you,
but my mandate's clear:
first we restore order,
then we take the next steps.
ANGEL:
Sir.
We got something, sir.
Captain Gordon,
this is my second,
Sergeant Angel Vallelunga.
Captain.
Ledger.
Our arms dealer kept track
of his buyers.
"Edward Nygma.
Two RPG."
Nygma.
Yeah, that name's on my list.
Think he's our bomber?
Only one way to find out.
All right,
you and I will get Nygma.
Harvey, I need you to set up
a command center
with the soldiers at GCPD.
- I'll grab some guys.
- Yeah.
Hey, look, hey, Jim.
I'm not as fast
as I used to be,
but I still got
some fight in me.
I'm not a desk jockey.
I'm a street guy.
What you are is the best cop
that I know.
We're going after Nygma.
He's ten steps ahead.
This thing goes sideways,
you're gonna have to take over.
I need your help, buddy.
I got it.
(door closes)
Alfred.
Oh, there you are, Master Bruce.
There's been a break
in the Haven bombing.
Seems that Gordon and Bullock
have got a rather
strong lead, apparently.
What's the matter with you?
I can't find Selina.
I've looked all over
the Green Zone.
Somehow, I think Miss Kyle
is perfectly capable
of looking after herself,
Master Bruce.
Except that she's not herself.
You saw what she
did to Jeremiah.
Yes. I did.
Listen, come here.
Jeremiah Valeska
deserved to die.
Jeremiah made Selina a murderer.
Just like Ra's made me
a murderer.
Ra's goaded you
into stabbing him, Master Bruce.
He used you as an instrument.
You're no murderer.
But Selina is.
You're not the same.
She did what she did
with open eyes,
and you got to learn
to respect that, son.
You're wrong about her, Alfred.
And I'm gonna
go find her.
(exhales)
(sirens wailing,
birds squawking)
NYGMA:
It's Monday, 5:32 p.m.
(over recorder): I'm standing
in a dumpster. My head hurts.
(fast-forwards)
It's happened again.
It's... Saturday, 12:16 a.m.
My fingernails are full of dirt.
Have I been digging?
(fast-forwards)
I think it's Sunday.
I can't find my watch.
And it's dark outside,
my feet are wet.
There's mud everywhere.
God!
It doesn't make sense!
You're not a murderer, Ed.
Except Kristen Kringle.
And Officer Dougherty.
But all those people...
and children.
How could you do it?
Why?!
(panting)
It doesn't matter why.
What matters
is that it was you
who killed them.
Not me.
(exhales)
(door thuds)
Edward Nygma, you're under
arrest for the attack at Haven
and the murder of hundreds
of innocent people.
No.
No, Jim, I can explain.
Explain?
You son of a bitch.
You actually did it?
- On your knees, now.
- No! I didn't.
I can prove
it, I just,
I need... I need
a little bit of time.
Say the word, Jim.
You know me, Jim.
The people
that I...
have hurt, they hurt me first.
I didn't know
a single person in Haven.
I'm innocent.
It's your call, buddy.
He basically confessed.
We bring him in.
He stands trial.
Yeah, I don't think so.
(steady beeping)
Your friend is standing
on a pressure-plated IED
One of several
throughout the rooms.
Twitch, and you'll repaint
the room with your organs.
Don't do it, Jim.
This little doohickey
monitors my heartbeat.
It increases by ten? Boom.
Decreases by ten?
Boom.
GORDON: You try to walk
out of here,
and a special forces sniper
will put a bullet in your head.
No, they won't.
This thing can detonate his bomb
from a mile away.
Or am I bluffing?
Once word gets out that
you're responsible for Haven,
you'll have a target
on your back.
I'll take my chances.
(whispers):
I think he's bluffing.
No, no.
He doesn't bluff.
I don't want anyone here
- if this thing detonates.
- You heard the man.
Tell Sergeant Vallelunga
to stand down.
- Yes, sir.
- Nygma walks.
A wristband that monitors
his heart rate.
Welcome to Gotham.
So what we do?
Well, the way I see it,
now we're all tied up.
I just got to save your life
one more time,
then I'm back in the lead.
Funny. Seriously,
the hell are we gonna do?
Well, he pulled a book
to set the booby trap.
I think I can make it.
Assuming the vibrations don't
trigger the IED, what then?
Then we just got to figure out
what sort of puzzle
he wants us to solve.
Puzzle?
There's always a puzzle
with Nygma. You ready?
(beeping continues)
(mouths)
(exhales)
(panting)
Chess Strategy: Knight Moves
Nimbly in the Dark.
I'm gonna wring
this nerd's neck.
In chess,
knights move in an "L."
Two spaces straight,
then one at a 90-degree angle.
Butterfly Collecting
with Conviction.
Or...
Chess Strategy:
Knight's Gambit:
Escaping Checkmate.
(beeps)
You okay?
You left the Army for this city?
It grows on you.
Harvey, come in.
BULLOCK (over radio):
Jim, you nab Nygma?
No. Put the word out:
Nygma's wanted for murder
and the attack on Haven.
(gunshots)
BRUCE:
I'm looking for Selina.
BARBARA:
Follow me.
Everybody,
raise your glasses to the killer
of Jeremiah Valeska.
(cheering)
(rock music playing)
CROWD (chanting):
The freak is dead!
MAN (over radio):
Citizens of Gotham,
this is a special bulletin
from the police department.
We have identified
the person who fired
a rocket-propelled grenade
that decimated Haven.
Be on the lookout
for a tall, skinny man
who goes by the name
of Ed Nygma.
He was last seen wearing
a green suit and eyeglasses.
Ed Nygma.
The monster of Haven.
- Let's go get him!
- ALL: Yeah!
- Let's kill him!
- (cheering)
Kill him!
ALL (chanting):
Kill him! Kill him!
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
Excellent.
200 bullets, as promised.
Go have fun.
And there's more
where that came from
if you keep up the good work.
Off you go.
Mr. Cobblepot, sir.
- It's...
- What? What?
"Edward Nygma
is the monster res...
responsible for killing
the innocents at Haven."
(strained):
Ed, what have you done?
I saw him go that way!
He's over there!
Get him! Come on!
(overlapping shouting)
ANGEL (over radio):
Bang Zero-One.
This is Bird Zero-Two.
What's your status, Angel?
ANGEL:
We cleared 13th to 36th Street,
west of Broadway.
Gonna keep pushing uptown.
That's progress.
Still no Nygma.
My boys will scoop him up
by nightfall.
Now tell me about this...
Scarecrow.
Well, he has
chemical weapons.
Your guys will need gas masks.
But taking him down
would be a big win.
Well, that's why
we're here.
Psst. Hey.
(singsongy):
Time to wake up.
(gasping)
Who are you?
I'm the woman who's gonna
carry out your execution.
(both whooping)
(whooping)
(laughter)
(grunting, gasping)
That's just a taste.
It's only fair you die
slow and painful
to pay for JoJo.
Who's JoJo?
JoJo was in Haven
when you blew it up.
(laughing)
This is a joke, right?
300 people died in Haven.
(scoffs)
We don't care about people.
- MAN: Yeah!
- (laughter)
Look at how happy JoJo was.
(crying): He always had
a smile on his face.
You anthropomorphizing
nincompoop.
Dogs can't smile.
- (screaming)
- (whooping)
(shouts)
I'm going to fix you, Ed.
What the hell?
Floor it!
- (whooping)
- Yeah!
(whooping)
Yeah!
I'm going to fix you, Ed.
Did I say stop?
I'm sorry, Ma.
Ma, can't we just
beat him to death?
(engine stalling)
It's not starting.
Yes. Anything but electrocution.
Please don't let
me die this way.
Oh, thank God
the fuel line's clogged.
Unclog the line.
- (laughs)
- We got it, we got it. Come on.
- (laughing)
- Please.
Shoot me, stab me,
anything but another jolt.
Hit it.
Oh, no!
(gasping)
(screaming)
GRETEL:
Put it out!
Boys!
Oh, my Lord!
Help him! Help him!
(yelping)
Who's gonna fix who, Oswald?
HENCHMAN: The Army's invading
the city, locking everyone up.
They're coming this way.
Please. An invasion
is tanks, infantry.
These are scouts.
What about Nygma?
HENCHMAN: Nobody's seen him,
but we got feelers out.
Well, you tell
your "feelers"
that the first man
to bring me Nygma
is the one who
gets to live.
Now!
(sighs)
(laughs)
I am surrounded
by morons, Edward.
If I didn't have
an empire to run,
I would go get Nygma myself.
(chuckles)
(gasps)
Hello, Oswald. We have
a great deal to talk about.
But first,
did you name your dog after me?
BULLOCK:
Jim, Harper just radioed.
She saw Nygma going
into City Hall.
He's going to Penguin.
EDUARDO: Cobblepot's
at the top of my list
from Walker.
Sounds like a twofer.
GORDON:
Penguin's sitting on all
the ammo in Gotham.
He's better defended,
better manned than anyone else.
We need shock and awe.
Shock and awe is my default.
You ready?
You know what,
take Harvey on this one.
I'll keep things
locked down here.
Let's saddle up.
(rock music playing)
Man, you're killing
my buzz.
Selina.
I know you, and
this isn't you.
- You know me?
- Yes.
Maybe better
than you know yourself.
Let me tell you something.
That night
that your parents were murdered,
I was in that alley
on the fire escape.
And I watched
that guy
shoot your father
and shoot your mother.
And through it all,
I did... nothing.
(laughs)
I didn't call for help,
I didn't...
(crying): I didn't scream
for the guy to stop.
It wasn't your fault.
You were just a scared kid.
No.
You were the scared kid.
We are not the same, Bruce.
I didn't do anything because
I wasn't willing to risk my neck
for someone else
because I didn't care.
That's who I was
and that's who I am.
("Psycho" by Grim Streaker
playing)
I love this song.
♪ When I want to go,
I know what you'll say... ♪
What did you do to me, Oswald?
What are you talking about?
Oh, please.
You did something to me.
You...
You are the reason
that I killed those people.
How could you?
You have made me
into some murderous puppet.
For weeks, I've been waking up
in strange places,
not knowing how I got there
or what I did.
Driving myself mad,
thinking I had gone mad.
And now I know
that it was all your doing.
Of everything
that you have put me through,
this...
this is the most cruel.
Ed.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I did not make
you do anything.
Then what is "I'll fix you"?
What did that mean?
You didn't fix me.
You broke me!
W-W-Wait. No.
I said that to you the night
the bridges blew. I-I...
Think I wouldn't remember?
No, Ed, I saved your life!
That's it!
What are you talking about?
You had been stabbed, I paid
Hugo Strange to save your life.
I bet he did something to you
when he was
patching you up.
You paid Hugo Strange
to save me?
Why?
What was I supposed to do?
Let you die?
After Butch,
you were my only friend.
You shot Butch!
Which is why I needed you!
(shouts)
(exhales)
Edward Nygma,
if I wanted
you to suffer,
I would never do it
in some backhanded way.
If you and I
are ever at
odds again,
you will know, without a doubt,
that I am your enemy.
I promise you that...
(crying):
...as a friend.
(grunts)
(panting)
What a mess.
I might have killed you, Oswald.
And if that day comes...
I swear to you...
...I will stare you in the eye
as I stab you in the heart.
(laughs softly)
(sniffles)
Look on the bright side.
If Hugo Strange did
do something to you,
it means you are not
responsible for Haven.
Where is he?
(rumbling)
Sir, GCPD and the Army
have blown the gates.
Stay here. You'll be safe.
(quietly): Grab Nygma.
They want him, not me.
He's gone.
Idiot! Ugh!
(high-pitched whirring)
(guns cocking)
(laughs)
Why, hello, Harvey.
Now, last time
we were in a standoff,
you ran out of bullets.
(laughs)
I hope you're better prepared.
We don't want to take
your territory, Oswald.
But you have to put down
your weapons
and hand over Ed Nygma.
Or, if you and your friends
aren't out
by the time I
count to three,
I will mow you all down!
We good?
Yep.
Go ahead. Count.
(laughs)
Harvey, you're not
thinking clearly.
Maybe call your boss,
see what he thinks.
I don't have
to call anyone.
Go ahead. Count.
One...
(panting)
How's that for better prepared?
Where's Ed Nygma?
The whole of Gotham
is looking for you.
I need information,
your specialty.
I am going to cut
your face
into a jigsaw puzzle
and watch you try
and put it back together again.
Barbara... Barbara! Am I dumb?
In all the years of plotting
and the betrayals between us,
have you ever... ever...
known me to do something
as idiotically brutal
as shoot a rocket
into a building full
of innocent people?
I did not kill
those people in Haven.
Not exactly.
There's more going on here.
I'm waiting.
The night the
bridges fell,
I was hurt. Oswald took me
to Hugo Strange.
And he did something
to my brain.
And that's your excuse for
murdering hundreds of people?
I'm saying that
Strange, or somebody,
can control me.
They killed those people.
Okay, let's say,
by some miracle, I believe you.
Why the hell should I help you?
Because who's working
with Strange?
Who would force me
to kill all of those people?
Information is
your lifeblood.
You help me, and I will give you
the best intel you've ever had.
I don't know where Strange is.
But I can tell you
where you'll find his Igors.
(punch lands)
(grunts)
Where is Edward Nygma?
You're protecting
a mass murderer.
Don't look to me for sympathy.
Fine.
But not with
that meathead around.
(laughs)
You know, they say you can judge
a man by his friends.
This from a man
who has no friends.
Talk.
Nygma's a patsy.
He is not a
mass murderer.
Puzzles, games,
perhaps the odd killing here and
there, but hundreds of people?
No. That's not him.
You know this.
So who set him up?
(laughs)
Jim, you want information,
I want to go home.
Eduardo's not gonna go for that.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought you were in charge.
Even if I were
to let you go,
sooner or later,
the Army's gonna come for you.
Things are changing in Gotham.
I'll take my chances.
Now,
do you want Nygma or not?
I know where Nygma's going.
I trust you know
what you're doing.
We do what we have to do, right?
Gentlemen.
Come in. You're late.
The last body you procured
for me was gangrenous.
Completely unsuitable.
Oh, my.
Bye.
Hello, Professor.
(chuckles)
Mr. Nygma.
Let's skip the part
where you deny
making me into
a killing machine.
Tell me how you took control
of my alter ego.
I don't follow.
You did something
to access
the Ed Nygma side
of my personality.
But... you're Ed Nygma.
I'm also the Riddler!
Tell me what you did!
Why did you make me
kill all those people
in Haven?
You did that?
How interesting.
I had no idea.
You really expect
me to believe that?
Mr. Nygma, I don't know
anything about
your alter egos.
But I will confess that
when I was sewing up
your knife wound,
I may have tinkered a little
with your grey matter.
- Would you just...
- I put a chip in your brain.
It allows you to be able
to be controlled remotely.
I knew it.
But I don't control you.
I gave control to others.
Who?
I will write it down.
That way,
if I'm ever confronted,
I can honestly say
that I never told you.
(sighs)
(thuds)
Not to worry.
You're experiencing a
simple neural cutout.
I am mystified as to
how you've become aware
you're being controlled.
I suppose we're just going
to have to open you up
and take a look under the hood.
Won't we?
Jim.
Sorry, kid, it's just me.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm just, uh,
just looking for Jim.
It's nothing.
I saw soldiers downstairs.
Yeah, the Army's
finally gotten off their asses
and decided to help.
Jim's out
with them now.
Are you sure you're all right?
(distant gunfire)
I don't know.
I see people losing
their will to do good.
People I love.
What if we don't make it
out of this?
I'm not gonna lie, kid.
These past few months,
I've wondered the same thing.
And when I don't know
what to do,
I come up here and I dig into
these case files.
I sit my ass down
and I get to work.
I used to hate this
kind of paperwork;
now it's the only thing
that keeps me going.
Why?
Because the little
things matter.
Act by act, deed by deed,
it means something.
Even if no one notices
or cares.
Thanks, Harvey.
You're welcome, kid.
If you really want
to do an old man a favor,
you can scrounge me up
a cup of joe because I, uh...
Kid's fast.
(drill whirs)
I apologize for the discomfort.
The neural cutout inhibits
muscular function,
but not pain receptors.
A simple reboot of the chip
should be all that is required.
- Although, the sound may be...
- (drill whirring)
...uh, somewhat unpleasant.
Not to mention the smell.
(Edward groaning)
(Edward snorts)
(grunts)
(Edward yips, growls)
(Oswald panting)
(Edward whines)
(sighs)
(inhales sharply)
Edward, I believe
the time has come
for a change of scenery.
(chuckles)
It seems a powerful
electrical charge
overloaded your chip, but I've
gotten everything updated.
I will pass the good news
along to your handler.
(gun cocks)
Care to expand on that?
I was merely helping a man
who needed medical attention.
Yeah, not buying it.
His eyes are open.
I gave him
a biomedical anesthesia.
Wake him up now. Do it.
Oh, very well.
(screams)
Oh!
I told you this wasn't me!
He put a chip
in my brain.
And someone's been controlling
it this whole time.
And then he
drilled in my head!
- Better talk now.
- (Nygma sighs)
I am a scientist.
A contract came along;
I developed a tool.
"A tool"?
How dare you?
A contract from who?
Please escort
the professor out, thank you.
Ta-ta.
What the hell is going on?
Sorry, pal, but this part
of the op is need-to-know.
I couldn't say anything until
we had the suspect in custody,
but Walker wants Ed Nygma
taken out now.
Walker was behind this?
She's been controlling Nygma
the whole time?
(scoffs)
You know I hate this spook crap.
I don't ask questions;
I follow orders.
She's responsible for Haven?
I don't understand, why...
Jim, stop right there, trust me.
Walker wants you
to put a bullet
in his brain.
No.
Call it proof of loyalty.
It's what she needs from you
before she can move forward
with final relief plans.
Hey, come on.
Look at him.
He's a loon.
A cop-killer.
Tell me the truth.
Did Walker destroy Haven?
Did you know?
- Tell me.
- Jim, ours is not to reason why.
And this is your chance
to be a part of this mission.
So...
please.
You pull the
trigger on him,
or I pull the trigger on you.
After all this, you'd kill me
for some bureaucrat?
Mission comes first.
You taught me that.
What's your answer?
Looks like I saved your life
one too many times.
- Maybe so.
- (grunts)
(Eduardo grunts)
You know Jim Gordon.
You know this city.
Find him.
And kill him.
(hammering)
(scraping on stone)
(gasps)
Boss. Wake up.
Wake up.
Ouch.
Oh! Stitches still sore, huh?
Never would
have happened
if you wore that armor
I prepared.
That bullet
is making you sentimental.
Give her a shake, huh?
Hmm. Better?
I told you I had to let
Selina thrust the knife
into my flesh at least once.
Verisimilitude
trumps precaution, you see.
I get it.
Selina Kyle and Bruce Wayne
needed to think
you were dead, boss.
Yeah. Right.
(gasps)
I take it you have news?
All systems go.
- Well, then lead the way.
- Oh!
Doctor.
I'm hearing good things.
The bandages are ready
to come off.
Your assistant thought
you'd like to see the results.
Indeed, I would.
(laughs)
Oh, you two look beautiful.
Oh...
I love family reunions,
don't you?