[rock music playing]
You two here
to pick up your grandchildren?
Come on, Babs,
you got the only full bar in Gotham.
And if you two dinosaurs want
to keep coming here,
you better up your intel.
We got a lead
on some black-market heating oil.
One drink...
To share.
Then you go wheeze
to death somewhere else.
[woman chuckling] Mmm-hmm.
Would you look at that?
Dix!
Look at you.
Up and walking around?
You old son of a bitch.
I've been looking for you two
for a while now.
Well, you found us.
You two ever think about the past?
What we did?
What are you talking about, Dix?
About her.
About what we did to the girl.
[Barbara] Who is that?
It's like the living dead in here.
Enough of this.
[both groaning]
Hey, gramps.
[Barbara gasps]
[Alfred] Can you please repeat
your story for Mr. Wayne, madam?
We live in a shelter in West End.
There are so many of us
crammed in there,
so much uncertainty, fear...
And with the river poisoned,
it should have been awful, but...
People came together,
made it a home.
What happened?
Couple of weeks ago,
we heard rumors about
something underneath the building.
We're connected to the sewer,
and people started going missing.
Hank, my husband,
wanted to look for them.
Said we were a family.
So the two of you went
searching for them.
It was so dark.
I didn't see what attacked us.
I hit my head and when I woke up,
Hank was gone. [crying]
Please, Mr. Wayne...
we have a daughter.
We'll do everything we can.
Should we tell Gordon?
Why, he's stretched thin as it is.
Alfred, we don't know
who or what is down there.
We know there's a man
down there in danger.
And we know this lady sent for us.
So go on then,
what do you think we should do?
Let's go find him.
Under normal circumstances,
I wouldn't call you
for a couple of stiffs.
What do you normally do when
a couple of your patrons get stabbed?
Bury the bodies.
Find out who did it
and then bury those bodies.
See, that's not something
you should be telling a cop.
We're living in
a different world, Harvey.
[Gordon]
So, why did you call us?
[Barbara] Take a look.
Boggs and Lewis...
You know them?
They were cops, they were gone
before you joined. What happened?
They came around
peddling third-rate intel.
It was closing time,
so I let them in.
And then,
some other fossil knifed them.
You saw him?
Yeah. He must have snuck in.
Looked like a cop too.
These two knew him.
Bartender said
they called him "Mix," "Hicks"...
-"Dix"?
-Maybe.
No way.
Dix was Harvey's old partner.
There we go, case closed.
So, you're telling me, this guy
rolled in here in a wheelchair,
stabbed these two and rolled on out?
He wasn't in a wheelchair.
Then it couldn't be Dix. He's been
paralyzed for the last 15 years.
Harvey, you're confusing me
with someone who cares.
I called you as a courtesy, and now,
I'm wishing I'd just dumped
these two corpses in an alley.
Do we even know that Dix is still
in Gotham after the bridges blew?
I heard he moved into
an apartment about a year ago.
I meant to check up on him,
but... It can't be him.
I hear what you're saying,
but we should still talk to him.
Maybe he knows something.
Fine.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine. Thanks for asking.
Look,
I've been giving you space,
but we have to talk about
how this is gonna work.
I'm gonna be
a part of this kid's life.
Oh, you seem pretty confident
about that.
I am.
Reunification's gonna happen,
you should think about what kind of
person you want to be when it does.
It's a chance for you to start anew.
I like who I am.
Uh-huh.
[door closes]
[bells ringing]
You were due hours ago.
Yes, I was.
But I had to get us lunch.
And I met Dale.
I see that.
Do you see this?
Our secret plan
to get off this island.
Relax. Dale is
completely trustworthy.
How do you know we can trust him
if you just met him?
Because, he's mute
and dumb as a post.
Look, I know you're paranoid
about people watching us...
Someone is watching us!
Why do you think
I installed this alarm system?
[scoffs] And as safe as I feel with
your jingle-bell contraption in place,
I went out and procured us
some muscle. You're welcome.
At least you're doing something.
Ah!
How's my SS Gertrude coming along?
Our submarine is coming along
just fine, thank you.
I've been working on the sonar,
which turns out is far more
complex than I anticipated.
Well, I am confident
you'll figure it out.
Of course I will figure it out.
Because, I figure everything out.
The navigation system,
the oxygen exchange.
I will figure everything out
because I'm the only one working!
This was supposed
to be a partnership.
It is!
I already did my part by stealing
everything valuable in Gotham,
-of which you get half.
-No!
Your goon stole it.
And then you killed him.
[bells ringing]
Are you expecting someone?
Who would I be expecting, Oswald?
I told you someone's watching us.
Dale, go do what I pay you for.
Protect us.
Wait!
Penn?
Hello, Mr. Cobblepot.
Are you really...
I don't believe it. You're alive.
Indeed, sir. I am.
But, you were shot. I was there.
This whole time, I thought
you were dead, but you're alive.
[Penguin laughing]
You're only coming to me now?
I'm so terribly sorry, Mr. Cobblepot,
I wanted to come see you, but...
He wouldn't let me.
"He"? He, who?
Mr. Cobblepot,
this is...
Mr. Scarface.
Wonderful.
Look, I'm sure Dix is in the clear,
but we do have to ask.
That's not it.
I just... I feel bad.
I should have been by before,
I'm all he's got.
Well, look, what can you do, right?
Dix!
What the hell?
Bullock, that you?
Yeah.
-Don't shoot.
-Okay.
Come in.
Uh-huh.
[Harvey] Is that the way you
always answer the door?
Nowadays, you can't be too careful.
Especially someone like me.
A kid comes in, he'd cut
my throat for a cup of soup.
[Harvey] Uh-huh.
[Dix] Anyway, I wasn't expecting you.
Figured you forgot about me.
Look, partner, when the bridges
came down, I got busy, and...
Oh, sure, sure, you forgot me.
Everybody forgets.
I didn't forget.
You planning on taking a trip?
Maybe.
I like to keep a bag packed
just in case.
Yeah? Where were you last night?
Where was I? I was right here.
Anybody else here with you?
Anybody that can back up your story?
You're asking me if I was out there
killing Boggs and Lewis?
Does it look like I was out there
So, you heard about that?
Let me tell you something.
If it meant that I can get out of
this son-of-a-bitch wheelchair,
I would confess right here
and now to Boggs, to Lewis,
to anybody you want me to confess to.
All right. Fine.
But, you were a detective,
what would you say if you were us?
We come in here,
you're packing a suitcase.
I would say either I did it,
which I didn't...
Or, I'd be very worried
that I'd be next.
What do you mean, you being next?
What's your connection
to Boggs and Lewis?
Come on, what?
Nothing.
I just worked with them. That's it.
We, uh... We worked a case together.
-The four of you?
-[Harvey] Yeah.
Dix wasn't my partner then.
I was a rookie cop.
Wet behind the ears.
So, what was the case?
Woman killed her husband,
as far as I can remember,
it was pretty open and shut.
But, at least, we can agree
that Dix didn't walk into The Sirens
and stab those two guys.
So, who did?
Barbara said Boggs and Lewis
recognized the killer.
They called him "Dix."
We come in here,
he's packing a suitcase,
-he shoots at us. This stinks, Harvey.
-[knocking on door]
Hey.
[both groaning]
[Gordon] You all right?
[panting]
What the hell?
[Alfred] These basements run
along Gotham sewers.
The river is right next to it.
You mean, the river
filled with Jeremiah's toxins?
Who knows that kind of damage
these chemicals could do.
Yeah, you're right.
Just don't you touch anything.
Hold on.
Bite marks.
Animal?
Well, it's no human I've ever seen.
And whatever it was...
It dragged him that way.
[Gordon] Seems like human skin.
Here's the file you asked for.
Victoria Cartwright.
How did you, uh...
I had Harper run every case
the four of you worked
cross-referenced with any woman
that killed her husband.
Do I need to read it,
or you gonna tell me what's in it?
Victoria Cartwright was a banker,
she led a very boring life.
Until she snapped and put two
.38-caliber slugs into her husband.
End of story.
You guys rehearse that?
Says here,
there was no physical evidence.
She was convicted on the statement of
her seven-year-old daughter, Jane.
This was 20 years ago.
Where's Jane now?
What's the point? The killer's a man.
A man that can
imitate friggin' faces.
What was the name of the guy
that Strange got to imitate you,
Basil something?
That's who we should be looking for.
That was different and you know it.
-We have an address for this Jane?
-No.
But the family's old home is in the
Green Zone, just east of the clinic.
Jim, it's a dead end.
Is there anything else
you want to tell me?
You know what,
why don't you hang back?
Whoa, whoa. Wait.
-You benching me?
-Killer's still out there.
Keep an eye on your partner.
[Penguin] Penn, Arnold...
It's Arthur.
[Penguin chuckles]
You're holding a doll.
It's not a doll.
It's a dummy.
Oh, this is great.
I'm going back to work. Excuse me.
You're saying he made you come here?
Mr. Scarface is very persuasive.
[laughing]
"Persuasive"?
He made me tell him
about your [softly] treasure.
Penn...
I think you need a rest.
And perhaps, a psychiatrist.
Then we can discuss you
resuming your former duties.
Obviously, I won't pay you
for the time you were gone.
Shut your pie-hole!
This the one you were
telling me about?
Punk who thinks he's in charge?
Yes, sir. That's Mr. Cobblepot.
Oswald, if you don''t
make him leave, I will.
No one's going anywheres.
Penn, show these two jokers
we're serious.
Forgive me.
[Dale groans]
Now, let's talk turkey,
turkeys.
What a mess, huh?
Yeah.
Boggs and Lewis were idiots,
complete idiots.
They should have known when they
see a guy walking, that it ain't me.
You think the Cartwright girl
said something?
How would I know?
So, how have you been
since the bridges came down?
You getting enough food, medicine?
What if I said no?
I'd feel like crap.
Then, no.
[Dix chuckles]
The Cartwright girl is dead.
A buddy of mine
who was a screw over at Arkham,
he said she was an inmate there,
and she died a couple of years ago.
So, this has nothing to do with her.
[wind howling]
GCPD.
Coming in.
Check upstairs.
[Harper] Looks like this place
has been abandoned
since before the bridges came down.
Yeah.
[wind howling]
[breathing heavily]
[officer] What the hell?
[officer groans]
[tinkling]
What the hell was that?
[woman grunting]
[wind howling]
Someone's been living here.
What's that smell?
[door opens]
Everything all right?
All good. No one's here.
Hey.
[all grunting]
[groaning]
[woman] Don't look at me.
Don't look at me!
[Gordon] We found your handiwork.
Nothing to say?
You're gonna have to
take that mask off.
The only way you're gonna keep
that mask on is if you talk.
Otherwise, I'm gonna
reach over this table
and I'm gonna rip it
off of your face.
-Who are you?
-Nobody.
You're not Jane Cartwright?
Because you were
in her childhood home.
You're about the right age.
Talk to me, Jane.
I know after your mother
was convicted,
you ended up a ward of the State.
In and out of institutions
until you ended up in Arkham.
Then you vanished.
Some say, died.
-What happened to you?
-Me?
Nothing happened to me.
Okay.
What happened to Jane?
[Jane] Oh...
Lots happened to Jane.
She was taken from Arkham,
down, down...
Down... The doctor did things to her,
experiments on her and others.
You're talking about Hugo Strange.
You were taken to Indian Hill.
The professor was obsessed
with the power to change.
The way a chameleon
would change its skin,
he wanted humans to have that power.
He made it
so Jane could change her skin,
her bones, her hair,
the color of her eyes.
All it takes is a single touch
and her body becomes a mirror.
When it's done, she sheds
her skin and starts anew.
It remembers everyone it touched.
It's touched you, Detective.
[Gordon]
We can help you, Ms. Cartwright.
Jane Cartwright is dead.
She died in Arkham.
That's when Jane Doe was born.
So why kill all these cops?
You want to know why they died?
Ask your friend.
[rustling]
What is that?
[grunts]
We should head out.
My battery's dying. [grunts]
[yelling]
[all grunting]
[panting] Please.
He's coming. He's coming.
Who's coming? What happened?
He's going to kill me.
I just barely got away.
Are you Hank?
Yes.
[Alfred] Your wife sent us.
Is anyone else left alive down there?
They're all dead.
[growling]
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God!
Oh, God. Oh, God.
[growling continues]
Oh, my God.
[roaring]
[yelping]
[screaming]
[Alfred] Hank! Hank! Hold on, Hank!
[Mr. Scarface laughing]
Hand over the heaters.
If you don't mind.
Mr. Penn,
can't we just talk this through?
Get back!
I'm so sorry.
At least,
tell me what happened after Haven.
Help me to understand this.
Go on.
Sing your song.
After I was shot,
I woke up in the GCPD morgue.
I was alone.
I patched my wounds as
best I could and crawled out.
I hid in a store.
An abandoned magic shop.
That's where Mr. Scarface found me.
And he told me all about you.
How you used him.
Chewed him up and spat him out!
Treated him like a Toluca.
-That's a lie!
-Oh, please, Oswald.
It's what you do.
Arnold...
Arthur, what do you want?
I don't want anything.
But, Mr. Scarface, well...
He wants your treasure.
And,
to be boss.
[Penguin scoffs]
Really?
The dummy wants to be
the boss of Gotham.
Bingo!
Now, give me the key
to your treasure room.
Why would I do that?
You're obviously
gonna kill me anyway.
What am I doing?
-I'm talking to a doll.
-Dummy.
Seriously?
You know what, Oswald?
Honestly, you deserve this.
Nobody asked you.
You are opportunistic,
your loyalty is shaky, at best,
and you will hurt anyone,
anyone to get what you want.
I hardly think you're one
to throw stones.
Listen, Penn...
Eyes down here, pal.
[chuckles]
Sorry.
Mr. Scarface,
I got a question for you.
Shoot. [laughing]
[Nygma chuckles]
After you get your tiny, wooden hands
on that treasure,
what are you gonna do?
Where you gonna go?
People are gonna come
after you eventually.
Then I'll...
I'll take them all on.
Yeah, show them who's boss!
Ah.
You wouldn't have to do that
if you could get off this island,
now, would you?
What are you doing?
Shut it. Let the smart one talk.
How do you feel
about submarines?
[Dix] What are we doing here?
[Harvey] I just wanted to
take us someplace quiet,
where we can talk.
We did a bad thing.
Oh, come on, not that again.
We put a killer in jail, all right?
What do you keep moping about?
She was guilty.
She got what she deserved. Drop it.
-Did you get what you deserved?
-What?
You made that girl into a murderer.
Oh, come on.
You,
your friends,
-the kid...
-Come on.
I'm gonna make sure
you never do that again.
[Dix choking]
Harper, where's Dix?
I saw Bullock take him in the back.
[Gordon sighs]
Barbara, what are you doing here?
Seems my bartender overheard
the killer say something
before he ice-picked Harvey's pals.
I thought I'd be a good citizen.
Okay.
"The kid's guilty too."
The kid.
Listen,
what you said before,
about me being a known criminal...
I was on some list
your army buddy had.
When the government rolls in,
am I gonna be arrested?
Honestly, I don't know.
But that would work out
for you, right?
I go to jail, you get the baby?
I don't want that.
Is that a promise?
I go straight, I'm clear?
Stay right here.
Hey, Harvey.
Where'd you take Dix?
I didn't take Dix anywhere.
Oh, God. Oh!
She got into your locker,
must have taken your clothes.
We have to lock down the GCPD.
Hey, Harvey,
we'll find her.
Come on.
[Hank screaming]
[Alfred] Look at the size of it!
[snarling]
Living down here.
The toxins in the river
must have driven him mad.
Get out of here now.
[both grunting]
[Bruce groans]
Alfred!
-Stop!
-Alfred!
Alfred, stop.
Stop.
Stop!
[groaning]
All right, everybody, listen up.
GCPD is now in lockdown.
Nobody goes in or out
unless I say so.
She could look like anybody by now,
how are we supposed to find her?
Jim.
Barbara.
What happened?
What do you mean, "What happened?"
I've been attacked.
-Where did she go?
-Wait a minute.
How do we know it's really you?
Seriously?
This isn't proof enough?
What the hell?
That's her.
She's the impostor, shoot her.
[guns cocking]
It's me, you idiot.
That sounds like Barbara.
Barbara.
Tell me where we first met.
Don't shoot.
I'm leaving here.
Anyone tries to follow me, she dies.
Shoot her!
Can't risk it.
-Stay back!
-[grunts]
Bullock, wait!
-I'm fine.
-Take her to my office.
-Don't let her out of your sight.
-Okay.
I cannot believe that
you told him about the sub.
And that you're playing along
with his psychosis.
Obviously, he was gonna kill you.
I bought us time.
I have an idea.
If you can just keep him busy
and wait for the signal.
Wait, what's the signal?
Quit your jawing.
[Mr. Penn] So,
Mr. Scarface and I
have discussed our options.
And the submarine
sounds like a good plan.
And since we'll need the smart one
to build this hay burner,
he can keep sucking air.
But Penguin ain't so lucky.
Do it, Penn.
Ventilate that mook.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Cobblepot.
I wish things would have
turned out differently.
Arthur,
I want you to listen
to what I'm saying.
You accuse me of manipulating you,
but what about him?
I never asked you to kill anybody.
-That is true.
-Hey...
Think of everything that
we went through together.
Sofia Falcone...
Getting cut off
from the mainland, starving.
You mean Penn was starving.
Fighting for scraps,
while your dog ate steak.
I welcomed you into my home.
And, yes, I was not a good friend.
To you or to anyone.
It's why I'm alone.
But I saw you for what you are,
and I valued that.
That must be worth something.
Applesauce.
You're a liar and a thief.
All you do is take,
take,
take!
And you never give anything.
You worked me to the bone.
Forced me to be your puppet.
Well, no more.
You hear me?
No more.
-[high-pitched ringing]
-[both groaning]
Take that.
And that!
[both grunting]
-No.
-No!
Mr. Cobblepot.
You freed me.
How can I ever thank you?
[yelping]
Why did you do that?
He wasn't the threat,
the dummy was the threat!
Oswald...
I accept you
for the person that you are.
Just as you accept me
for the cold logician that I am.
That's why this friendship is great.
And as friends,
I think we can both agree that
that lunatic had to be stopped.
[laughing]
Perhaps, Edward,
we really are meant for each other.
[both laughing]
Jane.
I know you're up here.
Jane, I knew you'd be here.
I'm sorry.
It was my job to protect you
and I let you down.
You made Jane into a killer.
You and your friends,
there have to be consequences.
You killed three men already.
When is it enough?
When you're dead.
Put the gun down!
Shoot me.
You killed Jane years ago,
and you didn't even know it.
Just shoot me.
Let me see your face.
Your real face.
Why? So you can see
what a monster she is?
Hugo Strange only destroyed her face,
you destroyed her soul.
Let me see it.
[Jane] You see?
Do you see what they did?
Jane...
We can work this out,
just put the gun down.
The only way this ends
is with one of us dead.
Oh, Hank, thank God you're alive.
The nurse thinks the man
that attacked us will never recover.
The toxins in the river have done
irreparable damage to his brain.
I just think it's a shame
we couldn't save
the rest of the people
that went missing, Master Bruce.
We should have went to
Gordon from the start.
-We were reckless.
-That's nonsense.
We took decisive action,
we saved a man's life.
The people in this city
have suffered, Master Bruce,
they need someone
that will protect them.
I agree.
But there are better ways
to find absolution.
I don't follow.
What happened to Wayne Manor
wasn't your fault.
I know you've been blaming yourself.
You didn't destroy our home, Alfred.
But I feel like I did.
I feel like I wasn't strong enough to
fight Tetch and that bastard Valeska.
I feel like because of my weakness,
you lost your last tie to the past.
You lost your home, Master Bruce.
I must never be that weak again.
Part of being a family
is that we can be strong
for each other.
And when did you get so smart?
I had a good teacher.
Victoria Cartwright killed
her husband.
After we arrested her,
she admitted it.
Later, she recanted.
But the physical evidence
wasn't there.
I was a new cop,
I wanted to make detective.
So, you leaned on Jane.
Forced a statement out of her
to put her mother away.
The woman was guilty.
Later, I found out the husband...
Beat the mother and Jane.
I didn't know till after.
Bartender overheard Jane
say something about...
"The kid's guilty, too."
She meant the young cop.
She meant you.
I knew something was wrong.
I felt it.
I said something, and they told me
to keep my trap shut,
just close the case, put a bow on it.
After a while, I stopped feeling it.
I went down that path
for a long time,
until I met you.
However much I've changed,
I can't change the past.
I made that girl a killer.
What do you want from me, Harvey?
Forgiveness?
Can't give that to you.
I just needed you to know.