Previously onGotham...
You paid off the mayor
to make Jim Gordon captain.
- Don't ever betray me again.
- Never.
I need to know
what Sofia's planning
and who she is planning it with.
Plain dumb Ed.
I would like you to go to
the Narrows and bundle them up,
bring them back to me.
They're the ones
who started the problem.
They work for Penguin.
I would like to announce
that we just quit
working for Penguin.
This is your turf now.
- What is he doing to them?
- He's cooking them.
They are people pies.
Eat the pies or the boy dies.
Suspect known as the Pyg
is in custody.
GCPD kept this promise.
I'm not your enemy, Jim.
I never will be.
Did you find anything out?
He saw Sofia kissing the policeman.
She will answer
for what she's done.
Yeah, Thursday.
Thursday is my day.
Because it's my day!
You keep... you keep this...
I don't like that song.
My Ma used to beat me to it.
It was playing when I killed her.
So now, you turn it off
or I'll do the same to you.
Why did your mother beat you?
Were you a naughty boy?
Did you soil in your trousers?
Stutter.
Perhaps.
Open the gate! Open the gate!
Open the gate now!
Back off! Back off! Open the gate!
I really wish you haven't done that.
I paid a fortune to look this good.
Everybody! Stay where you are!
All right, open the gate,
that's enough!
Okay, I told you,
open the gate, let us in!
The doctors at Arkham
took these after the fight.
The bigger titanium plate
surgically grafted
onto the bones of his face,
the result of which
radically changed its appearance.
When we booked him,
his fingerprints were burned off.
I've seen it before on criminals
that wanna hide their identity.
- But never anything like this.
- That's not all.
The doctors also noticed
a scar tissue
behind his ears
and along his neckline
indicating
he's had multiple surgeries.
That explains why we couldn't
ID him off his photo.
This doesn't make any sense,
the Pyg is a glory hound.
Everything he's done,
it's all been
about grabbing the spotlight.
Classic sociopath behavior.
So, why doesn't he
want us to know who he really is?
Now, is the time he should be
taking credit for his crimes.
Can he use this X- ray
to reconstruct his face?
See what he looked like
before he add any work done.
It certainly possible
but it will take some time.
Get started.
I wanna know who The Pyg really is.
Morning, Cap.
Barbara.
- How's your shoulder?
- This? Just a scratch.
You got a visitor.
Thanks.
Sofia.
What are you doing here?
I haven't heard from you
in few days.
I didn't realize
I was supposed to call.
I figured after the other night,
we were gonna start
seeing each other again.
We're not.
I get it.
You were worried about Penguin
finding out about us
that I made you a captain.
You don't have to be.
I already told him.
I'm sorry, you did what?
- I have it under control.
- Is that what you think?
It's what I know.
I'm going to remove Penguin
from the picture
and when I do,
I want us to be together.
It's not gonna work, Sofia.
Even if Penguin
is out of the picture,
I just don't see a way for it
for us, I'm sorry.
I run the dog races,
he runs the cockfights.
Now, he's coming in
muscling on my business.
I got mouths to feed.
You race those dogs again,
and now, I'll slit your damn throat.
All right. Enough.
If she stabs him,
it solves the issue.
I started this court
so we can work out
disputes peacefully.
This is how things are gonna be done
from now on, understood?
Now, you're both admitting
to having down months?
Seems the only solution
is for you to partner up.
Both of you work together,
you stay strong.
Okay, that's settle.
Thank you. Moving on. Next.
Wait.
How's your daughter?
Fever became down.
Thanks to you, Doc.
These bums are so lucky to have you.
You cure their children,
you solve their problems.
I haven't forgotten about you, Ed.
Yes, you say that
and, yet, I remain a moron.
I said I would fix you, and I will.
Out of my way.
Move! Out of my way!
Out of my way! I need to see the doc.
What happened?
Sampson sent his dogs to my shop,
demanding protection money.
I told them no.
I said this is your neighborhood now.
I'm sorry, who's Sampson?
He chose a territory
just south of here.
All right, go to the clinic.
I'll stitch you up.
You know, this was bound to happen.
You're the new leader
of the Narrows.
Sampson's just testing you, but,
you have to show him and his people
that you can't be pushed around.
What should I send,
Grundy to rip his arms off?
Look at him.
This is what he lives for.
I'm asking these people
to settle things amicably.
I can't just be a hypocrite
and send Grundy every time
I have a problem.
Okay, what would you like to do?
Hello, Sofia.
Oswald, what a...
pleasant surprise.
Oh, I assure you.
Dear.
There is nothing pleasant about it.
I have continually
been suspicious of you.
And yet,
every turn, you always had
a perfect explanation
to put my mind at ease.
But now...
I finally have proof
that you are my enemy.
You lied to me.
You told me you hated Gordon.
You are his lover.
Martin saw you kissing him
after the party.
That's ridiculous.
I'm not sure what Martin
thought he saw,
but I can assure you
- it was no kiss.
- Enough of your lies!
Our entire friendship,
the intimacies we shared,
they were nothing more
than a pathetic charade.
Oswald, I swear,
I swear I care for you deeply. I...
Oh, I wish that were true.
What?
After Martin found out
about you and Gordon,
I did a little digging
into your boyfriend.
Interesting.
He took a trip down south
shortly before you arrived
in Gotham.
Coincidence?
I think not.
So you see,
I know that the two of you
have been plotting to destroy me
from the very beginning.
Bravo, Oswald.
Do you know I was warned
you're a mastermind?
Turns out, you're an easy mark.
It is truly amazing
what you can accomplish
with goulash and a good foot rub.
Now, I see the real you.
I was blind to your manipulations.
But today,
I'm going to correct that mistake.
You will tell me
the full extent of your plan,
if your father was involved,
which of my captains you have turned,
and how you intend
to rid me from the city.
Bring him out.
Allow me to introduce you
to The Dentist.
And he is not the kind
who gives out lollipops
after the visit.
Captain Gordon.
I wondered if my little scuffle
would bring you here.
I'm so glad it did.
- I missed our little chats.
- Good.
And you can start by telling me
who you really are.
Don't you know...
Jim, I'm a reflection of you.
I don't see it.
Jim, you swine.
I want to know
who's hiding behind that mask.
What you see is what you get.
What I see is someone
who craves attention.
So, why are you concealing
your true identity?
Don't you wanna take the credit
for all your brilliant crimes.
Oh, I get all the credit,
the whole town.
It's gonna hog wild for the pyg...
Since I caught you,
you're yesterday news.
- It's not true.
- This is Gotham.
You're a second class psychopath
compared to what we've got.
Jerome Valeska, Fish Mooney,
Penguin.
They have staying power,
- you don't.
- You're wrong.
I terrified this whole city
for months.
People will remember that.
No, they won't.
In fact,
they've already forgotten you.
But not you, Jim.
- You're here.
- My final visit.
Now, I'm gonna walk out that door
and never think about you again.
Mind games.
You really think
that's gonna work on me.
Guard, we're done here.
James, we're not done here.
Have a nice life.
Don't you walk out on me!
You'll never forget me.
I promise you that.
There you are.
So...
you're Duck.
I heard you had a giant.
I think that you might have brought
him along with you rather than this
- has been.
- Excuse me...
Why would I bring Grundy along
for a friendly conversation?
Look, I understand you had
a deal with Cherry were you left
your people alone.
I expect you do the honor
the same with me.
Why would I do that?
You're not even from the Narrows.
You have no idea how things
work around here.
Maybe you're right.
But I do know that you love money.
I'm willing to offer you
10 percent of fight night.
Just don't get around,
I'm not negotiating. I'm taking.
I'm taking your clinic.
I'm taking you club.
I'm taking your whole damn
neighborhood.
Okay, we try this your way,
let's use Grundy.
That doesn't sound so good.
You cough off blood yet?
What is it to you?
Bad case of Narrows lung
going around.
What the hell is that?
The new virus.
I have seen it kill
a few people already.
First you cough up blood
and more than a few days
you're dead,
unless you have treatments.
I'll sweetened the deal.
I will doctor your people
free of charge.
You're not gonna get
a better offer than that.
All right.
I will be back in a few days
and negotiate
with whoever takes your place
after you drown
in your own blood.
I tell you what, doc.
Make it 30 percent of fight night.
- You got yourself a deal.
- It's too much, don't take it.
Come by the clinic later.
We'll see about that cough.
You teeth quite lovely.
I look forward to putting them
in my trophy case.
You have no idea who I am,
do you?
Of course, I do.
You are Don Falcone's daughter.
He killed my brother.
I'm going to enjoy this.
It's true he killed your brother
but not your wife, Elaine,
or your son, Joseph.
No, they're still alive.
Probably having lunch
in your two bedroom
on Seventh Ave right now.
See.
I made it a point to learn every
detail of Penguin's organization.
For instance,
I learned that he only trust
one man for this type of job, you.
And in the event
that I'm ever tortured,
my people have instructions
to kill your family.
Interesting threat.
But no one is going to know
that you were tortured.
Because no one is going
to find your body.
Oh, because you don't think
I have spies inside
Penguin's organization.
He's right about me, though.
I have been conspiring
against him for months.
Turning his captains against him
one by one.
And today is the day that
I will finally take him down.
So if my people
don't hear from me soon,
your family is dead.
But if you don't believe me,
drill away.
Excuse me.
Restraints need tightening.
A wise decision.
Now, untie me.
Things are finally looking up.
Wakey wakey.
Oh, hello.
I don't believe we've met.
I'm Barbara Kean.
This ferocious lady is
Tabitha Galavan, and that kitty cat,
that's Selina Kyle.
I know who you are.
Penguin wants you dead for betraying
him down in the Narrows.
What do you want with me?
Well, we heard you and Ozzy
are BFF's.
So you're going to try
and leverage me
to get Penguin not to kill you.
We have some other demands.
but essentially, yeah.
That's a good plan,
except for the fact that Penguin
just tried to kill me.
Why would he do that?
Because I am so close
to taking his underworld from him.
You're lying.
Am I?
I've been working Penguin for months.
Manipulating him to behaving
exactly like I want him to.
Every move he made today,
I orchestrated.
Now, you three,
are screwing things up. So...
You want him out of your life,
let me go.
Maybe she's telling the truth.
She's a Falcone.
She learned to lie
before she could read.
But...
whether you're a friend a foe
makes no difference to me
because Penguin
will still make the deal.
Get him on the phone.
You'll grow into it.
Because of you,
I was able to vanquish my enemy.
And now,
that you've proven yourself...
I see a beautiful future
ahead for you.
I have so much wisdom to impart.
And if you pay attention...
one day all of this could be yours.
What's wrong?
What are you talking about?
You mean...
you did not see
Sofia kissing Gordon?
"She wanted me to tell you
they kissed."
Why would she do that?
Unless...
she knew exactly
how I would respond.
She wanted me to confront her.
Instant torture.
Boss.
We have a problem.
The dentist is gone.
What happened to Sofia?
To be honest,
it's still a little unclear.
Barbara Kean has her.
What?
How do you know this?
She's on the phone.
She said she wants
to make a deal.
Barbara.
Hello, Oswald.
I see you have crawled out from
whatever rock you were hiding under.
What are you doing with Sofia?
We scooped her up this morning.
And of course when we did,
we thought she was your best friend.
Turns out, she's your worst enemy.
I want her back.
Name your price.
We keep the gun shop.
We don't share profits.
And from this point forward,
we operate with complete autonomy.
Fine.
I will send Zsasz over
to collect her.
She had better be there
when he arrives.
She will be.
And as for you, young man.
Our conversation is not over.
So this is what the Pyg
used to look like.
Well, that's him.
All right,
send it out to police stations
across the country.
Start in the south.
- The south. Why?
- When I press them,
they spoke in a southern accent.
Could have been that deliberately
- to throw you off?
- No,
he slipped up.
I saw it in his eyes.
It's the best way we've got.
Let's see where it goes.
I don't understand you.
It seems this cough will kill him.
Why not let him die?
No such thing as Narrows lung.
Probably just has bronchitis.
They give him some medicine,
he feels better. Problem solved.
Okay, what about the 30 percent?
Once he has that
he's just gonna want more.
Maybe.
Sampson, you son of a bitch.
Now, you see
who you're dealing with?
I know you wanted
to try this your way.
No more diplomacy, Lee.
Take Grundy, and end this.
No.
I have a better idea.
- That was easy.
- Yeah, a little too easy.
Because he couldn't wait
to get you off the phone.
We need to get out of here.
And then what happens?
You take over from Penguin?
We are not working for anyone
but ourselves.
I'm not asking you to.
I will give you
everything you want from Penguin.
You're not in
the position to offer us anything.
We're in charge here.
Guys, I think we should listen
to her.
- Why?
- Because Zsasz is standing
out front holding a rocket
launcher.
Ladies.
I'm gonna break his little Pyg
in half.
Jim!
Sorry, Captain. I tried to stop her.
I told her she had to wait.
It's okay, Detective. I got it.
Sofia? What happened to you?
I underestimated Oswald.
He found out we were plotting
against him,
and he just tried to kill me, Jim.
He can't hurt you here.
If he finds out I'm alive,
he will come after me
and he won't stop until I'm dead.
You are the Captain of the GCPD.
Your men would follow you anywhere.
Please, please.
Use the position I gave you
and end this.
What are you proposing that I do?
You have an army.
Just take the fight to Penguin.
So, this was your plan?
To start a war.
You knew you didn't have
the numbers to fight Penguin
on their own.
So you made me captain,
knowing it would come to this
- and I take him out for you.
- Your job is to stop criminals, Jim.
- And here you go.
- It is not that simple.
And you know it.
We could bring law and order
back to Gotham.
This is exactly what you asked for
when you came down south,
and it is yours for the taking.
You know what has to be done, Jim.
Crush Penguin.
I trusted you, Martin.
You betrayed me.
I think it's time for you
to go back to the orphanage.
- Boss?
- Hold on.
Let the little spy
step out of the room.
So?
Place one out
like a great ball of fire.
Good.
Alert the capos.
We are going to unleash a crime wave
to this city like it has never seen.
That will teach Jim Gordon
to align himself with Sofia Falcone.
I wouldn't make
that call if I were you.
I just spoke with Sofia.
She's alive.
And she told me,
you tried to kill her.
Hearsay, Jim.
Been here all day. I have witnesses.
I don't care.
I'm not here to arrest you.
I came to make a deal.
I think we've both put up
with Sofia long enough.
Victor, would you give us a moment?
Okay, Jim. You have my attention.
Since the moment
she set foot in Gotham.
Sofia has put us on a path to war.
She's willing to let this city
burn to the ground.
To prove herself to her father.
I can't allow that.
So, what do you want from me?
I'm putting her on a train
home tonight.
But I need assurances from you,
you won't get involved.
Not good enough!
She needs to suffer
for what she has done.
That is not gonna happen.
And how do you think
your girlfriend is gonna react
when she realizes you betrayed her?
You think she's gonna run away
quietly?
If she sets foot in Gotham again,
I'll put her behind bars.
And if I say no?
And I'll have no choice...
but to use the full force
of the GCPD
to tear you apart piece by piece.
That does not sound very pleasant.
It won't be.
I guess, I can put aside
my personal feelings
for the good of this city.
But I do have one question
for you, Jim.
Once Sofia is gone,
what does that leave us?
No more licenses.
If you or any other criminal
in this city break the law,
my men will enforced.
But at least you won't to worry
about Sofia again.
So?
Do we have a deal?
After all we have been through
together, Jim,
it is nice that we can resolve
this matter with diplomacy.
Oh, Doc...
I heard about what happened
to your clinic.
What a shame.
I was looking forward to you
curing my Narrows lung.
I want you to clear out
of the Narrows by the end of the day.
- What did you say to me?
- I think she was pretty clear.
Then allow me to be clear.
This is my turf
and I'm not going anywhere.
And you two have dug your own graves.
Oh, well, then I guess
you don't want this?
What's that?
The anecdote to the poison
I had slipped in your drink
about 30 minutes ago.
Ironic, isn't it?
It's the only thing from
the clinic that wasn't destroyed.
Some vials of medicine
I had mixed
into a deadly combination.
It should be kicking in
right about now.
You're bluffing,
I feel absolutely fine...
I'm sorry, what was that?
Get them!
Come any closer
and I'll destroy this.
Like I said...
leave by the end of the day
and you'll live.
Deal?
Okay.
Oh, catch.
I know you're disappointed but
I am doing this to protect you.
Disappointment doesn't quite
cover it, Jim.
You stay in Gotham
and Penguin will kill you.
Don't put this on Penguin.
If you have something to say,
I think you should say it.
We're the same, Jim.
I saw it the first moment we met.
We both want power.
You wanna deny it but it's true
and it is just easier
to send me away.
Detective Harper, please take
Miss Falcone to the train station
and escort her back home.
Please don't do this.
You better get going.
You'll miss your train.
Gordon put her on the train.
Talk about the turn of events.
I did not see that coming.
What about the kid?
You want me to take him back
to the orphanage?
That won't be necessary.
Martin, I have been thinking...
I was angry, I did not mean what I...
Martin?
Martin.
Oh, he's cute.
He doesn't talk.
He gives me the creeps.
Let's get this over with.
Nervous about something?
We have a long way to go.
So get comfy.
Tickets, please.
What?
Hello, Victor.
Where's the boy?
Alive. For now.
If Oswald wants to keep it
that way,
he will meet me
under the Crown Point bridge
in one hour.
Next stop, Fielding Stop.
It's my stop.
Do you mind?
Not at all.
Thank you.
Glad you can make it, Oswald.
Everything will be all right,
Martin, I promise.
Well, that depends on you.
Turn over control
of the Underworld
to me
and I'll let little Martin here...
Keep his head.
The name Falcone used to mean
something in this town.
Wait until your father hears of this,
threatening the life of a child.
- He will be disgusted!
- Wrong!
My father will be proud.
Must be hard to live your whole life
trying to get daddy's approval.
I, myself, can relate seeing
as my parents loved me
without condition.
Say one more word
and I will kill him.
And then I will execute you.
I am choosing compassion
but I am willing
to change my position.
Don't hurt the boy.
He's innocent.
I submit!
Go ahead.
Martin, I want you to know...
I'm sorry for what I said.
I do care about you.
You know that's true, don't you?
Yes.
Go wait in the car.
You were wise to use the boy.
As you know, my heart
is my greatest weakness.
But...
I will not allow him
to be used as a pawn
of your game anymore.
You wanted a war? You've got one!
Ed,
why so blue? We had a great day.
You had a great day.
We did nothing to help.
That's not true.
Couldn't done without you.
Not meant to be a sidekick, Lee.
Sampson is right. I'm a has-been.
No you're not.
Okay, I sort of trust me with
something today and you did.
So I'm gonna trust you
with something.
I haven't been looking for a cure
for your brain, Ed.
Because there's nothing wrong
with you.
- But you...
- Sure,
at first there was an effect
from the ice.
But I ran all the test,
it checks out.
There's nothing wrong with you,
physically.
Your condition is psychological.
Think about it.
You knew every move
that Sampson was gonna make
before he made it.
You lied to me.
Why?
Because I was afraid
that if I told you the truth
you would go back to be
who you are before.
The Riddler.
And I like who you've become.
Who's that?
Ed Nygma.
The Ed that you were before.
My friend.
Well, that backfired.
Penguin's gonna be coming for us.
What are we gonna do?
We hit him before he hits us.
Lady, you lost.
Penguin just blew up that kid.
I admit I didn't see that coming.
But Oswald still has
to align his capos
before he moves on us.
We use that window of time
to make our play.
You didn't get told no a lot
as a kid, did you?
You took a shot and you missed.
- We're going in alone from here.
- You leave now,
and you will never have
a piece of this city.
Now, that sounded like a threat.
Your club is destroyed,
you have nowhere else to turn.
You need me.
Penguin may have won the battle.
But tomorrow, we win the war.
Boss.
My boy.
You did a splendid job of dying.
Victor will take you
to a safe location.
You can never return to Gotham.
This is goodbye, my friend.
There, there.
This is what I have to do
to protect you.
One day, when you are older,
you will understand.
Sophia's on our heels, boss.
Let's finish her off.
Let someone else take the kid.
No, I want my top man on this.
Besides,
I have something much better
plan for Sofia Falcone.
You were right about The Pyg.
A precinct down south recognize
the picture you have me sent down.
His real name is Lazlo Valentine.
What do we know about him?
He was being held for a string
of murders down there
ten years ago,
but here's the thing,
his previous victims
weren't police officers
and there was no Pyg persona.
Serial killers don't usually
change their M.O.
This guy did.
You said he was being held.
Did they say
why their case fell apart?
They didn't. He escaped.
Call Arkham.
Have them put a guard
in the south.
I'm on my way.
Pyg?
Hello, Ed.
No.
No!
Miss me?
Open it. Let's go.
Here they are!