PENGUIN:
There's a war coming.
A terrible war. There will be chaos.
Rivers of blood in the streets.
I know it. I can see it coming.
It's time. Somebody has to take over.
It might as well be me.
[SCREAMING]
I'm looking for a connection between the
Arkham plan and the murders of my parents.
If Maroni gets even a piece of Arkham,
it'll prove Falcone is weak.
GORDON:
Don't ever come back to Gotham.
Hello, James, old friend.
- I told you never to come back!
- Nobody looks for a dead man.
So you want the job or what?
Yes.
I ain't looking for no girl.
I'm looking for a weapon.
MARONI: Falcone thinks he can hit me
in my place of business...
...and get away with it?
I wanna hit him back.
Fancy a stroll?
It's a lovely day.
- Stretch the legs, breath of fresh air.
- I'm busy.
I got a question for you, Master Bruce.
What if all of this...
...was a complete and utter
bloody waste of time?
What if you never discovered
who killed your mom and dad?
Hmm?
What if you never get to wreak revenge?
I don't want revenge.
I wanna understand how it all works.
How Gotham works.
Well, you'd have more chance
digging to China with a teaspoon.
Take the Arkham project, for instance.
How did the Falcone and Maroni crime
families get such big shares in the deal?
I mean, I know city hall is corrupt...
...but why didn't Wayne Enterprises
do something?
Can you pass me that blue folder?
Well, I suppose as hobbies go, this is...
...a damn sight better than grilling yourself
like a bloody pork chop.
Still, not particularly healthy, is it?
Thank you.
Are you listening to me?
Yeah, yeah, for sure. I'll take a walk later.
Thank you, Alfred.
I won a piece of Arkham.
I strong-armed the mayor...
...I made Falcone back down, and
you're telling me I can't rob a lousy casino?
Sal, the casino is Falcone's pride and joy.
I mean, what's the point?
For a few thousand bucks,
why mess with Falcone?
That's the point...
...messing with Falcone. I want him and
his people to know we're not backing off.
Arkham was only the beginning.
We're taking over, Frankie. Inch by inch.
- Yeah, okay, but--
- "But, but, but."
- Make it happen.
- Okay, boss.
What are you looking at?
You got something to say?
No, sir. Nothing at all.
[BENNY STRUMMING GUITAR]
[HORN HONKING]
Hey. Hey, man!
Ripped By mstoll
[GASPING]
[GRUNTING]
[HEART POUNDING]
[ITEMS CLATTERING]
Hey.
Hey, you gotta pay for that.
[BURPS]
Do not vex me, mortal.
Yeah?
Suit yourself, Zeus.
[BENNY GRUNTS]
Hey, it might look
like the heel of a hobo's shoe.
Best burgers in midtown. Huh, Efram?
- If you say so.
- All right, I want two cheeseburgers...
...hold the sauce, extra pickles,
two malted shakes.
- No pickles on mine, please.
- Oh, you gotta trust me on this one.
Yeah? All right, pickles. Bring them.
You wanna look good
in a swimsuit like me...
...come summertime,
you'll want a lot of this and this.
All right.
- You!
- Hey!
[TIRES SCREECH]
[HORN HONKING]
BULLOCK:
Jim.
Jim! Come on, it's lunchtime. Relax.
[ALARM RINGING]
It's lunchtime.
No, Jim. We're on our-- It's lunch!
Oh, brother.
Jim, you can't just pop up and jump
every time you hear a bell.
G.C.P.D. Anybody here?
CASHIER:
Unh. Over here.
GORDON:
Oh. You all right, sir? You okay?
- Thank God you're here.
- Anybody dead?
I don't think so. Some guy,
he was stealing milk. I tried to stop him...
...he hauls away my ATM machine.
All right, nobody dead.
We're Homicide, and it's lunch.
So have a good day, sir.
Call 911 and someone will take care of you.
Wait a minute. One guy did this?
Stole your ATM over milk?
Little skinny-ass dude. Guitar case.
Drinking milk like there's no more cows.
"Don't vex me, mortal," he says.
- I'm sorry, what?
CASHIER: Listen, if I had a dollar...
...for every hobo skeez that walks
through that door thinks they're God...
...I wouldn't be here.
But this son of a bitch,
he wasn't fooling around.
All right. You get a description
of the vehicle, license, something?
He didn't have a vehicle.
Then how'd he pull your ATM from the wall?
How'd he take it away?
That's what I'm telling you, man.
He pulled it out of here with his bare hands.
[PANTING]
[LIZA SINGING "O MIO BABBINO CARO"]
[MUSIC STOPS]
I'm bored.
Poor little baby girl.
Cooped up in here all the time.
- You want some excitement.
- Yes, I do. Can we just go somewhere?
- Ah!
- How's that? Excited now?
- What'd you do that for?
- Why are you here with me?
- I'm your secret weapon.
- Exactly.
But are you helping me help you?
No, you're not.
You won't even learn the damn tune.
I told you this is important.
- I'm sorry, Mama.
- I'm not your mama.
Now, you might be my baby girl,
but I'm not your mama.
Not yet.
You have to earn that.
[PUCCINI'S "O MIO BABBINO CARO"
PLAYING ON STEREO]
[LIZA SINGING "O MIO BABBINO CARO"]
How is that even possible?
Who is this guy?
No positive ID as of yet. He's a street guy.
We think that this thing has something
to do with his excessive joie de vivre.
Yeah, we found it in the suspect's guitar case.
It's some drug.
A drug did that? Wow.
GORDON:
Nygma found traces of the drug.
He'll have a read on what this is by tomorrow.
Meantime, we'll try and ID the strong man.
Yeah.
FALCONE:
I know your families are upset...
...but tell them everybody
got a piece of the Arkham project.
It was a business decision.
We didn't lose, Maroni didn't win.
Maroni thinks he won.
He thinks he won a great battle.
- We need to hurt him.
- No.
If we don't push back hard,
he's going to think--
Nikolai, that fool will think
what I want him to think.
No pushback, not yet.
In my country, we say,
"Even a fool may bite the king...
...if he has teeth."
Can the folklore, Niko.
We're not in your godforsaken country.
We are here in Gotham,
where we have plumbing, electricity...
...and Don Falcone is the boss.
He's playing that cluck Maroni
on a long line. Done.
Why so angry, Fish?
I speak my mind. ls no crime.
And I assure you in my country,
we have all modern conveniences.
Only difference, ladies.
Ladies are in kitchen or in bed...
...depending on their talents.
I bet your mother was a lousy cook.
NIKOLAI: Don't speak of my mother.
- Or what?
You're gonna hit a lady?
That's enough.
There'll be no bad blood here.
My apologies, Don Falcone.
We need each other. We're family.
Hey.
- Excuse me. You seen this guy, by chance?
WOMAN: No.
Mm-mm.
Seen this guy?
GORDON:
Excuse me.
BULLOCK:
Familiar to you?
Any chance you seen this guy?
Yeah, I know him. It's, uh, Benny.
He's a guitar player. Strung out like a string.
What'd he do?
Uh, nothing bad. He came into
an inheritance, actually, no one knew about.
That's right. A million dollars. Farm, horses,
real nice. You know where we can find him?
Twenty dollars.
Ten.
GORDON: Same as the bodega.
- Yeah, what's with all the dairy products?
Sir, G.C.P.D. Let me see those hands.
Oh. Help me. I need more.
More what? What'd you take? What is it?
It felt so good.
And now I don't feel so good.
Something's wrong.
I need more. Please. You have to find him.
- Find who? The guy that gave you the stuff?
BENNY: Yeah.
The man with a mangled ear.
With a mangled ear. Go ahead.
Stay calm, we got it.
We're gonna help. Just put your--
- No, no, no.
- Hey, hey!
GORDON:
Sir, we need you to calm down.
- Calm down.
BENNY: Unh!
[BENNY GRUNTS]
- I said no.
- Put it down!
[YELLS]
[BONES CRACKING & BENNY YELLING]
BULLOCK:
What the hell?
GORDON:
God help us if that drug gets out.
ALFRED:
Will you look at this shambles?
What would your mother say?
You know, I have half a mind to stick
all this lot straight into the bloody fire.
- No fire.
- We'll see about that.
Come on. Up you get.
Wayne Enterprises is hosting
a charitable luncheon tomorrow.
I took the liberty of accepting their kind
invitation on your behalf, Master Bruce.
Good. ls there breakfast?
Yeah, I'll make you an egg.
Does that mean you'll go?
Yes. I have some questions I need to ask
the members of the board.
- What kind of questions?
- About Arkham.
It seems likely those gangsters were given
their shares in Arkham by Wayne Enterprises.
Well, that's how business is done,
isn't it?
Is it?
My parents didn't do business that way,
did they?
No. No, they didn't, Master Bruce.
The board might not know.
There's quite a bit of clever camouflage used.
Shell companies, offshore accounts
and so forth.
Right. So you learned all of that
from all of this, did you?
Fantastic detective work.
I still want to get the whole lot
and chuck it straight in the fire.
Don't put anything in the fire, Alfred.
- That's an order.
- Right, Master Bruce.
Nothing in the fire.
We are live in downtown Gotham,
where a deadly new drug has hit the streets.
Nicknamed Viper, users of this
mystery drug acquire great strength...
...and a euphoric sense of power,
but only for a few brief hours.
Then without exception,
they die a horrible death.
[CROWD SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[GROWLS]
NYGMA:
It's really quite remarkable.
Viper somehow activates unused DNA.
The body starts to burn calcium
from the skeletal system as fuel...
...hence the victims' cravings
for milk and cheese.
They're desperately trying
to replace the missing calcium...
...but they can't consume enough.
Essentially, their bones crumble,
then they suffocate and die.
- Have you seen anything like this before?
- Nobody has. Totally new.
I can't tell you how thrilled I am--
No new reports for a few hours now. Maybe
they're done. Maybe they ran out of the stuff.
- I doubt it.
- Who would put this on the street?
Why? They're not even selling it.
They're giving it away.
- That's how you create demand.
- For a drug that kills you that fast?
First it makes you king of the world.
There'll be takers.
There'll be mayhem for sure.
But it's skell-on-skell mayhem.
If we keep the decent citizens indoors,
let the scumbags have at it?
Voilà, the end of crime.
Yeah, that's a nice thought, but no.
This stuff seems hard to make, no?
Oh. It takes a high level
of technical sophistication.
A state-of-the-art lab made this stuff.
So who has the biggest
and best lab in the city?
The best is WellZyn.
ESSEN:
But this is not them.
They're a subsidiary of Wayne Enterprises.
Multibillion-dollar corporation.
Why would they do this?
I don't know.
But we might as well start at the top.
Let go of me. Let go of me!
[CHARMAGNE & OFFICERS
SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
[BONES CRACKING]
[CHARMAGNE GRUNTING]
Fascinating. Fascinating.
[REPORTER SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY
ON TV]
Maybe I should hire that guy
to take the casino.
Maybe you should snort some Viper.
Either way, I want it taken.
Sure, we'll take it.
I mean, it's tight as a nut.
Ten armed guards,
blast-proof doors, cameras.
We're gonna lose a few guys,
but we'll take it.
Excuse me. I couldn't help but overhear
your conversation regarding the casino.
Go mind your business.
- I'm sorry, of course. I'm so sorry.
- No.
Tell me. What about the casino?
I know a janitor
who runs the boiler room of the casino.
He could get you inside quite easily.
There are access tunnels
nobody knows about.
- Access tunnels?
- Sit down. Come here.
Thank you, sir. A great honor indeed.
What's your name again?
Everyone here calls me Penguin, sir.
You don't like that name, huh?
Yeah, well, you're wrong. It's a good name.
It works for you.
So how do you know this man?
The janitor?
I have connections.
Reliable, is he?
- I think I can persuade him to be.
- Boss, this guy is a dishwasher in a suit.
Relax.
Is that right, Penguin?
Are you just a dishwasher?
Because I don't get that vibe.
You come off as all humble,
but you got a little player in you, huh?
That's very perceptive of you, sir. Heh, heh.
I guess that's why you're the don.
Well... Heh, heh.
I'm not a dishwasher...
...and this isn't my first rodeo,
so to speak.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
- So you rode some bulls, huh? I knew it.
- Well...
Well, tell all, cowboy.
- Well, my real name is Oswald Cobblepot.
MARONI: Mm-hm.
I think that once you hear my story, you'll
agree that I could be a great asset for you, sir.
Mm.
It's a long, funny story, really, but
the headline, just so you're not surprised...
- I used to work for Fish Mooney.
- Fish Mooney? Hey.
Yes, sir. I was privy to many aspects
of the Falcone family business.
- Until they tried to kill me. Heh, heh.
- Well... Heh, heh.
- Hello. Heh. Suffice it to say--
- Heh-heh-heh.
[PENGUIN GRUNTS]
- That is a funny story.
- Mm.
I'm Taylor Reece, general counsel,
public relations for WellZyn.
- Good morning, gentlemen.
- Thank you for saving us a trip.
We were en route as soon as
we were apprised of your inquiries.
WellZyn is committed
to good community relations.
- What do you know about Viper?
REECE: What we see on the news.
WellZyn has no connection to this tragedy.
We will vigorously pursue
legal action against...
...any individuals making assertions
to the contrary.
Do you think we push a button,
or does she just rewind automatically?
We're looking for an employee of WellZyn's.
Male, with a severely damaged ear.
Yes. Full disclosure, that does raise a flag.
That's Stan Potolsky.
He worked for us for several years
as a biochemist.
Primarily personal-care products.
Shampoos, toothpastes.
So, what happened?
Stan was frustrated that he wasn't
doing more important work.
He grew disgruntled and unstable.
We tried to get him help, but he resisted.
Last April, there was an incident.
He tried to cut off his own ear
during a disagreement with his supervisor.
Guess it was harder than he thought.
We had to let him go.
- Last known address?
REECE: After he was terminated...
...he didn't even clear off his desk.
Just disappeared off the grid.
You knew, didn't you?
You knew all along it was him.
That's why you came to see us so fast.
That's incorrect.
Viper can only be produced
in a state-of-the-art lab, like yours.
Stan Potolsky is a brilliant man...
...perfectly capable of building his own lab.
But you are more than welcome
to examine our facilities...
...with full and proper clearances,
of course.
- Of course.
- We'll get the paperwork started.
Lawyers. Scumbags, the lot of them.
Eh, some of them.
Let's go find Stan Potolsky.
Drive around looking for him? No.
I'll call Dispatch, have them put out an APB.
All right. I'll check with the desk,
see if his name's come up.
- Gordon, right?
- Yeah, who the hell are you?
You gotta come with me now,
nice and quiet, like.
- What are you talking about?
CARBONE: We got a mutual friend.
- Oh, yeah? Who's that?
- Oswald Cobblepot.
Yeah, him.
And if you don't come with me now...
...we're gonna put his head in a bag
and send it to Falcone...
...which would be embarrassing
for you, no?
Or maybe we've been misinformed.
If I'm not ringing any bells here,
you can go on your merry way.
No, I'll come.
CARBONE:
All right, shove over.
GORDON:
Hey, hey!
[SHELL CRACKING]
Welcome. I'm Salvatore Maroni.
I know who you are. What do you want?
- Here's the thing.
- Jim, just tell the truth.
You want a drink, Jim? I'm having
a Negroni. So good with seafood.
Water.
MARONI: So our friend here
told me a fascinating story.
Never heard a story so good.
It's hard to believe it's true.
- It is, it's true.
- Shut up! Shut up!
One more word,
and I'll jam this down your throat.
I try to be civil, Jim.
But I'm not the kind of man
that likes to ask twice.
- So here's how it's gonna go.
- Slow down, Mr. Maroni.
- I don't know you--
MARONI: No, no, no.
You let me finish.
You'll have your turn to speak.
Okay, then.
I want you to tell me the same
exact story that Penguin told me.
What story is that?
MARONI:
You'd better know what story, my friend.
Because if you tell me
the same story he told me...
...then I could believe it's true.
Then I'm happy.
But if you tell me another story--
Oh, Mama.
--Then someone's lying to me. I don't know
which one, then the both of you will die.
- Understand?
- Yes, I do.
Good. So...
...tell me a story, Jim.
Somebody murdered
Thomas and Martha Wayne.
- I caught the case--
- We didn't know each other then.
What did I say? Go put him on the slicer.
No, no, no.
MARONI: If I don't like what I hear,
slice his face, prosciutt.
Oh, I'm sorry, go on.
[SLICER WHIRS]
I was a pawn...
...in a conspiracy between Falcone,
the mayor and the G.C.P.D...
...to frame Mario Pepper
for the Wayne murders...
...with the help of Fish Mooney,
Mr. Cobblepot's employer at the time.
Mr. Cobblepot then told
the whole story to the MCU.
To prove
that I wouldn't betray the conspiracy...
...Falcone ordered me to kill Cobblepot.
I didn't do it.
I let him live.
And here we are.
Falcone, Mooney, the MCU cops...
...none of them know he's alive?
If they did, I'd be dead already.
[LAUGHING]
It's delicious. Ha-ha-ha.
Frankie, bring the Penguin back out here.
The little punk is telling the truth.
Thank you, Jim. Good story.
Told well. A lot of guys
in your situation, they freak out.
There you are, you rat, you snitch...
...you gorgeous turncoat son of a bitch.
Come here, I love you. Mwah.
Be happy, Frankie. We just got
a brand-new weapon against the Falcones.
- It's Christmas.
- Happy holidays. Can I go now?
Oh, yeah. Jim, you can go.
Just so that we understand each other...
...we'll keep all this hush-hush
between us pals.
And if I need you again, I'll call you.
[MOUTHS]
Thank you.
You do that.
MARONI: Look at you, come on.
Let's get you cleaned up. Come on.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING INDISTINCTLY
ON JUKEBOX]
LIZA:
I love you, baby.
- I love you, baby.
FISH: Okay, now...
...you're still putting
too much sex on it.
Keep it clean, like a mother.
I love you, baby.
Good. Better.
Now, act as if you've caught me in a lie.
Not angry. No. Disappointment.
Oh, honey.
There you go. Now, about your hair...
BULLOCK:
There you are.
Where the hell have you been?
Personal business.
You disappear in the middle of a case,
and you can't even tell me why?
That's what "personal" means.
You in some kind of trouble?
Forget it. I don't wanna know your problems.
WellZyn sent by Potolsky's stuff. Grab a box.
- Anything useful yet?
- No, classic geeky loner.
Lived for his work. No wife.
No family. No real friends.
Is it Barbara? She get into something?
Uh... Yeah. Kind of.
Figures. No offense. Need any help?
No, I'm all right. Thanks.
Hey, what do you think about this?
Looks like a friend, no?
Judging by the books, the mascot...
Philosophy professor. Gotham U.
- Worth a shot.
- Amen.
I was just on my way to an appointment.
But, yes, I know Stan Potolsky.
He was a student of mine,
a very brilliant student.
GORDON:
You've stayed in touch over the years.
We have. He may be a biochemist,
but philosophy is a passion of his.
What can you tell us
about WellZyn firing him?
Research for WellZyn
led him into some dark moral corners.
WellZyn said he made shampoo.
Where are the dark moral corners in that?
Shampoo? Heh, heh.
They say that, do they?
No, no. Stan designed
pharmaceutical weapons...
...to be used by combat troops.
Drugs that worked on an epigenetic level.
Imagine an army made up of soldiers
so strong that they can tear a man apart...
...with their bare hands. Of course,
at the beginning, there were side effects.
Yeah, death.
But Viper was the first batch.
They worked out the kinks...
...in the second version, called it Venom.
[COUGHING]
By then, Stan had acquired some clarity.
He appealed to his bosses
to end the program.
They refused. So he went over their heads,
to Thomas and Martha Wayne.
He convinced them to shut it down.
And when they died,
WellZyn immediately revived the program...
...with the blessings
of Wayne Enterprises.
In the end, there was nothing for Stan to do
but to resort to more radical measures.
Killing people. I'm not hearing
a sense of moral outrage, professor.
If you don't mind, I'll reserve my moral
outrage for the true villains of this piece.
You mean WellZyn.
You planned this with Potolsky.
- Yes.
- Where is he? Talk fast, bub.
What are you gonna do?
I'm an old man. I'm dying.
I'll help you die quicker, you terrorist.
Soon Stan will issue a statement
the world can't ignore.
Soon? Today?
- You're already too late.
- Now you tell us where--
You said you had an appointment?
Where are you going?
Bravo! You've asked the right question.
The first step to enlightenment.
[SNIFFS]
God!
[BULLOCK GRUNTING]
- Where is he? Where's Potolsky?
STEINER: Those hypocrites.
Empty altruism will not erase
what they've done.
- They must pay.
- Who? Who must pay?
WellZyn, Wayne Enterprises.
Everyone will finally see them
for what they are.
How? Where's Potolsky headed?
What's altruism?
Charity.
I know where he's going.
HOSTESS: Name, please?
- He's Bruce Wayne. Master Bruce Wayne.
- Just this way. Thank you.
- Thank you.
[ELEGANT CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[CROWD CHATTERING]
WOMAN [ON TV]:
Wayne Enterprises is...
...a helping hand.
A port in the storm.
Ah. That's Ms. Mathis.
She worked closely with your father.
WOMAN:
A shelter for all.
And clean water...
Please sit, Bruce.
It is so good to see you out and about.
Glad to be here.
All of us at Wayne Enterprises
are so sorry for your loss.
So are all you here on the board?
Oh, heavens.
No, we're middle management.
The board members
don't do this sort of thing.
No? Why not?
Well, they're very busy people, Bruce.
Your family created a company
worth billions and billions of dollars.
How awesome is that?
Awesome. I wanted to speak to them
because I found...
...what looks like serious irregularities
in the Arkham project.
Irregularities?
I can assure you, Bruce,
that Wayne Enterprises...
...would never countenance doing business
with criminals. Just wouldn't happen.
I hope so, but I'd like to speak
directly with the board myself.
Can you make that happen?
I can certainly try.
They prefer to communicate with minors
via the usual legal mediation, but--
Good evening.
This is a public service announcement...
...on behalf of all living creatures.
You've heard of a drug called Viper?
That's me. I made it for WellZyn...
...a subsidiary of Wayne Enterprises.
- Is this true?
MATHIS: Of course not, Bruce.
I mean, this man is clearly insane.
GORDON:
The AC plant, where is it?
- On the roof?
CLERK: Straight ahead, staircase.
GORDON:
Clear the ballroom.
I had hoped that a demonstration
using street people would suffice...
...but it seems bad things only truly happen
when they happen to important people...
...like you.
[GAS HISSING]
[CROWD SCREAMS]
G.C.P.D. Everybody out!
[CROWD SCREAMING]
Turn it off!
I can't do that.
Turn it off or I'll shoot!
Go ahead. My work is done.
Turn around, put your hands
behind your head! Interlock your fingers!
That's all right.
You're angry and confused.
I understand.
There's no more need for violence.
Don't shoot!
That's considerate of you.
I'm leaving now.
Go look in Warehouse 39.
- You're not going anywhere!
- I can go anywhere I want!
Don't do it.
[THUD]
[CROWD SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
You really can have
too much of a good thing.
[METAL SCRAPES]
Nothing.
What'd you expect?
It's Gotham.
It's Mathis. I'm outside the site.
They're here.
No, I think we should leave them be.
There's nothing here for them.
We'll review that if they get close.
- It's been 10 minutes.
- I-- I assure you my friend is reliable. Ahem.
You scared, Penguin?
Your voice is doing that shaky thing.
Heh, heh. No, sir. I'm fine.
You don't have to act tough.
Nerves are a good thing.
Perhaps I am a bit jittery, sir.
Good. You should be.
Because if my boys don't make it,
neither do you.
[GUNSHOT & GLASS SHATTERS]
HENCHMAN:
Keep going!
Ah. Take that, Falcone, you son of a bitch.
Huh? I told you, Frankie,
the kid's a player.
He's got a future.
What are you waiting here
like an old lady? Go.
Untie me.
Say "pretty please."
Please.
Ah!
[GRUNTS]
Sometimes I think you really don't like me.
Now, would I be backing your takeover
if I didn't like you?
That stuff with Falcone, well,
we have to look good for the old man.
If he figures out we're working together...
...we'd be cooked. Patience.
- I have no more patience.
- Mm.
The old man has to go.
We must strike soon.
Yes, mm...
...but softly.
[LIZA HUMMING
"O MIO BABBINO CARO"]
Excuse me.
I couldn't help but overhear
that aria you were humming.
- Oh, yes. It's my favorite.
- Mine too.
Ah, well, there you go.
I'm sorry. I just--
I didn't mean to bother you.
My mother sang that to me
when I was young.
Her whole life, she sang that to me.
I hadn't heard it in a while,
and I had to smile because you look...
[SIGHS]
Anyhow, sorry. I'm rambling on.
No, that's okay. Do you wanna listen?
Well, yes. Sure. Thank you.
Let's sit down.
[PUCCINI'S "O MIO BABBINO CARO"
PLAYING ON EARBUDS]
Ripped By mstoll