There's a war coming.
A terrible war. There will be chaos.
Rivers of the blood in the streets,
I know it. I can see it coming.
It's time. Somebody has to take over,
it might as well be me.
- My name's James Gordon. I'm a detective.
- My name is Bruce Wayne.
I promise I will find the man who did this.
Stop or I'll shoot!
He was framed.
To cover up for the real killer.
I know that you own the police department,
probably the mayor.
You can't have organized crime
without law and order.
You snitched, my little Penguin.
- Please.
- Falcone wants a bullet in his head.
Then we know you're with the program.
Don't ever come back to Gotham.
Ah. There you are.
Been all over the bloody house
looking for you.
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
You, my old son, are a terrible liar.
What you got there?
Come on, show me.
Oh, my God, you stupid little boy!
Aw.
It's all right. I'm sorry.
It's gonna be all right.
Hi, I'm Patti. This is Doug.
We're with the mayor's
homeless outreach project.
- We have some sandwiches and soup.
- We got cookies, candy.
Who here likes chocolate?
- Ha-ha-ha.
- Ain't you hungry, Cat?
Yeah, dig in. Take a sandwich.
Sure, go ahead. Plenty for everyone.
Haven't had a sandwich in forever.
Yeah, sure. Take two.
- Hey!
- Hey, lady!
- Oh, fudge!
- Don't worry, I'll go.
Slow down, there, buckaroo.
Stop struggling.
v.1.0
I got you one, but I dropped it.
Yeah, thanks.
- Where is everybody?
- I don't know.
- What do you think?
- I think it's been a long shift.
We give this bum three hours,
then we knock off.
- He was a vet.
- I salute his service. Now he's a dead bum.
People shoot bums all the time.
We might as well look for the tooth fairy.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey, Bo.
How come you weren't here?
- Whoa, whoa. Good morning to you too.
- Where were you?
At a restaurant down the street. Chez Vous.
They had some homeless junkie kid
fell through their front window last night.
- Been taking care of that.
- This is a potential murder.
You're first responder.
Supposed to preserve the crime scene.
He's got a point.
The restaurant that pays me 50 a month
to look out for them.
So I'm gonna babysit a dead wino?
I got a family.
He's got a point.
- Why'd the kid jump through the window?
- He was high.
- Did you ask him?
- Why am I the bad guy?
I'm asking about the kid because
maybe he's related to the victim.
- You're not a bad guy. Just a bad cop.
- Oh! Who are you talking to'!
- Hold on.
- Come on! Come on!
You want it? Any day.
Hey! Oh!
And then Zeb and Smoke went right down.
And that's when that wacky dude
just shot Soldier.
I realized I needed to get out of there.
I ran and I ran, and that's how I ended up
on the floor of that restaurant.
- She used a pen?
- I swear.
A big pen.
But listen, this is not the first time.
Street kids have been disappearing
for weeks now.
By the dozen. No one knows why.
- First we heard about it.
- Why would you?
Nobody gives a crap about us.
- Look, that is proof.
- That's not proof, that's a scab.
Listen, Macky, we're grown-ups.
We're smarter than you.
- Man, whatever.
- You're gonna tell the truth!
It was you, wasn't it?
It was you that killed that poor old man.
You're gonna tell me the truth,
or I swear to God, I'll beat it out of you!
- That man was a war veteran!
- Cat was there. Cat saw the whole thing.
- Ask Cat.
- Relax. No one'll beat you. Who's Cat?
What do you mean? Isn't that what I
just said I was gonna do right now?
Come here. Come here.
- He is 16.
- Yeah, and G-foot, 220.
He can take a punch. Look,
I wasn't gonna beat him. Just scare him.
But if I did want to, I could.
- It would be my prerogative.
- It's illegal.
Ille--?
How now so righteous? Hm?
Not long since you put a man in the river.
You wanna say that a little louder?
- Not everybody heard.
- Since then you've been a pain in the ass.
You think I or anybody here gives a crap
about a dead snitch or your conscience?
- We got our own problems.
- Conscience.
Call it what you want,
I'm gonna do what's right.
- You're beginning to irritate me.
- Get your hands off me.
Hey!
Watch the shoes, clown.
Shift's over.
Come on. Come on.
Come on, seriously.
My pretty baby
When I first came home...
Thank you so much, guys. Truly.
- I'm grateful. I've been waiting for hours.
- No kidding.
- Look like you crawled out of a cemetery.
- Smells like it too.
Open a window back there.
- There you go.
- Yeah. That's-- Thank you.
Forgive me, I am somewhat disheveled.
A temporary setback, I assure you.
- Thank you so much.
- What the hell happened to you, anyhow?
It was my own fault.
Foolish arrogance led me astray.
But I learned my lessons.
I'll be back.
Stronger and smarter than ever.
- Good luck with that, bro.
- Here I am riding around in a lovely truck.
Sharing an ice-cold beer
with my new friends.
My luck's already turned, right?
Dude, anyone ever tell you?
When you walk, you look like a penguin.
No.
Nobody's ever told me that.
He's saying he has a right
to stop me from beating on a mope.
- Damn right.
- How am I supposed to work with this?
Look, Jim, it's not like I can order you
to break the law, but this is Gotham.
You don't bend, you'll get broke.
- I understand.
- I thought you were with the program?
- He is.
- Let's get back to work. Where you at?
If the boy we have is telling the truth...
...there's a couple kidnappers out there
abducting homeless children. In numbers.
They lured them with a food truck from
the mayor's homeless outreach project.
Then they drugged them with a jab
from a big pen.
Why would anyone want to abduct
scraggly-ass orphans in bulk?
Where's the market? They're on the street
because no one wants them anyway.
If they said they were snatching
cute girls, I'd believe them.
Why would anyone want
a lard-ass like Macky?
What is it, Ed?
Guess what I found.
I did a blood test on him
and he had high levels of ATP.
What's ATP?
It's a fast-acting knockout drug.
Used to use it at the old Arkham Asylum.
Bring down troublesome patients.
It's hard to get, no recreational use.
- Okay. That's interesting.
- Anything else?
Thank you, Ed.
Ahem.
Get to work.
And keep this quiet. No press. Not a word.
Shouldn't we tell the public
what's going on? Warn them?
Department policy.
We don't advertise this kind of stuff.
Causes panic. The headlines will read,
"Gotham's Kids Snatched."
Which would be true.
No press. That's an order.
Follow up on the drug. The ATP.
And the Arkham connection.
- Arkham's been closed for, like, 10 years.
- Yeah, 15.
The drug suppliers
might still be in business.
Uh, this happened on Fish Mooney's turf.
Do you wanna see if it's safe for us to go
back there, or is, uh, she still mad at us?
It's a good question.
Bravo!
Don Falcone, what a wonderful surprise.
Welcome.
Thank you, my dear.
- Can we talk?
- Of course.
- Give me a moment to clear the place.
- No, no.
No need to spoil the fun.
Men who are about to die are very honest.
It pays to listen to them.
That's some toast.
I spoke with your man Cobblepot
before he died.
Odd little fellow.
Perceptive.
He told me the death of the Waynes
would bring troubled times...
...for our family and Gotham.
Ugh. What did he know?
Business is good as ever.
No, he was right.
The Waynes and the Falcones
were the pillars of the same house.
We understood each other.
Now that they're gone,
everything is out of balance.
And the Wayne empire is in flux.
Who knows who'll end up in control.
The Maroni family senses weakness.
They'll start making moves and every
criminal in the city will start making moves.
Please, don't lose any sleep over Maroni.
He's number two for a reason.
I never lose sleep over my enemies.
It's my friends that keep me awake.
- Oh.
- Cobblepot told me you say...
...I'm old and soft and ready to be
taken out, and you're the one to take me.
Don Falcone, I would never, ever say that.
I only have deep love and respect for you.
You have been like a father to me.
I'm so happy to hear that.
Let's forget all about it, then.
The babbling of a condemned man.
Ahem. Enough business.
How have you been, my dear?
Thriving, I hope.
Yes. Good. I'm good.
Which of these is your lover?
Please, my heart has been broken
far too many times for that nonsense.
Hm.
I heard you had a lover.
Well, if you're referring to the boy
that I keep around for exercise...
...my lover, he is not.
- What's your name?
- Lazlo, sir.
Lazlo, be good to this woman,
she's very precious to me.
If you break her heart, you break my heart.
Yes, sir.
Give me your hand.
Thank you for being honest.
It means a lot to me.
It shows wisdom...
...and humility.
Out!
Everyone out!
Never, never in his life
my son is away this long.
Nightclubs is his business.
Such hours.
But, always, he comes home to his mother.
His clothes are here.
My son would never leave his clothes.
Oh. So elegant he is.
Yes, I show you.
Damn, Mooney and the cops
must've had him killed.
Looks like. But snitches get bumped.
That's life.
But they won't get away with it.
Not as easy as they think.
- You take things too personally, know that?
- Yeah, I do.
That was a good snitch.
- What are we--?
- Nothing. Mrs. Cobblepot--
Kapelput.
Mrs. Kapelput...
...do you know anyone
who might wanna do your son harm?
Harm?
No, I would feel it.
A mother feels these things.
It's a woman.
Some painted slut has him in her clutch.
A woman? You think?
I'm sure.
So handsome he is.
And so naïve.
Uh, who are you, again?
Uh, detectives
with Major Crimes Unit, ma'am.
Oh, G.C.P.D.
- Like that.
- But honest.
Mm.
Boss, don't get mad at me...
...but I know that look.
Now is too early
to make a move on Falcone.
I know.
Not yet.
I need more money, more men,
more territory. I know.
I'll play this thing
loyal and bide my time.
But I swear, Butch...
...on my sainted mother's grave,
someday soon...
...I am gonna kill that old man
with my bare hands and my teeth.
I'll be holding your shoes.
I just wish that Penguin was still alive.
I didn't make that little punk suffer
near badly enough.
Excuse me, sir?
I couldn't help but notice
the sign on your trailer.
Is it still for rent?
- 100 bucks a week. It ain't much but--
- I'll take it.
- You don't wanna look at it first?
- No. I'm not fussy.
- It's all yours.
- The key?
Hey, sweet truck.
You got that big Hemi in there?
Yes. Yup.
That big Hemi's in there. Somewhere.
Uh, sir, the key?
It's in the door.
Okay.
What's up, players?
- You got any smokes?
- No.
Where are we?
Damned if I know.
I think we're dead.
Harvey. Jim. How marvelous.
Are you still mad at us?
No. Please.
I'm quite fond of you. And you intrigue me.
I knew I'd regret killing you
as soon as I gave the word.
But you know me.
I'm feisty.
What do you know about a man and
woman abducting street kids on your turf?
No foreplay with you. Hm?
Figures.
But you got with the program.
Killed Penguin your own bad self.
I was surprised. Straight arrow like you.
- I guess you misjudged me.
- I guess I did.
You're just a little sinner
like the rest of us.
I'm almost kind of sad about that.
We're looking for a man and a woman.
Middle-aged. White.
Targeting children under 16.
They use a poisoned pen,
if you can believe it.
Oh. Used to be, there was only a market
for nice-looking girls.
That's what I said.
But now there's a new buyer overseas
that'll take anyone young and healthy.
Overseas where? Who's "they"?
Nobody knows.
- What do they want them for?
- Nobody knows.
And no one cares to know.
Ta-da, moo sh...
Sorry. Go on.
They drugged them with a big pen?
That is so creepy.
Ah, you don't wanna hear this stuff,
it's depressing.
What do they use them for? The children.
Nobody seems to know.
And we can't say a damn thing to the press.
Bad PR.
- I can't believe the system is so corrupt.
- You have no idea.
What do you mean?
Oh. Figure of speech, I guess.
Did something happen
you're not telling me about?
These last couple of weeks
you've been different.
Troubled.
Mm.
No.
Been having trouble sleeping, I guess.
The newspapers must get anonymous tips
all the time.
Sure. Yeah.
You mean call it in myself? Heh.
No, I can't do that.
- Gotham Gazette? The news room?
- Wait. No.
I can't talk long. Somebody is abducting
homeless children off the streets.
And the cops are trying to keep it quiet.
Go talk to Captain Sarah Essen of G.C.P.D.
She has got a kid in custody
who can tell you the whole story.
- End the call.
- I gotta go.
Listen, Barbara, when I tell you stuff, it's
between us. You can't do what you just did.
- It was the right thing to do.
- Not the point.
What is the point?
You're right, it was the right thing to do.
Don't do it again. Okay?
Yes, boss.
"Gotham spirals ever downward.
Mayor James under attack.
Vows swift action.
Points finger
at police department's sluggish response."
Etcetera.
- It's just ink.
- Did you give them this?
- Me?
- You've done it before.
On my own case? Never.
It'd be a very stupid thing to do.
Jim?
I didn't call it in.
- I swear.
- Another mystery.
We have a thin lead on the case,
if you'd like to hear it, ma'am.
There's only three companies in Gotham
that stock this ATP.
You need a special license to buy it.
Chances are, one is crooked.
We're looking to lean hard on all three
like they are crooked.
See which one pops.
That was sneaky good.
- Almost couldn't tell you were lying.
- I wasn't lying.
Good morning, Judge Baker.
Thank you, sir. Yes, all three.
Wellzine, Dracotech,
and Quillan Pharma.
You guys have screwed me.
Against my better judgment
I sell you the juice.
I let you guys use my storage space
because, "No problem," you said.
And now look.
Heat. White hot heat.
No problems, my friend.
We're here to take the merch away.
You'll be clean as a whistle.
March?
They're children, damn it.
They're human beings.
Didn't I tell you to check on them
10 minutes ago?
I want another five large.
- But we had a deal already.
- I gotta stand up for what is right, here.
Be fair, sir.
We don't have that kind of cash on hand.
That's your problem. I can wait.
- I thought you was worried about the heat.
- If heat arrives in the meantime...
...I can get rid of the
evidence very quickly.
We have an obligation to deliver.
The Dollmaker doesn't tolerate failure.
- We need those children.
- Well, that's also your problem.
Ha-ha. Ah!
No. Hey, hey-- This
is totally inappropriate.
I mean, we were having
a business discussion here.
You weren't being fair.
Oh, gosh. Cops.
You didn't call the Gazette,
but did your girl call?
- Yeah.
- I knew it.
- I didn't know she was gonna call them.
- Seriously, you gotta control your woman.
I kind of like her the way she is.
These high-class temperamental broads
need firm handling, trust me.
- Trust you? On women?
- Damn right.
All varieties. From house fraus
to movie stars. I love them all.
Now, you, let me guess,
high school sweetheart...
...then a bunch of hos overseas
only made you sad.
And then there's Barbara.
- Pretty much.
- You, my friend, are a monkey...
...riding a race horse.
Good evening. May I help you?
Detectives Gordon and Bullock.
We need to speak to whoever's in charge.
Of course. Mr. Quillan,
detectives are here to see you.
Oh?
Wow. Detectives, hey. What's up?
Nothing serious, I hope.
Cut the crap. We have a warrant to search
the premises. We know what you're doing.
Then you know some boring stuff, then.
I mean, what are you talking about?
- You're peddling ATP to kid-snatchers.
- Oh, my gosh. No.
I mean, we used to stock ATP,
but not since the Arkham Asylum closed.
Uh, I heard that the Wayne Foundation is
planning on reopening the old place again.
But now that the Waynes are dead,
I guess everything's up in the air.
What a world, eh? Nobody's safe.
- Jim!
- Go, go!
Where the hell were you?
Get rid of them now.
Then hose down the room.
Ah! Zack.
Freeze.
Ash! No!
On behalf of all the citizens of Gotham,
I wanna thank you gentlemen.
From the bottom of my heart.
And I wanna promise you, kids...
...we will take care of you
as if you were our own children.
But here's the thing.
The people who victimized these kids
are still out there.
And hundreds of vulnerable youngsters
are still living rough on our streets.
Alone.
Unprotected.
And let's face it, that's
the real crime here.
So, what are we going to do
to help these kids?
Yesterday, I made a phone call
to juvenile services and the G.C.P.D...
...to initiate a humane but tough love
program to get these kids off the streets...
...and into the loving arms
of juvenile services.
- I think that went very well.
- I think so.
- A small toast, Your Honor?
- You read my mind.
Mr. Mayor, where are you sending
all the children that get rounded up?
Foster homes for the cute,
undamaged ones.
Upstate for the rest.
Upstate?
The Alpenia Youth Corrections Facility.
A fine institute.
Prison, in other words.
Forgive me, Your Honor.
- Detective Gordon's our house firebrand.
- No, no, no, that's okay.
Jim. May I call you Jim?
Half the petty crime in this city
is homeless kids.
They need structure.
People who care for them, for the greater
good of Gotham and for the children, see?
I see you're using the child-snatchers as a
pretext to lock up children without a trial.
Thank you, my friend.
Valuable input.
Most refreshing.
Yo, Gordon,
a man's been waiting for you upstairs.
Mr. Pennyworth?
Alfred, please.
It's bedlam, isn't it?
Rough job you got.
Best job in the world.
I wonder if it might be convenient for you
to visit us tomorrow.
Of course.
- Why? ls something wrong?
- I don't know.
Never had a child before.
Nor me.
The boy respects you.
Tea time, shall we say?
Tea time.
- Name?
- Ma'am, there's been a mistake.
I'm not meant to go upstate.
I need James Gordon. He's a cop.
You're allowed a phone call
when you get upstate. Name.
I need to talk to him now.
- He'll thank you for it.
- Not happening. Name.
Bite me, Pig-erina.
Jane Doe.
Hey.
Relax, kid. Juvie's not so bad.
First week, whatever you do, don't
make friends with anyone that's friendly.
When you get into a
fight, go for their eyes.
Hiya, kids. How you doing?
Are you ready to go on a big adventure?
Sit down, young lady.
I said sit down.
Like, now.
Okay.
Next naughty child to stand up...
...gets a black mark.
Right here.
One or two or three...
...I can explain that.
But a busload?
A whole busload of the little bastards.
What am I supposed to say? Oops?
Just tell me it wasn't them, I'm begging
you. Just tell me it wasn't the snatchers.
Bus driver was a man. Guard was a woman.
It could be them.
You're killing me. You're killing me.
We're working it, Your Honor.
I told you everything I know. I told you.
You see that man there?
He doesn't like it when I beat people.
But for you, no objection. Why is that?
Math. The lives of 30 children
versus one scumbag.
So I can beat you like a bongo drum,
and St. Jim here won't intervene.
Give us something.
Okay, okay! No!
The truck. When they came to pick up
the last bunch of kids.
On the side of it,
there was a picture, like a logo.
I didn't wanna say before
because it'll give a bad impression.
- It doesn't reflect really--
- What was it?
There's a blue plate and a silver fork.
- A plate and a fork?
- Yeah. You know, like...
- Like a catering company, like food'?
- Like that, I mean--
You know, but--
I mean, that doesn't mean...
It doesn't mean what?
Look, I don't know
what they do to them. Ah!
Hey. Hey.
All right.
Draw the logo. Uncuff him.
There you go, kids.
Don't worry, everything's
gonna be all right.
That's right. Come on.
- Come on. Come on. Come on.
- Come on.
Go.
Funny thing. By my count, according
to the sheet they gave us, we're one short.
Me too.
Maybe there's one on the bus. Hm.
Shh.
Nope. Weird.
Must be a miscount someplace.
Never mind. We got more than enough.
- We did good.
- Indeed we did.
The Dollmaker will be so pleased with us.
All right, thanks. Nothing. You?
Apparently no companies in Gotham
have a plate and a fork as their logo.
Selling children for food.
Is such a thing even possible?
We've got officers searching all the trucks
on every bridge and tunnel.
But they had a three-hour window.
We can only pray they stayed in the city.
If not, they can be any place by night fall.
Scum-sucking toads. Where are they?
It's not a blue plate. It's
not a fork either. It's a trident.
When you stow this on the ship, make sure
there's room for the doors to open.
- The ship's crew has--
- Let me out!
- Ls anybody there?
Quiet in there!
Hush. Hush.
My eyes! She scratched me. Oh!
Come on, follow me.
Hm. Let me look.
Mm. Uh...
It's nothing. It's a scratch.
We'll get you the doctor.
- You'll be right as rain in no time.
- You sure?
- What was that?
- Hang on.
Well...
You are a very naughty little girl.
Hi.
- What's your name?
- Why is that your business?
Jim.
Where are the kids?
Where are they?
He's not been sleeping.
And when he does,
he has these nightmares.
Now he's hurting himself.
Burning himself.
He's cutting.
- Is he getting professional help?
- Oh, you mean psychiatrists?
Oh, no, none, he won't have them.
No psychiatrists, that's a rule.
You make the rules, don't you?
You're his guardian.
Now, Bruce's father...
...gave me very firm orders
was him and his missus to die.
Now I will raise the boy
the way his father told me to raise him.
Which is how?
Trust him to choose his own course.
He is, after all, a Wayne.
Sounds like a recipe for disaster.
- What do you want me to do?
- He wants you to talk some sense into me.
Haven't I told you to stop creeping up
on people like that. It's bloody rude.
All right then, Bruce.
Talk to me.
I'm perfectly fine.
Alfred's a worrywart.
What'd you do to your hand?
I burned it.
Listen to me, Bruce.
You've been through a terrible experience.
Talking to someone can be very helpful.
You must have seen terrible things
in the war, does it--?
Does it help you to talk about
what you saw?
Yes, a little.
You're not a very good liar.
- Bruce, you're hurting yourself.
- I'm testing myself.
Different. But I appreciate your concern.
I've been following your adventures
in the newspapers.
I feel very sorry for
all those poor children.
Me too.
- I'll give you some money to give to them.
- I'm afraid it doesn't work that way, Bruce.
What way does it work?
Those children need someone
who cares for them.
Like you have right here.
Money won't buy that.
There must be something I can do.
What about clothes?
They all looked awfully ragged.
They did, didn't they?
After all this? You're sending us upstate?
- Selina--
- Cat.
Cat, even if you didn't have
outstanding warrants...
...you're 13. No parents or guardians.
- That's not true. I have a mom.
- Says here she's deceased.
That's not true. She's alive. Someplace.
Be that as it may, we're not allowed
to put you back on the street.
- It's for your own well-being.
- Heh.
Have you been there? Upstate?
- Yes.
- Then you know.
You know.
Go get Detective James Gordon.
He works here.
Cat.
- Police are very busy people--
- Go get him.
Or...
...I'll say you touched me.
Excuse me?
James Gordon.
I'm gonna scream in about three seconds.
Hello? Ah.
Yes, this is he.
Well, I'm looking at your son
right now, and...
...he doesn't look good.
Madam, I assure you,
your son is not trying to trick you.
No, he will die a
horrible death unless he--
No, no. No.
Really, truly, he isn’t joking.
I'm not joking.
I will poke his eyeballs out. And--
How can you say that? You saw
the video I sent. I'm not lying. Heh.
Madam-- Madam. Calm yourself.
If 10,000 is too much, I'm sure we can--
Hello? Hello?
Well, that's disappointing.
She didn't believe me.
You must be quite the scamp.
I got it.
Hello again, young lady.
- How can I help you?
- We need to talk.
So now you wanna talk, huh?
Okay. It's all right.
- Selina, is it?
- Cat.
Cat. You're Macky's friend?
Yeah, I know Macky.
Those bastards nearly got you twice, huh?
You're quite a survivor.
You have no idea.
Suppose I had something
you really, really wanted.
If I gave it to you,
could you get me out of here?
- What do you got?
- I've been watching you.
You're a friend of the boy.
You're not like the rest of these crooks.
The boy?
Bruce?
What do you mean
you've been watching me?
The Mario Pepper guy was a patsy, huh?
- What makes you say that?
- Could you? Could you get me out?
It's possible.
I saw who really killed the Waynes.
Saw him clear as day.