Previously, on Gotham:
I start a new job
in the morning.
A new job?! Congratulations!
I'm coming to work
at the GCPD.
I'm your new
medical examiner.
I have some questions I need to
ask the members of the board.
What kind of questions?
About Arkham.
It seems very likely
those gangsters
are actually given
their shares in Arkham
by Wayne Enterprises.
This nightclub makes
a lot of money.
That's why I want to
re-open it under
your care.
I can have the club?
You're with me now.
What is this place?
Where are we?
Some people think it's a
prison, some think it's Hell.
They took my eyes.
People call him Mace.
He's the one in charge.
Ah!
My name is Fish Mooney.
I'm in charge now.
Here's that song...
♪ When you're smiling... ♪
♪ When you're smiling ♪
♪ The whole world ♪
♪ Smiles with you ♪
♪ When you're laughing... ♪
What's she doing?
♪ When you're laughing ♪
♪ The sun ♪
♪ Comes shining through ♪
♪ But when you're crying ♪
♪ You bring on that rain ♪
♪ So stop your sighing ♪
♪ Be happy again ♪
♪ Keep on smiling ♪
♪ 'Cause when you're smiling ♪
♪ That whole world
smiles with you... ♪
Jim?
Hi.
Where's Jim?
He dropped off his keys,
like, last week.
So screw him anyway, right?
So who are you guys?
Thanks.
Ladies and
gentlemen, the Flying Graysons!
Show them your appreciation!
Thank you from
the Flying Graysons!
Thank you! Thank you!
What's he doing?
Coming through!
Get back in there!
What do you...?
Calm down, now.
Calm down! Stop that!
Come on!
Stop it! Calm down!
Ladies, come on!
I hate you!
GCPD!
Everybody freeze!
♪ The whole world ♪
♪ Smiles with you. ♪
Mwah!
Boo!
Get off, you old bag.
You...
Why did you attack
Mr. Grayson?
No reason.
I don't like him.
I have no idea why he did it.
Beats me.
Wow, you circus people
don't mess around, do you?
I swear, John Grayson,
if you give me
that look one more time,
I will slap you silly.
You wish.
Don't think I can't.
Whoa, kids.
What's the big problem,
anyhow?
The Graysons are a bunch
of arrogant buttheads
is the problem.
The Lloyds are feckless
drunkards,
is more like it.
So it's a family feud.
Graysons don't
get along with Lloyds.
Been that way for years.
It's sort of a tradition.
You guys fight like this
every night?
No.
That was just her idiot uncle
doing his thing.
You know damn well
it must be Lila's fault.
Mary...
What?
Hey.
Sorry the date went south.
Are you kidding?
Best date ever.
Who gets to see a circus brawl?
True.
None of them will talk,
of course.
So I've no idea what
those two were fighting over.
I think they're rival lovers.
Their families have been
fighting since way back,
but this particular fight was
apparently over
a woman named Lila.
She's a snake dancer
in the sideshow.
Wow.
I know.
How cool is that?
A snake dancer.
No, I mean, wow,
you're really good.
People talk to doctors.
I guess so.
I should find this woman
Lila, make sure she's okay.
Might take little awhile.
I'll have a patrolman
drive you home.
Oh... I could come with you.
Lee, this is police business.
Come on, Jim.
I'm dying to meet Lila.
Well, bringing along
medical personnel
is a justifiable precaution,
I guess.
There you go.
Sir... where's Lila?
Lila?
The Snake Dancer.
GCPD.
We need to speak with Lila.
She's not here.
Why? What's happened?
Where is she?
Uh, I don't know.
She was supposed to
be home ages ago.
You a relative?
Uh, I'm her son... Jerome.
Jerome, when did you
last see her?
This morning.
She was here when I
left for the library.
Relax, Jerome,
this gentleman is just here
because Owen and Al
had a disagreement.
Your mother's fine,
gone on a spree, no doubt.
- You know how she is.
- A spree?
Without her hat,
her coat or her purse?
And look at Sheba.
She's distraught.
She knows something's wrong.
The snake does seem
to be agitated.
Sir...
she's what you call
a party girl.
Back in the morning
with her knickers
in a handbag, sure as eggs.
But she didn't take
her handbag, did she?
How fast does an animal
like that move?
Oh, fast walking pace.
They rely on
surprise, mainly.
Let her out.
I'm sorry?
Oh! Oh...
Oh, my God.
You knew.
You knew she was here.
No.
Look at me.
She was like that
when we found her.
Let's talk straight.
Those people out there
are using us
as transplant donors.
We are simply spare parts.
Unless...
unless we do something about it.
How?
I have a plan.
But you must do
exactly what I say.
You do as I say,
and I promise you,
I will get some of us
out of here alive.
That's right.
No, you heard me correctly.
I said, some... of us.
Because the truth of the
matter is some will die.
But we will die with dignity.
We will die for a reason,
and we will die next to family,
and I tell you what...
we are family.
We're all we got.
That's family!
We have one simple choice:
we die here alone on our knees
or we stand up and we fight
with our family!
A couple of riggers
found her right here.
We decided to hide her
on the truck.
We were going to give her
a proper burial as soon as
we got back on the road.
Decent of you.
Who's "we"?
Who else knew?
Just me and the head
of the families.
If an outsider killed her,
what can you do?
An act of God.
If it was one of us,
we always find out.
And we make sure
they're punished.
How?
We have our ways.
And we have ours.
Hook him up.
Morning, partner.
Gonna need a little help here.
No kidding.
I mean, you're kidding, right?
This isn't
an elaborate prank or...?
Tell me about
your mother, Jerome.
She's my mother.
What can I say? I love her.
She's perfect.
Not a very good cook.
Except for that...
Did she have any enemies?
Someone with a grudge?
No.
Boyfriends?
No?
She had lovers.
They're sex partners
really, but not boyfriends.
She didn't want the commitment.
Alphonse Grayson?
Yes, he was one of them.
Owen Lloyd?
Yes.
Any others?
Not that I could put a name to.
How do you feel about
your mother's love life?
I feel fine about it.
If not for
my mother's love life,
I wouldn't be here, would I?
Sex is
a healthy human activity.
Yes, it is.
Do you have any other family?
The circus is my family.
One more time. Why did
you assault Mr. Grayson?
You know why.
Tell me.
He killed Lila.
Why would he do that?
She was gonna choose me
over him,
and he's an arrogant
son of a bitch.
Not gonna let a Lloyd
humiliate a Grayson that way.
How come your families
don't get along?
His great-grandfather
falsely accused
my mother's uncle Barry
of stealing a horse.
When was this?
Before the Great War.
World War One.
Yeah.
For three generations,
your families have been feuding
over a stolen horse?
Yes. And the Lloyds
are still trash.
Blood is blood.
Must be a hell
of a horse.
Why did Mr. Lloyd
assault you?
He killed Lila, and fears
I'm gonna kill him for it.
He says the opposite.
He says you killed her.
Yes, I suppose he would
have to say that, wouldn't he?
It wasn't Uncle Owen.
He could never do
such a terrible thing.
Holy crap, Mary!
How can you be so blind?
Quiet, you.
Yeah, quiet, you.
You're the blind one.
My brother is a man of honor.
Your uncle is
a violent drunk.
Do the math, little girl.
My uncle is an artist.
Your brother is a conceited
muscle-head, like the rest
of you flying douche bags.
I can't believe I ever thought
I loved you.
Enough. Huh?
They're coming.
Are you ready?
Yes!
I said, are you ready?!
Inmate 57A, raise your hand.
57A...
raise your hand.
Step forward.
One moment, please, sir.
We need to talk.
Back up, inmate.
You're in violation.
57A,
step forward!
Excuse me one moment, please.
I'm the new "shot caller" here.
My name is Fish Mooney,
and with all due
respect, for you and I
to have a good
working relationship,
there's some things
that need to change.
Is that right?
What's your name?
None of your damn business
what my name is.
Right. Okay, well...
I know you have a job to do.
And I am more than willing
to give you 57A,
in exchange for
60 crates of water, 30 blankets,
50 pounds of fresh fruit,
and a few magazines.
What if I refuse?
What will you do?
Well, I'd be willing
to give you 57A,
just not alive.
We need them alive.
Exactly.
I'm gonna count to three.
You'll disappear
or get a severe beating.
I'm gonna take that as a no.
One...
two...
It's simple economics.
Our lives are worth something.
60 crates of water,
30 blankets...
You...
you're coming with me.
The manager is gonna be
very unhappy with you.
I would think this manager
wouldn't be too happy
with you either.
So if he wants
to talk to me,
I'll be right here.
Manager doesn't come down here.
Well, looks like
we have a standoff.
I'll tell you what.
I can be flexible.
So I'll go talk to this manager,
but while I'm gone,
you're going to stay right here,
as our guest.
How's that sound?
We'll be back.
Yeah!
Wait, back up a little.
So you set the snake loose?
Yes, ma'am.
To track down the body?
Snakes have an excellent
sense of smell.
Well, now I know.
And your prime suspects
are a clown and an acrobat?
Yeah.
Ain't this one a doozy?
Your victim, Lila Valeska,
was killed by
a large knife or hatchet.
Multiple blows to the
head and upper torso.
Around 3:00 yesterday afternoon.
From 2:30 to 4:15,
both Grayson and Lloyd
were in the ring
for the matinee.
Well, how precise
is that time of death?
Give or take
45 minutes.
Still possible then,
but cutting it close.
Hold and press your guys,
but keep looking.
Yeah, boss. Forensics is
working the crime scene now.
We're going through
her phone records.
All right!
We're gonna send
the rest of you home now,
but the investigation
is ongoing.
Nobody leaves town.
And listen up.
No more fighting!
Look where your friends are.
What good is this feud
doing you?
I like it when
you act all tough.
"Nobody leave town."
Sounds better when you say it.
I feel like we should
finish up our date.
Do you want
to come over tonight?
I can cook you dinner.
Sure. That sounds good.
Good.
Get some rest.
I will try. See you later.
I have to ask.
If you were to guess, who
do you think killed Lila?
I try not to guess.
I work the suspects
and I wait on forensics.
Excuse me.
Am I speaking to
Detective James Gordon?
Yes.
Then this must be Dr. Thompkins,
the medical examiner.
I'm sorry, how did
you know who we were?
My name is Paul Cicero.
I'm a psychic
with the sideshow.
Lila Valeska was
an old friend of mine.
A psychic. I see.
How could I help you,
Mr. Cicero?
I sense that you don't think
Owen or Alphonse are guilty.
You must be psychic.
In which case,
perhaps you'd like to hear
the message
Lila sent me
from the other side.
Thanks, Mr. Cicero,
we're not quite looking at
the other side just yet.
As you wish.
I'm merely a messenger.
What's the message?
Thank you, Doctor.
Lila told me
that the servant
of the Devil
lies in the garden
of the Iron Sisters.
The Iron Sisters?
What does that mean?
I don't know.
We'll get right on it.
I don't think sarcasm
is your métier, James.
Make of the message
what you will.
Good day to you both.
Well, that wasn't
very open-minded of you.
Oh, come on, Lee.
He's a fraud.
He's gonna go straight
to the press
and say he's consulting
on the case.
He's looking for publicity.
Maybe.
If you were gonna send a message
from beyond the grave,
don't you think
priority number one
would be the killer's name
and not a riddle?
Who knows how it works?
All right.
I'm not gonna argue with you.
Good.
Later, then.
Later.
They called to confirm
your meeting with the board
of Wayne Enterprises tomorrow.
Excellent.
I was afraid
they'd postpone again.
Well, I'll say it one more time.
I think that, uh,
it's an incredibly bad idea,
Master Bruce.
I think it's reckless,
I think it's premature,
and, quite frankly,
I think it's bloody dangerous.
And we've already been over this
100 times, Alfred.
My mind is made up.
Can you pass me
that file over there?
The file...
Well...
I've said my piece.
If we're both found
dead in a ditch,
don't blame me.
Ta-da.
Nah.
No?
Jim loves me in this color.
It's too obvious.
You gotta dress like
you're not trying,
like you're on your way
to go meet
some other guy.
To go... sailing,
or whatever.
Really? Sailing?
Okay.
Oh, my God.
You like?
Oh, my God!
What's wrong?
No, it's good.
It's my sister's recipe;
she's a really,
brilliant cook.
I was thinking
of my sister,
and it came to me:
Mm-hmm?
I think I know
what the blind man's
message means.
The servant of the devil
lies in the garden
of the Iron Sisters?
Oh?
It's Arkham Bridge.
Hmm?
The Iron Sisters.
Arkham Bridge.
The towers.
They're called, uh,
Mary and Betty?
Mmm. I remember,
as a kid,
we used to call
them that, but...
Right. And there's a park,
um, under the towers
on the Gotham side.
A garden? It all fits.
Lee...
it fits an
impossible story.
He didn't speak
with Lila Valeska;
she's dead.
So you say!
Come on, you're a doctor.
A scientist.
There are plenty of things
in this world
that can't be explained
by rational science.
Yeah, people who enjoy
folk dancing, for instance.
Doesn't mean ghosts exist.
You're very arrogant
in your certainty.
What if this is
a clue to a murder?
The poor woman!
Fine. I'll go myself.
Thank you.
Sure.
I'll come with you.
Okay.
We'll go together.
First thing in the morning.
Morning?
Now?
You want to go now?
It's only a half a mile away.
It's dark.
I have a flashlight.
So what are we looking for,
exactly, do you think?
I know, I know.
This is probably a
complete waste of time.
Thank you for
doing this.
No problem.
But, uh, let's not make
a habit out of it, okay?
This is no place
for a lady.
Ha!
What do you
mean, "ha"?
You're a hypocrite.
You say you want
a strong woman
to share this crazy life
you've chosen,
but when push
comes to shove,
you want me to stay home
and bake cookies.
Not cookies,
necessarily.
Pie. Any kind of pie.
Ha, ha!
So if someone were
to throw something
from a car on the bridge,
this is where it would land.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Lee...
THFC.
What does that mean?
The Hellfire Club.
It's a Satanist cult.
Committed a string
of ritual murders.
But they haven't been active
for a decade or more.
I guess they're back.
No.
No, I don't think so.
Hey, Sarge, I'm gonna need
a couple of mobile units
to pick some people up.
But listen...
they need careful handling.
Sir, they're in
three and four.
Thanks, Zeke.
Neither of them knows
the other one's here, right?
Right, like you said.
Ah, good work.
Just bear in mind
that you could be wrong
about all of this.
I will bear
it in mind.
I will, but
I'm not wrong.
So go on home now, lady.
Hey.
We were having
a perfectly lovely evening.
I am not the
one who wanted
to go out searching
for Satanist hatchets.
You... know what I wanted to do.
You're right.
Uh-huh. I'm sorry, what?
I tend to get
overly enthusiastic
about things.
It's an issue for me.
My mom always said...
Oh, who gives a crap
what my mom said, right?
Have a good night, Jim.
Let me know
how it all turns out.
Good night, Lee.
Wait!
What you said earlier,
about hypocrisy,
sharing lives...
You're right. Let's go.
I'm what?
Right.
Good evening,
Mr. Cicero.
Sorry to bring you
down here so late.
Good evening, Detective Gordon;
Dr. Thompkins.
How did you...
He smells your perfume.
We solved the message
Lila sent you.
Oh?
Took us to Arkham
Bridge Park.
We found a hatchet there
with Satanist symbols
scratched into it.
Dear lord.
You know what that hatchet
means, Mr. Cicero?
Tell me.
It means you're
an accessory to murder.
Such drama.
I merely passed along a message.
A message
from the dead.
Didn't happen.
Which means
you invented the message...
which means you had someone
plant the hatchet
for us to find.
You wanted us to think
Satanist were responsible
for Lila's death.
You're protecting somebody.
Lila spoke to me.
That's all.
You know,
a hatchet is a clumsy ploy.
You wouldn't try it
unless you were desperate.
Which suggests
you're protecting someone close.
Someone you love.
This fantasia
was conjured
in your blinkered mind.
If you could only see
what I see...
Hi, Jerome.
Please.
Take a seat.
You know Mr. Cicero,
from the show.
Yes, sir.
Hello, Mr. Cicero.
Good evening, Jerome.
Do you know why you're here?
Did you find out
who killed my mother?
You killed your mother, Jerome.
Me?
You killed her up on that hill
and Mr. Cicero let you clean up
in his trailer.
He told you to scratch
the Satanist stuff
on the hatchet
and throw it
off the bridge.
Sir, that's... absurd and...
and offensive.
But it's the truth.
What I don't know
is why this man
risked so much
to help you.
I think he's your father.
You don't know
what you're talking about.
My father was a sea captain.
Am I wrong,
Mr. Cicero?
Yes.
He was a sea captain.
His name was Sven Karlsen.
He died at sea.
What was the name of his ship?
He worked on a lot
of different ships.
The one he went down in.
She never said.
We can do a blood test
to prove I'm right.
It takes only half an hour
to get a foolproof result.
Isn't that right, Dr. Thompkins?
Yes.
Save yourself a needle.
I do hate needles.
I'm sorry, Jerome.
What are you talking about?
He's right.
I am your father.
No, you're not.
Why would you say that?
You must have suspected
the truth.
You're not my father.
My mother would never...
Your mother was
a cruel woman;
she was often unkind to me,
but she did once love me,
in her way.
And she loved you very much.
That's why she gave you
a better father.
My mother
was a cold-hearted whore
who never loved anyone.
And she'd never touch
a pathetic old creep like you.
All these years,
do you think I was kind to you
because I'm such a good man?
If I wasn't your father,
would I help you as I have,
after what you did?
My father... Hm.
I'll be damned.
Oh, that's very funny.
Ba-doom-shh!
Looks like the bitch got me
with a zinger in the end.
Why did you kill
your mother, Jerome?
Oh, you know how mothers are.
She just kept pushing.
And I'm like, fine, Mom.
Be a whore.
Be a drunken whore, even.
But don't be
a nagging drunken whore.
You know?
Don't come yell at me
to do the dishes
if you've been banging
a clown in the next room!
You know?
Long night, huh?
Guess it got kind of ugly.
Yes, it did.
You okay?
I'm good.
Truly.
It was ugly, but it was also
kind of thrilling.
Thrilling?
Thrilling and scary.
Like-like looking
down a deep, dark tunnel.
Thanks for letting me be there.
You are an unusual woman.
You just don't know many women.
Can we go home now?
Mm-hmm.
Hello, Penguin.
Victor.
How nice.
Don Falcone thinks
you're messing up.
You don't know
how to run a club.
Your numbers...
stink.
With all due respect...
I didn't come here to talk.
Good manners cost nothing,
you know?
Relax.
He's harmless.
Say hi, Butch.
Hi.
Falcone didn't want
to throw him away,
so I worked on him
in my basement
for a couple of weeks.
He's a whole new man.
Right, Butch?
Yes, sir, Mr. Zsasz.
Butch knows the club scene
up and down.
He'll help you out.
But he's...
He's Butch Gilzean.
He's loyal to Fish Mooney.
And he'll do...
exactly what you say.
Really?
Really.
Hey, Butch,
dance for me.
I do good work.
Good morning, everyone.
Good morning, Bruce.
Welcome to Wayne Enterprises.
So happy to see you.
Thank you for
meeting with me.
I have some questions
regarding Wayne Enterprises
business affairs.
Of course.
It's your company, after all.
Fire away, young man.
I have two main areas
of concern.
Underworld involvement
in the Arkham Project.
And chemical weapons
manufacture
at our Wellzyn affiliate.
That's great.
Congratulations.
We wanted to thank you.
If you hadn't figure
out who killed Lila
and talked to sense
to us the way you did,
our families never
would have reconciled,
and we could've never
gotten together.
Just doing my job.
Hey, if we have a son,
we'll name him Gordon.
Well...
we'll discuss that,
but we're certainly
very grateful.
Sure.
Why so happy?
Happy customers.
That's not it.
It's something else.
You got laid, didn't you?
That's impressive.
You slept somewhere
without razors
and you smell like ladies' soap.
Easy catch.
I can only conclude
that high-level individuals
or groups
within Wayne Enterprises
have colluded
in corruption,
bribery, racketeering,
and unethical medical research.
Thank you for
that input, Bruce.
I'm so sorry if
you've been alarmed
or upset by these
shocking stories
and rumors
you've been exposed to.
These are much
more than rumors.
We'll look into them thoroughly
and carefully, of course.
Bruce, let's be fair.
You've told us nothing with any
substantive proof behind it.
I haven't told you all I know.
No?
What else is there?
I hope you do look closely
into these issues.
Because I'll be raising them at
the next shareholders' meeting
with a view
to possible legal action.
Dear me.
Legal action?
These are all
very deep waters
for such a young man.
My youth is not relevant.
Except that if I were a man,
I would be chairing this board.
And I would be sure
that Wayne Enterprises
was run honestly.
Thank you for your time.
The manager says
you have a deal.
You go up and see him,
I stay here.
What's your name?
Schmidt.
Your first name.
Thomas.
Welcome.
Why don't you
take off that heavy gear
and relax?
My family's gonna show you
a good time.