Previously on Gotham:
- I wish something would happen to Falcone.
- Who would take over then?
Let me guess.
Maroni had nothing to do with
the armory job.
You have a mole obviously.
Someone close to you.
Arkham Asylum.
Security guard for nut jobs?
Criminal nut jobs. Yeah.
Metal needles were inserted to the brain.
Electricity was applied
to his frontal lobes.
I want you to find out
which one of our inmates did this.
Well done, Aaron.
Exactly like I told you.
Now you are my best work so far.
No. Oh, no, no.
The merchandise has gotta be mint...
or you won't get a dime.
My God.
Jack.
Hi, lrvvin.
Where's my stuff?
Aaron Danzig...
6'4", 225, mental age of a young child.
We believe he's under the control
of this man.
Jack Gruber.
In Arkham off a rape-murder beef.
We can't find any records on Gruber
prior to his incarceration.
So we're guessing Gruber is an alias.
We're sending his prints nationwide,
see if we could find another name.
Whoever he is, he's clever and angry...
and a grave public menace.
The commissioner is deeply concerned
and he is on his way here...
to talk to all of you right now.
You know what that means
and you know...
Jim?
- Captain.
- Hey, partner.
- Hi.
- You're out of your jurisdiction.
- Captain, this is my case.
- Jim.
- Get out of here.
- My case.
No, no, no. The captain is right.
You need to leave
before the commissioner gets here.
Why?
Because he holds you responsible
for all of this and... Oh, fudge.
He's here. And you're there. Side step.
- Captain Essen.
- Good morning, commissioner.
Officer Gordon, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
- Why are you here?
- I have a better question.
Why are you here, commissioner?
Excuse me?
This is the first I've seen you down here
with the rank and file.
You must be desperate.
Follow me.
Really nice knowing you.
Bring your friend Bullock.
I hate you.
It wasn't my idea, it was your friend.
He came up with the double-cross,
made me go along.
- You have a mind of your own, don't you?
- Hey, come on.
See?
Ha, ha. I kept your gadgets safe.
I know what it means to you. All of your...
experiments.
Oh, I appreciate that.
Please.
You don't have to kill me.
I don't...
have to do anything.
I'm free.
You know the funny thing? I think
it was my time in Arkham that freed me.
I mean, in here.
Now I see the world for what it really is.
An abandoned factory
full of broken machines.
Some...
very few...
can be fixed.
Most...
just have to be scrapped.
Danzig, hold him, please.
Please.
Please. No, stop, please.
Two maniacs on the loose makes the whole
Arkham project look kind of shady, huh?
The moneymen want results fast I bet.
You're strangely self-righteous.
It was you that let them escape.
Blame me all you want.
My name is already mud.
Those two will still be out there.
And that means you need me.
James.
Why did you become a policeman?
Your father was the district attorney.
A proud station for a man of substance...
you would think that would inspire a son
to practice law.
I'm enforcing the law.
You wanna talk about dad
or catch Gruber and Danzig?
Where do you get that rebellious fire
in your belly?
Can I take this opportunity to say
that I have no rebellious fire here.
Jack Gruber is out there.
Planning a catastrophe.
I know the man.
I know how he thinks.
- I know what he'll do next.
- Which is what?
That I'll keep to myself.
I guarantee I'll bring in these two men.
But first I need you to reinstate me
as detective first grade in the G.C.P.D.
Extortion, Officer Gordon.
Twenty four hours?
- What?
- You've got 24 hours to bring these men in.
You don't, you can both spend
the rest of your careers down at Arkham.
That will be all, detectives.
- What the hell just happened?
- It's okay. It's gonna be fine.
- Yeah?
- We just gotta catch the bad guys.
- Where are we going?
- I don't know.
What? You just told him...
you knew what Gruber
was gonna do next.
I lied.
Please.
Don Falcone.
Have mercy.
We're family.
I know, son.
I know it's hard.
A young man like you.
Doesn't seem fair.
Please.
Don Falcone, please!
This whole area used to be slums
when I was a boy.
You've come a long way.
Some of your people are looking for you,
you know.
But you're the one I wanted to see.
I've worked so long all my life
to get where I am.
So long I forget why I wanted to be here.
Well, you wanted to be someone
and you are.
I mean, look at all the stuff you have.
You're a good girl, Liza.
You need to find a young man
and get married, have babies.
It's not fair of me
keeping you cooped up here...
doing my house work.
You'll never find a good husband here.
Anyhow, if you'd like to...
get out in the world,
I was thinking I could...
set you up with a bakery
or some type of business like that.
So...
you can be independent.
That's really nice, Mr. F.
Thank you.
But I would rather be here with you.
You would?
I like it here.
You make me feel safe.
Well, good.
I like having you here.
Maybe I'll try to get a little work done
before dinner.
Making something special tonight.
What are you laughing at?
Ah, it's good to be back.
Only a man from an asylum
would say that.
You're like a rollercoaster
except you only go down.
Wouldn't that make him
more of an elevator?
You have anything useful? Got less
than 20 hours before I lose my job.
I do have something useful.
- And it is?
- I cross-checked fingerprints.
The clinically insane Jack Gruber of
Arkham, he's a figment of the files.
The man is really a career criminal
by the name of Jack Buchinsky.
- How is that even possible?
- Easy to bribe someone to change records.
He wanted to be transferred to Arkham.
It's really good work, Ed.
What's this Batinski's deal?
It's Buchinsky. It's all in the files.
Miss Kringle.
- I believe you left this on my desk.
- It's a riddle.
It's a cupcake with a live bullet
sticking out of it.
- It's a riddle.
- It's menacing and weird and inedible.
Thank you for the files, Miss Kringle.
This Buchinsky and his partners
pulled four successful bank robberies.
Killed six along the way
before G.C.P.D. caught him by accident.
- He never named his accomplices.
- He's in prison.
He hears Arkham is opening its doors.
He uses connections and gets a new identity
as patient Gruber.
- He must have good connections.
- Right.
When the rest of the nuts
get transferred to Arkham, voila.
So he had partners, huh?
Yeah. G.C.P.D. never identified them,
still out there.
Yup. We find them, we'll find him.
Easy enough, huh?
Detective.
A hit.
What have we got?
Hey, detective.
We dusted for prints, two sets.
Gruber and Danzig. Just like we thought.
- Thanks.
- All right.
Van checks out. It was them.
- Our man's an electronics freak, right?
- Yeah.
Think he went shopping?
He's dead. Fried like a donut.
Turn around slowly,
let me see those hands.
Hey-
Hey, buddy.
Aah! No! No!
Get back in the store.
Please, there's been a terrible
mistake. I am Don Falcone's housekeeper.
Fish? Thank God.
Why did you have to pull me out like that?
You scared me.
It's time, Liza.
I'm gonna make my move on Falcone.
And don't be scared, baby girl.
I got this.
Mr. Falcone, we have your girl Liza.
Would you like to see her again?
Yes, I would.
She'll be glad to hear that.
For a fit young woman,
she has a low pain threshold.
Please, no. Stop.
An intermediary
will be in contact with you soon.
Don't hurt her. She's a civilian.
Hello?
What now?
Now we let him sit and think
about his life for a while.
The electrocutioner.
- Cute. No pressure.
- Don't worry. We'll get him.
- We got 17 hours to do so.
- I love the name.
It's catchy. It has drama.
The electrocutioner.
Speaking of which, given the
mode of attack, may I suggest...
you both wear your galoshes
while you're out in the field.
- Galoshes?
- In the event of electrical misadventure.
Your footwear should be insulated.
No, Mom. I'm not gonna wear my rubbers
on the case.
Nygma, give them here.
Seriously?
All right. So, what do we know?
Gruber wasn't too happy with lrvvin.
Maybe they were partners in crime.
Irwin turned on him.
- Gruber took the fall.
- Detective Gordon.
- Dr. Thompkins.
- My friends call me Lee.
Congratulations. You got your job back.
- Or not, depending. It's good to see you.
- Is it?
I know you're caught up with the escape.
That's why I'm here.
Is everything okay?
It must be chaos down there.
- We're getting by just fine.
- Ahem.
Oh, right.
This is my partner, Harvey Bullock.
- Detective Bullock.
- Who's your little friend there?
Oh, this is why I'm here.
- A woman in my wing is a pagan sorceress.
- Of course.
She's very popular.
Inmates make dolls to look like people
that they want to curse.
They give it to her to curse them
in exchange for soda and candy.
I curse you. You never give me candy.
I asked if Gruber had ever given her
a doll to curse and she said yes.
This is the doll. His name is Mr. M.
You owe me
for a double six-pack of root beer.
Mr. M.
- Mr. M.
Who does this look like to you?
I told this guy, I said, "Maurice...
we've pulled half of your teeth.
What are you waiting for?
The tooth fairy?"
So you know what Maurice does?
He smiles.
I'm gonna take out another.
I go to his molar.
Gotta get Mario and Gabe
to help me pull it out.
Do excuse me.
All right. We're pulling it,
we're pulling it, right?
Finally, we get it out.
The thing is this big.
- Yes?
- Come see me. I need you.
I'm on my way.
What's wrong?
Somebody took Liza. Come. Quickly.
Fish.
Sly devil.
You took her.
You're mine now.
I'm trying to tell this guy, let him talk.
He's trying to talk but I don't understand
him because he's got no teeth. Okay?
So I'm saying, let him talk. Clean him.
He's gonna tell us something.
Don Maroni, sir, forgive me.
Such fun we're having.
But I regret that I must run away.
If you'll let me.
My mother is sick.
A sick mother is a sick mother.
Go.
Hey.
Penguin, you all right?
Hey, kid, what...?
What's going on here?
My eyes are burning.
I don't know what happened.
It was like a silent bomb.
- You know who did this, right?
- Who?
A few years ago, Jack Buchinsky and
partners unknown knocked over four banks.
Killed six people.
Buchinsky went down for life.
His partners were never caught.
You're one of those partners.
One that took his share
and sold him up the river, I expect.
What guy was this?
Bu...
Who?
Well, he's out there looking to hurt you.
He doesn't care who else he hurts.
- Women, kids.
- Hey.
That's not my fault.
Help me do the right thing here,
Don Maroni.
- Let me place you in protective custody.
- Heh, heh.
- Protective custody?
- Yes.
Bait, you mean.
We catch our bad guy,
you get rid of a dangerous nuisance.
- We both come out ahead.
- Excuse me?
Hello?
I must be going.
Very urgent business.
With Falcone.
All right.
Make yourself at home.
Hey, sweetheart.
Get me a double espresso, extra sugar.
I'm Barbara.
Barbara Kean.
My parents. They live here.
It's very nice to see you, Barbara.
Isn't it, Everett?
Yes, very nice.
It's nice to see you too.
You've been well?
I hope.
Yes.
And you?
Splendid.
Are you staying the night?
Uh, if that's all right.
In fact I, I thought maybe
I could stay a few days.
If that's...
Oh, I see.
Yes, of course.
I'm sure you're going to be
frightfully bored.
But stay until the weekend.
By all means.
Thank you.
How's that young man of yours?
James.
The policeman.
All well, I hope?
Yes.
He's well. Thank you.
Good.
We're very happy-
Very haPPY-
You guys are hungry for this.
What do you do for excitement?
Remember the joke about the two cops and
the undertaker that go on a fishing boat?
When you use a goat as bait, shouldn't the
goat be out in the jungle, not in the house?
This house is the best defended spot
in Gotham.
Buchinsky is crazy
and arrogant and resourceful.
Wherever Maroni is, he'll come after him.
He'll enjoy the challenge.
Hey there.
Hi, boss.
How long have I been unconscious?
Couple of hours.
Oh, my gosh.
I must go.
My, my poor mother is...
Your mother can wait.
It's her heart.
Poor thing.
Valves.
She might be taken at any moment.
But... But by all means,
of course, she can wait.
When you woke up before,
you said you had urgent business...
with Falcone.
I did?
I said that, did I?
Carmine.
Some people have called me
about your girl Liza.
They want me to help make a deal.
I didn't think it was going to be you.
I'm sorry.
I'm just an intermediary.
I just wanna help.
Please, my dear, stop.
I know this is you.
Be honest.
- It's me.
- Of course it is.
How long have I known you?
You're the smart one in the family,
didn't I always say so?
She won't be hurt.
Leave Gotham, that's all.
Leave Gotham, never come back.
You can take her with you.
Agreed.
That's the right decision.
I'll make the arrangements.
You were always my favorite.
Wait for my call.
He's leaving?
You did it?
Boss.
The genius, the vision.
You brought down the old man. Finally.
Let's celebrate.
Butch, this is not the time to celebrate.
He was a great man once.
You don't think somebody
would take him out if he stayed on.
I am doing him a favor
and giving him an easy way out.
I owe him...
at least that.
Of course. You're right.
It's best for everyone.
How did he sound?
Sad.
Look at me.
Is there something you're not telling me?
No.
You're gonna have to leave town with him.
String him along for a while.
Do you think you can do that?
- Sure.
But you like him though, don't you?
Well, I can like him, can't I?
He's been a perfect gentleman.
He could've done anything...
and he never laid a hand on me.
Liza, you can like him all you want.
But you can never tell him the truth.
I know that.
Sir.
Let me go to work.
No.
No?
If Fish and the others...
And there must be others.
If they all want me to step away so badly,
maybe it's time.
Why not?
Why am I still here fighting?
For what?
For respect.
You're Don Carmine Falcone.
Respect?
Who cares?
They all want me to go live
in the country with Liza.
I would like that.
That's what I want too.
So why not do it?
Please don't talk that way, sir.
Just me on my own...
I can take out Fish's crew easy.
You're not listening, Victor.
Your job is to keep me and Liza safe
through the coming transaction.
That's all.
Yes, sir.
- Miss Kringle.
- Ah! What?
What?
The cupcake is sweet, the bullet is deadly.
A beautiful woman is a dangerous thing.
Uh, listen, I...
That is so...
I don't... I don't even know
what to say to that.
Nygma, you perv, back off.
Can't you see
the lady doesn't want you bugging her?
Hey there.
Hey, now. Who's bugging who?
I'm just... I'm just...
What's green and then red?
Frogs in a blender.
Walk away, Nygma.
Walk away.
I'm very sorry if I offended you, Miss
Kringle. That was not my intention.
- Do you hear that?
- Go.
Thank you.
He is so weird.
I have no business with Falcone.
I swear on my mother's life.
May God strike her dead
with horrible torments if I'm lying.
Okay then, my friend.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
Go see your morn.
- Give her a kiss from me.
- Thank you.
What the hell's going on here?
- Hey, hey!
- What's going on?
Ah, there's the one.
Under that funny looking fella there.
Take him to the truck.
They didn't cook, just stunned.
I expected more oomph.
You want oomph, Jack?
Ah.
Officer Gordon.
Nice shoes.
Detective Gordon.
Hands up, both of you.
You might wanna drop that.
Why fight me, Gordon?
Who here deserves your protection?
Any of them?
- All of them.
- Even Maroni? Please.
Just let me kill this false friend
and get on with my life.
All this fight, and for what?
I'm putting you back in Arkham, Jack.
That's closer to the mark now,
isn't it, Jim?
You need to win, don't you?
You pretend to care about the law but in
your heart, it's all primitive ego...
and your lust for blood and power.
You just hate to lose.
You know what? You're right.
I do hate to lose.
Congratulations, young man.
New day.
Next man that tries to take away my shield,
one way or another, I'll make him eat it.
Say again.
New day, commissioner.
I hope you have some nasty pictures of him,
because I bet what you said was very rude.
I'm done being careful.
You think you've been careful so far?
Men like Commissioner Loeb
are never gonna trust me.
- You think you've been careful so far?
- So why play nice?
- You think you've been careful so far'?
- Don't worry, I know what I'm doing.
Let's go grab a beer.
Now you're messing with my mind.
I need something stronger than beer.
Hush, young man.
I can hear you sigh.
Sorry, sir.
Let him be.
It's good to see you, old friend.
I am so sorry
it took me so long to get here.
Such a day I've had.
I won't even tell you.
But I'm here.
You were right about Fish.
It's her that's taken Liza.
Sir, allow me.
I must tell you what I've discovered.
You're not gonna want to hear this.
Speak.
Liza was planted on you by Fish.
She belongs to Fish.
This was a setup from the start.
She found a girl that looked just like
your mother and trained her to... Unh!
No.
I'm sorry.
- Prove that.
- How?
I can't.
I just know.
You're wrong.
When have I been wrong?
Hello, Fish.
Don Falcone.
We will meet at my place.
Acceptable?
Yes.
Is she there? ls Liza there now?
- Can I speak to her?
- No.
What time?
In an hour.
I'll be there.
Fish.
Don Falcone.
How's this work?
Liza is close by.
All I need for you to do is sign papers.
Relinquish all control of the family...
and then you're both free to leave.
Papers.
You think papers make a don?
I'm offering you a way out, Carmine.
I appreciate that. Thank you.
But I need to see her first.
Before I sign anything,
I need to know she's all right.
She's fine.
I need to see her, or no deal.
Are you all right?
I'm okay.
How long have you known Fish Mooney?
Huh?
I don't.
I just met her now.
No.
A little bird told me
you and she have been friends for a while.
No.
Told me that she told you stuff about my
mother so that I'd get all caught up in you.
Because Fish knows,
you know, about my mother.
You know how much I love my mother.
Because we talked about her all the time,
you and me.
Remember, Fish, back in the day?
I do.
It seems as though a little bird
has been making a bit of mischief.
Yes...
that's what I had hoped.
But the truth is plain to see.
I'm very disappointed
at my own stupidity.
I'm sorry, Liza.
Is that your name?
I'm sorry you had to get mixed up in this.
Because I'm sure
you're a good, honest girl, really.
No.
I want these two alive for now.
Lock them up some place.
Don't bother yelling for help.
All of your people are dead.
Carmine, you have to under...
I can forgive all kinds of betrayal
and dishonesty.
But my mother...
How dare you use
my sainted mother against me?
That's wrong!
- You'll suffer for that.
- I need you...
Thank you, Fish.
For the first time in a long time,
I feel alive.
I remember who I am.
I remember why I'm here.
- Just listen...
- You can come out now.
Right as usual, my friend.
Say your goodbyes quickly.
Miss Mooney has places to go.
Hello, Fish.
Hi.
Dr. Thompkins.
Lee.
The desk sergeant said
it was okay to come back here.
I didn't mean to disturb you.
No, no. It's okay. Something wrong?
No. I was in the area.
And, uh, my sorceress
wants her doll back.
Right. Yeah.
Is that why you're here?
Yes.
No.
She does want her doll back...
but not entirely. No.
You live here?
I'm sort of between places right now.
I don't know why I'm here.
Sorry.
A whim.
Wait.
Hey, Gordon, did you hear?
There's been a big shootout
at Fish Mooney's place.