Previously on Gotham...
I saw a vision
of a cataclysmic event.
We will create a legacy in this city.
I think you could be so strong.
He sees it too.
Jeremiah escaped. He's got Bruce.
I have bombs planted around the city.
I know seeing is believing,
and I do want you to believe me.
So...
Now the government declared
the city off limits
until the situation can be evaluated.
In two hours, this city's gonna be
a battle ground.
Well, I'm not leaving.
Gotham is soon be each man
for himself.
A most savage place.
What should I do with you?
You took away the one person I loved,
so I took away the one person
you loved!
Out of this crucible of blood
will rise the dark knight
that your city needs.
Gotham falls, we rise.
We'll meet again
Don't know where
Don't know when
But I know we'll meet again
Some sunny day
Fire on my command.
For Gotham.
Mr. Gordon, your people decided
to ignore evacuation...
No, no, no, no, no,
it is clear you don't understand.
What to understand, Mr. Gordon?
I am afraid you are not
making yourself...
For the last time,
after the bridges blew
and the government declared
Gotham off-limits,
the city was up for grabs.
Given over to the criminals
and murderers.
Now territory is controlled
by whoever has enough power
to hold it.
I mean, we have Penguin in City Hall,
for God's sakes.
He raided the armory
and stockpiled weapons.
Then re-purposed a factory
to manufacture ammunition.
It's made him unassailable.
Barbara and the Sirens control
an area around their club.
It's the only place in Gotham
not suffering for food.
Or booze.
Barbara trades mainly in information.
Just be gone by midnight.
It's women only.
Men can buy windows of time.
It's two minutes past pumpkin-time,
sweetheart.
- Wait...
- Word is...
she enforces her rule
with an iron hand.
To the west is Jonathan Crane.
The Scarecrow.
Victor Freeze is further north
and warring with Firefly.
And to date, there have been
no confirmed sightings
of Jeremiah Valeska.
And there's us.
The GCPD controls the ten block area
around the precinct
where we feed and protect
a hundred and fifty civilians.
That number could grow
as who knows how many others
are trapped around the city.
These are people who couldn't get out
when the city was abandoned.
The poor, the sick. Whole families.
The government has a duty,
you have a duty to help them.
Mr. Gordon.
Captain Gordon.
We've been over this time and again.
No one is allowed in
or out of Gotham.
The people we are protecting
are not criminals.
And anyone who stayed
after the evacuation order
is no longer the government's
responsibility.
We're surrounded by hostile forces.
We are running out of food.
Ammunition. There are children here.
You have to evacuate them.
A committee is being formed
regarding the situation in Gotham.
A committee.
At least let us resupply ourselves.
We understand the situation.
You don't understand.
If you did, you would do something.
Just say we're on our own.
Paralysis aside, we need to operate
before her spine collapses
upon itself.
In truth, she should've
been evacuated.
Well, we tried to get her out
the night everything went to hell,
and then they blew
the bloody bridges.
Can you operate here?
I don't think we have a choice.
Selina...
- the doctor wants to operate.
- Fine.
Whatever.
I'm gonna be here the whole time.
- Enough.
- You cops are getting fat
while the rest of us are starving!
While the rest of us are starving!
You hungry, yeah?
- I got something for you to chew on.
- Harvey. Harvey. Harvey.
May I? May I?
Everyone. Sir, everyone gets the same
share, police and civilians alike.
If we start handing out more,
the supplies will not last.
You're lying!
He's lying!
- The cops get more.
- You shut up!
That's enough.
You don't like the rules, leave.
- I'm just saying...
- Say it walking.
Putz.
- Come on!
- You look well fed!
Come on. Let's go.
Come on listen up,
we're getting out of here.
So, how are we doing?
Well, we've got a month of food left.
Less if refugees keep coming.
What'd the Department
of Douchebaggery say?
Same as always.
They're not sending any help,
and not letting anyone leave.
- I had to try.
- I swear to God,
I am never paying taxes again.
And if people ask?
Sooner or later, the government
will do the right thing.
Rebuild the bridges.
Take back the city.
We just have to be patient.
And the truth? We're on our own?
The truth is we have no idea
what might happen.
And our job is to keep ourselves...
and everyone else alive.
We're down to our last rounds
of ammo.
What if Penguin or someone else
decides to make a move?
We're sitting ducks here, man.
Okay, where was I?
It happened again.
This time I woke on a rooftop.
Same thing.
No idea how I got there or what
happened during the proceeding hours.
Show yourself!
I know it's you inside there, Ed!
Idiot Ed still won't appear...
coward.
But I know it's him controlling me
when I'm sleeping.
Why?
What is he doing?
You know, you can get someone else
to turn on the spotlight.
I like doing it.
Because it reminds people that even
in darkness, there is light.
And it reminds me.
We're low on supplies.
The government won't evacuate,
won't send in help.
It doesn't make sense.
I imagine from where they sit,
it's pretty easy
to ignore people suffering.
Give Lucius permission to raid
the Wayne Enterprises R&D lab
for whatever he can scavenge.
He's working on night vision goggles
for your men.
- It's not much.
- Everything helps.
Bruce, we stayed because people here
still need protection,
that hasn't changed.
I should go.
The doctor's worried Selina's
condition is getting worse.
They're going to operate.
Let me know how it goes.
Are you sorry you stayed?
No.
You?
Hell no.
Mr. Cobblepot offers
a thousand rounds of freshly minted
9mm stock for a thousand
pounds of grade A steak.
So what we're hearing is true,
the cupboard's a bit bare
in Penguinland?
Absolutely not.
Mr. Cobblepot just had
a hankering for red meat.
Oh, please.
Ozzie wants to get fat on rib eye
while his minions starve.
- Shocker.
- I have a question.
Why hasn't your boss not left
his citadel since the bridges blew?
He's scared I'm gonna stick him
in the throat?
Tabby's still raw from when Penguin
murdered Butch right in front of her.
So it'll have to be
two thousand rounds.
Barbara, we're not giving
that bastard anything.
Exactly.
We're trading for something we need.
No.
Honey, no one is asking you
to forget what happened,
but how do we protect the women
who come in here
every day looking for safety?
We need this.
Penguin's time will come, I promise.
He's gonna regret giving me this.
Better make it 3,000 rounds.
Something's out there.
There.
See? The shadow moved.
It's just a shadow, man.
No.
Something's out there.
There, see?
Hey! You okay?
You okay?
Would you like me to make it stop?
Yes.
Open this door.
No, no, no, don't open the gate.
Split up.
Take what we came for.
Kill whoever stands in your way.
Show these fools the face of fear.
These here are the weak points.
Reinforce all the barriers
that front Penguin's territory.
I want to be ready.
What the hell?
Find Lucius.
Tell him to meet me at the generator.
Lights are out everywhere.
Well don't you worry, Master Bruce.
The clinic's got its own backup
generator.
See? Everything's shipshape
and Bristol fashion.
No.
Something's wrong.
Men. In the basement.
They're stealing all the medicine.
Alfred, stay with Selina.
Of course.
But you can't go down there.
It's gonna be pitch black
and you'll need a torch or something.
Lucius gave me something better.
Careful.
I know what you're thinking, Captain,
I have so few bullets.
Do I spend one on him?
Is it worth it?
I already know it's not.
Now the question is,
why are you here?
It's not to steal the generator.
Why would I want light?
Fear lives in darkness.
So what then?
You came for our supplies.
Exactly so.
But since I'm here,
I'll also take your life.
It's been a while since you tasted
my toxin, Captain.
What are you scared of now?
Not you.
Hey! Hey!
Hey.
They got the beans.
- Go. The lights are back up.
- Go, go, go, go.
Did you hear that?
Hello?
Scag?
Hey... Hey, guys.
Guys, this isn't... this isn't funny.
Go back!
First,
their government abandons them,
and then some freak dressed
like a scarecrow steals their grub?
I'd be pissed too.
So where are we?
At current consumption,
we've got a week of food.
Go to half-rations.
We're already at half-rations.
Cut 'em again.
The people won't be happy.
I haven't been happy in 10 years.
At least they'll be alive.
All right. That buys us two weeks.
Then what?
Jim, at this point,
the bastards across the river
are gonna have to step up and help.
Why start now? They haven't before.
For the love of... We, because we
stayed to do the job they wouldn't!
Huh? And now they're just gonna
sit back and watch while we starve
or tear ourselves apart
because that's what gonna happen.
I know, Harv.
But right now, we have
to tell these people something.
Tell them help is coming.
I'll fly in supplies.
We tried that.
We couldn't even get permission
to take off.
Zero tolerance. Nothing in or out.
Well, I'm not asking for permission.
It's ready.
Alfred's already radioed to have it
delivered from our East Bay hangar.
We can have a supply chopper here
within hours.
Man, it is nice to have
a billionaire around.
Even if it succeeds,
the government's gonna find out.
It's a one-time solution.
Scarecrow's men
didn't just take food.
They stole medicine from the clinic.
There are people in pain.
Harvey, tell the people
help is on the way.
You got it.
How's Selina?
She's strong.
She'll pull through.
Doc says the surgery was a success.
My spine's not gonna turn to jelly.
I'll still never be able
to walk again.
So, that's a bummer.
There's limited resources here.
But there's hope
once we join the mainland.
Gee.
For a second there I was worried.
Selina, I know you're in pain.
The medicine is on its way.
You know what's funny?
Jeremiah shot me to get to you.
After all the things I've done.
What did me in was being your friend.
I just wish Jeremiah killed me.
Doctors can't help her.
She needs the witch.
- How's the mood?
- They're hanging in there.
They love their Jim Gordon.
But if that chopper doesn't come,
it'll be bad.
It'll come.
Feels good.
Missing something, no?
Put a knife on.
Another shut down at the factory.
A worker fell into a hydraulic press.
It appears he passed out from hunger.
Sir, I worry if we don't increase
the food allowance...
Mr. Penn, I feel
for all of our workers.
But I cannot give what I do not have.
Overcooked.
Edward!
Such a good boy.
Quality at the factory
is also suffering.
- More misfires.
- Nonsense.
Our rounds are fine.
And now you've upset Edward.
As you see, more misfires.
Sir, if we don't give
- better quality...
- Stop.
Sir?
- Sir?
- Shut up!
Shut up!
Do you hear that?
You said yourself,
Penguin has locked himself
in City Hall with a small army...
- I know that.
- And I know you miss Butch.
Do you?
Because he only did it to hurt me.
That's why I have to make it rain.
And how are you going to do that
and not get killed?
I need you too.
Tabby, you hear me?
Is that a chopper?
There it is.
This is Bruce Wayne.
I'm at the GCPD. We can see you.
Copy that, Mr. Wayne, we'll meet you
at the rendezvous point.
Mayday. Mayday.
We've been hit,
we're going down hard.
Harvey. Chopper went down.
Get a team together now.
Ready for evac. Going down.
Oh, my God.
The chopper went down
in Lo Boyz territory.
I expect we'll have to fight
our way in and out.
I know it's a lot to ask, but without
those supplies, we're done.
Can we get some more ammo?
We're running dry down here.
Be happy you got what you got
and get in.
Alfred, I expected to see Bruce here,
he wanted to come along.
Well, you'd think, wouldn't you?
His chopper. His pilots.
Maybe he thought you wouldn't
allow it.
Just keep an eye on things
while I'm gone.
Hello.
The Lo Boyz, is it?
I suspect you know who I am.
This ain't your turf, bird man.
Be that as it may.
I'm here to claim that.
Like hell.
Get it in the truck.
Oswald.
Jim.
I thought you might show up.
It is so good to see you, old friend.
How are you faring
in these troubled times?
Tell your men to step away
from the chopper.
Sorry.
Mouths to feed.
And you know all about that,
don't you?
I hear you are up to your ears
in refugees.
We're protecting children.
Families. We need those supplies.
You shouldn't have shot it down,
Oswald.
You think I did this?
No, no, no, no.
That would mean I knew a chopper
was coming which I did not.
I mean, don't get me wrong,
we're still taking everything
but I did not fire the shot.
It was an RPG.
Who else has that kind of firepower?
Fair point.
But if it was me,
wouldn't I just admit it?
I mean, it's not like I'm going to be
arrested.
- Then who was it?
- No idea.
Now, nice as it was catching up,
it's time you skedaddle.
While you can.
We are, kind of out-gunned here,
partner.
Listen to Harvey,
after all we have been through,
do not make me kill you.
Not like this.
You should've stayed home.
Listen to me.
I know you're upset about Butch.
- He thought you were his friend!
- I was his friend!
Liar!
You put a knife in my mother's back!
His blood is on your hands!
You really think that I expected
come here and walk away?
Jim, are you just going to let her
kill me like this in cold blood?
Jim! Listen to me.
You are not the one keeping Gotham
from the abyss.
I am! I provide stability!
I may have pulled the trigger,
but you killed Butch.
Shut up and die.
Now if that was one of my bullets
I will certainly be having a word
with my foreman.
Unacceptable!
Say hello to Butch.
No.
Barbara, don't.
- I'm out.
- Me, too.
Oh, Jim!
Sounding a little quiet over there!
What the hell do we do now?
I know, I shouldn't be here,
but look.
Penguin had a truck out back.
I took these, and there's more.
I could kiss you, kid.
For the record, this is not
how I wanted things to go.
You son of a bitch.
- I will rip out your heart.
- Quiet!
Now that is exactly the kind of talk
that is going to force my hand.
But for old times' sake,
I'll give you a chance.
Can we move past this?
Say the whole Tabitha-Butch
chapter is over?
I am gonna feed your guts
to the rats, you beaky-nosed freak!
So, no?
What's the plan, boss?
Cover me.
Oswald, I want to make a deal.
A deal, Jim?
We split whatever's in the chopper.
50-50.
And you let Barbara go.
No!
He does not get to limp
out of here alive!
I got a deal for you, Jim.
She dies.
I take everything.
And you go home and reflect long
and hard on my generosity.
And if I say no?
What happens when the government
finds out
you murdered the only cops
left in Gotham?
Nothing?
Jim, as far as I can tell,
you have nothing to offer.
And, you're out of ammo.
Not anymore.
The truth is I was never gonna make
that deal.
I need all those supplies. Load up.
We got it. Here we go, people.
Heads up.
Finally, here we are.
You think Penguin's gonna
pull through?
Cockroaches are hard to kill.
At least he'll be out of commission
for a while.
You had him dead to rights.
You could've put him down for good.
Yeah, shot a man without warning.
Three months ago,
I would've lost my badge for that.
Three months ago we weren't fighting
for our survival.
You think it didn't cross my mind?
I know what we're up against, Harvey.
No one is coming to help.
Why didn't you do us all a favor
and put that murdering
son of a bitch in a hole?
You want rules for this game?
I'll tell you.
I'll make it simple, okay.
You win or you die.
Next time, shoot to kill.
- Everything all right?
- No.
But we're alive.
So that's something, what's up?
The medicine's just been taken
to the clinic.
I need to check on Selina.
Yeah, sure, I'll get you a ride. Hey.
Let me know how she is.
And, Bruce...
next time you want to help,
just ask.
You've earned a place here.
Captain Gordon?
Hello? Captain Gordon?
Come in.
Captain Gordon? Do you read me?
Hello? Come in.
This is James Gordon.
Who am I speaking to?
A friend.
We want you to know,
you have allies across the river.
We will find a way to help you.
And who are you?
Get out of here.
Really?
A dumpster?
What are you doing to me?
Show yourself.
What is happening to me?
I promise...
if it's the last thing I do...
I will kill him.
My leg.
He shot my leg.
I just fixed this!
Mr. Cobblepot, if you could
hold still...
Put out the word!
100,00 rounds of ammunition
to whoever kills Jim Gordon!
I want his head!
No!
- No!
- Selina. Hold it.
Let go.
Let go!
I have no reason to, I can't...
You should have just let me do it.
Let her do what?
What happened?
She was trying to kill herself.
I'll get restraints
for when she wakes.
I told you... you want to cure her,
you have to go to the witch.
And where do I find this witch?
- Thank you so much.
- No problem.
Thank you very much.
Saint Jim of Gotham. All right.
Hey, every new refugee who comes in,
I want them questioned.
Need information on Jeremiah Valeska.
I haven't heard that clown's name
in three months. Why now?
Just call it a hunch.
Well, rather than a week of food,
we've got six weeks.
- It's not a lot.
- Yeah, but it's better than we were.
- Don't give up hope.
- Captain Gordon.
Captain Gordon.
What's going on?
I was on duty
at the Thompson Street barricade.
He just appeared.
He said he needed to see you.
What happened, son?
Where'd you come from?
Past the train station.
That's on the other side of town.
This kid must've made it through
half dozen sectors to get here.
My brother and sisters...
they're killing us.
Who is?
You have to help us.
Get him to the clinic.
I know you're all been asking,
why are we still here
when our own government
won't help us?
It's simple.
We're supposed to be giving
these people hope.
Hope that if they're in danger,
someone will come.
We come.
Suit up.