[air hissing]
[switch clicks]
[breath trembling]
[Walker] Rest easy, Eduardo.
I made you a promise when I found you
in that hole in Pena Dura.
And I intend to keep it.
To give you a true purpose
and the strength to see it through.
However, I'm afraid this process
will be agonizing
and unfortunately, quite lengthy.
Apologies in advance.
[rat squeaking]
[dial clicks]
[shuddering]
[breathing rapidly]
You're going to be reborn,
and then you'll be the bane of the unjust,
the bane of the corrupt,
the bane of anyone who opposes us.
[muffled screaming]
[screaming]
Radio confirmation,
General Wade's landing craft docked.
His convoy is on the way here now.
Reunification day is today.
Oh, that is great news, but then what?
Just 'cause we rebuilt some bridges
doesn't mean things are gonna
suddenly improve.
So, future got you spooked?
[sighs] Yeah, I guess.
I mean, I wanna believe
things are gonna get better,
but sometimes it's just hard for me
to see it, you know.
Can't say I understand.
I don't have kids,
at least none that I know of.
But, you got one coming.
So we got no choice but to believe.
It's gotta be better than what
we've been through, right?
[sighs] Damn well better be.
Seven days in a row of .07 water
toxicity levels.
Lucius' filters did the job.
Ah, good work. Hope it's not wasted.
Is there a reason to think
there's a problem?
Jim's got a lot on his mind,
what with Gotham rejoining the world
and a baby coming
into the world next week--
Give it a rest, Harvey.
All joking aside,
we are here because of you.
Hmm? And you're gonna be a father,
that's a future I'll take.
[officer] Yeah, well done.
[officer 2] Yeah. That's my boy.
Over the past year,
we've all done good work.
We've made Gotham a safe place
for kids and families.
We've given people
the food and medicine they needed.
But it's not over yet.
So no matter what General Wade says today,
the work continues.
Give yourselves one more
round of applause.
And get back to work.
Here they come.
[brakes squeal]
Captain Gordon.
Nice to finally meet you in the flesh.
General, welcome to Gotham.
Good that you've re-established some
semblance of law and order around here.
Seems like the Green Zone stretches
to every corner of the island.
General,
Wayne Labs show toxicity levels way below
the threshold the government set for us.
All due respect, Mr. Wayne,
but I got to go
with what my people tell me on this.
[Penguin] Cutting it a little close,
aren't we?
[Nygma] Is that under 27 pounds,
13 ounces?
It can't possibly make
that big a difference.
It's only the difference between getting
off this island
or sinking to the bottom of the river.
Well, then, Pengy can off-load
a few of his knick-knacks.
Not a chance.
Because, you know what's worth
its weight in gold?
Gold.
[groans]
[breathing heavily]
Congratulations!
[chuckles]
-Go to the clinic, go have your baby.
-Ugh.
What? So the two of you
can hightail it off this rock without me?
I don't think so.
I assure you
we will not launch without you.
Ed and I will finish making preparations
and we'll be ready to launch
the moment you get back here
with that little bundle of joy.
Or, unless I should
drive you to the clinic
in light of your delicate condition?
I can do it. I'm not that delicate.
Remember that, if you even think
about double-crossing me.
[Nygma] Very kind of you
to offer to drive her.
[Penguin] I knew she would
never accept my help.
Shall I start the engine?
One less passenger to worry about.
No, two actually.
You are so right.
[chuckles]
[gasps]
Found it.
Oh, well done, Miss Kyle.
Right, let's have a look.
Oh, well, here we are.
[Selina] Oh, so this guy's the architect
who designed Wayne Manor.
[Alfred] Yeah, that's right.
With the reunification,
a new Wayne Manor must follow.
[Alfred sniffs]
And it will be just like the old one.
Oh, nothing is just like it was.
So, why are we looking at the old plans?
Perhaps I'm not ready
to let go of the past.
Well, if it makes you feel better,
I wish I could blow up my past.
Well, maybe you will.
Then one day when you build something new,
the past will always be part of it.
As for me, now Master Bruce has grown,
building a new manor
might be my last great service to him.
A home.
And then what?
You retire?
No.
I will stand guard as I've always done.
[indistinct chatter]
[Harvey] I thought this was all settled.
This is bull.
My results are accurate, Jim.
[Harvey] We don't know this General,
maybe he's with Walker.
Let's not get carried away.
Bruce, go and check on the tech.
[police radio beeps, crackles]
[sighs]
This is Gordon.
[over radio] It's Lee.
Everything okay?
-Barbara just showed up here, in labor.
-[breathing heavily]
You're kidding.
You better come quick.
Are you okay?
Yeah, yeah.
[Gordon] I'll try to get over there
as soon as I can.
Try to...
Um...
Try to wait for me.
It doesn't really work that way.
I know.
Okay.
Wait...
I love you.
I love you, too.
Jim!
What? What's wrong?
We did it.
You did it. We got through it, Jim.
[General Wade] Captain.
All clear, congratulations.
Reunification can begin.
Well, I'm glad I can make you so happy.
Funny thing is, sir,
that's just the second best news
I've got today.
[rumbling]
What's that?
-[gun fires]
-[gas hissing]
-Jim?
-Incoming!
Everybody, get back!
Get inside!
-[soldier] Take cover!
-[engine revving]
[Gordon] Go! Go!
[automatic guns firing]
[man breathing through respirator]
[bullets ricocheting]
[soldiers grunting]
[bone cracking]
[soldier grunts]
Eduardo?
[heavy breathing continues]
Not anymore.
[dart fires]
[Harvey] All right, people! Listen up!
I want squads headed for Knights Stadium,
Yeavely Park and Granton Station.
Work your way out.
We gotta find 'em, people.
What the bloody hell happened?
Seems that Jim's old army buddy
wasn't quite as dead as we'd hoped.
I got squads covering the North Side.
They're sweeping from Coventry,
down to Miller Harbor
but they could be anywhere.
Well, give us an area to search,
we'll get it covered.
Uh, take Reatton,
work your way to South City Park.
Looks like you're not done
protecting Bruce yet, Alfred.
[breathing heavily]
Eduardo.
What did Walker do to you?
When I was in Pena Dura prison, Jim,
the guards played a game.
They'd choose one of us
and they buried us alive.
They'd take bets on whether
you can dig your way out,
but then, they'd bury you deeper,
and play again.
I was the champion.
To survive that,
I had to stop being human.
I had to become something else.
I became Bane.
Only, I didn't know it yet,
but she knew and she showed me the way.
If the world is full of monsters,
the only way to defeat them
is to become one yourself.
I'm sorry.
You were a good soldier.
[sighs]
Don't pity me, Jim.
We are building the future.
She's given me a purity of mission,
and unlike the army,
she is willing to carry things out.
A new world is coming.
Strong,
merciless, unyielding.
I've heard it all before.
Not gonna happen.
And how are you going to stop me, Jim?
Not me.
You kidnapped Bruce Wayne
and a general of the U.S. Army.
You talk about your future, Eduardo,
but you don't have one.
But Eduardo's dead, Jim.
There is only Bane now.
[door opens]
Rise.
I said, rise!
[Walker] Not so formal.
Captain and I are acquainted.
Get the other one.
I recognize your voice,
but I don't know what to call you.
I know it's not "Walker."
So who are you?
That's a good question.
Perhaps Bruce Wayne
can help us figure that one out.
[Bruce panting]
You okay?
Yeah.
[Gordon] You want hostages?
You've got me
and a general of the U.S. Army.
Let him go.
This has nothing to do with him.
"This has nothing to do with him"?
But, Captain,
you don't even know what "this" is.
"This," everything I have done here,
is about punishing Gotham.
For the sins of Bruce Wayne.
You can start now.
No, no!
[Gordon grunting]
[Walker] And again.
[Gordon groans]
So,
Bruce Wayne.
I'm thinking of a name.
Can you guess whose it is?
What?
Wrong.
And again.
[groans]
Wanna take another guess?
Farewell, my beloved Gotham.
City of my birth.
Parting is such sweet sorrow.
Though I leave you today,
my heart will always remain.
I do so hate goodbyes.
Well, you're in luck.
We're not going anywhere.
-What are you talking about?
-Engine won't start.
Pressure regulator valve's missing.
Or rather, it's stolen.
Barbara!
[Barbara breathing heavily]
[Lee] Blood pressure's normal.
I'm glad something about this is normal.
So, how long
is this gonna take, Doc, soup to nuts?
Are you in a hurry or something?
No, it's just that, uh...
I just feel like you've been
so great about this.
You know,
it's been awkward as hell for you and...
I haven't even really said, "Thank you."
I don't expect a thank-you
from you, Barbara.
Then perhaps the best thank-you
would be for me to get out
of here as soon as possible.
Whatever's on your mind,
the health of the baby comes first.
I know that.
So, long haul or short, we're here
until you have
a healthy baby in your arms.
That's all I want.
Okay.
[sighs]
-[bone cracks, groans]
-Stop it!
-A name, a person.
-[breathing heavily]
The reason this is all happening.
Can't you guess yet?
I don't know!
-[yells]
-If you wanna punish me, then do it.
Hurt me, not him.
I am hurting you.
There's nothing more painful
than seeing your friend suffer.
But, he's more than just a friend,
isn't he, Bruce?
Jim Gordon's been like a father to you.
How awful it must be
to watch another father die.
Who am I doing this for?
Say the name.
[groans]
[whimpers]
When the ones you love die,
it's like a part of yourself
is cut off forever.
[Bruce inhales sharply]
You know that.
So why do I hate you so much?
Who was cut away from me?
Last chance.
[groans weakly]
Yes.
Now you know.
Say his name.
Say it.
Ra's al Ghul.
This is revenge for his death.
And who am I?
You're his daughter.
My name is Nyssa al Ghul.
And revenge is just the beginning
of what I want.
[Nyssa] The League of Shadows
is everywhere.
Did you think my father's mission
would die with him?
Humankind will be purged of weakness.
I'm just starting with you and yours.
You're right. I killed Ra's.
So, whatever you need to do, do it to me.
No. You can't take all the blame
for killing my father.
I mean, you did have some help, right?
Someone who, quite literally,
gave you a helping hand.
What are you doing?
-[grunting]
-[grunts]
Well done, Barbara.
Go get Barbara Kean.
Eduardo...
She's pregnant.
She's carrying a child.
[Bane] A child?
One soul's future
weighed against the world's.
Your concern seems petty, Jim.
If he touches a hair on that child's head,
I will destroy everything you have.
I don't have anything left.
Just my father's mission.
Bane wants you
to join that mission with us.
To see the world as he sees it.
Never.
[Strange] Never say never, Captain Gordon.
No!
[Nyssa] How does it feel, Bruce,
knowing that all of this is your fault?
Tell me. I'd really like to know.
[Barbara screaming]
[breathing heavily]
[moans]
There must be something you can give me.
We're out of the drugs that you need.
It's okay. You're almost there.
I'll get you some ice chips
-so you don't get dehydrated.
-Gee, thanks.
-Lee.
-Ed.
Don't worry. I'm not here for you.
But for the record, you stabbed me first.
If you two are quite done,
we are actually here for Barbara.
Or more precisely, what she stole from us.
I don't know what this is about.
And I don't care.
You two need to get out of here right now.
[chuckles] Gladly. Just as soon
as Barbara gives us the...
-What's it called?
-Pressure regulator valve.
Right. That.
I should've known
that you would try to screw us over.
You only noticed because
you tried to screw me over first.
Second, technically.
Okay. She's in the middle
of having a baby.
And we are in the middle of
trying to leave Gotham.
And we can't do that
without a crucial part of the submarine,
which will ferry us all away from here!
That's why you were in such a rush
to get out of here.
[Penguin] As are we.
Hand over the part.
Now.
Don't point that at the baby.
What? No, I did not.
I was merely trying to make a general
threatening gesture with a firearm--
But you did, though.
You pointed the gun at the baby.
All right, fine. I'm sorry!
Now give us what we want!
Oh, you think I'm stupid enough
to have the part on me?
It's hidden away somewhere safe.
And if you think you can
torture me into telling you where,
there is literally nothing more painful
than what I'm going through right now!
[explosion, rumbling]
[woman screams in distance]
[nurse] Hey! You stay out of here!
This is a hospital!
[bone snapping]
[bell dings]
[P.A. system activates]
Barbara Kean, your time is up.
There's no place for you to hide.
No one will save you
nor mercy that will spare you.
You simply cannot run from your sins.
And you cannot run from me.
What do you want from me?
Let me let you in
on a little military secret.
It's called Special Order 386.
In the event that Gotham
is irretrievably lost,
a contingency plan was put in place
to reduce this city to rubble.
No. There are still innocent people here.
You asked me what I want from you.
I want you to suffer, Bruce Wayne,
and then I want you to die.
Spend a little time with that thought.
We'll be starting soon.
-[Lee] Who are those guys?
-[Barbara] No idea.
[Lee] Exactly how many people
have you screwed over?
-[Penguin] Present company excluded?
-[Barbara whimpering]
[Lee] There are 79 people
in this building.
[Nygma] Fortunately, they seem to only be
trying to kill one.
So, by all means,
let's gather around the target.
-[Lee] All right.
-[Barbara groaning]
Maybe we can
cut through the abandoned wing
and we can get to
the ambulance bay that way.
Might take some time, but--
Oh, if only there were two able-bodied men
who could buy us some!
And why, pray tell,
should we risk our necks for you?
-[wincing] Chivalry!
-[Penguin laughing]
But if that's too much,
remember, if I die,
-you will never find that sub part.
-[Nygma] Fine.
We'll keep them busy.
We'll meet you at the docks.
Thank you.
-What?
-"Keep them busy"?
I only brought enough ammunition
for a light firefight,
not to repel a paramilitary assault!
What do we use? Bedpans?
I was actually thinking of something
a little more flammable.
[both laugh]
[grunts]
Why, Captain Gordon,
how nice that you're awake.
Picked the losing side, Strange.
The Army's coming to Gotham.
Help me, and you can do what you do best,
survive.
I happen to think more of
Miss al Ghul's chances for success
than a man in your, well, position.
You really think
she can take on the entire Army?
As a matter of fact, I do.
With my help.
You are just a few modifications away
from being a mighty soldier in her forces.
Not unlike your friend, Eduardo,
I will help you
to realize your full potential.
Give you true strength.
I'll pass.
Consent is hardly a prerequisite.
We will begin with,
uh, physical improvements.
Sorry.
And finish
with certain mental adjustments.
[elevator bell dings]
[regulated breathing]
[exclaiming]
[breathing continues]
[Lee] Your contractions
are about a minute apart.
-We gotta get you out of here.
-[Barbara grunting]
-[yelling]
-[man grunts]
[Barbara screams]
[Lee] Nice shot.
[yelling]
-[Lee exclaims]
-[screaming]
-[groaning]
-Keep breathing!
[grunts]
[chair creaking]
[Nygma] Some try to hide,
some try to cheat,
but time will let us always meet.
What am I?
-Pregnant lady with a gun?
-Death. But close enough.
[Penguin] So, where to now?
Well, I believe we have a sub to catch.
[both chuckling]
How long have you had that?
Long enough to know
she'd never let it out of her sight.
[laughing]
And you stuck around long enough
to risk both of our lives
to save Barbara's?
Or was it to protect Lee?
Do you want me to answer that,
or do you want to sail away from here?
Bon voyage.
[screaming] Those bastards have stolen
the damn sub part!
-You mean they stole it back.
-Whose side are you on?
-Clearly, I'm on the baby's side, Barbara.
-[breathing heavily]
What was your plan, anyway?
You were going to be a fugitive
with Nygma and Penguin?
Well, I'm not exactly the stay-at-home
and bake-apple-pie type.
Yeah, and running off on a submarine
seemed like a great alternative.
Barbara.
You can live here.
You can have this baby here.
Jim is not taking the baby away from you.
You really believe that?
You really think Captain Jim Gordon
is gonna let a criminal raise his kid?
People are already shooting at my baby.
I have to protect him, or her.
I have to be strong.
Hey. Being strong does not mean
you have to be a criminal.
Jim will help you.
And so will I, if you'll let me.
That's just weird.
I know.
Hey, baby, this is your Aunty Lee.
Mommy tried to kill her once,
-maybe twice.
-[laughing]
All right, okay. That's enough of that.
Come on, we gotta keep moving.
I think this is happening now.
[screaming]
[whimpering]
[breathing heavily]
[straining]
[screams]
[henchman] What's going on in there?
[grunts]
This is Bruce Wayne. Can anyone read me?
This is Bruce Wayne.
Does anyone at the GCPD read me?
This is Bruce Wayne. Can anyone read me?
Bruce, it's Alfred.
Where the devil are you? Over.
Some abandoned mansion in North Side Park.
-On my way.
-No. I'll get out myself.
I need you to get to the clinic.
The clinic?
It's Ra's al Ghul's daughter, Alfred.
She wants revenge.
She mutated Eduardo Dorrance,
and sent him after Barbara.
[Selina] Oh, gosh.
I'm fine.
I need you to get to Barbara and the baby.
Now, you're going to feel
a slight discomfort.
That's the stimulant I've given you
to prepare your muscles.
You'll need it for what comes next,
which, I'm afraid,
is going to be excruciating.
[grunts]
Do you feel that?
Yes.
[Strange groans]
[grunts]
There's that fighting spirit
I've always admired so much.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
there's an alarm I must sound.
[grunts]
[door opens]
What the hell are you doing?
Checking to make sure Strange doesn't have
one of those chips in your head.
We need to hurry up.
Get out of here before he trips the alarm.
[alarm buzzes, blares in distance]
Come on.
Alfred and GCPD
are on their way to the clinic.
-Where's Nyssa?
-I don't know.
But she's planning on using the military
to wipe out Gotham.
I can order them to stand down.
Now let's get you out of here.
[Lee] She's beautiful. Congratulations.
[Barbara] Hi, there.
Guess I'm gonna have to figure out
what to call you.
[Barbara sobbing]
Thank you.
[baby crying]
[tires screech]
[Lee gasps]
[car doors open]
-[Selina] Come on.
-[Alfred] Get in the car now!
I'll hold him off.
[Selina] Alfred and I got this.
[Alfred] Selina, get in the car.
-Selina, get back in the car!
-No!
Go.
Oh, my, look at you.
You're a big one, ain't you?
Bloody baby.
But let's see what you got.
[Alfred grunting]
[Selina groans]
[grunting]
Ugh, bastard.
[Alfred yelling]
[yells]
[Selina groans]
No!
Alfred!
Alfred.
Somebody help!
Somebody... Oh, no.
[soldier] Attention!
[soldier 2] Welcome back, General.
Get me a secure line to the mainland now.
[Harvey] Jim! Hey.
Just got word from Lee.
She and Barbara
made it out of the clinic okay.
And your baby daughter, too.
-Congratulations.
-They're going to The Sirens.
You just had a baby girl, brother.
Say something.
I just can't believe it.
We won, didn't we? It's over.
We did, and she's gonna have
a better world because of it.
She is.
I promise.
-Is Alfred with them?
-Didn't say.
This is General Wade.
I am authorizing Special Order 386.
No!
Gotham City is lost.
Begin your bombing run on my order.
-Wait, wait, wait.
-Arrest them.
[guns cocking]
[Bruce] You can't do this.
Take them away.
You can't do this!
[Lee] Okay. Nice and slow.
-[Nyssa] Barbara Kean.
-[gasps] Run!
It's nice to finally meet you.
My name is Nyssa al Ghul.
I believe you knew my father.
I don't understand how
the general could have been chipped.
I didn't see a scar
on the back of his neck. Did you?
No. Strange must've hidden it.
Nyssa let us escape.
She knew we'd bring the general here
and do her dirty work for her.
-[Harvey] What now, Jim?
-Son...
If you're gonna stick a gun in my face,
you should at least know
you're doing it wrong.
[soldier grunts]
Come on. Let's go.
[helicopters whirring]
[explosions continue in the distance]