Previously on Gotham...
You left me the virus.
You've got two options.
You can take the virus.
And find the strength
and get out of there.
Or you can make that coffin
your permanent home.
- Fish! Why are you here?
- I was alive.
Goodbye, Fish!
- Then, I was dead.
- Let's try subject 13, shall we?
And then I was alive.
- Impossible.
- Nothing is impossible.
Things are looking up.
My little Penguin
and I will be leaving.
This detonator
will trigger the bomb.
1000's will be infected with a virus.
Let Gotham fall so you may rise.
I won't have him turn you
into a murderer.
No, you will press it.
When you're ready,
come and find me.
Oh, my.
- What is that?
- What's happening out there?
My, my money.
- My money, my savings. My savings...
- Excuse me, what?
My, my money, my savings.
I want them. My money, my savings...
- My whole life.
- What's your account number?
My money, my savings.
This account was closed
- due to unpaid fees.
- No, no, my money,
- my savings, my life, everything!
- You have no money,
- the account is closed.
- I have to...
- Give me my money, now!
- Oh, god. Security!
Hey! What are you...
My money! My savings! Now!
- Get out!
- Stop it.
- Come here!
- Stop this!
Come back! Buy our cookies!
Move on!
Killer.
Killer,
you're a killer.
Killer.
Killer!
- Jim?
- Yeah.
- You okay?
- Fine.
I'm fine, Harvey.
Listen,
I hate to do this to you, pal.
But I'm going to have
to ask for your gun.
This virus is tearing the city apart.
You need me. I can control this.
That's why I'm not asking
for your badge.
Some of the guys are talking.
These cops are going to be watching
you for the smallest sign.
Okay? And if you've got a gun
they'll be double jumpy.
It's for your own protection.
- Any word on Lee?
- Nada.
What happened after the bombing?
A mob of infected swarmed
the clock tower.
- She disappeared in the chaos.
- I don't get it.
She went through all that effort
to get you infected
with the virus and she just bolts?
She saw I was fighting it.
She's waiting for me
to give over to it.
Prove her wrong.
Where's Bruce?
Detective Gordon.
Alfred.
Has he said anything?
No, no, he just sits there staring.
I need to talk to him, Harvey.
- We sure that's not the clone?
- No, that's Bruce.
God knows what those
bastards done to him
but he's only brainwashed.
Are you really the best person
to talk to him?
I mean, from what you said,
you killed his mentor or something.
He might be a bit peeved.
Listen, whatever they did to him,
that is Bruce Wayne in there.
That boy is stronger than
you can possibly imagine.
I just need to make him remember...
Who he is.
As long as he doesn't
leave the precinct.
Harvey, something
you need to see.
An antidote?
Lucius, I could kiss your face.
Before you do that,
I don't actually have the formula.
But there is an antidote?
That's what you're saying?
I was going through
the papers you recovered
from the Owl leader's house.
They suggest that while Strange was
working to weaponize the Tetch virus
he was also working
on a parallel project
tailoring different antiviral agents
to his own ends.
- Strange was designing an antidote.
- That makes sense.
The Court was careful
to protect its own.
They would want a safeguard.
We need to talk to Strange.
Is he still here
or has he been moved?
Well, when you were buried
in the coffin
and the city was
about to be virus-bombed
- some decisions had to be made.
- Harvey...
I told Alfred to question Strange.
In exchange for him telling us
where the bombing was
going to go down
Alfred let Strange walk.
Yes, I'm blaming it on the butler.
All right. Strange is a weasel.
He'd try to get as far away
from this as possible.
Union Station is shut down.
Downtown train station's
our best bet.
Okay. Wait up.
- Harvey?
- Lucius,
I know what you're going to say,
all right?
He can handle this.
Hell, Barnes had the virus
for weeks before anyone knew.
What I was going to say,
from all I see here
Strange's virus is an accelerated
version of the Tetch virus.
Why do you think people
are reacting so quickly?
Gordon isn't going to be able
to fight this for long.
Well, we'll just have
to wait and see?
You keep working on that antidote.
One second, one second,
one ticket at a time...
- Two.
- Keep the change.
Sir, excuse me!
Excuse me.
Oh, no.
I think you mean,
"Hello, Fish. I miss you."
And don't worry, sweetheart.
The fun has just begun.
"As the flames of hedonism
licked the very foundation
of its society
"Nero" played and sang...
"The Destruction of Troy."
I will say this
about the Court of Owls,
they have style.
Not to mention they've handed us
the perfect opportunity.
- For what?
- The city is in total disarray.
What better time
to consolidate power?
Barbara, I've told you again
and again
I have no interest
in running Gotham.
- I only want...
- To kill Penguin, yes.
I got it the first billion times.
And where is he now?
Oh, that's right, with Fish Mooney.
- So we find her.
- And then what?
You blast through her army of goons
until you get to Oswald?
You're going to need muscle, honey.
- Which you provide.
- Oh, so you expect my help?
But when I need yours
to take advantage
of an opportunity of a lifetime...
Nothing.
Baby.
Listen, all I ask
is that you use this beautiful
big brain of yours
to help me, finally...
Get this city under my thumb.
And afterwards,
I will help you
pry Penguin away from Fish.
Deal?
I will give you a day.
I thought we were friends.
When the Court of Owls calls,
no-one does not refuse.
Still, I'm not upset.
I knew when your old masters
summoned you
it was to cook up some horror,
and here's the thing,
I need horror.
They're responsible
for all of this, aren't they?
At the behest of the Court,
I weaponized a virus
that releases
a person's darkest urges.
1000's have been infected.
So, where is this virus?
I know there's more.
It has all been used.
Please, I must go.
Don't.
You will give me the virus.
You will make me the army
you promised.
You will do everything I say
until this city
is in the palm of my hand.
Are we clear?
Yes, madam.
Sorry, folks, this exit's off...
I'll look around for the station cop,
see if he found Strange.
Hello?
Oh, geez. He's right here.
- This is Gordon.
- Hi, Jim.
I was just checking in,
seeing how you're feeling.
Crazy day?
- Lee, where are you?
- Somewhere very familiar to you.
I know how you're feeling.
All that blood rushing
through your veins
your heart beating faster
and faster.
Listen to me you need
to turn yourself in, it's not safe.
The infected are being killed
all over the city.
Wow, you're really fighting this?
You know, you don't have to.
The cage is finally open, Jim.
You're free.
- No.
- I thought you loved me.
I thought you wanted us
to be together.
Not like this.
Well.
This is the only way, Jim.
Just listen to the whispers.
Killer.
They'll lead you to me,
tell you who you are.
Killer.
- That's not who I am.
- I wonder what they're saying.
That you like hurting people,
killing people?
- Killer.
- See how well I know you, Jim.
Now, I'm going to go have some fun.
We'll catch up soon.
Promise.
Killer, killer, you're a killer.
Jim! Jim.
Someone spotted Strange.
Just don't shoot
any innocent bystanders.
Or me. Especially me.
- GCPD!
- Don't move!
Fish?
What a surprise.
My goodness, Harvey, you look awful.
It's good to see you, too.
We just want Strange.
You can walk away.
Yeah. Oh, no.
Fish, I know in your own sick way,
you love this city
and Gotham is bleeding to death.
- We need this dirtbag to fix it.
- Enough talking. Hand him over.
He has it.
It's in his eyes.
- He has the virus.
- Really?
So tell me, James
what's it feel like?
Like it's taking all my willpower
not to kill you.
Oh, my.
Harvey, when you say Hugo here
can save the city
does that mean there's a cure
for this virus?
Fish, I swear to god,
if you don't step back
I will shoot you
and these two nimrods right here,
- right now!
- Hugo, is it true
that you're the only one
that can stop this madness?
- Obviously, I can't give him up now.
- Fine, you had your chance.
Did you really think
that I would come without backup?
- You're a killer.
- Jim, dial it down, buddy.
Victor, looks like our little
Detective Gordon is overheating.
Perhaps you should cool him off.
Both of them.
Marvelous. Just marvelous.
There he is,
the real James Gordon.
Nice to meet you, at last.
There we go, Master Bruce.
Two lumps, just how you like it.
You hungry, mate?
Can I whip you up a sandwich?
Anyway, if all goes well,
we should be able to
head back to Wayne Manor tomorrow.
Although, I was thinking
that we could go abroad.
We could go to Switzerland.
I mean, we used to go with your mum
and dad this time of year.
Stop it.
Your attempts
to elicit an emotional response
by reminding me of shared memories
is clumsy and pathetic.
The last memory, I have is
of you killing the best friend
and teacher I ever had.
You mean that old geezer
that kidnapped you,
poisoned your mind then tried
to turn you into a mass murderer.
Let me tell you something,
Master Bruce
that man...
Lied to you.
Him and his bloody Court of Owls
they tried to use you,
they tried to manipulate you.
You say he was a liar.
How?
By taking away the pain
I've carried for years?
By giving me revenge against
the people
who killed my mother and father?
That's more than you ever did.
Anyway, the Court of Owls
does not matter.
They merely paved the way
for the one who is to come.
What do you mean?
Who, who's coming?
You'll see.
- I should cook him.
- They want him alive.
- So, I'll just cook part of him.
- Oh, no, my dear.
Let's be calm.
You don't have that kind of control.
And you do? In my hands,
this flamethrower is a scalpel.
Fine. We each take a foot.
Whoever goes above
the ankle loses.
- You're on.
- No. No, no. Stop!
- Ms. Mooney! Ms. Mooney!
- Mooney's busy.
I'm here now.
Also, I think your children
are angry with you.
- Mr. Cobblepot.
- It's understandable.
You made them what they are...
Then abandoned them.
- You are working with Ms. Mooney?
- We're partners.
But you tried to kill her.
And she forgave me.
I know. Surprised me, too.
But, Mooney is not the old Mooney.
She has evolved.
And she has a vision for Gotham.
She sees a city
where people like myself
Victor, Bridgit freaks are in charge.
And you are going to help us
achieve that.
- I can't.
- Wrong, Professor!
This virus is tearing Gotham apart.
That makes your antidote
the most valuable thing in the city.
We could demand half of Gotham
and the city council deliver it
to us on a platter.
So, I'm going to ask you once,
where is it?
If I tell you
where the antidote is...
I have nothing.
I can't.
You can torture me all you want.
- Okay.
- What?
You know, when I was in Arkham,
I was tortured daily.
Well, that was therapy, Oswald.
Therapy.
And that device you used
to administer the therapy
remember that?
It gave the sensation
that your head was being torn open
so that hot lava could be poured
directly into your brain.
Afterwards...
Just thinking of it
would make me physically ill.
So, naturally, I had to have it.
One moment, Oswald.
- No!
- All right, all right! I'll tell you
anything you need to know.
I'll tell you where the antidote is.
I know.
- But not just yet, okay?
- What?
They're not answering
at the precinct.
They must be overwhelmed.
Well, we're not shooting
our way out.
Killer.
Jim, take it easy.
Someone will come!
Yeah, and by then,
Mooney will have gotten Strange
to give her the antidote!
We're running out of time!
Killer.
Killer. Killer.
Killer!
I knew you could do it.
Come on, Jim!
Fight the damn virus!
Not my car. That's my car!
Let me drive.
Alvarez, spread the word.
Mayor James has called
in the National Guard.
We don't want any soldiers
getting shot by mistake.
Leave me alone.
The hell's wrong with you?
- Alvarez, I'm talking to you.
- I said, leave me alone!
So, I will ask you again.
Who's coming?
I mean, I thought the man
that I dispatched
at Wayne Enterprises
was the leader of the Court of Owls.
I want you to leave.
Yeah, well, that ain't going
to happen, is it, mate?
You can't get rid of me
that easy.
You have to remember
who you are.
I know who I am.
- I have a destiny.
- Now, you listen to me.
That man that wanted you
to detonate that bomb,
whatever he promised you
freedom from pain, power, none of it,
none of it was real.
I want you to remember what is real.
I know what's real!
I got vengeance
for my parent's murder.
That's real!
No.
No, that's not real.
What's real...
Is every time that you were sick
when you were a kid,
your mum used to sit up
with you all night
and read to you till you fell asleep.
That's real.
Or when you were seven
and you took
your silly rowing boat out
and you got lost in that storm
and me and your dad were out,
shouting and screaming
losing our minds.
And when your dad found you,
how he cried.
That's real.
Yes,
your parents died in that alley
three years ago
and maybe that man took away
the pain of that night.
But there is no life,
there is no love without pain.
He could not touch the love
that your mom and dad gave you
that you still have it in you,
that you still have in here.
The same love
that I have for you.
I love you, Master Bruce.
I would do anything for you.
I would die for you.
You must find that love again.
Come back to me, Master Bruce.
- Thank you very much.
- No, problem.
Excuse me.
Oh, bloody hell.
What I'm saying is
if Penguin and Fish have hooked up
things are going to get real bad,
real fast.
- You want to run?
- No.
I'm saying maybe she takes care
of Barbara and Nygma for us.
I mean, we can even help
things along.
Send word to Fish
about where Babs is weak.
This is our shot.
I'm not ready.
What the hell is she doing here?
One whiskey, here you go.
Well, this is a strange day.
Never thought I'd see you in here.
Had some time to kill
while my ex sees the light.
Figured I'd have a little fun.
- Where's Babs?
- What do you want with her?
None of your business, errand boy.
I'm sorry, what did you call me?
I'm sorry, you're not an errand boy.
You're more of a shoeshine boy.
They should give you a little stand
in the front cute little hat.
- That's more your speed.
- Right. Out.
Yeah.
You've got the virus.
Wow, you're not as dumb
as I've heard.
Are there any other glaringly
obvious remarks you'd like to make?
How about I cut your lungs out
and show them to you?
Wow, that's incredibly vivid.
I'd like to see you try it.
But I'm here for your boss,
the crazy blonde.
She's not my boss.
I may have a virus making me
freakishly strong and mildly insane,
but even I know that you were
a sidekick to your brother
and you're a sidekick to Barbara.
So...
Can you send her a message for me?
Would you?
Your boss...
Tell her next time I see her,
I'm going to rip her head
right off her body.
Bye now.
- God.
- What, you need help?
Hey, wait for me.
It's all criminal activity.
- Go back inside.
- I got this guy.
- Gotham Curfew.
- Got him.
Sun down.
All individuals must remain indoors.
Any activity outdoors
will be considered criminal activity.
Clear here.
Let's go, let's go. Clear out.
He's following directions
or something.
I've got to find out
who's controlling him,
who's brainwashed him.
And then what?
I'm going to kill the bastard.
You two, wait here.
Professor, if this is a trap,
you will soon find yourself hanging
with the rest of the meat.
It's no trap.
I tested earlier versions
of the virus
and the antidote on livestock.
I made sure to set aside
a successful batch.
- This place gives me the creeps.
- I like it.
It's concentrated.
Once you dilute it
there is enough here to cure
every infected person in Gotham.
Oswald, you and I will rule
this city together.
Yes.
But first, I have to kill Ed Nygma.
- He has to die.
- Oh, he will.
And all those
who try to stand in our way.
What's this?
Who's there?
Show yourself.
Who are they?
Don't look at me, I don't know.
Really?
That's all you've got?
Hand over the antidote now.
I want the Strike Force
and all available units there now.
I'm on my way.
Reports of an ice storm and fireball
at an East Side slaughterhouse.
- Do you think maybe...
- Just drive the damn car.
Sweet mother mercy.
Killer.
You damn fool.
Fish!
Oswald.
It's okay. It's, it's...
We can, we can
get you some help.
No, no, no.
I've done this enough times
to know I'm finished.
No, do not say that.
- We will get you help.
- Listen to me.
Listen to me.
Make this city yours...
Or you burn it to the ground.
People call me a monster.
You, Jim Gordon
you're the mons...
You're right. I am a monster.
- GCPD!
- Arrest them! All of them!
Strange.
You better tell me that you can make
more of that antidote.
Yes, yes. I just need one thing.
How's it hanging?
You sure about this?
According to my sources,
Fish Mooney and the GCPD
are scrambling to recover
the antidote to this virus.
But Fish is dead.
And Hugo Strange,
who designed the antidote
is setting up a lab in the GCPD
but they are missing one very,
very important element.
So, yes, I am sure that this bozo
is the key to controlling Gotham.
Are you my saviors?
Are you the ones to set me free?
Not exactly.
Let's make Gotham beg.
Seek out the Yuyan building.
Find the demon's head.
Fulfill your destiny.
Right. Find Bullock,
let him know where we are.
I'm going to follow Bruce.
I wouldn't touch that, Bruce.
You know, who I am?
Who do you think told the Sensei
to send you here?
He's dead.
He was murdered.
He died.
But he completed his task.
The Court of Owls is destroyed,
Gotham burns, and you...
...are here.
He told me to complete my training
to find the demon's head.
You already have, Bruce.
I'm the one you seek.
I'm the demon's head.
I am Ra's al Ghul.
Why have you come to me, Bruce?
The Sensei told me to seek you out.
That you would complete my training.
And did the Sensei tell you
who I am, what I seek?
I know you are not a part
of the Court of Owls
that you only used them.
But I don't know why.
Then know that I have been alive
more years than you can imagine.
That I have seen and done things
that would shake the core
of everything you believe.
That I'm thought to be a demon,
a saint,
a ghost.
But for all my years,
all my travels,
there is one thing
that I have never found...
A true heir.
But I need to know if you're ready.
I am.
The Sensei trained me.
Are you?
He set you a task.
He asked you to be the one
that released the virus
that now envelops this city.
- You failed.
- I would have.
- But, but Alfred, he distracted me.
- I know.
I know.
And that's why I'm going
to give you another chance
to complete your journey.
Oh, don't look so surprised,
Master Bruce.
I told you,
you couldn't get rid of me that easy.
Just got a bit sloppy.
Got a bit of ring rust.
Let these little ninja monkeys
get one over on me.
You all right, mate?
What you come as?
Enough.
This man is your past, Bruce.
Now, embrace your future.
Kill him.
Join me.
Fulfill your destiny.
He's wrong.
Master Bruce,
there's no other way to put it.
He's wrong. Your destiny
is to be Bruce Wayne.
And one day,
you're going to remember that.
And you're going to remember
how much I love you.
I remember the first time
your mum and dad brought you home.
They were so exhausted.
And they gave you to me.
This tiny,
defenseless little creature.
And they said, "Look after him,"
and I said, "Sure."
And I scooped you up in my arms
and I held you,
and you opened your eyes,
and you looked at me.
And at that moment, I decided
that I would do anything for you.
Anything.
So, if this is what you need to do
Master Bruce, you crack on.
You do it.