NARRATOR:
Previously on Gotham:
[LOUD THUD THEN GUNSHOT]
Fish Mooney's alive,
and you've been playing me for a chump.
No, no, no.
You better stop this machine right now.
Because if I die,
Don Falcone is gonna send a team up here...
to skin you alive
and slaughter your family.
[MAN SCREAMING]
That man who was thrown from the roof,
the killer removed his adrenal glands.
Essentially, it's the fear gland.
G.C.P.D.
GORDON:
He's still out there.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[GROANS]
[WINDOW RATTLING]
Hello?
Who are you?
[DOOR RATTLING]
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
[WOMAN YELLS
AND GRUNTING CONTINUES]
[GROANS]
- I'm dreaming, right?
MAN: Oh, I hope so lady.
I sure hope so.
FISH:
Hell.
What's up with them?
What are they waiting for?
First man that comes at a new girl nearly
always gets jumped by the second man.
Is that right?
Here's a promise, boys.
The first of you to come at me
will die like... that.
The second will die slow.
So boys...
who's first?
LESLIE: Thank you, that was wonderful.
GORDON: Yeah, taxi!
And no case files.
We didn't mention work once.
- Ha-ha-ha. There's hope for us yet.
- Yeah.
So, what is this, our third date?
LESLIE:
I believe that's correct.
Three dates, and I still haven't been
to your apartment.
What particular room of my apartment
are you interested in?
- I don't know. How's the kitchen?
- Small.
- Living room?
- Dark.
- How about the bedroom?
- The bedroom, I think you'd like.
Yeah. Taxi!
But not tonight.
- No?
- I have to get a good night's sleep.
I start a new job in the morning.
- A new job? Congratulations. Since when?
- I heard this morning.
I didn't wanna spoil dinner
with a discussion about it.
Why would it spoil dinner?
I'm coming to work at the G.C.P.D.
I'm you're new medical examiner.
You're kidding.
Wow, that's great.
Is it?
Of course. I mean, I was the one
that suggested you work there.
- Yes, but now it's real.
- So good.
We'll see, won't we?
Good night.
Hey. Gennaro Marx, single, 63.
High-school English teacher.
Same exact surgical incisions
as our last victim.
What are the odds
he's got no adrenal glands?
GORDON:
So, what's he doing with them?
[GRUNTS]
[HEART BEATING RAPIDLY]
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]
WOMAN:
Why?
[YELLS]
What's the matter with you?
Why won't you help me, Gerald?
[SCREAMING]
Help me.
ALFRED: Do you have everything you need,
Master Bruce?
Yes.
I can still come with
you, if you want me to.
No.
- Wouldn't be right.
- No, of course.
- I'll be fine, Alfred. You don't have to worry.
- Who said I was worried?
I'll be back before dark.
I've been on this hike before, you know?
Not without your father.
Come here.
He would've approved, you know...
carrying on the tradition like this.
My father and I stayed overnight.
We woke up early to watch the sunrise.
It's not the same.
Well, maybe next year then.
Well, off you go then.
OSWALD:
And then, the worst of it.
Maroni had me locked inside a sedan
and tried to crush me alive.
So, well, you can imagine my concern.
Maroni's not a man to let things go, and I
fear he will come after me in retaliation.
- Were you planning to clean up the place?
- What?
Oh. Uh...
- I can. If you like.
- It needs it.
Is that blood?
Perhaps.
But, Don Falcone...
While you're at it, maybe you could
do something about the design.
The design?
It reeks of Fish Mooney.
What do you think about the lamps?
[OSWALD CHUCKLES]
Don Falcone, maybe you didn't hear me.
I need your protection.
- Maroni will surely try and kill me.
FALCONE: Yes.
The lamps should go.
Don Falcone, please.
Maroni wants my scalp,
and you'd have me redecorate.
This nightclub makes a lot of money.
Without money, we lose influence.
Without influence, we lose control.
And without control, Maroni killing you
is no longer a hypothetical...
it's a foregone conclusion.
That's why I wanna reopen it.
Under your care.
I can have the club?
- It's mine?
- You've earned it.
Your days of sneaking around
spying on Maroni are over.
You're with me now. Publicly.
Things are gonna be much different.
So spruce up the place. Get it open.
As for Maroni, leave him to me.
GORDON:
What do you got?
BULLOCK:
Yearbook where the victim taught English.
I'll tell you one thing. Girls didn't look
like this when I was back in high school.
- Easy.
- I'm just saying.
- Hi, Jim.
- Lee. You remember Harvey, right?
BULLOCK: Hi, Lee.
- Hi.
Lee's our new ME.
You're joking.
- No.
ESSEN: Oh, good. You've met.
Detective Gordon and I know each other.
- Oh, right. From Arkham?
- Right. Arkham.
Welcome aboard.
Thank you.
ESSEN:
You can fill her in on your cases later.
Dr. Thompkins, will you follow me?
Lots to get you up to speed on.
- It was good to see you again, detective.
- It was really good to see you, doctor.
- You have no luck at all, do you, brother?
- What do you mean?
You find a fine lady like that, and she comes
to work with you in the same building?
- It's a damn shame.
- Why?
Office romance always ends in tears. Tears.
- It's not gonna be like that.
- Trust me. I know.
There.
Holy mother Mary.
- You got him?
- Staring right back at me.
That's him.
That's him, that's the guy from the pool.
His name is Gerald Crane.
He's a biology teacher.
School doesn't let out for hours. Let's go.
- I'm Kelly.
- Fish.
- Fish?
- That's what I said. Fish.
So where are we? What is this place?
Some people think it's a prison.
Some think it's hell.
I just think it's cold, mostly.
[DOOR OPENS]
Breakfast.
Ah-ah-ah!
You gotta let the boss eat first.
People call him Mace.
He's the one in charge, huh?
- Okay. Okay
MAN: Get off me. Get off me.
WOMAN: Gerald called in one day
and said he wasn't coming in.
- That's the last I heard of him.
- Let me guess. Three weeks ago?
- Yeah.
- That's when neighbors said he moved out.
Unis searched the place. Nothing.
- So, what can you tell us about Crane?
- He was a good teacher.
Focused. And a good father. He was
very protective of his son, Jonathan.
But he could be quiet too. Somber.
I think it had to do with his wife.
She died six or seven years ago.
- She died. How?
- Uh, car accident.
- Did Crane ever talk about fear or phobias?
- Why?
Is someone targeting phobics?
Yeah.
- Killing them?
- Does this mean something to you?
These victims,
were they missing their adrenal glands?
How'd you know that?
This was an academic paper
Gerald wrote a few months ago.
He asked me to proof it.
See, Gerald had a theory that fear
was an evolutionary flaw in humans.
That war, rape, theft, murder,
it was all caused by fear.
He was obsessed with it.
So Crane killed these people
and took their glands to test a theory?
No. Gerald wasn't trying to prove
he was right about fear.
He was trying to cure himself of it.
Crane's idea of curing fear
was to inoculate himself against it.
- Like a disease?
- Exactly.
In order to do so, he needed a condensed
source of the hormones that cause fear.
- Phobics.
- Crane's preying on them?
Spiking their fear by scaring them and then
killing them in order to harvest hormones.
BULLOCK:
Damn.
- How much of this stuff does he need?
- What do you mean?
- How many more people is he gonna kill?
- Oh. Of course. Good question.
Depends on how scared he is, I guess.
What's he scared of?
In Scottie's phobia support group,
he said he was afraid of failure.
GORDON:
Who isn't? It's gotta be something else.
- Did you hear?
- Hear what?
That we got a new medical examiner.
Much better than the old one.
And she smells nice.
[CHUCKLES]
See, Jim? Competition already.
Look at this. Crane developed protocols
for two inoculations.
Himself and somebody else. Subject B.
Ooh. I wonder who that is.
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]
[HEART BEATING RAPIDLY]
[H EARTBEAT SLOWS]
JONATHAN:
Dad?
Dad, you okay?
I'm glorious.
It's working, Jonathan.
I said it would.
And it's almost your turn.
You will be free of fear forever.
You'll be cured.
Are you ready, Jonathan?
Are you ready, son?
MARONI: Thank you for having me.
FALCONE: My pleasure.
MARONI: We're friends, eh?
- Of course.
Then let me talk to you as a friend.
You wanna have lunch, take a walk?
I'm happy to.
But a sandwich and a stroll
ain't gonna keep me from killing Penguin.
That little rat is dead.
So be it.
MAN 1:
Mr. Cobblepot, will this do?
We will not be serving that.
No, no, no.
I said lose the drapes, not tie them back.
We're opening in 10 hours.
MAN 2: Sorry.
GABE: Hey, boss.
Ah. They're ready.
GABE:
Still warm from the printer.
Nothing can go wrong tonight, Gabe.
This is more than an opening.
It's my moment.
They're perfect.
Take these to everybody on the list.
But not this one.
This one I wanna deliver in person.
I just want a word. I mean no harm.
That's close enough.
No harm, huh?
- So, you're the boss in here?
- I am.
Why you?
I see a lot of tough guys around here.
This is the only blade in the place.
And I'm holding it.
Fair enough.
- I wanna make a deal with you.
- A deal.
Yeah.
I think I might have skills
that could be useful to you.
Really.
What skills, exactly?
All kinds.
You protect me from these animals,
and I'll show you.
You think you're worth protecting?
You have no idea.
Huh.
- Can I help you?
- I don't think so. Can you?
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
What do you want?
What I want the poor have,
the rich need and if you eat it you'll die.
Is this...? Are you asking me a riddle?
- Do you like riddles?
- No.
So, do you give UP?
[CHUCKLES]
Friend, lo0kit...
Nothing. The answer is nothing.
The poor have it, the rich need it...
- Who are you?
- Edward Nygma.
I know who you are.
Then you know
that you're standing too close.
You know male emperor penguins
keep their eggs warm...
by balancing them on their feet?
Isn't that neat?
Nice to meet you, sir.
Keep moving.
Will do.
Cell-phone records?
And credit-card statements.
- Give me a hand.
- Yeah, sure.
- Uh, give me a minute.
- Take your time.
- It's good to see you, old friend.
- What are you doing here?
I wanted to invite you
to a party I'm hosting.
No, thanks.
I hear you. Too busy, I suppose.
Are you on a tricky case?
Anything I can help you with?
It worked so well the last time.
I don't want your help.
It was a mistake to ask.
I don't want you coming here.
You shouldn't treat me this way, Jim.
One day soon, you'll need my help.
You'll come to me.
And walking with a friend in the dark
is better than walking alone in the light.
Good luck with your police work.
And please, reconsider my invitation.
It won't be the same without you.
Do you trust me?
Of course.
I love you, son.
I wouldn't do anything to harm you.
Just go. Go ahead.
[HEART BEATING RAPIDLY]
You're being a very good boy.
[PANTING THEN YELLS]
Yes, don't struggle. Look at me.
Look in my eyes.
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
[SOBBING]
[GRUNTING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Ow!
[THUNDER CONTINUES RUMBLING]
GORDON: Hey.
- Hey, yourself.
- How's your first day going?
- Busy.
- Good, good. I've gotta get back, so...
- Yeah, hey.
Lee.
We can't do that here.
- Why? You kissed me in the bullpen.
- You weren't working here then.
- That makes a difference?
- It's not professional.
Well, I should hope not.
Lee.
Oops.
- Hey, Bullock.
BULLOCK: Sorry to interrupt.
What's up?
Nothing that can't wait on your love life.
Just business.
FALCONE: How does a cigar sound?
I've got some beautiful Castros...
I've been waiting to try.
Carmine, talk straight with me.
Why you doing this?
Granted Penguin is a money-maker.
How come you laying all this grease on me
to keep him alive?
What's your angle?
He's clever.
And I like to have a clever man beside me
who knows his place in life.
- You know how that goes.
- Yeah, all day.
He's clever enough to know that a little man
like him is never going to be the boss.
True enough.
So I'm supposed to give you
a prime asset like that...
and you're gonna bring out
some nice old cigars?
Heh. Of course, I'll show my gratitude
to you in a more formal way.
This is not a money thing.
- This is personal.
- I understand.
Do you know
Chief Judge Stanley Turnbull?
Of course.
He's the meanest son-of-a-mother bitch
in the courthouse.
Yes. A hard and righteous man.
- Powerful too.
- Put down some good friends of mine.
You bring me his ugly head
and, say, 200 grand, and you got a deal.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, I'll give you a better
deal than his head.
[MAN WHIMPERING NEARBY]
[SLAPPING]
[MARONI CHUCKLES]
MARONI:
On my mother's life.
Judge Turnbull.
FALCONE: He was out with the young man.
I had him drugged and brought here.
Now he's all yours.
Mine?
I mean, we'll share him, of course.
But, uh, in spirit, he's yours.
Now smile for the camera.
[TURNBULL WHIMPERS]
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
It's beautiful.
GORDON:
We must be missing something.
BULLOCK:
What about your pal, Penguin?
What about him?
He helped us with Flass.
- Maybe he'll help us with Crane.
- No. I'm not going back to him.
- It's worth a try.
- No, it's not.
Then we wait for another body to drop,
because we're not gonna find him here.
Yeah, you're right.
We're never gonna be able to track Crane.
We gotta get ahead of him
by finding out what's driving him.
We know what's driving him.
He's obsessed with fear.
Yeah, but why?
What's he afraid of? What happened to him
that made him this way?
His wife was killed in a car crash.
Yeah. Let's check that out.
BULLOCK: Got it. Karen Crane.
- Yeah.
Says here she died in a house fire,
not a car accident.
You think the coworker was lying?
Three other people said the same thing.
Crane must've lied about it
for some reason.
What happened in the fire?
Says she was sleeping
when the fire broke out.
Her husband, Gerald and son,
Jonathan, 8, were downstairs.
Crane was in the house when his wife died?
And didn't save her.
- No wonder he lied.
- He's ashamed.
His fear is the reason his wife died.
That's why he's doing this.
Address for the old Crane house. Let's go.
[HEART BEATING]
Jonathan?
Stop, Johnny. Stop! Stop there!
We've started the protocol.
It must be completed.
It will be harmful for you otherwise.
- I can't do it again.
- Think of it, Johnny. No more fear.
- I'm not even afraid like you.
- We're all afraid.
Every man and woman on the planet.
We're all standing at the edge
of the abyss, paralyzed by fear.
Come on, son. Trust me.
I just want to help you. And mankind.
Mankind, Johnny.
Now, you must be brave, hmm?
Come on, son. Are you with me?
Then let's go back to the house. It'll all
be over before you know it. I promise.
Come on.
[GRUNTING]
What's up, doc?
The name's Mace.
That's cute,
but I like to give my friends nicknames.
And yours is "doc"...
because you have a wise look
in your eyes for such a big man.
A real little firecracker, huh?
Hmm.
A firecracker goes off once,
and then just lies there.
What you're looking at
is the Fourth of July.
Come sit by me.
- Does that mean we have a deal?
- Sure, baby.
I have a couple of riders
I would like to talk...
Hush now, baby.
You talk too much, and you'll make me mad.
Hmm, let's see.
That's rider number one.
Don't call me baby.
Ah!
My name is Fish Mooney.
I'm in charge now.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
GORDON: G.C.P.D.
- No, no, no.
Dad, we have to go now.
[KNOCKING CONTINUES]
G.C.P.D.
Dad, they're going to arrest you
once they come in. We have to go.
There's time. We can complete the protocol.
GORDON:
Coming in.
[CLANGING NEARBY]
- What are you doing?
- We have to finish the protocol.
- It's the only way.
- Dad, that's too much.
It's the only way.
Dad.
- There's not enough time.
- It'll be fine.
- I love you, son.
- Stop!
[HEART BEATING]
[JONATHAN PANTING]
[SCREAMING]
Hands where we can see them!
Hands in the air or we'll shoot!
- You think I'm afraid of you?
BULLOCK: Not another step.
Afraid of your guns?
[GRUNTS]
I have no fear.
[GRUNTING]
You take him. I get the kid.
Call an ambulance.
It's all right, son. It's all right.
[PANTING]
Hello there, Master Bruce.
Well, you certainly took your time.
What, you stop off for a pie and a pint
on the way out, did you?
How long have you been there?
I don't know, about an hour.
Just when you were started climbing up
that really nasty hill.
- Well, thanks for your help.
- Yeah, I never got you down there, did I?
Are you all right?
Come here.
I'm cold, I'm tired and
my ankle's sprained.
ALFRED:
Oh.
[BRUCE GRUNTS]
I just wanna go home.
You wanna go home...
or do you wanna wait
and watch the sunrise?
Like you did with your dad?
Well, Alfred, you can only stay
if you think you can handle it.
If I can handle it?
Mate, this place is positively cushy...
compared to some of the places
I've slept at.
Cup of tea, you cheeky monkey?
[BAND PLAYING THE STRANGLERS'
"NO MORE HEROES"]
No more heroes anymore
[PUNK GRUNTING AND WHOOPING]
[PUNK CHEERS]
Penguin.
Where you going?
Don Maroni. It's such a
pleasure to see you.
Look at you. From the trunk of my car
to running your own club.
The place looks good, Penguin.
Hell of a turnout.
[MEN CHUCKLE]
MAN:
Yeah.
How about a table? Drinks?
My compliments, of course.
Expensive stuff. Let me see.
I had a little chat with Falcone.
I came here to let you know
that all is kosher between us.
As long as you don't go giving Falcone
any more of my secrets.
No.
Nothing like that.
Of course not. Grab a glass.
You better hope that old man Falcone
lives a long life.
Because the second he's out of the picture,
so are you.
Master B.
Sunrise.
Oh, hey. How are you?
I heard your suspect was killed.
He came after Harvey and me with a gun.
We didn't have a choice.
I'm so sorry. What about his son?
Paramedics were able to stabilize him.
I'm heading to the hospital
to check in on him.
- Well, let me know how he is.
- I will.
So all settled in here, huh?
Uh, almost.
- Think you're gonna like it here?
- I do, so far.
Good.
Um, I have tickets to the circus.
Do you wanna come with me?
- A circus?
- Yeah, they're good.
No, uh, sad elephants. Heh.
Circus, sure. Why not. Look, Lee...
Um...
No kissing here on the job, okay?
I'm serious.
"Okay" Okay?
If your hardass reputation
is worth that much to you.
- This is a place of work.
- Cops have feelings too.
- It's not unprofessional to show feelings.
- Yeah, it is. Those kinds of feelings. Yeah.
Fine. Be that way.
Hey-
I'm just joking. I'll be discreet.
All right, everyone, gather around.
Up until now, there's
been no order in here.
No structure.
Things are gonna change.
[DOOR OPENS]
[WOMAN GRUNTING AND WHIMPERING]
MAN:
She's back.
MY eyes.
They took my eyes.
The boy received a massive dose
of condensed hormones.
Cortisol, adrenalin and another compound
we're still trying to identify.
The combination nearly killed him.
But he's gonna live?
Yes.
But we ran a CAT scan in order to
determine if he suffered any brain damage.
The results, we've never seen
anything like them before.
The hormones themselves
have long since worn off.
But the effects, they seem to be lingering.
What are you saying?
That he's still in fear?
Well, not just fear.
Jonathan's brain activity shows
he's in a constant state of intense terror.
- How long until this goes away?
- Well, that's just the thing, detective.
We can't be certain it ever will.
Imagine the thing
you fear most in the world.
Imagine that's all you see.
Every waking hour.
[GRUNTING]
JONATHAN:
No.No.No.
[JONATHAN SCREAMS]
[English - US - SDH]