PENGUIN:
There's a war coming. A terrible war.
There will be chaos,
rivers of blood in the streets.
I know it. I can see it coming.
It's time. Somebody has to take over.
It might as well be me.
[SCREAMS]
Hello, James, old friend.
Mooney, the MCU cops,
none of them know Penguin's alive.
- If they did, I'd be dead.
- James Gordon is not a good guy.
He framed Mario
for the murder of the Waynes.
BARBARA: James Gordon is
the most honest man I've ever met.
This is not a city or a job for nice guys.
- You're a cynic. Slovenly, lackadaisical cynic.
- You're probably right.
[WHISPERING]
I am the Spirit of the Goat.
[IN DEEP VOICE]
MAN [ON TV]:
Gotham still held in a grip of terror...
as the mysterious masked killer...
...known as the Spirit of the Goat
remains on the loose.
But Gotham's Goat
hasn't cast his shadow...
...over Thomas
and Martha Wayne's celebration...
...of beloved son Bruce Wayne's
third birthday.
The Wayne family opened their home
to the children of the city orphanage...
- ...to share in the joyous day...
MAN: Shelly.
SHELLY: Aah!
MAN: Shh, Shh, shh.
That's the van registered
to Randall Milkie.
- We were right, Dix.
- Of course we're right.
Dispatch, Detective Dix...
...requesting backup
at 1100 Cannery Drive.
WOMAN [OVER RADIO]: Roger. On your...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Come on, man. We gotta get in there.
- Wait a second. Listen to me. Wait a minute.
Listen to me.
Randall thinks he's the reincarnation
of some ancient murdering goat spirit.
- We are waiting for backup.
- He's got Shelly Lawson.
If he kills her,
that's three people we lost to this maniac.
Gotham's golden rule, Harvey: No heroes.
Son of a bitch.
- Idiot, she's already dead.
BULLOCK: You don't know that.
DIX:
Yeah. I know it.
I told you.
Ripped By mstoll
BULLOCK: Shelly.
DIX: I told you she'd be cold.
She's been here half of the night.
BULLOCK:
Wait a minute. New candles, barely melted.
Just lit.
That's great. That's great news.
[FLOORBOARD CREAKS]
BULLOCK:
Randall Milkie, you're under arrest...
...for the murders of Shelly Lawson,
Daniel Tremont and Edward Talbot.
DIX:
Randall, be smart.
Come out of there,
or we're gonna have to blow you away.
MILKIE:
Randall Milkie is undone. Gone.
This body is moved
by the Spirit of the Goat.
BULLOCK: Ah, we're gonna go with Milkie.
I already did the paperwork.
[DIX YELLS]
Dix!
[DIX GRUNTING]
You can never stop the Goat.
This body may fail, but I will not.
I will always come back.
Come back from this.
[GUNSHOTS]
Milkie.
Dix!
Dix.
Talk to me. Talk to me.
Dix, come on. Come on. Dix. Help!
We got an officer down!
We need help, now!
NYGMA:
Detective Bullock.
- Detective Bullock, do you give up?
- What?
My riddle. A man has to cross the river
with a wolf, a cabbage and a goat.
Ed, please, what's the time of death?
Examiner pegs it at just before 3 a.m.
this morning.
He's a bit eager with his coagulation marker,
so I'd put it at closer to 1.
Killer left her identification for us.
Amanda Hastings, 21 years old.
- She comes from money.
- Mm-hm.
- Guessing she was the oldest in her family.
- Why is that?
The Goat always kills the firstborn.
It's all the same.
Same MO, same victim choice,
presentation, it's all the same.
We got a copycat.
- You all right, detective?
- No, I'm not all right.
I already solved this case.
- Where's Gordon?
- Apparently, he's not answering his phone.
He's not answering his...?
You mean I'm on the clock
before the Boy Scout?
- Mm-hm.
- This is frigging ridiculous.
Fine, I'll tell you the answer.
The man crosses the river
with the wolf and the cabbage.
- He leaves the wolf, goes back with the cab--
- Ed.
[BUZZING]
- I'm not apologizing for my past.
- I'm not asking you to.
- You're not listening.
- No, you're not listening.
- I'm not asking you to walk away from this.
- Really? It sounds like you are.
And we keep going around and around,
and I keep telling you I don't have a choice.
Barbara...
This city, the law, the crime here, they're
all twisted up in each other like a maze.
I came here to be a cop...
...but the city needs something else.
It's okay. I understand.
I'm just asking for one thing.
Half of what you have to carry.
God knows I've dumped my half on you,
and you carry it.
What I'm dealing with, it's so dangerous.
Half of what you carry.
If you think I care about the risk,
then you're forgetting who I am.
I swear I'm not.
Are we okay?
Are we still fighting?
We're negotiating terms.
Hmm.
That's not good for me.
You tell me what you're up against...
...okay?
You let me in.
Then we're okay.
[BUZZING]
- That's work again.
- Yep.
I'll tell you everything.
Everything I can.
Okay? I'll make it right.
Okay.
Right there.
We've been canvassing this waterfront
for days, Monty.
None of these river rats are gonna help us.
If we don't get a lead in the next 24 hours,
MCU is dropping this.
Hey.
I'm on the disability six months.
Where do you expect me to go?
I'm not flushing you, old-timer, okay?
Just wanna ask you some questions.
About a shooting that took place
on that pier back there.
A shooting? Yeah.
- I saw it good.
MONTOYA: Okay. Great.
- You ever see this man?
- That was the man did the shooting.
Cold customer, ice water in the veins.
We got the son of a bitch.
We got Gordon.
- Gotham Goat?
- A wannabe.
For a copycat, the copy is, uh,
downright creepy, is what it is.
- You moonlighting or something?
- Huh? Me?
Yeah, because you're late,
and you look like crap warmed over.
- Write me up if you want.
- Screw you, Boy Scout.
- You're in a good mood.
- I'm in a déjà vu acid flashback.
Someone's hunting the kids
of Gotham's 1 percent.
The press will have a field day.
City turns upside down.
The whole thing's gonna come down
on the G.C.P.D. like a ton of bricks.
Let's catch him quick.
BULLOCK: I'm guessing the killer knew
the victim, Amanda Hastings, somehow.
We'll go see the family, see if we can try
to get something we can work with.
Hey, Nygma.
Let me know when they're set up
for the autopsy.
- Anything in particular you want me to--?
- Just call me.
You see, the strange thing,
and the horrible thing...
...is that I've been having the same dream
for weeks...
...of a dark overbearing presence.
Mr. Hastings, about your daughter,
and we know that this is difficult...
...but did she have anyone in her life
that worried you?
- Anyone who might have wished her harm?
- Everybody loved my Amanda.
Mr. Hastings, are you all right?
Robert, if you need to take a moment,
I'm sure it will be all right.
Absolutely.
Come on.
I know you gentlemen
are working against the clock...
...but I'm afraid Mr. and Mrs. Hastings
might not be ready for this.
I can see that. And you are
the Hastings' therapist, Dr. Marks?
Yes. I treat mostly Mr. Hastings,
but we've had many family sessions.
Mr. Hastings has a very delicate nature.
He's not capable
of dealing with this kind of tragedy.
No one's capable of dealing
with this kind of tragedy.
It's a freight train.
It runs you over,
and you try to pick up what's left.
You don't believe in treatment.
I believe in the tranquilizers
you clobbered Mrs. Hastings with.
- If you're giving out samples...
- Okay. Uh...
- Detective, maybe we should, uh...
BULLOCK: Yeah, you're right, we should.
Excuse me.
- Thank you, doctor.
MARKS: Mm-hm.
KRINGLE:
Uh-huh. All right, got it.
And got it.
Yes, sir, I'll bring those files right away.
- Mr. Nygma.
- Hello, Miss Kringle.
[SNIFFS]
I'm just looking for all the information you
have on the Goat murders from 10 years ago.
Don't you find it curious...
...why someone would resurrect the myth
of a centuries-old bogeyman?
What is it about the Goat that has made
two people decide to kill in his name?
No, I don't find it curious.
- I think I would like your parents.
- Excuse me?
Kringle. Such a rare surname.
Most people changed it generations ago
out of embarrassment.
Not only did your parents keep it,
they called you Kristin.
Kristin Kringle. Ha, ha.
They must be very humorous people.
Humor is so important, don't you think?
Remember,
you have to sign out any evidence you pull.
How do you find anything at all in here?
I mean, organizationally speaking,
this place is a shambles.
I am warning you, Nygma.
I have this as exactly as I want it.
I know where everything is.
- Understand?
- Preternaturally.
But...
...I can help you, Kristin Kringle.
I doubt that very much.
There is a much better way to do this.
Amanda Hastings was last seen
entering this building Tuesday midnight.
That's about 36 hours ago.
GORDON:
You think she was abducted from here?
I don't know.
It was Milkie's MO 10 years ago.
He took each one of the victims
from their homes.
- But CSI found no signs of a break-in.
- They didn't with Randall either.
He worked for an air-conditioning
maintenance crew...
...that covered all three buildings.
He had keys?
He had keys.
This is Detective Gordon.
I need the employee list of every
maintenance and janitorial company...
...with access to the Hastings' building.
Yeah, I'll tell him.
They're ready for the autopsy.
Mother!
GERTRUD: Away for so long,
and now he scratches at the door...
...the filthy tomcat.
Hi, Mom. I'm alive.
Why you always think I'm running off
with some painted lady?
- I don't even date.
- Ha!
Why you don't call your mother
in all this time? I tell you why.
You got tangled
in some hussy's demon purse.
Mother, there was no hussy.
Only betrayal and savagery and...
All I wanted was a little respect.
And they hurt me so cruelly.
- Oh. There was no other woman?
- Heh-heh-heh.
I have been to hell and back.
They tried to kill me.
The bullies again. My poor, poor darling.
They only do these things
because they resent you.
Envy and spite...
...that's all it is.
You watch, Ma.
I'm gonna be somebody in this town.
I always knew this.
The victim was asphyxiated,
likely with ether or chloroform.
Look under the scalp.
Humor me.
At the base of the skull,
there'd be an incision about an inch long...
...sewn closed.
EXAMINER:
Wait a minute.
Yes. How did I miss that?
An incision stitched closed
near the occipital.
Over a foreign object.
- What is it?
- It's a penny.
He's right.
- A penny?
- I know Milkie's MO.
No one could know that detail.
It isn't a copycat.
It can't be.
BULLOCK: Ten years ago Randall Milkie
took an 1813 Liberty penny just like this one...
...and sewed it into the heads
of each of his victims.
Why?
How the hell do I know?
He bum-rushed me wearing animal horns.
- I shot him. We didn't talk coin collecting.
- You're sure no one else found this out?
Milkie was the definition of a loner.
He didn't tell anybody.
- We left it out of the file intentionally.
- Suppressed evidence.
We Easter-egged it.
A killer like the Goat had a good chance
of drawing admirers.
Yeah, it's copycat porn.
We left out this one detail. The coins.
It never hit the papers.
How the hell did this copy-Goat know
about this?
Okay, so you hid it,
but the medical examiner, he had to know.
Ed Hayes, yeah, sure.
But he died of cirrhosis. That just leaves me.
And Dix.
- Captain, please, there's no reason--
- Go talk to him.
Make sure he didn't tell anyone
about the coins.
Hell, see if he's got any ideas.
[ON TV] I'm Lacey White,
and this is the Gotham Seven Goatwatch.
Tonight, Gotham's wealthiest 1 percent
rest fitfully. ..
...under a copycat killer's deadly shadow.
And if you happen to be one of the city's
high-society silver spoons...
...then you're probably headed
to the Swiss Alps right now and away from...
- They've got them all running like rabbits.
- Yeah.
I don't know why he chose an ungulate
for his totem...
...but he does know how to scare them.
You do realize you happen to be one of them,
don't you, Master Bruce?
Yeah, a firstborn son of Gotham's rich
and powerful.
I don't know,
maybe we should leave town for a little bit.
Pop down to the lake house.
You like it there.
I'm not going anywhere.
I have work to do.
Besides...
...why would the Goat take me?
There's no one to take me from.
- Oh, my God.
- I'm improving your system.
Implementing a rhizomatic cross index,
with your case files classified by subject...
...but arranged more like the way
a peat-moss organism grows.
You know, laterally.
- I had this entire room organized.
- Yes, but now it will be rhizomatic. Lateral.
What did I ever do to you, Nygma?
What did I do that compels you to come here
with your endless suggestions and riddles?
My god, the riddles.
Are you trying to get me to quit?
- You can't want my job.
- No, no, no. I want you.
To keep your job and to have it here...
...for working.
Okay.
I'm getting a sense
that this was somehow inappropriate.
You are so odd.
I'll just take my nonhierarchical data
paradigms out of your hair...
...and leave you to your work.
How long has it been
since you've seen this guy?
Bullock, I know what happened.
Anybody in your situation--
Listen. You think you can shrink my head,
Boy Scout?
You can't. This is the black box, man.
And we don't open the black box, ever.
- Okay, fine.
- Why don't you sit your ass down?
I'll be back in a few minutes.
We're both on this case.
BULLOCK: Dix.
- Hey. What do we have here?
Harvey Bullock, boy detective.
Look at you up there, huh,
living the high life?
And me down here,
all broken up with a busted liver.
Don't put that on me, old man.
Your bum liver's between you and the bottle.
I just busted up your gams
and put you in that chair.
Gotham's golden rule:
- No heroes, Bullock.
- No heroes.
Listen, Dix,
we have to talk about the case.
About the Goat.
I was wondering
when you would ask for my help.
- I'm not asking for your help.
- That don't mean you don't need it.
Who's this? Your partner?
- James Gordon. Nice to meet you.
- Come on, Dix.
Did you ever tell anyone about
Randall Milkie? The Liberty pennies?
We said we weren't going to.
We sealed them.
I know we sealed them, you jackass.
I told you to seal them.
Okay, but this new killer's
doing the same thing.
He's stitching up coins
in the heads of his victims.
Any idea how he came up with that?
I didn't tell anybody.
Ed Hayes didn't tell nobody.
And you didn't tell nobody.
- So, what the hell does that mean?
- It means we were wrong about Milkie.
- He was not working alone.
- No.
Mm-hm.
You do not have a copycat killer here.
You do not have a lone killer.
What you have...
...is a conspiracy.
A conspiracy to hang rich kids
off local historical landmarks?
Yeah, right.
He always thinks he's the smartest one
in the room.
I know, right?
That's because I'm always in a room
full of idiots.
Watch out for him.
- Oh, yeah? Why's that?
- He's a loose cannon.
He thinks he's a white knight,
jumping into the breach...
...like some idiot in the movies.
We talking about Bullock here?
- We're talking about Bullock here.
- Harvey Bullock?
Harvey Bullock.
Detective Bullock, do you wanna settle
the bill or should we send it to you?
You can just put it in the mail, thanks.
- Is he getting those magazines I ordered?
- Those are awful magazines, detective.
BULLOCK: But he's getting them?
ADMINISTRATOR: Yes, he is.
Good.
Thank you.
No, Mom, I'm just grabbing a few things.
Yes. Yes, I know.
I'll be at the marina at 9. Okay.
- Here you are.
- Thank you, Anita.
Will you put
some snack stuff together, please?
[FLOORBOARD CREAKING]
Miss Ember?
Anita, have you seen the tops
to my yellow silk...?
Anita?
[SCREAMS]
Ember Copley was supposed to meet
her parents tonight at 9:00 at the marina.
When she didn't show, they came back,
found the maid out cold, Ember gone.
- You think it's our guy?
- It's our guy.
He slips in, chloroforms the maid,
grabs Ember.
- No sign of B and E, nothing, like a ghost.
- Like he had keys.
Randall Milkie had a ritual.
Dress the victims, kill them, do his coin trick.
Whole thing took eight hours.
If our copy-Goat's doing the same thing,
we're running out of time.
I pulled the employee list from the agencies
that do maintenance on Copley's building.
Looking for an employee that had access
to both victims' apartments.
- That's a lot of people.
- Yeah, but our guy's been busy.
He had to have called in sick
the last couple days.
Get Nygma in there.
He's freaky good with puzzles.
You got it.
- Renee, we have to talk.
- What are you doing here?
I know you think he's done terrible things,
but I also know you care about the truth.
You shouldn't be here.
You shouldn't be seen here.
Damn it, Renee, will you listen to me?
I'll work with you, okay? I will tell you
whatever I know, whatever I can find out.
- I need you to keep an open mind, okay?
- It's too late for that.
Whatever's happening,
you've got it wrong, Renee.
He can't tell me, but it isn't what you think.
He's trying to protect me.
He won't tell me who's out there,
who he's afraid of.
He's right not to.
- Wait, why?
- Because it'll get you killed. Okay?
You understand?
What he knows, who he knows, will kill you.
We got a judge issuing a warrant tonight.
You know how much I care about you.
When Gordon gets arrested, get out of here.
If Jim gets arrested, then this is exactly
where I have to be, by his side.
Please, just leave.
Get out of Gotham just till this is over.
And don't come to me again.
So four guys have called in sick
since last week.
The suspects from the outer boroughs
are cleared, another is out of state...
...but apparently, it's unconfirmed, so...
- So that leaves one last guy.
- Raymond Earl.
Shift supervisor says
he's been squatting in a place...
...near Cannery Park
around the 1100 block.
- That's him.
- You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure. I'm 100 percent sure.
Déjà voodoo all day long.
This is where we got Randall Milkie
10 years ago.
This is where Dix fell.
Bullock.
- Gotta go in. Come on.
- Yeah. Yeah.
EARL: We're going to put you to sleep
for good now.
You're lucky to be the sacrifice.
[CLATTERING NEARBY]
Go get her.
GORDON:
It's okay. You're safe.
You all right? Okay.
[EARL YELLS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
You'll never stop the Goat.
- I will always come back.
- Quit saying that.
Raymond Earl, you're under arrest.
Not bad.
All right.
[METAL CLANKS]
[BRUCE GRUNTING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
GERTRUD:
Your suit is ready.
- I steamed it nice.
- Thanks, Mom.
GERTRUD:
Mm-hm.
I'm worried for you.
So anxious you look.
These moves you make...
...they're safe, yes?
- You're not doing anything illegal?
- No, Mom, don't worry.
- It's just business.
- Well, business is all very fine.
But always remember,
you can trust no one.
No one but your mother.
I know. I know.
But you know what?
I think I finally found somebody
I can trust.
- A policeman.
- Police?
- The police are liars.
- Mm-mm. Not this one, Mom.
He's a real friend.
Hmph.
He'll help me come out right in the end.
GORDON: Raymond Earl, 33 years old.
Janitor in the city.
Works with an agency
that services the buildings of both victims.
And he's not talking.
History of mental illness, misdemeanor arrest
for lewd and lascivious, public disturbance...
Thank you, Jesus. You got him.
Good work, detectives.
I got a lot of phone calls to make.
Bullock, look happier.
What?
Randall Milkie worked for a company
that serviced the buildings of his victims.
Same as Raymond here.
Milkie was mentally ill.
No violent crimes in his history.
Same as him.
Ten years apart, they never meet,
and one day, suddenly out of the blue...
...they both decide to become the Goat?
It's like...
It's like something found them,
changed them.
Are you talking about Dix
and his conspiracy theory?
No, no. It just doesn't add up.
How'd he know about the coin?
I know that we're missing something,
and if we keep missing it...
...l'm afraid we're never gonna stop this.
Okay. We go back to Milkie's files, we look
for possible accomplices, connections.
Tomorrow, tomorrow.
I just-- I need to think.
Why don't you get some rest?
Yeah.
Good night.
Good night, Jim.
No. No. No. No.
Oh, no. No. No.
No. No. No.
Holy Ghost on a bicycle.
Barbara?
Jim, look, I don't know everything,
but I know enough.
You have to listen to me now.
- Baby, I can barely stand.
- Montoya has a witness.
- What?
- They believe you killed...
...this Cobblepot person.
- I didn't.
- It doesn't matter anymore.
They've got a warrant for your arrest.
What aren't you telling me?
For weeks now,
it's like you've been a different person.
Something happened not long
after you started the job, something...
Something you don't feel right about.
Somehow they've cornered me.
- Tied my hands.
- Come with me now.
I don't care what I leave behind
as long as we leave it together.
If they take you away, Jim,
I'm scared I'll lose you.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Barbara--
- Please.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
I can't run.
Can't run.
James Gordon...
...you're under arrest for the murder
of Oswald Chesterfield Cobblepot.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can be used against you
in a court of law.
MARKS:
You're drifting down and away, deeper--
- I got it.
- I'm sorry to interrupt.
It's Detective Bullock, isn't it?
Did you wanna interview Mr. Hastings?
Your secretary told me
I might be able to find you here.
I was hoping to pick your brain
about the case.
Oh. Uh, I'll just be a minute. It's okay.
BULLOCK: I didn't realize this before.
You're a hypnotist, right?
- A hypnotherapist.
- Oh, therapist. It's a funny word, "therapist."
It can either mean "therapist"
or "the rapist" if...
So you do pro bono work
at an outpatient clinic or a couple of them?
- I do. I try to give back.
- Yeah, you've been giving back for a while.
- Uh... Twelve years now.
- Mm-hm.
That's good.
To be honest, I wanted to talk to you
about one of your pro bono patients.
Raymond Earl.
He's a person of interest in our investigation.
Our records indicate you've seen him
at least a few times, right?
Hmm. Sounds familiar. Last year, maybe?
And Mr. Hastings, Amanda's father,
we know he's your patient.
When we were here yesterday,
he was doing something really curious.
He kept clenching his fist, over and over.
- Yes, he does that.
- Yeah.
See, I was reading about that,
and it said that if a patient has a compulsion...
...like a bad idea or an impulse...
...that the hypnotist
can put the poor sap under...
...and introduce a physical movement...
...like clenching your fist.
So instead of doing what the compulsion
wants the person to do...
...they just...
...clench their fist.
That's how it works. Pretty much.
So Mr. Hastings,
when he's in a room full of people...
...and he wants to start screaming,
I don't know...
...instead of doing that, he just:
Mm-hm.
Yeah. Okay.
What about Raymond Earl?
Why does he clench his fist?
And What about Randall Milkie?
I know you treated him over 10 years ago,
and I want you to follow me...
...because this part gets weird.
See, I think a hypnotist completely
turned both those men upside down...
...until their own identity was the bad idea...
...and then it wasn't even them
clenching their fists anymore.
It was the Spirit of the Goat.
Hmm.
I underestimated you.
- I really did.
- So I'm right.
Aha! Yes. I'm right.
So you trawled the outpatient clinics...
...so you could find a suitable
borderline case like Randall Milkie...
...and then you hypnotize the poor bastard
until he doesn't even know who he is.
And then I tell him who he is.
That's pretty good intellection, detective.
Why? Why hypnotize a janitor...
...and turn him into the Goat?
- You wouldn't understand.
- Try me.
It isn't an act of murder or madness.
It's an act of therapy.
- Therapy? For who?
- For Gotham.
- Excuse me?
- This city used to have hope.
And they gunned it down in the streets,
the rich, the powerful.
Their greed is pathological,
an id run rampant, eating Gotham alive.
So your 1 percent solution
is to kill the city's rich kids?
Negative reinforcement.
To believe that the Goat is real...
...that it wouldn't tolerate this?
Gotham wanted that,
no matter how painful it was.
It's true what they say.
You can't really hypnotize somebody
to do something...
...that deep down
they don't already want to do.
And deep down we all wanna eat the rich.
Tell me.
You are 100 percent nuthouse crazy, lady.
- Dr. Marks, is everything okay?
- No, it's not.
Dr. Marks, you're under arrest
for conspiracy to commit murder coercion...
...and a few things
we'll probably have to name after you.
Well, I do have another one for you.
Robert, the golden temple is open.
Now, kill this man.
- Aah!
- No, Robert--!
You must die.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Freeze, lady!
[MARKS SCREAMING]
One more time, take me through the part
where you drove to the nice part of town...
...and shot the doctor lady?
We caught the other half of the killer.
Dr. Marks was the Spirit of the Goat.
That's the part that I don't--
GORDON:
We're on the same side. You understand?
We're fighting the same war,
and I'm getting somewhere.
- Getting into a 6-by-8 at Blackgate Pen.
- What is this?
MCU's taking Detective James Gordon
in custody.
- What?
- Your boy here murdered Oswald Cobblepot.
- That's a damn lie.
- He's right. It was a lie.
I didn't shoot Oswald Cobblepot.
I lied. I didn't shoot him, Bullock.
- Of course you didn't, partner.
- No, I mean it.
- Harvey Bullock, you're under arrest.
- For what?
Accomplice in the murder
of Oswald Cobblepot.
Our witness places you at the scene.
You think you can walk in here
and take my people like that?
We're not here to take down the G.C.P.D.,
just these two.
They're G.C.P.D.,
so the MCU's got a problem.
Yeah, you got a problem.
You got a real problem, you...
[DOOR CLOSES]
- Holy crap.
- Hello.
[CHUCKLES]
I am Oswald Cobblepot.
- You son of a bitch.
- Harvey.
You son of a bitch!
Ripped By mstoll