Previously on Gotham...
Where is Xander Wilde?
My God,
there's two of 'em.
I'm gonna drive you mad...
brother.
All of Gotham will be joining you, too.
You shall become the Demon's Head.
She's got the mark of the Demon's Head.
No woman has ever been allowed
to lead the League of Shadows.
But the sisters of the
League are yours to command.
Tell me what I need to know.
I could have killed
Jerome, but I didn't.
Don't take so much responsibility that
you get yourself killed.
I came up with a plan
to turn this city into a madhouse.
Oh, we're gonna need a lot more of this.
Thank you all for coming this evening.
As your interim mayor, I
know my recent appointment
was sudden.
And, perhaps, a bit of a shock to some.
Quite frankly, I was shocked.
What is important now is the
future of this great city.
And that is why I am
meeting with all of you.
Well, Mayor,
as chairperson of
Gotham's Moral Authority
Society, our members
have been, quite frankly,
unnerved by the recent going-ons
in our great city.
We have seen
criminals take office, gun fights
in our streets, corruption...
Mrs. Haverstock, the
commissioner and I have worked
tirelessly these past few weeks
to improve the way
this city conducts itself.
Wyatt? Everything all right?
We're looking into it now, sir.
Did a window blow open?
It's gotten so cold.
- What's happened?
- Don't come any closer!
Good evening, everyone.
- What do you want with us?
- Sorry,
no time for questions, Mr. Mayor.
You see, your presence is
urgently needed elsewhere.
Whatever you expect as ransom,
I-I will double it.
I have access to the
police pension fund.
Wow, that could be a lot of money.
Tempting, but, uh...
no, thanks.
Bridgit, isn't it?
I can get you safe passage
from the city, money, a new home...
It was people like you that locked me up
in Strange's lab, and thanks to that,
there is no Bridgit anymore.
I can get you a pardon, son.
All will be forgiven,
just stop this lunatic.
"Lunatic" is a little harsh.
I prefer "visionary."
Oswald, can't you do something?
Afraid not.
I am with Mr. Valeska 100%.
Every cop in this city
will be looking for us,
and when they find you, expect no mercy,
just a hail of bullets.
So serious.
That's why your approval
ratings are so low.
Hey, tell you what.
Try threatening me again, but this time,
try it with a smile.
Aw, see, this is what's wrong.
Nobody knows how to
have fun anymore, right?
But see our friend down there?
Bag head?
He's figured out a way to solve that.
It's time to give this city
the boost it needs.
Time to stop taking ourselves
so seriously
I mean, come on, Gotham.
What do you have to lose?
Except your sanity.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
You gonna tell me why we needed
to come to the garage, Alfred?
Happy birthday, Master Wayne.
You remembered.
Of course I remembered.
I bloody love your birthdays.
Your seventh was an absolute blinder.
Yeah, I remember you had
about 50 kids come up here,
but you were off outside, on your own.
You were obsessed by this one
gift that your dad gave you...
This bright red wagon.
You were in the garden all
day, collecting all these rocks.
When I asked you what you
were gonna do with these rocks,
you said, "I'm gonna build a home
for my wagon.
A secret place that only I know about."
- What's this?
- Well, it's the reason why
I brought you out to
the garage, Master Bruce.
Alfred, I don't know what to say.
V-8, five liter, 460 horsepower engine.
Painted matte black, anti-reflective.
Very difficult to see at night.
Oh, and, of course, this.
100% bulletproof.
Best be prepared, eh?
Oh... Oh, mate.
Jim, hey.
What gives?
The mayor and the police commissioner
have been kidnapped by Jerome.
Got every cop in the city out there
searching all the spots
Jerome's been seen the last week.
You got something for me?
I was gonna say I just
won a hundred bucks
in the scratch-off lotto
at the liquor store, and we could go
to the track with it, but, uh,
we can do your thing first.
- Gordon.
- We need to talk.
Oswald?
I'm out back. Come alone.
Yeah. All right.
Well, this is a first.
Are you doing anything about Jerome?
We're looking for him.
Do you know where he is?
And if I did, do you really
think I would just tell you?
Have you march in there, guns blazing?
He needs to be stopped.
He has everyone under his thumb...
Freeze, Firefly, Hatter.
They are all part of his plan.
A dark, terrible plan.
Which is?
Scarecrow has made a gas for him.
- Like a fear toxin?
- Worse.
Much worse.
I saw it turn someone into
a maniacal, cackling, violent animal.
And what does he plan to do with it?
He's smart. He hasn't shared
the details of his plans with anyone.
Instead, we all have a
separate task to perform.
Such as?
He has yet to give me my role.
Why did you come here if
you're not gonna help me?
He scares the living
hell out of me, okay?
I mean, I was willing
to play along with him
for a while.
Perhaps he had a way
to make us all rich?
A return to the good old days, you know?
But nothing good will come of this.
Or maybe you just don't
like the competition.
Jerome casts quite the shadow.
Oh, please!
He's a maniac, an anarchist.
He is not interested in money or power.
And I am an honest criminal, Jim.
Where is he? Where is the gas?
He only tells you what he needs to,
when he needs to.
I just know he has to be stopped.
Jim! Hey!
You down here?! Jim?!
- Yeah.
- Hey.
A uni just spotted Jerome
near Paisley Square.
All right, let's go.
♪ Time has come today ♪
♪ Young hearts can go their way ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Can't put it off another day ♪
♪ Time has come today... ♪
Hey, what happened to my mic?
Hey, buddy, beat it, will ya?
I'm trying to work here.
Whoo!
Where's everyone going?
Ladies and gentlemen, we are
the Arkham Asylum Lunatics.
We came here to blow some minds! Whoo!
Sorry to interrupt your little show,
but you are gonna love this next one.
Introducing Mayor Pritchard,
Commissioner Reynolds,
Archbishop McGregor,
and this lady...
whoever she is.
This is everybody.
Everybody, say hi.
Now, as you can see,
we're still waiting
for two guests of honor.
But in the meantime,
let's go over the rules
of tonight's entertainment,
shall we?
Dynamite.
Trigger.
I don't get what I want?
Boom. Headless people.
And if any of you are thinking
of going anywhere, you'll die, too.
Now, the one man who can
give me what I want...
Come over here.
Calling Gordon.
Calling Captain James Gordon.
I speak on behalf of myself
and all other gang leaders in this city
when I say your arrogance and disrespect
will no longer be tolerated.
You beat and then dragged
my brother from here
like a dog.
Your brother's an ass.
He abuses our staff and refuses
to pay his exorbitant tab.
He is my brother,
and he demands your respect.
And I suppose an apology
would be out of the question?
Your blood will be
his apology.
Thought so.
Could've handled them.
That's the advantage of having
your own personal army, Tabs...
You don't have to.
Isn't that right?
What's wrong?
Ra's al Ghul chose you, no one else,
to pass on his spirit.
We will serve you,
protect you, of course,
but surely, you intend
to continue his legacy
and not just remain here in this place?
What does that mean?
"Continue his legacy."
I like the sound of that.
As I told you...
we have much more to show you.
Are you ready?
Yes.
What the hell is that?
Gentlemen, ladies, your assistance
is urgently required.
Be careful... these are
very dangerous materials.
Oh, we're counting on it.
More laughing gas
we need to make.
What?
There's no time to waste!
We need it in bulk, you see.
W-Well, how much of it do you need?
Oh.
This much.
Ladies and gentlemen,
as I live and breathe,
James Gordon is in the house.
I'm not talking to you
until I can get up there
and check on the
well-being of your hostages.
First of all, Jim, you're late.
Secondly, I think I'm the one
who should be making demands.
Don't you?
What you're doing is an
act of terror, Valeska.
- Yeah, you scumbag!
- Ask our mayor
what this city's policy is on
negotiating with terrorists.
Terrorist?
Frankly, I'm offended.
No, no, no!
That's close enough, Gordon.
And none of you go anywhere, either.
Dead man's trigger.
This falls out of my hand
for any reason and...
bang!
I got two empty chairs here.
You haven't even asked
me who they're for yet.
All right, I'll bite. Who are they for?
Come on, James.
You're a detective.
Do some detecting.
Jeremiah, your brother.
Bingo. That's one.
- And the other?
- Well, the only other
irksome do-gooder who's ever
spoiled my fun in this town.
Bruce Wayne!
No.
No?
You can take me.
I'll sit up there with
one of those things
around my neck, but I
won't let you have him.
Well, I don't want you,
Jim.
I want my brother
and I want Bruce.
I want them now.
All right. Let me get
these people out of here,
I'll come up there...
You are not listening to me!
And that is forcing my hand.
Jerome...
No...
Bring me my brother.
Bring me Wayne.
Bring 'em now.
♪ Happy birthday ♪
♪ A dear, Master B. ♪
♪ To you. ♪
I'll get some plates.
You know, for a billionaire,
your security system is...
lame.
Miss Kyle.
Thank you, Alfred.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
For what?
Visiting me on my birthday.
Oh.
I actually didn't know
it was your birthday.
I just happened to be
strolling in the neighborhood.
- Mm-hmm.
Either way...
it's good to see you.
I knew it was an act.
What?
The brat...
and the drinking, the-the friends.
It was an act.
I think you're more
sure about that than me.
Master Bruce,
we have visitors.
Bruce, we need your help.
What happened?
Don't you know it's rude
to keep a guy waiting?
Bring me my hostages, James.
My trigger finger is getting itchy.
The hostages he wants are his brother...
and you.
What, you have a laugh? No bloody way.
I don't like it any more than you do.
But, Bruce, you have to trust me.
Lucius and I have a plan.
You know what?
I don't think you're
taking me seriously enough.
Well...
all right.
Let's see.
Eeny meeny miny moe,
one of these people have got to... go.
Oh, it's that guy.
Oh, well.
Did you see what just happened?
That man's a raving bloody lunatic.
- He can't be trusted.
- For once I agree with Alfred.
Bruce, listen to me.
With your help, we can
prevent more deaths.
What's the plan?
Jerome is using a
shortwave radio trigger
with a dead man's
switch... If we can cut
the signal, he won't be able
to activate the explosives.
This emits a powerful
signal that disables
all radio waves close to it.
Once within a few feet of
Jerome's device, his trigger
- will be useless.
- That will give us the time
for the snipers to get a clean shot
on Jerome, Firefly and the others.
If I wear this, that gives
you time to take them out.
Correct.
Are you sure it's gonna work?
I'm positive.
99% positive.
What are we waiting for?
Those people need our help.
Good man.
Ra's owned this house for as
long as this city has existed.
He said he kept his secrets in here.
Ancient secrets.
None of us have ever seen
what's behind this door.
It remains locked,
and there is no key.
Tried dynamite?
No need.
Our master chose you
for a reason.
All my life...
I have known that I was meant for more.
That there was something
deep inside of me
that I couldn't explain.
I'm home.
Sir, we got target in sight.
No way in from below the stage.
Four of my men have found positions.
Good.
Stay low, hang tight.
No hair triggers.
One missed shot means adios Mayor.
Copy that.
Standing by.
I watch the news.
I know why you're here, Mr. Gordon.
And you must be out of
your mind if you think
I'm gonna be led like
a lamb to slaughter.
I understand your concern,
but your brother doesn't bluff.
If we ignore his demands,
there's no telling what he might do.
- We can block his remote's signal with this.
- Thanks.
If you and Bruce can get
within a few feet of him,
it will disable his remote...
He'll be a sitting duck.
- Our snipers can take it from there.
- For God's sake, Gordon,
you have to know what he wants.
To... murder us both
on live television.
Mr. Valeska.
I'm Bruce Wayne.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Likewise. I... wish the
circumstances were better.
May I ask what it is
you've been working on?
Um, yeah.
It's a compact electrical engine.
It generates power.
Fascinating.
How much power?
Just two could light up every building
south of Westward Bridge.
You have a brilliant mind.
And we all hope we can soon
be rid of your brother,
so that you can carry out
your work free from fear.
I understand if you choose
not to help us today.
But I trust that Captain
Gordon and Mr. Fox
will see that no harm comes to me.
But even if it does...
maybe, by facing Jerome...
I can show the people of Gotham
that standing up to terror
is the only way to take its power away.
Well said.
Harvey?
Hey. Just got word
that Freeze and Scarecrow broke into
Wayne Industries' chemical lab.
Jerome's playing the long game, here,
but we're not gonna be sure what it is
- unless we get ahead of him.
- The gas.
Penguin told me about
a new Scarecrow toxin.
Head over to the lab, we're
on our way to the Square.
They've got a weapon.
Poison gas.
Okay, let's go.
Thank you.
You two.
Hey!
Hey, buddy.
What happened?
What's so funny?
No, no, no, no, no!
Ma'am.
Let me help you.
What happened?
They made us make it.
Tons of it.
Where is it?
It's gone.
They took it.
♪ Why are we waiting? ♪
♪ Waiting, waiting,
waiting, waiting ♪
♪ Someone's gonna die! ♪
Well.
Look who decided to show up.
We were starting to get nervous.
Especially, the mayor here.
My guests of honor,
please, take your seats onstage.
Come on.
Don't be shy.
It's all right.
We don't have all day.
It's activated, just let
them get a little closer.
On my command.
My men have all targets in view.
Standing by.
Hi, brother.
- Now.
- Fire.
All targets, fire!
I had my guys take up the
best vantage points last night.
So they've been watching
your little SWAT team all day.
Now, Bruce, brother dear.
Get up onstage.
It's time to get this
party really started, huh?
What are you doing here?
This is a restricted area.
Our cargo is too precious to waste.
Let me give you something I like to keep
up my sleeves for times just like these.
Oh, my God!
You can pilot this
contraption alone, sir?
Yes.
Then, look into my eyes.
The kidnappings, the
concert in the Square.
All to draw the biggest crowds,
so we can drop the laughing gas on them?
This is madness.
I thought
you'd appreciate the beauty of it all.
But Jerome was right.
You know, he anticipated your betrayal?
That's right.
You went to Gordon.
Judas.
Tie him up,
put him on the blimp.
Jerome wants him to have
a bird's-eye view.
This book tracks Ra's legacy
dating back nine centuries.
Did you know he not only
overthrew governments,
but infiltrated royal families?
Ra's influenced history.
He was a cult leader, and he
still has them brainwashed.
And what about me, am I brainwashed?
There are things written here
that could change the way
we view the past forever.
Perhaps, I am the one to
bring that change to light.
Look. This book was compiled
by shamans and mystics
from all over Eastern
Asia and the Middle East.
Shamans and mystics? Give me a break.
It contains formulas for
potions and incantations
said to raise demons,
curse our enemies and contact the dead.
This isn't you.
The Barbara I know would've already sold
all of this junk to the highest bidder.
Junk?
This is my destiny.
And being with me and
Selina at the club?
That isn't?
You begged me
to partner with you.
Can't you see who that is up there?
That is me and Ra's, 400 years ago.
Oh, please, I mean, she
doesn't even look like you.
It looks exactly like me.
It is me.
I have finally found my true purpose.
I'm not gonna let your
jealousy distract me.
Ladies, escort Miss
Galavan to the street.
I'll show myself out.
Actually, I think it's time
my loyal servants
taught you some manners.
Why don't you do it?
Because I am the one true heir
of an immortal god's ancient dynasty.
And I don't dirty my fingers
with the likes of you anymore.
No parent will admit it,
but everyone's got their favorites.
Right, brother?
The one who cleans their
room, does their homework,
doesn't try to kill everybody.
Little Mr. Perfect here.
Yeah.
He was that guy.
He got adopted by rich folks.
Went to the top schools,
then, a top college.
Meanwhile, I got dragged
through the circus by my
depressed alcoholic mother.
Forced to clean up
elephant dung every day.
Who cares?!
Do you know how big
those things are, folks?
But I know something
that Mommy and Daddy,
they never knew.
You're as crazy as I am.
It's in your DNA.
See, we got the same blood
running through us.
We are practically identical.
You are a killer.
It's your nature.
Stop trying to fight it.
Take your best shot. Hmm...
Hey! What the hell happened?
The snipers are dead.
Get up on the roof,
take as many as you can.
All right. Just know, a bunch of
chemicals are heading this way.
Scarecrow had the Wayne
chemists mix it up.
That's why he's been stalling.
He wants a big crowd. He's gonna release
the laughing gas right here.
We need to evacuate the area!
Get these people out of here!
Do whatever you have
to! Get them out of here!
It's time to kill this
maniac once and for all.
That was so good!
I love you!
Hey, look up in the sky!
Holy crap.
E-Excuse me, sir, could you help me?
No can do, sport.
Got to get this rig into
position for the boss.
And where is that?
Paisley Square.
Almost there.
Then, I can drop the load.
With this lever.
Now, you turn this
thing around right now!
Can you not see...
Like I said, pal,
no can do.
Keep coming!
Get into position.
Holy moly.
Jim, are you seeing this?
Yeah. Get everyone out of here.
I'm going after Jerome.
I can take it down with a shot.
And risk spilling the chemicals?
Oh, yeah, right.
Oswald?
Jim, Jim, help me.
They knocked me out and-and-and
now I am in some blimp
with-with that horrible
gas and-and the pilot,
he's been hypnotized and I-I don't...
You're on the blimp?
Yes.
Yes. You have to help me.
No, no, no.
You're gonna help us.
You're near the river.
I need you to steer it over there.
Steer a blimp?!
Are you out of your mind, Jim?!
I don't even drive my own car.
If you don't, thousands
will die, maybe worse.
What's worse than that?
How can you run an empire
in a city full of lunatics?
Hands up.
Beautiful, isn't she?
Just give me a second.
Got to call the pilot.
Tell him he's in position.
Yes, Jerome.
Not cool.
Jerome? Jerome?
I'm in position.
It doesn't matter.
Too late, anyway.
Bombs away!
Funny.
No!
Okay, okay. Uh... um, up, up, up.
Up, up, up. Oh! Oh...
Oh, okay.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
River, river. Where is the river?
Quite the dilemma, Jim.
You gonna let me fall and die?
Or are you gonna pull
me up and arrest me?
What's it gonna be?
Lawman or murderer?
Ah.
Good ol' Gordon.
Always playing by the rules.
That's why I'll outlive you.
That's why I'm loved
'cause I don't give a
damn about the rules.
It's a long way down.
You sure you'll outlive me?
Oh, I'm sure
'cause I'm more than a man.
I'm an idea, a philosophy.
And I will live on in the shadows
within Gotham's discontent.
You'll be seeing me soon.
Au revoir.
Never thought I'd see this.
Sure is dead.
Yeah, but is he?
Yeah.
Get back!
GCPD. Everybody get back.
Mr. Valeska.
I meant what I said about
your work being of importance
to this city.
Let Wayne Enterprises fund
your work with a grant.
Thank you.
Captain.
Oswald.
Um, hello. Still here.
Will someone please get me
the hell off of this thing?
Uh, we're on it.
How do we get a blimp down
safely from over a river?
You asking me? I say we let him
stew up there for a few more hours.
We'll get ahold of the standby pilot.
Have him advise.
Sit tight, all right?
Oh, and Oswald Cobblepot,
Gotham thanks you.
Wait, wait, Jim.
Jim. Jim?
Jim. Jim!
Jim...!
Never touch me again.
Miss Kean has a new path to take now.
It no longer involves you.
- Is that so?
- We will accept you leaving this city
and never coming back.
The only thing I'll accept
is you kissing my ass.
We have been trained
by the League of Shadows
in 90 different forms of combat
- since we were five years old.
- Oh, yeah?
Which one of you bitches
wants to go first?
Next time
we kill you.
Let me help you.
Who the hell are you guys?
The ones that have been watching you
and Barbara Kean, the
imposter, for quite some time.
We serve the one and only true master,
Ra's al Ghul.
But he's dead.
Death is only an illusion.
Aah.
Hello, brother.
Didn't think you could
get rid of me so easily,
did you?
See, my days were numbered,
but you...
oh, you will continue on for me,
be my ultimate revenge.
So... calm yourself.
Don't fight it.
Breathe it in.
This gas was a special
mixture I had made
just for you.
Something to finally set you free.
It's time to have some fun.
Burn it down, brother.
Burn it all down.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --