NARRATOR:
Previously on Gotham:
I need to siphon his strength.
So when the time is right,
taking over his organization...
...will be like slipping on a glove.
The point wasn't to steal that money,
Butch.
It was to hurt Falcone.
BRUCE: What's her name?
GORDON: Selina Kyle.
BRUCE: So she saw everything?
GORDON: Yes.
Her being here
will put Master Bruce in danger.
She's the best chance we have
of finding who killed my parents.
You are gonna keep working for Fish.
You are gonna tell me every little thing
that she says.
DENT: Lovecraft, I have a witness
who ties you to the crime.
You and all the others involved.
- So tell me, Dent, who did I kill?
- Thomas and Martha Wayne.
You lost, miss?
This is Wayne Manor?
Yeah, but not sure you should be here.
- I'll point you back to the road if you're lost.
- No, thanks.
I am where I need to be.
[GRUNTING]
Open him.
Ripped By mstoll
Keep it tight here.
Better?
Better.
If you wanna test yourself, you should
come with me to the Midtown Bridge.
- You've climbed it?
- Yeah, to the top.
Kids go up there to make out all the time.
I could take you if you want.
Okay. I'd like that.
Let me ask you a question.
What's up with all the weird homework
about your mom and dad?
- I'm trying to understand why it happened.
- There's no why.
Bad stuff happens.
You-- You gotta get over it.
Maybe you're right.
Of course I'm right.
You wanna kiss me?
No, thank you.
No?
I would like to, but I can't help feeling
you have an ulterior motive.
I don't imagine you consider me
a suitable romantic partner.
So why would you wanna kiss me?
I don't know.
You think too much, kid.
I'm just trying to be nice.
No offense,
you don't strike me as a nice person.
What do you mean? I'm nice.
I don't mean you're not a good person,
but you're not nice.
You don't care much for other people.
Screw you, orphan.
Climb the damn bridge on your own.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
Yes, hello, miss. How can I help--?
- Oh, dear.
- My car-- It went off the road.
- Please.
- Please, come in.
Come in at once.
- If you could call an ambulance--
ALFRED: Where exactly are you hurt?
Alfred.
Is everything all right?
No, Master Bruce.
This lady's been involved in a car accident.
Run. Run!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GLASS SHATTERS]
SELINA: This better be a way out.
- Through the closet.
- We need to help Alfred--
- There's no time.
[SNAPS]
- Bruce, come on.
- Alfred might be hurt. I can't leave him.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
He told you to run.
Fine.
Stay, but I'm out.
Bruce!
Local P.D. is searching the woods.
So far, no sign of Bruce or Selina.
What can you tell me about this woman?
She was in her early 30s.
Pretty tasty fighter, actually.
Mate, it's just a scratch.
Shove off, will you? I got stuff to do.
Look, we got 50 police in the woods,
even more on the roads.
We need to focus on this woman
and her people.
- What can you tell me?
- They were trying to kill us.
- Your little girl brought them here.
- We don't know that yet.
BULLOCK:
Jim.
You must be Alfred Pennyworth.
- Nice job out there.
- Yeah, well, not nice enough, eh?
This was taken off the dead guy.
Nothing else. No keys, no ID, nada.
Now, I know this girl.
She was grabbed by the child snatchers.
And now she's getting attacked
by assassins at Wayne freaking Manor?
What the hell is going on, compadre?
- What, you hadn't told him?
- Told me what?
Selina Kyle was in the alley
the night the Waynes were murdered.
- Saw the killer's face.
- For Pete's sake, don't do this to me.
Harvey Dent in the DA's office
is investigating Dick Lovecraft.
He thinks Lovecraft is connected
to the Wayne killings.
So he leaked that we had a witness.
He thought he could spook Lovecraft.
Get him to reveal himself.
Why, that's a hell of a plan.
How did it work out? Bravo.
Thought she was safe.
No one knew she was here.
Well, you were wrong,
weren't you, you plank?
How did they know?
- Why didn't you tell me?
- You would've tried to stop me.
Of course I would've, you putz.
What the hell are you thinking?
The Wayne case is closed. It is closed!
- You know it's not--!
- Don't tell me what I know!
Would you shut up? The pair of you!
You can argue later.
Right now we need to find Master Bruce.
All right.
If they don't come back soon, they would've
gone to Gotham. Selina feels safe there.
Good luck trying to find her in the city.
Street kid like that?
- But you will help us find her, right?
- Yeah.
Of course I will,
because I have to be crazy.
Thank you. All right,
I'll focus on Lovecraft. I'll find him.
If he's behind this,
I'll get him to call off the contract.
- How you gonna do that?
GORDON: I'll think of something.
Run the streets, huh?
Focus on your contacts.
- Go to work.
- I'll come with you.
All right.
You're pretty handy for a valet.
[GUN COCKS]
Butler, mate.
I'm a butler.
- We need to call Alfred.
- You see any phones?
No.
Perhaps we should go back to my house.
- If the police are there, we'll know it's safe.
- Yeah, right.
The police will make it safe?
We have to contact the police
at some point.
Someone tried to kill you.
Me?
Nobody knew I was there.
It's your house.
Someone wants to kill you. Duh.
Why would anyone wanna kill me?
Must be all that lame detective work
you're doing.
Paid off good, huh?
Cheer up.
We're cool.
We lost them.
- I'm worried about Alfred.
- Relax.
Once I got you safely hidden in the city,
I'll find you a phone.
Thank you.
- I appreciate your help.
- Hey.
Just trying to be nice.
[DOOR CLOSES]
How did Maroni know
where my money was?
Well, that's a very good question.
Not to criticize,
but you could've just called me.
I'm going to ask you once more.
How did Maroni know
where I kept my money? No one knew.
The robbery at the armory--
That wasn't Maroni.
I thought we were friends.
We had an understanding.
You tell me every move Maroni makes.
What happened?
When did you turn on me?
Never, Don Falcone.
I swear. Never.
Maroni had nothing to do
with the armory job.
I would know. I would've told you.
Who was it if not Maroni?
And how did they know about my money?
[DOOR OPENS]
Thank you, Liza. Won't be long.
I'll come back.
[DOOR CLOSES]
I asked you a question.
Oh, you have a mole, obviously.
Which is not Maroni's forte, is it?
This is someone else.
Someone artful.
Someone close to you.
I know who you're going to name.
But your hatred of Fish makes me doubt
anything you say against her.
With respect...
...I don't understand
why you still tolerate her existence.
She has proved her disloyalty
a hundred times.
She wants your head.
Like half the people who work for me.
Fish makes me a lot of money.
I can handle Fish Mooney
or whatever son of a bitch did this to me.
Tell me how to find the mole.
You leave that to me, Don Falcone.
Dirty work. I'll find your mole for you.
Trust me...
...he'll belong to Fish.
Bring me proof.
- I don't get it.
- You, Gabe, not get it?
[CHUCKLES]
Quelle surprise.
What, pray, don't you get?
Why not just tell Falcone the truth?
It was that Liza girl that betrayed him.
Timing, Gabriel.
Timing is everything.
And Liza is a time bomb.
Just wait a while.
Then watch and learn.
DENT:
Stay there in case he shows.
Lovecraft's not home. Housekeeper
hasn't seen him since yesterday.
Allen says he didn't come into his office.
He and Montoya are watching.
How'd the killer find my witness?
Let's keep calm here. It's a win.
We made Lovecraft panic.
This is a panic move.
A win? There's two children out there
with professional assassins after them.
Bruce and Selina could end up dead.
We'll get Lovecraft to call them off.
How did they know?
I never told you her name,
let alone where she was hiding.
- So you couldn't have--
- I should say not.
And you never mentioned my name
to anyone, right?
No, we agreed.
I didn't mention any names out loud.
No names out loud?
What about whispering?
Don't hold out on me. I'll know.
For deep background, I leaked your name
to a couple select sources.
I had to for credibility.
You're the Wayne-murders cop.
Damn it. That's how they got to her.
I'm surprised it took them this long
to find her.
This is on you, Dent.
I'll stipulate mea culpa.
Kick my ass, be my guest.
But let's find Lovecraft first
and get him to call off the killers.
He's not at home. Not at his office.
He could've left Gotham.
Someone could be hiding him.
Lovecraft has got a couple of condos
that he keeps under his mistress's name.
One up in Stevensburgh and one uptown.
I'll take the one uptown.
If anything's happened to these kids...
We know you ran with a girl called Cat.
She's in serious danger.
Who isn't, right? Crazy world.
How much?
There's 100.
All right, listen.
I don't know where Cat lives, all right?
She's private about stuff like that.
But I heard that she got a new fence
because her old one got popped.
- He'd know where to find her.
- Who's the fence?
I don't know.
- But I know who would know.
- Yeah? Who's that?
Damn it. Save your cheese.
I'll beat the truth out of this kid
with a roll of quarters.
Yo, ask Fish Mooney.
She runs all the fences.
[GUNSHOT]
Forgive me for shocking you.
But let me give you some context here.
I love Bannion. We came up together.
But he was supposed to guard the armory,
and he didn't.
And maybe, just maybe,
he looked the other way.
I don't know.
So, what do I do?
- Let it lie?
- Boss, we understand.
FALCONE:
Whoever else was involved...
...will very soon wish
they could die quickly like Bannion.
In the meantime,
all of us must do what's right for the family.
Each of your tariffs will increase 25 percent
until we've built the reserves again.
No disrespect, that's high.
- A little bit.
- What do you think, Fish? Am I being fair?
We're family. We sink or swim together.
FALCONE: You could all learn from Fish.
She trusts me.
Trust me and I'll trust you.
It goes both ways.
Let's eat.
There's a phone. Come on.
I don't-- I don't carry coins.
Do you have any coins?
Nope, not a dime.
Why does Alfred matter so much?
He's just your butler.
He's my family.
Good luck, kid. See you around maybe.
What? Wait.
Look, those bad guys were there for me.
Not you.
You have nothing to worry about.
- Go home.
- But you said--
I was just trying to freak you out.
- I was playing with you.
- You were playing with me?
- That's kind of cruel, isn't it?
- Yeah.
No, look. You're right about me.
I'm not nice.
Not like you.
- You got a nice way about you.
- A nice way?
SELINA:
Yeah.
That's why I said you were the target.
So we could hang out a while longer.
I see.
It's very convoluted reasoning.
Whatever.
Anyhow, it's been cool.
I'm gonna disappear.
- You can't.
- I wasn't asking.
You can't disappear.
You have to come home with me.
When Detective Gordon finds the man
who killed my parents, you have to testify.
You really think
that was ever going to happen?
Grow up, B.
[GASPS]
No, don't. You won't make it.
Help.
[BRUCE PANTING]
- You're crazy.
- Don't run off again. I'm out of breath.
Okay, kiddo.
You earned it.
You wanna hang with me? That's cool.
But my world, my rules. You do what I say.
Yes, ma'am.
Why can't I call Alfred
or Detective Gordon to say I'm okay?
Because we're disappearing.
You gotta be like smoke.
Smoke doesn't make phone calls.
BRUCE: What is this place?
SELINA: The Flea.
It's like the mall for street kids.
Without the crappy music.
We'll be safe here until dark.
Falcone's making me nervous.
If he suspects it was us who blew up
his money, why hasn't he made a move?
Because he can't be sure.
There are 10 other people
who could've done this.
- So, what now?
- You're going to stick to the plan.
You're gonna reach out
to Saviano and Turski.
They are both very angry
their taxes have been raised.
And they're worried
about ending up like Bannion.
They're ready. The old man
is herding his sheep toward me.
- You got it, boss.
- All right.
MAN:
You know what, let's just take five, okay?
WOMAN 1: We are.
WOMAN 2: Thank you.
WOMAN 3: Hello, gentlemen.
WOMAN 4: Hi there.
Busy day, Harvey.
Come back next year.
Hand to God, Butch, I'll be quicker
than a sailor on shore leave.
Thief we're tracking down. Look familiar?
Goes by Cat.
- Nope.
BULLOCK: Maybe Fish knows her.
Fish knows everyone. Fish is busy.
- Works with one of your fences, a new guy.
- What's a fence?
Come on. Butch, be nice.
This is important.
- Where's Fish?
- I told you, she's busy.
I once knew a fella called Butch.
Yeah, he was a Whitechapel lad.
We called him Butch, you see,
because he wasn't.
It was a windup. It was like a joke name.
- In fact, he was a horrible little toerag.
BUTCH: Wait.
I can't tell. Are you-- Are you
threatening me? ls he threatening me?
Heh. Yeah? You gotta--
[BUTCH GRUNTS]
Now, where is this Fish?
Right here.
So, what's the fuss?
They're just fooling around.
We're looking for this girl.
Street thief, goes by Cat.
Works with one of your fences.
Looks familiar.
What's the urgency?
- Professional killers are looking for her.
FISH: Professionals, hmm?
This wouldn't be the Lovecraft witness,
would it?
How'd you know?
Streets talk.
Using her to scare Lovecraft.
She saw the Waynes' killer, supposedly.
- Yeah.
- Mm.
And you're here because you want me
to help you find her, don't you?
Yes.
Harvey.
[CHUCKLES]
Why in the world
would I help you find her, of all people?
She has Bruce Wayne with her, miss.
Really?
Yes, miss.
I'm Alfred Pennyworth,
the boy's legal guardian.
- I'm pleased to meet you.
- Likewise.
- Miss Mooney, we need your help.
- Well, you see, I would love to help you.
But it would infringe
upon my personal interests.
And why would I do that?
You have a very eloquent gaze,
if I may say so, Miss Mooney.
And I can see that you're not a woman
that would let petty self-interest outweigh...
...honor...
...and compassion.
I'll make some calls.
But remember this kindness.
Much better.
Really?
- I'm not sure.
- You look bad-ass.
No lie.
IVY:
Hey, Cat.
Ivy, what are you doing here?
What've you been up to? I thought--?
Yeah, juvie caught me.
- I got adopted upstate.
- Didn't take?
Good people, but they wanted
me to cut my hair, dress nice...
I know you.
- You're Mario Pepper's daughter.
- Yes. Who are you?
I'm Bruce Wayne.
Yes, you are. Billionaire Bruce Wayne.
- Stay cool now, Ivy.
- I am cool.
Why are you telling me what to do?
I'm not, I'm just saying I don't want you
to get mad at him. He's a friend.
Why would I get mad at him?
It's not his fault, is it?
Did you kill my father?
Did you make my mother cut her wrists?
- No.
IVY: Somebody did.
Somebody did, but not him.
- How are you doing? You doing okay?
- I'm okay.
- And you?
- I'm doing great. How do I look?
You look good.
- Have you seen Clyde the fence around?
- Yeah.
He's working out of the factory
on the Narrows.
- He's cute, isn't he?
- Yes, he is.
Thanks, Ivy. Good to see you.
- Oh, we gotta go run and see Clyde.
- Oh. Okay, fine.
Bye, then.
Keep moving.
She's just a little girl.
- Why are you so scared of her?
- Because she's scary. Don't look back.
GORDON:
G.C.P.D.
Drop it.
Kick it over.
You're under arrest.
Conspiracy to commit murder.
Murder? Me, murder?
- What are you talking about?
- You put a hit out on Selina Kyle.
No, not me.
Same people that came after her
came after me too.
Attacked me on the street.
Why do you think I'm hiding in here?
- Why would they come after you?
- Why do they ever?
Because I know too much.
Cut the crap. Who are you so scared of?
You have no idea, do you?
You think I'm the big wheel.
When it comes to the crunch, kid,
I'm nobody. Just like you.
And the people who truly run this city,
they're watching you huff and puff...
...and run around crusading.
And they are laughing at you.
You're so deep in the maze
you can't see over the wall.
- Tell me something I don't know.
- My briefcase.
- Under the bed. Files.
- Go.
Right before the Waynes got killed...
...there was a run
on Wayne Enterprises' stock...
...like somebody knew
something bad would happen.
So I figured I deserved a cut.
So I started digging.
[DOOR CREAKS]
I have come for that man.
You need not get hurt.
[ALL GRUNTING]
Mm.
That was nice.
Let's do it again sometime.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
- Yeah?
- Fish got a lead on the kids.
Place in the Narrows called The Factory.
Word is Cat used a fence named Clyde.
He hangs there.
We're on our way now.
Alfred, let's go.
Fish, thank you.
You owe me.
BULLOCK:
Who don't I owe?
Mr. Lovecraft?
No, no, no.
Detective Gordon.
Badge number 231611.
Reporting a body at 1257 Antioch.
Cat.
My babe.
Hey, Clyde.
Well, what have you got for me?
- Hey.
- Shh.
Wow.
Sweet swag.
- Not your usual junk.
SELINA: I'm moving on up.
- Where'd you get this?
- You want a story or the swag?
- How much?
- A thousand bucks.
[LAUGHING]
- Please, give me a break.
- That's rock bottom. You know it is.
- Fifty bucks.
- Fifty?
This pen is real gold.
That's an antique jade netsuke.
It's worth $2000 on its own.
And who is this well-spoken little dude?
Never mind who he is.
Look, 500 is rock bottom.
- Why are you wasting my time?
- Relax.
I'm sure we can make a deal.
No, thanks. We'll go elsewhere.
Cool down, Cat.
Or we'll poke your little friend's eyes out.
That's it.
Relax.
I've got some friends coming over
who would just love to meet you.
[TIRES SCREECH]
[SELINA GRUNTS]
It's all there.
Don't look so anxious.
Yeah, well, um...
...you guys are kind of sporty.
- Where is she?
She's upstairs.
She better be.
[GRUNTS]
Find me something heavy.
[METAL CLANGING]
[SELINA CHUCKLES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[GRUNTS]
[METAL CLANGS]
Am I the only one in this damn town
who waits for backup?
[GUNFIRE]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Bruce!
Follow!
[SIREN WAILING]
[GUNFIRE]
- Where's Alfred?
- He's in there.
Go.
Down!
Where's your girlfriend?
- I have no idea.
- Don't make me hurt you.
You're not on the contract.
She's gone.
LARISSA:
Some advice, kid.
Don't ever mistake bravery
for good sense.
[GUN COCKS]
[DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
BRUCE:
Alfred.
Fancy seeing you here.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
How are you?
You really scared me, Master Bruce.
If you die...
...who employs butlers anymore?
Oh, thank God.
JAMES: Lovecraft was a beloved pillar
of this community.
A dedicated servant of Gotham.
So, what do I tell the media, huh? Huh?
Any ideas?
He was a crook.
We nearly had him, and he was killed
by whoever he would've implicated...
...if he had lived to testify. Say that.
Forgive me
if I can't get behind your approach.
It was your gun.
- I didn't kill him.
- On balance, I believe you. On balance.
- Suicide is cleaner--
- It wasn't suicide. It was murder.
It was suicide.
He went mad
under your relentless questioning...
...overpowered you,
and killed himself with your gun.
And don't tell me otherwise.
What do you say, counselor?
I'm at your disposal, Mayor James.
I'm sorry if we've caused you
any disquiet.
Disquiet.
You arrogant clowns.
You're hacking away
at the very foundations of this city.
Trying to take me down.
Should have you both stuffed in a sack
and thrown in the river.
But I can't do that.
Two scapegoats would look like panic.
But one of you is going down,
mark my words.
Sir, that's not right.
Hush.
It's not you, Dent.
Obviously, it's Mr. Gordon.
Sir, I protest.
But not too much.
You see, Counselor Dent
knows how to walk the line.
He knows where the edge is.
You, Mr. Gordon,
do not know where the edge is.
Mayor James...
...kiss my ass.
Dick Lovecraft's suicide
is a terrible, terrible tragedy.
Fighting the trumped-up charges
of an overzealous police officer...
...was too much for him.
You have my word, Dick.
This officer is being dealt with.
Arkham Asylum?
- A security guard for nutjobs?
- Criminal nutjobs, yeah.
- Are you taking the assignment?
- It's that or quit.
So quit.
That's what they want me to do.
Damn, Jim.
Whoever your next partner is, he or she
will be a lot easier than me.
- Ed?
- Detective Gordon.
You've been thrown out in disgrace,
is this true?
Yeah, it is.
- I'm gonna write a letter to the boss.
- You do that.
Which boss should I write to?
Forget it, Ed.
That's the breaks, huh?
You take care.
Maybe you should take him with you.
- You'd miss him if he was gone.
- No, I wouldn't.
Let me buy you a drink sometime.
Soon.
SELINA:
Your security still sucks.
No one's hunting for me.
I didn't expect to see you again.
Never said goodbye.
No, we didn't.
Didn't want to be rude.
- It's good to see you.
- Here.
Thank you, but you could keep this.
- You need it more than I do.
- No.
Let's keep things honest between us.
I'm keeping this one anyway.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[DOOR OPENS]
Having a little chat, Master Bruce?
Thinking out loud.
Right.
Right. Of course you are.
Shall I take that for you?
The old house seems very quiet
without her, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER PA]
Ripped By mstoll