THEO: Previously on Gotham...
My forefathers were betrayed,
their legacy erased.
And I am here to punish those
who wronged us.
- We have a deal?
- We do.
(GROANING)
(GROANS)
(KRINGLE SCREAMS)
I'll do whatever it takes.
I'll train every day.
Yeah, but you said that before,
didn't you?
- I'll even go back to school.
- (SELINA GRUNTS)
(SCREAMING)
I saved your life.
You wanted to do it, too.
You just didn't have the guts.
Selina, I miss you.
THEO: This is not what we rehearsed.
- (CHOKING)
- THEO: I'm so sorry, Jerome.
Enter the hero.
(ALL CLAMORING)
(GUNSHOT)
COBBLEPOT: Gentlemen,
ladies, others,
let us discuss the future
with a little civility, shall we?
(COCKS GUN)
(ALL MURMURING)
So, not one of you knows who orchestrated
and/or executed the Arkham breakout?
I find that hard to believe.
I mean, the cop's only lead
is an old blind man, for God's sake.
A blind man!
Then, who here is to be trusted?
Because someone knows.
Uh... We thought it was you.
Why would I do that?
We've never had it better.
I gave you all the freedom in the world
and business boomed for all of us.
A new generation.
Then that ginger maniac
had to spoil everything.
Even now he's dead,
public is still terrified,
business is in the can,
and what are we doing?
Fighting among ourselves.
Is this how any of us wants to live?
Squabbling, brawling, running, hiding?
This city belongs to us now.
But kids, that brings responsibilities.
We need to restore
confidence in our brand, if you will.
We need discipline and unity, yes?
There will be no more chaos,
no more gang wars,
no more blood in the streets
scaring decent folk.
From now on, if you want to kill someone,
blackmail, steal, or kidnap anyone,
I need to hear about it first.
Understand?
- We got it.
- Fine.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Bravo.
Quite the King Solomon.
You had them nicely in line.
Who are you?
My brother would very much like
to talk to you.
Alone.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You don't know me.
COBBLEPOT: Relax, Butch.
He has issues. Bipolar.
She don't know me. I'm just saying.
(SIGHS) Your brother?
Theodore Galavan.
There's a car waiting for you outside.
(OFFICERS ARGUING INDISTINCTLY)
I'm sick and tired of your
holier-than-thou crap, Gordon.
Yeah? Then do some police work.
The last arrest you made was your bookie.
- Which is why--
- Back off!
My name is Nathaniel Barnes.
Captain Nathaniel Barnes.
That's right, I'm your new boss.
Ten hut!
You, clean that up.
You know when this place was built?
Over 100 years ago.
Can you imagine how many perps have been
booked in here since that time?
All the murderers, rapists, thieves
that have been locked up?
They don't make them like this anymore.
Strong, sturdy.
And yet,
just days ago,
an escaped convict just strolls in here,
into our house.
Our house.
And murders your commissioner,
and nine of your fellow comrades.
I wasn't even here, and I'm ashamed.
Are you all ashamed?
I hope so.
Anyone that's here
that's not ashamed and angry
should resign.
Right now!
Huh.
Some of you are lying to yourselves.
I've got your files here.
I've read them all.
Step forward if you hear your name called.
Pollard. Guthrie. Coulson.
Dowler. Brooks. Perez. Hightower.
You aren't ashamed. You have no shame.
You're not police,
you're lowlife criminals.
Bribery, drug abuse,
extortion, racketeering.
Sons of bitches! You're all fired.
Drop off your badges
and your guns with the desk sergeant
on your way out.
Hey. You can't do this. We got rights.
Yes, you're right.
You do have rights. (GRUNTS)
You have the right to remain silent,
you have the right to an attorney.
Take him.
From now on,
any officer, detective, rookie or clerk
who breaks the law
will not just lose their job,
they will go to jail.
If you turned a blind eye to crime,
I will bust you.
If you fail to help a fellow officer
because of cowardice or apathy,
I will bust you.
What the hell are you still doing here?
Don't make me mad.
Anyone who didn't hear their name called,
get back to work.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
I'd like to see you in my office, please.
Well? What do you think about
what I said out there?
I agree with every word, sir.
Every word, huh?
You a sycophant, Gordon?
No, sir.
"No, sir."
I've read all your files.
Army, Academy, G.C.P.D.
You're a troublemaker.
A fighter.
Is that an accurate assessment?
Yes, sir.
Good. You're my second-in-command.
Starting now, Jim,
we're gonna fix this department
and bring respect for law and order
back to this city.
Yes, sir.
We're, uh, kind of shorthanded.
What, do you think I cut too deep?
You could have thrown out 20 more guys
and not hit bottom.
Fixing this department is gonna be tough.
Maybe tougher than you think, sir.
Welcome to my unit, you sad-ass Army hump.
Tough is what we eat for breakfast.
(CHUCKLES) Jarhead, huh?
Who would have guessed.
Sir.
I hope you just told him
he made a huge mistake.
I don't think he did.
Come on, Jim.
We've seen his type come and go.
Idealists, always looking
to walk the straight line.
Gotham doesn't have straight lines.
It's got twists and turns and dead ends.
Yeah. But it doesn't have to be that way.
With Mayor James still missing
and the deputy mayor recently murdered,
the need for leadership at City Hall is of
paramount concern to Gotham's citizens.
Today, two more hopeful candidates
have thrown their hats into the ring.
Janice Caulfield is a city councilor
who began her political career
as an environmental activist.
Randall Hobbs, the longest-serving
teamster boss in Gotham's history,
is another candidate with a strong base.
In the latest polls, though,
a surprise surge for a man
who has not even declared his candidacy,
Theo Galavan.
The dashing billionaire businessman has
not ruled out a bid for the mayor's job.
But he is considering his options,
according to a spokesman.
THEO: Mr. Cobblepot, finally, we meet.
Call me Penguin.
I thought I heard you hated that name.
It grew on me.
Penguin it is. Please, sit.
- How's your head?
- Oh, healing, thank you. (CHUCKLES)
Gave me quite a scare.
You were lucky to get out of there
with your life.
Wasn't I just?
(CHUCKLES)
Was it luck?
You are a clever man.
Perfect timing, dear.
Do you two know each other?
We've met.
Oh, my.
The Arkham breakout,
the G.C.P.D. massacre,
Jerome and the Maniax.
All you. (CHUCKLES)
- Of course.
- Guilty. (CHUCKLES)
It was foolish of me to think
I could trick the King of Gotham.
BARBARA: Here.
You need this more than me.
I'll make another.
My sister tells me you're doing a
stellar job of organizing your new empire.
- I try.
- (TABITHA SCOFFS)
You're not the King of Gotham,
you're the King of Garbage.
A year ago, I held Fish Mooney's umbrella.
Now she's dead by my hand.
Along with Maroni.
Falcone is in hiding
and all of their businesses are mine.
They all underestimated me.
I suggest you not make the same mistake.
THEO: My sister is too blunt.
But she is honest.
The foundations of this great city
were laid 200 years ago
by some very dedicated people.
Now, it's an old, crumbling pigsty,
full of human waste.
It's time to move into the future.
A cleaner, brighter
future.
COBBLEPOT: Uh...
Those are all residential areas.
So, thousands of homes would
have to be destroyed, wouldn't they?
TABITHA: Yeah, so?
THEO: Here's the rub.
In order to rebuild,
I need first to destroy.
But I can't do that.
I mean, watch the news, I'm a hero.
But you have a certain flair
for such a task.
You, Penguin.
You will be my destroyer.
(CHUCKLES)
Truly, I'm flattered.
Thank you so much for thinking of me.
But, my dear sir, you have me all wrong.
I have no flair for destruction.
I'm a builder, a problem solver.
Besides, such a huge project would need
the support of hundreds of city officials.
Yes. Only the highest authority
could see it through correctly.
Say, a mayor with a landslide mandate.
But you're not a candidate.
Oh, I will be.
(INHALES DEEPLY) By popular demand.
Alas, some of my fellow candidates
actually stand a chance of winning,
so, they'll have to go.
(CHUCKLES) "Go"?
And I'm gonna need you
to take a crack at me, also.
And miss, of course.
Don't want anyone to think
that I had anything
to do with my fellow candidates' demise.
That's smart thinking.
However, with all due respect,
Mr. Galavan,
I'm not your man.
You need an assassin.
This is Gotham,
you can find them in the phone book.
Under "A."
(SMACKS LIPS) One moment, Mr. Penguin.
I'm sorry. I took you for a man of vision.
Taba, do you wanna get the remote, dear?
Yay.
THEO: Before you leave,
my sister would love to show you
her favorite reality show.
She's addicted! (CHUCKLES)
She's being kind of dull right now,
but sometimes,
she cries and bangs on the door.
- Free me.
- COBBLEPOT: Mother!
GERTRUDE: I swear.
I swear, I don't know about--
You'll pay for this!
(CHUCKLES) That's the spirit.
They die, your mother lives.
Simple.
(GERTRUDE PLEADING INDISTINCTLY)
GERTRUDE: Please!
I swear. I don't know nothing.
(THEO LAUGHS)
- (PHONE RINGING)
- (GROANS)
- Thompkins.
- BARNES: Good morning, Dr. Thompkins.
Captain Barnes, G.C.P.D.
- Captain Barnes, hi.
- I hear great things about you, Doc.
Get ready to get real busy.
We're gonna be sending you
a whole lot of dead bad guys.
(STUTTERS) Oh, uh, okay, okay.
May I speak to Jim?
He wants to talk to you.
(CLEARS THROAT) This is Gordon.
Meet me at the Police Academy at 0700.
The Academy, yes, sir.
If you don't mind me asking, sir--
Everybody knows you're banging the ME.
I'll see you in an hour.
BARNES: Oldest in your class.
Not the strongest, or the fastest,
or even the most
academically-gifted, either.
And yet,
you finished at the top of your class.
Now how did you do that?
I'll tell you how.
You were a soldier.
You saw combat
while your classmates
were still playing with themselves
in their parents' basements.
You got blood on your face.
You could say that.
You're a warrior, Jim. So am I.
But you can't carry on
the way you've been.
Going after everyone on your own.
You need help that you can rely on.
With all due respect, sir--
What if there were a team of young cops
who haven't been bought yet?
Not jaded, not corrupted,
still filled with hope and faith
in the system.
Cadets?
This is the greatest academy
in the country.
Graduation is next week.
We could grab a group of their finest
before some precinct kills their spirit.
Wouldn't hurt to look into it, right?
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
GUS: I don't want anybody getting shot
under my supervision, okay?
- BARNES: Gus!
- Captain Barnes.
This is Gordon.
Sure, I remember this guy.
He argued a lot.
- I like to think I was raising questions.
- (CHUCKLES)
- What do you got for us?
- This way.
(BOTH GRUNT)
Keep your eye on the little one.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
The one getting her ass handed to her?
Wait.
- (WHISTLE BLOWS)
- (CHUCKLES)
Patience.
Not your strong virtue,
if I remember right, Gordon. (CHUCKLES)
State wrestling champ,
Academy running back.
Why this place
and not a sports scholarship?
People from my neighborhood
don't get scholarships.
They join gangs, sell drugs.
I needed to change the direction
my life was going.
Mr. Martinez,
it says here you're the best shot
this school's ever seen.
Where'd you learn to shoot?
Gotham Gun Range.
One of my mother's three jobs
was cleaning it.
When she died, the owner let me go there
after hours and practice,
until I worked out my anger.
I still go there.
You're way too smart to be here, Garrett.
Don't tell me, your father's a cop?
Negative.
My father's family business
was destroyed by armed thugs
who demanded he pay them protection money.
When he refused,
they beat him half to death.
I'm here to make sure
that doesn't ever happen again.
Garrett!
Pinkney!
Josie!
Martinez!
Do you swear to honor that badge
with your life?
ALL: Yes, sir!
Congratulations.
You are now Unit Alpha
of the G.C.P.D. Strike Force,
under the command
of Detective James Gordon.
You will answer only to him,
and him, only to me.
Dismissed.
"Strike Force"?
Got a nice ring to it, doesn't it?
They're good kids.
But facing what's out there
at their age...
It's a big risk, sir.
True.
But what have we got to lose?
Yes, sir.
CITY OFFICIAL:
For your acts of courage
in the face of overwhelming uncertainty,
the city of Gotham would like to
give you this token of appreciation.
The Medal of Valor and Bravery.
(CROWD APPLAUDING)
- (CLEARS THROAT)
- (CAMERAS CLICKING)
- Mr. Galavan...
- Uh...
Please, "Theo." (CHUCKLES)
Theo, for Pete's sake,
why aren't you running for mayor?
(TIRES SCREECHING)
- Get down!
- (CROWD SCREAMING)
SECURITY OFFICER:
Everybody, stay where you are!
- THEO: Everyone okay?
- (POLICE SIREN WAILING)
Everyone?
(EXHALES)
You know what?
Gothamites don't buckle under pressure,
and neither will I.
We will not be intimidated by the scum
that seek to reduce this
great city of Gotham to ruins.
If the bad guys want to stop me running,
well, then, I guess I got no choice.
I will run for Mayor!
Yes!
(CROWD CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
FEMALE VOLUNTEER:
Hello? Caulfield for Mayor.
Yes. Will do.
Excuse me! You can't go in there!
COBBLEPOT: Miss Caulfield,
what a pleasure.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I can see what you are.
How did you get in?
I know it's late,
but I'm afraid there's no time for delay.
Someone tried to kill
Theo Galavan this morning.
Are you here to kill me?
Actually, yes.
Please, no.
I'm a mother.
- (GASPS) Wait!
- I have a mother, too.
(CAULFIELD SCREAMING)
BUTCH: Steady now, folks.
- CAULFIELD: No!
- Just think of blue skies and cornfields.
That's what I do.
Why are you doing this?
Darling, I got no freaking idea.
We've been doing crazy stuff all day long.
Well, we're away, then.
Sorry to ruin your evening.
Now, remember...
Yeah, I got your names and addresses.
So, think about your families
and keep mum, eh?
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
MALE STUDENT:
That's Bruce Wayne, right?
Are you waiting for someone?
No.
That's your job.
(GRUNTS)
That's for Reggie.
I know you killed him.
Now, I don't know what you want
with Master Bruce,
but I'm certain
that his life's gonna be
a damn sight better without you in it.
(SCOFFING)
So, you do yourself a favor, treacle,
and jog on.
(SNIFFLES)
All good.
Oh, Master Bruce.
You know, I could always
pull out front, if you want.
No, I...
Alfred, I don't want
the other kids to see--
To see that you've got a butler.
Yeah, I completely understand that.
I made dinner reservations,
as requested, for tomorrow night.
Mr. Galavan suggested the Regal Hotel.
Very posh.
You're gonna be forking out
serious dosh for that, I'll tell you.
He saved my life.
Dinner's the least I can do to repay him.
Uh, Master Bruce.
Where are you going?
Now, I clocked Wayne Manor
at exactly six and a half miles.
It should take 90 minutes to two hours,
depending on how many times
you stop, of course.
I know you said you wanted to train.
To prepare.
Well, this is it.
Wait, you...
(STUTTERS) You expect me to walk?
No, Master Bruce. I expect you to run.
- (CAR DOOR CLOSES)
- (CAR ENGINE STARTS)
Miss Kringle,
ever since I first laid eyes on you,
I've felt this deep connection.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Perhaps you've felt it, too.
(GROANS) Not cheesy.
Miss Kringle,
you've perhaps
felt my affections from afar.
"Afar"? Really? Oh, God.
Miss Kringle... (CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLES)
Be quiet.
I don't need your opinion.
And what you need is to stop mumbling
and fumbling and tell her what's up!
Well, she's been bullied
and taken for granted for too long.
- And I want her to understand--
- You saved her life, for God's sake!
She owes you.
Take what you deserve.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Miss. Kringle. Dinner, tonight.
Um...
Chez Moi. 8:00.
Okay. I'd like that.
You will.
(MOUTHING) What?
A wise cop once said,
"If you catch a kid smashing a window,
"even a small one, bust him.
"If you let it slide,
he'll smash another one.
"Then he'll tag a wall, steal a bike,
"rob a store, maybe hold someone up.
"Crime unpunished is a crime in itself."
This city is bleeding to death
from the amount of free passes
we hand out.
Time to put a tourniquet over that wound.
From now on, no one gets a free pass.
What is this strike force for?
To send a message that this epidemic
of lawlessness will no longer be treated,
but extinguished.
With extreme prejudice.
Gentlemen, lady, your new uniforms.
Sir, got a caller,
says Councilor Caulfield has been
attacked. Says she's dead.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
MALE OFFICER:
You got an extra pair of gloves?
No security cameras.
Galavan, and now her.
Looks like a damn pattern.
Only, she's dead.
Come on, people.
Who knows what?
Just give us a name, a description.
You will not have to testify.
They have our names and addresses.
FEMALE OFFICER: All right, ma'am,
so could you show me your...
Miss Caulfield was stabbed repeatedly.
Probably drowned in her own blood.
Forget it, Jim.
The man with the knife
was short, fancy clothes,
walked funny.
Mr. Galavan, thank you for meeting me.
It's an honor, the pleasure's all mine.
- I'll meet you in the lobby, Master Bruce.
- Oh, why not dine with us?
That's very kind of you, sir,
but I don't think it's appropriate.
And I know that Master Bruce
wants to speak to you on his own.
Sir?
Thanks, Alfred.
Enjoy.
(THEO SIGHS)
THEO: You like this place?
BRUCE: I've never been here before.
To be honest, I don't go out much.
Well, I hope I can change that.
There's always some tedious function
I could drag you to.
I just...
I wanted this opportunity to thank you
in person for saving my life.
Oh, you're very kind.
The truth is,
I don't know what came over me.
I don't think I was in complete control
of my faculties. (CHUCKLES)
I also wanted to speak with you
face-to-face.
It's regarding your parents' passing.
I find it astonishing that the police have
failed to produce any evidence
or any real suspect in all this time.
It is disappointing.
Even your father's own company,
Wayne Enterprises,
has failed to advance the investigation
in any way.
It's shocking.
(SILVER CHUCKLING)
Yes, Mr. Galavan, it's very disappointing.
That's Silver.
(STUTTERS) I'm sorry?
Silver St. Cloud.
Her father was my stepbrother.
He passed, sadly. She's my ward now.
Would you like to meet her?
Yes.
Hello, my dear.
(CHUCKLES) Uncle.
I'd like to introduce you to Bruce Wayne.
- Nice to meet you, Bruce. (CHUCKLES)
- Hello.
I was early, so I came out here.
It's such a warm day.
Do you know, I do believe that you two
will be sharing a school soon.
Anders Prep, yes?
Silver just got back to Gotham
after two years abroad.
Switzerland, Geneva. Ugh.
Yes. We have a house there.
So, what's it like?
- Switzerland?
- No, Prep, silly.
I think it's fine.
I've been homeschooling
for quite a while now.
So, I'm virtually a new boy, too.
Then we shall brave it together.
(CHUCKLES)
(MUSIC PLAYING)
I was kind of expecting a restaurant.
Miss Kringle, I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, I should have been more clear.
Uh... I like to cook. (CHUCKLES)
I'm a good cook. Is that okay?
It is, it is. Uh, and perhaps
you should call me Kristen.
Kristen.
Hobbs' campaign office
is the entire second floor.
You sure about this?
Don't worry, I've got it under control.
Okay, you gotta tell me
what the hell's going on.
I know I gotta do whatever you say,
but at least tell me
why the hell we're doing it.
- They have my mother, Butch.
- Who?
Galavan and his sister. They have her.
They're making me do this.
Holy smokes.
We gotta find your mom.
If they find out we're looking,
they'll hurt her.
Don't worry. We'll find her.
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
He's here. (CLEARS THROAT) Let's go.
Got it. Thanks.
I still think we should move you
somewhere a little more secure.
HOBBS: Forget it.
Anyone has the guts to come after me,
they'll find out real soon
who they're messing with.
BODYGUARD: All right,
sweep around. Whoa, oh, oh.
Who the hell are you?
Oh. (CLEARS THROAT)
- I came here to volunteer.
- (SCOFFS)
Well, run back to whoever hired you.
Tell them I'm not going anywhere.
This city needs me.
Oh. (LAUGHS)
Cool pins.
Count, idiot.
There's five of us.
I know, hardly seems fair.
Move, move, move, move, move! Go!
(SCREAMS)
(GROANS)
(SIREN WAILING)
Keep going.
- There you go. Right there! Go!
- (GROANS)
JIM: G.C.P.D.! Put down your weapons!
Fan out! Flank him from both sides,
catch him in our cross fire.
Yeah, do that.
I'll cover you! Go!
Okay, so, they move well.
(GROANS)
(GROANS) Unexpected.
Move, move, move.
(JOSIE GASPING)
PINKNEY: Let's go.
The shooter got away, sir.
You just met Victor Zsasz.
Works for Penguin these days.
What the hell is Penguin playing at?
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
No, but I... I feel like, uh,
I owe you an apology.
I feel as though I have been
nothing but mean to you.
No, I don't think that's fair.
I feel like all I've ever done
(STUTTERS) is annoy you.
(CHUCKLES)
I've been consistently inappropriate.
No, no, no, no, no, it's me.
You have been nothing but sweet.
And I ignored your card, and your gifts.
Miss Kringle, I can honestly say
that our interactions are
always the highlight of my day.
Please, uh, "Kristen."
Oh, my God, I even accused you of
writing Dougherty's good-bye note.
(CHUCKLING) Right. Crazy.
I mean, oh, who knows
what that jerk was thinking?
Jerk.
How I ever let him lay a hand on me,
I'll never know.
I'm glad he's dead.
(MUSIC STOPS PLAYING)
Well, he's...
He just left town, he's not dead.
Right, yeah, I know.
Figure of speech. (CHUCKLES)
He's dead to you.
Out of your life. Not "dead" dead.
Um... (CLEARS THROAT)
I'm gonna use the restroom.
You blew it, dummy. Nice work.
Leave me alone!
Are you talking to me?
No.
Honestly, Kristen,
I wasn't talking to you.
Who else is there?
I talk to myself.
It's crazy, I know, just...
I have this, uh...
I have this voice inside my head,
a sort of stronger version of me,
that keeps this me in line,
because I'm such a klutz.
I can understand that.
I think that we all have
a voice like that.
You think?
What was your inner voice saying?
He was mad at me for spoiling the mood.
- Mmm-hmm.
- (CHUCKLES)
It was... It was a really nice mood.
But my inner voice is telling me that
I think maybe we can get back there.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
JIM: You killed Caulfield.
We have a witness.
And the attempt on Galavan?
Was that you, too?
- Not now.
- And Hobbs?
- You sent Zsasz there?
- It's complicated! Okay?
What does it profit you
to mess with the election?
You have your own
sordid empire to rule over.
Walk away, Jim. Let me be.
The G.C.P.D. has new leadership.
No more deals, no more favors.
If they find out
you're behind these attacks,
- we will come after you--
- Rousing speech! Really.
Goose bumps.
But you came here alone, Jim.
With no warrant, no cuffs,
no backup, and why?
Because you would hate
for your new captain to find out
about how you gunned down
Ogden Barker in cold blood.
Over a debt.
(CHUCKLES) A debt to me.
He was trying to kill me.
Where are your witnesses?
And just that day before,
I suppose you did not ask me
to run Commissioner Loeb out of town
so that you could get your old job back?
I'll face whatever's coming to me.
As will I.
Good-bye, Jim.
JOSIE: Obviously.
MARTINEZ: I don't think so.
- I'm serious.
- For a second--
Hey, you shouldn't be joking
about near misses.
Next bullet might get stuck
right in your eye.
Yes, sir.
No joking.
BARNES: All right. Gather around.
Today, I'm giving the Strike Force
its first real mission.
Build a case to put away
Gotham's enemy number one.
Time to take down the Penguin.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Bruce!
GIRL: Hey, Selina, come on, let's go!
ALFRED: I don't know what you want
with Master Bruce,
but I'm certain
that his life's gonna be a damn sight
better without you in it.
So, what do you think? Red? Or Blue?
- Red.
- Blue.
- Blue it is.
- I want some fun.
I'm sick of staying indoors.
Patience, Barbara. Your time will come.
The wheel is turning.
While the G.C.P.D. chase the Penguin,
I'll steal the mayor's office
right from under their noses.
Did you find her?
(DOOR CLOSES)
(GROANS FURIOUSLY)
(SCREAMING)
English - SDH