If thou neglect'st, or dost
unwillingly what I command,
I'll rack thee with old cramps.
Fill all thy bones with aches,
make thee roar that beasts
shall tremble at thy din.
Go, go.
No. Pray thee.
I must obey.
His art is of such power...
Such power...
"It will control my dam's God."
It would control my dam's God Setebos
and make a vassal of him.
So, slave, hence.
Hence.
Full fathom five my father lies
of his bones are coral made
those are pearls that were his eyes
nothing of him that doth fade
but doth suffer a sea change
into something rich and strange
Oh! Get back!
Get back.
- Don't kill me!
- Stay down.
This is the fourth inmate outburst
in as many weeks
as you've been stationed here.
I understand this is punishment duty
for you,
but I expect professional standards
nonetheless.
This is unacceptable, Gordon.
Unacceptable.
It's my fault, Mr. Lang.
The play was too upsetting.
We'll stick to comedies from now on,
I think.
Thank you, Nurse Duncan.
It's "Director" or "Dr. Lang,"
as you prefer.
Recreational activities are not
pertinent to this conversation.
Officer Gordon is responsible
for security on this wing,
a task which he seems unable
to manage.
What have you to say about this,
Gordon?
This man needs medical attention.
I'd see to him myself,
but there's rules.
I dispense meds, not treatment.
He needs a doctor.
Very well.
I'll send one in.
Any more incidents,
and I'll have you placed
on the remedial duty roster.
Think you can't fall any farther?
Think again.
How is he?
He's fine.
Will be.
And you?
I'm good. Few bruises.
What?
You're the famous Detective
Jim Gordon, aren't you?
That's my name.
I'm not sure about "Famous."
Notorious, then?
Nearer the mark.
Who are you?
Leslie Thompkins. Dr. Thompkins.
- You work here?
- I'm not an inmate.
I haven't seen you on infirmary duty
before.
I work in the female ward.
I come over here
when they're short-handed.
All the girls are talking about you.
Brave detective brought low
by fighting City Hall.
They say that, do they?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to make
light of your situation.
It's okay.
Personally, I think what you're doing
is admirable.
I'm guarding lunatics.
No. You're not quitting.
Not yet.
Who are you?
Oh, sorry. I didn't mean to blurt all
that out like I did.
It's none of my business.
Dr. Thompkins,
you sure this inmate's gonna be okay?
He's fine.
He's just sleeping off his meds.
I'm trying.
Get a room, you guys.
I should go.
It's nice to meet you, Jim.
Likewise.
Ivy?
How you doing?
I... I'm good. I'm good.
You look sick.
- Like you need a doctor.
- No doctors. Never, ever again.
I'm fine. I was resting.
I got a place we can go, Ivy.
Come on.
I'm shivery is all.
Okay.
Come on.
They're gone. It's safe.
- Sure?
- Sure as sure.
We'll only stay until
you feel better.
Come and lay down on the couch there.
What if the real people come home?
There's dust on everything
and something smells rotten.
Nobody's coming.
Whose place is this, anyways?
How come you ask so many questions,
Ivy?
I'm trying to help you.
Now lie down
and I'll get you a blanket.
Morning, gentlemen.
- Have you considered my proposition?
- Yeah. No.
- No?
- We already pay enough.
Don Maroni set the rates last year.
And now I'm raising the prices.
Inflation is a bitch.
- Maroni said...
- Maroni, Maroni...
You're beginning to irk me.
- You're talking to me, the Penguin.
- So you're Penguin.
So what? I called the cops on you.
It's The Penguin.
And that was a very naive call
to make.
Hello, we own the cops
on the waterfront.
Tell that to the cops, buddy.
Boys.
Why the frowns?
Jones?
Jones.
Hey, Frogman.
Hey.
These are electrode wounds.
This man was given a crude,
invasive kind of electroshock
therapy.
Metal needles were inserted
into the brain
and electricity was applied
to his frontal lobes.
- What for?
- Surgically,
it's used to modify
aberrant behavior,
but in this case, way too much
voltage was used
and his brain is completely fried.
Another under your watch, Gordon?
How did this happen?
You rushed into opening,
and now you're running this place
with skeleton staff
and zero surveillance
in an unsafe
and unsecure 200-year-old maze.
Excellent. Excuses.
That's that nature of municipal
operations.
You inherit problems
and you use the resources at hand
to do with you can.
Well, our resources don't stretch
nearly far enough
to cover a criminal assault
investigation.
We should call the GCPD.
No, this is an in-house medical
issue.
He still breathing?
Well, yes,
but he's effectively brain dead.
What does... He's still breathing.
Unaided.
For all official purposes, well,
he's still alive.
Keep him comfortable, Doctor.
Officer Gordon?
I want you to find out which one
of our charming inmates did this.
I want a report on my desk Friday.
Another day, another dollar.
Really? This is rather usual
and sinister, isn't it?
Yes.
So, who are we looking for?
What does it take to pull this off?
Some basic knowledge
of human anatomy.
Basic electrical skills.
A circuit board, some wiring.
Is that all?
And the door keys, of course.
"The door keys." Right.
No, man, I got my keys right here.
Look at me, Steven.
Look at me.
Tell me the truth.
Why you picking on me?
There's five other guards with keys
to this wing.
True, and you're the only one
who looks
and smells like a hunted animal.
Look, Steven.
Whoever fried Frogman had keys.
Now, we've searched all the inmates'
cells.
No keys.
But I know they're out there.
And I need to know where.
I'm backed up against the wall here.
And I'm starting to lose
my patience...
do you understand?
That fight... during the play.
Right after,
I noticed my keys were gone.
You lose equipment,
that's a big deal.
They dock me a week's pay,
so I tracked done a spare set!
Who took the keys?
I don't know.
Anyone could've taken them.
Walk away.
- Sorry...
- Walk away!
And then he raises our taxes
after his money blows up.
Killed Bannion like he was nobody.
I'll say it.
I wish something would happen
to old man Falcone
before he comes after one of us.
That's where this is going.
Slow down. Now, let's imagine
God forbid anything happened
to Falcone.
Just for kicks...
who would take over then?
Who would take over? I do.
You?
Now, that never occurred to me.
What never occurred?
I'm next in line. Seniority.
That's the way the system works.
That's how the system used to work
back in the day.
It's a new dawn, a new city.
I would believe we would need some
fresh thinking at the top.
And who is the fresh thinker
that you got in mind?
Let me guess.
- Who?
- Her.
She's talking about her.
Really?
You don't think
I could run the family?
Hey, no, why not?
Woman's lib and all that.
But fair play, Jimmy is next in line.
Well, there's no need to argue.
It's all hypotheticals anyhow.
We're just talking, right?
Inmate 5075 Jack Gruber.
Inmate Gruber?
Did you take Officer Wenger's keys?
You're looking into the sad demise
of the Frogman.
The Frogman disrupted your play
last night.
Yeah.
You didn't like him very much,
did you?
Well, I had no opinion of him.
He was called the Frogman
because he believed a giant bullfrog
lived inside his abdomen,
controlling his thoughts.
He was already dead.
I don't waste psychic energy
on the dead.
Rape, murder...
You're no stranger to violence,
Gruber.
Your psych evals say you're a grade-A
sociopath.
Why should I take your word
for anything?
You shouldn't believe everything
you read, Jim.
May I call you Jim?
- Did you take the keys?
- Please,
search my cell if you do not find me
trustworthy,
but, no, Jim,
I did not take anyone's keys.
Thank you.
Guard?
Did you take Officer Wenger's keys?
No.
Hey, hey.
Settle down.
Settle down. Settle down.
Did you take Off...
You have the keys?
Get the straps! Need a restraint!
- Keys?
- Yes.
Keys. Did you take the guard's keys?
No. Am I in trouble?
No, Aaron,
unless you're lying to me.
Lying?
Aaron never lies, Mr. Gordon.
He doesn't have the concept,
poor peaceful soul that he is.
He killed his family with an ax.
Isn't that what you did, Aaron?
Never harmed a fly before or since.
I said sorry.
Okay, Aaron.
You're free to go.
Thank you. Guard?
You saw how that went.
Saviano's the problem.
Now, on his own, Janacek,
I can turn him around.
And the junior capos will follow him.
But that Saviano,
we got to deal with him before
we make our move on Maroni.
Why not let me talk to Saviano
on my own?
Me and Jimmy go way back.
That's true. You do go way back.
What would you tell him?
I'd say you're the best candidate.
He knows that.
He just can't admit it to your face.
Too proud.
Okay, then.
- Talk to him.
- Will do.
Butch,
you're not turning on me, are you?
What kind of question is that?
Why would you even joke
about something like that?
I'm just asking.
A girl gets insecure once in a while.
Royston, what are you doing out
of your cell?
Hey, cut it out!
Full fathom five thy father lies.
Of his bones are coral made.
Hell.
Royston, is that your name?
Sea-nymphs hourly ring his knell.
Fascinating.
The poor man can walk and talk,
but all he remembers are lines
from the play.
Same electroshock technique
as Frogman
but with slightly less drastic
results.
It's like whoever's doing this
is improving their methods.
Or maybe their process is
so haphazard,
they don't know what kind of outcome
they're gonna get.
One man ends up a vegetable,
while the other one recites
Shakespeare on a loop.
I don't understand
what an inmate gains
from scrambling up another inmate.
You should stay on the female wing
for a while.
There's no reason
to put yourself in danger.
I'm perfectly capable
of protecting myself.
Besides, my patients need me.
There's gonna be some drama
around here.
The missing keys made me focus
on the inmates,
but I think it's a misdirection.
I think I should be focusing
on the staff.
I see.
There will be some drama.
But, wait, I'm staff.
What if it's me?
- It's not you.
- How can you tell?
- You're not the type.
- Cop skills, huh?
You can read people.
Some people.
A staff member? That's absurd.
- It was an inmate.
- I don't think so.
Your job is to oversee inmate
security.
You're not authorized to conduct
an investigation of the staff.
You're trying to force my hand.
You want me to call the police.
No.
I already called them.
Barbara, you need to wake up.
- Morning.
- I got you coffee.
Extra sweet.
You always remember.
Yeah.
Have you spoken to Jim recently?
Why would I?
Renee, you don't have to be jealous
of Jim.
I'm over him.
This was a mistake.
What was?
This. Us.
I should have never let it go on
for this long.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Oh, I see.
Look, Barbara...
No. No. I mean, you're...
No, you are absolutely right.
This, this was a mistake.
This has been a really long process
for me, and I've worked too hard
to get right with myself.
I wanted this to be good,
but I can't fall back now.
The drinking, the drugs.
We're toxic together, you and me.
Please, Renee, stop.
There's no need to say another word.
I am sorry that I interfered
with your process.
Barbara, you need help
I can't give you right now.
- Let me call Jim for you, please.
- No.
Where's my purse?
You don't need to go. Stay here.
Take time to get yourself together.
I'll go.
I am perfectly together, thank you.
I am just toxic, that's all.
- Now, where's my damn purse?
- Barbara, stop.
Calm down, please, all right?
I'll go. Please.
Fine.
Do what you want. Go.
- I'm sorry...
- Just go.
Hey, pal.
In a cow slip's bell, I lie,
there I crouch when owls do cry.
All right. I can dig that.
- Detective...
- Jim!
Partner!
Let me take a good look at you.
Lord have mercy, a screw.
- Excuse me.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, you weren't exaggerating.
Freaky as advertised.
Nobody of authority called on you,
sir.
This is not a police matter.
You must be Director Dr. Lang.
See, I beg to differ.
This is third degree assault,
at the very least.
A friend of yours, is it?
Egregious insubordination.
Your job here was already
hanging on a thread.
This is the end of your career
in law enforcement.
- Count on it.
- Take it easy, hotshot.
Officer Gordon did the right thing.
Why wouldn't he call the police?
Anyone would think you'd want
to keep this business quiet.
Gerry... it is Gerry, isn't it?
Now, did you do this terrible thing,
Gerry?
That doesn't even merit a reply.
No, I did not do this terrible thing.
But you have the skill, though,
as a doctor.
I mean, you could do it,
lickety-split.
Now, why would I do this?
Why would anyone?
Exactly, Officer Gordon.
Gerry, I think we're gonna have
to take you down to the precinct
you're raising a lot of questions
that need clearing up
in a more formal setting.
- Well, you can't do this...
- Shush.
As of this moment, this is an
official GCPD investigation.
You, sir, will cooperate
or face arrest.
Officer Gordon?
Would you mind going through the,
staff records
while I take Gerry, here, downtown
for a chat?
Will do, Detective.
Sir?
Jimmy.
Butch.
- Good to see you.
- Come on.
Like old times, huh?
All we need is a bottle of applejack.
What happened, man?
In my head, it's...
we're still kids, chasing girls
in Harlow Park.
We caught a couple of hot ones, huh?
Especially me.
Thanks for meeting with me.
What did you tell your boss-lady?
I suggested I reach out to you.
She agreed.
Talk some sense into me?
It's a new dawn.
Yeah, like that.
She's not wrong, you know?
City's changing.
You really want Falcone's job?
Since we were kids,
I love you like a brother.
I love you, too.
- Always. You know that.
- I do... I do.
That's why I trust you.
And that's why I say to you
with love...
Fish is doomed.
There's no way she gets the chair.
It ain't gonna happen.
She's a smart cookie,
but she's overreaching.
I mean, come on, Butch,
without you and your crew,
what's she got?
Very little.
Everybody knows it. You know it.
Maybe.
What's it gonna take to make you
make a move?
- What are you offering?
- Name it.
Drop Fish, come over to us.
The club, all the businesses attached
they're yours.
That's day one. A welcome bonus.
What else you want?
That's a good question.
Let me think it over.
Yeah.
Hey, brother.
Don't think too long, huh?
Detective Bullock.
Wait here.
Penguin. It's good to see you.
- What are you guys doing?
- Old friend.
Thank goodness you're here.
- There's been some silly mistake.
- Looks like it.
Unless you irritated someone
important...
you didn't do that, did you?
Me? Of course not.
You sure?
Examine your soul, Penguin.
Wait!
Don't go. Please, sir, I beg of you.
My patron, Don Maroni, is obviously
unaware of my predicament.
A simple phone call
would resolve things, I'm sure.
But, see, I like having you here.
'Cause I can sit at my desk
and look at you.
It's soothing.
Like a bonsai tree.
What's a bonsai tree?
So...
did you see our friend?
I saw him.
And?
I'm working him.
He's a stubborn cuss, that one.
Just give him a little time.
Time?
Okay. He can have time.
Yeah.
I'm optimistic.
Good.
All right, Doctor,
pretend I'm an ignoramus.
Shouldn't be too hard, hmm?
Explain to me this whole crazy
electric needle business.
When a real doctor like you does it,
what's it supposed to do?
Electroshock therapy
is a common procedure
for mood and behavior alteration.
- Like mind control?
- Of a sort.
Blue sky experimentation on humans
is considered unethical,
so we know very little of the hard
science.
- Okay.
- But skilled surgeons can elicit
very specific responses.
But those inmates weren't treated
by a skilled surgeon.
You sure about that?
There are no skilled surgeons
amongst the inmates.
- Or the staff.
- You're a skilled surgeon.
What... We've been over this.
I haven't opened a body since
med school.
I'm just messing with you.
I don't think you're the man
behind this.
No, you're not the type
to break rules.
Too scared of authority.
But you're hiding something.
What is it?
Well, everybody's hiding something.
Don't play tag.
You're right, Detective.
I am afraid of authority.
And the things I'm hiding?
I'll never tell you.
- Sounds heavy.
- Heavy?
Yes. And if you know what's good
for you, you won't dig any deeper.
All right.
I don't want to hit any power lines.
Don't have to tell me twice.
No digging. Unless, of course,
it has something to do
with the case at hand.
Nothing.
Great, thank you.
Oh, you poor thing. You look so pale.
Any joy?
Not so far.
The files seem to be incomplete.
I'm wondering if there's more
in the basement.
Blueprint says there's a records
office down there.
Oh, the basement's closed off.
Unsafe chemicals.
Nobody's been down there
for 10 years.
Do you know the way down there?
All right, suppose you had to pick
out one member of your staff
as the culprit. Who would it be?
It wasn't a staff member.
Whatever. Just the first face
that pops to your mind.
Nobody.
They're good people.
I know them well.
They've all been with me
for more than five years.
We all came to Arkham together.
Wait. Hold that.
You just saw someone. Who was it?
- No, she couldn't...
- She?
Who?
What's that?
Everybody's in their cell.
Dorothy.
Jim, hi. What's up?
Hi, Leslie.
We're going on an adventure
to the basement.
Well, that sounds fun.
- Can I come?
- No.
- But...
- Dr. Thompkins,
what did I tell you earlier?
You should go home.
Why? What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong.
Go home.
I don't understa...
You okay?
- I'm fine.
- Okay.
I need you to find the main entry
guard,
tell him to hit lockdown,
then get out of the building, quick.
Okay, hit lockdown. Get out. Will do.
- Yeah.
- Jim, listen,
Dorothy Duncan isn't staff.
She's an inmate.
I know. Get over here now.
Leslie!
Guard! Guard! Help!
Dr. Thompkins.
Jim, behind you.
Men!
Men! What the hell do you think
you're playing at?
Go back in your cells, right now!
You hear me?
That's an order!
Remember, I'm a vegan, no butter.
Yeah... yeah.
- Hi.
Is this...
Is Jim Gordon there?
Yes, he is.
But I'm sorry,
Jim is kind of busy right now.
Can I take a message?
No.
No, that's okay.
I...
Who is this?
I'm a friend of Jim's.
Who's that?
Go to hell!
M.E.'s got her in the morgue.
When Dorothy Duncan was a 16-year-old
nursing student,
she killed five kids
with poison candy
for homework, she said.
She's spent over half her life
at Arkham.
When the asylum closed,
there was chaos.
She must have just hunkered down
in the basement until it reopened.
Forensics is sweeping
the basement level
looking for her lair.
Poor soul.
What was she trying to do?
Who knows? Maybe she was just trying
to find a cure for her own madness.
She was crazy. Enough said.
- Yeah.
- It's good to see you, Jim.
And you got a win, huh?
Still fighting. Nice work.
Yeah, I don't think my boss is gonna
see it that way.
He's working for the king
of all cheese grinders.
It's a crying shame, Cap,
we need to get him back on the job.
You know, I'd bring you back here
in a second...
if I could.
I know.
It's all good, Captain.
You do look spiffy in the uniform.
Yeah, if spiffy means dorky.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
How about a drink for old times'
sake?
Sounds good.
Penguin.
Hi.
Sir.
Don Maroni.
Thank heavens you're here.
You look kind of frowsty.
Forgive me.
I've had nothing but a moist
towelette since yesterday morning.
A very sad picture.
You know why you're in there?
- I have no idea.
- A rhetorical question.
You're in there
because I put you in there.
But, Don Maroni, why?
What did I do?
Do you know what hubris is?
Do you know?
Sorry.
I thought that was another
rhetorical... question.
Yes, I do. Hubris. It's when...
It's when limping little chicken butt
second bananas
think they're hot stuff.
- Sir...
- When dumbass underlings
raise taxes without asking me first.
- Yes, sir.
- On fishermen.
You raised taxes on fishermen.
They're out there in the freaking
ocean risking their lives for us,
and you raise their taxes
without asking me?
That's hubris, my friend.
I'm sorry, Don Maroni.
Deeply... sorry.
I will never do it again.
All right, then.
Hey, you.
Let my friends out.
- Excuse me?
- What, am I talking Hungarian?
Open the cage, mook.
Come here.
Holy Mother, you stink!
Let this be a lesson to you, yes?
Yes, sir.
You're a smart monkey...
but you're a monkey.
And I'm the zookeeper.
Yeah, you're all right.
Captain, you should see this.
Look here.
Dorothy Duncan.
Electrode wounds, both sides.
Same gauge as the other victims.
About a month old.
They were hidden by her hair.
This is crazy, how could she have
done this to herself?
She couldn't. Not humanly possible.
Which means
she was just another victim.
- She couldn't.
- Oh, crap.
Hey, Aaron.
What's up?
Hey. Where'd you get those...
Well done, Aaron.
Exactly like I told you.
Oh, now you are my best work so far.
Hello, Dr. Lang.
Lang?
Lang!
They're gone.
- Get an ambulance. Go.
- Not... staff.
Don't speak. Just breathe. Breathe!
Gruber.
Dear Officer Gordon,
sorry, I had to run.
I very much wanted to enjoy
a proper chat with you
before I left, but...
that's show business.
I've been practicing my skills on
these sad creatures for a while now.
Electricity is an amazing thing.
It can work wonders.
Nurse Dorothy was an early success.
This last time, I think
I finally got one just right.
Bravo to me.
But time to go.
It was nice to meet you, Jim.
And I hope to see you around.
All the best, Jack Gruber.
Barbara?
- How you doing?
- Well. You?
Tip-top. Always.
So, what's the deal, brother,
are you in?
Yeah. I'm in.
That's my boy!
Name your terms.
You remember when we were 14,
we stole all that meat
from Satriani's?
Yeah, I do. It was, like, 50lbs
of pork and whatnot.
- Never seen my mom so happy.
- Yeah.
Thing is, when I was sharing it out,
there was, like, 15lbs of prime
angus beefsteaks in there.
And I kept it all for myself.
I didn't give you any.
Gave you all the cheap cuts.
I never knew that.
Yeah,
it's been bugging me ever since.
Hey, we're talking a long time ago.
I want to say I'm sorry.
I apologize for cheating you out
of your beefsteak.
- Forget about it.
- Nah... Nah.
Brothers don't do that.
Why did I do that?
Hey.
Forget about it. It's okay.
Apology accepted.
Thank you.