Previously onGotham...
Harvey is weak.
And how many more cops need to die
because of his incompetence?
As of this moment, I'm assuming
the captaincy of Gotham Central.
Nothing in Gotham is free.
You wanted a gangster
to help you get rid of Penguin.
This is what that help looks like.
The whole town has gone hog-wild
for the Pyg.
Turns out the Pyg's real name
is Lazlo Valentine,
and he just escaped.
I haven't been looking for a cure
for your brain, Ed.
Because I was afraid
that if I told you the truth,
you would go back to being
who you were before.
And I like who you've become.
I'm not the hero Gotham needs.
I took the dark path.
Yes, you did. And it's gonna
be a long, bumpy journey back.
What?
- Hello, Victor.
- Where's the boy?
Alive for now.
If Oswald wants to keep it that way,
he will meet me under
the Crown Point Bridge.
You wanted a war, you've got one!
We will wait for Mr. Cobblepot
to send instructions.
Hello.
Where is Penguin, little man?
This is Gordon.
I need forensics in West End Alley.
Black market doc.
Pyg was here,
looks like he got a new face.
So, Penguin's out building support
amongst the gangs.
Pretty soon every criminal in Gotham
is going to be hunting us.
He's out building support
because we made him look weak.
We kill him and all the gangs
will support me.
I'm still a Falcone.
Yeah, you mentioned that
about a billion times.
He doesn't know where Penguin is.
What?
I'll be right there.
Is that about Penguin?
No.
Harper.
We were an hour outside of Gotham
when I got waylaid by Victor Zsasz.
He took Sofia, gave me this.
I woke up in Virginia.
Damn it. I had a deal with Penguin.
There's more.
We're getting word Penguin
had some meeting
under the Crown Point Bridge
late last night.
Gunfire, a car blown up.
Sofia Falcone was there.
All right. We have to find Penguin.
- Harper.
- I'm good, Cap.
Put out a city-wide BOLO.
I'll find Sofia.
What about the Pyg?
I heard he escaped from Arkham.
Tracked him
to a black market surgeon.
He's already got a new face.
Lazlo Valentine is gone.
- But if we don't find him, what...
- Focus on the bigger problem.
We've got a war to stop, people.
So, are you going to tell us
why we're in your dad's house?
Why do you think?
Sofia.
You look tired.
Miss Kean.
It's good to see you again.
Likewise. So this is weird.
Why are you here, Father?
What did I tell you when you asked
to return to Gotham?
- I know...
- What did I tell you?
- That I wasn't ready.
- Exactly.
And you came back anyway.
Perhaps I should've acted then.
But I was indulgent, curious.
Who is this daughter I raised?
Father, Penguin is weak.
If you help me, we can end this.
I don't want Gotham.
I don't believe that.
You love this city.
I used to, yes,
but I'm dying, Sofia.
Someone else can have Gotham.
What I care about now is my family.
And I am your family and I want this.
I deserve this. Gotham belongs to me.
Your actions have disgraced
our family.
Tell me how sleeping with Jim Gordon,
the man who killed your brother,
helped reclaim Gotham.
I'm sorry. What?
I have done many things
I will have to answer for.
But I always knew the meaning
of honor.
You have proven that you do not.
Children...
they can be such disappointments.
I kill him, and this is over. Please!
You know why I came
when Penguin called?
It's because you were going to lose.
If you were anyone but my daughter,
you'd be dead right now.
Come on. Here we go.
Oh, good morning.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- In there.
Dear, oh, dear.
Good morning, officer.
My name is Alfred Pennyworth.
Neighbors called
in a noise complaint.
He's all yours.
Thank you.
Right.
Well.
Good morning, Master Bruce.
God!
I do believe the party's well
and truly over.
Morning, miss.
Good morning, miss.
G.C.P.D.
I'm looking for my daughter.
You can stop.
She's with me.
Carmine, I didn't expect to see you.
I imagine not I arrived this morning.
- You heard Sofia's in danger.
- Was in danger.
I made a deal with Cobblepot.
I take her out of Gotham today,
and she lives.
I made the same deal.
He didn't keep it.
He will with me.
I'm glad I never killed you.
- Thanks.
- Don't thank me.
Killing you would have been
a kindness.
You've no idea what you've brought
to your city.
I imagine when you find out the truth
it will destroy you.
That's a comfort.
Another day.
Another man sending me out of Gotham.
We're both just trying
to keep you alive.
Tell yourselves that.
But what I know is that neither
of you believed in me.
It could've been so different.
Good-bye, James Gordon.
I doubt we'll see each other again.
The sun never shines here.
Everything I did,
I did for your love.
But that doesn't matter, does it?
What matters is that after everything
you've done,
I still consider you my daughter.
That's enough.
Mother planted those roses.
She loved them.
I want to take one with me.
Get down!
Gotham is still reeling
from the violent death
of Carmine Falcone three days ago.
Falcone ruled the Gotham underworld
for nearly 30 years.
No arrests have been made,
and a strange quiet...
How was the night, Master Bruce?
There's a mess in the Rolls.
You'll need a bucket.
...girding itself
for further violence.
Which many had attributed
to the Pax Penguina.
Indeed the Don's claim
to the throne of Gotham...
He shouldn't have come back.
...in most recent years,
by a new breed of criminal.
Leaving some to ask,
"Does Gotham still..."
Yes, Victor?
You would've told me, right?
If you were gonna ice the old man.
Obviously!
Victor, I did not kill Don Falcone.
Well, everyone on the street thinks
you did.
So let them.
My hands are clean. You have my word.
With Don Falcone's passing,
it is unknown how or indeed,
when the void of power
at the center of the city's
underworld will be filled.
Sofia.
I came to the hospital.
I told them not to admit you.
I am truly sorry about your father.
You know it was Penguin.
And if I had evidence supporting that
I'd arrest him.
He is over there,
waiting to see my face and gloat.
He is a liar and a murderer
many times over.
But you need evidence.
I have to bury my father.
Excuse us.
Victor.
- Harvey.
- Jim.
Your leave is almost up.
Be good to have you back.
We'll see.
So why haven't you arrested
the little weasel?
Penguin still owns the judges.
If I arrest him,
and it's not rock solid, he'll walk.
So him whacking Falcone
and you sitting on your hands.
What good does that do?
It was Sofia who paid off the mayor
to make me captain.
I didn't ask her to.
Oh, well.
And pressing me to move on Penguin,
even before this.
I told you, didn't I?
That bill would come due.
I can't allow her to turn the G.C.P.D
into her own private army.
We've come too far.
This has to be by the book.
And forget Falcone.
Penguin's too smart to get nailed
for that anyway.
What do you mean?
Get him to do something
you can really bust him for.
And then yank his ass
off the street once and for all.
You're saying start a war.
I'm saying get him to start one.
You know he's gonna come for her.
I don't give a tinker's damn
about Sofia.
The way I see it, everything
that's happened down
to Don Falcone lying in that box,
comes from you deciding months ago
to go after Penguin.
This is all on you.
So finish what you started.
Goodbye, old friend.
I will not forget all
that you taught me.
I had great respect for your father.
Once he's in the ground, you...
Excuse me.
Not here!
What are you doing, Jim?
Finishing what I started.
There you, get back.
- Stop.
- All right. All right.
Testing. Testing. One, two, three.
James Gordon!
James Gordon?
What do you want, Oswald?
You know what I want. Where is she?
No.
You're seriously going
to go to war for her?
I'm upholding the law.
No one gets to decide who lives
or dies in Gotham.
Can you not see, Jim,
she has manipulated you,
lied to you...
The law is the law.
Now either get over it,
or face the consequences.
Let's try it this way.
Sofia Falcone is in this building.
Whoever brings her to me
will be richly rewarded.
I'm going to count to five.
Count as much as you want, twerp.
Yeah, we don't work for you.
This man is asking you to risk your
lives to protect a gangster!
I am offering you money, huh?
And bonus, no one gets killed!
- Hey, Captain, can we?
- Sure.
- All right. Come on.
- Get off of me!
Blood will run, Jim! Mark my words!
Blood will run!
And it will be on your head!
Get on that way!
Shut your beak.
- Enjoy the trip.
- Yeah.
From the first day
I put on the badge,
I was told things
could never change.
Gotham was corrupt.
G.C.P.D. was corrupt.
Criminals and low lives ran things.
You just showed me different.
Penguin will be coming.
It's time we showed Gotham
who we are.
Suit up!
Let's move, move, move!
Take them out.
Just let us go.
You obviously got your hands full.
Shut up!
Whatever.
They'll all be dead in a few minutes.
Listen, you stupid...
Drop your weapons and come outside
with your hands up...
Screw you, copper!
More left.
She means your left.
Then say that.
Your left! Your left! Your left!
Yay, teamwork!
Penguin thugs in Cell Two.
- You're winning.
- So far.
But every gang in Gotham owes
Penguin allegiance.
I can't arrest them all.
So arrest Penguin,
wasn't that the point?
As long as he's using proxies,
he's protected.
I have to keep pressing him.
When his back's against the wall,
he'll do something
he can't take back or explain.
And then I'll have him.
So you're baiting him into committing
a public atrocity.
What if he already has?
There's this boy from my orphanage.
Martin.
Oswald cared for him.
I hid him away for his safety
but Oswald forced me into telling
him where Martin was,
and then put him in a car
and blew it up.
Why didn't you tell me this before?
Because I'm his enemy.
Who's going to believe me?
Also, I didn't see him plant
the bomb.
- So you have nothing.
- I didn't say that.
Oswald never understood the way
people cared for my father.
And one of those people
just called me.
How is Jim Gordon beating us?
Well, every cop in Gotham
is behind him.
I'm guessing he has great
leadership skills.
Victor, when this is said and done,
you and I need to have a frank
discussion about chain of command.
But now go do something horrific!
Show the G.C.P.D. exactly...
Oswald Cobblepot!
You're under arrest.
Have you completely lost your mind?
Nobody has to die.
We only want Cobblepot.
Well, see, Jim, that's a problem
as they work for me.
But, just so I know,
what's the charge?
Murder.
Enough! Enough!
I did not kill Don Falcone!
And I dare you to prove otherwise!
It's not for Falcone.
I'm arresting you for the murder
of the boy you blew up
under the Crown Point Bridge.
What's so funny?
Nothing.
Well, everything, actually,
because, because you see...
He's not dead!
I only faked his death,
so that Sofia Falcone
couldn't use him against me.
She's the one who told you
I killed him, isn't she?
Then where is he?
He... I don't know.
Victor took him out of Gotham.
Tell him.
What's to tell?
You blew that kid sky high.
What?
You sent that pipsqueak
to Kingdom come.
No.
That's not true.
And I'll testify to that.
- What?
- Look.
I ain't taking the rap
for no kid murder.
- Hey, hey.
- Get him out of here!
You are a liar!
You are a lying traitor!
Victor Zsasz is a liar!
No! I will kill you! Traitor!
This...
doesn't give you a free pass,
you know?
Jim...
not now.
You did it, Cap. You won.
So I'm guessing Gordon doesn't know
the kid's actually alive.
Jim Gordon played his part.
He showed the underworld
that Penguin was weak.
That he did.
End of the day...
he's a Cobblepot.
You're a Falcone.
Smile, ladies.
It's a new day.
So, Sofia was as good as her word.
We got our club back.
Yippee. We get to serve drinks again.
It's just a base of operations.
But I am meeting with the designer
later to make it less...
Penguiny.
Have fun.
Music to soothe the savage beast?
Something like that.
Alfred!
Oh, the front page up.
Didn't expect you to brave the light
of day for a couple more hours,
Master B.
Tommy wanted to go
to the horse races.
What's all this?
It's a little project of mine.
I like to call it,
"Operation Save Bruce Wayne."
Switzerland.
Few months up in the Alps,
you'll be tickety-boo.
Are you going to kidnap me?
No, I'm going to appeal
to your better angels.
And if that doesn't work,
I shall beg.
Please, Master Bruce.
If for no other reason, do it for me.
These past weeks, you know how much
I've thought about Ra's Al Ghul?
About my parents?
Not at all, Alfred.
All you're offering me is pain.
Well, there is no life without pain.
There's no love, there's no joy.
I don't know about that,
I'm having a fair amount of joy.
A bloody miserable is what you are,
I mean, I can see it.
Alfred, I know you care about me.
But I'm asking you
to stop what you're doing.
I'm not who you thought I was.
I'm not who my parents
might've wanted me to be.
- And I'm okay with that!
- I'm not okay with it.
- And I don't I believe it.
- And that's your problem!
Now I'm gonna go meet Tommy.
I can't let you do that,
Master Bruce.
You're going to stop me?
If need to be, yes.
You really think you can?
Oh, I know I can.
I just don't want you to make me try.
Well...
Don't do this, Master Bruce.
No, Alfred, we're doing this.
Getting slow, Master Bruce.
You haven't been training,
have you, son?
- Got a bit of ring rust.
- Really?
Because you're the only one
breathing hard, old man.
Stop it, will you!
Stop it!
- Stop it.
- Fine.
All right.
Fine.
Oh, no. Master Bruce, I'm so sorry.
I didn't...
I don't know what came over me,
mate.
I am in control!
Me, Ed Nygma.
But why would you want that?
You don't understand.
We had so much fun when we were me.
Oh, no.
Tell me it's not that.
Not what?
I leave when spurned.
I give all. I take nothing.
I can raise you to a king
or make you to a beggar.
What am I?
Okay, I'm just gonna tell you
because you're not going to get it.
- "Love."
- I am in control!
You're in love with Lee Thompkins.
You pathetic loser.
Shut up!
Ed angry at mirror?
No, Grundy,
I'm not angry at the mirror.
Ed angry at...
- Ed?
- That is...
surprisingly perceptive.
I need some air.
This was the end of Solomon Grundy
Where is Grundy?
I kidnapped you.
For the record, you're not light.
What pretty lady want?
When we were fighting,
you called me, "Tabby," remember?
Grundy want to go back to friend Ed.
Ed.
Right, your friend.
Well, your best friend, Ed, tied you
and me to chairs,
electrocuted you,
and cut off my hand.
Look at the scar. Ring a bell?
Remember me, Butch.
I'm Tabby.
I'm your Tabby.
Grundy sorry.
Yeah, I'm sorry too.
Before, when you said my name,
I'd just hit you in the head.
Maybe that's the only way.
So you're gonna remember me, Butch.
Or I'm gonna beat your head in.
Pretty lady.
When I called,
I wasn't sure you'd come.
I was going to anyway.
We need to talk.
I agree.
I'm going to ask you not to do what
you're about to do.
Which is?
Unify the gangs.
Put the Falcones back in charge
of the underworld.
But wasn't that our deal?
I'd replace Penguin.
You'd be the law, I'd be the order?
No. And if you try and take over,
I will have to come after you.
James.
You're nothing if not predictable.
Now I think it's time you heard
my proposal.
I'm not interested.
I think you are.
Surprise.
I know.
You thought I'd have a different face
because I killed that doctor.
That was just to throw you
off the scent.
That's not why he's surprised, Lazlo.
Can I tell him?
You came to this beautiful woman
because you had a problem.
A Penguin problem.
Pax Penguina was gonna last.
But Sofia had an idea.
I'd heard of a contract killer
that was impersonating serial
killers. So...
What if there was a killer?
Real vicious son of a bitch,
hunting the police,
all slice and dice?
I needed the police to turn
on Penguin.
I knew a few cops would have to die.
So you sent this monster to my city?
I let him improvise.
I'll admit.
I'm a little carried away with
the whole cooking folks routine.
I really got into the role.
Now, only hiccup was
that mess with her daddy.
That was you.
I gave him a chance, Jim.
And if he would've shown
one iota of appreciation
for everything I have done
for this family, for him...
he would be alive.
But I saw you shot.
There was another shooter there.
I had to do something to throw off
suspicion.
She wasn't about
to get herself plugged
by a bunch of yahoos in a car.
It was some pretty shooting,
if I do say so.
I missed all her vital parts.
I want you in jail.
And this time it's Blackgate.
You're gonna rot in there.
Jimmy, just...
That's done now.
My father had his moment of truth.
This is yours.
How many cops died under
the Pax Penguina?
Not one.
It was you who couldn't stomach it.
It was you who came
to the Falcones for help.
There is a direct line
from your decision
to a dozen police officers
who have been brutally murdered.
You're insane.
Why not just kill me?
Because, Jim, I need you
at the head of the G.C.P.D.
- I need...
- Someone you can control.
You've been planning this
since the day we first met.
This isn't about Gotham.
This is revenge.
For me killing Mario.
You want to arrest me, arrest me.
But I will talk.
And the cops that died,
the friend that you betrayed,
will all have been for nothing.
The G.C.P.D. will crumble.
Penguin, or someone worse,
will take over.
And you will lose Gotham, forever.
Or...
take on this sin as your own.
Keep the G.C.P.D.
Let them think you're a hero.
But live knowing who you are,
what you've done.
That is my revenge.
G.C.P.D.
G.C.P.D. How can I help you?
Hello, anyone there? Anybody?
This is Gordon.
I'm at Sofia Falcone's.
I just shot and killed the Pyg.
Oh, thank Christ! You're safe.
Master Bruce, listen to me.
I don't want to fight anymore.
You win.
If this is how you want to deal with
what you've been going through,
then so be it.
I'm not gonna try and stop you.
But just know this.
you will remember who you are,
and when you do,
I will be right here.
No. You won't be.
I went to my lawyer and had him draw
up emancipation papers.
You're no longer my legal guardian.
I won't sign them.
You don't have to.
Now I'm going out.
If you're still here when I get back,
I'll go to the police
and show them my face.
- Master Bruce, please...
- Alfred, you're fired!
Now get the hell out of my house!
Butch!
Say something!
Say something.
I'm sorry.
I tried.
Harvey.
Was just dropping something off.
Oh, I heard you got the Pyg.
- And Penguin.
- Yeah.
So everything turned out well.
You didn't even need me.
You got a second? Could we...
They...
They believe in you.
Don't let them down.
What the hell happened to me?
True, I was...
Every single one of them!
Because of her! I will kill her!
I will flay her alive!
Her and Gordon and Zsasz! And...
Hey, buddy.
Do not talk to me, you...
I get it, pal.
This place is full of loonies.
I just thought,
we could help each other out.
And how can you help me?
Well, not to toot my own horn,
but I'm a very resourceful fellow.
So, toot.
Toot, toot.
I know that laugh.
What do you say, pal?
I'll be your best friend.
Give me a smile.