(distant siren wailing)
- Oh.
- Hey!
What? I think she... got my wallet.
Yeah. Hey!
Hey, stop!
Stop her!
(sirens wailing distantly)
(indistinct chatter)
- (meowing)
- Psst, psst.
(laughter)
(gasps)
Oh, come on, Tom.
- It wasn't that bad.
- Oh, no?
Childish drivel.
(laughter continues)
The acting was fine; the music was lovely.
What about you, Bruce?
Sorry, Mom, I agree with Dad.
- It was kinda lame.
- "Kinda lame"?
There's no such word as
"kinda." It was totally lame.
You two, so judgment...
What's up, folks?
(gasps) Stay calm, Bruce.
Give me your money!
No problem.
We're cooperating.
The necklace.
(whispering): It's okay.
Easy.
(gunshot)
- (gasps)
- (gun clicks)
- (gunshot)
- (grunts)
(gasping)
(gasping continues)
Mom! Mom?
Dad?
Dad!
(groaning softly)
(crying)
(screaming)
OFFICER: Sit down!
Don't move! Yeah, don't touch my face!
(indistinct shouting)
Shut up!
I need my pills.
(indistinct radio transmission) You wish.
- Come on! Where are my pills?
- Back, back.
- Come on. Give them to me.
- Back. Come on.
Where are my pills?!
(gunshots)
(indistinct shouting)
I said give me my pills, bitch.
Hold your fire!
Hold your fire. I got this.
Hold your fire.
Hold...
Easy, easy.
Sir,
look at me.
Not at them, look at me.
My name's Jim. Jim Gordon. What's yours?
(grunts)
I need my pills.
Okay, well, everything's
gonna be all right.
Look at me, huh?
Got your pills right here.
Huh?
Want some pills?
Here you go, here you go, here's
some pills for you, all right?
(groans)
These aren't my pills.
(groaning)
(sighs)
(indistinct radio transmission)
Sorry, guys. Didn't mean to
bark at you all like that.
- Got a little bit carried away.
- Get up! Hey!
Hey, hey, come on, man, take it easy!
Come on, guys! Hey, hey!
What the hell are you doing?
We had the drop on him.
Yeah, well, he's dropped, isn't he?
You could've gotten hurt. Rookie mistake.
Next time, shoot the son of a bitch.
If I shoot, that sets everybody off.
Gunfire every which way.
Somebody takes a cop's gun, you shoot him.
That's basic.
SERGEANT: Yo, Bullock, Gordon, you're up!
Double homicide, Theater District.
Give me a break; shift's nearly over.
Yeah, nearly.
(distant siren wailing)
(indistinct radio transmissions)
Oh, the legendary Harvey Bullock.
- No rest for the wicked, eh?
- Tannenbaum, looking crisp.
This is my new partner, James Gordon.
- What do we got?
- Just got here myself.
Male, female, gunshot.
Their kid saw the whole thing.
Poor bastard hasn't spoke a word yet.
(crying)
My name's James Gordon.
I'm a detective.
What's your name?
(sniffles)
It's okay. You don't have to talk.
Listen, T., do me a favor.
You didn't see me, okay?
I see you right in front of me.
- What's your problem?
- That's Thomas and Martha Wayne.
I don't need that kind of hassle.
Call Major Crimes;
they'd love to have this.
Yeah, but they're not here.
And your partner is talking to the witness.
So... that makes it your case.
(softly): Bruce.
My-my name is Bruce Wayne.
Can you tell me what happened, Bruce?
(camera shutters clicking)
(crying)
(sobbing)
When I was about your age,
a drunk driver hit our car.
Killed my dad.
I was right next to him.
I know how you feel right now.
(sniffles)
And I promise you,
however dark and scary the
world might be right now,
there will be light.
There will be light, Bruce.
We just got out of the movies.
(sniffles)
We were walking through the alley
to catch an uptown cab, and...
a man came out of the shadows.
He-he was tall
(sniffles) with a black mask and...
he had a hat and gloves...
and shiny shoes.
He took my dad's wallet
and my mom's necklace.
And then he shot them
for no reason.
I should've done something!
But I was too scared.
There was nothing you could've
done to stop what happened.
But there is something you can do now.
You can be strong.
Be strong.
I promise you,
I will find the man who did this.
TANNENBAUM: Hey.
Who the hell is that?
(crying)
James Gordon.
Alfred Pennyworth.
We're gonna get the guy that did this, sir.
New boy, are you?
You could say.
Good luck, mate.
Come on.
(Bruce sniffles)
Don't look. Head up, eyes front.
Don't let them see you crying.
Shouldn't we be there
when they move the victims?
Why?
Listen, hot shot, do me a favor.
Don't start talking to
witnesses until I say so.
- What's your problem?
- My problem, soldier boy,
you just caught us a
gigantic, flaming ball of crap.
Oh, yeah, how's that?
You never heard of Thomas and Martha Wayne?
Yeah, sure, the Wayne Foundation.
Yeah.
Two of the richest and most
powerful people in Gotham.
You can't begin to imagine the pressure,
we don't close this thing quick.
- So let's close it quick.
- Yeah, right.
This is random street robbery, Holmes.
Perp could be any one of
10,000 mopes out there.
(bell dings) Oh, crap.
COOK: Order up!
Well, well, well, if it
isn't Montoya and Allen.
Major Crimes Unit.
This is my new partner, Jim Gordon.
Nice to meet you.
Hi, Harvey.
You're on the Waynes, huh? Terrible thing.
Yeah.
Any leads?
- Just getting started.
- I'll be straight.
You want us to take it off your hands?
- No, no, no, no, no, this is our...
- Hold on, rook. Ah.
Why you want it?
You got a lead?
Nah. Just need the press action.
I don't know.
Come on, Bullock, you know
you're scared of this case.
- You're damn right I'm scared.
- So then do the right thing for once.
"For once"?
Where the hell you get the
nerve to say that to me?
You can kiss my ass.
Okay, you be that way, brother.
Just trying to be collegial here.
You know, I almost gave it to you,
but you couldn't help yourself, could you?
You had to go and be disrespectful.
Okay, Harvey.
Stay frosty.
Good luck.
Self-righteous do-gooding skell huggers.
Always bad-mouthing us
like they're such freaking angels. Please.
MAN: As mayor of this great city,
I swear to you, the perpetrators
of this heinous crime
will be captured
and will be punished to the fullest extent.
I swear that to you.
Poor bastard. First a
crime wave and now this.
You take all the people
and resources you need.
You just close this case.
Yes, Captain.
Jim, will you give us a minute?
Captain.
(door opens, closes)
The answer's no.
(indistinct shouting)
- Yes!
- What do I have to do, change his diapers?
You got to be kidding!
(speaks indistinctly) I don't care!
(continues indistinctly)
She said you had to keep me, huh?
Yeah, she did.
She said you were a war hero
and your daddy was a big shot
D.A. back in the olden days,
so I have to keep my trap
shut and do as I'm told.
Ouch.
Listen, kid, you got juice; do me a favor.
Ask for a transfer.
Sorry, this is where the action
is. You'll get used to me.
Jim, you seem like a nice guy,
but this is not a city
or a job for nice guys.
You understand?
No.
And that's your problem.
You're a cynic.
A slovenly, lackadaisical cynic.
(chuckles)
You're probably right.
Okay, soldier boy,
let's go roust some muggers.
"Lackadaisical"? Hmm.
(woman screams)
(panting)
Hey.
How you doing?
- Guess what this is?
- Just tell me, Ed.
I want riddles, I'll read the funny pages.
It's a .45 caliber 300-grain
cupronickel wadcutter.
Came out of Thomas Wayne's chest.
- That's a six-dollar bullet.
- Uh-huh.
What kind of gun...
Ah-ah-ah, don't ask, just tell.
It's from a pistol not
known by our database.
And no prints, either.
What else you got?
What's nowhere but everywhere,
except where something is?
Nothing.
You need professional
help, Nygma, seriously.
Let's go.
GORDON: So I'm thinking,
our man wears shiny shoes,
uses high-end ammo, and nobody
on the street knows who he is?
Maybe he's not from the street.
Like a debonair playboy
robber, does it for kicks?
Who would pretend to
be a street robber, huh?
A professional contract killer
or somebody with a personal
grudge against the Waynes.
How did this professional know the
Waynes would be coming down that alley?
That's a good question.
Essen said we don't catch
a break in the first 48,
it's time to go see Fish Mooney.
Fish Mooney? That works
for Carmine Falcone?
Her. Theater District's her turf.
Anything happens down
there, she hears about it.
(thunder rumbling)
(door closes)
Tell Fish I'm here.
(muffled screaming)
(grunts)
(groans)
I still care for you,
deeply, but I don't believe
that you still care for me anymore.
(stammering)
I c-c-care for you!
Then where's my money?
I'll get it, I'll get it, I'll get it.
(groans)
Boy!
Sorry.
If you let this hair
go frizzy, you will be.
(sniffing)
WAITER: Ma'am, Detective Bullock is here.
- Keep him warm.
- Yes, ma'am.
Hey, Oswald?
You want a turn? May I?
Knock yourself out, kid.
(groaning)
Thank you, Mr. Gilzean.
(stammering)
(groans)
(laughing, thunder rumbling)
(laughing)
- Harvey. (chuckles)
- Fish.
Where have you been?
Where haven't I been?
(chuckles)
- Who's the friend?
- Detective James Gordon, ma'am.
(grunts)
Well, aren't you a cool glass of milk?
Ma'am, was that screaming
we heard back there?
Yes, my boys are watching a scary movie.
- Really?
- No.
Actually, one of my staff has
been stealing money from me,
so we're beating his punk ass.
BULLOCK: Relax, Junior.
Fish gets some leeway.
Her staff are rough
characters, need firm handling.
So, this isn't a social visit then?
Unfortunately not.
Brass sent me by to talk to
you about the Wayne murders.
Terrible thing.
(muffled screaming)
Listen, Junior, if you're worried,
why don't you go back there and see
if anyone wants to press charges?
If that's okay with you, Fish.
Mi casa es su casa.
(blows landing, muffled screaming)
(metallic banging)
(groaning)
- Oswald, whoa.
- Yeah, take it easy, penguin.
You know I don't like to be called that.
Ooh, scary.
How's everybody doing?
Who are you?
James Gordon, GCPD.
Oh.
You came with Harvey, huh?
Glad to know you, James. I'm Butch Gilzean.
Drop the bat.
Ah, come on now.
Oswald and Raoul here
were just having a little
fun, weren't you, boys?
All in fun.
RAOUL: No problem.
Fun.
(laughs)
You a new guy, huh?
How do you like Gotham so far?
Well enough.
See you around.
(groans)
(Fish and Bullock laughing)
Oh, hey.
Everything all right back there?
It's always good to see you, Harvey.
Wow.
And look at you in your excellent suit.
You know, I'm so happy
you don't have to wear
that silly uniform anymore.
You told me it looked good.
(whispering): I lied.
(chuckles)
You ready to rock and roll?
Uh... Barbara, I'm beat.
Do we really have to go to this thing?
No.
Of course not.
- Thank you.
- You owe me.
(sighs)
So...
talk to me.
We're getting nowhere on the Wayne case.
I made a promise to Bruce
Wayne and I can't deliver.
But you will.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm out of my depth.
Hey.
I very much doubt you're out of your depth,
but even if you are,
you know how to swim, don't you?
Yes, I do.
So swim.
(sighs)
I'll swim, you're right.
You hungry?
I'm all right.
Had a few dogs.
When I am Mrs. Gordon, and you
are living here all the time,
I am gonna put you on
a proper, healthy diet.
Mm-hmm.
(phone buzzing)
BULLOCK: I got a lead.
Meet me at Fourth and Grundy in an hour.
On my way.
(rock music playing over speakers)
Hey.
Whoa.
You all right?
- Couple drinks, I'll be fine.
- Bullock...
Fish Mooney heard from one of her fences,
guy tried to sell him an antique
four-strand pearl necklace
with gold settings, one strand broken.
Like Martha Wayne was wearing.
Guy's name is Mario Pepper.
Career street thug.
Long sheet: robbery, assault,
rape, extortion, drug dealing.
Nice guy.
Hi.
- What's your name?
- Ivy.
Ivy. Is Daddy home?
You don't want to talk to Daddy.
Why's that, Ivy?
(whispers): He's mean.
PEPPER: Hey, who is it?!
Mario Pepper, we need to talk.
I've done nothing.
So it'll be a pleasant talk.
Where were you last
Saturday night around 9:30?
I was here at home with my family.
That's right. He was here.
Pearl necklace sound familiar?
No.
Then I guess you don't mind we,
uh, take a look around the place.
You need a warrant.
You're a felon on parole.
All we need is reasonable cause.
(grunts)
Stop! Stop or I'll shoot!
(gun clicks empty)
(machines rattling)
(woman shrieks)
(men shouting)
Out of the way!
(metal clangs in distance)
(yelling)
(gunshot)
Thanks.
Probably? I had to.
We got him!
We got him.
(chuckles)
Huh?
Hmm?
(cheering)
(siren whoops)
Mario Pepper was framed by
Fish Mooney and the cops.
I saw Ms. Mooney with
Martha Wayne's necklace.
She was discussing how to
get it into Pepper's home
inside a bag of drugs.
This was shortly after she met with
Detectives Bullock and Gordon
from the homicide squad.
Mooney works with Carmine Falcone's mob.
You saying Falcone had the Waynes killed?
I'm just telling you what I saw.
Why? Why snitch on your own boss?
I confess, that...
that poor orphan boy pricked my conscience.
Nah.
You want to push Fish out, huh?
That's beside the point.
I've done my civic duty.
Good day to you both.
(car door opens, closes)
You kept your promise.
Thank you.
I'm sorry you didn't see a trial.
That's okay.
Renee.
Long time.
Yeah.
(sighs)
Sorry to drop by unexpected like this.
How have you been?
I'm good.
- You?
- All good.
You're running an art gallery now, right?
- Yeah.
- That's so cool.
And I'm engaged.
That's why I'm here.
Oh?
The GCPD framed Mario Pepper
for the murder of the Waynes.
What?
They framed and killed an innocent man.
And you're here to tell me
that James was in on this?
- Yes.
- And what's your proof?
I can't tell you, but it's the truth.
James Gordon is not a good guy.
You deserve better.
James Gordon is the most
honest man I've ever met.
He's not capable of doing that.
You sure you know what he's capable of?
Yes, thank you. I know him.
Does he know you?
Don't.
Like I know you?
(siren wailing in distance)
Here you are.
Barbara?
What's wrong?
Did you frame Mario Pepper?
- No.
- I knew it.
Who told you that Pepper was framed?
It doesn't matter, as
long as it's not true.
It's not. Who told you it was?
Nobody.
Bee, I know when you're lying.
GORDON: Montoya!
What's your evidence
that Pepper was framed?
I was wrong to reveal that
information to Barbara.
- We're old friends.
- I asked what evidence you have.
You'll see the evidence when we get you
and your crooked friends into a courtroom.
We're working on it.
Save your energy.
If Pepper was framed, I'll find out.
Hey. We got a problem here, Gordon?
And then you and you just
need to stay out of my way.
- GORDON: Mrs. Pepper...
- Go away.
Ma'am... if your husband was
innocent, you need to talk to me.
If your husband didn't kill the
Waynes, how did he come to have
Martha Wayne's necklace?
You bastards planted it on him.
IVY: Bastards.
Alice, how would the
police have the necklace?
- We didn't kill the Waynes.
- So you say.
God knows my husband had his demons,
but he never killed nobody.
Can I see his shoes?
Shoes?
This is all of them?
Uh-huh.
(whispers): Damn.
BULLOCK: Framed?
How you figure?
You were there. We framed him?
Somebody could've planted
the necklace on Pepper
for us to find.
Fish Mooney could've
set the whole thing up.
Why?
To cover up for the real killer.
Mooney works for Falcone.
Maybe Falcone wanted the Waynes killed.
Whoa-whoa-whoa, wait, wait.
Why would such a nutty
idea even enter your head?
Montoya from MCU.
That pill-head loony
bird? What's her proof?
Wouldn't tell me. Didn't trust me.
She doesn't have any.
If they did, they would've used it.
Pepper didn't wear shiny shoes.
He didn't own any shiny shoes.
Shiny shoes! Mother of God.
Shiny shoes.
Just suppose for a moment, just suppose
Pepper was innocent.
I killed him.
We killed him.
We'd lose our jobs at the very least.
The case is closed. Forget about it.
Even if the real killers
are still out there?
Yes.
This is very perilous
stuff you're messing with.
Listen to me, for once, Jim.
Forget about it.
(door opens)
Detective Gordon.
Tell Mooney I'm here.
- May I ask why?
- No.
No. Yes. (chuckles)
James Gordon.
How nice.
Day I met you, when I was
out back with your boys,
what did you and Harvey talk about?
Should you ask Harvey?
He's your partner.
I'm afraid he might lie.
Hmm.
He might.
And you think I'll tell you the truth?
You just did.
James, wait.
You have a little danger in your eye.
I wonder what you plan to do with that.
You'll have to wait and see.
I hate surprises.
(panting)
BARBARA: Detective Bullock?
Miss Kean.
Uh, James went for a walk last
night and he never came back.
Have you heard from him?
I'm really worried about him.
He's on a stakeout.
Yeah.
His phone probably ran out of juice is all.
Oh.
Right. Well, that's a relief.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Wait! Wait!
Wait.
Shut up.
Hey, what are you doing?
- We're over here, you'd get a better angle.
- What?
You're a director now?
Get fresh, I'm just saying.
Hey, Butch!
Harvey.
Who told you we'd be here?
Everybody knows this is where you...
Take your problems.
That's my partner you got there.
Ex-partner.
Oh.
Let me talk to Fish.
I'm not afraid of death
so much as I am of dying.
I, um... I want to die how my father died,
peacefully in his sleep.
Not like his screaming,
terrified passengers.
(laughing)
(cell phone ringing)
Yeah?
Yeah. Bullock showed up at the plant.
- Wants to talk to you.
- MOONEY: Put him on.
Give me a moment, kid.
You're doing good.
- BULLOCK: Fish?
- Speaking.
Don't be like that.
Listen, you got to let my boy go.
How long we been friends?
For a long time, until today.
I did a big favor for
you and your little pals,
and now it's all about
to blow up in my face
on account of your stupidity.
Look, the kid's not your problem here.
He was hipped to the frame by Major Crimes.
They're gonna be coming after you.
How did they get onto me?
Usual way, I guess.
Somebody talked.
Huh. Not one of my people.
That's what everybody says.
True.
Listen, you got to let my boy go. Hmm?
You kill my partner, I
got to come after you.
(chuckles)
I don't want to do it,
but how am I gonna look,
you kill my partner, I don't make a move?
All right.
Well, you have to promise me that
you'll keep him under control.
- I promise.
- MOONEY: Cool.
Put Butch on, please.
Yeah, boss?
That son of a bitch just threatened me.
You hang him up with his partner.
You got it.
(sighs)
Hey, how you doing?
I'm good. We're going home.
- Yeah?
- Gentlemen,
I'm just glad everything could work out...
Cops.
Bless your heart.
Would you be a sweet boy and rub my feet?
Give me a moment, darling. I
haven't forgotten about you.
I like you. You're funny.
(chuckles)
Now, this amateur nonsense is a good sign.
There used to be some discipline.
Falcone is getting old and soft.
It's time.
Somebody has to take over;
it might as well be me.
Yes, it might as well.
And you, you're like a son
to me, you know that, Oswald?
I feel that way also.
Which is what I don't understand.
After all I've done for you,
and right when I'm on
the verge of great things,
you betray me.
Why would you betray your mother?
I-I... I don't know what you mean.
It was you.
(sighs)
You snitched to the MCU.
You want to know how I know?
Because only you saw me with the pearls.
No one else.
It was Gilzean.
He's the snitch.
(chuckles)
(clicks tongue)
No.
- Gilzean is loyal.
- So am I.
I would open a vein right here
and now if you asked me to.
Go on, then.
Open one.
I... I was speaking poetically.
Prove it.
Prove your loyalty, my little penguin.
Please, Ms. Mooney.
Please don't!
You broke... my... heart!
(Oswald screams)
(sobbing)
How you doing?
Been better.
Thanks for trying to help.
Wish I hadn't.
Did you just slap my hand?
Hey, Butch!
GILZEAN: Yeah, save your breath.
Look, if it was up to me,
you'd get a bullet in the
head and a decent funeral,
but Fish has her ways.
Yo! Frankie!
Showtime.
(machines whirring, alarm blaring)
(groans)
Oh, God!
Don Falcone.
Forgive me, young man, I
forget what your name is.
Or perhaps I never knew it.
Gilzean, sir.
Gilzean.
Tell Ms. Mooney she's too impetuous.
If she wants to kill policemen,
she has to ask permission.
Sir.
(groans)
There are rules.
Cut them down.
That's right, there are rules!
It's good to meet you at last, James.
I knew your father very well.
Best D.A. this city ever had.
He and I understood each other.
There was respect,
- friendship, even.
- Friendship?
Trust me,
that's the only reason you're alive now.
Blood doesn't lie.
I know that when you leave
here, you'll do the right thing.
I will.
- I'll tell what I know.
- Which is what?
I know that you own the police department.
Probably the mayor, too.
And I was pretty sure that
you had the Waynes killed,
but if you did,
you wouldn't risk letting
me live, would you?
Then again,
how did Fish Mooney come to
have Martha Wayne's necklace?
- A replica?
- Yes.
But if you didn't have them
killed, why frame Mario Pepper?
Or are you covering up for somebody else?
Who knows who killed the Waynes?
Some lowlife.
We needed a culprit before the funeral.
Pepper was sacrificed so that
the people of Gotham would see
swift justice done.
So they can feel safe and secure.
- And that matters so much to you.
- Of course.
I'm a businessman.
You can't have organized
crime without law and order.
I love this city,
and I see it going to hell.
But I won't let it fall
apart without a fight.
You make a life of crime sound very noble.
You have a hard head,
James, just like your father.
Don't be self-righteous.
Don't be arrogant.
You want me to keep quiet about all this?
Gotham is on a knife
edge. What do you suppose
bringing down City Hall
and the police force
will do, even if you could?
Would it make things better?
In bocca al lupo.
(thunder rumbling)
(seabirds cawing)
- Lookit, Jim...
- I'm listening.
I wasn't being honest with you.
But you weren't ready for the truth.
You didn't tell me
because you were ashamed.
Why are we stopping here?
No, please. Please, I beg of you!
Shut up!
This is the fool
that snitched to Montoya and Allen.
Falcone wants you to walk
him to the end of that pier
and put a bullet in his head.
Then everybody knows
you're with the program.
(gasping)
And if I don't?
Then I'm supposed to take you out
and him, too.
And here's the thing, Jim. I like you.
I might not have the stomach
to do it, but I'll try.
'Cause if I don't,
someone will get to you quick enough.
Then they're gonna get to me
and probably Barbara as well.
Who knows what you told her.
I told her nothing.
You think Falcone cares?
Come on.
You've killed people before.
- That was war.
- This is war!
We're at war with scumbags like him.
Sometimes in war, you got to do
a bad thing to do good, right?
So do you do this bad thing
or do you die and maybe your girl dies?
I might be lackadaisical,
hmm?
But that's not a tough call.
(whimpering)
(grunting)
Walk.
Please, Mr. Gordon, just let me live.
I'll do whatever you say.
I-I'll be your slave for life.
Listen to me,
there is a war coming.
A-a terrible war.
Falcone is losing his grip,
and his rivals are hungry.
There-there will be chaos.
Rivers of blood in the streets.
I know it! I-I can see it coming.
See, I'm clever that way.
And I can help you.
I-I can be a spy.
Shut up!
Turn around.
(whimpers)
For God's sake, have mercy.
Don't ever come back to Gotham.
(gunshot, groans)
Attaboy.
My God, James.
I've been so worried.
What happened to you?
Oi!
Master Bruce, get your
bloody arse down off there!
How many times have I told you?!
Why were you up on the roof?
I'm learning to conquer fear.
Fear doesn't need conquering.
Fear tells you where the edge is.
Fear is a good thing.
And you think I haven't
told him that, do you?
You came here for a reason, I imagine.
Yes,
Mario Pepper didn't kill your parents.
He was framed by the police department
and the mob working together.
We killed an innocent man.
ALFRED: Right.
- So who did it then?
- I don't know.
I see.
Sterling work there then, mate, isn't it?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
I'm glad he's still alive.
I want to see him again.
I'm asking you
to give me a second chance.
I'm going to find out who
killed your parents and why,
and I'm gonna clean up the
damn police department if I can,
but I can only do that from the inside.
So I'm asking you
to stay silent
about what I've told you.
Your call.
Right, well, that's all
convenient, isn't it?
Alfred!
Thank you.
(gasping)
(rustling)
(grunting)
Sync and corrections by madhatters
www.addic7ed.com