BRUCE: Previously on Gotham...
I went to see a sergeant
that I know and we did some digging
for any M. Malones
that fit our particulars.
Patrick Malone.
Goes by the nickname, "Matches."
So, you found him.
What do you need me for?
I need you to get me a gun.
So, you're gonna kill him?
ED: I love you.
Kristen? No!
If we can cure a man like
Oswald Cobblepot, we can cure anyone.
Nobody yet has failed to regret
vexing the Penguin,
and you are vexing me!
(SCREAMING)
- (GRUNTING)
- GERTRUDE: You don't eat?
What's the matter, Liebchen, you're sick?
So pale you look.
Tell Mama what's wrong.
(SHIVERING AND GRUNTING)
You don't have to tell. I know.
Life is hard when you're special.
And you are so special.
So clever, so handsome.
(GASPS) When you are older with a stick,
we will beat away the women.
But only if you eat your goulash
so you can grow big and strong.
(SCREAMING)
Matching the Crane formula
to our own enforced REM stimulation
seems to be providing the desired results.
How's his behavior day to day?
Docile. Friendly.
Appetite?
Low, but I'm not concerned.
Hmm, I'm curious to see
how he responds to adverse stimuli.
Let's move on to the ice cream test.
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
(MALE OFFICER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY OVER RADIO)
Ice cream. Why do you have ice cream?
(CHUCKLES) I'm sure I don't know.
- (CHUCKLES) It's unusual, isn't it?
- (BREATHES DEEPLY)
My name's Oswald, what's yours?
I don't have ice cream.
Why do you have ice cream?
Please, by all means, you can--
(YELLING) I don't have ice cream!
Why do you have ice cream?
I apologize, sir, I don't--
Ah! (GRUNTS)
- Excellent. No violent reaction.
- (INMATES TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
The treatment is working perfectly.
Guards!
HELZINGER: Where is my ice cream?
How come you have ice cream?
I want mine.
- Where is it? Where is it?
- (COBBLEPOT GROANING)
I want ice cream.
What flavor is it? What flavor is it?
(POLICE SIREN BLARING)
(CAT MEWS)
- BRUCE: Hey.
- Hey yourself.
What? You asked me for it.
- I know.
- If you don't want it--
I want it.
You look scared.
I'm not.
- Is it loaded?
- Ain't no point in an unloaded gun.
Guns aren't for show, Bruce,
and they're not for protection.
They're only for one thing.
Of course.
(CLEARS THROAT)
- Lee, good morning.
- Hey.
Look, what we talked about after Arkham--
It's not why I'm here.
I wanted you to take a look at these.
It's Kristen Kringle's final paychecks.
Her paychecks? How'd you get these?
I went to human resources to get
her new address and they gave them to me.
She never picked them up.
They don't know where she is.
She never cashed them,
never left a forwarding address.
That's odd.
Well, Dougherty has money.
Maybe they're traveling.
I don't like it.
She said that Dougherty hurt her before.
Really? Have you talked to Ed about it?
- No.
- Maybe he's heard from her.
I didn't feel like
it was right to worry him.
I just want to know that she's all right.
I can take it to Missing Persons.
No, no, that's all right.
I'll look into it.
Let you know what I find.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Ah, Master Bruce. You ready?
Yes.
I'm gonna need more than that.
We're on the hunt
of an extremely dangerous man.
This is life and death stuff.
I need you to tell me that you are sure.
Now, are you sure?
Yes, Alfred. I'm sure.
Right. And when we're on the street,
you follow my every lead,
no faffing about, is that understood?
- Yes.
- Good lad.
Our quarry is an east side boy.
This misspent youth,
Patrick Matches Malone,
was arrested several times
with a geezer called Cupcake.
I suspect there's irony at play there.
They're partners in crime
until Matches' testimony
put Mr. Cupcake
in the Blackgate Pen for 10.
Says here that Cupcake is out now,
and he runs this strong-arm
little firm called "The Mutants."
So, I guess we have to start there then.
MOHAWK: Solomon.
CHICKEN: Grundy.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
- Solomon.
- Grundy.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Remember. Let me do the talking.
I know how to handle this type, all right?
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen.
Hope we find you well.
We're hoping to have a little chat
with a gentleman called Cupcake.
You found me, sweetheart. What's up?
Mr. Cupcake, pleasure to meet you.
My name's Alfred Pennyworth.
Now, we're on the hunt for a guy
called Matches Malone.
Now, we know
he stitched you up a few years ago,
so I'm sure you wouldn't mind returning
the favor, if you know what I mean.
- Who's your friend?
- Never mind who he is...
- I'm Bruce Wayne.
- Boy billionaire Bruce Wayne?
That one.
I'm willing to pay you a lot of money
if you can tell us where to find Malone.
Oh, really? Why?
- Master Bruce, please let me talk--
- I think he killed my parents.
- Oh, that's a good answer.
- (CROWD LAUGHING)
How much money?
- How much will make you talk?
- $1 million.
- MAN: Hell yeah.
- (INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
- That's too much.
- (SCOFFS) The boy is cheap.
Mr. Cupcake, if I may be so bold as to--
- Yo, I'm talking to the shot caller.
- MAN: That's right.
Tell you what, son, I'll make you a deal.
Give me $50,000. You won't get Matches,
but you get to leave here
with your fingers and toes.
(LAUGHS)
Steady on, pal.
I'm just messing with you.
I wouldn't hurt the little boy.
I like little boys.
You on the other hand,
I'm not sure about you.
Tell you what, I'll give you
that rat Matches for 50 grand.
But first, you must fight me. (CHUCKLES)
- I beg your-- Excuse me?
- Fight me, baby.
No, you see, I'm not really a...
I'm not really a fighter.
Oh, shh. I saw you step up just now.
"Steady on, pal." (CHUCKLES)
Mr. Cupcake, I really can't foresee
anything positive
coming out of this altercation.
You're in my house.
Fight is what we do here.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
I'll pay you $100,000
for the name and no fighting.
I'm not about money, little boy.
I'm about respect.
No fight, no deal.
No Matches. No exit.
All right, well, I suppose, you know,
Mr. Cupcake, if you put it like that...
If you wouldn't mind, sir.
Will you be all right?
We'll have to wait and see, won't we?
Are you acting like this is my fault?
- It's not for me to say, is it, sir?
- How is it my fault?
I told you to let me do the talking,
did I not?
And did you do the talking? Yes. I think
you'll find yes, you did do the talking.
To be fair, I think the result
would have been similar in any case.
If, Master Bruce, we are lucky enough
to walk away from this alive,
let this be a lesson to you.
And another thing, pick your battles.
Don't let them pick you.
Right. On your honor, I win, we walk.
Sure thing, mister. On my honor.
They'll understand.
But the fight doesn't stop till somebody
says "uncle," or goes to sleep.
Now, get it on.
The other thing, of course, Master Bruce,
to remember,
is that timing is everything.
- (GRUNTS)
- (CROWD EXCLAIMS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
See, there's other factors at play here,
Master Bruce. There's footwork. Leverage--
Stop talking.
(CROWD CHEERING)
What? What, you want some?
(CUPCAKE GRUNTING)
(CROWD EXCLAIMING)
Alfred!
(CROWD CHEERING)
Uncle! Uncle!
No! He's slowing.
See, Master Bruce.
Big muscles require lots of blood.
(CUPCAKE GROANING)
Strength costs wind.
Now, if you gotta beat a big man,
all you have to do
is outlast him.
No. No.
Uncle, uncle.
I'm calling it, the butler wins.
- Are you okay?
- I'm absolutely flipping peachy, mate.
You're a tough old cat.
Not too shabby yourself, Mr. Cupcake.
Matches?
- (PANTING) Fifty grand.
- Will, will a check be all right?
(CROWD LAUGHING)
Yeah, yeah, sure, a check will be fine.
Make it out to cash.
Go see Jeri down at Celestial Garden,
it's on the east side.
She'll know where to find Matches.
Pleasure doing business with you,
Mr. Cupcake.
How do you feel?
A couple of hours kip,
and I'll come up lovely.
Good.
You stay here.
You ain't going nowhere
till I'm up and about, all right?
Yes. I hear you.
Promise me, Master B.
Say again?
(INAUDIBLE)
Sorry.
- Blood.
- Life.
Throat.
Song.
- Cat.
- Kitten.
- Mother.
- Hug.
- Crime.
- Punishment.
Revenge.
Remorse.
Ah, remorse. Let's talk about that.
I feel it. A lot.
Remorse is progress. Remorse is huge.
Is it?
I feel terrible about stuff. (SNIFFLES)
I was so mean to people.
Remorse is a healthy and natural response
of the human condition.
It is a good sign. It is a normal sign.
I want to be normal.
I want to be good.
(GROANS SOFTLY)
You must think I'm lying to you.
Oh, no. (CHUCKLES)
I can tell when someone's lying to me.
Oswald, you are making
a magnificent transformation.
Your real self is emerging.
A kind, decent, young man.
Just a few more therapy sessions
and you'll be right as rain.
More therapy?
Oh, just a little.
I know there's a discomfort factor,
but after all,
it is making you better, yes?
Oh, you do want to get better,
don't you?
Yes, Professor Strange.
(CHUCKLES) Oswald, please. Call me Hugo.
Yes, Hugo.
(SIGHS)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hey, Ed. You busy?
I'm studying the decomp rate
of various colors of ink
to see if we can use tattoos
to help determine time of death.
Hmm, is that a yes or a no?
Please come in. How can I help you?
I was wondering if you'd heard
from Kristen Kringle lately.
I'm strong as a rock,
but a word can destroy me. What am I?
Silence. I've heard nothing.
Well, I don't want to alarm you,
but we can't seem to locate her.
She hasn't cashed her last few paychecks.
Oh, my Lord. Do you...
Do you think
that something bad has happened?
No. No, no. We're not there yet, anyway.
We? Who is we?
Oh, just me and my curiosity.
I don't know Tom Dougherty well.
What is he like?
(INHALES DEEPLY)
What is Tom Dougherty like?
(SIGHS) Rotten.
Hmm, that's what I'd heard.
And Kringle told you herself
that she was moving south with Dougherty?
Not in person. She left a note.
Can I take a look at it?
I didn't really think of it as a keepsake.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Right. Yeah, excuse me.
Yeah.
(SIGHS) Again? Yeah, okay. I'm on my way.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
- So, that's the game, is it, Jimbo?
Gonna try to outsmart me?
Play me for a fool?
I don't think so.
Well, that took you long enough.
For a butler,
you sure do get beat up a lot.
What happened?
We got his name, Jim.
The name of the man
that killed Bruce's parents.
Matches Malone.
BULLOCK: Dude, we're the cops.
Thank you for sharing this with us.
When were you gonna tell us?
I haven't got time to explain now.
We got a good solid lead
from the same place
that I got seven bells knocked out of me.
Now Bruce, he won't answer his phone.
So, my guess is
he's gone after this Malone.
Solo.
Going after him? To do what exactly?
What can he do? He's a kid.
ALFRED: Only reason to go alone.
He's gonna kill the man.
I mean, I, I told him not to.
I said you're too young for killing.
Said I'd do it for him.
Again. We're the cops.
Do not tell us stuff like this.
You've got to understand. Both of ya.
This is not a game.
I understand.
Tell me where he is.
Hey, cowboy.
Yes, sir?
(CHUCKLES)
Have fun.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE CHEERING INDISTINCTLY)
(JERI SINGING THE DAMNED SONG
"NEW ROSE")
(CROWD CHEERING)
Ha! Hello, Bruce. What took you so long?
I'm looking for Jeri.
Yeah, you are.
Follow me.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Come.
(MAN COUGHS)
(GIRL CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS) Come.
Take a pew.
Iced tea? Soda? (CHUCKLES)
- No, thank you.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
You like the show?
I liked it.
- Are you Jeri?
- (CHUCKLES)
Some people call me that.
What? What can I do for you?
Oh...
Sorry. You know my name,
so Cupcake called you.
I assumed you already know why I'm here.
I just want you to say it.
I'm looking for Matches Malone.
Why?
He killed my parents.
What you gonna do if you find him?
Ask him some questions.
Kill him.
(LAUGHING)
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Killing people isn't, you know, that easy.
Hey, maybe you've killed people before.
You've killed people before, blood?
No.
But no one's killed my parents before.
Well, Matches has killed dozens of people.
Men, women, children.
He's a professional.
And what exactly are you?
Do you know where he is?
Of course I know where he is,
he's a friend of mine.
You gonna give me a good reason
to tell you where he is?
- Justice.
- (LAUGHS) Please.
- Money.
- No. I don't care about money.
Try something else.
I have a gun.
That's a good reason.
Please.
Tell me where he is.
Come on, kid,
you ain't even pointing at me!
(CHUCKLING)
What is your problem?
I've been told it's unwise
to point a gun at someone
if you're not ready to shoot them.
And I'm not.
Very wise young man.
Thank you, Jeri.
It's been interesting talking to you.
Matches lives in that big building
on Grand Street, between 9th and 10th.
Apartment 9B.
Why did you tell me that?
I thought he was your friend.
He is.
Well, he was.
Matches is gonna be happy to see you.
You, my boy,
are the childish hand of fate.
Well, that makes me God,
in a way, doesn't it?
(CHUCKLES)
And who doesn't like to play God?
(CROWD TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Bruce.
Bruce! Hey.
Please let me go.
Bruce, listen to me.
I know what you're doing.
Alfred told me everything.
He shouldn't have done that.
I understand how you feel.
No, you don't.
No, you're right, I don't.
And it doesn't matter.
This is as far as you go.
You're gonna take over from here, are you?
Yes, I am.
I'm sorry, Detective Gordon,
that doesn't reassure me.
Bruce, I can't let you do this.
GCPD. One, two, three, four...
- (LOUD MUSIC PLAYING)
- (CROWD CHEERING)
Hey!
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(STUTTERS) Matches Malone?
Mmm-hmm.
I want to hire you.
(CHUCKLES)
Kids now.
So you want to hire me?
I want someone to die.
Wait a while. They will.
I don't wanna wait.
You're kind of young
to be putting out contracts.
I'm old enough.
Are you a proficient killer?
I thought you wanted to hire me.
You didn't say nothing
about a job interview.
I have to be sure
I'm getting the right man.
Don't you know a killer when you see one?
Actually, you look very ordinary.
Have you killed a lot of people?
I've killed all kind of folks
just about every way you can.
Rich, poor, guilty, innocent.
By hand, by blade, by gun.
Burn just one guy to death, they call you
Matches the rest of your days.
Life's funny, isn't it?
Cat got your tongue?
What's the matter, kid? You sick?
Sorry, I'm fine.
Nervous is all.
You seem to be the right man.
Damn right, I am. (SNIFFLES)
Where is Bruce Wayne?
You are so angry.
I'm sensing a personal relationship.
Maybe like a surrogate father
type of thing.
- Where is he?
- He is...
He's a really good kid.
He's got steel in him.
He's gonna grow up
and be a strong man one day.
Well, if he lives long enough.
This is gonna go a lot better for you
if you don't make me angry.
Angry is your natural state, isn't it?
You are the infamous Jim Gordon.
Everybody knows about your temper.
This isn't about me.
There's a kid out there in danger.
Oh, there's lots of kids
out there in danger.
Why does this poor, little, rich boy
got your special attention?
You're trying to make me angry.
Do you want me to hurt you?
Could you? I got nowhere else to be.
No.
Tell me where you sent Bruce Wayne. Now.
You are a lot less fun than advertised.
What time is it?
Yep, he should be there by now.
So you could get there
just in time for the cleanup.
(MAN TALKING INDISTINCTLY OVER RADIO)
Price starts at 10 grand or so
for a simple hit on an adult male vic,
then there's a sliding scale
depending on how hard the job is.
I charge double for women,
and triple for kids.
No babies. I won't kill babies.
Ten grand.
That's cheap.
Low overhead.
Who do you want dead, son?
You really don't remember me, do you?
Remember you?
No. We've met before?
Yes, we've met before.
You killed my parents.
Oh...
Keep your hands where I can see them.
Relax, kid. I won't jump you.
I could if I wanted to, but...
I'm too tired.
Who are you now?
My name is Bruce Wayne.
When was this we met before?
Two years ago.
An alley in the theater district.
You killed my mother and father,
Thomas and Martha Wayne.
I was there.
Rings a bell.
You looked right at me.
I was busy that year.
My parents were important people.
It was a big deal in all the newspapers.
I don't read the papers much.
Don't watch TV.
It's always the same bad news.
You really don't remember?
Oh, hey, some of 'em stick with you.
There was this mustached fella,
he was a big fat crybaby,
comes back to me in my dreams
all the time,
like he's important.
I can't even recall his name.
Did I stab him? Toss him off a roof?
I don't know.
My parents were in evening clothes.
It was cold and wet.
You grabbed my mother's pearl necklace,
it broke.
Oh...
Oh, yeah.
And the beads went everywhere.
Coming back to me now.
Nice looking blonde lady,
silver fox type dude, and a kid.
That was you?
That was me.
Who hired you?
Maybe nobody did.
Maybe I just saw some rich suckers.
Somebody like that
walks into a dark alley,
they deserved it
'cause they let it happen.
That's the way of the world,
isn't it, son?
Don't call me son.
Why? If I did what you think I did,
then I made you what you are.
Just like Gotham made me.
Just like the rich folks
like your parents made Gotham.
I might as well call you son.
I can make you tell me who hired you.
You think so?
I could hurt you.
I can shoot you in the knee.
Or the stomach.
But you can't make me
tell you a damn thing.
Killer's code ain't much,
but it's what I've got.
If I did what you say I did
and someone hired me to do it,
you'll never know their name.
Not if you take me apart piece by piece.
You better believe that.
Well, then I guess
there's nothing left to say.
(COCKS GUN)
Here's to you, son.
You've been a long time coming.
You want me to kill you?
Why?
Little rich kid like you
wouldn't understand.
Try me.
A man gets tired.
Doing wrong and going unpunished.
Nothing happens.
You start to wonder if there is a God.
Tighten your left hand grip.
Aim right here,
a little low. She'll kick.
Come on. Pull the damn trigger.
No.
Don't lose your nerve now. Do it!
Look at me.
I'm a monster.
You need to kill me.
I wish you were a monster.
But you're just a man.
Bruce.
- He's in there.
- (GUNSHOT)
(PANTING)
- MALE NURSE: Good luck, buddy.
- Huh.
Hey. Hey.
Hey!
I think there's been a mistake.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (WHISPERS) Just wait.
- Hey.
Who's there?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- (GRUNTS)
- No. Remember me?
I'm the man with the ice cream.
(BREATHING HEAVILY) Oh, yeah.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
You knocked me around pretty good.
I guess that ice cream
must be delicious, huh?
(CHUCKLES) It was pretty good.
You look kind of uncomfortable.
I have a sharp knife here.
What say I help you out?
HELZINGER: Help me out?
You have to promise to be nice, okay?
There's no ice cream in here,
so there's no reason to get mad. Okay?
Promise?
Okay.
(GRUNTS AND CHUCKLES)
- There you go.
- Thank you.
COBBLEPOT: Oh, you're welcome.
HUGO: Bravo, Cobblepot.
Sir?
This is an official certificate from
the Gotham Board of Health and Hygiene.
It states that Oswald Cobblepot
has passed all mandated tests,
and by the laws of Gotham City
is hereby declared
sane.
I'm sane?
You're as sane and normal
as any other citizen.
Ms. Peabody even.
Do you know what that means?
No more therapy?
Oswald, you're a free man.
I don't follow you.
You are sane,
ergo there is no reason for you
to be in a mental health institution.
You are free to go.
I'm fine right here.
Oswald, Oswald, Oswald,
you are just feeling anxious about change.
That is totally normal, to feel that way
upon release from care.
Okay. I guess if it's normal...
You are a sane, gentle, good man.
And good things happen to good people.
They do?
I've never heard that before.
A true thing. Trust me.
Well, you've been right so far. (CHUCKLES)
Thank you, Professor Strange-- Hugo...
(CHUCKLING)
...for being such a kind mentor
and friend.
That's very touching, Oswald.
Thank you so much.
And now,
why don't you go back to your room
and get your belongings together.
Okay. (CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLES)
- (BUZZER SOUNDS)
- (DOOR OPENS)
Are you sure about that? Letting him go?
Not really. He's an experiment.
He's a notorious criminal.
There'll be an outcry.
The outcry will pass.
People are afraid of progress,
Ms. Peabody,
and yet somehow we keep progressing.
I hope you'll at least alert the police
he's been released.
Enough input, Ms. Peabody.
I have other reasons,
deeper plans for Cobblepot
that you can't know about now.
(INHALES DEEPLY) For your own safety.
Deeper plans?
Deeper than building semi-human creatures
in the basement?
I'm sure I don't want to know,
thank you very much.
On your head be it.
There's a reason why
we might've missed Malone, okay?
His record goes back
to nursery school on up.
Assault, robbery, battery, couple of hits
for the mob. But this is way, way back.
Last few years, nothing.
That's why his name
never came up as a potential suspect.
Oh, flying under the radar, I guess.
It happens.
Guess we'll never know
if he really did it.
Ah, the boy says he confessed.
That's good enough for me.
Malone killed the Waynes.
The question is,
who paid him to kill the Waynes?
It's a question
I no longer care to ponder.
Hey, Ed. How you doing?
Oh, getting along just fine. Keeping busy.
Any news on the Kringle front?
Uh, no. Damn.
Sorry, I've been a little busy.
I'll get into it, don't worry.
Me, worry? (CHUCKLES)
Yeah. I'll let you know
as soon as I know anything.
- Detective Gordon, do you have a second?
- Uh, yeah.
You'll let me know? I bet you will.
Acting like you forgot all about
Kristen Kringle. Sure you forgot.
- You're ready.
- Thanks, Detective.
ED: You suspect me somehow.
That must be it.
You're trying to lull me
into a false sense of security
while the claws of your investigation
close around me, eh?
Is that it, my little man?
You take me to be a fool?
We'll see about your clever little plan,
Jim Gordon. We'll see.
I can make plans of my own.
ALFRED: Master Bruce.
BRUCE: Alfred,
I have left home for a while
to live on the streets with Selina.
Please. Wait and listen before you react.
You need not worry that I'm in danger,
or that I've lost my mind.
I've thought long and hard
about this decision.
And I know it's the right one.
Malone's death made me realize
a couple of things.
You can't kill murder.
You can't get revenge on evil.
You can only begin to fight such things
by not doing them.
And you can only fight them
where they live.
Not just at Wayne Enterprises.
In the streets, in the slums,
in the bad parts of town.
So that's where I'm going.
He's lost his mind.
BRUCE: I'm not going to start
battling muggers or anything.
But one day I am going to do something
to help the people of Gotham.
I don't know what yet.
But I will.
Meantime, I need to learn stuff.
Number one, I need to learn how to live
in the same world
other people have to live in.
Selina is giving me a place to sleep
and will show me the ropes,
so like I say, there's no need to worry.
I'll be in touch soon,
and I'll come home eventually.
Please, Alfred, trust me,
and honor my wishes.
Don't try to bring me back.
I need to do this.
Sincerely, your good friend,
Bruce.
English - SDH