Previously onGotham...
Jim. Meet my daughter, Sofia.
Do you ever think about walking
away from it all?
Sometimes.
This drawing depicts a man being
healed by water.
That's Ra's Al Ghul.
He wants the knife.
Opening bid will begin
at 50,000 dollars.
A hundred thousand dollars.
Two million dollars.
Sold! To Mr. Bruce Wayne!
I guess you could say
I'm your number-one fan.
What's black and white,
and read all over?
Zebra. With a gaping hole.
I think something is wrong
with your brain, Ed.
Gordon. You got a visitor.
You shouldn't have come back here.
I'm a Falcone.
You came looking for a gangster.
That's exactly what you found.
That knife is the key to everything.
Well. Not everything.
Beautiful.
And you bought this at auction?
Supposedly, it was the embalming
knife of the first-century
Mesopotamian king. Balahsi.
And what is it that you want
of me, Mr. Wayne?
Anything you can tell me,
Doctor Winthrop.
I want to know
exactly what it is I bought.
Perhaps you should've considered
that before you shopped
2 million dollars on it,
shouldn't you?
Leave it with me overnight.
I'm back.
Man. You really need to clean
that room.
My delightful grandson.
I have access to the very clean
Historical Records Room
at Gotham Central Library.
And he uses it for his homework.
Oh, Alex, let me introduce to you
Mr. Bruce Wayne and his guardian,
Alfred Pennyworth.
What's up?
Where'd that come from?
That Cuneiform's definitely
pre-Phoenician.
Alex is an avid student of History,
and sometimes assists me.
A word, Master Bruce.
Now it's all very well
involving that old geezer.
But a young man?
Just so you remember
who's after that knife.
What's so important about it
that Ra's Al Ghul wants it so badly?
We need to know.
Doctor Winthrop.
Alex.
I have to ask you to keep
this matter between us.
Of course.
Yeah. Cool.
I mean, yes, Mr. Wayne.
I'll check back tomorrow.
Until then.
Come on, Ed. Come on.
You can do it.
This has to be...
the perfect riddle.
No!
Yes.
Yes! Yes!
Tomorrow night, Oswald,
is the night you die.
Alex.
Bring me the Palmerian Codex.
What is it?
"He who rises from the waters,
whom death shall not touch,
with this sacred blade his final,
savage destiny shall be fulfilled.
The Earth will quake.
Blood will flow.
All tremble...
before the demon's head."
What's "the demon's head?"
Not, "what," my boy. "Who?"
There is a legend in the time of this
knife of a man who could not die.
Or who died, but was reborn.
Have you ever in your reading come
across the name, "Ra's Al Ghul?"
He was a warlord.
But those guys always had
stories invented about them.
They're just stories.
My boy, people believe
in these stories.
They kill for them.
I think Bruce Wayne has stumbled
across something
much more complex than he imagined.
And infinitely more dangerous.
No one should be here.
Here.
Take this into my office.
Stay quiet. Quickly.
Doctor Niles Winthrop.
What a pleasure.
Who are you?
Museum's closed.
How did you get past the guard?
My apologies.
But my business is pressing.
"Greek vase. Second century."
This was made by a forger in
Marrakesh in the 15th century.
He had some talent,
but told the most obscene jokes.
Tell me who you are,
or I shall call the police.
I am looking for a knife Bruce Wayne
brought you earlier today.
I don't know what you mean.
The best liar I ever met
ran a brothel in Shanghai.
Her quite considerable gift was
that you knew she was lying,
but didn't care you so
badly wanted to believe her.
You, Doctor Winthrop,
are a terrible liar.
Where's the knife?
No, the police, they're coming.
I imagine they are.
"End of crime," my ass.
Harper?
Where's Bullock?
He asked me to fill in.
He took a sabbatical for a few days.
You babysitting me?
Do you need babysitting?
- What do we got?
- Doctor Niles Winthrop.
Curator of Antiquities...
Looks like somebody snapped his neck.
No witnesses, of course.
Fire alarm triggered security.
Maybe the dead guy pulled
it right before the...
Yeah. Thanks. Anything else?
Yes, actually.
According to Professor Von Dead's
log book,
the last person who visited him,
I'm talking just yesterday
afternoon...
Bruce Wayne.
It's a crime scene.
Get him out of here.
It's all right. Let him in.
Detective Gordon.
What happened?
We were thinking we would ask you
the same thing.
You met with Doctor Winthrop
just yesterday, correct?
I, I, I bought an old knife
at auction.
Doctor Winthrop agreed to examine it
for me.
I was coming by
to check on his progress.
When was he killed?
According to the fire alarm,
just past midnight.
Whoever did it
must've slipped past security.
His grandson. Alex.
He's my age, little bit younger.
Have you talked to him?
No one's seen any kid.
I'll get on it.
Where's the knife?
Alfred was right.
I shouldn't have left it.
Bruce. Slow down.
What's this knife?
You think someone would actually kill
for it?
Detective Gordon,
I'll tell you what you wanna know.
But all I ask
is that you let me come along.
If this is because of the knife,
then I'm responsible.
Bruce, a man is dead.
A child is potentially missing.
This is no time to play detective.
What do you know?
What's so special about this knife?
As far as I know,
it was just an old knife.
But I paid a great deal for it.
And there was another bidder.
A very aggressive one.
Barbara Kean.
Right.
Well, Harper will track down
the grandson.
I'll deal with Barbara.
You go home.
I'll call you when I need you.
You're here. Finally.
I've kept you waiting. Apologies.
I see my guests have arrived.
Oh, yeah.
Got to say...
they don't do much
for the vibe of the place.
If you had acquired the knife
when I first requested it,
it wouldn't be necessary.
What's so special about this knife,
anyway?
Sentimental value?
Only a destiny,
borne of blood and magic,
2,000 years in the making.
Now dog-boy here is gonna fetch it.
His name is "Anubis."
And, yes...
Bring me the knife.
And you can kill the boy.
Boss.
Knocking, Victor. We discussed this.
She's here.
Show her in.
Ms. Falcone! Welcome to Gotham!
Mr. Cobblepot,
it's a pleasure to meet you.
Call me Oswald.
Please, have a seat.
Thank you for coming to see me.
I learned from my father,
"When the king of Gotham
summons you, you come."
And how is Carmine?
Can we hope to see him sometime soon?
Shall we just address the elephant
in the room?
By all means.
My father's illegal businesses
hold no interest for me.
I'm here because the Falcone family
has a number of charities
that need my attention.
And you can only provide
that attention
by being here personally.
In my city.
- I understand your concern...
- Oh, do you?
But I assure you...
it's unfounded.
You know, your father taught me
many things.
Among them was,
"To nurture a healthy paranoia."
For example, when I took over,
some of his old cappos
went underground.
Now, perhaps
they've vanished for good.
Or perhaps they're waiting
for a Falcone to return
to lead the rebellion.
Who knows?
But...
I hear your father's voice
whispering in my ear...
"Be careful."
Now, I need to know that you
are not on some fool's errand
to rebuild your father's empire.
Otherwise...
I'm gonna stab you.
I was 13 when my father first
sent me away.
He said that Gotham
was too dangerous.
This is my home.
I wanted to come home,
that's why I'm here.
Is that enough?
Gotham. Mother to us all.
I think we have nothing
to worry about.
Give your father my best, will you?
Jim.
What a lovely surprise.
Barbara.
I heard you popped up.
Seems like you landed
on your feet, as usual.
A woman has to stay busy.
You seem different.
You like this "me" better?
You recently bet on a knife
at auction.
So much for catching up.
The knife is now missing,
and the person who had it is dead.
What were you doing last night
around midnight?
I was here. With witnesses.
We done?
No.
This place.
The money you used
to bet on the knife.
Who's bankrolling you?
A client.
And, no.
Though tempting,
I can't give you the name.
Is it Ra's Al Ghul?
If it is Ra's Al Ghul,
you don't know
who you're dealing with.
I don't know who
or what you're talking about.
Now should I call my lawyer?
I'll be in touch. Come on.
You followed me?
After I told you to stay away?
What the hell were you thinking?
I told you I'm responsible.
You should've let me come with you.
It's clear she's lying.
I can help you find the killer,
find Alex.
That's my job. You wanna help?
Who is Ra's Al Ghul?
And why didn't you mention him
before?
I wasn't certain he was involved.
- The way she talked...
- You're lying. Again.
Ra's Al Ghul is the real leader
of the Court of Owls.
He's the one responsible for
the virus and having me kidnapped.
And you didn't think
to mention any of this before?
Why would he want the knife?
What's so important about it?
I have no clue.
That's what
I've been trying to find out.
- Yeah?
- Gordon, the kid's not at home.
Apparently, granddad
was looking after him
while the parents were traveling.
He's not at school.
No one's seen him.
Great. Listen, I need all
the info you can get on a man
named Ra's Al Ghul.
He could be connected.
Sure. But, how do you spell...
No one's seen the boy.
He's either hiding.
Or the man who killed his grandfather
has him.
Police were triggered
by a fire alarm at the museum.
Alex could've pulled it.
Taken the knife.
If so, he'd be hiding. Scared.
Where could he be? Think.
I only met him for a second.
You wanna play detective?
Now is your chance.
What was he wearing?
What did he say? Give me anything.
He had on his school uniform.
He just came from studying at...
Gotham Central Library.
His grandfather had a room there.
Alex has a key.
If he's hiding, he's made a choice
not to trust the cops.
If I show up, he might run.
He needs to see a face he knows.
Come on.
Ed Nygma sent you?
The Edward Nygma?
Do it again.
My once friend Oswald, now my foe
It's me, Ed, just so you know
It's time we meet,
I think you'll agree
You'll find me where
The Earth meets the sky
Where water flows, and birds fly by
At dusk we'll meet,
I'll see you there
We'll settle things,
Unless you're scared
What the hell was that?
We should torture them.
Just get them to tell us
where Nygma is.
No, he just found us on the street.
Well, that's exactly
what you would say.
Leave!
That barmaid who kidnapped Ed
said he lost a step.
Clearly, she was mistaken.
He's up to all of his old tricks.
So I'll meet him.
You and your men will hide nearby.
Attack when I say.
Do not kill Ed, though.
I want Victor to freeze him again.
- Huh?
- Not you! The other Victor.
"Earth meets sky.
Water flows, birds fly."
Obviously, he means the pier.
Gather your men.
I want Ed Nygma.
Historical Records room?
It's in the back.
Alex. It's me. Bruce Wayne.
You can come out. It's safe.
Alex, please,
I, I just wanna help you.
Alex.
This is Detective Gordon.
You can trust him.
Okay. Okay, all right.
I'm so sorry.
That, that, that man.
He killed him.
He killed my grandfather.
It was a man? You saw his face?
I only saw him from behind.
It was the knife.
Did you know it was dangerous?
No.
I had no idea.
Alex, we need to get you down
to the station.
I can't.
That man, he'll think I saw him.
He'll come after me.
I will protect you. I promise.
He'll keep coming till
he gets the knife.
Alex, do you have the knife with you?
No. I hid it.
Take Alex, and meet me
at the station. Go.
- Who sent you?
- (Foreign language)
Thanks for clearing that up.
Bruce! Run!
- Bruce Wayne call in?
- No.
We released a city-wide BOLO.
What about that name I gave you?
Zip. I tried Richard Ghul,
Ralph Ghul...
Detective Gordon.
Ra's Al Ghul.
Minister of Antiquities attached
to the Consulate of Nanda Parbat.
Yes. Thanks for coming in.
Nanda Parbat,
that's in the Himalayas, right?
Well done, detective.
Few in your country have even
heard of our tiny nation.
Why don't we speak
in my captain's office?
Bit more private.
Of course.
- I'll be with you in a minute.
- Thank you.
I don't get it. This is the guy
that you're looking at for murder?
Why does he just walk in?
Barbara must have told him
we were looking for him.
- Yeah. But...
- Two thugs at the library.
If they're working for him,
they would've told him
that we've contacted Alex.
He could think
that Alex gave us the knife.
We can use that.
Call Alfred Pennyworth.
See if he's heard from Bruce Wayne.
And then this thing bit me.
I need to get you to a hospital.
- No. No.
- Then the police. Detective Gordon.
No, I can't. I can't.
They'll find me.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared.
I don't know how you do it.
You fought those men, and I...
I just froze.
Same as when that man killed
my grandfather.
Fear is normal.
In the alley,
when my parents were killed,
I was terrified.
I just stood there.
There's nothing wrong
with being afraid.
Once you realize it's normal,
then you can put it in its place.
Then you can act.
Fight back.
I felt bad for you.
When that happened to your parents.
You were all
the kids at school talked about.
What did they say?
That you live alone in a mansion,
don't go to school,
fly around in jets.
They make you sound weird.
Maybe I am.
No! You're, you're cool.
I'm weird.
And, you're a little weird, too,
I guess, but...
you're weirdly cool.
I'll take you to the knife.
Can I get you anything? Coffee?
That won't be necessary.
I think you know why I'm here.
Enlighten me, Minister.
Barbara Kean, with whom you spoke,
is acting on behalf of my government
to procure a certain property.
Said property is the cultural
patrimony of my people.
Why not bid on the knife yourself?
There were competing claims.
And if we bid officially,
alarms may have sound.
So it seemed better to do it quietly.
But Miss Kean failed.
And now, regrettably,
I understand there's been a murder?
Doctor Niles Winthrop.
Curator at the Gotham Natural
History Museum.
That's awful.
But the reason I'm here, Detective,
is to press my claim on behalf
of my government and entreat
you to return the knife to me.
You say this knife is important
to your country. Please explain.
There is an ancient story amongst
my people of a man...
who could not die.
In his time,
he committed terrible acts,
raised a great kingdom,
and then vanished.
What happened to him?
If the legend is to be believed,
he walked away from his throne vowing
that one day he would return
and complete his destiny,
but that would require
a particular knife.
This knife.
A story, as I said.
But to my people, very meaningful.
I hope that satisfies your curiosity.
Some.
But you see, Minister...
my chief concern...
is there's a boy,
the grandson of the curator.
He's being hunted.
Now perhaps that's because
of the knife,
or perhaps the killer thinks
he saw something.
Did he?
No.
Well, then he's safe.
Yes, but you see, I would have
to know that for certain
before I would do anything
that might affect the case.
Such as release the knife.
May I see the knife, Detective?
It would so set my mind at ease.
Hey!
Where the bloody hell is Gordon!
Gordon! Incoming!
Gordon! Where the hell is Bruce?
- You!
- Alfred!
- Wait, wait, wait!
- Back off!
Get your hands off me!
You don't know what you got in there.
Yeah, I am starting to,
but you are not helping.
I need you to calm down.
Let me finish talking to him.
Gordon!
- Not now!
- Gordon!
He's bloody vanished.
He knows we don't have the knife.
We have to find Bruce.
- Donna Falcone.
- Do not call me that.
You got to hear us out.
No, I don't.
I didn't invite you here.
We're not having this meeting.
Now I'm gonna ask you,
please, politely, to leave.
We served your father for years.
When Penguin took over,
we had to go underground.
Then we heard a Falcone
was back in Gotham.
We knew it was time.
Did you ignore my father
like you're ignoring me?
I just told you to leave.
Just tell us when your
father's coming back
to put that Penguin in his place.
Please understand me.
My father is not coming back.
This is Penguin's city.
And I want you to leave
before he finds out you're here...
Too late, I'm afraid.
Victor, how many graves did you dig?
Two.
But they're roomy.
And there we are.
My paranoia is put to rest.
You used me.
You had me come to your club.
You knew word would get out that
my father's loyalists would find me.
I was a worm on your hook.
With one difference, my dear.
The worm is usually eaten.
So you trust me now?
You're alive, aren't you?
I would plant roses.
They cover up the smell.
My father wouldn't
have killed those men.
He would have invited me
to his club as you did
but then gone further.
He would've invited me
to dinners.
Had us seen in public.
Sent the message
that the old order supports me.
And those men you killed
would've pledged you loyalty.
Now they're fertilizer.
See my father, he knew how to build
on the strength of others.
But it's your city.
New times, new methods.
There was an ancient
Sumerian jewelry box here.
I had just replaced it.
Hiding in plain sight.
Good thinking.
Bruce.
There's a legend about this knife.
That terrible things happened
because of it.
But, what if it's not just a legend.
My grandfather is dead.
The man that killed him,
he can't have this.
I won't let him.
I promise.
We have to get out of here. Run! Run!
The Nanda Parbat Consulate's
giving us the run around.
We can't get in there
without a warrant.
- Bruce still hasn't called you?
- No.
What the bloody hell were
you doing letting him tag along
with some murder investigation
in the first place, eh?
Oh, no, no.
You do not get to lecture me
about a lack of honesty and openness.
You and Bruce have been up
to something for weeks.
What have you two
gotten yourselves into?
Damn it, Alfred, I'm on your side.
Well, that may be, mate.
But whatever Master Bruce
decides to tell you,
is his decision, isn't it?
You are his guardian.
You are allowed
to violate his privacy
if it is gonna
keep him out of danger.
Stick to the point.
What are you doing to find my boy?
What can I do? Huh?
I have every cop
in the city on alert.
But as long as Ra's Al Ghul
thinks he has that knife,
his life is in danger.
Yeah, right,
and what about the other boy.
Did he tell you where
he put the knife?
No. But I have to assume Bruce
is taking him to get it.
All right.
Well, there's got to be a clue
or something inside here.
- What? What?
- You stay here.
The access I gave you
depended on trust.
If you can't be honest with me,
there's nothing I can do.
Harper, if Mr. Pennyworth tries
to leave, arrest him.
Oi, on what charge?
She'll think of something.
I went to the pier.
I waited.
Ed didn't show.
He...
Oh, just get on with it.
Right.
One, two.
I waited and waited
But you never came
You must be a coward
Or worse, a lame brain
I'll give you one chance
To make it right
Meet me again this time at midnight
I'll make this one easy
This place makes some people lie
Some people speak
And some people cry
Honestly, that could be anything.
Can we please just torture them now?
Why not?
Wait, man.
Run!
Bruce!
Down!
Let's go. Let's go.
Take him. Take him. Go!
Get off of me!
It's time you tell me
what's going on.
What is so important
about this knife.
Why are people dying for it?
Excellent question, Detective.
And you shall have your answer soon.
Just give me the knife
and I will release the boy.
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
Of course.
Bruce, hand me the knife.
Bruce! Hand me the knife.
You don't understand.
He killed Alfred,
and then brought him back to life.
And Alex's grandfather
was afraid of this knife.
I can't give it to him.
If we don't hand it over now,
Alex is dead.
- That is all that matters.
- No.
You don't know who he is.
I can't.
Well done, Bruce.
You're finally beginning
to see things clearly.
The question is...
are you strong enough?
- No!
- Drop the weapon!
Hands in the air. On your knees.
Arrest me.
Ra's Al Ghul is on his way
to Blackgate.
We made contact with Alex's parents.
It's gonna take them a couple
of days to get home.
Bruce.
Ra's is a psychopath.
You're not responsible
for his actions.
I wanna help.
But everything you've said so far,
Alfred dying, and coming back
to life, magical waters.
Give me something I can believe.
Perhaps now you understand
why we held back.
It doesn't matter what you say,
Detective.
This is all my fault.
Alex is dead because of me.
I killed him.
Oswald!
I waited for you.
Again.
And you didn't show! Again!
You coward.
Where are you?
Here. And I may be many things,
but I am not a coward.
Your riddles suck!
"This place may make some people lie,
some people speak,
and some people cry."
That could mean anything!
Lying! Speaking! Crying!
You're just describing
a range of human behavior!
No! I meant lying, as in lying de...
Laying down, lying down! As in dead!
The answer was Stoker Cemetery.
Clearly.
Only an idiot wouldn't see that.
Face it, Ed.
You can't make riddles
to save your ass anymore.
- I guess she was right.
- What? Who was right?
Your number one fan.
She said that there was something
wrong with you.
Took me a while to believe it, but...
You're not smart!
I am, too, smart.
- I'm The Riddler.
- Oh, God, that name again? Tell me.
How long did it take you
to come up with those riddles?
I don't know.
A minute, two minutes?
Few hours.
Six hours.
- Six hours?
- Yes!
For two bad riddles?
Does that sound anything
like the old you?
Well, perhaps, I'm still recovering
from being frozen in a block of ice!
But revenge will certainly
make me feel better.
You will never have revenge on me.
Oh, yeah. I will!
Oh, no, you won't.
Oswald!
I'm going to shoot you.
Yes.
You might shoot me. Kill me.
But only he can get revenge on me.
The man I froze on that pier.
The man who would've killed himself
before writing those idiotic riddles.
The man who's name
I still will not speak!
But he's gone.
You're just Ed Nygma.
And not even Ed Nygma.
Because Ed Nygma
would've noticed something.
What?
Doesn't it feel
kind of chilly in here?
You remember him?
My other Victor?
I'm going to put you on ice. Again.
You want the same pose
or something else?
No! Wait. Please.
Got it. Same pose.
No!
Okay, Oswald.
I'm not The Riddler.
Do it.
Stop.
I've changed my mind.
I'm not gonna freeze you.
I would only be freezing Ed Nygma.
Who cares about that?
No.
A better revenge is having you live
knowing that you are not him.
And you never will be again.
Goodbye, Ed.
Who am I?
I must've been seven or eight.
It was late.
I snuck downstairs to find my father
with a man before him on his knees,
begging for forgiveness.
My father stabbed him in his neck.
The next morning,
there wasn't a trace of blood,
and we had breakfast at that table.
Now you'd think I'd wanna stay far
away from Gotham but this house,
this city is in my veins.
I'm home, Jim.
Word on the street is three Falcone
capos have gone missing.
They were in hiding.
Penguin used me
as bait to draw them out.
And kill them.
And you let him.
Don't act the innocent, Jim.
You came to Carmine Falcone for help,
it was never gonna be bloodless.
So was that your plan?
Get close to Penguin,
gain his confidence, what then?
I need to know
what you're going to do.
No.
You don't.
You want the city back from Penguin,
I'll give that to you.
But you have to trust me.
Lockdown in effect.
Ready. Prisoner walking.
Stay sharp!