Previously onGotham...
Our brothers are crossing
the ocean even now.
Gotham will be redeemed in blood.
By killing nine random people,
you're insane.
But not all the victims are random.
The son of Gotham.
I'm gonna make sure
that you are telling the truth.
Touch me, and my uncle
will have you gutted.
- Are we good?
- Yes.
- Bruce.
- I never bought your stupid act.
You pretended to be my friend.
Goodbye, Silver.
Kill him.
Where's Galavan?
What do you want?
Well, your life, of course.
Hey, guys. I fixed the hard drive.
Bruce? Alfred?
Are you okay? Glass of water?
I won't sign those papers
no matter what you do.
Oh, I'm resigned to that.
You're a very brave boy.
I'll just have to acquire
the company by other means.
My true name is Dumas.
And a long time ago,
my family was dishonored
and degraded by yours.
I'm sorry about that but...
For centuries,
our noble clan lived in vile,
squalid, obscurity
but we lived in hope
because our patron saint
spoke of a glorious day to come.
But that day would only come
when nine men of Gotham
and the last son of our mortal enemy
are slain by righteous hands.
That's you, Bruce.
You're the last son.
- Stop that.
- Be glad, boy.
You are the anointed
redeemer of your family.
For seven generations,
the Wayne Family has wallowed
in vice and corruption.
So tonight, at the foretold
hour of midnight...
the Dumas will be avenged...
and the sins of the Wayne Family
shall wash away in your blood.
Oh, bloody hell!
For my mother looks over me
What the hell?
At last!
- How are you feeling?
- Not so good.
- Nygma?
- Hi.
Long story. He's a friend.
- A friend?
- You're welcome, by the way.
No thanks needed,
saving your life and all.
Yeah. Thanks, I guess.
No, really.
What are friends for?
You got beat pretty bad.
That Galavan is a pistol, isn't he?
Yeah, he is.
Cool. You're free to go,
of course, Jim.
Desperate fugitive from the law,
though you be.
But I beg of you, sit and consider.
You and I share a bond
in Theo Galavan.
A passion, if you will.
If there was ever a time
for us to work together...
now is that time.
Yes, brother, it's all yours.
For God's sakes, smile.
- Did you find the manservant?
- Nope.
You lost him.
- What can one old butler do?
- Well, that's not the point.
The point is your lackadaisical
attitude.
- We're building an empire now.
- Getting nervous, are we?
Your childishness is no longer funny.
You need to grow up.
Oh, please, pull the stick out,
big shot.
Like I don't know you from way back.
Don't.
Without all of this wealth and power,
what are you?
- A sad little...
- I said, don't.
Uncle Theo?
Yes, my dear.
- What is it?
- I'm fighting off a cold.
I was thinking
I'd go to bed early tonight
if it's okay to miss out on...
the ceremony?
A cold?
Really?
I'm beginning to wonder, Silver,
if you're cut up
to the task ahead of us.
I am.
Bruce Wayne bested you.
And yet you still feel for him.
He should be nothing to you.
He is. He's nothing to me.
But you can't watch him die. Can you.
You're soft, Silver.
You have compassion.
No.
No?
Let's see, shall we?
I'm going to give you a test.
Anything.
Make Bruce Wayne fall in love
with you all over again.
I want to see him kiss you
before he dies.
But he knows.
He knows what I am now. He hates me.
Well, that's what makes it a test.
If you're guileful enough
to win back his heart
and cruel enough
to smile at his killing,
then I'll know you're worthy
of the family name.
Brother, seriously.
- Cut the poor kid some slack.
- More from you? Really?
Isn't there some other way?
Oh, my dear.
I like you very much
but family interests come first.
And there are other girls
of the Dumas blood I could turn to,
should you fail to prove your mettle.
Understand?
Do you?
My charming brother,
he will throw you out on the street.
If he's kind enough not to kill you.
Well, let's not dwell
on the negative.
You can do it. I know you can.
Be resourceful, be ruthless.
Why don't you get yourself
something pretty to put on.
Hey.
Why are you here?
I wanted to say...
I'm really, really sorry
for what's happened...
and I'm sorry
that I had to lie to you.
I had to do what my uncle said.
But I think you're a good person...
and if I could help you I would.
But I can't and I'm sorry.
And I thought maybe you would
like some company.
But if you don't, that's fine.
- I'll go.
- Yes.
Please go.
You really hate me.
I have no feelings for you
whatsoever.
Well, I like you.
And I'm sorry.
That's all.
You can stay, if you like.
Excuse me, stop, stop, stop!
Stop, stop. Stop, stop, stop!
Excuse me, sir.
Oh, what you're crazy something?
Stop! Wait!
- Look, I have to get to work!
- Don't hurt me!
I'm most terribly sorry, sir.
I'm in a most frightful hurry.
- Freeze!
- Oh, officer, I'm just gonna take...
Captain, what the hell?
You've put out a warrant on Jim?
- Armed and dangerous?
- That's right.
He's not a criminal.
He was obviously
abducted or something.
Look, I hope you're right.
But the facts on the ground
don't look that way.
He assaulted the mayor and escaped
GCPD custody with Penguin.
Two good cops died.
And now he's a fugitive.
What would you call that,
if not criminal?
- Galavan is obviously...
- Galavan is innocent
until proven otherwise.
If Jim isn't dirty,
I need to hear that from him.
Where is he?
- Do you know where he is?
- No.
Do you know how long
he's been working with Penguin?
He's not working with Penguin.
And he's not dirty.
And I resent being
questioned like this.
Stop it. You're his girlfriend.
You know I have to ask you
these questions.
I'm gonna ask you again
if you know where he is
because if you do
and you don't tell me
that makes you an accomplice
after the fact.
I don't know where he is.
I don't like this any more
than you do.
Jim is like a son to me.
A father would have shown more faith.
Are you sure you know Jim
as well as you think you do?
Is your lover man alive,
go to Grundy, 8:05.
Will you please talk to me?
Silence makes me sad.
Talk about what?
It doesn't matter.
Anything.
Top ten lists, best vacations.
What's your favorite animal?
- Owls.
Owls are okay.
Owls are cool.
Did you ever swim with a dolphin?
- No.
- I did once.
Oh, my gosh.
It was magical.
It was like we were friends.
They have this power.
They can like, read your mind.
- No, they can't.
- No, they can.
They can see your brainwaves.
They have a form of sonars
so they can see inside you
and detect tumours,
that sort of thing.
But they can't read minds.
Well, the one I met
could read my mind.
Lee.
- What the hell are you doing?
- I need to get you out of town.
Penguin has a reliable man
who can take you upstate.
Things are gonna be unsettled
here for a while.
- Unsettled?
- We're gonna take down Galavan.
Are you out of your mind?
Miss Thompkins, I can assure you...
- He has to be stopped, Lee.
- By you?
- And these people?
- He has to be stopped.
You keep trying to kill yourself.
Have I got you all wrong?
Are you just crazy?
- Of course not.
- You're on the run from the law.
You wanna attack the mayor with
the help of a depraved sociopath.
That's not crazy?
- I can hear you.
- Don't speak.
Jim, don't do this.
Let's get out of town together.
I don't care
what you've done already
or what you have to leave undone.
Let's just go.
- I can't.
- Jim, please.
I can't.
I can't let Galavan win this way.
I'm pregnant.
There were silver white roses
and red lilies all over the house.
All of my friends were there.
There was music, dancing...
and my mom made a cake with
my name spelled out in chocolate.
That was the year before she died.
She looked so beautiful and happy.
So yeah...
that's my favorite memory.
My ninth birthday.
How about you?
I don't know.
Come on, you must have one.
So your parents really are dead,
are they?
Yeah.
I wasn't lying about that.
I'm sorry.
Hey...
that's show business.
We went camping once in a forest.
My father and I climbed
an oak tree and ate oranges.
We could hear my mom singing
to herself while she built a fire.
That was a good day.
Damn it.
Damn it. I can't do this.
I can't let you die.
That's good of you to say so
but is it up to you?
If we can get out of the cell
and past the guard,
I know a back stairwell
that isn't watched.
That's a big if.
What are you going to do?
I am a Dumas.
I have some pull around here.
Open up.
Come in.
Give me your gun.
Come on.
Oh, you silly girl.
What were you thinking?
Bruce and Alfred have been gone
for at least 12 hours.
I'm afraid they've been abducted.
We're very busy now, Mr. Fox.
12 hours isn't very long.
I am sure that something
has happened.
We usually don't post missing persons
until they've been missing
for 24 hours.
But out of respect
for Wayne Enterprises.
Bruce Wayne. Alfred Pennyworth.
Run them through the system.
Thank you.
Was there any evidence
of an abduction?
There was a lamp stand knocked over
and there was a window opened.
Who do you think abducted them?
Well, Theo Galavan
is the obvious suspect.
You have any proof of that?
- Threats made? Physical evidence?
- No, but it's obvious.
He's trying to take over the company.
Captain, we know the man's dirty.
Of course, we know he's dirty.
We know the names of every dirty
crook in Gotham, so what?
Proof, Bullock. Proof.
To get a warrant against Galavan,
we need proof of a crime
and proof that he's involved.
Speak.
Where's Master Bruce?
We were hoping you knew.
I was in process
of commandeering a vehicle
when two of your idiot
cozzers shot me straight
in the bloody face with a stun gun.
- Here I am.
- There's your warrant, captain.
Where?
He was assaulted
on Galavan's property
by known associates of Galavan.
While trespassing in Galavan's Tower,
he was lawfully pursued
off the property
by the rightful occupants.
You got nothing there.
Galavan's got Bruce Wayne, boss,
sure as eggs.
Give me real proof.
We already jumped the gun once
with Galavan and we got screwed.
Without solid proof,
no judge is gonna sign a warrant.
Eggs or no eggs.
- So, what do you propose we do?
- You hang tight.
We'll dig up some health
and safety issue,
get a backdoor warrant
for Galavan Tower.
Right, so how long
is that gonna take?
Probably until tomorrow morning.
- But...
- That's the best we can do.
Oh, and you're free to go.
We'll drop your charges.
Right, I'm gonna thank you
very much indeed.
But Bullock, I'm gonna need
some clean bandages,
I'm gonna need a car
and a couple of guns.
You got it.
- What are you going to do?
- I've got no choice.
No time.
- I've gotta go visiting.
- I'll come with you.
Are two men enough?
It wouldn't seem so,
but violence is not my metier.
No. Two men are not enough.
I would gladly join you,
but I imagine an amateur is no asset,
a hindrance perhaps.
That's very true.
Where is Jim Gordon?
He's perfect for this kind of thing.
- Where is he?
- Yeah. "Where is Jim Gordon?"
It's a long story
but nobody knows.
- Something funny, Ed?
- Do you know where Gordon is?
Do you?
Start speaking, Winters.
A diamond plate, a glowing grate,
a place you never leave. Where am I?
- What?
- Home.
Whose home? Your home?
Gordon's at your home?
No. Yes.
Who are you?
Good luck, old friend.
- See you around.
- I hope not.
- Goodbye, Penguin.
- Goodbye, Miss Thompkins.
Please don't think too badly of me.
We are what we are.
That's true. Goodbye, Mr. Cobblepot.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
Wait here.
Galavan has Bruce.
I understand.
- Just promise me...
- What?
Never mind.
Do what you think is best.
Call me when it's over.
I'm so terrible.
No, you don't.
Thank you.
You're so calm.
- It's like you're not scared.
- I guess I'm not.
It's weird.
You are weird.
But I love you.
- Do you?
- I do.
Do you love me?
No.
No?
Silver, I don't know
why you're doing it,
but I know you're playing with me.
I know that whole escape
was a ghoulish charade.
That's a horrible lie.
I'm only telling you this
because when I'm dead...
you may feel bad and I don't want
you to think you tricked me.
So far, I don't love you.
I pity you.
Why did you do this?
What's the point?
Uncle Theo made me.
He said if I can't make you
love me again...
if you don't kiss me goodbye,
then I'm not good enough
for the family.
He's going to kick me out.
Or kill me.
Same thing, really.
- I see.
- God, I'm such a loser.
- An evil pathetic loser.
- You're not.
You're young and scared
and under the control of bad people.
You can change.
There's hope.
You can't even imagine
the things I've done.
There's no hope.
There's no going back to normal life.
My family is all I have.
And now I've lost them too.
All right, everybody set? Let's go.
What's the plan?
Get into that building, find Galavan
put a gun in his mouth
until he gives up Bruce.
- Then I kill him slowly.
- No. Then we arrest him.
Yeah, no.
Are you nuts?
- After all that he has done?
- He's going to stand trial.
Gotham needs to know
who he really is.
- Gotham needs him dead!
- Rub it, rub it, rub it.
Can we just stop the bunny and just
first get in there, please, chaps?
- Yes, let's go.
- Seriously that's it?
You have no plan?
How are you even
going to get into the building?
I know a way.
- Who is she?
- Fox, that's Cat. Cat, Fox.
- You know a way in?
- Yeah, I know a way in, Gordon.
How do we know
you're not gonna stitch us up?
I mean, you've switched sides
often enough.
How do we know that you're not
working with Galavan?
How do I know you're not
a Martian in a rubber suit?
I trust her.
You're in, Cat. Thanks for your help.
Grab a vest, let's go.
People, surely we should
have a backup strategy,
given the strong
possibilities of failure.
Au contraire, Mr. Fox.
Failure is not an option.
What he said.
As you like.
Stop acting like you're not scared.
I know you are.
Sure.
Maybe a little but...
mostly I feel very alive.
Happy even.
I'm going to see my parents.
Hold that thought.
Show time.
One moment, please.
Goodbye, Silver.
I love you, and I forgive you.
Hey, Bravo.
Come on in.
Oh, for Pete's sake.
Death to the son of Gotham.
- What in hell is that?
- Nothing good.
Death to the son of Gotham.
- I'll be right there.
- Death to the son of Gotham.
Death to the son of Gotham.
Prepare yourself, boy.
You're a deluded old fool.
And you'll pay for this.
Ancestors, be our witness!
- The prophesy is fulfilled.
- Stop!
Please?
Sacrilege.
Listen to me, Barry.
Hold on just a moment.
All right, Mr. Fox, make it quick.
What do you got?
I have the current location
of James Gordon.
I'll call you back.
Drop the knife, old man. It's over.
So it would seem.
That was a lot of stairs.
Are you alright?
Where's Galavan?
The only way out of here now
is straight down.
There's only two of them.
Yeah.
Silver isn't coming.
I just wanted to take a moment,
sweetheart
to express my deep disappointment.
- Theo, Leave her be.
- Silence!
Bite me.
What... what are you doing?
I don't know who you are anymore.
Oh, please,
that's such a ridiculous cliché.
Forget it, brother. You lost.
It's time for me to look out
for number one.
Sorry.
Tabitha!
Theo Galavan.
You're under arrest.
Oh, God.
You scared me, man, I thought
you were gonna shoot me.
Cuff yourself.
Thank goodness for simple
men of principle...
who believe in the system.
This time you'll get the chair.
You want to make a bet?
- Maybe you're right.
- Steady now, Jim.
I was just talking big,
as they say I am.
- You got me fair and square.
- Had you that way the last time.
And you turned it around.
Jim!
Back up!
I got him. Back up, I said!
And you, on your knees.
We have a warrant
to search these premises.
Jim.
Now you put your gun on the ground.
Put your hands on top of your head.
- What?
- You heard me.
- You're still a fugitive.
- Captain, I've done nothing wrong.
I want to believe you, Jim,
so we're gonna do this by the book.
Put your gun on the ground
and let's handle this the right way.
You're making a mistake.
Nobody shoot.
We are all friends here.
- Like hell, we are.
- I apologize for that.
But there we are. It's done now.
They're still alive.
That's something.
Look forward now, Jim. What now?
I will kill you to get to him
if I have to.
Forget that this man
sicced Barbara Kean on you.
Forget that he nearly killed
the mother of your child.
Forget revenge.
Think of the greater good.
Think of Gotham.
He has the courts in his pocket
and billions of dollars
at his command.
Are you 100 percent sure
that he won't beat this
and walk free again?
Are you sure, Jim?
Think of Gotham.
Captain Bravo. Team Bravo, moving in.
Entry in 10.
But think fast.
I do believe, Master Bruce,
this falls very firmly into
the category of "I told you so."
I told him so too, Alfred.
Yes, well, thank you both
for your help.
But I had a perfectly feasible
escape plan.
You're a man of conscience, Jim.
You'll regret this.
I have many regrets.
This won't be top of the list.
Here we are.
Shame.
It's gonna be a beautiful morning.
Goodbye, Jim Gordon.
This is for my mother.
Kill me. Please.
Enough! That's enough.
It's over.
- Is it?
- Yes.
Good.
Will you marry me?
Here you go, Ms. Peabody.
- Fresh meat from the city morgue.
- Show some respect
Doctor Strange has high hopes
for this one.
That's unusual.