Previously on Gotham...
I'm arresting you for the
murder of the boy you blew up
under the Crown Point Bridge.
And how can you help me?
What do you say, pal?
Give me a smile...
I'm not who my parents
might've wanted me to be.
- And I'm okay with that.
- I'm not okay with it.
I went to my lawyer to have him
draw up emancipation papers.
Alfred, you're fired.
Now get the hell
out of my house.
I am in control!
But why would you want that?
We had so much fun
when we were me.
Surprise.
I needed the police
to turn on Penguin.
So you sent this monster
to my city?
I need you
at the head of the GCPD.
Let them think you're a hero.
This is Gordon.
I just shot and killed the Pyg.
Ivy?
What happened to you?
I've been reborn.
And I will never
be underestimated
or ignored ever again.
Let's make Gotham our bitch.
Can I help you?
You're so beautiful.
Thanks.
Now, move.
Hey, Dad, guess what happened
at school today.
Oh, my God,
you're gonna love this.
- Can I just tell him?
- Wait. No, can I tell him?
Just let me tell him.
Nice score.
Cindy, who are these two...
Well, what a charming
young lady.
She's so beautiful, Mom.
- That's cool.
- So your perfume
turns people
into your super fans?
Like all good things,
it'll fade.
But until then,
they're mine.
Freeze.
Not bad.
I'll check out
the rest of the house.
My friend thinks
we're here to rob you.
But I know who you work for,
Roland Charles, PhD.
How you torture plants
in the name of science.
Do you ever wonder
how those plants feel?
Soon, you'll share more
with them
than you ever could've imagined.
What did you do to him?
I gave him what he deserves.
Captain, Captain Gordon. Yoo hoo.
Captain, Captain Gordon.
Chaz Carmichael.
- Congratulations.
- The Boss ain't gonna be happy
I'm in here.
Let's say
I got a lot of responsibility
in my organization.
Well, you seem like a real
responsible guy.
My boss is Sofia Falcone.
Oh, yeah?
What's that got to do with me?
Easy, all I know is, she told me,
if I ever got pinched,
to tell you to give her a call.
Is that so?
You can't do this. I got rights!
Oh yeah, how about you exercise
your right to remain silent?
Hey, Cap.
Got something.
Victim is Roland Charles,
over in R&D, Wayne Enterprises Biotech.
Did you know him
from when you worked at Wayne?
I met him in passing, not that
I recognized him right away.
It's like the tweaker
we found last week.
The toxin entered the bloodstream
through the cuts on the neck.
If it is the same as the last victim,
the toxin creates vines
that feed off
of the victim's body,
while also attacking
the hippocampus
like some plant-based psychedelics.
So it kills you
and makes you hallucinate?
- Any witnesses?
- The family is saying
that it was two women.
Redhead and a brunette.
The redhead used some kind
of hypnosis on them,
and the brunette
wore a leather whip.
Selina Kyle?
Murder's not really her thing.
The family says
the redhead killed Roland.
She left with his briefcase.
If his briefcase is missing,
maybe this is related to his work
- at Wayne Biotech?
- Doubtful.
He oversaw standard projects,
pharmaceuticals, pesticides.
What?
Nothing.
I'll track down Selina.
This is Bruce. Leave a message.
Bruce, I know
we haven't talked in a while.
But someone just killed
Roland Charles.
We may have a problem.
Roland Charles asked
for clearance
for some top-secret
biotech experiment.
Project M.
Ivy, do you think I care
about that?
You just killed a man in front
of his family.
He had it coming. You have
no idea what these people do.
We need to find out everything
we can about Project M.
And whatever it is,
all access would've had to have
been approved by Bruce Wayne.
You know, I really thought
that doing a crime spree
with you would be fun.
But...
I was wrong.
- Selina.
- Leave me alone.
Enjoy your shrubs.
We don't need her.
Now let's show everyone
just how strong we are.
Pour me another shot.
Party time.
- Shut up.
- Gonna throw up.
Gonna throw up.
You know,
I've had some crazy nights.
But I've never bought
a talking bird.
Sorry, party's over.
I wasn't at the party.
I've seen you before.
At The Sirens.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to speak for those
who can't speak
for themselves, Bruce.
I'm here to speak
for the plants.
Okay.
My head hurts. Please get out.
First,
tell me about Project M.
How do you know about that?
Oh, I know a lot of things,
billionaire boy.
Ivy?
You're so beautiful.
Now, Project M.
Hi, guys.
Get it off!
Is this seat taken?
If I say "yes,"
will it make a difference?
You know,
I've always been a fan.
When you got locked up
in this loony bin,
I expected great things,
a murder or two,
maybe a prison break.
But all you've done is mope
for the last six weeks.
You must know I cannot escape.
Why?
None of your business.
Because Sofia Falcone is holding
someone important to me captive.
And if I escape,
she will kill him.
Wow, what a boring story.
If there's one thing I can't stand,
it's someone boring.
The last person who bored me
was Dietrich.
- Dietrich.
- I had to sneak into his shock therapy
session and goose the juice.
Now he pees himself 10 times
a day and sometimes, uh...
Poos himself.
Well, that's very sad.
I'm gonna cure you
of this attitude, Oswald.
I'm gonna find
that entertaining guy
I know is inside of you.
And when I do, ooh,
we are gonna have
so much fun together.
That's quite a story.
Not what I was expecting.
You're just so easy to talk to.
Normally, I'd make this quick
like I did with Roland.
But it's your name
on the company
that murders
my little green friends.
I'm so sorry, Ivy.
I would never want to upset you.
But you have, Bruce.
Hide out here all you want.
Bury your head in the sand.
You're still guilty.
It'll be slow.
and it'll be painful.
But it's what you deserve.
I'm just sorry I won't be here
to see you bloom.
Nope, nope.
No. None of these will do.
Where's Ivy?
What did she do to me?
Where am I?
Ah!
Just the thing.
Ra's al Ghul?
Nope, never heard of him.
I'm Dr. Greenthumb, just here
to do a little light pruning, really.
No!
There.
That's better.
Mummy always used to say,
"A little pruning
encourages growth."
- Where are you taking that?
- Thanks, poppet.
Where are you taking my face?
Please, what's happening to me?
My dear boy,
you're dying.
Just hold still,
while I put these in place.
- No.
- Good Lord.
Jim, what a pleasant surprise.
- I'm looking for Selina.
- Haven't seen her.
She's more of an alley cat
than a house cat.
- Now I'm just in the middle...
- Let him in.
Hello, James.
It's been a while.
Barbara, can you give us
a moment?
Sure.
Have fun, lovebirds.
What is your business
with Barbara Kean?
You're worried that I told her
about our arrangement?
I know how to keep a secret.
Now, I want my man Carmichael
released from GCPD custody.
That wasn't the deal.
You run the underworld.
I run the GCPD.
Your guy got arrested.
That's on him.
Let me make something clear.
Our deal is
whatever I say it is.
Unless you want people
to know you're responsible
for bringing the Pyg to town.
You brought him to Gotham.
I was just trying to stop Penguin.
But you covered it up
and took credit for killing him.
Word gets out, you're destroyed,
along with your beloved GCPD.
And if I go down,
so will you.
And I think you like
being Queen of the Underworld.
You still think you know
what I will and won't do?
I know a bluff when I see one.
I have a job to do.
Selina.
Hey, Jim, I found Selina.
She went that way.
No! No! No!
Shut your beak.
No, no!
What do you want?
I told you, Pengy.
I'm gonna cure you
of this sad sack mopey act.
And the best cure
is the laughing cure.
Make me laugh.
Make him laugh! Make him laugh!
So what'll you be performing?
Contortionism, juggling act,
a tight five?
Oh. What's that?
You want to do a clown dance?
- Yeah!
- Wonderful.
I will not!
Ooh.
No.
Get your hands off. No!
Make him laugh!
Make him laugh! Make him laugh!
In your own time.
You have no idea how I've suffered.
The betrayals I've endured.
Just leave me alone.
- Leave me alone!
- Cut!
Oswald, Oswald, Oswald.
You are trapped in a prison
in here.
And I'm offering you the key.
So, dance!
Make him laugh!
Make him laugh! Make him laugh!
Now we're talking.
I can feel the funny coming.
Here it comes!
Here comes the funny. Again!
Fred Astaire, you are not.
I'll try again tomorrow.
What the hell, man?
Why were you running, Selina?
'Cause a jerk with a badge
was chasing me.
So not because you were
in Roland Charles' house
last night when he was turned
into a tree?
His family saw a redhead
and a brunette.
The brunette was carrying
a leather whip just like yours.
Tell me I'm crazy.
I swear, I was only there
to rob the place.
So what about the redhead?
She killed some tweaker
in The Narrows the same way.
I need a name.
Ivy Pepper.
Try again. I know Ivy.
No, Gordon, she's changed.
Like a lot.
She can use plants to hypnotize
people and poison them.
So why'd she wanna kill Roland?
'Cause he works
for Wayne Enterprises.
Wayne Enterprise?
She's obsessed with a super
secret project they're doing.
Lucius lied.
Come on, let's go.
Admiring my handiwork?
Excuse me?
Look how beautiful he became.
And all it took
was a little scratch.
What do you want from me?
I wanna know about Project M.
- What is Project M?
- Mmm-mmm.
Bruce Wayne told me everything.
How he didn't even trust himself
with the location
but that you know where it is.
And you're gonna take me to it.
But first,
you probably wanna tell me
I'm beautiful.
Yes.
Help.
Help! Somebody help me!
Beautiful.
Jim. Jim, you need to help me.
Ouch.
Looks like you cut yourself
shaving, old man.
Jim, it's me. It's Bruce.
I'm Bruce Wayne.
Honey, I think we'd know
if you were Bruce Wayne.
He's the one throwing this shindig.
That's him yonder.
Bruce, you're incorrigible.
I may bust a gut.
Luckily, I am a doctor.
Ain't he the cat's pajamas?
Go on.
Easy there, sport.
It's Italian velvet.
What did you do?
Where's Ra's al Ghul?
Ra's al who?
It's my face.
He gave you my face.
That's my face.
I think you've been hitting the gin.
Give me back my face.
I'm Bruce Wayne.
Get off of me.
You're ruining my fun.
Everything all right?
- Master Bruce?
- Yes, thank you.
Just getting rid of the riffraff.
Dude, what is it with you
and arm-grabbing?
Harper, I need keys to lockup.
And is Lucius in his office?
Lucius? No, he left with Ivy
a little while ago.
- Ivy Pepper? She was here?
- Yeah.
She asked me
to introduce her to everyone.
Isn't she the coolest?
She's a psycho who turned
a guy into a potted plant.
What's going on with you?
Did he just say
that Ivy's a psycho?
But Ivy's the best.
Is this the hypnosis I've been
hearing about?
I'm gonna say yeah.
Until it fades, they'll
do anything for her.
And think she's the coolest.
What do you mean by,
"Ivy's a psycho"?
Hold that thought, Harper.
We'll be right back.
You hear what
the Captain said about Ivy?
- But Ivy's awesome.
- Yeah, she is the coolest.
No more! No more!
You have a visitor.
Hello, Oswald.
I see Arkham's
treating you well.
I take it you're here to gloat.
You are correct.
And why not?
I am in an insane asylum,
being pummeled by lunatics.
Then again,
at least I'm not a moron.
I may not be the man I once was.
But I have many things
that you do not have.
A purpose.
Friends.
You have neither of those.
And I wanted you to see that.
No.
I know you.
There's something else going on.
Something else brought you here.
There's nothing else.
I wanted you to see
how well I am doing.
And I wanted to see
how miserable you are.
Mission accomplished.
Ed.
I'm going to be out of here soon.
And once I am,
I am going to wipe
that smile off your face.
Preferably with a chainsaw.
Now, how are you going
to do that?
You have no friends,
no one to help you escape.
You are utterly alone.
Goodbye, Oswald.
Sorry, but I don't put
too much stock
in the opinions of simpletons!
"I am held captive all day,
my brilliance locked away.
"This prison must be broken.
The key?
"My name which must be spoken."
You're still in there.
That's why you came.
You're still there.
And you're gonna help me
find a way out of here.
Hello? We should be leaving.
Not until we find out
where Ivy took Lucius.
There has to be something.
You know where it is and
you are going to take me to it.
Mmm. You're so incredible.
Uh-huh. Where is Project M?
Wayne Biotech has a secret
facility outside the city
at the edge of Kane Park.
Good man, Lucius.
In here.
Hey, Cap, the boys and I
were talking,
and we didn't really like
the way
that you were talking about Ivy.
I told you we should've left.
Look, I think you misinterpreted
what I was saying.
You called Ivy a psycho.
That's a term of endearment.
I love Ivy. I think she's great.
What about you?
Do you love Ivy?
Yeah, I love Ivy.
How much?
I love Ivy so much that I wish
I could be her.
You're not really selling it.
And you think you did?
Run.
Get them!
Selina!
All right, Oswald,
old buddy, old pal.
Tonight, we're gonna cure you.
Make me laugh or else.
Let's call this
the sudden death round.
Dietrich?
Okay, that was clever-ish.
Yeah, that's a spoon.
It is also a fork!
Looks like you got
some fight in you still.
But it's just too little,
too late, too...
Boring.
Lobotomize the little bird.
Wait. Wait.
You said this prison
was all in my mind.
Maybe I'm in a prison right now.
A prison where
you can't get to me.
Okay.
You really are nuts.
Try laughing now,
you ginger sap!
Yes!
See? I told you I'd cure you.
Don't flatter yourself!
One more.
And so I said to the guy...
You wanna know what I said?
I said, "What is this?
"A three-ring circus?"
And keep them coming.
How long do you think
you can hide in here?
Look.
Out there.
He's going to find you eventually.
I don't understand.
Who's going to find me?
Alfred?
Special Agent Pennyworth
to you, you scumbag!
The kid's secured,
requesting extraction.
No!
Just be careful, here.
We're gonna go this way.
This way.
So this is it.
Project M.
Also called "Lazarus Water."
It belonged to a man
known as Ra's al Ghul.
It stimulates cell growth
at an alarming rate.
We've yet to figure out how.
I assumed Project M killed plants,
but it's the opposite.
Just like humans to lock up
something so beautiful.
What are you going
to do with it?
I'm going to make miracles happen.
Release me!
Listen to me. I'm Bruce Wayne.
I can pay you whatever you want.
You need to let me go now!
Sorry, I can't do that now, love.
- You see, I have a mission.
- What mission?
For me to bring you to him.
What is that?
Well, giddy up, son.
What do you want?
Why did you bring me here?
This is where
my parents were killed!
No.
This is where I was born.
No!
That's far enough.
Jim Gordon.
Ivy Pepper.
It's been a long time.
I'm not the same kid
you remember.
The kid who's father
you and you partner killed
all those years ago?
How is this possible?
Well, first, I was a seed.
Then a sprout.
Now I've bloomed.
Drop your gun.
Or your friend Lucius
becomes a flower arrangement.
Lucius, you okay?
I'm in the sweet embrace of one
of my favorite people, Jim.
Never been better.
Now I know you're tenacious,
Jim Gordon, gun or no gun.
You'll come after me.
But then,
Bruce Wayne will die.
What have you done to him?
I went to Wayne Manor
and planted a seed.
I imagine he's about to bloom.
But if you let me go,
you may have a chance
to get him the antidote.
This isn't over.
You have no idea
how right you are.
I love you.
Lucius, give me the antidote.
Let's just wait until
Ivy is at a safe distance.
Give me the antidote. Come on.
- Don't make me hit you.
- Jim.
I must warn you,
I'm a black belt in jiu-jitsu.
Since when?
Night classes.
- The Lazarus Water.
- Come on.
We've got to get to Bruce Wayne.
Let's go.
Help!
Somebody help!
Who's there?
Show yourself!
Who are you?
I am the one you cannot escape.
The one you cannot kill.
You're me?
- Please...
- You're scared.
You should be.
It's okay, Bruce.
It's all right.
You're safe now.
According to Lucius,
Ivy's toxin attacks the brain
like a hallucinogen.
So whatever you went through,
I doubt it was pleasant,
but it wasn't real.
I think I saw who I really am.
I know what you're gonna say.
But what I saw, it was real.
Well, then you're lucky.
Most people go their whole lives
not ever knowing
- who they really are...
- I'm not lucky.
You didn't see it.
I've seen my own darkness.
I'll say this.
You have people around you
who care for you.
Don't fight this alone.
Trust us.
I'll leave men outside tonight.
I'll come by tomorrow,
check in on you.
Jim.
When I was under,
I saw you.
You had a mustache.
Well, clearly,
that's a very dangerous toxin.
Alfred, it's...
It's me. It's Bruce. I...
I need your help, Alfred.
Please call me.
We're not hypnotized.
Just embarrassed.
Good to have you back.
All right, listen up.
I want an APB on Ivy Pepper.
Finding her is our top priority.
All right, you heard him, people.
Let's get to work.
- What do you want?
- I thought about what you said.
How if I used the Pyg to destroy you,
I'd also destroy myself.
And?
And
you're right.
I've come to enjoy being
the Queen of Gotham.
Glad we understand each other.
Not quite. You see, I also
realized I don't need the Pyg.
There are other ways
for me to hurt you.
Thank you so much for coming.
I thought we were overdue
for a chat.
How could I say no
to my sister-in-law?
So I strangled him
with his lower intestines.
Relax, buddy.
You gave me what I needed.
The laugh of the century.
Tell me something.
You appear to have everyone here
under your thumb,
- the guards, the inmates...
- What can I say?
I'm a charismatic guy.
You could escape anytime.
- Why stay?
- Hmm.
Why indeed?
- You're planning something.
- Righty, old boy.
Something spectacular.
See, I'm in this funny farm
'cause I need to find
the crème de la crazy,
which is why I need you.
Ah, you get it.
But when we're done,
the world out there,
that'll be the asylum.
What do you say?
Thank you for your kind offer.
I don't expect
to be here very long.
You'll come around.
They always do.
Nope.
Where did these plants
come from?
Get out!
Before we call the police.
Oh, friends.
You're all so beautiful.