Previously on
"Gotham"...
You know you can't commit
a crime in Gotham without
a license
from Penguin.
Tell your families
Oswald Cobblepot
keeps them safe,
not the GCPD.
We'd need
an army to take on Penguin.
I am not giving the city
over to Penguin.
I don't care what
the commissioner says.
Makes me miss Falcone.
I'm done with this business.
I'm out.
I've got a place down south
I can go to.
We need an army.
He's got one.
You show your face
to Falcone,
he will kill you.
An opportunity awaits you.
Why do you want this so bad?
I'm sick
of not being taken seriously.
With you and Barbara,
the three of us
could give all those creeps
a run for their money.
You were the one time
I let love weaken me.
- No!
- And I want you around
as a constant reminder
to never make that mistake
again.
I'm the one you seek.
I am Ra's al Ghul.
I have to be ready
for when Ra's al Ghul returns.
You need to find your true north
and let that guide you.
♪♪
It is you.
At last.
I was no more.
And now you live.
How can this be?
The power is in the water.
It has given you life and a destiny.
You must find your heir, as I found you.
Find him.
Be free.
*Gotham*
Season 04 Episode 03
Title: " They Who Hide Behind Masks"
Alfred, you read?
Loud and clear, Master Bruce.
Looks like the rumors
around town are true.
Penguin's bringing in a big shipment.
Whatever it is, it must be valuable.
He's got four armed men
loading it onto a truck.
I'm gonna go down for a closer look.
How did I know
you were gonna say that, then?
I'm wearing bulletproof armor,
remember?
Yes.
Lucius Fox's armor was bulletproof.
My mask... is not.
Don't get shot in the face? Got it.
Do I detect a note
of sarcasm, Master Bruce?
Hold on.
I just picked up a thief
heading toward the truck.
Thieves stealing from thieves
is a victimless crime, Master Bruce.
You just walk away now.
They're walking into a trap.
Master Bruce,
I'm all for you
protecting the innocent,
but I won't have you risking
your life
over a thief.
Now walk away.
Master Bruce?
♪♪
The hell are you supposed to be?
Must be real stupid
trying to steal from Penguin.
Bad idea.
Hold him!
Let's get out of here!
Come on.
In the truck!
Damn it.
Hola, señor.
Can I help you?
James Gordon.
I'm here to see Carmine Falcone.
He's not expecting me.
Come with me, please.
♪♪
Carmine.
Jim.
You're a long way from home.
Came down to see you, Carmine.
Heard you retired down here.
Sorry for not calling ahead.
No, you're not.
It's quite the spread you have here.
I think we're past the point
of small talk, Jim.
Just tell me why you're here.
Morning, Daddy.
- How was Artemus?
- He's feisty,
as usual, but I whipped him into shape.
Who's this?
James Gordon.
Jim, meet my...
only daughter, Sofia.
What are you doing here, James?
Go ahead, Jim.
I have no secrets from my children.
Penguin has taken over the city.
The GCPD has turned its back on Gotham.
There are families
that are still loyal to you.
I need your help
to knock him off his perch.
Sure this isn't about you, Jim?
Your loss of power in Gotham?
This is bigger than me.
You have fight, kid.
I've always admired that in you.
But I can't do what you ask.
Why?
Because I'm dying.
Doctors don't know why.
Maybe old age.
Karma.
They seem to think the air
is better down here for me,
give me more time.
I'm not one to argue with doctors.
Or time.
So, you see, I can't go back with you.
I'll go back.
Hush.
You're not ready for Gotham.
There was a time in my life
when I would have done
anything for the city.
Those days are gone.
I'm sorry, Jim.
You're on your own.
You sure you know what you're doing?
You're mad because I didn't
listen to you, Alfred.
You're damn bloody right I am, yeah.
You're right.
I let my guard down.
It won't happen again.
All right, there we go.
Might leave a little bit of a scar.
Thanks, Alfred.
All right.
Oh, no, wh-where do you
think you're going?
To the docks.
I'm sure there's a manifest
on the freighter.
Whatever's in that crate
must be important
if the thief was willing
to steal it from the Penguin.
I want to know what it is.
Right, so being shot
wasn't enough, was it?
You got to let this slide,
Master B.
There's more to this, Alfred.
I can feel it.
This is my chance
to investigate a real crime,
stop it before it becomes
something bigger.
Fine.
But just don't go charging
around in broad daylight
with that bloody mask on.
It'd be like having
a socking great bull's-eye
on your back, all right?
So how do you suggest
I get onto the ship?
There are other kinds of masks
you can wear,
Master Bruce.
As you can see,
the scatter pattern
is tighter than most. You won't find
a superior weapon anywhere
in Gotham.
I'll take two dozen.
Excellent.
You can pay out front.
Right this way, sir.
Thank you, everyone, for coming.
Tabitha planning on coming to work?
I am paying her half the profits.
Don't you mean a third?
That depends.
Where's my crate?
I ran into some trouble.
- Did Penguin's men see you?
- No.
I wore a mask like you said.
I know you're pissed.
I'm not mad.
I misjudged you.
I was wrong to cut you in
on my new business.
You're clearly not ready.
You're serious?
I can get the damn thing.
I'll do it myself.
But if you do want to redeem yourself,
you can do the floors.
Mop's in the closet.
Oh.
You can mop your own damn floors.
Another excellent night
of business, Victor.
Except for the part
where a couple of thieves
- tried to rob your shipment.
- What?!
Relax, boss.
My men stopped them
before they could get
their hands on anything.
You see what I'm dealing with, Ed?
That shipment is full
of black market items
I am auctioning off tonight
to Gotham's elite.
I stand to make a killing.
I cannot do that without the items.
Where are they?
At the warehouse.
Take me.
I want to be sure it is all
accounted for, and once I do,
bring everything back here
for safekeeping.
Okay.
♪♪
No.
No...!
This cannot be happening!
I don't know.
Kind of opens up the room.
Whoever did this, I want them found.
I want them dead!
And I want Ed back here today!
Where are you, Ed?
♪♪
Oh, he's up!
- He's up, he's up!
- Where am I?
Who is... how did I get here?
I brought you here.
You're in my home.
What do you think?
What?
I'm sorry.
Who... who are you?
You don't remember?
Hilltop Elementary?
Mrs. Macher's class?
I was
third row closest to the window.
Eddie, it's me, Myrtle Jenkins.
Um, I followed your rise
to becoming the Riddler.
I've read every article,
all the police reports.
I guess you could say
I'm your number one fan.
Okay.
Um, I'm... I should get going.
Whoop, that's gonna be tough.
Why am I tied up?
You're not.
Your muscles have atrophied
from being on ice.
Okay? But don't worry.
These warming lamps
should help thaw you out.
Ice?
Yeah.
- The last thing I remember...
- Yeah.
Was being frozen by the river.
How long was I on ice?
Five months.
I know.
Since then, Penguin opened a
club called the Iceberg Lounge.
You were its centerpiece.
That little freak.
He put me on display
like some caged animal.
Yes.
And I will nurse you
back to health
so you can reclaim your throne
as Gotham's greatest villain!
Oop, ah, caveat.
With me as your sidekick, of course.
Doesn't that sound wonderful, my love?
You lost, kid?
My Uncle Al works on your ship.
My aunt hasn't heard from him
in a few days and she's worried.
There are a few men below deck.
I'm pretty damn sure
none of their old ladies
are looking for them.
Listen, I told my aunt I'd find him.
Can I just take a quick look?
I'll be in and out
in a few minutes, I promise.
Sure. Go ahead.
Thank you.
You think you're real smart
giving us the slip.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Ah, save it.
Somebody tried to steal
from this ship last night.
Did this to my face.
Tell me who you are working for.
I assure you,
I'm just here looking for my uncle.
I took a wrong turn.
Sure. Here's a little advice.
If you're gonna play the part
of a street kid,
learn how to talk like one.
Hey, Andy!
Get over here.
What did I tell you about
bothering me at work?
Sorry, fellas.
You're right, though.
The boy's acting does need
some work, doesn't it?
You see, improvisation,
Master Bruce, is a very important weapon
in any actor's tool kit.
Should we go?
There's a knife
being sold at your auction tonight.
I was thinking you might be kind enough
to sell it to me ahead of time.
Hmm.
And why is this knife
so important to you?
It's not.
I have a client who's interested.
Gave me a ton of cash,
so I was hoping to get it
for a lower price and make a profit.
That start with the attempted
five-finger discount last night?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Of course you don't.
I'll triple the opening price.
It'll probably go for less at auction.
My dear,
wherever you disappeared
to these last few months
has not made you a better liar.
It's clear that this
isn't about profit, but about
your mysterious benefactor.
He is your client, is-is he not?
Reveal his identity to me
and you have a deal.
Wow.
He's really got his hooks into you.
See you tonight, I guess.
Don't forget to bring your checkbook.
Always a pleasure, Oswald.
The knife was used
to embalm King Balahsi.
According to this, he ruled
ancient Mesopotamia
for the first century.
And what thief in Gotham
would want a knife like that?
That's a good question.
According to the manifest,
the shipment was full of jewels
and expensive art, yet our thief
went for the item with
the least intrinsic value.
Well, that tells me
she was a gun for hire.
But who hired her?
I think I just found the answer.
Alfred, look. This drawing
depicts a man being healed by water.
Look at his eyes.
His face.
Who does that remind you of?
That's impossible.
I mean, this-this drawing
is 2,000 years old, Master...
I know.
That's him.
That's Ra's al Ghul.
He wants the knife.
I struck out with Falcone.
That right?
Try not to sound too happy
about it.
Look, if you brought back
Falcone,
that would mean gang wars
and blood in the streets.
And I don't like it when
the streets are bloody, Jim.
Yeah. Well, see how
you like it with Penguin.
See you tomorrow, Harvey.
Mind if I join you?
What are you doing here?
I figured you didn't
know anyone in town.
I thought I'd keep you company.
Or maybe I just didn't
want to drink alone.
To my dad.
I am sorry about your father.
We may have had our
differences over the years,
but I always respected him.
Hmm.
When I was a little girl,
if I wanted to spend
time with my father,
he'd have me schedule an appointment.
Save the respect, I know
who my father is.
Took him getting sick for us
to finally have a real relationship.
How long have you lived down here?
Since I was 13.
My father thought sending
me away from Gotham
would keep me safe.
I mean, there are worse
places to grow up.
People are happy here,
you see the sun every day.
But I wasn't alone. I had Mario.
We took care of each other.
I know there's nothing I can say.
I am sorry for what happened to him.
You're right,
there's nothing you can say.
He was infected with the virus.
You did what you had to do.
♪♪ Dance music playing...
There's no sign of Nygma
anywhere in Gotham.
Word on the street is,
it was an inside job.
Find whoever is in charge of hiring.
Kill them.
I want everyone here interrogated.
There's a traitor amongst us.
Those needles should
help stimulate your muscles.
You'll have feeling back in no time.
Just call me the Riddlette.
I know.
What do you think?
I think that rehashing
someone else's idea
isn't very original.
Well, it's an homage,
and I thought you'd like it.
It's very nice.
Ah... this is so much fun.
If only I were the criminal
mastermind you are,
we would have been together sooner.
I'm sorry, I don't really follow that.
Well, it took me months
to plan your escape.
I had to learn Penguin's schedule,
when he came and went,
devise an exit strategy.
I'm sure it would have
taken you two seconds
to think something up.
It is slightly impressive
you were able to outwit Oswald.
Though, as you said, my plan would have
taken much less time.
Oh, wait, that is a great idea.
You should tell me what
your plan would have been,
because a window
into your master villainy
would mean so much to me.
I...
Um...
Oh, here I am bombarding you
with silly questions.
After everything you've been through,
you must be exhausted.
Yes.
Yes, I must be exhausted.
Ooh, soup's ready.
Do you like tomato?
I put little question marks in it,
too.
Last one.
One, two, three.
Anything, my love?
No!
Acupuncture... is therapeutic snake oil.
I've been focused on
repairing the wrong muscle.
What?
Your brain.
It fires synapses that carry neurons
to the rest of your body.
And if we can stimulate it,
perhaps your other muscles will follow.
- Logical.
- Yeah.
- What do you suggest?
- Well...
in anticipation of our partnership,
I have been working on a few
riddles.
Yes. Riddles.
Yeah.
That's exactly what I need.
It's gonna make me feel
like myself again.
- Fire away.
- Okay, here goes.
What's black and white and red all over?
Easy. Zebra, with a gaping hole.
- Next.
- Um,
no, it's actually a newspaper.
That's ridiculous.
There's nothing red
on a newspaper. Next.
- Well, it makes sense if you know...
- Next!
Oh, um...
I have a face and two hands,
but no arms or legs.
- What am I?
- Deformed baby.
Come on. Surely you can
do better than this.
Uh, the answer is a clock. Hands...
Oh, my.
I think something is wrong
with your brain, Ed.
There... is... nothing...
wrong with my brain.
The problem is your riddles.
Bring me a riddle
that is worthy of my name!
Next time I'll know
to pack a swimsuit.
You actually own one?
Yeah, I got a nice two-piece.
He comes with a sense of humor.
Do you ever think about
walking away from it all?
Gotham?
Sometimes.
But I can't.
Why not?
It's in my blood.
My father spent his entire life
fighting for the city.
Never took the easy way out.
Neither can I.
What?
Give 'em to me.
I don't really think they're your size.
Come on.
- That, too?
- Mm-hmm.
- What are you doing?
- Come on.
You can't be serious.
Just a little water, Jim.
I can't remember the last time
I just stood still.
All right, Master Bruce,
let's go over the plan again.
It's simple.
I show up at the auction
and buy the knife.
Should be easy enough;
I am a billionaire.
And a very public one at that.
Turning up at the Penguin's
black market auction's
certainly going to raise
a few eyebrows, isn't it?
You're the one that said
that bidding on it
was the smarter play.
That I did, but I didn't mean
as going as yourself, did I?
What do think the idea was
of going down to the docks,
pretending to be someone else?
I was trying to teach you a lesson.
Now, if you're going to continue
down this vigilante path,
Master Bruce,
you've got to learn how to assume...
other roles.
Play the role
that you were born to play.
That of a privileged, somewhat...
pedantic teenager with deeper pockets
than anybody else in this city.
You mean behave like a spoiled brat.
It goes against everything
that your beautiful parents
tried to ingrain in you.
But yes...
sir.
Bruce Wayne...
billionaire brat.
$250,000!
$250,000 going once,
twice... sold
to Mr. Bruce Wayne.
Ha-ha!
That's what I'm talkin' about.
I love art.
I love it, yeah!
I'm gonna put it in my,
uh, in my bathroom.
Steady on, Master Bruce.
Let's not overplay our hand,
shall we?
I must admit, this is fun.
And try to exercise a modicum
of financial restraint.
Technically, you are the richest man
in the room, but let's not try and buy
absolutely everything, shall we?
True, but if I only bid on the knife
everyone's been trying
to steal from Penguin,
it might draw his suspicion.
If I go on a spending spree,
recklessly throwing my money around,
he won't think twice.
Nice. When'd you think of that?
Improvisation, Alfred.
It's a weapon in any actor's tool kit.
Oh, heads up.
Here we go.
Oswald, my friend!
Bruce Wayne, what a lovely surprise.
You certainly are getting out
quite a lot these days,
aren't you?
The way I see it, everyone else
in this town is having fun.
- Why shouldn't I?
- I agree!
You and your insanely
large bank account
are more than welcome here.
Barbara Kean.
I thought she died.
Unfortunately, nobody
stays dead in this town.
Excuse me.
You do realize, don't you, Master Bruce,
that if you actually win,
Ra's al Ghul will come after the knife.
Let him.
The next item up for auction
is an embalming knife
from the tomb of King
Balahsi of Sumeria.
Opening bid will begin at $50,000.
A hundred...
thousand dollars.
What does she want with it?
I have no idea.
Stay focused.
$100,000 to Ms. Kean.
- Do I hear one...
- One hundred thousand
and one dollar.
Actually, Mr. Wayne, the bidding
amounts are in $50,000...
- $200,000.
- Fine.
We have $200,000.
Two hundred thousand
and one dollar.
Mr. Wayne.
How about you let someone
else have some fun?
Oh! Sure.
No problem. I'm sorry about that.
- $300,000.
- Very well. Three hundred...
$300,000 and one cent.
$500,000.
Now back off, you little brat.
Wow, Ms. Kean.
That's a lot of money.
For someone like you.
$2 million!
Two...
Sold to Mr. Bruce Wayne.
Congratulations, Bruce.
Thank you.
I do love
seeing that woman lose.
But a little piece of friendly advice.
Barbara Kean does not give up easily.
She'll be coming for that knife.
I would just, uh, keep a
close eye on it if I were you.
Well, there's a new wrinkle, isn't it?
What's green and red
and goes round and round?
Someone's obsessed
with the color red.
The answer, obviously,
isn't "newspaper."
You're stalling.
No.
- You don't know the answer.
- Of course I do.
No, you don't, Ed.
- Mm-hmm.
- Your brilliant mind is as damaged
as the rest of your body.
Actually,
my body is feeling fine.
Frog in a blender.
Selina?
Why are you sitting
in the dark by yourself?
I was expecting someone else.
- Like who?
- Doesn't matter.
What are you doing here?
Heard about Penguin's auction.
So Barbara sent you for the knife.
Figured, what, because we're
friends, I'd just hand it over?
Something like that.
- Why is it so important to her?
- How should I know?
She was supposed to get it
for some client.
Said he was a pretty dangerous guy.
And that if you were smart,
you'd hand it over
and save yourself the trouble.
So you're here to protect me,
is that it?
The knife can't possibly mean
that much to you, Bruce.
I don't know.
Like you said, I spent $2 million on it,
I think I'll keep it.
Why are you acting like this?
Me? What about you?
Are you really Barbara Kean's
errand girl now?
I'm her partner.
But if I don't give her this knife back,
she won't ever see me as an equal.
So I'm asking you to do me a solid.
I'm sorry, Selina.
You should go.
Morning, Harv.
Jim, hey.
This is Detective Harper.
She just transferred over from the 3-5.
- Jim Gordon.
- Nice to meet you, Detective.
- Heard a lot of good things.
- From who?
It's good to have you
in the fold, Harper.
Thanks.
Gordon.
You got a visitor.
Hot damn.
Fox in the henhouse.
No offense, Harper.
None taken.
But you got the wrong idiom, Captain.
No, I don't.
Be right back.
Sofia.
What are you doing here?
I came to help you.
Oh, yeah? How's that?
Penguin.
Oh, I know you didn't directly ask me,
but
I find men tend to have trouble
seeing the simple solution even
when it's presented to them.
You shouldn't have come back here.
Oh, Jim.
I don't need your permission.
Or my father's.
I'm a Falcone.
This city is my birthright.
My father might not think
I'm ready, but I am.
Is that so?
What do you think
I've been doing down south
the past ten years?
You knew you were coming back
from the moment
I left your father's house.
Everything that's happened was what?
You sizing me up?
No.
Not everything.
But I had to get to know you
if we're gonna work together.
We're not.
Don't be sore, Jim.
You came looking for a gangster,
that's exactly what you found.
We can do great things
together, you and I.
I'll be in touch.
You?
You were the one
who stole from me?
Some good it did.
The ice broke his brain.
What are you talking about?
What's green and red
and goes round and round?
Frog in a blender.
Exactly.
Ed couldn't even get that.
Hmm.
It does seem unlike Ed to keep this
rube alive.
Sound the word: I want him found.
And her?
A lot of people have been
trying to steal from me lately.
An example needs to be made.
Have fun, Victor.
Love your dress.
Thank you.
I made it.
Hmm.
Excellent technique, Barbara.
I'm impressed.
I had a good teacher.
I wish you'd have called ahead.
Does that mean you don't have the knife?
No, Bruce Wayne has it.
Bruce.
Really?
How interesting.
You're not angry?
No, not at all.
You see, Barbara,
when I bathed you in the Lazarus Pit,
I did it in the knowledge
that you would become
a competent ally of mine.
And so far,
you've done an admirable job.
I'm glad you feel that way.
And I wouldn't worry about that knife.
Didn't seem all that special to me.
Oh, but you couldn't be more wrong.
You see,
that knife... is the key
to everything.
Well, not everything.
♪♪
Sync corrections  by  srjanapala