Previously on Gotham...
CREEL: Our brothers
are crossing the ocean
even now.
Gotham will be redeemed
in blood.
By killing nine random people?
You're insane.
And not all the victims
are random.
The Son of Gotham.
I'm going to make sure
that you are telling the truth.
Touch me and my uncle
will have you gutted.
Are we good?!
Yes.
Bruce.
I never bought your stupid act.
You pretended to be my friend.
Good-bye, Silver.
(grunts)
Kill him.
(gunshots)
Where's Galavan?!
What do you want?
Why, your life,
of course.
(machine engines humming)
(grunts)
(door closes)
Hey, guys.
I fixed the hard drive.
(calling out):
Bruce?
Alfred?
(Bruce crying out, panting)
You okay?
Glass of water?
I won't sign those papers,
no matter what you do.
I'm resigned to that.
You're a very brave boy.
I'll just have to acquire
your company by other means.
My true name is Dumas.
And a long time ago,
my family were dishonored
and degraded
by yours.
I'm sorry about that, but...
For centuries our noble clan
lived in vile, squalid
obscurity.
But we lived in hope.
Because our patron saint
spoke of a glorious day
to come.
But that day would only come
when nine men of Gotham
and the last son
of our mortal enemy
are slain by righteous hands.
That's you, Bruce.
You're the last son.
Stop that.
Be glad, boy.
You're the anointed redeemer
of your family.
For seven generations,
the Wayne family
has wallowed in vice
and corruption.
So tonight, at the forewarned
hour of midnight,
the Dumas will be avenged,
and the sins
of the Wayne family
shall wash away in your blood.
♪ ♪
(grunts)
Oh, bloody hell!
NYGMA:
♪ The path is dark ♪
♪ So dark I cannot see ♪
♪ But I will not fear ♪
NYGMA AND OSWALD:
♪ For my mother looks over me. ♪
(both laughing)
What the hell?
At last.
How are you feeling?
(groans)
Not so good.
Nygma?
Hi.
(laughs)
Long story.
He's a friend.
A friend?
You're welcome, by the way.
No thanks needed,
saving your life and all.
Yeah, thanks, I guess.
No, really.
What are friends for?
You got beat pretty bad.
That Galavan is a pistol,
isn't he?
Yeah, he is.
Oh, you're free to go,
of course, Jim.
Desperate fugitive
from the law, though you be.
But I beg of you,
sit and consider.
You and I share a bond
in Theo Galavan.
A passion, if you will.
If there was ever a time
for us to work together,
now is that time.
(footfalls approaching)
Yes, brother,
it's all yours.
For God's sakes,
smile.
Did you find the manservant?
Nope.
(liquid pouring)
You lost him?
What can one old butler do?
That's not the point.
The point is your
lackadaisical attitude.
We're building
an empire here.
Getting nervous, are we?
Your childishness
is no longer funny.
You need to grow up.
Oh, please.
Pull the stick out, big shot.
Like I don't know you
from way back.
Don't.
Without all of this wealth
and power, what are you?
A sad little...
(quietly):
I said don't.
Uncle Theo?
Yes, my dear.
What is it?
I'm fighting off a cold.
I was thinking
I'd go to bed early tonight,
if it's okay to miss out on...
the ceremony?
A cold?
Really?
I'm beginning
to wonder,
Silver, if you're cut out
for the task ahead of us.
I am.
Bruce Wayne bested you,
and yet you still feel for him.
He should be nothing to you.
He is.
He's nothing to me.
But you can't watch him die,
can you?
You're soft, Silver.
You have compassion.
No.
No?
Let's see, shall we?
Hmm.
I'm going to give you a test.
Anything.
Make Bruce Wayne fall
in love with you
all over again.
I want to see him kiss you
before he dies.
But he knows.
He knows what
I am now.
He hates me.
(laughs):
Well, that's what
makes it a test.
If you're guileful enough
to win back his heart
and cruel enough to smile
at his killing,
then I'll know you're worthy
of the family name.
Brother, seriously?
Cut the poor kid some slack.
More from you?
Really?
Isn't there some other way?
Oh, my dear,
I like you very much,
but family interests
come first,
and there are other girls
of the Dumas blood
I could turn to,
should you fail
to prove your mettle.
Understand?
Do you?
My charming brother here
will throw you
out on the street,
if he's kind enough
not to kill you.
Well, let's not dwell
on the negative, hmm?
You can do it.
I know you can.
Be resourceful,
be ruthless.
Why don't you get yourself
something pretty to put on.
(clattering, latch clicks)
(door closes, latch clicks)
(softly):
Hey.
Why are you here?
I wanted to say...
I'm really,
really sorry
for what's happened.
And I'm sorry
that I had to lie to you.
I had to do
what my uncle said.
But I think
you're a good person,
and if I could help you,
I would.
But I can't,
and I'm sorry.
And I thought maybe
you would like some company.
But if you don't, that's fine,
I'll go.
Yes.
Please go.
(sighs softly)
You really hate me?
I have no feelings for you
whatsoever.
Well, I like you.
And I'm sorry.
That's all.
You can stay if you like.
(gasps, groans)
(car horn honking)
Excuse me.
Stop, stop, stop!
Stop, sir! Stop, sir!
Excuse me, sir.
Oh, what, are you crazy
or something?
Stop!
Hey, come on!
Come on, I got to get to work!
I am most terribly sorry, sir.
I'm in the most frightful hurry.
OFFICER:
Freeze!
Oh, Officers...
(electrical crackling)
Captain, what the hell?
You put out a warrant on Jim?
"Armed and
dangerous"?
That's right.
He's not a criminal.
He was obviously
abducted
or-or-or something.
Look, I hope you're right,
but the facts on the ground
don't look that way.
He assaulted the mayor
and escaped
GCPD custody
with Penguin.
Two good cops died
and now he's a fugitive.
What would you call that,
if not criminal?
Well...
Galavan was obviously...
Galavan is innocent
until proven otherwise.
If Jim isn't dirty,
I need to hear that from him.
Where is he?
Do you know where he is?
No.
Do you know how long
he's been working with Penguin?
He's not working with Penguin.
And he's not dirty,
and I resent
being questioned like this.
Oh, stop it.
You're his girlfriend.
You know I have to ask you
these questions.
I'm gonna ask you again
if you know where he is,
because if you do,
and you don't tell me,
that makes you an accomplice
after the fact.
I don't know where he is.
I don't like this
any more than you do.
Jim is like a son to me.
A father would have
shown more faith.
Are you sure you know Jim
as well as
you think you do?
Is your lover-man alive?
Go to Grundy. 805.
(ticking)
SILVER:
Will you please
talk to me?
Silence makes me sad.
Talk about what?
It doesn't matter.
Anything.
Top ten lists...
best vacations.
What's your favorite animal?
Owls.
Owls, okay.
Owls are cool.
Did you ever swim
with a dolphin?
No.
I did, once.
Oh, my gosh.
It was magical.
It was...
like we were friends, like...
They have
this power.
They can, like,
read your mind.
No, they can't.
No, they can.
They can see your brain waves.
They have a form of sonar,
so they can see inside you
and detect tumors,
that sort
of thing.
But they can't read minds.
Well, the one I met
could read my mind.
(boat horn blows)
(guns cocking)
Lee.
What the hell
are you doing?
I need to get you
out of town.
Penguin has a reliable man
who can take you upstate.
Things are gonna be
unsettled here for a while.
Unsettled?
We're gonna take
down Galavan.
Are you out of your mind?
Ms. Thompkins,
I can assure you...
He has to be stopped, Lee.
By you?
And... these people?
He has to be stopped.
You keep trying
to kill yourself.
Have I got you all wrong?
Are you just crazy?
Of course not.
You're on the run from the law.
You want to attack the mayor
with the help
of a depraved sociopath.
That's not crazy?
I can hear you.
Shh! Don't speak.
Jim, don't do this.
Let's get out of town together.
I don't care
what you've done already
or what you have
to leave undone. Let's just go.
I can't.
Jim, please.
I can't. I can't let Galavan
win this way.
I'm pregnant.
(Oswald gasps)
(sighs)
There were
silver-white roses
and red lilies
all over the house.
All of my friends
were there.
There was music
and dancing.
And my mom
made me a cake
with my name
spelled out in chocolate.
That was the year
before she died.
She looked so beautiful.
And happy.
So, yeah...
...that's my favorite memory.
My ninth birthday.
How about you?
I don't know.
Come on.
You must have one.
So your parents
really are dead, are they?
Yeah.
I wasn't lying about that.
I'm sorry.
Hey...
that's show business.
We went camping once,
in a forest.
My father and I
climbed an oak tree
and ate oranges.
We could hear my mom
singing to herself
as she built the fire.
That was a good day.
Damn it...
Damn it. I can't do this.
I can't let you die.
That's good of you to say so,
but is it up to you?
If we can get out of the cell
and past the guard,
I know a back stairwell
that isn't watched.
That's a big if.
What are you going to do?
I am a Dumas.
I have some pull around here.
Open up.
(lock clicks)
Come in.
Give me your gun.
(screams)
(guard groaning)
(panting)
Come on!
(Silver screams)
Oh, you silly girl.
What were you thinking?
(crying quietly)
LUCIUS:
Bruce and Alfred
have been gone
for at least 12 hours.
I'm afraid
they've been abducted.
We're very busy now, Mr. Fox.
12 hours
isn't very long.
I am sure that
something has happened.
We usually don't post
missing persons
until they've been
missing for 24 hours,
but out of respect
for Wayne Enterprises...
(line ringing)
Bruce Wayne, Alfred Pennyworth.
Run them through the system.
Thank you.
Was there any evidence
of an abduction?
There was a lamp stand
knocked over
and there was a window opened.
Uh-huh.
Who do you think abducted them?
Well, Theo Galavan
is the obvious suspect.
Do you have any proof of that?
Uh... threats made,
physical
evidence?
No.
But it's obvious.
He's trying to take
over the company.
Captain, we know
the man's dirty.
Of course we know he's dirty.
We know the names
of every dirty crook in Gotham.
So what?
Proof, Bullock!
Proof!
To get a warrant
against Galavan,
we need proof of a crime
and proof that he's involved.
(phone ringing)
Speak.
Huh.
(sputtering)
Where's Master Bruce?
We were hoping you knew.
I was in the process of
commandeering a vehicle
when two of your...
idiotic cozzers shot me
straight in the bloody
face with a stun gun.
Here I am.
And there's your
warrant, Captain.
Where?
He was assaulted
on Galavan's
property
by known associates
of Galavan.
While trespassing
in Galavan's Tower.
He was lawfully pursued
off the property
by the rightful
occupants.
You got nothing there.
Galavan's got Bruce Wayne, boss,
sure as eggs.
Give me real proof.
We already jumped the gun once
with Galavan
and we got screwed.
Without solid proof,
no judge is gonna sign
a warrant... eggs or no eggs.
So what do you propose we do?
You hang tight.
We'll dig up some...
health and safety issue.
Get a backdoor warrant
for Galavan Tower.
ALFRED:
Right, how long's
that gonna take, then?
BARNES:
Probably till
tomorrow morning.
But...
That's the best
we can do.
Oh, uh...
you're free to go.
We'll drop your charges.
Right, well, you know, thank you
very much indeed.
Look, Bullock,
I'm gonna need some
clean bandages, I'm gonna need
a car...
and a couple of guns.
You got it.
What are you going to do?
I've got no choice. No time.
I've got to go visit him.
I'll come with you.
LUCIUS:
Are two men enough?
It wouldn't seem so, but
violence is not my métier.
No. Two men are not enough.
I would gladly join you, but I
imagine an amateur is no asset.
A hindrance, perhaps.
That's very true.
We need Jim Gordon.
He's perfect
for this kind of thing.
Where is he?
Yeah, where is Jim Gordon?
It's a long story,
but nobody knows.
(chuckles)
Something funny, Ed?
Do you know
where Gordon is?
Do you?
Start speaking,
Windows.
Um, uh... A diamond plate,
a glowing grate, a place
you never leave. Where am I?
What?
Home.
Whose home? Your home?
Gordon's at your home?
N... No. Yes.
Who are you?
Good luck, old friend.
See you around.
I hope not.
Good-bye, Penguin.
Good-bye, Ms. Thompkins.
Please don't think too badly
of me.
We are what we are.
(chuckles)
That's true.
Good-bye,
Mr. Cobblepot.
(siren wailing in distance)
(tires screeching)
GORDON:
Huh.
Let's go.
Yeah.
Wait here.
Galavan has Bruce.
I understand.
Just promise
me...
What?
Never mind.
Do what you think is best.
Call me when it's over.
(crying)
I must look terrible.
No. You don't.
Thank you.
You're so calm.
It's like you're not scared.
I guess I'm not.
It's weird.
You... are weird.
But I love you.
Do you?
I do.
Do you love me?
No.
No?
Silver, I don't know
why you're doing it,
but I know
you're playing with me.
I know that whole escape
was a ghoulish charade.
That's a horrible lie.
I'm only telling you this
because, when I'm dead,
you may feel bad,
and I don't want you to think
you tricked me.
Silver, I don't love you.
I pity you.
(exhales)
Why do you do this?
What's the point?
Uncle Theo made me.
He said if I can't make you
love me again,
if you don't kiss
me good-bye,
then I'm not good
enough for the family.
He's going to kick me out.
Or kill me.
Same thing, really.
I see.
God, I'm such a loser.
An evil, pathetic loser.
You're not.
You're young and scared
and under the control
of bad people.
You can change.
There's hope.
You can't even imagine
the things I've done.
There's no hope.
There's no going back
to normal life.
My family is
all I have.
Now I've lost them, too.
All right.
Everybody set? Let's go.
Whoa, whoa.
What's the plan?
We get into that building,
find Galavan,
put a gun in his mouth
until he gives up Bruce.
Then I kill
him slowly.
No. Then we arrest him.
Yeah, no.
Are you nuts?
After all that he has done?
He's going to stand trial.
Gotham needs to know
who he really is.
Gotham needs him dead!
ALFRED:
Rabbit, rabbit, rabbit.
Can we just stop the bunny and
just first get in there, please,
chaps?
Yes.
Let's go.
LUCIUS: Seriously, that's
it? You have no plan?
How are you even going to get
into the building?
I know a way.
Who is she?
Fox, that's Cat.
Cat,
Fox.
You know a way in?
Yeah.
I know a way in, Gordon.
ALFRED:
How do we know
you haven't stitched us up?
I mean,
you've switched
sides often enough.
How do we know
that you're not
working with Galavan now?
How do I know you're not
a Martian in a rubber suit?
I trust her.
You're in, Cat.
Thanks
for your help.
Grab a vest and let's go.
People,
surely
we should have
a backup
strategy, given
the strong possibilities
of failure.
Au contraire, Mr. Fox.
Failure is not an option!
What he said.
As you like.
Stop acting like
you're not scared.
I know you are.
Sure.
Maybe a little but...
mostly, I feel very alive.
Happy, even.
I'm going to see my parents.
(footfalls approaching)
Hold that thought.
Showtime.
One moment, please.
Good-bye, Silver.
I love you.
And I forgive you.
Hey.
Bravo.
♪ ♪
Come on in.
Oh, for Pete's sake.
MONKS:
Death to the Son of Gotham.
Death to the Son
of Gotham.
Death to the Son of Gotham.
Death to the Son
of Gotham.
Death to the Son of Gotham.
What in the hell is that?
Death to the
Son of Gotham.
Nothing good.
Death to the Son
of Gotham.
I'll be right there.
Death to the Son of Gotham.
Death...
Prepare yourself, boy.
You're a deluded, old fool.
And you'll pay for this.
Ancestors,
be our witness.
The prophecy is fulfilled.
Stop!
Please?
(crash)
Sacrilege.
(shouting)
Listen to me very...
Hold on just a moment.
All right, Mr. Fox,
make it quick, what do you got?
I have the current location
of James Gordon.
I'll call you back.
(grunting)
Drop the knife, old man.
It's over.
So it would seem.
(shouts)
(gunshot)
That was a lot of stairs.
You all right?
Where's Galavan?
Only one way out of here now...
straight down.
There's only
two of them.
Oh.
Yeah.
Silver isn't coming.
I just wanted
to take a moment,
sweetheart,
to express my deep...
disappointment in you.
Theo, leave her be.
Silence!
Bite me.
What...
what are you doing?
I don't know who
you are anymore.
Oh, please, that is such
a ridiculous cliché...
(grunts)
Forget it, brother. You lost.
It's time for me to
look out for number one.
Sorry.
(screams)
Tabitha!
(groans)
GORDON:
Theo Galavan.
You're under arrest.
Oh, God. Uh...
you scared me, man. I thought
you were gonna shoot me.
Oh.
Cuff yourself.
Well, thank goodness for...
simple men of principle.
Who believe in the system.
This time you'll get the chair.
You want to make a bet?
(chuckles)
Whoa.
Maybe you're right.
Steady now, Jim.
I was just talking big,
as they say.
You caught me fair and square.
Had you that way the last time.
You turned it around.
Jim.
Back up.
I got him.
Back up, I said.
And you--
on your knees.
I have a warrant
to search these premises.
Jim,
now, you put your gun on
the ground and put your hands
on top of your head.
What?
You heard me.
You're still a fugitive.
Captain, I've done
nothing wrong.
I want to believe you, Jim.
So we're gonna do this
by the book.
Put your gun on the ground
and let's handle this
the right way.
You're making a mistake.
(gun clatters)
(thump)
(man grunts)
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, nobody shoot--
we are all friends here.
Like hell we are.
I apologize for that.
But there we are.
Done now.
They're still alive.
That's something.
Look forward now, Jim.
What now?
I will kill you
to get to him if I have to.
Forget that this man
sicced Barbara Kean on you.
Forget that he nearly killed
the mother of your child.
Forget revenge.
Think of the greater good.
Think of Gotham.
He has the courts
in his pocket and billions
of dollars
at his command.
Are you 100% sure that
he won't beat this
and walk free again?
Are you sure, Jim?
Think of Gotham.
OFFICER (on radio):
Captain, Bravo Team
in the vicinity
of the penthouse.
But think fast.
I do believe,
Master Bruce,
this falls
very firmly
into the category
of "I told you so".
I told him so, too, Alfred.
Yes, well,
thank you both for your help,
but I had a perfectly
feasible escape plan.
You're a man of conscience, Jim.
You'll regret this.
I have many regrets.
This won't be top of the list.
Now, uh...
here we are.
Shame.
It's gonna be
a beautiful morning.
Good-bye,
Jim Gordon.
This is for my mother.
(grunting)
Kill me, please.
Please.
Enough!
That's enough.
(grunting)
(Penguin laughs)
♪ ♪
(indistinct chatter)
It's over.
Is it?
Yes.
Good.
Will you marry me?
♪ ♪
Here you go, Ms. Peabody.
Fresh meat from
the city morgue.
Show some respect.
Professor Strange has
high hopes for this one.
Huh.
That's unusual.
(panting)
(grunts)
(machinery whirs)
(glass shatters)
(panting)