Previously onGotham...
Word of the chemical spill
reached the mainland.
Reunification isn't happening.
No action until the Government
can determine if Gotham is safe.
I sentence you, Victor Zsasz,
to die.
Get him out of there.
What the hell are you doing?
Trying to keep you all
from making a terrible mistake.
- Her name is Ivy.
- She's a witch.
I'm feeding the earth
with these wretched creatures.
It consumes them,
and then it flourishes.
We wouldn't have escaped without you.
You saved me and my friends.
I wanted to help.
Come with us.
Are you telling me you found a way
out of Gotham?
It's a submarine.
I've been giving you space,
but we have to talk about
how this is gonna work.
I'm gonna be a part
of this kid's life.
Oh, you seem pretty confident
about that.
- I am.
- You're having a baby with Barbara.
Can't change the past so,
I guess we just have to live with it.
Come on, people, time's a-wasting.
The filtration system
that Lucius designed is working.
What you're doing is both
unnecessary, and it's reckless.
Our supplies of drinking water
are at critical levels.
Every day the gangs
get more aggressive.
If I can get a cease-fire,
even a temporary one,
then when reunification does happen,
at least there will be people
left to save.
They deserve that much.
And does your child deserve a father?
You have no problem taking care
of the entire city.
What about focusing on just one life?
Why are you always so ready
to put yourself in the cross-hairs?
It's like you won't be satisfied
until you sacrifice yourself.
- You really believe that?
- I do.
And it scares me.
How is this gonna work?
Am I supposed to stay at home
and raise this child with Barbara
while you go cowboying off
all the time?
It won't always be like this.
- After reunification...
- Nothing will be different.
- Unless you stop being...
- Me?
Hey, Jim.
I have to go. We'll talk after.
If there is an after.
Oswald, where the hell is Nygma?
Shouldn't we have left the city
already?
Miss Kean,
this may come as a surprise,
but building a submarine
from scratch by yourself takes time.
- Patience.
- Easy for you to say.
You're not a walking egg timer.
Tell him to get a move on.
And why exactly are you hosting
Gordon's gangland get-together?
Keep your friends close
and your enemies closer, my dear.
If we're really going to leave
Gotham, we need to keep Gordon happy.
You know all about that, don't ya?
It was a momentary slip.
The world was on fire.
Jim, it's your show.
Mi casa, su casa.
I'll make this short.
Gotham is running dry.
Our supply of clean water
will only last a few more months.
So you have a choice.
You can keep killing each other,
fighting over
what little water's left.
Maybe eke out a few more months,
then die.
Or...
we can all agree, right now,
to an immediate cease-fire.
Government will not annex a war zone.
If we can show them that we deserve
to rejoin the mainland,
supply chain will be restored
and we will all survive
until reunification.
That's the choice.
Life or death.
Your call.
This is, no way.
Do we?
Yeah?
- All right.
Weapons down! Get back!
Jim. You see where the shooter was?
Jim?
Oh, my God.
Get back!
You're gonna be all right.
It's bad. We gotta move him. Now.
Clinic's too far.
M.E.'s office.
Alvarez, come on, help.
On it.
On my count. One, two...
All right, get back.
Did not see that coming.
What made you choose this of all
places for a scavenging mission?
Just trust me, okay?
What the hell?
Sit.
Wow.
Candles.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say this was a date.
Maybe it is.
That okay with you?
Maybe.
Good.
So, let's eat.
Lee!
It's Jim, he's lost a lot of blood.
Can you save him?
Come with me.
Doc says he's gonna be okay.
He's gonna pull through.
But until then, I'm acting Captain!
Now the gangs in this city
think this is their time,
that they can run wild!
They are dead wrong!
I want us to take to the streets.
It is show of force time!
We ain't gonna give 'em an inch.
Harper, I want you to organize
patrol teams.
What're you gonna do?
I'm gonna find out
who shot my partner.
The bullet shattered against a rib.
I have to get all the fragments out.
I haven't done general surgery
since med school.
There.
All right, there's an exit wound
so the rest must've gone through.
I need to sew him up.
Can you get me my kit?
Right away.
Come on, Jim.
You can do this. You have to fight.
You hear me?
You have to fight.
Order in the court.
James Gordon,
you have been brought here
to be judged for your many crimes,
and your very life hangs
in the balance.
- Do you understand?
- No, I...
The defendant understands
and waives his right to appeal.
The trial of James Gordon
will now begin.
No! Wait!
That was the best-canned meal
I've ever had.
And if this was a date,
I don't know how you're gonna top it
when everything gets back to normal.
I don't think things
are ever gonna be normal.
For me anyways.
What do you mean?
Wayne Manor's gone.
And I know that lot of people
lost a lot more,
but part of me wonders
if it wasn't fate.
It wasn't. It was Jeremiah
blowing up your house.
Maybe it's time to move on.
You mean like, leave Gotham?
Bruce, forget Wayne Manor.
This city is your home.
And how many terrible things
have happened to it because of me?
Galavan.
Ra's al Ghul.
If this city really is my home,
then maybe the best thing
I can do for it is leave.
I have to say...
kind of agree with you
on that one,
billionaire boy.
Jim Gordon's blood on my floor.
Olga!
Why is the help never around
when you need them?
This could be good for us.
You especially.
Are you serious?
Your baby daddy
is the top cop in Gotham.
A dead Jim Gordon is the only way
you can hold on
to your little bundle of joy.
Harvey, how is our dear...
Who the hell did it?
If I find out it was you,
- I swear to God...
- It wasn't me!
I merely supplied the venue!
At your boss's request!
- That doesn't mean squat!
- Fine.
You want to know who's to blame?
James Gordon!
He invited every criminal in Gotham.
What did he think
was going to happen?
How about you? Huh?
When did you two become
so buddy-buddy?
Maybe when you hatched up a plan
so you can keep that baby
for yourself.
Harvey, whatever you think of me,
I did not plot
to kill my child's father.
Well, someone here did!
Someone in this room shot Jim Gordon
and I'm not leaving
till I find out who it was!
Wrong!
The shooter was not here.
Look at the window, stupid!
The shot came from outside!
If the shooter was there
and the trajectory was here,
Jim was...
then the bullet...
I'm gonna find out who this was
and when I do there's gonna be
hell to pay.
Harvey...
is there anything I can do?
Yeah, you can keep the gangs
from tearing the city apart.
What do you want?
You, I will deal with later.
I'm here...
for you.
I need you to come with me.
Why would I do that?
Because you love me so much.
Well, not yet, but you will.
- Don't mess with him, Ivy.
- Protecting your boyfriend?
That's cute.
But I thought that might happen,
so I brought a friend.
I stumbled across this charming man
on the way over here.
And apparently
you two know each other.
Leave her out of this!
You know, I heard you talking about
the future of Gotham.
But Gotham will be what I decide.
A green world.
Won't that be beautiful?
Gorgeous.
Bruce and I have to go.
You always did think
you were better than me.
But without my plants,
you never would've left your bed.
I made you strong again.
Think about that while my friend
is cutting out your heart.
There are so many things
I wish I could say to you.
So many things I wish we could do.
This can't be the end.
Come on, Jim.
Talk to me.
Say something.
Speak.
No.
This isn't right!
I shouldn't be here!
- You have to listen to me.
- Silence. Silence.
The prosecution will now give
its opening remarks.
Your honor, Jim Gordon's crimes
are a matter of public record.
He's failed Gotham at every turn.
He failed to clean up the city...
failed to stop the bridges
from being destroyed,
failed to protect those poor,
innocent souls
in the refuge he himself created,
Haven.
I tried.
- I did the best...
- Silence!
One more outburst
and you will be held in contempt.
I'm hurt.
I need help, please.
Continue.
The issue here
is not how many people have died
because of Jim Gordon.
But how many more must die in order
to satisfy his need to be a hero.
Therefore we pose one simple
question.
Are the people in Jim Gordon's life
better off with him alive or dead?
I think I'm dying.
Prosecution would like to call
its first witness, your honor.
Doctor Lee Thompkins.
Come on, Jim. Hold on.
- How is he?
- Touch and go.
He's stable for now.
I removed all the bullet fragments.
But something keeps pulling him down.
Where are the fragments?
What is it?
VZ?
Victor Zsasz.
Okey-dokey.
Time to boogie.
Hey, I'm only here for Gordon.
So all of you stay down.
I see anyone, and, you know...
- bang.
- Oi, oi!
Now, I heard you were looking
for Jim Gordon.
Listen, I know we have history,
let's just let bygones be bygones.
Yeah, right.
- You did this to my face.
- Whatever.
It's not like you were much
of a looker before anyway.
Ivy says you hurt her feelings.
Why would you do that?
She's so sweet.
Ivy didn't make me strong.
I made me strong.
Tell me where she took Bruce.
The only reason
I'm not ending you right now
is the thought
of the look on your face
when Jim Gordon walks
through that door.
Because he's alive,
you son of a bitch!
What did you eat?
You smell like a butcher.
You know I'm vegan now.
Why kill Jim now?
Makes no sense.
He saved your miserable ass.
He prevented Penguin
from executing you.
If anyone, you should be going
after Cobblepot.
Yeah. That's a good point.
Maybe I'll do him next.
It's kinda not up to me.
You're working for someone?
Sorry.
I want a name!
What's in a name?
A rose by any other name
would smell as sweet.
You know, I'm really taking the time
to stop and smell the roses
these days.
Like actual roses.
They're great.
- Are you high?
- On love.
But, like I said...
my lips are sealed.
Ivy Pepper.
You said it, not me.
I'm technically not allowed to
say it. Her name.
Which is such a bummer because it's
the most beautiful name in the world.
- You watch him.
- I could say it all day.
Yeah, I will say it all day.
Ivy, Ivy Pepper.
This is Ivy Pepper's ass.
Oh, it sounds good.
Here you are, Ms. Thompkins,
carefully. It'll be hot.
Forgive me, but I heard
on the grapevine
that you and Captain Gordon had a
rather heated exchange this morning.
Oh, God.
Was it that bad?
Apparently, it was like a session
of the Italian parliament.
You have misgivings about the arrival
of this child, don't you?
What am I getting myself into,
Alfred?
How am I supposed to raise a child
alongside a psychopath
like Barbara Kean?
I mean, how the hell
is this gonna work?
But that's not all of it.
If Jim and I are gonna do this,
then we have to do it together.
You know how he is.
I don't know what's going on inside
that man's head sometimes.
I think you'll find that he needs you
a lot more than he's letting on.
Well, I need to hear it from him.
I never thought that this was
how my life was gonna be.
I had no interest in being a father
myself.
I always presumed
that I was unfit to be one.
But then I found myself
one night, staring down an alley
at this little boy,
quite literally shaking with fear.
I don't know, it's funny
then what throws at you.
I'm keenly aware that I am not
Master Bruce's flesh and blood.
But it's the moments.
The little things like,
like when he uses a skill
that I once taught him
or we laugh at a joke
that only he and I share.
Those have been some of the most
ecstatic moments of my life.
Nothing can possibly prepare you
for that joy.
The how's and the what's,
you'll figure that stuff out.
What matters is this,
you'll be an exquisite mother.
And that child, he or she,
will be extraordinary...
because of you.
Thank you, Alfred.
Jim. can you hear me?
I'm right here. Right next to you.
Can you feel me?
Lee.
Doctor Lee Thompkins.
You've suffered at this man's hands,
more than anyone.
Broken heart.
Broken engagement.
A lost child.
And yet you're still with him.
I love him.
For all the pain he's caused you.
Would your life have be better,
could it not still be better,
without Jim Gordon?
- Answer the question.
- Lee...
I'll ask you in a different way.
Would you, Doctor Lee Thompkins,
be better off
if Jim Gordon were dead?
I'm sorry.
Everything he touches dies.
The prosecution rests, your honor.
You made her say that.
I didn't make her say anything.
Ask them.
Who are they?
More people who trusted you.
Who believed you when you said
you would protect them.
They're from Haven.
I think I'm dying.
And isn't it about time.
The verdict's in.
You're guilty.
Hey, Jeff. Listen to me.
One day you're gonna meet someone
who's gonna totally change your life,
and it's gonna make you happy.
And you deserve it.
Or not.
Is she here? She's here, isn't she?
Sweetie...
all I asked of you
was to kill Jim Gordon.
You're not angry, are you?
Cause I'll do it.
I'll do it right now.
I'll do it.
You keep the cops busy.
Luckily, the other part of my plan
is coming together nicely.
Lucius!
Bruce, I had no idea
you were stopping by.
I wanted to check on your progress.
Well, the toxicity levels
in this river continue to drop.
At this point, we'll be under the
threshold mandated by the government
sooner than expected.
It's not glamorous work,
but we are helping to save the lives
of thousands of people.
People...
I'm sorry, did you just say,
"People, ugh"?
Lucius, what if I were to tell you
I have in my possession
the most intoxicating perfume
you'll ever smell?
I would tell you
that is an abrupt change of topic.
Can we go back to the part
where you said, "People, ugh"?
Oh, my goodness.
Lucius, Ivy sent me here
to get you to shut down the plant.
Can you do that for her?
For Ivy?
Anything.
She is so great.
Raise your glasses.
I called you all here because
Jim Gordon is at death's door.
For years, he has hounded us,
beaten us, shot us.
And today he got his due.
To Jim Gordon, may he rot in hell.
What exactly are you doing?
I'm trying to keep this city
from ripping itself apart.
So this has nothing to do
with your feelings for Jim?
What if Ed fails?
And we're stuck here?
This will put us in Gordon's
good graces.
Consider it a backup plan.
Listen up.
Now to the real reason
I brought you all here.
I want you to agree
to an immediate truce.
Get out of here.
And what if, instead,
we shoot you and take your club?
I don't think so.
See, those drinks I just gave you?
They're poisoned.
And you had two shots
before everyone got here.
So that should be taking
effect around...
Now!
The rest of you have
forty-eight hours
before you'll need the antidote.
Which I will deliver to you, provided
you go back to your territories,
play nice, and send me all your guns.
Deal?
I said deal?
Now get out of here.
All right.
Jim would be so pleased.
Keep your friends close
and your enemies closer.
Isn't it right? Pengie?
Once I reverse the system,
all the toxin we've pulled
from the river will be re-released,
and the overload
should destroy the filters.
In a matter of minutes the
entire facility will be inoperable.
Perfect.
Ivy's gonna be so happy.
You think so?
Security breach.
Zone one.
That's odd.
Selina.
I'll take care of it.
Okay.
All right, listen up!
I know you're probably familiar
with Ivy Pepper,
in fact, you were probably here
when she hypnotized
the whole freaking precinct.
Okay? She is on the loose
and we've gotta find her
and take her down.
Actually, fellas, she's already here.
That's right. Ivy came to free me.
That is true love for you.
She really understands
what makes me tick.
Don't worry, though.
I'm just a distraction so she can
finish off Jim once and for all.
You know, that's how
great couples work.
Maybe I shouldn't have told you that.
Oh, well.
- I'm sorry, Miss Thompkins.
- I know. Go.
Thank you, Alfred.
Come on, Jim. Can you hear me?
Stay with me.
Stay with me, Jim.
Jim.
Want a drink?
Alvarez makes a hell of a Mai Tai.
I can barely feel my face.
Harvey? What is this?
It's your wake.
Pretty nice turnout, huh?
For he's a jolly good fellow
Which nobody can deny
Wake?
I'm not dead yet.
Well, be a little bit of a bummer
to have it after you died.
Don't you think?
I'm gonna have a kid, Harvey.
How do I protect that child
when everything around me dies?
Harvey?
That's a good question.
Will.
You said I'd be safe in Haven.
I trusted you.
I know. I did my best.
Your best never seems good enough.
It's time to go.
No, no, no. Jim.
Where's my adrenaline?
Oh, looks like Victor succeeded
after all.
I guess I'll have to settle
for killing you.
I can tell you one thing, I am sick
and tired of getting shot
at in my own precinct.
Bullock, what the bloody hell
is going on?
I thought you had this lunatic
locked up?
Ivy broke him out
and gave him arsenal.
But I have an idea. I gotta get
to the storeroom. Give me cover.
Alvarez, go.
Why are you doing this?
What has Jim ever done to you?
Gotham has a chance to be born anew.
To return to what it was
before people ripped down the trees
and paved over the earth.
He's trying to re-unify with the
mainland to save all these people.
A return to filth.
Pollution.
He's fighting for death.
While I promise life.
In its purest form.
Is that your plan to have the plants
take over Gotham? By killing Jim?
Oh, killing Gordon's
just the first part.
Bruce Wayne is taking care
of the rest.
For what it's worth, I am sorry.
For what?
This pain is nothing compared
to what you are about to feel.
- Say goodbye to Jim Gordon for me.
- No!
No, no, no.
No!
Jim.
Selina, you're wasting your time.
Bruce. You have to snap out
of Ivy's spell. This is not you.
You're wrong.
Ivy's given me a purpose.
Stop! Stop, I don't wanna fight you!
What're you gonna do?
Kill everything in Gotham?
The toxins will only kill
all the people.
The plants will adapt.
They always do.
- Can you hear what that sounds like?
- Yeah. It sounds great!
I guess I shouldn't be surprised.
You don't care about Gotham.
You were gonna leave anyway.
What about the rest of us, huh?
The ones who're gonna be stuck here
without you!
Selina.
Selina. I'm okay.
- Bruce, I'm so sorry.
- We need to stop Lucius. Come on.
Okay.
Lucius!
You have to stop the shutdown.
Oh no. I can't do that.
Ivy would be so mad.
Listen to me, I used Ivy's perfume
to hypnotize you.
She's using you.
No.
Ivy would never do that.
We're perfectly bonded.
Like carbon and oxygen,
or hydrogen and oxygen.
- We do not have time for this.
- I'm sorry.
- There.
- Oh, you kicked me in the head.
I didn't have a choice, Lucius.
Bruce, where's Ivy?
She was headed to the GCPD.
I wonder what Ivy's doing right now.
Hey, lover boy!
- Are you serious right now?
- As a heart attack.
What an idiot.
Oh, my...
Oh, that felt good.
Come on, Jim! You fight
for everyone else. You never give up.
Fight for yourself, Jim! Come on!
It's time.
Jim.
Lee?
Is that...
Yes.
Do you wanna...
I don't know.
I don't know that I can.
Oh, I see.
- No!
- Goodbye, Jim.
No! I want to live!
- I want to live!
- It's too late.
No, Will, no!
- Lee.
- Don't move.
Don't move.
How you feel?
Like I almost died.
But you didn't.
- You fought. You came back to me.
- Because I need you.
- Lee, this child...
- It's okay.
It's okay to be scared.
Only thing scarier than doing this
is doing it without you.
Can I ask you something?
- Cheers.
He seems nervous.
I know.
He should be thrilled.
Marrying a woman who's smarter
and better looking than him.
Selina, while we were fighting,
when I was hypnotized,
you talked about me leaving Gotham...
Quiet.
Here she comes.
You may sit.
I'm just gonna say, this isn't gonna
be some long, drawn-out
tearful affair like you
all are used to. Okay?
Yeah, this is gonna be
a short wedding.
I'm gonna try and make it quick
so we can all get to the bar.
Okay?
I first met a young Jim Gordon
when he was a,
pain-in-the-ass
moralistic rookie detective.
In the years since,
he's evolved into a
pain-in-the-ass moralistic Captain.
I'd say he's my best friend,
but in truth, he's my only friend...
so we'll skip that.
Onto Lee.
Lee's always had his back.
Except for that time
when she was infected
with the crazy-making virus,
and she tried to kill him.
But that's love.
But I will say,
if there's one beautiful thing
that's happened
over these last few crazy years,
it's that these two people
met each other.
And that truly is a beautiful thing.
Jim, will you please take Lee's hand?
Do you, Jim Gordon,
take Lee Thompkins to be
your lawfully wedded wife,
to have and to hold,
from this day forward,
for better, for worse,
for richer, for poorer,
in sickness and in health,
to love and cherish
till death do you part?
I do.
And you, Lee Thompkins?
Do you do the same?
Sure, Harvey.
I do.
By the power vested in me
by absolutely no one...
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
What?
And now Jim Gordon
and Lee Thompkins are man and wife.
Thank God, you held the city together
so that this blessed event
could take place.
It was never gonna work.
- What?
- Controlling the gangs
was not a backup plan.
You saw a chance to convince
James Gordon that you had changed.
But he will never see you as anything
but a dangerous woman
keeping his child from him.
Then I'd best be long gone
before he can do anything about it.
He will hunt you
to the ends of the earth.
Let him.