Your chances of survival
are astronomically low, James.
Continuing to run is ill-advised.
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com
Hope you're well rested, Edward.
We have a lot of work ahead of us.
Edward?
Edward, what is it?
Is someone down there, boy?
♪ Cash and jewels aplenty ♪
♪ Sparkle in the sky ♪
♪ Five and ten and 20 ♪
♪ Time to say bye-bye ♪
Ooh, pretty, pretty.
I'll call you Charlotte.
Ooh, you're a handsome devil.
What's your name?
Oswald Cobblepot.
But I'm guessing you already knew that.
Stop!
Penguin. Didn't think
you'd miss a couple things.
Couple things go missing all the time.
How did you know about this place?
All of the thieves I used are dead.
Yep, yep.
Was on a job.
Someone got there first.
Followed them back here.
Saw you. Bang, bang.
Then you know what is in store.
I do hope whatever you came
here for was worth your life.
The Russifer Diamond.
Not Russifer. Charlotte.
What's in your other hand?
Wait, how did you...
Bye-bye.
Who the hell was that?
Oh, God...
Oh!
Oh, God. It happened again, didn't it?
What did I do?
You tried to kill me.
Oh. Is that all?
I need answers, Ed.
I know Walker gave the orders
to destroy Haven
and the supply helicopter.
What is she planning next?
I don't know.
Jim, I don't remember anything
once I go under.
You're bleeding.
You have to let me go.
I'm not responsible for this.
That chip in your head
could be evidence.
So unless you want me to rip it out,
- you're coming with me.
- Okay.
Bruce.
There you are.
So, go on, then.
How'd it go with Selina?
Oh, dear.
Well, I am sorry, Master Bruce,
but perhaps it's for the best.
Maybe. That's not why I called
you here. You see this?
Yeah, I know, right?
Looks like Captain Gordon's
finally getting the help
this city so desperately needs.
Is he?
What the people desperately
need is food and medicine.
Not just more guns.
What is it?
No, it's just this unit.
Their motto is "Born of Blood."
You know them?
Yeah, by reputation only.
They're a horrible bunch of bastards.
They specialize in military
coups, assassinations.
They're certainly not the vanguard
for humanitarian relief.
Excuse me.
When's the supply
shipment gonna be here?
Supplies?
These people are desperate for food,
clean water, medicine.
Oh, yeah. It's on its way.
Where's Captain Gordon?
We lost sight of Gordon.
But don't worry. Eduardo's out
there looking for him right now.
Unless you know where we might find him?
Logically, he'd come here.
Unless there's some reason he can't.
Tell you what, kiddo.
I'm gonna find you and your
friend a quiet place in the back
where you can wait for Gordon.
Ah, don't you worry about it, mate.
We'll just catch up with him later.
I insist.
We need to find Jim.
So the government is behind
Haven and the supply helicopter,
and they did it with a chip
in this one's head?
Is that really the craziest thing
you've ever heard, Barbara?
Bruce hit me up on the radio
a little while ago, looking for you.
Said things are amiss in the GCPD.
I'll reach out, see if we
can meet up somewhere safe.
Can you pull in some of your
people, see if they can help?
No. I need them guarding my territory.
- But you have me.
- And me.
I don't trust you.
With or without that chip in your head.
Jim.
They used me as a pawn
to murder innocent people.
They messed with my brain.
The thing that I want is revenge.
How do I know that chip
can't be reactivated?
Well, when you found
me at Strange's lab,
he was fixing it after a...
car battery mishap...
I-It's safe to say
that I think you shorted it out.
Let me look at that.
- What?
- Your neck.
That's gonna need stitches.
I have a first aid kit.
I need to keep moving.
Just name your fee.
Can't I just want to help?
Not you, not usually.
Friend of mine just tried to kill me.
I don't want anyone else
waiting for an excuse
- to stab me in the back.
- I gave you Gerry the Jerkwad,
and I'm letting you hide out in my club.
If I wanted to betray you,
I would have done it earlier.
So, where's that first aid kit?
Gonna make myself useful.
What's it gonna take
for you to trust me?
After everything you've done,
I honestly don't know.
I'd listen to her, Jim.
I hear trust is in short supply.
You forget your PSYOPS training, Jim?
Lesson one: when a person is in trouble,
they go to a familiar place.
Your ex-fiancée's bar was
just a stone's throw away,
so it's nice to finally
meet you, Barbara.
Screw you.
Hmm.
It seems you've lost your tail.
You mean the psychopath
you ordered to kill me?
You had your chance.
It could have been
like old times, buddy.
You, me, together,
making the world a better place.
- By murdering civilians?
- Civilians?
This hellhole is infested
with criminals and terrorists.
Sometimes you just have
to clean house, you know?
I won't let you.
It's not your call, Jim.
I'm not dead yet.
James Gordon,
I've been ordered to kill you.
Well, looks like you haven't
lost that tail after all.
If I die,
you'll never get the evidence!
Stand down.
I have evidence that you
and Walker are behind Haven.
If I die, it gets out
to the entire country.
It's time to make a deal.
You don't have any evidence.
Is that a risk you're willing to take?
It is.
Nygma, kill them both.
Bad time?
What do you want?
Depends.
What did they want?
Oh. A shot at me.
I killed Jeremiah Valeska.
So the rumors are true.
Yeah.
And now, every scumbag in town
wants to take me down
to make a name for themselves.
So I got to find a new squat.
How about, in exchange
for helping me find someone,
I let you crash in my citadel?
It's seen better days, but...
- ...then again, right?
- Who?
A miscreant I caught in the act
of stealing from me.
She was going to replace the stolen item
with an exact replica,
except the replica was a bomb.
Ring any bells?
White hair, feathered collar,
kind of of resembles a goth chicken?
You do know her.
She goes by the name Magpie.
What'd she steal?
The Russifer Diamond.
What makes you think I would help you
after you killed Tabitha in cold blood?
Because you believe
in an eye for an eye.
Hard as it may be to swallow,
Tabitha made her bed
when she killed my mother.
Tell you what.
I will help you
if I get to keep the diamond.
What?
Not a chance.
Ha, ha, ha. Then you'll never find her.
And every person in Gotham
will think it's okay
to steal from Penguin.
Is that what you want?
You know me too well.
Fine.
Good.
- What happened?
- I want every soldier
in the field looking for Jim Gordon.
Sir, we maxed out the holding cells.
We may need to keep men here
to control the overflow.
Ethan, Sumiko.
We're moving to phase two.
What in the hell's going on?
Listen up.
I am not here to play nice.
I am not here to hold anyone's hand.
I am here on a simple mission.
Any questions about the nature
of that mission?
Are you insane?
You can't just execute people.
Do not question me.
This is the mission.
If you don't like it,
you'll be locked up,
you'll remain locked up,
until we purge the criminal element
from the streets of Gotham.
Sir, Secretary Walker's on the radio.
We've moved on to phase two,
but we've lost track
of Gordon and Nygma.
I think Gordon found a way
to fry the chip.
We can't have Nygma
in the wind with all that
evidence in his head.
Just trust me. Once we find them...
Don't bother.
I have an idea that will bring
Jim Gordon and Nygma to us.
Thanks for getting everyone here.
And for the Wayne R and D.
Are you sure about including
Barbara Kean and Ed Nygma?
War makes for strange bedfellows.
It's good to have
a friend nearby, Bruce.
Ow! Would you be careful?
If you'll stop moving,
this will go a lot faster.
Well, if you would be more
careful, I wouldn't potato
all the long legs from the hidden spoon.
What just happened?
I believe the chip is installed
against his speech center.
Huh. Do it again.
The human brain is not
a plaything, Ms. Kean.
Please don't habituate the curtain rod.
And... ah.
Stay.
There. How does that feel?
Peter Piper picked
a peck of pickled peppers.
Oh, God. Thank you, Lucius.
So what exactly are we looking for?
Anything tying Walker or Eduardo
to the destruction of Haven.
Why would Walker kill all those people?
That's what we have to find out.
Oh, yes.
It appears the chip retains an audio log
of every verbal communication
with Nygma while he was under.
There's some damage, but...
if the command to attack
Haven is still here,
I can trace it back to the computer
from which it originated.
It has to be Walker.
They won't be able to sweep
this under the rug anymore.
Are you out there, Jim?
What do you want?
We have someone here...
...who wants to say hello.
J-Jim? What's happening?
Lee?
We found the Queen of the Narrows
in a run-down hidey-hole
on the north side. Tell me,
how many ex-fiancées
do you have, anyway?
Leave her out of this.
She's not involved.
Ah, but she's a criminal,
and all criminals in Gotham
are now under a death sentence.
But what happens next is up to you.
A trade, perhaps.
Lee Thompkins for Ed Nygma.
Fine.
Good. Bring Nygma to the GCPD now.
No, we meet at Haven.
I want you to see
the carnage you've caused.
Always so emotional.
That's not how wars are won, Jim.
Those are my terms. Take it or leave it.
Okay. I'll play your game.
What are you doing?
He's never gonna
let you walk out of there.
I don't recall volunteering
as a trading chit!
He doesn't want Ed. He wants the chip.
So I'll give him the chip.
Bruce, do you have any contacts
in the mainland press?
Several.
What would it take to broadcast
the information from the chip
- to the mainland?
- A transmitter, which I have,
and a very large antenna,
which I do not.
I know where there's an antenna
in the Green Zone,
but you're not gonna like it.
The roof of the GCPD.
Lee.
- Harvey.
- Where the hell have you been?
You've been gone for months.
I don't know.
I can't remember anything.
What happened to me?
I don't know. We're gonna figure it out.
I promise.
Let's go.
It's gonna be okay.
Eduardo just arrived.
He brought backup, like we expected.
- Time to move.
- Copy that.
Let's go.
Jim! Who are these people?
I'm gonna get you out of here, Lee.
I'm not sure that's true, Jim.
It seems you forgot to bring someone.
It's hard to make a swap
when you have nothing to trade.
We both know this
is really what you want.
Proof that you and Walker
are responsible
for the destruction of Haven
and the murder of hundreds
of innocent people.
Now let her go.
Let me guess, you made a copy
so you can do this little bit
of theatrics for me.
I expected more from you, Jim.
Three soldiers against one man
without a gun.
You sure you brought enough help?
I don't need any help.
Is that why you sent Nygma
to do your dirty work?
So he could pick up your slack
like I used to?
Still dining out on pulling me
from that burning truck.
I carried more than my fair share.
I was always the first man in.
Your recklessness got people killed.
I don't know what the hell
you're talking about.
Ramirez?
No.
Johnson.
Bolton.
Their deaths were not on me.
Yeah.
Put a bullet in my mouth and shut me up.
No.
Not a bullet.
But I am gonna shut your mouth.
Once and for all.
Come try.
- You sure this is the place?
- Yep.
This is the place.
Stop her!
Ouchie. You're quick.
I know you?
- Doubt it.
- Uh-huh.
You killed Jeremiah. You're famous.
Not so scary.
I could be famous.
You want a shot at me, too?
Unfortunately, you won't
have the opportunity.
Careful.
This is my workshop
where I make my boom-booms.
Anything here, boom, boom.
Then more boom
and more boom, then the whole room...
- Boom, boom. We get it.
- You're bluffing.
Catch.
Ooh! No, no!
Whoops!
That watch must have been an original,
but other stuff in there, boom, boom.
Good luck.
We tie our shoelaces together,
then we lasso the keys off the desk.
And then what, Roy Rogers, huh?
They surrender in awe?
No harebrained scheme is
gonna get us out of this.
Hello!
Hope you don't mind, I...
borrowed some cop stuff from the garage.
Oh, boy, you can put your guns down.
Kevlar in this thing
is designed to withstand a blast
that can tear down a building
twice this size.
What is that?
Is it not obvious?
It's a bomb!
Okay.
Let's play a game.
- Clear out.
- Ah, ah, ah, ah.
If anyone leaves this building,
this thing blows.
You gomers messed with
the wrong super genius,
and now it's time for a little payback.
Nygma, you're a son of a bitch!
Oh, not now, Bullock.
The body count at Haven
wasn't big enough for you, huh?
Shut up!
What's your game?
The only way to deactivate this bomb
is to put a four-digit code
on the keypad there.
What's the code?
The pallid beach mouse
can give birth every four weeks.
Assuming we start with two mice,
and that the size
of an average litter is 12 mice,
and that they are equally
split male to female,
how many pallid beach mice
would we have at the end of one year?
The answer to that question is the code.
Oh, I almost forgot.
You have two minutes.
After that, everyone in here goes splat.
Except for me, of course.
I'm in position.
Copy. Plug the recorder
to the transmitter.
Next, you'll connect
the transmitter to the radio.
There should be a black box
at the base of the antenna.
Let me know when you get it open.
Nygma's bomb ploy won't last forever.
We just have to wait for
the exhaust fans to come
to a complete stop before
you can use the gas.
What are you doing?
You want to take responsibility
for people dying?
Look around.
This is all on you.
What the hell does that mean?
Walker spent months
trying to convince
her superiors that Gotham
was overrun by criminals.
We were this close to being sent in
when you set up Haven.
The fact that one man was able
to safely house and rescue hundreds
of innocent civilians
showed the military higher-ups
that the criminal element of Gotham
must not be so big and scary after all.
They were ready to send in relief,
so it had to come down.
Why? What the hell does she want?
They were innocent people, children.
They were an acceptable loss
for the mission.
What mission, damn it?
That's enough.
Take her out back and shoot her.
He doesn't need to see this.
It's my gift to you,
a small mercy.
You never should have
brought her into this, Eduardo.
Can we speed things along,
please, Mr. Fox?
The exhaust fans have to wind down
before they can change directions.
If you throw the canisters in
now, the gas will blow outside.
Bruce, status?
One second.
I'm here. The box is open.
Two dark green wires right in front.
Attach those to the transmitter.
The message will send.
It's done.
One minute left.
Everybody hear that?
One minute before this thing explodes.
I know the answer.
Uh... Nope, don't think you do, Bullock.
My high school zoology class is
still rattling around up here.
High school was a long time ago,
so let's just take
the full minute, shall we?
Really think about it.
I don't need to.
The pallid beach mouse is extinct.
It disappeared in 1959.
The number you'll have at
the end of the year is zero.
The number is zero. Trust me on this.
I got in trouble. I had to
write an essay about it.
I swear to God.
Oh, dear.
I got a math problem for you.
Count these bullets.
Yes!
You want to know why
Ramirez and the rest didn't make it out?
After your tour of duty was up,
we were caught behind enemy lines,
taken to the darkest hell on Earth...
Peña Duro.
Have you heard of it?
Prison? I didn't know.
No one did,
'cause it's where we were
left to die by our government.
I was the only one that survived.
Walker...
Walker, she found me in that place.
She pulled me out.
She gave me a new purpose.
She made you her killer.
No, no, Jim.
She's the killer.
And you have no idea.
Lee?
You and your stupid revenge.
The diamond isn't even worth
anything in Gotham anyway.
Unless...
The diamond is worth
something on the mainland.
And I bet you have
way more where that came from.
You're leaving Gotham.
Congratulations, you're a genius.
Why?
"Alexander the Great
"then looked upon his land
"and wept.
For there was nothing left to conquer."
I've done all I can in Gotham.
Some things twice.
There's nothing left
for me here anymore.
I want in.
I can't even walk around the city
without some lowlife
trying to take me out.
Just so he can up his cred.
I don't want to be the person
who killed Jeremiah Valeska.
I just want to be myself.
And I can't do that in Gotham anymore.
My heart weeps for you.
But no.
What if I could get us out of here?
You do that, I will cut you in.
50-50.
Ten percent, and I won't murder you
- once we reach the mainland.
- Deal.
Selina, wait!
She said, "Anything in the room
could be a bomb."
Not the room itself.
- Did you know that the whole time?
- Just thought of it.
We should hurry before
she gets away with all our stuff.
Don't worry.
She won't get far.
Alvarez, take Lee to my office.
Be right there.
I got to be honest with you, man.
I don't know how many more
of these close calls
this old heart can take.
We were able to transmit the audio logs,
but until I hear back from my contacts,
I won't know if they received them.
Well, if they did,
probably have a lot of questions.
We'll spend the night and help out.
Alfred can go back to the
apartment and grab what you can?
Certainly, Master Bruce.
Thanks, Bruce.
The next time I get a short straw,
I'm just gonna walk into traffic.
Where has Lee been this whole time?
I don't know.
I'm not gonna wait around
to watch their touching reunion.
What is happening here?
I don't know where to start.
When I didn't hear from you,
I'd hoped you'd gotten out of Gotham.
The last thing that I remember
is Jeremiah destroying the bridges.
That was over three months ago.
Three months? Oh, my God.
You don't remember anything?
I'm trying, and...
Right before the bridges came down,
you said you were leaving the city.
- Why didn't you?
- I don't know, Jim.
None of this is making any sense.
We're still cut off.
There's no help.
It's been hard.
Actually, that's not true.
It's been hell.
People needed hope,
so I put on a brave face.
Pretended I knew what to do.
But you know me, Lee.
I'm just a cop.
And now I'm really lost.
Hey, it's okay.
We're here now.
We'll just try to put
the pieces back together again.
Maybe we can help each other.
Let's start with my memory.
I went back to the Narrows.
I saw Ed.
We fought. We...
Oh.
He stabbed me.
- What?
- Wait, let me remember.
I stabbed him.
There was so much blood.
Then I was...
somewhere...
A hospital, maybe?
Eduardo.
So much potential,
but not quite up to the task.
Walker.
How?
We've been burned.
The press have recordings of me
instructing Nygma to take down Haven.
I thought I might accomplish my task
without setting foot in this foul city,
but that's not to be.
You won't die yet, my warrior.
There is so much more for you to do.
Professor Strange will have you
fixed up in no time.
Jim Gordon.
Don't worry about Gordon.
Nygma was never alone.
There was a second operative.
You okay?
You cold?
The hospitals were
all out of commission.
Just the one clinic in the green zone.
Lee?
Time to die, Jim Gordon.
Ah...
Wanted: one butler.
Military background a plus.
References required.
Yes, Mr. Pennyworth.
I have a job for you.
Well, you weren't lying when you said
she wouldn't get far.
Pretty crown's... booby-trapped.
Ouch.
Ouch, indeed.
I couldn't have you coming back here
and making off with
all of my belongings.
Our belongings.
Cut my wings, let me go?
Bang, bang.
What the hell?
The buckshot in her gut
wasn't enough punishment?
Just a little reminder of what happens
when people try to steal from me.
Good to know.
Partner.
So Lee has a chip, too?
I don't know how, but it seems that way.
Walker must have been holding onto her
as some sort of plan B this whole time.
Three months? That's a hell
of a long game she's playing.
Which means she probably has
other tricks up her sleeve.
Hey.
- Welcome back.
- Oh, hell.
This is gonna keep happening.
What's wrong with me?
The good news is, I think
I can actually answer that.
Jim.
I need to talk to you.
Now is not a good time, Barbara.
Don't you remember the good time
we had the other night?
- Over there?
- Say what?
You need to leave now.
I'm pregnant.
Good to see you, Lee.
Long time.
Congratulations?
You.
You're supposed to be dead, mate.
Sorry to disappoint.
You hurt my boy...
and I will bite your face off.
Yeah. Yeah.
Ah... Bruce will be along shortly.
In the meantime...
This place is in desperate need
of some good, old-fashioned butlering.
How did you even find a way off
the bloody island anyway?
How?
One if by land, two if by sea,
three if by digging
a tunnel under the river.
But enough questions.
Today is the big day.
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com