Previously onGotham...
Monsters are coming, Mr. Mayor.
Six criminally insane inmates
busted out of Arkham Asylum.
I want mass panic.
Hello, Jim. How do I look?
- Barbara!
- Yo, commish.
Yeah?
Don't move.
You should probably get back to work.
Who knows what went wrong
while you were gone.
It's a new day, Jim.
Jerome Valeska,
the attack on the G.C.P.D.
Someone on the streets is talking.
Somebody knows something.
Valeska has red hair, crazy laugh
might be rolling
with a blonde number.
I don't know anything. Honest.
- You believe him?
- Nope.
Me neither.
It's the truth.
But, hey, I can help you guys.
You know, spread the word and stuff.
Valeska killed a friend of ours.
Anybody hides him,
anybody protects him,
they go down too. You got it?
- Now spread the word.
- No, no.
Sneaking out.
Just like a guy.
There are loose ends that need tying.
Need this?
Bring back bagels.
No need for that.
I thought Miss Kean and I could have
a little chat. Good morning.
Jerome is waiting outside.
Try and keep him focused.
You be nice.
You two seems to be getting along.
I'm so glad.
She needs a friend.
My sister is a very special person.
She seems so strong
but yet she's quite fragile.
- Sugar?
- Sure.
You acquitted yourself very well
at the adventure at the G.C.P.D.
Jim Gordon escaped the carnage
unscathed.
- Top marks.
- Thank you.
Did you know my family
built this city?
We carved the bedrock
upon which it stands.
Yet there is not a bridge, an alley,
a ditch that carries our name.
My forefathers were betrayed,
their legacy erased.
And I am here to punish those
who wronged us.
And reclaim what is ours.
Strawberry?
I didn't ask.
So you're gonna take over Gotham
by unleashing a bunch of loonies?
- Awesome plan.
- It's only part one.
So, what's the second part?
Oh, you're gonna love it.
There's a starring role for you.
You're gonna be famous and powerful,
and your finest dream will come true.
You know my dreams, do you?
When Jim Gordon has outlived
his usefulness,
I'm gonna help you destroy him.
Not kill him.
Destroy him.
Body and soul.
Shocking images.
Gotham is on high alert today...
Look, I'm saying
I'll chuck mopes out of windows
until the cows come home
but at some point,
we gotta go see Penguin.
Why would he break Jerome
out of Arkham or attack the G.C.P.D.?
He wouldn't, but that weasel's
running things now.
- If there's chatter, he'd know it.
- I'll think about it.
- Jim.
Alvarez, where are you
with Jerome's circus contacts?
- Circus is upstate. I'm waiting...
- Follow up.
His father is probably with him.
He covered for him once before.
He might have some information.
Do it.
Yo, detective.
- Which escapee are you tracking?
- Helzinger. No one's seen him.
He's 6'7, 275 with a mind
of a five-year-old.
Somebody's seen him.
Hey!
What are you doing?
That stays up until we have
our killer in custody.
- Do you understand?
- Yes sir.
Sarah Essen and nine of your brothers
were killed in this house.
In our house.
Their murderer stood right there
and he laughed at us.
Never forget that.
What?
- So how are you?
- I'm fine.
Really?
- I know Essen was your friend...
- Lee, whatever you're about to say
I know it's coming from a good place,
but I can't hear it right now.
So the Gotham Children's Hospital
gala is tonight,
which I helped organize.
I can't.
- You can't go?
- No.
Even though a few hours away
from all of this might help.
Lee...
Okay.
I just have to tell you something
because if I don't
and you find out,
you're gonna be pissed.
There's gonna be a magician.
Yeah. Right.
- Stop beating yourself up.
- I'm trying.
- I know you are.
- I should've been here. I wasn't
Stop it.
Kiss me.
Better.
Not to interrupt your weirdly
timed make-out session
but Alvarez got in touch
with the circus manager,
the blind fortune teller,
Jerome's dad,
bailed on him, stayed in town,
got an address.
- I'll call you.
- Okay.
Who's there?
I know someone's there...
Hi, Pops.
Long time...
no see.
So how are you doing?
The silent treatment, eh?
Here, I'll tell you a story.
You remember Kansas City, Dad?
The circus went through town.
Every spring.
Right around my birthday.
There was this guy.
Him and my mom used to drink
and fornicate
and beat the crap out of me.
They'd make a whole night out of it.
And I remember one time,
it was my ninth birthday.
Him and my mom
had just finished round one
of boozing, boning, beating up Jerome
and were deciding to take
a little break.
Anyway...
I was outside the trailer
and you were there.
And you said:
"Why are you crying, Jerome?"
It's my birthday.
And my mom and the snake-eye
are beating me.
And then you said:
"This world doesn't care about you
or anyone else, Jerome.
Better to realize that now."
And that was it.
You see, there's this guy, dad.
He believes in me.
He thinks I'm gonna be a star.
And tonight, all of Gotham
will see that too.
Except for you.
Because you'll be, you know, dead.
- Jerome...
- Is this the part
where you say how sorry you are?
How you should've believed in me,
how it's not too late to start again?
News flash, Dad. It's too late.
You don't have to do this.
No.
I'm pretty sure I do.
I was a bad father
but I did love you.
To kill me for that?
That's not why I'm gonna kill you.
Plans to Arkham Asylum.
Look at these.
Letters between you
and your troubled son.
Innocent at first glance,
but Detective Gordon...
You remember him, right?
He will feel little bumps.
A secret message
written in Braille between you
and your son discussing my escape.
Finally, the knockout gas
used to disable the orderlies.
Because you see, Dad,
this guy I was telling you about,
he's the one who broke me
out of Arkham.
He doesn't want anyone
to know about that. Obviously. So...
The police will find these letters,
they'll think...
"The blind old fool
really loved his son.
What a wonderful father."
There won't be a dry eye
in the house.
They'll never believe it.
Sure they will.
Cops are dumb.
There's nothing to eat in this dump.
Finish up and let's go.
Sorry you're gonna miss
my big night, Dad.
But, hey, you're psychic, so tell me,
do I kill?
You will be a curse upon Gotham.
Children will wake from sleep,
screaming at the thought of you.
Your legacy will be death
and madness.
Well...
Say hi to mom for me.
G.C.P.D.
Mr. Cicero, it's Detective Gordon.
We need to speak
with you about your son.
Mr. Cicero.
Mr. Cicero?
Harvey. Window.
Harvey?
Detective Gordon. Old pal.
That gas sure packs a wallop, huh?
That's cute.
- I'm sensing anger.
- You killed Sarah Essen.
Now I'm gonna kill you.
Don't shoot him.
How about a little flesh wound?
No, no.
My dibs.
This is a waste of time.
We had a deal.
Didn't we, Master Bruce?
A part of which was you resuming
a normal lifestyle.
Your parents were patrons
to the Children's Hospital.
Therefore, it makes you a patron.
Besides...
there's gonna be a magician.
And you like magicians, don't you?
No, I don't.
I hate magicians.
You know what I said
about being normal?
Excuse me.
I'm Lee Thompkins.
I work with James Gordon.
He's mentioned you.
- I saw you and thought...
- Of course.
- Very nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
This is my guardian,
Alfred Pennyworth.
- It's an absolute pleasure.
- Thank you.
How is Detective Gordon doing
since the attack on the precinct?
- I was thinking I should call him.
- He'd appreciate that.
- Can I get you something to drink?
- Just water. Thank you.
So...
I hear there's gonna be
a magician.
Hello, Selina.
Hey.
I didn't expect to see you here.
Well, you wanna steal stuff,
it helps to go
where the rich people are.
You do know this is a benefit
for a children's hospital.
- So?
- So these people
are here for a good cause.
Me eating is a good cause.
Besides, didn't I steal something
for you once?
- Selina, that was different.
- Right.
How'd that go?
You get into that guy's safe?
Yes. Though things didn't turn out
quite like I planned.
A lot's happened since then.
Alfred says there's gonna be
a magician.
I'm working.
And I hate magicians.
See you around, Bruce.
So you wanna share your plan?
Remember I told you I could divine
the thing a person truly wants?
What Gotham wants is a hero.
And tonight...
I'm going to give them one.
Shall we?
Jerome and Tabby went on ahead.
Great cape.
Thank you for filling in
on short notice.
But how did you hear our magician
dropped out, Mister...
Rudolpho.
Well, you know, magic.
Oh, I won't be needing that.
- Come on.
- I'm sorry
but really there is no mystery.
Tabitha, have you met
Deputy Mayor Kane?
Harrison, this is my Tabitha.
Nice to meet you.
Could you please tell your brother
that when a handsome billionaire
appears out of nowhere,
people get curious.
Where he'd come from?
How did he make his money?
Who's he dating?
My wife would kill me
if I don't get something. A tidbit.
He's a monster in the sack.
Do you have any news of Mayor James?
No. No, it's a real mystery.
We don't know where he is.
How intriguing.
Harrison, would you mind?
A little family business.
Of course. Miss Galavan.
Everything's ready.
See you at home.
So how do you go from being
in the Royal Marines to a butler?
Well, it is a bit tedious,
really, after a while.
You know, parachuting
into one global hot spot
after another warlords putting
ridiculous bounties on your head.
- It gets a bit boring, really.
- You have amazing stories.
Yeah, well, you know, one or two.
You know,
I don't really get nights off,
but if ever you'd like to
pop by Wayne Manor
for dinner one evening, I...
That's very kind of you,
Mr. Pennyworth...
No.
Alfred. Please, Alfred.
Alfred.
That's very kind of you but...
Now, having said that, I don't see
why I can't take a night off and I...
I happen to know the head chef
at Chez Parnasse.
Well, I'm afraid I...
Did you say Chez Parnasse?
I've been trying to eat there
for quite some time.
You have the most beautiful eyes.
Oh, wow. Okay, look.
Thank you but...
- Alfred, I'd like to leave.
- Yup.
What about Dr. Thompkins' water?
And of course,
you're gonna miss the magician.
Sorry, I must have forgotten
your water.
Alfred, I still want to leave.
- Are you not feeling well?
- No he's absolutely fine. He's fine.
Why don't you just hop off
to the bar, Master Bruce?
- Show's about to start.
- Is it time?
I've roped myself into emcee duties
for the night.
I hope you'll stay for the show.
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
What?
Good evening.
I'm Dr. Lee Thompkins.
For the past five years,
I've had the honor
of being part
of the Children's Hospital.
Thank you for your support and thank
you so much for coming out tonight.
Over the years, we've had magicians
come and entertain our children.
And so tonight, we have
one of the magicians here for you.
Without further ado,
please allow me to present to you,
The Great Rudolpho.
Very nice.
Greetings, ladies and germs.
I am indeed The Great Rudolpho.
Please ogle my lovely assistant.
For my first act,
I'll require a volunteer.
Let me see.
Duck, duck, duck, duck, duck, duck,
Goose.
Go, Master Bruce. Be a sport.
Don't keep the lady waiting.
Fine.
Hello, young man.
Please.
Does this handsome gentleman
have a name?
- Bruce.
Well, Bruce.
This won't hurt a bit.
Is there a doctor in the house?
No. Just...
Excuse me, just wait. Wait.
Wait one second.
Go home.
I'm fine.
You've been running this
since last night.
And you got a face-full of that gas.
Go home.
You going home?
I didn't think so.
- Maybe I will go get some sleep.
- Good idea.
Well, we got somewhere, right?
At least now we know
who broke Jerome out of Arkham.
Yeah, a crazy old blind man
that lived alone.
A clever, crazy old blind man.
If his father broke him out,
why'd Jerome kill him?
He was probably planning this maniac
shtick since you sent him away.
He was just kid.
Every evil bastard in the world
was just a kid once.
Yeah.
But I don't think it was his father
that broke him out.
Oh, cool. Back to square one.
All right, I will go
and get some sleep.
And for the record, I knew Essen
a hell of a lot longer than you.
She saved my ass hundreds of times.
You really should go home.
First thing tomorrow,
we'll go see Penguin.
You're right.
He's got his ears on the street.
Jim.
Never mind.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Give them a wave.
Some people say Bruce
has a split personality.
Very good, Master Bruce.
For my next illusion,
I'd like to call to the stage
esteemed deputy mayor,
Harrison Kane.
Is there something familiar to you
about those two?
Oh, my God.
- Lee. I was just...
- Jim, it's Barbara. She's here.
And I think maybe Jerome...
By the way, nobody here
is getting out alive.
Really?
Right, Master Bruce, time to leave.
Ta-da!
- You're not going anywhere.
- Don't shoot!
- Selina.
- Bruce!
You.
- What's going on?
- Hostage situation.
The magician just killed
the deputy mayor.
It's Jerome Valeska, the same man
that killed Commissioner Essen.
- Who's in charge here?
- I guess you are.
Lee. Thank God.
I've been trying to...
Sorry, Jimbo,
it's just little old me.
- Jerome.
- Are you outside?
You are, aren't you? Oh, goodie.
I swear to God,
if you've hurt her...
Breathe, James.
I haven't touched a hair
on your girlfriend's pretty head.
See for yourself.
This is live television after all.
The police are here,
they are trying to...
The feed just came back.
You son of a bitch.
True, but not the point.
Hey, let's talk about what I want.
Excuse me.
47 million dollars, a helicopter,
obviously, the dry cleaning
I left at Mr. Chang's...
Be careful, that man is a crook.
And I don't know, a pony.
You got 10 minutes,
or I start killing people.
Remember, this is being broadcast
to every home in Gotham,
so, you know, don't let people die.
Bye.
I think that went well.
Enough.
You need to pack up your pathetic
little sideshow and leave.
Is that right?
It may be presumptuous to speak
for all the citizens of Gotham,
but we are sick of you.
You're a small vicious man
with a pathetic need for attention.
Enough, man.
For God's sakes, enough.
I'm curious what your leverage
is here, Mister...
Theo Galavan.
Well, Mr. Theo Galavan,
if you don't sit down,
I'm going to shoot you.
In the face.
I know there is some human decency
left in you.
If you need to take a hostage,
take me.
But let these people go home
to their families.
To their children.
Boring.
Right?
Get your men. We're going in.
I used this to sneak into the party.
We're lucky those dummies
didn't know about it.
- Wait. Wait.
- We're almost outside.
- I have to go back.
- Are you crazy?
- That guy was killing people.
- Yes, and Alfred's back there.
- I'm not going back.
- I don't expect you to.
Selina.
I miss you.
I just wanted to say that.
You're refusing a direct order?
I could have your stripes.
That maniac killed the commissioner.
Not my men,
we're not equipped for this.
Fine. I'll go it alone.
Hold very still.
I can't look.
Someone tell me how it turns out.
Damn.
Turn around.
Well, clap.
So, Lee, how's Jim doing?
I hope he's not blaming himself
for this whole Essen-being-killed
thing.
You are one crazy bitch.
So rude.
You know, I'm gonna,
I'm gonna make a prediction.
Within a year,
Jim and I are gonna be back together.
Wanna know why?
Because we're both the same.
We both have a dark side.
And one day,
we will tell our grandchildren
about how this man-eating harpy
almost tore us apart.
But in the end, love conquered all.
- You...
- I'm sorry. What's that?
Hasn't been 10 minutes.
I need to buy you a watch.
Well, I think it's time
for tonight's first official victim.
You all know and love him.
Poor rich boy.
Parents murdered in an alley
and my favorite volunteer.
Where is Bruce Wayne?
Did you know I'm an orphan too,
Bruce?
I killed my parents, though.
Where are you hiding?
Bruce.
Where are you, buddy?
Kill his butler.
Come on, move it, butler.
All right, last chance, Bruce,
but it's about to get
very butler-brainy out here.
Detective Gordon.
He's going to kill Alfred.
I have to help him.
Brucey!
No. It's you he wants.
Bruce, he just wants you.
I will not let him hurt Alfred.
I'm bored. Shoot the butler.
Stop!
What the bloody hell
are you doing, Bruce?
There's a gun in my jacket.
Detective Gordon
is behind the curtain.
Let's get this started, huh?
You. Check behind the curtain.
Make sure no one's playing
silly buggers.
Drop the knife!
I don't have a clean shot.
Stay calm, Bruce.
Seems like we've got
ourselves a pickle.
What do you say, Brucey boy?
Wanna boost our ratings, huh?
Smile.
I said, enough.
I know, I know.
This is not what we rehearsed.
I'm so sorry, Jerome.
You have real talent,
but now you see, the plot thickens.
Enter, the hero.
You said...
I was gonna be...
Jim, stop her!
a pony.
See, someone like that
has no interest in building things.
He's not part of a tradition.
It's chaos for chaos' sake.
Perhaps I could use a new laugh.
Huh?
Wow.
Dude! Color me impressed.
You know, if I close my eyes,
I can still see you holding
Fish's umbrella.
"Yes, Miss Mooney."
"No, Miss Mooney."
"Whatever you say, Miss Mooney."
"That wig looks great on you,
Miss Mooney."
Seriously, the worm has turned.
Detective Bullock.
I heard you rejoined the force.
I'm so happy.
But aren't you missing
all of the excitement?
Yeah, I got the word too late.
Besides, I wanted to talk to you.
Of course. Always happy to help.
See, there's talk on the street
that Jim Gordon did a favor for you.
Collected a debt,
and the guy ended up dead.
Rumors!
Rumors.
Then again, where there's smoke...
Jim shouldn't worry about that.
He and I are good friends.
Well, see, that's the problem,
Oswald.
I think he is worried.
Because something happened today,
and you were the obvious person
to come to
and I sensed Jim was a little
reluctant to come down here.
Like I said, he shouldn't worry.
Yeah, as long as you two
remain friends.
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
I got a half a mind
to take you outside
and beat you senseless
with a garbage can.
Maybe some other time.
Call yourself whatever you want, man.
The king of Gotham.
But to me, you'll always be
that little umbrella boy.
And if you come after Jim Gordon,
you gotta come after me.
And I still owe you for Fish.
But seriously, this place is amazing.
Give me another drink!
You were very brave.
You helped save the lives
of everyone in here.
Your parents...
they would have been proud.
That they would have been.
They also would have given me
the sack
for letting you do something
so idiotic.
It was all of us. We were a team.
Yeah. I guess we were.
- Is he okay?
- Fine.
Though I'd still like him
to get checked out at the hospital.
Barbara gave him quite a knock.
Any word on her?
No, she went through a trap door
on the stage.
They must have always been planning
to use that as their exit.
Don't worry. We'll find her.
Mister Galavan, sir.
Alfred Pennyworth.
I'd just like to thank you
for saving young Master Wayne's life.
If there's anything I can ever do
for you, sir...
Or I.
I really just did what any citizen
of Gotham would have done.
I wish that were true.
Jim Gordon.
Theo.
Well, if you ever need anything,
please call.
We're all in this together, right?
Thank you, sir.
Right. Well, I suppose I better
be getting this young man home.
It's been much more of an exciting
evening than originally planned.
I never did like magicians.
Good night.
It was very nice meeting you,
Dr. Thompkins.
And you, Bruce.
A good night's sleep,
and you'd be right as roses.
I do hope we get to see you again
soon.
Thank you.
Alfred.
Sure you're okay?
I'm fine.
Kiss me?
- Jim...
- Kiss me.
- Oh, bugger.
- Alfred.
- You knew, didn't you?
- I didn't know, Alfred.
You did. You let me
make a mug of myself.
Alfred, I had no idea.
- You did.
- I didn't know.
Well, I didn't know.
Despite the presence
of the G.C.P.D,
it was billionaire Theo Galavan,
newly arrived in Gotham
but already making his name
who stood up to the escaped lunatic.
Am I a hero?
Apparently.
I think tonight, the people of Gotham
have said enough.
The reign of tyranny is over.
Now the real fun begins.
- Poor Jerome.
- Yes. Very sad.
Such a compelling character,
but limited, you know?
He was never gonna last long.
I don't know about that.
The kid had a way about him.
Oh, poor baby.
Did you get a bump?
Jerome Valeska is dead.
His murderous escapades
left a deep impression on Gotham.
Nobody here is getting out alive.
Coming through.
You will be a curse upon Gotham.
Children will awake from sleep
screaming at the thought of you.
Your legacy will be death
and madness.