Previously on Gotham...
Word of the chemical spill
- reached the mainland.
- Reunification isn't happening.
No action until the government
can determine if Gotham's safe.
I sentence you,
Victor Zsasz, to die.
Get him out of there!
What the hell are you doing?!
Trying to keep you all
from making a terrible mistake.
- Her name is Ivy.
- She's a witch.
I'm feeding the earth
with these wretched creatures.
It consumes them,
and then it flourishes.
We wouldn't have escaped
without you.
You saved me
and my friends.
I wanted to help.
- Come with us.
- Are you telling me
you found a way out of Gotham?
It's a submarine.
I've been giving you space,
but we have to talk
about how this is gonna work.
I'm gonna be a part
of this kid's life.
- Oh, you seem pretty confident about that.
- I am.
You're having a baby
with Barbara.
Can't change the past, so...
I guess we just have
to live with it.
Come on, people!
Time's a-wastin'!
The filtration system that
Lucius designed is working.
What you're doing is both
unnecessary and it's reckless.
Our supplies of drinking water
are at critical levels.
Every day, the gangs
grow more aggressive.
If I can get a cease-fire,
even a temporary one,
then when reunification
does happen,
at least there will be people
left to save.
They deserve that much.
And does your child
deserve a father?
You have no problem taking
care of the entire city.
What about focusing
on just one life?
Why are you
always so ready
to put yourself
in the crosshairs?
It's like you won't be satisfied
until you sacrifice yourself.
You really believe that?
I do.
And it scares me.
How is this gonna work?
Am I supposed
to just stay at home
and raise this child
with Barbara
while you go cowboying off
all the time?
It won't always be like this.
After reunification...
Nothing will be different.
Unless you stop being...
Me?
Hey, Jim.
I have to go.
- We'll talk after.
- If there is an after.
Oh, yeah?! Oh-ho!
Oswald, where
the hell is Nygma?
Shouldn't we have left the city
already?
Ms. Kean,
this may come as a surprise,
but building a submarine
from scratch
by yourself takes time.
- Patience.
- Easy for you to say.
You're not
a walking egg timer.
Tell him to get
a move on.
And why, exactly,
are you hosting Gordon's
gangland get-together?
Keep your friends close and
your enemies closer, my dear.
If we're really going
to leave Gotham,
we need to keep Gordon happy.
You know all about
that, don't you?
It was a momentary slip.
The world was on fire.
Jim,
it's your show.
Mi casa, su casa.
I'll make this short.
Gotham is running dry.
Our supply of clean water
will only last
a few more months.
So you have a choice.
You can keep killing each other,
fighting over
what little water is left,
maybe eke out a few
more months, then die.
Or...
we can all agree right now
to an immediate cease-fire.
The government
will not annex a war zone.
If we can show them that we
deserve to rejoin the mainland,
supply chain will be restored
and we will all survive
until reunification.
That's the choice.
Life or death.
Your call.
Weapons down!
Get back!
Jim, you see
where the shooter was?
Jim.
Oh, my God.
Get back!
You're gonna be all right.
It's bad.
We got to move him. Now.
Clinic's too far.
M.E.'s office.
Alvarez, come on. Help.
On it.
Take my gun.
One, two, three.
All right.
Get back.
Back! Get back!
Well,
I did not see that coming.
What made you choose this,
of all places,
for a scavenging mission?
Just trust me, okay?
What the hell?
Sit.
Wow.
Candles.
If I didn't know
any better,
I'd say this was
a... date.
Maybe it is.
That okay with you?
Maybe.
Good.
So let's eat.
Lee!
It's Jim.
He's lost
a lot of blood.
Can you save him?
Come with me!
Doc says he's gonna be okay.
He's gonna pull through.
But until then,
I'm acting captain.
Now, the gangs of this city
think this is their time
that they can run wild!
They are dead wrong!
I want us to take
to the streets.
It is show-of-force time!
We ain't gonna give 'em an inch!
Harper,
I want you to organize
patrol teams.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna find out
who shot my partner.
The bullet
shattered against a rib.
I have to get
all the fragments out.
I haven't done general surgery
since med school.
There.
All right,
there's an exit wound,
so the rest
must've gone through.
I need to sew him up.
Can you get my kit?
Right away.
Come on, Jim.
You can do this,
but you have to fight.
You hear me?
You have to fight.
Order in the court.
James Gordon,
you have been brought here
to be judged
for your many crimes,
and your very life hangs
in the balance.
Do you understand?
No, I...
The defendant understands
and waives his right
to appeal.
The trial of James Gordon
will now begin.
No! Wait!
That...
was the best canned meal
I've ever had.
And if this
was a date,
I don't know how
you're gonna top it
when everything gets back
to normal.
I don't think
things are ever gonna be normal.
For me, anyways.
What do you mean?
Wayne Manor's gone.
And I know that a lot of people
lost a lot more,
but part of me wonders
if it wasn't fate.
It wasn't.
It was Jeremiah
blowing up your house.
Maybe it's time to move on.
You mean, like, leave Gotham?
Bruce, forget
Wayne Manor.
This city is your home.
And how many terrible things
have happened to it
because of me?
Galavan.
Ra's al Ghul.
If this city really is my home,
then maybe
the best thing
I can do for it is leave.
I have to say...
...kind of agree with you
on that one,
billionaire boy.
Jim Gordon's blood on my floor.
Olga!
Why is the help never around
when you need them?
This could be good for us.
You especially.
Are you serious?
Your baby daddy is
the top cop in Gotham.
A dead Jim Gordon is
the only way
you can hold on
to your little...
bundle of joy.
Harvey, how is our dear...
Who the hell did it?!
If I find out it was you,
I swear to God...
It wasn't me!
I merely supplied the venue!
At your boss's request!
That doesn't mean squat!
Fine. You want to know
who's to blame?
James Gordon!
He invited
every criminal in Gotham!
What did he think
was gonna happen?
How about you, huh?
When did you two become so...
buddy-buddy?
Maybe when you
hatched up a plan
so you could keep that baby
for yourself.
Harvey, whatever
you think of me,
I did not plot to kill
my child's father.
Well, someone here did!
Someone in this room
shot Jim Gordon,
and I'm not leaving
till I find out who it was!
Wrong! The shooter was not here!
Look at the window, stupid!
The shot came
from outside.
If the shooter was there...
and the trajectory was here...
Jim was...
then the bullet...
Uh-huh.
I'm gonna find out who this was,
and when I do,
there's gonna be hell to pay.
Harvey.
Is there anything I can do?
Yeah. You can keep the gangs
from tearing the city apart.
What do you want?
You...
I will deal with later.
I'm here...
...for you.
I need you to come with me.
Why would I do that?
Because you love me so much.
Well, not yet, but you will.
Don't mess with him, Ivy.
Protecting
your boyfriend?
That's cute.
But I thought
that might happen, so...
I brought a friend.
I stumbled across
this charming man
on the way over here,
and apparently,
you two know each other.
Leave her out of this!
You know, I heard you talking
about the future of Gotham...
but Gotham will be
what I decide.
A green world.
Won't that be beautiful?
Gorgeous.
Bruce and I have to go.
You always did think
you were better than me.
But without my plants,
you never would
have left your bed.
I made you strong again.
Think about that
while my friend
is cutting out your heart.
There are so many things
I wish I could say to you.
So many things
I wish we could do.
This can't be the end.
Come on, Jim.
Talk to me.
Say something.
Speak.
No.
This isn't right.
I shouldn't be here.
- Silence! Silence!
- You have to listen to me.
The prosecution will now give
its opening remarks.
Your Honor, Jim Gordon's crimes
are a matter of public record.
He's failed Gotham
at every turn.
He failed to clean up
the city...
failed to stop the bridges
from being destroyed,
failed to protect
those poor, innocent souls
in the refuge
he himself created...
Haven.
I tried.
- I did the best...
- Silence!
One more outburst and you
will be held in contempt.
I'm hurt.
I need help. Please.
Continue.
The issue here is not
how many people have died
because of Jim Gordon,
but how many more must die
in order to satisfy
his need to be a hero.
Therefore we pose
one simple question:
Are the people
in Jim Gordon's life
better off with him alive
or dead?
I think I'm dying.
The prosecution
would like to call
its first witness,
Your Honor.
Dr. Lee Thompkins.
Come on, Jim.
Hold on.
How is he?
Touch and go.
He's
stable for now.
I removed all the
bullet fragments,
but something keeps
pulling him down.
Where are the fragments?
What is it?
"V.Z."
Victor Zsasz.
Okey-dokey.
Time to boogie.
Hey!
I'm only here for Gordon.
So all of you stay down.
'Cause I see anyone...
and, you know...
bang.
Oi, oi!
Now, I heard you were looking
for Jim Gordon.
Uh-huh.
Listen, I know we have history.
Let's just let bygones
be bygones.
Yeah, right.
You did this to my face.
Whatever.
It's not like you were much
of a looker before, anyway.
Ivy says you
hurt her feelings.
Why would you do that!?
She's so sweet!
Ivy didn't make me strong.
I made me strong.
Tell me where she took Bruce.
The only reason I'm not
ending you right now
is the thought of
the look on your face
when Jim Gordon walks
through that door.
Because he's alive,
you son of a bitch!
Ugh. What did you eat?
You smell like a butcher.
You know, I'm vegan now.
Why kill Jim now?
Makes no sense.
He saved your
miserable ass.
He prevented Penguin
from executing you.
If anyone, you should be
going after Cobblepot.
Yeah, that's a good point.
Maybe I'll do him next.
It's kind of not up to me.
You're working for someone?
Oh.
Sorry.
I want a name!
Ah, what's in a name?
A rose by any other name
would smell as sweet.
You know,
I'm really taking the time
to stop and smell the roses
these days.
Like, actual roses.
They're great.
Are you high?
On love.
But like I said...
my lips are sealed.
Ivy Pepper.
You said it, not me.
Uh, I'm technically
not allowed to say it.
Her name. Which is
such a bummer,
because it's the most beautiful
name in the world.
You watch him.
I could say it all day.
Hey, I will say it all day.
Ivy.
Ivy Pepper.
Mrs...
Ivy Pepper Zsasz.
Oh, that sounds good.
Here you are,
Miss Thompkins.
Careful, it's...
a little bit hot.
Forgive me, but I...
heard on the grapevine
that you and Captain Gordon
had a rather heated exchange
this morning.
Oh, God.
Was it that bad?
Apparently,
it was like a session
of the Italian parliament.
You have misgivings
about the arrival
of this child, don't you?
What am I getting
myself into, Alfred?
How am I supposed
to raise a child
alongside a psychopath
like Barbara Kean?
I mean, how the hell
is this gonna work?
But... but that's
not all of it.
If Jim and I are gonna do this,
then we have to do it together.
You know how he is.
I don't know
what's going on
inside that man's
head sometimes.
I think you'll find
that he needs you
a lot more than
he's letting on.
Well, I need to
hear it from him.
I never thought that this was
how my life was going to be.
I have no interest
in being a father myself.
I always presumed that
I was unfit to be one.
And then I found myself...
one night staring
down an alley at this little boy
quite literally
shaking with fear.
I don't know, it's funny,
isn't it, what life throws you?
I'm keenly aware that I am not
Master Bruce's flesh and blood.
But it's the moments.
The little things, like...
like when he uses a skill
that I once taught him,
or we laugh at a joke
that only he and I share.
Those have been some of the most
ecstatic moments of my life.
Nothing can possibly
prepare you for that joy.
The hows and the whats...
you'll figure that stuff out.
What matters is this:
you'll be an exquisite mother,
and that child, he or she
will be extraordinary...
...because of you.
Thank you, Alfred.
Jim, can you hear me?
I'm right here,
right next to you.
Can you feel me?
Lee?
Dr. Lee Thompkins.
You've suffered at this man's hands
more than anyone.
Broken heart,
broken engagement.
A lost child.
And yet, you're still with him.
I love him.
After all the pain
he's caused you,
would your life be better,
could it not still be better,
without Jim Gordon?
Answer the question.
- Lee?
- I'll ask it a different way.
Would you, Dr. Lee Thompkins,
be better off
if Jim Gordon were dead?
I'm sorry.
Everything he touches dies.
Prosecution rests, Your Honor.
You made her say that.
I didn't make her
say anything.
Ask them.
Who are they?
More people who trusted
you, who believed you
when you said you
would protect them.
They're from Haven.
I think I'm dying.
And isn't it about time?
The verdict's in.
You're guilty.
Hey, Jeff, listen to me.
One day, you're
gonna meet someone
who's gonna totally
change your life,
and that's gonna
make you happy,
and you deserve it.
Or not.
Is she here?
She's here, isn't she?
Sweetie.
All I asked of you
was to kill Jim Gordon.
You're not angry, are you?
'Cause I'll do it.
I'll do it right now.
I'll do it.
You keep the cops busy.
Luckily, the other part of my
plan is coming together nicely.
Lucius!
Bruce.
I had no idea
you were stopping by.
I wanted to check
on your progress.
Well, the toxicity levels
in this river continue to drop.
At this point, we'll be under
the threshold mandated
by the government
sooner than expected.
It's not glamorous work,
but we are helping
to save the lives
of thousands of people.
People. Ugh.
I'm sorry. Did you just say
"People. Ugh"?
Lucius,
what if I were to tell you
I have in my possession
the most intoxicating perfume
you'll ever smell?
I would tell you that's
an abrupt change of topic.
Can we go back to the part
where you said "People. Ugh"?
Mmm.
Oh, my... goodness.
Lucius,
Ivy sent me here to get you
to shut down the plant.
Can you do
that for her?
For Ivy? Anything.
She is so great.
♪ They say, they say
she's got to grow up ♪
♪ And they say, they say
she's got to get a job ♪
♪ I know, I know
I'll never be like the rest ♪
♪ Of the bunch. Oh! ♪
Raise your glasses.
I called you all here today
because Jim Gordon is
at death's door.
Yeah!
For years, he has hounded us,
beaten us, shot us.
And today, he got his due.
To Jim Gordon.
May he rot in hell!
Yeah!
What exactly are you doing?
I'm trying to keep this city
from ripping itself apart.
So this has nothing to do
with your feelings for Jim?
What if Ed fails,
and we are stuck here?
This will put us in
Gordon's good graces.
Consider it a backup plan.
Listen up!
Now to the real reason
I brought you all here.
I want you
to agree to an immediate truce.
Get out of here.
And what if, instead,
we shoot you and take your club?
I don't think so.
See, those drinks
I just gave you...
they're poisoned.
And you had two shots
before everyone got here.
So that should be taking effect
around...
...now.
The rest of you have 48 hours
before you'll need
the antidote, which
I will deliver to you,
provided you go back
to your territories,
play nice,
and send me all your guns. Deal?
I said, "Deal?"
- Now get out of here!
- All right.
- Yeah. Out.
- Come on.
Hmm.
Jim will be so pleased.
Keep your friends close,
and your enemies closer.
Isn't that right... Pengy?
Once I reverse the system,
all the toxin we pulled from
the river will be rereleased,
and the overload should
destroy the filters.
In a matter of minutes,
the entire facility
will be inoperable.
There.
Perfect.
Ivy's gonna be so happy.
You think so?
Security breach. Zone 1.
That's odd.
Selina.
I'll take care of it.
Okay.
All right, listen up!
I know you're probably familiar
with Ivy Pepper.
In fact, you were probably here
when she hypnotized the whole
frigging precinct, okay?
She is on the loose,
and we've got to find her
and take her down.
Actually, fellas,
she's already here!
That's right.
Ivy came and freed me.
That is true love for you.
She really understands
what makes me tick.
Don't worry, though.
I'm just a distraction
so she can finish off Jim
once and for all.
You know,
that's how great couples work.
Maybe I shouldn't have
told you that.
Oh, well.
- I'm sorry, Miss Thompkins.
- I know. Go.
Thank you, Alfred.
Come on, Jim.
Can you hear me?
Stay with me.
Stay with me, Jim.
Jim!
Want a drink?
Alvarez makes
a hell of a Mai Tai.
I can barely feel my face.
Harvey, what is this?
It's your wake.
Pretty nice turn-out, huh?
♪ For he's a jolly good fellow ♪
- ♪ For he's a jolly good ♪
- GORDON: Stop.
♪ Fellow ♪
♪ For he's a jolly
good fellow ♪
♪ Which nobody can deny. ♪
Wake?
I'm not dead yet.
Well, be a little bit
of a bummer
to have it after you died,
don't you think?
I'm gonna have a kid, Harvey.
How do I protect that child
when everything around me dies?
Harvey?
That's
a good question.
Will.
You said I'd be
safe in Haven.
I trusted you.
I know.
I did my best.
Your best never seems
good enough.
It's time to go.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no. Jim.
Where's my adrenaline?
Oh...
Oh, looks like
Victor succeeded after all.
I guess I'll have
to settle for killing you.
I can tell you one thing.
I am sick and tired of getting
shot at in my own precinct.
Hey, what the bloody
hell's going on?
I thought you had this
lunatic locked up.
Ivy broke him out
and gave him an arsenal.
But I have an idea. I got to get
to the storeroom. Give me cover.
Alvarez, go!
Why are you doing this?
What has Jim ever done to you?
Gotham has a chance
to be born anew.
To return to
what it was
before people ripped down the
trees and paved over the earth.
He's trying to reunify
with the mainland
to save all these people.
A return to filth.
Pollution.
He's fighting for
death, while I...
promise life...
in its purest form.
Is that your plan?
To have the plants take over
Gotham by killing Jim?
Oh, killing Gordon's
just the first part.
Bruce Wayne is taking
care of the rest.
- For what it's worth, I am sorry.
- For what?
This pain is nothing
compared to what you
are about to feel.
Say good-bye...
to Jim Gordon for me.
No!
No, no, no,
no, no!
No!
Jim.
Selina, you're wasting
your time.
Bruce, you have
to snap out of Ivy's spell.
- This is not you.
- You're wrong.
Ivy's given me a purpose.
Stop! Stop! I don't
want to fight you!
What are you gonna do?
Kill everything in Gotham?
The toxins will only kill
all the people.
The plants will adapt;
they always do.
- Can you hear what that sounds like?
- Yeah.
It sounds great!
I guess I shouldn't
be surprised.
You don't care about Gotham.
You're gonna leave anyway.
What about the
rest of us, huh?
The ones who
are gonna be
stuck here without you?!
Selina...
I'm okay.
- Bruce, I'm so sorry.
- We got to stop Lucius.
- Come on.
- Okay.
Lucius! You have
to stop the shutdown.
Oh, no, I can't do that.
Ivy will be so mad.
Listen to me, I-I used
Ivy's perfume to hypnotize you.
She's using you.
No.
Ivy would never do that.
We're perfectly bonded,
like... carbon and oxygen
or hydrogen
- and oxygen...
- We do not have time for this.
I'm sorry.
There.
Oh, you kicked me
in the head.
I didn't have
a choice, Lucius.
Bruce, where's Ivy?
She was headed to the GCPD.
I wonder what Ivy's doing
right now.
Hey, lover boy.
Are you serious right now?
As a heart attack.
What an idiot.
Oh, my...
Ah, that felt good.
Come on, Jim.
You fight for everyone else.
You never give up.
Fight for yourself, Jim.
Come on!
It's time.
Jim.
Lee.
Is that...?
Yes.
Do you want to...?
I don't know.
I don't know that I can.
Oh, I see.
- No!
- Good-bye, Jim.
No!
I want to live!
It's too late.
No! I want to live!
Lee.
Don't move.
How do you feel?
Like I almost died.
Well, you didn't.
You fought.
You came back to me.
Because I need you.
Lee...
- this child...
- It's okay.
It's okay to be scared.
The only thing scarier
than doing this
is doing it without you.
Can I ask you something?
He seems nervous.
I know.
He should be thrilled.
Marrying a woman who's smarter
and better-looking than him.
Selina, while we
were fighting,
when I was hypnotized,
you talked about me leaving...
Quiet.
Here she comes.
You may sit.
I'm just gonna say,
this isn't gonna be some
long, drawn-out, tearful affair
like you all are used to, okay?
This is gonna be
a short wedding.
I'm gonna try and make it quick
so we can all get to the bar.
Okay?
I first met a young Jim Gordon
when he was a, uh...
pain-in-the-ass, moralistic
rookie detective.
In the years since, he's evolved
into a pain-in-the-ass,
moralistic captain.
I'd say he's my best friend,
but in truth,
he's my only friend.
So we'll skip that.
Uh, on to Lee.
Lee's always had his back.
Except for the time
when she was infected
with the crazy-making virus
and she tried to kill him,
but that's love.
But I will say,
if there's one beautiful thing
that's happened
over these last few crazy years,
it's that these two people
met each other.
And that truly is...
a beautiful thing.
Jim, will you please
take Lee's hand?
Do you, Jim Gordon,
take Lee Thompkins to be
your lawfully wedded wife,
to have and to hold,
from this day forward,
for better, for worse,
for richer, for poorer,
in sickness and in health,
to love and cherish
till death do you part?
I do.
And you, Lee Thompkins,
do you do the same?
Sure, Harvey.
I do.
By the power vested in me...
by absolutely no one...
...I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
What?
And now Jim Gordon
and Lee Thompkins
are man and wife.
Thank God you held the
city together so that
this blessed event
could take place.
It was never
gonna work.
What?
Controlling the gangs
was not a backup plan.
You... saw a chance
to convince James Gordon
that you had changed.
But he will never see you
as anything but
a dangerous woman
keeping his
child from him.
Then I'd best be long gone
before he
can do anything about it.
He will hunt you
till the ends of the earth.
Let him.