- GORDON: Previously on Gotham
- (ALARM RINGING)
BRUCE: Ifound this when
Iwas in the city.
GORDON: Penguin's licenses.
Apparently, crime is legal now.
I got a license.
I'm not giving this city
over to Penguin.
I don't care what the commissioner says.
Oswald Cobblepot
keeps your friends safe.
Not the GCPD.
- Is Barbara around?
- No.
She's not coming back.
I want more.
- (WHIP CRACKING)
- (MEN GRUNTING)
Jonathan Crane's father
created a toxin that makes people
see their greatest fear.
Jonathan, you're going with these men.
Now you're gonna
take your daddy's notebooks
and make as much of that
fear juice as I say.
(SCREAMS)
No.
OFFICER:
Gotham Police, you're under arrest.
- Crane?
- Jonathan Crane isn't here anymore.
It's just the Scarecrow.
(SCREAMS)
(SIRENS WAIL)
This is where Merton said they would be.
Let's go, everybody, stay sharp.
There's no one here.
They're long gone by now.
This place smells like death.
Reminds me there's a Thai joint
not far away
if you wanna grab
something to eat after.
Very funny. It's the toxin.
They made more of it.
HARVEY: Lookie here.
An asylum uniform.
1109.
That's Crane's number, right?
He's coming!
Who?
Scarecrow!
ALFRED: Right, thank you very much,
Officer.
Alfred, you need to explain
this was just a misunderstanding.
Worry not, Master Bruce.
We have Wayne Enterprises' most talented
and expensive lawyer on the case.
- This is an outrage.
- He'II have you out in a jiffy.
How did they nick you anyway?
I fell through the skylight.
These thieves must have
triggered an alarm.
The police were so quick to respond.
I wasn't expecting that, Alfred.
You could've broke your bloody neck.
I had them red-handed.
If I could've only...
Only what?
Only taken on
an entire crew twice your size?
Perhaps, yes.
GORDON: Well, here's something
you don't see every day.
Bruce Wayne behind bars.
There's been a terrible mistake,
Detective Gordon.
You see, I fell in from the roof
into a robbery in progress.
I wasn't breaking in.
Is that so? Why were you up on the roof?
I was looking for Selina Kyle.
I see.
ALFRED: Yes.
We will, of course, have our lawyer
post bail, Detective Gordon.
I hardly think that's necessary.
We'II talk more about this, Bruce.
But not tonight.
Thank you, Detective.
Thank you.
(BABBLING)
(SCREAMING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER ON P.A.)
MAN: (ON P.A.) Everybody in bed.
Everybody in bed.
(GASPS)
Covering your dirty footprints, Warden?
It's too late, I'm afraid.
Your dirty deeds have stained you.
How did you get in here?
Come on.
You don't spend three years
in this hellish place
without picking up a thing or two.
Jonathan?
That's right.
I'm not the same
frightened boy you threw in a cell.
No treatments, no therapy.
Just some ice baths
and some...
Electric shocks once in a while.
You know, you could just leave.
I wouldn't tell anyone.
I don't want to leave, Warden.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
(YELLS)
- N0w, are you paying attention?
- Yeah.
I cured myself.
You see, I feared the scarecrow.
And now we are one.
Jonathan, please. If you just...
You're not listening to me, Warden!
Jonathan Crane is no more.
Call me by my true name.
The Scarecrow.
(RAPID HEARTBEATS)
(SCREAMING)
LUCIUS: Rough night, Bruce?
- Get into a fight?
- No, he fell through a skylight.
He was on the rooftop
talking to Selina Kyle.
Bloody teenagers, eh? Whew.
But your clothes.
Looks more like concrete
and stone residue. though.
What were you doing before that?
Rock climbing.
- Rock climbing.
- Yes, we were rock climbing.
Alfred's been teaching me.
At the rock faces in the south gardens.
Taken to it like a duck to water. he
has, but we've got to plod on, Mr. Fox.
Of course. Sorry to have kept you.
Be careful on those rocks, Bruce.
It's a dangerous sport.
We will, Mr. Fox. We will.
Did you know my father was a genius?
He wanted to end fear.
For my sake.
Because he loved me.
So tell me.
What do you fear, Warden?
Something from your childhood, maybe?
- (SCREECHING)
- (SCREAMING)
Face your fears.
Face your fears and defeat them.
What?
No.
Stop.
Brothers and sisters, look at you.
Prisoners, all of you.
My father would have freed you.
But he was killed.
Murdered by the GCPD.
Men who couldn't understand.
But they will.
For you will be my army.
(ALL SCREAMING)
And those men who killed my father
shall truly know fear.
(SCREAMING)
James Gordon.
James Gordon?
There you are.
Play nice.
No.
I see you've caught one of them.
What about the other fellow?
I have no idea who you're talking about.
Jonathan Crane?
People share with me because they
trust me to get things done.
Unlike you.
S0 this boy who created this
lethal toxin which almost killed me,
where is he?
Whereabouts unknown for now.
Why am I not surprised?
I mean, really.
The only thing the GCPD
knows how to do well is fail.
What is a penguin? A bird or a mammal?
Bird. It is a bird.
Like a chicken?
Time and time again. the GCPD expose
themselves for what they truly are.
An outdated, ineffectual.
And corrupt institution.
How much longer must our citizens
suffer their incompetence?
This coming from a man
who takes money from criminals
in exchange for a license allowing them
to victimize innocent people.
And it is working.
Jim, why can't you see that I am not
here to destroy your beloved GCPD,
but to save it?
And through that, Gotham.
Your licenses are illegal,
and I will arrest anyone I find
who is issued one.
S0 sure your Boy Scout morality
can protect this city, Jim?
How well has that worked in the past?
Should I list the victims of
your antiquated righteousness?
Instead. let me make you a deal.
Find this Jonathan Crane
and lock him up within 24 hours
or admit to me, your subordinates.
And the people of Gotham
that you failed.
And allow me to clean this city up!
Good for you, Jim.
- (Game on.
- UNDISTINCT CHATTER)
What are you doing here?
Have I taught you nothing?
I could've slit your throat
before you even saw me.
I found this on the door this morning.
Someone left this inside last night.
Thank you for coming, ladies.
No way.
I saw you die.
That so?
It is Gotham.
- Check for a pulse next time.
- I will.
Right after I slit your throat.
So what happened to you?
Long story.
Right now, all you need to know
is that I'm back.
And like the card says.
An opportunity awaits you.
A new beginning.
You sure you wanna get this close?
Please hear me out.
Not a day goes by
where I don't think about what I did.
If I could take it back,
trust me, I would.
I wouldn't mind a do-over myself.
Perhaps I'II finish the job this time.
I was jealous.
I was stupid.
I am sorry.
Kill me if you don't believe me.
S0 is this your place now?
This is our place.
Another club?
In Gotham?
How original.
It's not a club.
Penguin's taking over.
Like it or not,
every criminal in this city
is gonna go to him for a license
to mug. steal, or blow stuff up.
Those criminals are gonna need supplies,
and that is where we come in.
Not only will we be able to facilitate
these lowlifes,
but we'II also find out
what they're planning
and how it's going down.
But I will not go forward
without you both.
This is our way back on top.
No.
What you took from me,
I will never be able to get back.
Just feel lucky I don't burn this place
to the ground.
(nooa CLOSES)
This will be good for all of us.
Please talk to her.
I don't wanna hear it, Alfred.
I'm going back out there.
I'm not gonna let this trail go cold.
Farbe it from me
to stop you, Master Bruce.
You're not coming?
No, sir.
And why not?
Because, as last night proved,
you are simply not ready.
Yeah, you can chuck a punch.
You can block one.
You're quick on your toes.
I'Il give you that.
What if they've got guns, Master Bruce?
Out there,
Alfred, I feel more alive
than I've ever felt before.
Do you understand that?
And that is precisely why
I am not stopping you, sir.
But you'll excuse me
if I don't wanna stand by
and watch you get shot.
Hey.
Mental asylum's under siege.
The lunatics are running riot.
The guards called it in
before they bolted for the hills.
- Crane?
- He made more toxins, right?
What happens when you dose 100 nutjobs?
AII right, listen up!
There's a riot at the asylum.
I need as many of you as can come.
Who's with me?
Good luck with that.
You really think
Penguin is gonna make this go away?
He's just getting rich
off the same lowlifes
you guys used to hate as much as me!
Ah, forget it.
Not one of you is fit to wear the badge.
This badge gets us
spat on and shot at every day.
For what?
What difference have we made out there?
- Yeah!
- He's right!
Let's go, Harvey.
Come on. Don't do this.
I told you one day
that you would say
now or never, and I would say never.
Well, today is that day.
If I go with you, I lose them.
And then who's gonna be the new captain?
Because it's damn well gonna be
someone Penguin chooses.
So I am sorry, partner,
but you are on your own on this one.
Yeah.
(SHRIEKING)
GCPD.
(DISTANT CLAMORING)
(LAUGHING)
I'm not scared of you anymore, you see?
'Am you!
Ah. It's you.
(SCREAMING)
You came.
(STATIC CRACKLING ON P.A.)
CRANE: Brothers and sisters,
the enemy is here.
Crap.
(ALARM BUZZES)
Tonight, Detective, you will pay
for what you 've done.
Tonight,
you will know fear!
(GUN CLICKS)
Get him!
AII right, Mr. Cop.
Let's have some real fun.
My, mv!
Well, come on in, I guess.
Word was you were dead.
Imagine my surprise when I hear
you've popped back up alive
and gone and opened
a brand-new business.
We're not open yet.
Looks pretty open to me.
Yeah. I'd say it's open.
Hot damn. It's like Christmas.
Which is upsetting because this was
definitely something
you'd want to run by me first.
Is it now?
Oh, yes, absolutely.
AII enterprises pertaining
to the criminal Underworld shall,
from this time forth, be approved,
monitored. and taxed by me.
MY apologies.
I'm still waiting for my partners
to come aboard.
Who? Tabitha?
Seüna?
Perhaps.
Well, good luck with that.
Slippery characters, the both of them.
Also, people can often carry grudges
after you shoot their boyfriends.
I can talk to them if you want...
I distinctly remember saying you could
come if you kept your mouth shut!
You will need
an operating license, obviously.
Then pay a weapon tax...
- "Weapon tax"?
- And then,
perhaps, your little store can open.
Well, you don't ask for much
now, do you?
I am not asking for enough.
Let me be absolutely clear, Ms. Kean.
Iwill be keeping
a very close eye on you.
The first rumor I hear
about you and your little partners
making moves to contest me,
and Victor...
(GUN CLICKING)
will end you
with your own merchandise.
Understood.
Couldn't have been cheap.
L\\ \ \ n\\ \
You lost your money on the Sirens club.
Then went missing.
Rumor was you were dead.
And now you're back
with a brand-new fancy place.
Who paid for it?
You really think
Iwon't find out who it is?
(SIGHS)
I'm gonna take this.
Crane?
Do you believe in fate?
I didn't before today,
but you, sir, have made me a believer.
Of all the police in Gotham, it was you.
You came.
Jonathan.
What happened to you?
Well, first,
you killed my father.
Your father was insane.
He was trying to kill you.
He tried to help me.
Help all mankind.
- He was a murderer.
- He was a pioneer!
Å Genius!
He taught me
we can live our entire lives
imprisoned by our fears.
Or we can embrace them.
You should know that better than anyone.
What will you see. I wonder.
What scares you the most?
One of your victims, perhaps?
One of your victims?
What haunts you the most?
- (GROWLS)
- (WOMAN SCREAMING)
Lee.
Ijust...
I just want some...
God, no.
- What have you done?
- Don't touch me.
Let me go.
Please let me help you.
You've caused me so much pain.
I've suffered you long enough.
We could've been a family, had a child,
but you destroy everything you touch.
Ijust want
- peace.
- No.
Lee. No.
You can join her
to show her how much you truly love her.
Don't let her die hating you.
It's what she would want.
It's the only way to show her, love her.
Cut deep.
Cut deep. It's what she would want.
Cut deep and find peace.
Don't let her die.
- Follow her to death.
- No.
She wouldn't say that.
She wouldn't want that. She loves me.
- Cut deep and find peace.
- No.
She loves me. She loves me.
She wouldn't want that. She loves me.
No.
Crane? Where are you?
Crane?
How did you do it?
How did you defeat the toxin?
It's impossible!
I overcame my fear.
Liar.
You liar!
You can'tjust stop being afraid.
You can only become your demon
like I did.
No.
You have a choice, Jonathan.
And whatever your father was,
he didn't want this for you.
You need help.
My father thought that I was weak.
My whole life.
Scared little Jonathan.
Okay.
I can help you.
Let me help you.
But I'm not weak anymore.
And I will never go back
to being that boy.
(DISTANT LAUGHTER)
MAN 1: Come on, man.
MAN 2: Right this way.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Just around the corner.
I'm telling you, man.
He leaves the back gate open.
Ha-ha! It's gonna be too easy.
Well, well.
Seems we've caught our stalker.
And he made it way too easy.
Didn't know when he was being played.
Who are you, huh?
Some... Some Boy Scout?
He'sjust a kid.
Some kind of do-gooder?
Did I date your mom
and not call her back?
(ALL LAUGH)
Why you hassling us, kid?
I don't know, guys.
His face, it seems familiar.
You famous or something?
You know we got licenses for this, kid?
We're all above board.
- Penguin gets his share.
- That's right.
It's within our rights
to do anything we want to you.
Anything.
Look what you went and did.
You've seen my stash.
You've ticked off my boys.
Now, you're gonna die.
Wait.
I'm telling you, I know this kid's face.
Would you shut the hell up?
Hey, I'm telling you,
I've seen this dude.
Don't matter.
No matter who he is,
he's gotta go.
- (YELLS)
- (GUNSHOT)
Get up!
Think you're s0 slick, huh?
Now, I hate to tell you,
"I told you so," Master Bruce.
Up you get.
We gotta leave.
She said she's sorry.
She chose Nygma over me and Butch.
So? Nygma's a popsicle now.
Let's give her a chance.
Why do you want this so bad?
Because I'm sick and tired
of not being taken seriously.
AII those selfish guys out there
who treat me like I'm stupid?
Alone, I can't do much about it.
With Barbara, maybe.
But with you and Barbara?
The three of us could give
all those creeps a run for their money.
Iwant in.
- Get out.
- No. Please, just hear me out.
No.
You're a Penguin stooge.
What? I hate that freak.
Oh, please, you guzzled down
his Kool-Aid. Beat it.
No one takes me seriously, either.
There's nothing
Iwouldn't do to get back
at the men who treated me like garbage.
Nothing.
Not buying it.
You're working for Penguin.
Cool down, okay? I believe her.
Thank you.
Know what?
You're rude.
And you're about to get your skinny ass
kicked down the block.
I won't ask again.
Get out.
(nooa CLOSES)
Get word to Barbara. I'II talk business.
But I'II need something in return.
GORDON: Crane?
- CRANE: The demon is here.
- Crane?
CRANE: The demon who haunts
and tortures you is here.
The one who poisoned your minds.
Destroy him and free yourself
from his tyranny.
(SCREECHING)
Kill him!
Water. Right.
(SCREAMING)
WOMAN: I'm so happy.
Jonathan.
- You could've been killed.
- But I wasn't.
That's 'cause I followed you.
I had it under control.
How am I supposed to suppen you
if you refuse
to accept the realities
of the situation?
Alfred, the realities of the situation...
(KNOCKING ON moon)
Mr. Fox.
Bad time?
No. Not at all.
Please come in.
Forgive me.
I should have called, but...
Well, Ijust couldn't stop thinking
about our last chat.
Wayne Enterprises were developing
a durable material
for military uniforms
when I worked there.
It is a thin Kevlar weave
with reinforced forearm protection.
The gloves have a faceted grip design
to help you cling to any surface.
The whole uniform
is extremely lightweight
and actually bulletproof to impacts
from 10 feet or more.
You know, for rock climbing.
Oh, and long-distance
radio communicators.
In case you two wish
to talk to each other
whilst climbing rock.
Well, I will not keep you.
I just didn't want to see you
get hurt again, Mr. Wayne.
Thank you, Mr. Fox.
I feel safer already.
Ladies. Thank you for returning.
I'm glad...
Not so fast.
I'II be needing proof of your sincerity.
Yes. Selena said you would
need something from me.
- You can have anything you like.
- Fine.
I'II take your hand.
My what?
Both Butch and I lost a hand due
to Penguin's Machiavellian war games.
I believe it's your turn.
- You didn't say anything about this.
- Quiet.
- Tabitha, I assure you...
- No more words.
Penguin cut off Butch's hand,
Nygma mine.
Now I take yours.
Fine.
If this is the only way
I can get you to trust me,
so be it.
Fine.
I'II trust you.
For now.
I'II start Monday.
PENGUIN: Where is he?
We had a deal, Detective Gordon.
That you would apprehend Jonathan Crane.
You made a demand
in front of your cronies
in an attempt to undermine
me and this department.
There was no deal.
I spoke for all of
the citizens of Gotham
when I said that the GCPD
can no longer keep us safe.
How many of you are sick
of risking your lives every day
just to see criminals escape?
How many times has this very building
become a war zone?
(INDISTINCT MURMURING)
I say it is time to start anew.
To police ourselves.
I will triple the wage
of any cop here who wants to work for me
in ensuring the safety
of this city's people.
The future is now.
Follow me into it.
Police yourselves.
He just wants to pay you
to look the other way.
Would you blame them if they did?
- I've got nothing to say to you.
- Hey, hey, hey.
This is a war, not one battle.
If I would've went with you,
I would've lost them.
And we need them to win this war.
Now, you don't have to say nothing,
but I am buying you a drink.
Oh, no, not you. Leave!
You never paid
for the last stuff I gave you.
You make me smell perfume.
Make me giddy. Cheap trick!
Out! Out!
I'm done with perfumes.
I'm here for the good stuff.
Don't know what you're talking about.
Leave! I'm closing up.
Word is you have potions here.
Ancient, mystical potions
made by shamans all over the world.
Who told you that?
I'm done playing nice.
I need a change. A big one.
I need strength, power.
No..
Where are they?
My safe.
Under the register.
- Combinationil
- It's open.
Which ones make me stronger?
That's dangerous stuff.
It's too powerful for you.
It can get in your blood, your DNA.
Good.
No!
Stop! No!
No, you must stop!
(PANTING)
You let me walk into
that nightmare alone.
Yeah, well, I figured it would take
more than a couple of loonies
to take you out.
Besides, I figured you and me
taking on Penguin
and the entire criminal underground
by ourselves wasn't the best idea.
So, what, you wanna sit here,
do nothing, get drunk?
- Is that your plan?
- Unless you got a better one.
What makes you think those cops
back there were wrong?
Are we really making a difference?
One worth risking our lives over?
We'd need an army to take on Penguin.
Makes me miss Falcone.
I mean, I know he's a vicious bastard,
but he was... He was fair.
He ran the criminals in this city
with an iron fist. There was...
There was honor.
- No.
- What?
Do not mess with Falcone.
You killed his son, remember?
Italians do not forget that crap.
He must hate what Penguin's doing
as much as we do.
You show your face to Falcone,
he will kill you.
Yeah, well...
Like you said, we need an army.
He's got one.
(OVER RADIO) That's a lovely leap,
Master Bruce. Positively gazelle-like.
It's so lightweight,
it's like I'm wearing nothing at all.
(GRUNTS)
Yeah, well, let's not get ahead
of ourselves.
Remember to keep your face covered
at all times.
Try wearing that mask I made you.
English - SDH