- Previously on "Gotham"...
- Where are you, Ed?
What's green and red
and goes round and round?
Zebra with a gaping hole.
Your brilliant mind is as damaged
as the rest of your body.
(chuckles): I guess she was right.
You're not smart!
We'd need an army to take on Penguin.
Makes me miss Falcone.
SOFIA: You came looking for a gangster.
That's exactly what you found.
I'm a Falcone.
I need to know what you're going to do.
You want the city back from Penguin,
I'll give that to you.
Did you really think
I wouldn't figure it out?
The two of you have been whispering
like teenagers for weeks.
You never deserved her
in the first pl...
BARBARA: Yes, I killed him.
I am sorry.
There's a legend about this knife.
The man that killed my grandfather
can't have this.
I promise.
That's Ra's al Ghul.
RA'S AL GHUL: That knife
is the key to everything.
Give me the knife
and I will release the boy.
- Bruce, hand me the knife.
- I can't.
(screams)
(siren wailing)
DRIVER: So, who's the vegetable?
ORDERLY: Ah, used to be a gangster.
Name's, uh, Gilzean. Maybe Gold?
Took a slug in the noodle.
Been in a coma six months.
So, hospital brass wants
to free up some beds?
Yeah, say take him upstate.
(both laughing)
Rest in peace, Butch Gilzean.
Cyrus Gold. (laughs)
Whoever the hell you are.
(both laughing)
♪ ♪
Hey, Harvey.
Has anyone contacted you
about Ra's al Ghul?
No.
I just heard from Judge Bam Bam's clerk.
- His trial got pushed off the docket.
- And?
And I want to make sure
him being minister
of a foreign country doesn't
let him weasel out of this.
He killed a boy.
That's above my pay grade, pal.
I just, uh, bust the bad guys.
Do you?
These are release forms.
Of my collars.
Let me guess,
each one of them has a license
from Penguin, right?
Jim, I am stuck between
a rock and a hard place.
Every mook you bust with a
license, the commissioner
orders me to let him go.
What am I supposed to do?
- Your job!
- I am doing my job!
HARPER: Gordon, got a call
from the judge's clerk;
it's about Ra's al Ghul.
Here.
I'm doing my job.
Master Bruce.
No sleep?
Again?
Once more, about that boy's death...
Don't say it's not my fault.
It is my fault.
Alex is dead because I hesitated.
Well, perhaps you did,
but that doesn't make you
his murderer, does it?
Ra's killed that innocent little boy,
and he's gonna pay for it.
You really think locking him up
in Blackgate will stop him?
He still wants this dagger.
Stop going on about
the bloody dagger, will you?
Just so we can just get some breakfast.
- Please.
- I think I finally found something
in Dr. Winthrop's notes.
There's a description on the handle
that Dr. Winthrop was able to decipher.
Says the knife is intended for the one
who has bathed in the healing waters.
Right. Well, assuming that's not me,
that must be our boy Ra's.
But that doesn't have
to mean it's for him to use.
Perhaps it's to be used against him.
I see.
No.
You clearly don't.
What you're suggesting is
that knife and that knife alone
is the only thing capable
of doing him in.
If Ra's al Ghul believes
this knife will kill him,
that could explain why
he wants it so badly.
So he can destroy it.
Before someone fulfills the prophecy.
Master Bruce, I know that
you feel bad about Alex.
We all do.
But at this point, you
must remember your vow.
No killing.
Taking a life, never mind how justified,
will lead you down
a darker path than
you could ever possibly imagine.
I know. I've been down it.
You understand me, Master Bruce?
I understand.
Good.
Let's get yourself ready.
Chop, chop.
WOMAN: Such a tragedy.
He was only a child
and always so lovely.
A heinous crime
perpetrated against
such an innocent boy.
WOMAN: And his grandfather,
murdered just the day before.
MAN: I know, I know.
ALFRED: I'll just be
a moment, Master Bruce.
Diplomatic immunity?
You are joking, aren't you?
The Nanda Parbat embassy filed
papers to have him extradited.
Could happen this week.
- That monster killed a child.
- I know.
I was there.
Look... I am telling you
this as a courtesy.
- Oh.
- But the news will get out.
When it does, I need you to watch Bruce.
I'm worried about him.
And you blame me?
You're his guardian, aren't you?
You're supposed to protect him,
and instead you've been
placing him in harm's way.
ALFRED: Oh, I see. So that's
what rankles, is it?
Keeping you in the dark.
Well, if I was you,
I'd focus on your own job, Detective,
which is keeping Ra's al Ghul
behind bars, tucked up.
Just keep the news away
from Bruce as long as you can.
On that, we agree, Detective.
The boy's been through enough.
♪ ♪
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com
(door buzzing)
Thank you for coming, Barbara.
Hell of a chicken coop.
So, what's the angle?
How about this?
Say the word,
we'll be home drinking
Chianti by dinnertime.
I think I'll decline.
So why did you call me here?
To say good-bye.
When I brought you back to life,
I asked you to be
my eyes and ears in Gotham.
You became so much more.
Save it.
What about everything you promised me?
"Do as I ask and I will give you
a gift beyond your imagining."
(low rumbling)
(gasping softly)
(whispers): What the hell was that?
You'll see.
Good-bye, Barbara.
(door closes)
(water bubbling)
(frogs croaking, insects trilling)
♪ ♪
(grunts)
- ♪ Born on a Monday ♪
- (record playing music)
♪ Christened on a Tuesday ♪
♪ Married on a Wednesday ♪
♪ Took ill on Thursday ♪
♪ Grew worse on Friday ♪
♪ Died on Saturday ♪
- ♪ Buried on Sunday... ♪
- Sweet mother of Mary.
Never seen nothing like him before.
- He's white as a picket fence.
- (grunts)
Easy. We ain't gonna hurt you.
What happened
to your drawers, big fella?
- (shouts)
- Easy.
(grunts)
No!
(growls softly)
We're gonna get you, you freak!
Who... are you?
(record skips)
♪ Born on a Monday ♪
♪ Christened on Tuesday ♪
♪ Married on Wednesday ♪
♪ Tool ill on Thursday ♪
♪ Grew worse on Friday ♪
- ♪ Died on Sat... ♪
- (record skips)
♪ Solomon Grundy ♪
♪ Born on a Monday... ♪
GILZEAN: Solomon... Grundy.
- ♪ Solomon Grundy ♪
- Born...
on Monday.
♪ Born on a Monday ♪
♪ Solomon Grundy ♪
License compliance
amongst the GCPD remains high.
The program is an unmitigated success.
Numbers, Mr. Penn.
A-According to my tabulations,
86% of crime is accounted for
under Pax Penguina.
Which means that 14% of crime
happens outside of my licensing system!
Uh... the numbers are
very good, Mr. Cobblepot.
Get Firefly. I want examples made!
Yes, that might help.
But, then, if scorching a
few idiots was all it took,
anyone could rule Gotham.
Thank you for your
insight, Miss Falcone.
I don't recall summoning you.
I came to see if you had
lunch plans tomorrow.
An invitation?
After...
I killed your father's
last remaining loyalists?
(chuckles): Perhaps you
overestimate the pleasure
of your company.
Oswald...
you may think you have everything,
but there is one thing you don't have.
The Falcone name.
A name that once accounted
for all criminal activity
in Gotham... as in...
one hundred percent.
Now you're just rubbing it in.
I propose we have lunch
somewhere public.
By doing so, you'll show
Gotham that you have
the support of the Falcone family.
And that should be enough to send
those outlying criminal elements
scurrying back under your umbrella.
Mr. Penn, item number
four on my to-do list.
"Kill Sofia Falcone."
Add a question mark, will you?
Tomorrow it is.
Come on, you people have
pills for everything!
Insomnia, anxiety! You have
to have something for me!
I don't know, a pill
to reverse the effect
of having your brain
frozen and unfrozen?
That's kind of specific.
(bottle shatters)
I will not be condescended to
by an idiot in a lab coat!
You're not even a doctor!
Okay, relax, man.
Just... tell me your symptoms.
Fogginess of the mind.
Decreased capacity
to think ten steps ahead.
Inability to solve riddles!
God.
I have got to improve my brain function.
I could take a pill or a vitamin.
I'll even consider a natural remedy.
I don't want to get your hopes
up, but there is something.
What? Tell me.
A trial drug.
It claims to boost your
natural cognitive abilities.
That's perfect. Where is this?
The sample drawer.
What is it called?
Uh, Smartivia.
Blue pills, diamond-shaped.
Smartivia. Smartivia.
I don't see them.
Try towards the back.
I don't see it.
Ah, here it is.
Ow!
Oh! God!
(pained grunting)
A fake gun?
Seriously?
Ow! Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I just need to know.
- Do these work?
- No, dummy.
They're sugar pills.
And I'm calling the police.
(groans)
(alarm blaring)
Go on, do it, do it...
(groans, pants)
(siren approaching)
(low growl)
(panting)
- (growls)
- Oh!
Butch.
You... know Grundy?
Butch...
I have never had an issue with you.
Barbara Kean... she is the problem.
You and Tabitha are innocent bystanders.
Wow, you don't get much sun.
No...
Man talk too much.
(sirens wailing in distance)
- Collins, deal with this, will you?
- Yep.
Gordon.
Bruce is gone.
- What?
- You've got to get me into Blackgate.
What are you talking about?
When we got back from the
wake, he said he was gonna go
straight to bed, but he must've
snuck out between then and now.
My concern is that he's
taken the knife...
and he's gonna try and kill
Ra's al Ghul.
You're serious?
Yes, I'm bloody serious.
We've got to go to Blackgate now.
And then you can tell me the many ways
I've failed the child, all right?
- Oh, I will.
- Listen to me.
The boy is on the verge
of doing something
that there's no coming back from.
He needs our help.
Right.
Let's go.
(dogs barking)
Yeah, it's about time.
Shift ended five minutes ago.
Come on.
(lock clacks)
(beep)
(soft whooshing)
♪ ♪
(sheathes knife)
You weak...
foolish... boy.
You're still not ready.
(coughs)
My name is Bruce Wayne.
Stop him. Stop him.
Master al Ghul.
Take him below.
What? What are you doing?
We got your call, but...
I checked the logs...
- Bruce Wayne hasn't been here.
- With all due respect,
I don't think he'd come
as a regular visitor.
He's a billionaire, after all.
I think what Mr. Pennyworth
is trying to say is
Bruce Wayne could have paid
someone to get him in here.
No offense.
We just want to look around.
Sure. Whatever you want.
But you came all the way here
for nothing.
And we're gonna need your weapons.
Standard procedure.
Of course.
(clears throat)
- Finished?
- That's absolutely it.
Unless you want to check
my undercrackers.
This way.
(whispers): Undercrackers?
(lock buzzes, latch clicks)
They're here.
(sirens wailing)
(car horns honking in distance)
(groans)
(pained gasps)
Sugar pills, my foot.
That dream was horrible.
Oh, God!
Oh, you're real. (gasping)
Oh...
You... know...
...Grundy?
What? No. No.
No, who's Grundy?
Solomon Grundy.
Born on Monday.
Your hand! How...
I'm sorry.
What happened to you?
Grundy not know.
Okay, let me get this straight.
You don't... remember...
who you are
or how you got here?
(laughs)
I'm sorry.
Grundy...
I don't know you. Best of luck, though.
Hope you get the skin thing
figured out. Later.
(groans)
Ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
You know Grundy.
You help Grundy.
Be...
Grundy...
friend.
I'm attempting to be civil...
but I can't help you.
Why?
I just can't, all right?
- Why?
- Because...
Why?!
Because I can't even help myself!
Ow.
You don't know who you are.
Well, that makes two of us.
I used to be smart... brilliant...
and now that's gone.
I can't even rob a pharmacy!
So you want me to help you?
I can't.
Well, I am feeling a pit peckish.
We are closed.
Janos.
Last I saw you was at my tenth birthday.
You bought me ruby earrings.
Said it would be a fitting gift
for the daughter of the king of Gotham.
Sofia Falcone.
I heard you had returned to Gotham.
What can I do for you?
I was wondering how you were faring
under Penguin's rule.
The Szabo family is quite content
under Oswald Cobblepot's
licensing system.
But even if we were not,
we would be wise enough
not to say anything.
Good. Because I've invited him
to your restaurant for lunch,
and I want it to be a lunch
he'll never forget.
RA'S AL GHUL: Bruce.
BRUCE: Where am I?
Beneath Blackgate Penitentiary.
Alfred Pennyworth and Jim Gordon
are upstairs in the company,
unbeknownst to them, of my men.
Let them go.
They have nothing to do with this.
Still playing
the white knight, Bruce.
You replaced the guards
before I got here.
I'm sure your friends
can fend for themselves.
You applied for diplomatic immunity,
knowing I'd hear about it
and come for you.
I wanted the knife,
but not for the reason you think.
It's been ages since
I first held this dagger.
It was given to me
moments after I was bathed
in the Lazarus Pit.
Submerged in the waters...
(gasps)
...suspended between
life and death,
I saw a vision of you...
...my heir.
You're insane.
I'm not your heir.
I don't even understand what that means.
It means that you are the only one
who can end my suffering.
Please.
You want me to kill you?
Set me free.
Well, thanks for the snack, big guy.
It's been an emotional day.
I got to go.
- No.
- Oh.
Not this again. Come on!
God... I've told you,
I'm better off on my own,
and you are, too.
So let go!
Let go!
MAN: Hey, freak.
Ha, I knew we'd find you.
And it looks like you got a friend.
(chuckles) I assure you,
we are not friends.
MAN: Get 'em.
Both of 'em.
No! No!
(grunting, screaming)
Grundy!
(screaming)
- (screaming)
- Hot... hot!
Grundy friend, help!
Don't leave, no. Help. Help.
Hot.
Hot... hot...
- (steam hissing)
- (sighing)
Grundy friend not dumb.
Grundy friend... smart.
Well, I guess...
...yeah, you're right.
Water beats fire. (laughs)
That was smart. (chuckles)
Oh, boy...
(grunts)
(straining): I can't breathe.
(horn honks, siren wails)
Oswald. They said this is
their best table.
Interesting choice.
Are you sure it's not too intimate?
The point was to get the word out
that the Falcones support me.
Don't worry, people will talk.
I chose this place
because I heard your mother
was Hungarian.
I thought you might like
a taste of home.
I can assure you, Oswald,
I'm not here to poison you.
Perhaps.
(coughing)
The chef likes to go heavy
on the paprika, doesn't he?
(coughing)
How is the food, otherwise?
Serviceable.
Well, I'm stuffed.
Thank you so much
for meeting me, Miss Falcone.
(louder): And thank you to your
family for their support.
You can't leave until
you've tried the goulash.
If it's anything like
the chicken paprika,
- I'll pass.
- It's the house specialty.
(sighs)
My mother made goulash.
Brought the recipe from Budapest.
Handed down through her family
for 300 years.
I doubt this will hold a candle.
- I'm leaving!
- SOFIA: Oswald?
Oswald?
It took me forever
to find his mother's recipe.
Did you follow it exactly?
I followed the recipe to a T.
The little man didn't like?
Honestly, I don't know.
GORDON: How long have you worked here?
Two years, thereabouts.
I was in Blackgate for a time.
We must not have overlapped.
Here? As a guard?
As a prisoner.
Oh, yeah. Heard about that.
Is there a reason why
you're not taking us
through maximum security?
Prisoners are in the yard
this time of day.
Been some changes since you were here.
"McCloskey."
That's funny.
I know another J. McCloskey
who works here.
My cousin. Gets confusing sometimes.
All right, let's go.
- Through this door.
- ALFRED: I got to say, mate,
I really love what you've
done with the old place.
However, I've got a question for you.
Yeah?
Where are the real guards?
(grunting)
(gunshots)
Where is Bruce Wayne?
Ra's al Ghul has plans for the boy.
Where is he?!
(laughs) You'll never find him.
Oh, you underestimate my resolve, pal.
Well, at least we know Bruce is here.
Well, we've walked the floor.
Where could he be?
There's the yard,
the tower... but they're too public.
There's a sub-basement,
accessible by the service elevator.
Which way?
(car horns honking in distance)
(door opens)
(scoffs)
Who did I tell you specifically
not to let in here?!
Uh, Miss Falcone is here
to see you, sir.
I'm sorry, Oswald.
I'm not sure what upset you, but I...
Enough!
Did you think I would really believe
this was all some coincidence?
That goulash tasted exactly
like my mother used to make!
You can't fault me for
the restaurant's authenticity.
You're buttering me up.
But for what?
Is it so hard to believe
that someone would want to do
something nice for you?
There was only one person
in my whole life
who ever did things for me
without wanting something in return.
And that was my mother.
Then I envy you.
My father never helped anyone
unless it benefited him.
And eventually it drove away
everyone who loved him.
Go.
I'll decide what to do with you later.
Oswald, I only want to help you.
Oh, you want to help? Try leaving.
(sniffles)
Your foot.
It's just the weather.
(exhales)
What are you doing?
- Don't.
- It's okay.
I won't judge.
When I was a child, I broke my ankle
while playing with my cousins.
I was desperate.
Crying in pain.
My father told me to put ice on it.
Toughen up, stop with the tears.
But my mother went with me
to the hospital.
And on the way, she told me
that cold actually increases the pain.
What's needed is warmth.
My mother.
She used to sing.
(humming)
RA'S AL GHUL: This may be
hard for you to understand.
But I have walked this earth
for centuries.
Waiting for you, Bruce.
Only you can kill me.
And only with that dagger.
That is my curse.
That is the meaning of my vision.
I don't believe you.
Believe me.
This is just another manipulation.
See.
Look.
My true form.
Every moment of my life
is agony.
End my suffering.
Whatever your curse is,
you deserve it for what you've done.
You're angry, Bruce. I understand.
But unless you strike me down
with that blade,
you will never be free.
No!
I won't.
Then allow me to tell you
what will happen...
...if you don't kill me.
I will disappear
and let you live your life.
You will follow the path of light.
Grow into a fine man.
Become a husband.
A father.
There may be a day
when you forget I ever existed.
But then I will return.
And I will kill everyone you love.
Just as you watched your parents die,
just as you watched me
slice your friend's throat,
I will slaughter your wife and children
before your very eyes,
and there will be nothing
you can do about it.
(shouts)
- Die.
- (dagger slices)
(yells)
Yes.
(panting)
(crackling)
MAN (over speaker):
Attention, all inmates.
The prison is on official lockdown.
(continues indistinctly)
Are you going to arrest me?
For what?
For murder.
I don't know what I just saw in there.
But as far as I'm concerned,
Ra's al Ghul's men broke
into Blackgate and he escaped.
I betrayed myself
and my parents' memory.
I took a life.
I did exactly what Ra's said I would.
Just because you know you're
capable of doing something
doesn't mean it has to happen again.
Bruce, you and I have known
each other a long time.
Since the night
your parents were murdered.
Now, you may not feel
like you're that kid anymore,
but I know that you are.
One who believes in doing good.
In fighting for what's right.
Who will do anything to keep
the people he loves safe.
Nothing that happened today
changes that.
What are you doing?
You said it yourself.
It's over.
No.
- Can't let you do that, Master Bruce.
- Alfred.
Listen, we started
this vigilante caper to prepare
for Ra's' return, didn't we?
But it's become
so much bigger than that.
I see that now. I mean,
I was wrong and you were right.
You can make a difference.
I'm not the hero Gotham needs.
I made that decision the
moment I killed Ra's al Ghul.
I took the dark path.
Yes, you did.
And it's gonna be
a long, bumpy journey back.
But I believe in you, Master Bruce.
I always have, and I... I always will.
Now, I understand
that you don't feel worthy now.
But when you do, this...
...this will be waiting for you.
As will I, sir.
(car horns honking)
(rock music playing in distance)
NYGMA: Those guys that attacked us
didn't even have five bucks between 'em.
(scoffs) We need a new plan.
What?
Truth.
Grundy friend...
know Grundy?
You deserve to know.
You and I...
...were the very best of friends.
And then something happened to you.
And I just didn't recognize you.
But what is important
is that, with your muscles,
we can make money.
And with money,
we can make me smart again.
And then we'll figure out
what happened to you.
Just trust me. Okay?
Grundy, come on.
("I Wanna Be Your Dog"
by The Stooges playing)
♪ So messed up, I want you here ♪
(people shouting, whooping)
♪ In my room ♪
♪ I want you here ♪
♪ And now I wanna ♪
- ♪ Be your dog ♪
- Yeah, come on!
♪ Now I wanna ♪
♪ Be your dog ♪
♪ Be your dog... ♪
(wrestler yelling)
(shouts)
What is this, a knitting circle?
Let's see some blood!
Hey, I'm looking
for the person in charge here.
You're looking at her.
What do you want, squirt?
Well, if there's money to be had,
we'd like to put our hat in the ring.
(laughs)
And who are you?
I'm... hey.
I'm this fine gentleman's manager.
Trust me, he's a monster.
Well, more grist for the mill.
CROWD: Seven, eight...
We'll get you patched up.
Then we'll talk.
Hey.
Go get the doc.
All right, one, two, three.
♪ Now I wanna... ♪
Hey, Doc.
Cherry wants you to come
look at some new guy.
THOMPKINS: I'll be right there.
♪ Now I wanna ♪
♪ Be your dog ♪
♪ Well, come on ♪
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com