Previously on Gotham...
I need to siphon his strength
so when the time is right,
taking over his organization will be
like slipping on a glove.
The point wasn't to
steal that money, Butch.
It was to hurt Falcone.
- What's her name?
- Selina Kyle.
- So, she saw everything?
- Yes.
Her being here will put
Master Bruce in great danger.
She's also the best chance we have
of finding who killed my parents.
You are gonna keep working for Fish.
You are gonna tell me
every little thing that she says.
Lovecraft, I have an eyewitness
who can tie you to the crime.
You and all the others involved.
So, tell me, Dent, who did I kill?
Thomas and Martha Wayne.
You lost, miss?
This is Wayne Manor?
Yeah, but not sure you should be here.
Point you back to the road if you're lost.
No, thanks.
I am where I need to be.
Shh...
Open him.
Keep it tight here.
Better?
Better.
If you want to test yourself,
you should come with me
to the Midtown Bridge.
You've climbed it?
Yeah, to the top.
Kids go up there to make out.
All the time.
I could take you, if you want.
Okay.
I'd like that.
Let me ask you a question.
What's up with all the weird
homework about your mom and dad?
I'm trying to understand why it happened.
There's no why.
Bad stuff happens.
You-you got to get over it.
Maybe you're right.
Of course I'm right.
You want to kiss me?
No, thank you.
No?
I would like to,
but I can't help feeling
you have an ulterior motive.
I don't imagine you consider me
a suitable romantic partner, so
why would you want to kiss me?
I don't know.
You think too much, kid.
I'm just trying to be nice.
No offense, you don't
strike me as a nice person.
What do you mean?
I'm nice.
I don't mean you're not a good
person, but you're not nice.
You don't care much for other people.
Screw you, orphan.
Climb the damn bridge on your own.
Yes, hello, miss. How can I help?
Oh, dear.
My car, it went off the road.
Please...
Please come in. Come in at once.
If you could call an ambulance.
Where exactly are you hurt?
Alfred.
Is everything all right?
No, Master Bruce.
This lady's been involved
in a car accident.
Run. Run!
This better be a way out.
The old servant's hallway,
it's through the closet.
But I need to help Alfred!
There's no time!
Bruce, come on!
Alfred might be hurt.
I can't leave him.
He told you to run.
Fine.
Stay, but I'm out.
Bruce!
Local PD is searching the woods,
but so far no sign of Bruce or Selina.
What can you tell me about this woman?
Well, she was, uh, early 30s.
A tasty fighter, actually.
Look, mate, it's just a scratch.
Shove off, will you?
I've got stuff to do.
Look, we've got 50 police in the
woods, even more on the roads.
We need to focus on this
woman and her people.
What can you tell me about her?
They were trained killers.
And your bloody little
girl brought them here.
We don't know that yet.
Jim.
You must be Alfred Pennyworth.
Nice job out there.
Yeah, well, not nice enough, eh?
This was taken off the dead guy.
Nothing else... no keys, no I.D., nada.
Now, I know this girl.
She was grabbed by the child snatchers.
And now she's getting attacked by assassins
at Wayne freaking Manor?!
What the hell's going on, compadre?
What, you haven't told him?
Told me what?
Selina Kyle was in the alley the
night the Waynes were murdered.
She saw the killer's face.
Oh, for Pete's sake, don't do this to me.
Harvey Dent in the D.A.'s office
is investigating Dick Lovecraft.
He thinks that Lovecraft is
connected to the Wayne killings.
So, he leaked that we had a witness.
He thought he could spook Lovecraft.
Get him to reveal himself.
Wow, that's a hell of a plan.
How did it work out? Bravo!
We thought she was safe.
We thought no one knew she was here.
Yeah, well, you were wrong,
weren't you, you plank?
How did they know?
Why didn't you tell me
about this foolishness?
Because you would have tried to stop me.
Of course I would tried
to stop you, you putz!
What the hell are you thinking?
The Wayne case is closed. It is closed!
You know damn well it's not
closed! Don't tell me what I know!
Will you shut up, the pair of ya!
You can argue later!
Right now, we need to find Master Bruce.
All right.
If they don't come back soon,
they would have headed to Gotham.
Selina feels safe there.
Good luck trying
to find her in the city.
A street kid like that?
But you will help us find her, right?
Yeah, of course I will.
Because I have to be crazy.
Thank you. All right,
I'll focus on Lovecraft,
I'll find him, and if he is
behind this, I'll get him
to call off the contract.
How you gonna do that? I don't
know, I'll think of something.
Run the streets, huh?
Focus on your contacts. Go to work.
I'm coming with you.
All right.
You're pretty handy for a valet.
Butler, mate.
I'm the butler.
We need to call Alfred.
You see any phones?
No.
Perhaps we should go back to my house.
If the police are there,
we'll know it's safe.
Yeah, right.
The police will make it safe?
We have to contact the
police at some point.
Someone tried to kill you.
Me?
Nobody knew I was there.
It's your house; Someone wants to kill you.
Duh.
Why would anyone want to kill me?
Must be all that lame
detective work you're doing.
Paid off good, huh?
Cheer up.
We're cool.
We lost them.
I'm worried about Alfred.
Relax.
Once I got you safely hidden in the city,
I'll find you a phone.
Thank you.
I appreciate your help.
Hey...
just trying to be nice.
How did Maroni know where my money was?
Wha...
Well, that's a very good question.
Not to criticize, but you
could have just called me.
I'm going to ask you once more.
How did Maroni know where I
kept my money? No one knew.
The robbery at the armory.
That wasn't Maroni.
I thought we were friends.
We had an understanding.
You tell me every move Maroni makes.
What happened?
When did you turn on me?
Never, Don Falcone.
I swear, never.
Maroni had nothing to
do with the armory job.
I would know.
I would have told you.
Who was it if not Maroni?
And how did they know about my money?
Thank you, Liza.
Won't be long.
I'll come back.
I asked you a question.
Oh, you have a mole, obviously.
Which is not Maroni's forte, is it?
No, this is someone else.
Someone artful.
Someone close to you.
I know who you're going to name.
But your hatred of Fish makes me doubt
anything you say against her.
With respect...
I don't understand why you
still tolerate her existence.
She has proved her
disloyalty a hundred times.
She wants your head.
Like half the people who work for me.
Fish makes me a lot of money.
I can handle Fish Mooney,
or whatever son of a bitch did this to me.
Tell me how to find the mole.
You leave that to me, Don Falcone.
Dirty work.
I'll find your mole for you.
Trust me...
he'll belong to Fish.
Bring me proof.
I don't get it.
You, Gabe? Not get it?
Quelle suprise.
What, pray, don't you get?
Why not just tell Falcone the truth?
It was that Liza girl that betrayed him.
Timing, Gabriel.
Timing is everything.
And Liza is a time bomb.
Just...
wait a while.
Then watch and learn.
Stay there in case he shows.
Lovecraft isn't at home.
Housekeeper hasn't seen him
since yesterday. Allen says he didn't
come into his office. He
and Montoya are watching it.
How did the killers know
where to find my witness?
Let's keep calm here. It's a win.
We've made Lovecraft panic.
This is a panic move. A win?!
There's two children out there with
professional assassins coming after them.
Bruce and Selina could end up dead.
We're gonna get Lovecraft to call them off.
How did they know?
I never told you her name,
let alone where she was hiding,
so you couldn't have... I should say not.
And you never mentioned my name
to anyone, right?
No, we agreed.
I didn't mention any names out loud.
No names "out loud"?
What about whispering?
Don't hold out on me.
I'll know.
For deep background, I leaked your name
to a couple of select sources.
I had to, for credibility!
You're the Wayne murders cop.
Damn it! That's how they got to her.
I'm surprised it took
them this long to find her.
This is on you, Dent! Whoa.
I'll stipulate mea culpa.
Kick my ass, be my guest.
But let's find Lovecraft first
and get him to call off the killers.
He's not at home, he's not at his office.
He could've left Gotham.
Someone could be hiding him. Lovecraft...
has got a couple of condos
that he keeps under his mistress's name.
One up in Stevensburgh and one, uh, uptown.
I'll take the one uptown.
If anything's happened to these kids...
We know you ran with a girl
called Cat.
She's in serious danger.
Who isn't, right?
Crazy world.
How much?
There's $100.
All right, listen.
I don't know where Cat lives, all right?
She's... private
about stuff like that.
But... I heard that she got a new fence,
'cause her old one got popped.
He'd know where to find her.
Who's the fence?
I don't know.
But I know who would know.
Oh, yeah? Who's that?!
Damn it, Alfred, save your cheese!
I can beat the truth out of this kid
with a roll of quarters!
Yo, ask Fish Mooney.
She runs
all the fences.
Forgive me for shocking you,
but let me give you some context here.
I loved Bannion.
We came up together.
But he was supposed to guard
the armory, and he didn't.
And maybe, just maybe,
he looked the other way.
I don't know.
So what do I do?
Let it lie?
Boss, we understand...
Whoever else was involved
will very soon wish
they could die quickly, like Bannion.
In the meantime,
all of us must do what's
right for the family.
Each of your tariffs will increase 25%
until we've built the reserves again.
No disrespect, that's high.
A little bit.
What do you think, Fish? Am I being fair?
We're family.
We sink or swim together.
You could all learn from Fish.
She trusts me.
Trust me, and I'll trust you.
It goes both ways.
Let's eat.
There's a phone!
Come on!
I don't... I don't carry coins.
Do you have any coins?
Nope.
Not a dime.
Why does Alfred matter
so much to you anyway?
He's just your butler.
He's my family.
Good luck, kid. See you around maybe.
What?
Wait! Look...
those bad guys were there for me.
Not you.
You have nothing to worry about.
Go home.
But you said...
I was just trying to freak you out.
I was playing with you.
You were playing with me?
That's kind of cruel, isn't it?
Yeah.
No, look,
you're right about me.
I'm not nice.
Not like you.
You got a nice way about you.
"A nice way"? Yeah. That's why
I said that thing about
you being the target,
so, you know, we could
hang out a while longer.
I see.
It's very convoluted reasoning.
Whatever.
Anyhow, it's been cool.
I'm gonna disappear. But you can't do that!
I wasn't asking. You can't disappear!
You have to come back home with me.
When Detective Gordon finds the man
who killed my parents, you have to testify.
You really think that
was ever going to happen?
Grow up, B.
No, don't! You won't make it!
Help.
You're crazy.
Please don't run off again.
I'm out of breath.
Okay, kiddo.
You earned it.
You want to hang with me, that's cool,
but my world, my rules.
You do what I say.
Yes, ma'am.
Why can't I call Alfred
or Detective Gordon to
let them know I'm okay?
Because we're disappearing.
You got to be like smoke.
Smoke doesn't make phone calls.
What is this place? The Flea.
It's like the mall for street kids,
without the crappy music.
We'll be safe here till dark.
Falcone's making me nervous.
If he suspects it was
us who blew up his money,
why hasn't he made a move?
'Cause he can't be sure.
There are ten other people
who could have done this.
So what now?
You're going to stick to the plan.
You're gonna reach out
to Saviano and Turski.
They are both very angry
that their taxes have been raised,
and they're worried about
ending up like Bannion.
They're ready. The old man
is herding his sheep toward me.
You got it, boss.
All right.
Hello, gentlemen.
Busy day, Harvey. Come back next year.
Hand to God, Butch,
I'll be quicker than a
sailor on shore leave.
Thief we're tracking down.
Look familiar? Goes by "Cat."
Nope.
Maybe Fish knows her.
Fish knows everyone.
Fish is busy.
She works with one of
your fences, a new guy.
What's a fence?
Come on, Butch. Be nice.
This is important.
Where's Fish?
I told you, she's busy.
I once knew a fella
called Butch.
Yeah, he was a Whitechapel lad.
Now, we called him Butch,
you see, 'cause he wasn't.
It was a wind-up.
It was like a joke name.
In fact, he was a horrible little toe rag.
What?
I can't tell. Are-are you...
are you threatening me?
Is he threatening me?
Yeah?
You can't...
Now...
where is this Fish?
Right here.
So... what's the fuss?
They're just fooling around.
We're looking for this girl,
a street thief, goes by Cat,
works with one of your fences.
Looks familiar. What's the urgency?
Professional killers are looking for her.
Professionals, huh?
This wouldn't be the Lovecraft
witness, now would it?
How'd you know?
Streets talk.
Using her to scare Lovecraft.
She saw the Waynes' killer,
supposedly.
Yeah. Mm...
And you're here because you want me
to help you find her, don't you?
Yes.
Harvey...
Why in the world
would I help you find her,
of all people?
She has Bruce Wayne with her, miss.
Really?
Yes, miss.
I'm Alfred Pennyworth. I'm
the boy's legal guardian.
Very pleased to meet you. Likewise.
Miss Mooney, we need your help.
Well, you see, Alfred,
I would love to help you,
but it would infringe
upon my personal interests.
And why would I do that?
You have a very eloquent... gaze,
if I may say so, Miss Mooney.
And I can see that you're
not a woman that would
let petty self-interest outweigh... honor.
And compassion.
I'll make some calls.
But remember this kindness.
Much better.
Really?
I'm not sure.
You look badass.
No lie.
Hey, Cat.
Ivy...
what are you doing here?
What have you been up to? I thought...
Yeah, Juvie caught me.
I got adopted upstate.
Didn't take?
Good people... they wanted me
to cut my hair, dress nice.
I know you.
You're Mario Pepper's daughter.
Yes. Who are you?
I'm Bruce Wayne.
Yes, you are.
Billionaire Bruce Wayne.
Stay cool now, Ivy.
I am cool. Why are you telling me that?
Why are you telling me what to do?
I'm not. I'm just saying,
I don't want you to get mad at him.
He's a friend.
Why would I get mad at him?
It's not his fault, is it?
Did you kill my father?
Do you make my mother cut her wrists?
No.
Somebody did... somebody did,
but not him.
How you doing? You doing okay?
I'm okay. And you?
I'm doing great. How do I look?
You look good.
Have you seen Clyde the fence around?
Yeah, he's working
out of the Factory on the Narrows.
He's cute, isn't he?
Yes, he is. Uh, thanks, Ivy.
Good to see you. Uh, we
got to go run and see Clyde.
Oh. Okay, fine. Bye, then.
Keep moving.
She's just a little girl.
Why are you so scared of her?
Because she's scary. Don't look back.
GCPD!
Drop it.
Kick it over.
You're under arrest.
Conspiracy to commit murder.
Murder? Me, murder?
Look, what are you talking about?
You put a hit out on Selina Kyle.
No, not me.
The same people that came
after her came after me, too.
Th-They attacked me on the street.
Why do you think I'm hiding in here?
Why would they come after you?
Why do they ever come?
Because I know too much.
Cut the crap. Who are you so scared of?
You have no idea, do you?
You think I'm the big wheel.
When it comes to the crunch, kid,
I'm nobody, just like you.
A-And the people
who really, truly run this city,
they're watching you huff and
puff and run around crusading,
and they are laughing at you.
You're so deep in the maze,
you can't see over the wall.
Tell me something I don't know.
My briefcase, under the bed. Files.
Go.
Right before the Waynes got killed,
there was a run on Wayne Enterprises stock.
Like somebody knew something
bad was gonna happen.
So I figured I deserved a cut.
So I started digging.
I've come for that man.
You need not get hurt.
Mm... that was nice.
Let's do it again sometime.
Yeah?
Fish got a lead on the kids,
at a place on the Narrows
called The Factory.
Word is, Cat used a fence named Clyde.
He hangs there. We're on our way now.
Alfred, let's go.
Fish, thank you.
You owe me.
Who don't I owe?
Mr. Lovecraft?
No, no, no, no, no.
This is Detective Gordon.
Badge number 23-16-11.
Reporting body at 1257 Antioch.
Cat! My baby!
Hey, Clyde. Well...
what have you got for me?
Hey! Shh!
Wow.
Sweet swag.
Not your usual junk.
Moving on up.
Where'd you get this?
You want a story or the swag?
How much?
Thousand bucks.
Please. Give me a break.
That's rock-bottom, you know it is.
Fifty bucks.
Fifty?
This pen is real gold,
and that's an antique jade netsuke.
It's worth $2,000 on its own.
And who is this
well-spoken little... dude?
Never mind who he is.
Look, 500 is rock-bottom.
Why are you wasting my time?
Relax.
I'm sure we can... make a deal.
No, thanks. We'll go elsewhere.
Cool down, Cat.
Or we'll poke your
little friend's eyes out.
That's it.
Relax.
I've got some friends coming over
who would just love to meet you.
It's all there.
Don't look so anxious.
Yeah, well, um... you
guys are kind of sporty.
Where is she?
She's upstairs.
She better be.
Find me something heavy.
Am I the only one in this damn
town who waits for backup?!
Bruce!
Follow!
Where's Alfred?
He's in there.
Go!
Down!
Where's your girlfriend?
I have no idea.
Don't make me hurt you.
You're not on the contract.
She's gone.
Some advice, kid:
Don't ever mistake bravery for good sense.
Alfred.
Fancy seeing you here.
You all right?
I'm fine.
How are you?
You really scared me, Master Bruce.
If you die...
who employs butlers anymore?
Oh, thank God.
Lovecraft was a beloved
pillar of this community.
A dedicated servant of Gotham.
So, what do I tell the media, huh?
Hmm?!
Any ideas?
He was a crook.
We nearly had him.
And he was killed by whoever
he would have implicated
if he had lived to testify.
Say that.
Forgive me if I can't
get behind your approach.
It was your gun.
I didn't kill him.
On balance, I believe you... on balance.
But suicide is much cleaner...
It wasn't suicide, it was murder!
It was suicide!
He went mad
under your relentless questioning,
overpowered you
and killed himself with your gun.
And don't tell me otherwise.
What do you say, counselor?
I'm at your disposal, Mayor James.
I'm sorry if we've caused you any disquiet.
"Disquiet."
You arrogant clowns.
You're hacking away at the
very foundations of this city.
Trying to take me down!
Should have the both
of you stuffed in a sack
and thrown in the river.
But I can't do that.
Two scapegoats would look like panic.
But one of you is going
down, mark my words.
Sir, that's not right.
Hush.
It's not you, Dent.
Obviously, it's Mr. Gordon.
Sir, I protest.
But not too much.
You see, Counselor Dent
knows how to walk the line.
He knows where the edge is.
You, Mr. Gordon,
do not know where the edge is.
Mayor James.
Kiss my ass.
Dick Lovecraft's suicide is
a terrible, terrible tragedy.
Fighting the trumped-up charges
of an overzealous police
officer was too much for him.
You have my word, Dick.
This officer is being dealt with.
Arkham Asylum?
A security guard for nut-jobs?
Criminal nut-jobs, yeah.
Are you taking the assignment?
It's that or quit.
So quit.
That's what they want me to do.
Damn, Jim.
Whoever your next partner is,
he or she will be a lot easier than me.
Ed.
Detective Gordon, I hear you've
been thrown out in disgrace.
Is this true?
Yeah, it is.
I'm gonna write a letter to the boss.
You do that.
Which boss should I write to?
Forget it, Ed.
That's the breaks, huh?
You take care.
Maybe you should take him with you.
You'd miss him if he was gone.
No, I wouldn't.
Let me buy you a drink sometime.
Soon.
Your security still sucks.
No one's hunting for me.
I didn't expect to see you again.
Never said good-bye.
No, we didn't.
Didn't want to be rude.
It-it's good to see you.
Here.
Thank you, but you could keep this.
You need it more than I do.
Nah, let's keep things honest between us.
I'm keeping this one anyway.
Having a little chat, Master Bruce?
Thinking out loud.
Right.
Of course you were.
Shall I take that for you?
The old house seems very quiet...
without her, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.