GORDON: Previously on Gotham...
LEE: What's your record for
how many banks
you 've robbed in one day?
GORDON: You can't take ownership
of everyone's problems.
LEE: We all have our flaws.
But you're still breaking the law.
JEROME: I want you to throw me a wake.
- Dig me up!
- (YELLING)
NYGMA: Iwill liberate Lee Thompkins
with surgical precision.
Dead or alive.
Jerome uses distractions.
Got a plan for that?
Bruce?
Jeremiah?
Oh, God, no. He's still alive.
JEREMIAH: Jerome is dead.
Long live me.
I could not have done any of this
without your help.
Those generators that we built
work even better as bombs.
(ALARM BLARING)
Sources tell us Captain James Gordon
was at the scene
and is missing and feared dead.
Investigators are certainly looking into
what could've caused
the sudden explosion.
Harvey.
Ijust got off the phone
with Search and Rescue,
whatever blew Jeremiah's bunker
was catastrophic.
There are no signs of life.
Tell them to keep looking.
- Harvey, I think...
- Listen, Jim found his way out.
Understand?
Gotham City Police Department has
dispatched an investigative unit,
which is currently canvasing the area,
looking for any traces
of Captain Gordon.
(SHOUTING) Screw that. And screw her.
Listen, in two minutes,
Jim Garden's gonna come
walking through that door
and chew all your asses out
for standing around
and not doing yourjob.
Now, first responders are on the scene,
I want CSis out there pronto.
And I want everyone looking for
Jeremiah Valeska and Bruce Wayne.
That's who Jim was looking for
when this whole thing went blooey.
- You ain't the captain.
- The captain ain't here.
I'm ranking detective.
Last time we followed you,
the Pyg slaughtered us.
AII right, look, enough.
Jim trusts him, okay?
So, everybody get back to work.
ALVAREZ: Harvey.
Jeremiah Valeska wasn't inside
the bunker when it blew.
How do you know?
'Cause he's outside,
and he's not alone.
What the hell?
You might not recognize
Jerome's followers as I've given them
something of a makeover.
But I assure you they're as loyal
to me as they ever were to him.
More so, 'cause I accomplished
something my brother never could.
Killing James Gordon.
- ALL: Jeremiah! Jeremiah!
- You're a liar.
Not so fast.
I have bombs planted around this city.
Just like the one
that killed Jim Gordon.
ALL: Jeremiah! Jeremiah!
AII you need to know is,
if I hit this detonator,
Gotham's blown back to the Stone Age.
If I pull this trigger,
your brains are blown
through the back of your skull.
Dead man's switch. You're familiar.
It's another little something
I took from my brother,
except mine is a bit more advanced.
You shoot me, my thumb loosens,
and then boom, boom, boom.
Boom.
Now, if you won't do what I say...
- You're more sick than your brother.
- (CHUCKLES)
Don't compare me to that
shortsighted psychopath.
He just wanted to destroy things.
Me, I'm a builder.
I'm going to create
a new Gotham in my image.
But every artist
needs a blank canvas.
S0, all of this has to go.
I detonate the explosives
in six hours,
I want this city empty when I do.
You need us to evacuate Gotham
in six hours? That's impossible.
Then everyone who dies screaming.
Who watches their loved ones
crushed before them
will have you to thank,
Detective Bullock.
Look,
nobody has to die.
Well, except for these people.
I know seeing is believing,
and I do want you to believe me.
So...
(BEEPING)
(PEOPLE SHOUTING AND SCREAMING)
- 0h, my God.
- (CAR ALARM BLARING)
Get officers on the scene now! Go!
Six hours, Detective.
The clock is ticking.
BARBARA: Shame. I liked the clock tower.
Jim took me there on a date once.
Now they're both up in smoke.
Good riddance.
He always did want to die a hero.
PENGUIN: And that was Jim's problem.
Me, I'd rather live.
And live well.
(SCOFFS) If it isn't little Penguin.
Oh, and Butch's corpse.
- Hey, Tabby.
- Butch.
The man responsible for the recent
fireworks is Jeremiah Valeska.
Twin brother of our old associate.
He has plans for Gotham.
Plans we learned about,
courtesy of this gentleman.
- They ripped out my fingernails.
- (LAUGHS)
I believe that this is a golden
opportunity for cash and glory.
Normally, Iwould keep
both of them for myself.
But I find myself a bit short
of the necessary manpower.
- Or woman-power, if you will.
- Hmm.
I'II go 50/50 on the take.
An alliance with you. I'Il pass.
Pity. With the money
we were going to make,
I'd hoped to finally be able to
cure Butch of his condition.
Wait, what do you mean?
Hugo Strange ran Indian Hill.
Indian Hill's toxic sludge
turned Butch into this.
Hugo Strange can fix Butch,
but it won't be cheap.
Strange might be my only hope, Tabby.
Don't look at me like that.
I almost got killed fighting
your ex-boyfriend's rotting corpse.
I think it's time to return the favor.
Fine.
But swamp boy keeps his funk
ten feet from me at all times.
What did you have in mind?
Evacuate this city in six hours?
Five and a half hours.
And it will happen,
because this maniac has
bombs hidden all over Gotham.
Think of how many lives are at stake.
And every minute you hesitate
means fewer people get to safety.
- We'II need police.
- We are police!
We're here to help. Harper,
please, will you help the mayor?
HARPER: You got it.
Holy Mother of God. Bruce Wayne.
Hey.
Bruce, are you okay?
I'm fine. I heard about Jim.
- Is it true?
- As far as I'm concerned,
Jim Gordon is alive, kicking,
and waiting for us to iind him.
Detective, don't lie to me.
It's not looking good, kid.
I was hoping you could help me.
Did you see Jim?
How did you get out of the bunker?
Jeremiah and I had
already left the bunker.
Jerome sprayed him with a gas
that drove him insane.
I'm so sick of that freaking family.
Did you hear about
Gotham Clock Tower? Huh?
This guy's got these massive...
- It's my fault.
- What?
Jeremiah had plans to create
next-generation generators.
Ifunded him.
Wayne Enterprises built those bombs?
Listen,
the schematics for the battery
should be in the Wayne Enterprises
R&D lab.
Lucius can take a look at them and
figure out how to disarm the bombs.
- I'm going to go get them now.
- No, you're going home.
- No, I have to do this.
- (SHOUTS) Look, I know you feel guilty,
but Jim Gordon was...
Is important to all of us.
And it's my job. S0. go home,
be with Alfred, be safe.
It's what Jim would want.
Lucius.
- (SIGHS)
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
Alfred, where have you been?
JEREMIAH: No, notAlfred.
I hope you didn't
catch a cold in my brothers grave.
I know those things aren't
exactly designed for the living.
What have you done? Where's Alfred?
Such anger.
Some people, not me, of course,
might consider that ingratitude
considering all I've done for you.
AII I'm still doing for you.
You mean lying to me?
Using my company to build bombs?
Trying to kill me?
Bruce, let's get something straight.
If I wanted you dead, you'd be dead.
I'd have put a bullet through your brain
and left you to rot in that grave.
But I meant what I said.
You're my best friend. And today,
I'm going to prove it to you.
You are insane.
And you killed Jim Gordon.
And if you don't want
your man-servant to die, too,
you will follow
my instructions to the letter.
71 Welling Avenue,
be there in an hour.
Tell the police and I'II know.
Just like I know
that's where you are right now.
(GROANS)
Well, well,
Jim Gordon, back from the dead.
Where am I?
The Narrows.
I was in Jeremiah's bunker.
There was a bomb.
Ed had you followed.
His people found you after the blast.
I'II have to thank him
when I arrest him.
I'm surprised you didn't kill me.
I am, too, actually.
What do you plan to do with me?
I don't really know.
Lee, I have to get back to the GCPD.
Jerome's brother Jeremiahu
Blew up the Gotham Clock Tower
about an hour ago.
The city's being evacuated.
I have to... (GROANS)
Ifsjust a painkiller.
Does make you easier to handle.
You're not going anywhere.
Myjacket... In myjacket.
I got those from Jeremiah's office.
They may give us
some clue as to what he's planning.
Please, let me take them to Harvey.
Oh, Jim, you still think you're
the only one who can save this city.
- Wait.
- Get some rest.
Doctor's orders.
(DOOR LOCK RATTLING)
Jeremiah's followers must have taken
Alfred while Iwas at the cemetery.
I bet he put up a fight.
Thanks again for meeting me, Selina.
- Sure.
- I didn't have anyone else to call.
I know it's asking a lot.
So I just really appreciate...
Bruce, I'm going to be here
whenever you need me.
Okay. that's the address.
I don't see anyone though.
That could be a trap, right?
I don't know.
Jeremiah could have killed me
at the Cemetery.
He wants something out of me.
Like what? To be your best friend?
Trap or not, if Alfred's in there,
I need to find out.
BRUCE: Alfred?
- (SCREAMING)
- Alfredl Alfred!
(SCREAMING)
- (ALFRED GRUNTING)
- (MANIACAL LAUGHTER)
- Alfredl
- (SCREAMING)
You want to help Jim Gordon?
Have you lost your mind?
You brought him here because
you thought it would give us leverage
- with the GCPD.
- Yes, by holding him hostage.
This drawing is the key
to Valeska's plan.
We solve it, and we trade
the information for clemency.
Perhaps.
Or, perhaps there's
something more going on.
(SIGHS)
What happened between Jim and I is over.
I'm trying to protect
what we've built.
I still like my plan better.
Ed, if this maniac
levels half the city,
it's going to disrupt food
distribution, water supply, power.
The people of The Narrows
will suffer the most.
We can prevent that,
while at the same time
helping us out of this mess we're in.
Please.
Fine.
If this is what you want,
I will do it.
For you.
Do it for us.
REPORTER: After the mayor's
evacuation orders,
the new Trigate Bridge
is absolute bedlam...
HARVEY: Where are we at
with the evac?
Bridges and tunnels
are bumper to bumper.
National Guard is
bringing in the choppers.
Look, we're talking about evacuating
hospitals, nursing homes, jails.
Some people just don't want to leave.
We are seeing
the same levels of panic
on every bridge
and tunnel out of Gotham.
God, what a mess.
Just make it happen.
- Okay.
- Excuse me.
LUCIUS: I got the schematics from
Wayne Enterprises R&D.
The Wayne kid said
the bombs were batteries.
A series of network
self-perpetuating generators.
But when Supercharged,
they contain enough energy
to level a city block.
Got it, battery bombs from hell.
Just tell me this will
help us find and disable them.
Disable. yes. Find, no. But...
Look. Look here. Because they were
created to be networked together,
Jeremiah would have to send a signal.
A centrally-located core relay
in order to blow all the bombs
- from a single detonator.
- Lucius, just English, please.
Sorry, the bombs are connected
by a nervous system.
The core relay is the brain.
We find that, we destroy that.
We can stop the bombs from going off.
- Yes.
- But how do we find it?
How do we find this brain?
Oh, Bruce. you are about to have
a very transformative experience.
I envy you.
Call our friends.
Tell them to kill the butler.
He is no longer necessary.
Oswald Cobblepot.
Barbara Kean.
In my stronghold.
Not one step closer. Mr. Valeska.
And is that my dear Jongleur
with my core relay in his hand
and a grenade taped to his mouth?
- PENGUIN: Indeed, it is.
- (SHUDDERING)
Huh.
Well, it seems you have
the upper hand.
Undoubtedly.
And now,
we have our own demands.
$50 million. That's what you want?
It's a nice, round number.
I don't quite have that
on me right now.
You gave the mayor
six hours to evacuate Gotham.
An impossible task.
Let him buy another hour.
He will save thousands of lives.
$50 million will seem cheap.
I see. I play the villain,
you get away scot-free and rich.
I get you the money,
you give me back my core relay.
That is usually
how a hand-off works, yeah.
You drive a hard bargain,
but I'II see what I can do.
Just like that?
After knowing your brother.
I expected something more...
Insane?
I'm nothing if not sane and reasonable.
Two things my brother never valued.
That's why l'II be successful
where he failed.
Well, that and being
vastly more intelligent.
Now, to see about your money.
This is Jeremiah Valeska.
I'd like to speak to the mayor.
I have additional demands.
Yes, really.
50 million, unmarked bills.
I'II tell you the location.
We're not going tojust
hand this thing over
and let him destroy Gotham, are we?
Of course not.
Once we get the money,
we kill Jeremiah and his people.
Give the core relay to the police,
split the 50 million and are
hailed as the heroes of Gotham.
And we cure Butch.
And that, certainly.
JEREMIAH: Would you believe it?
They put me on hold.
(MUFFLED GRUNT)
Well, there's always plan number two.
- Get down!
- (SCREAMING)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(COUGHING)
Are you out of your mind?
Why do you keep insisting I'm insane?
What's insane about having
a backup plan,
something Jongleur never knew about.
And, so you know, this building
is within the blast radius.
And because of your interference.
I'm going to detonate the bombs
as soon as I'm far enough away
to observe the destruction in peace.
No, you promised the city six hours!
Whose fault is it
that I changed my mind?
Tell our men to rewire the bombs
to work in direct sequence,
and the rest of you, kill these idiots.
Alfred?
JEREMIAH: Hello, Bruce.
Jeremiah?
I imagine you 're wondering,
"Why is Jeremiah doing this?"
My brother once said, "AII it takes
is one bad day to reduce
"the sanest man alive to lunacy.”
(ALFRED SCREAMING)
Jerome gave me what I thought
was the worst day of my life.
But only by losing everything
was lable to face
what was inside me.
And I believe I've seen something
very special inside of you as well.
Alfred.
But to free it,
you'll have to lose everything
and everyone you hold dear.
(HOARSE BREATHING)
Iinstructed Scarecrow
to mix up something exceptional.
No!
Your butler is going
to show you the path ahead.
Now, watch closely.
(SCREAMING)
No! Alfred!
Hello, sleepyhead. You do realize
the city's about to be blown up.
It's an odd time for a nap.
- You know that she drugged me.
- Yeah, don't really care.
Thank you, gentlemen.
I want to make one thing very clear.
If Gotham becomes a rock pile.
I mind zero percent.
I'm only helping you
because I'm with Lee now.
Fine, whatever.
Feign nonchalance. It's very cute.
It's almost convincing.
Ed, Jeremiah Valeska is threatening
to destroy half the city.
You really think I care
if you've deluded yourself
into thinking
you and Lee are a couple?
You see?
That is my point.
You don't believe that
Lee could actually love me, do you?
Honestly? No.
Hmm.
You're a psychopath and a murderer.
And the fact that you need me
to validate your crazy fantasy
means that
you don't believe it either.
That doesn't matter.
What matters is stopping Jeremiah
from killing thousands of people.
So, can we...
Yeah, we're going to settle this.
:Ed...
- No, Jim!
This isn't the GCPD.
Here, I make the rules.
So, we're not going to do this
until we talk about
what I want to talk about.
Lee's changed. I accept that.
Maybe she will never be
the person that I knew. Fine.
- But she is not who you think she is.
- (SCOFFS)
The fact that she is with you
in whatever way she's with you...
[Oh, Jim, she's with me in even] way.
Means that
she wants something from you.
So, when it's done,
she'II get rid of you.
So, you're saying that she
wouldn't be with a killer and yet.
She was with you.
And you, Jim, are 10 times
the killer that I ever was.
You have a point.
Maybe that's why she's not with me now.
Can we do this?
Why not?
Just try to keep up.
I'II speak slowly.
So most labyrinths
are constructed as contiguous lines
along concentric circles.
One way in, one way out.
But this 0ne's different.
Undoubtedly.
Those red rectangles.
They're unbound on one side.
And they overlap black lines which
would lead out of the labyrinth.
So maybe we're not looking at plans.
But the end result.
Voilâ. Look familiar?
So, this is Wayne Enterprises.
This would be Gotham Central Bank.
These are the buildings Jeremiah's
planning to demolish with his bombs.
Once those buildings are blown,
they collapse and create
the labyrinth
from the finished drawing.
Jeremiah lived his entire life
in a maze.
Now he's trying to remake the city
into the place he feels most safe.
It's actually rather elegant.
- I need to get to the GCPD.
- (CHUCKLES) No, sorry.
You're not going anywhere until
we get this information to the mayor.
Lee and I have some
legal knots we need untangled.
Yeah, before we spend
the rest of our lives together.
So you're going to use this
to hold the city hostage?
Time is running out.
Well, then the mayor would be wise to
forgive Lee and I our indiscretions.
Ed. Wait.
There's one thing I can't figure out.
One, be a little kind to yourself.
Yeah, I'm sorry, I think
you made a mistake right there.
Where?
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
"Get the core relay," he says.
"Have the upper hand." he says.
(SCREAMING)
Finally.
Let's get the hell out of here
before Jeremiah
blows us all to smithereens.
This is all your fault, Oswald.
- You better...
- Fix it! I know!
(PHONE RINGING)
- What?
- PENGUIN: Harvey...
Is this Oswald?
I'm, uh, kind of busy.
I have information
regarding Jeremiah Valeska's plan.
(MAN GRUNTING)
- What information?
- (GUNSHOT)
Wait a second. is that gunfire?
Just listen!
Jeremiah is not honoring the six hours.
He will blow the bombs
as soon as he can watch
the catastrophe from a safe distance.
Jeremiah said something
about rewiring the bombs
to communicate with each other.
He called it a direct sequence.
Communicate with each other.
Harvey...
Harvey!
It's a backup system from when
they operated as batteries.
That means we can disrupt them
by disarming the first bomb
in the sequence.
It's like removing one light
from a string of Christmas lights.
If only we knew where the bombs were.
- (DOOR SLAMS)
- MAN: He's back. Hey!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Jim! Oh!
Oh. buddy!
AII right, easy there, big fella.
Remember, Ijust got blown up.
- How did you get out of the bunker?
- It's a long story.
But what matters is,
[I have the locations of
even] bomb Jeremiah planted.
BRUGE: Alfred?
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
Alfred?
(CHUCKLING)
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Alfred?
(HOARSE BREATHING)
Jeremiah said Bruce Wayne
might try to bring his friends.
I suppose you're one of them.
What? No. Ijust wandered in here.
I think our little experiment is
about to get much more interesting.
Jeremiah wasn't bluffing.
There's at least
a dozen bombs on this map.
But you're saying, if we disarm
one of them in the sequence,
we'II stop all of them
from going off.
And according to this,
the closest one is just a mile away.
I need to look at the schematics
to determine the best way
to neutralize them.
Alert the bomb squad.
Tell them to meet me there.
Wait, Harvey.
Let the bomb squad handle this.
You don't have to go.
Yes, I do.
I need this, Jim.
Yeah.
(GRUNTING)
- (BONES CRACKING)
- (SCREAMING)
(MAN SCREAMING)
(SELINA YELLING)
It doesn't matter. The experiment
is nearing it's conclusion.
Your friend will soon be driven mad.
(HISSING)
(HEAW METAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(WHIRRING)
- (CRACKLING)
- (SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING)
No!
- (WHIRRING)
- (BRUCE SCREAMING)
(GASPING)
(CHUCKLING)
Alfred.
(CACKLING)
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
(LAUGHING)
Alfred, please. Please, stop.
(conrmues LAUGHING)
(GASPS)
- Alfredl
- (BOTH GRUNTING)
Alfred! Alfred, stop.
Alfred!
Just stop, Alfred. Please.
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(GAS HISSING)
(HISSING srops)
- (POUNDING AT DOOR)
- (MUFFLED GRUNTS)
What the...
(GRUNTING)
Come on, Brucey, give me a smile.
Smile.
Alfred, listen to me.
You can beat this!
You can fight this!
Alfred, you're stronger than him!
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
Do not let him win!
(eunsnor)
(SCREAMS) No.
- No! Alfred! Alfred! Alfred!
- Bruce, Bruce. Bruce.
Breathe. Look at me.
Scarecrow was just
pumping his fear gas in here.
You were only seeing
what he wanted you to.
- No, no, no.
- No, Bruce. Bruce. Bruce.
ALFRED: Bruce! Bruce,
listen. Listen to me.
Listen, look at me now. Look at me.
Just look at me.
Look, I'm fine. It's me.
It's Alfred.
Alfred?
- (PEOPLE SHOUTING)
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hey, I'm at the site.
Where the hell is the bomb squad?
The evacuation's jamming the streets.
They're still en route.
I can't wait. I've got to go in.
Do you see the bomb?
I don't know what
it's supposed to look like.
But I think it is exactly
what I'm staring at.
Oh.
Lucius, we've got to do this thing.
- Harvey...
- Listen, we can't wait.
We don't know when Jeremiah's
going to set this thing off.
Then you're going to
have to unscrew the antenna
- to activate the kill switch.
- Okay.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
- Uh...
- (WHIRRING)
Lucius.
It's making some kind of weird noise.
What kind of a noise?
A bad one, and it's getting all glowy.
(SIGHS) Then, you are going
to have to work quickly.
Okay.
ALL: Jeremiah! Jeremiah!
(DETONATOR BEEPS)
AII my life I spent by myself.
Hidden away.
I am so glad to be sharing
this happy moment with all of you.
Today marks the dawning
of a new Gotham City.
One where we will all be free.
Now,
shall I do the honors?
LUCIUS: Once you unscrew the antenna,
a kill-switch breaker should pop out.
Destroying it should stop the signal
from the detonator to all the bombs.
Which breaker is it?
What the...
What do you mean, which breaker?
There are two of them.
Jeremiah must have changed them
since making these schematics.
- Okay, l'll break both of them.
- No, wait. Harvey,
one of the breakers could be
the super-charged fail-safe.
Whatever you do,
do not touch that one.
- Or?
- Or all the bombs will blow.
Lucius, they're identical.
Then, Harvey, I don't know.
REPORTER ON TV:
We interrupt this program...
- WOMAN: That's Jim Gordon.
- He's not dead.
What?
GORDON: This is a message to
the followers of Jeremiah Valeska.
Jeremiah claims to have killed me.
Well, bad news, I'm alive.
JEREMIAH: No. No, it's a trick.
I killed him.
So, just know,
you 're worshiping a fraud.
A pale imitation of Jerome.
You did your worst, Jeremiah.
And I'm still here.
- MAN: You lied to us.
- Gordon's alive.
Doesn't matter whether he's alive.
When I hit this switch,
you'll hear the sounds
of a new world being born.
Oh, for the love of God.
Our world.
Eenie, meenie, miney, mo,
which of you will make it blow?
- Now, listen.
- (CLICK)
(SNIFFLES)
(SIGHS IN RELIEF)
- He's a liar! Liar!
- He's a fake!
- (ALL CLAMORING)
- Shut up!
I want you all to know
I find your fickleness
quite hurtful.
And more so, very predictable.
(ALL CLAMORING)
- Jeremiah!
- Jeremiahl
(ALL SCREAMING)
Well, that is disappointing.
You know, if you had asked me
this morning
how many people I was gonna kill today,
I would have been way off.
Perhaps the outcome
was not what we had hoped.
- But it was worth the risk.
- BARBARA: Ozzy,
if I were you, I would limp
out of here while you still can.
Fine.
- Let's go, Butch.
- Nope.
I'm done.
Ever since we teamed up,
everything's gone to crap.
Hell, we don't even know
where Strange is.
Except, I do know where Strange is.
(SHOUTING) You mean to tell me you've
known where he is the whole time
and never told me?
- (CHOKING) Ijust got word.
- No more excuses.
He fixes me now!
And how exactly do we pay him?
I can be very persuasive.
Think, think, think.
How did they beat you, huh?
How did they figure you out?
Gordon must have stolen
the blueprints to the maze,
found one of the bombs,
and sabotaged the sequence.
I'II have to start again. (SIGHS)
MAN: You're tenacious. I like that.
Who are you? What do you want?
I had a vision of Gotham in flames.
Together we can make that happen.
Well, I appreciate the offer,
but recent events have convinced me
of the benefits of working alone.
(GUNSHOTS)
Don't be so rash.
Your dream of a new Gotham
will come to be, with my help.
(SIGHS)
You're behind me, aren't you?
I can conquer Gotham on my own.
What makes you think I need your help?
Whoever you are.
Because, my boy.
All this is not just about Gotham.
This is about Bruce Wayne.
You here to arrest me?
To thank you.
And to present you with an offer.
Leave Gotham.
Start a new life somewhere else.
Alone.
And if I don't?
I know we can't change the past.
What we've done...
We've done to each other.
I can't pretend to recognize
the person I see before me.
But whatever happens
after I walk out that door,
I care about you.
And I always will.
Lucius, call the mayor.
Tell him not to lift
the evacuation order
until all the bombs
are under lock and key.
And I want every cop out there
to keep looking for Jeremiah Valeska.
What?
Give it up for Harvey Bullock.
(CHEERING)
MAN: Give it up.
Dude, come on.
Thank you. No. come on.
Right. Well, I'm going to take
a very long and a very hot shower.
And then I'm going to make us
a legendary fry-up.
Will you be joining us, Miss Kyle?
- I've got no plans.
- Excellent
You all right, mate?
Okay. then.
Thank you again.
I don't know what would have
happened if you weren't there.
You're welcome.
Why do you think
he's so obsessed with you?
Jeremiah said, "AII it takes is one
bad day to drive a person insane."
I wonder if my parents dying
made me a little insane?
Maybe he sensed that.
Maybe he wanted to bring it out.
Well, you proved him wrong.
JEREMIAH: To be fair,
the day's not over yet.
(GASPS)
(INAUDIBLE)
English - SDH