Previously onGotham...
- I heard they let you out of Arkham.
- Yes. I'm sane.
- I'm Elijah Van Dahl.
- Oh, Oswald Cobblepot.
- You're related to Gertrud?
- My mother.
- She never told me.
- Told you what?
That I had a son.
You have a home now and a father.
Big happy family.
- Is this a dream?
- It's not a dream, my boy.
- You're home.
- Hello, Officer Pinkney.
- Can I come in?
- Sure.
Murder weapon was a crowbar.
- Your fingerprints were on it.
- I was set up!
Detective Gordon guilty
on all counts.
How can you not be with us?
Birthdays and first steps
- and skinned knees.
- You need to go somewhere,
start a new life.
Jim, don't do this! I love you!
- I'm so, so sorry.
- Jim! I love you! Don't do this!
Jim!
On your feet, let's go.
Get out!
Line it up.
Face right.
Walk.
Lights out!
Keep it moving!
Stay in line!
Stop!
Prisoner Gordon, step out of line
and remain silent.
Let's move!
Several weeks
with no incidents, Gordon.
I'm impressed. Not what I expected.
Word was you were a troublemaker.
I just want to do my time.
Well, it's time to move you.
- Where to?
- F Wing.
"World's End."
General population.
This should not come
as a surprise to you.
Protective custody is just
a temporary privilege,
one which can't be sustained
for a sentence as long as yours.
Perhaps you have an appeal pending,
in which case,
I can prolong this arrangement.
That's got to sting just a little,
no?
Your people seem
to have abandoned you.
Being convicted
for murder has its downsides.
Don't fret so.
I'm sure, you'll see a lot
of familiar faces over in F Wing.
Many of which you arrested yourself.
It's payback time!
Here comes the flying scissor kick!
That one wasn't mine?
If you show yourself to be
a team player, anything's possible.
Are you a team player, Gordon?
I love it.
Oh, and I forgot to pass on
my good friend's regard.
Ex-Commissioner Loeb, says hi.
Follow the rules
and perhaps you'll survive.
Break them
and you most certainly won't.
It's why they call
this wing World's End.
For most here,
it's exactly that, the end.
Only way out, parole or a body bag.
And nobody gets parole.
It's true. I swear it.
Clear as day... A ghost.
She was this pale old woman
in a long black dress.
- She was this close.
- What did you do?
Oh, I ran away screaming, of course.
Oh, do you believe in ghosts, Oswald?
Yes, I do.
- I've seen them.
- This house has several of them.
But don't worry,
they're all quite friendly.
Don't listen to him.
There are no ghosts here.
Oh, there's ghosts, all right.
This house was built
by my grandfather.
He died here.
His wife and two sisters
also passed away upstairs.
And my poor dear parents.
Yes, many ghosts.
How did you meet?
Oh. That's a boring story, really...
No, let me tell it, dear.
After my mother died, I sat alone
in this house for months.
Barely got out of bed, in fact.
Finally, I found a diner,
not too far from here.
I'd go there every day
at the same time,
order the same thing.
- Chicken soup and a seltzer.
- Grace was my waitress
and I grew very fond of her.
She told me of her two poor children,
Sasha and Charles
and how they suffered at the hands
of their abusive father.
I had to help. I offered her refuge
and she accepted.
And this house heard laughter
once again.
Then one thing led to another.
Love blossomed.
And here we are.
But you are my only
true blood relative, Oswald.
Oh, my poor dear.
- Are you hurt at all?
- No, no. I'm, I'm fine.
Clumsy girl.
To family.
- Family.
- To family.
Dent, they got him
in general population now,
F Wing. You know what that means?
Everyone we've ever
put away is in there!
Stop saying that!
There's always something you can do.
A retrial. Or have him
transferred to another prison,
for God's sake.
You know what, just keep
doing what you always do,
which is nothing!
Ed.
He's wasting away in that place
while the real killer's
out there somewhere,
- eating donuts and getting laid.
- The real killer?
The fingerprints on the murder
weapon...
Jim is innocent.
He didn't kill Pinkney.
Well, gee, that's...
Unfair if that's true.
What are you gonna do about it?
I wish I knew.
My health forbids me from drinking,
but at least I can watch
you enjoy this sherry.
It was my father's favorite.
Is that him?
No, that's my great-grandfather
Manfred.
He started a small tailor's shop
in Gotham many, many years ago.
Made suits for the city's elite.
My father became an apprentice
like every son before him.
- You were an apprentice, too?
- I was.
Had rather a flare for it.
But it was not to be.
When my father succumbed to illness,
my mother held me close to her.
Homeschooled me.
She felt a need to protect me
from the temptations of the city.
All this time, I've been afraid
to ask about your mother.
I'm so sorry, I abandoned her.
Had I known
I was also abandoning you...
Dear god, such a cowardly fool.
Did she have a happy life?
No, not a happy life. But a good one.
She never hurt a soul.
I was not always a good son
and she never spoke
a word of reproach.
Not always a good son?
I find that hard to credit.
An nice young man like you?
Believe me.
I've done bad things.
We're all sinners, my boy.
It's time for your medicine, my love.
Thank you.
Doctor gave them to me for my heart.
Better safe than sorry.
You have a visitor, Mr. Gordon.
This way, please.
No, I'm not going back to the hole!
- He promised!
- The warden's the one
- who's moving you.
- What?
This wasn't our agreement!
No, you listen! This isn't fair!
I paid for this cell! This is mine!
You hear me?
This way, please.
A lot of business going on.
The warden get a cut?
Almost there.
I want the Boy Scout dead
by week's end.
Damn.
You look good, brother.
This place agrees with you.
Maybe I'll check-in.
Lose a few pounds?
Get a cool tat.
- You don't need to check up on me.
- Are you kidding?
Highlight of my week
to see your smiling face.
Look, I spoke to Dent.
He's looking into reopening the case.
But you got to keep your nose clean.
Last thing you can do is do more time
because you lost your temper,
all right?
Shouldn't be that hard.
Everyone seems really
nice around here.
I'm looking for Penguin.
See what he's got to say.
He's laying low someplace,
- but don't worry. I'll find him.
- How's Lee?
Been writing to me a lot.
The letters stopped a few weeks ago.
Know why?
I didn't want
to be the one to tell you this.
Tell me what?
Lee lost the baby, Jim.
I'm so sorry.
How is she?
I... I don't know.
I think she's fine.
She moved down South.
No one's heard from her since.
Hey, don't let this beat you.
It's good to see you, Harv.
Jim, I'm gonna get you
out of here, I promise.
Jim, don't let this break you!
Don't give up hope.
Jim! Jim!
Where you going, pig?
My little brother ran
with a crew that pulled off
a few bank jobs last year.
Papers called them the Red Hood Gang?
Remember them? You put
a bullet in my brother's head.
Now, who's this?
How about I have my friends
on the outside pay her a visit?
Show her what she's been missing?
Oh, snap!
Hey, hey, hey, guys,
cool it, cool it?
Peace, peace.
- Don't.
- It's all right, Mr. Gordon.
I got this. Now, come on now, guys.
Let's just take a deep breath...
Get back to your cells!
You!
Assume the position now.
- Now!
- Back it up! Back it up!
Take inmate Weaver to the hole.
And these two to the infirmary.
Get up. Get up!
Let's go. You heard him.
- Father?
- What?
- Who?
- It's okay. You were sleepwalking.
Oh, I was.
My father's office.
Here, let me, let me get you a chair?
- No, help me back to bed, won't you?
- Of course.
They're for my condition.
- Your heart?
- I have a hole in it.
It keeps getting bigger apparently.
I think my demons are feeding on it.
You have demons?
Sadly, I do.
You, too, I fear.
There's so much I haven't told you.
So much that I'm ashamed of.
I was a criminal.
I've done...
Horrible things.
Hurt people, manipulated, lied.
For power, for revenge.
I've killed people, Father.
Our lives together started the moment
I met you at the cemetery.
Nothing before that concerns me.
I forgive you for all
your past transgressions.
Be free of them
and live here in peace.
We showed them?
- Look, whatever your name is...
- Puck... Well, Peter actually,
but people call me Puck.
Stay away from me, okay?
I don't need your help.
Can't do that, Detective Gordon.
- I'm not a detective anymore.
- Oh, I know.
You're way more than that.
You're a true hero.
Two winters ago,
my little sister was abducted
by child snatchers.
Three days she was gone.
And then you found her and,
and busted the scum that took her.
You saved her life
and dozens of others.
Right there, that's a true hero.
- Just doing my job.
- No, sir.
- What are you in for?
- A girl.
Beautiful girl.
I asked her out and she said yes.
And she was classy.
I couldn't make her take the bus
so I snatched a car.
Well, borrowed it.
I was gonna take it back.
Cops didn't believe me,
so here I am.
- What they give you?
- Six years.
- Steep.
- Hey, I can't complain.
I broke the law, right?
The law is the law.
I'm not gonna be like my grandfather.
He died in here.
And wouldn't let me and my father
visit him after a while.
But finally, we did.
Last time I saw him,
he was different.
Didn't recognize him.
That's not gonna happen to me.
No, sir, I won't die in here.
Then stay away from me.
What are these prisoners
still doing here?
Get them to their cells immediately.
And watch this one.
He just lost a child.
Makes him mad.
That's right. I hear everything.
I see everything.
Everything you know,
I know.
I know something you don't know.
Yeah, what's that?
I know what kind of man you are.
Get him out of here...
Now.
- Gin.
- Elijah?
Brace yourself.
I'm afraid we have some bad news.
Oh, dear.
Charles was
at the public library today.
Research for the novel I'm writing.
I was reading some old newspapers
and I made an alarming discovery.
My dear, Oswald is not
the nice young man he says he is.
If we didn't lead
such sheltered lives here,
we would know
what the whole world knows.
He's a notorious criminal.
We've been sheltering a killer.
We could have all been raped
and murdered in our beds.
Raped and murdered.
They call you the Penguin?
To be fair...
I never raped anybody.
Oh, well, that's a mercy,
now, isn't it?
My son told me about his past.
He just didn't tell me
how famous he was.
You're too modest, son.
Elijah a violent criminal
in our house?
Grace, relax, he's changed. Redeemed.
You're not this man anymore, are you?
- Oh, no, sir.
- But how...
Ho... How do you know?
How do you know he's not?
I've looked into his soul.
I've seen his beautiful heart.
"The Dapper Gangland Kingpin."
What now?
Plan B.
What's plan B?
You are, my dear.
Good morning.
I was hoping to spend a little time
with you, Mr. Penguin.
Okay, but please, call me Oswald.
I... I'm not that man anymore.
There isn't a little bit
of Penguin left?
A little bad boy?
No.
I got a little bad girl in me.
Whatever you've got planned
for the old man, I want in.
- In?
- We could do great things,
- you and me.
- I suppose. I hadn't...
If you and me work together,
we could have it all.
We could squeeze my mom
and brother out.
- Why would we do that?
- I don't know.
I guess we're just a couple
of crazy mixed-up kids.
Restrain yourself, woman.
I'm your practically your brother.
What are you thinking?
- He didn't bite.
- Should I try?
No, I don't think he's faking.
I think he's kind of simple.
Gordon.
Watch yourself.
Weaver's coming out the hole. Now.
Already?
Nothing happens around here
like it's supposed to.
Your day's coming, Gordon.
You're a dead man!
Take a look at your boyfriend
over there.
Puck!
Who's gonna help you now, pig?
Yeah, you like that, Gordon?
Let it go.
Don't extend your sentence.
Jim didn't kill that kid.
We all know it.
Thing is, who did?
I mean, who'd set him up that way?
I just don't know how much longer
he can stay alive in that place.
I guess I'm asking for your help.
Funny?
You have every right
to tell me to go to hell.
But I...
I got no one else to turn to.
You know, Harvey...
It's very rude to wear a hat indoors.
You like the fabric? It's Italian.
I love it.
A man can say so much
about himself by what he wears.
I couldn't agree more.
I weep for today's casual youth.
I'm so glad you suggested we do this.
It's been so long.
Are you all right?
Father?
Help!
Have someone call for an ambulance!
Grace! Help! Help, Grace!
What did you do to Elijah?
- Nothing.
- Help!
Coming, my dear.
Clean up this mess
and call the doctor.
Go on.
Hard at it, I see.
Thanks for getting me
my old job back.
Your friend Puck is pretty banged up.
Might do him some good if you were
to come see him in the infirmary.
Yeah, no.
- I'm not his friend.
- He thinks you are.
The kid's gonna die in here,
one way or another.
We'll be quick.
Hey.
How you holding up?
Cool.
They, they said,
I have a clot or something.
I just feel seasick.
Thanks for coming to see me.
Means a lot.
I'm sure they'll take good care
of you in here.
- You hang in there?
- Listen...
Don't give up hope.
I feel your sadness.
I do, but...
You got to choose life, you know?
Okay.
Choose life.
Good.
Listen, kid...
When you get better,
you learn the lesson here
and you stay the hell away from me.
I'm not a hero
and I'm not your friend.
I'm just a convict.
Tonight's movie night.
Everyone in the main hall together
with the lights off. Be ready.
- For what?
- Just be ready.
His condition has gotten worse.
The hole has gotten bigger
and now there's an infection.
I've given him antibiotics
and rehydrated him,
but I fear it will have
little consequence.
It's time for him
to get his affairs in order.
He may not have long.
I'm going to have them make
you some nice chicken soup.
- You need your strength.
- How kind.
Come here, my boy.
Don't listen to doctors, son.
I've proved them wrong
so many times I've lost count.
You and I will have many more years
to spend together.
Trust me.
But perhaps we should
speak with my lawyer, dear.
I have some things
I'd like to go over with him.
So much has changed these past weeks.
Of course. I'll have him stop by.
Sit down.
Settle man.
He's called for his lawyer.
- He's going to change his will?
- Yes.
And when he dies,
Cobblepot will get
what's rightfully ours.
That old man was a shriveled-up wreck
when I met him.
I made him feel young again.
I brought him back to life.
And what has this gutter rodent done?
Played stupid board games
and whined about his wretched mother.
- That vermin has to go.
- But he likes it here.
How can we persuade him to go?
How do you get rid of rats?
- Glue traps?
- No, silly.
Hello. Hello.
Father is feeling much better,
but he is resting,
so he will not be joining us tonight.
Well, that's fine. Let's eat?
Thank you.
I'm a pretty fly. Look, everybody.
- Yeah! Come on, everybody.
- You, show's over.
You, get down!
What are you doing? He's mine!
He's mine!
Stay down!
You're dead. You understand?
You understand?
You're dead, pig.
We're gonna need a body bag.
Bullock?
What the hell are you doing here?
What's it look like we're doing?
We're getting you out of here.
Come on, let's go.
Fake blood, retractable knife.
Can't believe it worked.
Wait. Wait.
Harvey,
what if this is where
I'm supposed to be?
- What? Let's go!
- Bullock...
You sure?
Are you tripping?
A lot of good men put their butts
on a live rail for you. Me, him,
Don freaking Falcone.
While walking around somewhere
is the guy that killed Pinkney,
framed you and destroyed your family.
He's walking around
while you're standing there
all blue and misty.
Well, screw your self-pity
- and let's go!
- Amen.
All right.
But I need one more favor.
Hello?
- Detective Gordon?
- We're out of here.
I need you to move as quickly
and quietly as you can.
- You mean, like, escaping?
- Like that.
- But that's against the law.
- Yeah, like you said, choose life.
Told you, didn't I?
Whether you like it or not,
you're a hero.
Prisoner Gordon.
You're supposed to be dead.
I'm as surprised as you are.
What brought you back to life?
- Friends.
It's good to have friends.
But where are they
when you need them?
Man, that felt good.
Sorry, I got you into all this.
Are you kidding?
Never felt more alive. Now,
hit me hard, make it look good.
Just don't touch the teeth.
I just had them fixed.
Look at your mother.
She was so young.
Oswald.
Thank you so much, Grace.
I lied to you, son.
My father was never physically ill.
He only suffered a deep melancholy.
He was plagued by dark impulses,
evil thoughts of violence.
Mother said, many in his family
had the same affliction.
I remember the sound of the gunshot.
I was outside his room.
I screamed for my mother
to get the key.
I saw the warm gun in his hand.
The blood.
His face.
Mother said, never to talk about it.
For years after the funeral,
we never left the house.
I don't pretend
to understand my father's torment.
But I think perhaps you do.
I feel for you...
And I beg of you, my son.
Never give in to the pain as he did.
You are loved and you are not alone.
And the sun will come up tomorrow.
Thank you, Father.
Now, I feel like a drink.
But your health?
To hell with that.
I want you to have it all, my son.
This house and all that's in it.
Keep it just the way it is,
a piece of history,
our history.
Gotham's history.
First thing tomorrow,
I'll have my lawyers draw it up.
Father?
- Oh, no!
- Elijah!
- Did he... Did he drink that?
- Yes.
Why? Why? He's not supposed to.
Sasha, call an ambulance. Call an...
Stay with us, Father.
Help is on the way.
No!
We made it, buddy.
Wait here.
Don Falcone had all the contacts
inside of Blackgate.
He made this whole thing happen.
Thank you.
I'm not sure I can ever repay you.
It won't be necessary.
I'm happy to help an old friend.
What now?
You're asking me?
Two hours ago, I was a dead man.
I have people that will
get you out of the country.
Or I can arrange a safe
place for you in Gotham. Your choice.
What do you want to do?
I want to go find Lee.
But to do that,
I have to clear my name.
And to do that,
I have to go back to Gotham.
So there's your answer.
Part of me says, run.
I'm breathing fresh air.
I can't go back inside.
If you run,
you've got to keep running.
Some people can live with that.
You're a fighter, Jim.
You got knocked down.
Do you stay down?
Or do you get back up?
What do you think, kid?
Puck?
No, no, we made it. Come on.
Come on. No, come on! Don't give up!
Puck?
He's gone.
Jim, he's gone.