Well, you must be the B-team.
We just handle transpo.
Bob will be taking care of you.
- Bob?
- One of our top guys.
You're in good hands.
Good morning.
- You're up early.
- I haven't made it to bed yet.
Word is you got caught with
Doc Thompkins in the locker room.
Strictly business.
- Any word on Fish?
- No.
Club's all shot up. Blood everywhere.
No sign of Fish.
It's her own damn fault.
She played the game,
she knew the risks.
Sorry, I know you have
a thing for her.
I don't got a thing for nobody.
My thing is for me.
If anyone can make it out
of a scrape like that, it's Fish.
The woman's nails.
Come on. We got a case.
Yeah. So, what do we got?
Public service homicide.
Vic's a douche.
Flass, Gordon. Gordon, Flass.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Flass works Narcotics.
Hence the bling
and the no doubt expensive yet
somehow cheap-looking Italian suit.
Bullock.
Still dressing in the dark and
smelling like a tap-house whore.
One of Flass's connections
tipped him off on the body.
Why don't you tell Gordon
about the kid.
Pinky Littlefield.
Dealer from a crew known
as the Uptown Assassins.
He works this block.
Well, at least he did.
- Any drugs on him?
- Didn't find any.
My big wild guess, deal gone bad.
Kid like this,
bound to happen sooner or later.
Like I said, public service homicide.
Well, boys, I've got another case
I've got to attend to.
So if you don't need
any more hand holding,
I'm gonna walk you out.
Hey, unis think they may have
found a witness. Night janitor.
They're bringing him over.
- Jim, Mr. Winkler.
- Sir.
No need for formalities.
Call me Leon.
Leon. We really appreciate you
stepping forward.
My wife Louisa always says if you
don't step forward, you step back.
She sounds like a smart lady.
Yeah. She is.
So, do I give a statement?
A description of the killer?
I'm not sure how this works.
Would you be willing to
come down to the precinct?
Work with a sketch artist?
That really is the best way
to catch the killer.
It'd be a huge help.
Yeah. Of course.
Thank you, sir.
Yes, sweetheart.
I'm still at the precinct.
I know. Of course. Yeah.
But, okay.
- They send in the sketch artist yet?
- No, not yet.
Louisa, I have to go. Bye-bye.
But you did see the killer, right?
Yes. That's what I told
the detectives earlier.
I'm sorry. Who are you?
How the hell did this happen?
Security cameras inside
and outside were turned off.
Ed, you got any thoughts
on the weapon?
What's strong enough to smash ships
but still fears the sun?
Can it with the riddles, Ed.
I don't have the patience today
or any day.
- Ice.
- Correct.
Gauging by the circumference
of the wounds,
I believe the weapon is an ice pick.
Carbon steel. Six inches long.
Driven in deep enough it
marked the surrounding tissue
with an imprint of a distinctive
hexagonal handle.
It's not your standard kitchen fare.
Fun fact, gentlemen.
Mr. Winkler's wounds here
are the exact same as the wounds
on the victim from this morning.
The drug dealer? Littlefield?
Him. Same weapon.
Same killer, one would suppose.
Damn it. Right in our house.
Okay. What is your name?
You know who I am.
It's just a formality.
I like to be sure.
Bob?
Is that short for Robert?
You have any family, Robert?
Two lovely daughters.
I'm putting you down
as Maria Mercedes Mooney, aka Fish.
We'll be extracting a very sincere
apology from you today.
Shouldn't take too long.
How old are your girls, Robert?
I bet you they're some
ugly little creatures.
Now, come on, Fish.
No call for rudeness.
Only my friends call me Fish,
darling.
And you and I, we're not friends...
yet.
You go get him.
I got to find the keys
to the incinerator.
Hey, Marco.
Where's Fish Mooney?
How is anyone gonna trust us
to keep them safe?
We can't protect people
in our own house.
Upside is the place,
is crawling with criminals,
so we got beaucoup suspects
to choose from.
That's an upside?
Security cameras were turned off.
Could've been a cop. Probably was.
You do not even think
something like that.
The second that those guys out there
hear that you're looking at a cop,
they are gonna turn on you.
Bullock's right.
You start pointing fingers.
You could jeopardize
your reinstatement.
You need concrete evidence
to even think
of accusing another officer
of murder.
I'll start with the guard
duty logbook.
- Jim.
- Winkler was my witness.
No way I'm letting this ride.
I asked him to come in here,
I'm gonna find his killer.
No matter who it is.
Proceed with caution.
Yes, ma'am.
No big moves without my say-so.
I do believe,
this is the second time we've been
around this block, Master Bruce.
Selina likes to hang out here.
It's worth doubling back.
Besides, you got what you wanted.
I went out of town like you asked.
For weeks.
Yeah, well.
It wasn't safe here, was it?
The assassins weren't after me.
They were after her.
Yeah, and we'll be back on that plane
straight back to the bloody Alps
the first sign of trouble,
I tell you.
Master Bruce. Master Bruce,
get back in the car now.
Can we walk around
the block just once?
Then, I'll get back in the car.
Please, Alfred.
Once around the block and then home.
Thank you.
Got the rest of your life like that
to get whipped into a frenzy
by the females.
I don't know why you want
to start now.
It's not like that.
Out of my way.
Ivy?
Steady, Master Bruce.
Looks like she's got the mange.
Look who it is?
Billionaire Bruce Wayne.
Who are you, his bodyguard?
If needs be, miss, yes.
What's in the bag?
It's for Selina.
- Have you seen her?
- Sure.
I can give it to her if you want.
Perhaps you could pass
on a message for me.
Tell her I'm looking for her.
Twenty bucks.
Alfred.
There we are, miss.
Delightful friends you have,
Master Bruce.
Home.
That's all you got?
You are gonna bore me to death,
fella.
That's impressive. Different strokes?
You know, me,
I can't stand hot spicy food,
but my wife, you know, she loves it.
Hotter the better.
Now, where, oh, where
are we gonna begin?
Now, taking off a hand,
that's devastating.
But I've found
that taking out a knee.
You okay, Fish?
A page is missing from this logbook.
Now that in and of itself is grounds
for dismissal from the force.
So my question to you is:
Who was on guard duty outside
of interrogation this morning?
No idea, man.
Nobody's talking.
They're protecting their own.
- Or they just don't like you.
- Face it, Harvey.
Leon Winkler's killer is a cop.
Not proven.
Come on, you know these guys.
You've known them since way back.
Give me some leverage.
Give me an angle.
You really want to work
with a murderer?
Somebody gets whacked in the GCPD.
Somebody's gonna get fired for this.
Not me, pal.
Grover.
We got a reliable guy,
says it was you pulled the page
from the guard duty logbook.
No way. Where did you get that?
- Who said that?
- Alvarez.
If he said that,
that son of a bitch is lying.
Why would he lie?
Look. Six years ago,
I had a thing with his wife, okay?
Six years ago.
He is a vindictive bastard.
Well, look,
that's none of our business, huh?
Look at it from our point of view.
We got to find the culprit.
Brass demands one.
But it wasn't me.
Then who was it?
Delaware? Anybody seen Delaware?
Saw him go to the garage.
Hey. Delaware! Hey!
Hey!
You're gonna regret that.
You were guarding interrogation
this morning, weren't you?
Screw off.
Hey!
Hey.
Jim.
What the hell are you doing?
You couldn't bring him in here
quietly, put him in some back room?
You making some kind of statement?
Damn, right I am.
I warned you and you didn't listen.
I have evidence.
The same drugs I found
in Littlefield's shoe
at the crime scene yesterday morning.
That evidence is part of an ongoing
undercover Narco investigation.
You expect us to believe that?
Jim, Narco's been knee-deep
in the uptown drug trade for months.
I've got a matrix of undercovers
that have put their lives at stake
for this investigation.
Your little stunt gets out,
you unravel the whole operation.
Not to mention,
the search was illegal.
So we're ignoring Delaware's
involvement in Winkler's death?
Is that what we're doing, Capt?
No, but this isn't the way, Jim.
I'm turning over the case
to Internal Affairs.
I.A.? Two old drunks in the basement?
You and Bullock are no longer
investigating the Winkler murder.
What about the Littlefield murder?
Or, wait, is that also a part
of an ongoing narco investigation?
All you, buddy.
Let me know if you need any help.
I'm sorry about the confusion.
Can I help you with something?
Did you know, Miss Kringle,
that the earliest greeting cards
dated back to Germany in the 1400s?
I have a lot of work to do.
This is for you.
Doesn't say anything weird, does it?
No, ma'am.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa.
Take it easy. Take it easy.
I'm fine, Butch.
Here. Try this.
- You okay?
- I'm starving.
You are one tough cookie.
Thank you, Butch.
Listen, we should hit the road.
I figure we've got about
an hour before Falcone.
Oh, I'm not going anywhere
until I find Penguin.
He's the one that told Falcone
about Liza.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, boss,
I don't know if you remember,
but as of last night,
we don't have any men.
Falcone's gonna have the whole city
looking for us.
I'm not going anywhere
until I cut Penguin's throat!
One, two, three.
What do you think, Mother?
Oh, it's beautiful.
Oh, so classy.
Like an opera house.
Oh! A chandelier.
Like home.
Someone left a scarf.
It's beautiful with my dress.
Finders keepers.
And now, you are in charge
of this club?
Spoiled my surprise.
No. Oh, no, no, liebchen.
No, don't be angry. No.
Such good news.
My boy has a club.
Will have a club.
There's still a few loose ends
to tie up,
but soon it will be mine.
I am so proud of you.
I could spit.
Listen, Jim, there's something
I got to tell you.
A few years ago, Flass and his people
started busting drug dealers,
taking over their stash houses,
running them themselves.
Now? You tell me this now?
Look, I respond to crises
as they arise.
I'm not a forward planner like you.
I didn't tell you then
because I didn't want to get you
all riled you up,
but I'm telling you now
because I want you to stop.
Flass is protected.
By who?
Serious people.
Really high up. Big money.
For all I know, the commissioner
gets a piece too.
You mess with Flass,
you can forget going back to Arkham.
These guys do not play.
These stash houses, think you can get
me a location on them?
Did you not hear a word I just said?
The stash houses
could give us evidence
linking Flass to Littlefield's
murder.
We nail him for Littlefield,
we can nail him for Winkler.
- Jim.
- I can't let it be, Harvey.
You should know that by now.
Mick, it's Harv.
You know that thing you
and Donnie were working on?
The Flass thing?
I need your help.
- Prime spot for a stash house.
- Yeah.
Delaware.
Hand over the boxes.
You don't learn, do you?
Get out of my face.
Hey. Hey!
No need to rough each other up,
gentlemen.
I got a warrant.
Giving us the legal right
to search and seizure.
It seems this warehouse
was being used as a home base
by the Uptown Assassins.
You expect us
to believe you got a signed warrant
to clear your own stash house?
On the commissioner's request.
Signed by Judge Bam-Bam.
Guess you don't have
a leg to stand on.
"Homicide."
- So, what's our next step?
- Next step?
We got nothing to tie Flass
to the drugs or the murders.
Murder. Just one.
Internal Affairs just ruled Winkler's
death as a suicide.
They're releasing the body
to his wife.
Leon was so very happy.
This just can't be right. Can't be...
A suicide?
He stabbed himself in the back
with an ice pick? That's absurd!
A ruling this quick means
the commissioner was involved.
Screw the commissioner.
Going forward with this
puts all of our jobs at risk.
Look, I want to help you, Jim.
There are people here in GCPD
who want to help you.
- So why don't they?
- They have. I have.
And we learned the hard way.
With men like Flass,
you need more than words.
You need results.
And that's not gonna happen
this time around.
So, do us all a favor
and move on to the next vic.
Please.
Where you going?
Back in an hour.
- Listen to this. This is classic.
- Stop it.
Hey, come on.
"Dear Miss Kringle,
your eyes are as green as a meadow.
Your smile is as bright as the sun.
Your skin is as white as a snowflake.
It seems like your life is fun."
- Really?
- Oh, hey!
It's the writer himself.
It's a real piece of work
you got there, perv.
I wouldn't quit your day job
if I were you.
Roger, dodger.
- Roger, dodger?
- Stop it.
What a creep.
One, two, three. One, two, three.
One.
Now. Now, you are getting it.
You are so graceful
for such a big man.
Isn't he graceful, Oswald?
Yes, Mother.
Jim.
Welcome.
Come in.
Another handsome man at the party.
I am so lucky.
This is Jim Gordon,
the detective friend
I was telling you about.
Oh. So nice to meet
a friend of Oswald's.
I am Gertrud Kapelput.
Nice to meet you too, Mrs. Kapelput.
Mother, Jim
and I have very important business.
No. Oh, sad. Oh, no, sad.
A little soon to be celebrating,
don't you think?
Well, don't just stand there. Sit.
This won't take long.
I insist. Sit.
I'm so very glad you called,
Jim Gordon.
It's been far too long
since we've seen each other.
I was beginning to think
you'd forgotten about me.
I need a favor.
Do you know anything
about a narcotics detective
by the name of Arnold Flass?
I've heard the name.
I'm investigating him
and his crew for murder,
but I've hit a wall.
He's too well-connected.
I figured since Maroni runs
the drug trade
maybe you could find somebody
with the goods on Flass? But...
Say no more.
Favor is done. I'll make some calls.
And what do I owe you in return?
Friends don't owe friends, silly.
They just do favors
because they want to.
Because they're friends.
Nobody gets hurt.
Of course. No one gets hurt.
Champagne?
Oh, dear me.
What happened here?
Call Falcone.
No kidding?
Thank you. Thank you, boys. Lovely.
No. I am dancing still.
- You may go.
- Oh, why you make them go?
Gabe, on your way to help
my dear friend Jim,
could you be a gentleman
and take Mother home?
Sure thing, boss.
Come on, Mrs. K.
A palace.
My boy has a palace.
Such a good boy.
Don't worry.
I will be back.
I wanna be somebody else today
I wanna take my shoes out it
Ain't like me to complain
But it just feels like I'm losing
Ladies and gentlemen, friends,
celebrities from around the world,
my name is Oswald Cobblepot.
Here we are at last.
It is with deep and sincere pleasure
that I bid you welcome
to the official grand opening
of my newest night spot, the...
Not bad.
I do believe you need
to project more.
Just to create a bit more excitement
for the audience.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to Fish Mooney's.
Like that.
What kind of weirdo plays chess
with himself?
Don't you have a butler to do
that kind of stuff with you?
He's making lunch.
I got your message.
I'm glad you're safe.
Alfred made me go out of town.
Switzerland. We have a house there.
Chalet, I guess.
A chalet?
It's basically a house.
Why did you want to see me?
We're friends, aren't we?
You've been driving around
looking for me.
Sending messages. What's up?
I got you a present.
It looks like the town we stayed in.
Whoa!
Thank you.
Also, I wanted to know if...
if you wanted to stay here
in my house.
Why?
I figure we can help each other out.
You can help me find the man
who killed my parents
and I can give you
a better place to live.
What's better about it?
Listen, kid. Chill.
I came here to tell you to stop
hassling me.
- Hassling you?
- Yeah.
You're beginning to bug me.
I thought we were friends.
Listen, I lied.
I didn't see who killed your parents.
I didn't see his face.
I don't understand.
I lied so I wouldn't get locked up
in juvie.
So, it's no use buying me presents,
or sending me messages,
or trying to hang out.
There's no point
because I can't help you.
Pinky Littlefield was light
two weeks running.
If you don't pay up,
there's consequences.
Flass killed him to send a message.
But please, please!
I swear that's all I know.
- You sure?
- I swear, man, I swear!
I believe you.
But I think I'll need something
a bit more tangible.
No, no, no! Please, no!
No! No! Please, no!
I swear, man! I swear!
How are you liking show business now?
Please, Miss Mooney.
You're making a mistake.
I... I beg of you, let me speak.
I know we've had our differences.
We could combine our forces.
Think how'd we fool everyone.
Me work with you?
I found you.
I made you!
When you walked in here,
you were a sad little wannabe.
Remember that, Butch?
You were so afraid.
Shook like a leaf in fall.
You're a servant.
An umbrella boy.
You're a nobody.
This nobody still outfoxed you
at every turn.
I was working for Falcone
the whole time!
And you didn't have
the sense to see it!
Hello. Seems like Mooney's
is the place to be today.
- Come on, come on!
- No!
Come on!
Go, go, go!
Here.
You got to go!
I'll slow them down!
- No, no!
- Go!
Hello, again.
Where is she?
What do you think, girls?
Should we kill him...
or should we take him home
to play with?
Mr. Nygma?
Miss Kringle?
- Am I interrupting?
- Yes.
I'm surgically removing
the onions from my takeout,
so if you don't mind...
Mr. Nygma, I owe you an apology.
I didn't give Arnold the card.
He found it in my desk.
He has a strange sense of humor.
I thought your card was very...
thoughtful.
I guess. Anyway, I'm sorry.
- Miss Kringle, would you...
- No, no, no.
Please, don't say anything else.
Just, please.
There's hope.
What's this?
Murder weapon and a tape
of Delaware rolling on Flass.
Smart cookie, that one.
Flass gave me the ice pick
to throw away.
Delaware kept it in case
he had to cover his own ass.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Master Bruce?
She was lying.
Oh.
I see.
Shall I get a broom then?
Or would you rather continue crying
over the shattered fragments
of your young dreams?
Yes, Alfred. A broom.
Very good, Master Bruce.
I'll find other leads.
No doubt.
I knew she was a wrong one.
Arnold Flass!
You're under arrest for the murder
of Leon Winkler.
Keep walking, mutt. You got nothing.
That's 20 years upstate right there.
Delaware gave you up.
Jimbo, you really think these guys
are gonna let you arrest me?
These are my friends.
- This is my house.
- This is not your house.
You're a drug dealer and a murderer.
You don't belong here.
You don't deserve the badge.
You believe this crap?
How long you been here?
A few months?
Why don't you come preach to me
in five years?
He murdered Leon Winkler!
An innocent man who trusted us!
Who trusted this!
- That's right.
- Yeah.
Enough to step forward
and help us solve a case.
A man who died so Detective Flass
could protect himself.
I.A. ruled it a suicide.
I'm arresting this man.
Get real, dumb-ass. I'm protected.
You can help me or you can try
and stop me.
Either way, I'm doing my duty.
Hey, back off, all right?
I'm protected! Get out of here.
Shut up, Flass.
Arnold Flass,
you're under arrest for murder.
The hell do you think you're doing?
Are you crazy?
Read him his rights.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
You can't keep me in here!
- You have the right to an attorney.
- Do you know how many people I got?
- If you cannot afford one...
- You don't know me. You got nothing!
Thanks, Cap.
Here.
So, what's the plan?
I'm gonna leave town,
lay low for a while.
But then I'm gonna come back
and kill Penguin...
when the time is right.
Listen, you know,
I have your best interests at heart.
- Don't come back.
- No.
You will see me again.
And in the meantime, do me a favor.
Find Butch.
And if he's alive, help him.
I will.
See you soon.
Be good.
Always.
- Good night.
- Night, Detective.
Yo.
That big guy visit you?
- Give you the package I sent?
- Yeah.
Thanks. That was...
Yo, this... so this means we're even?
I ratted out Flass like you wanted.
So now you back off, right?
Nothing more is gonna happen
to my wife?
She's safe? My family's safe?
I don't understand
what you're talking about.
Okay, okay! No worries.
Look, never mind I pressed.
I won't say nothing to no one.
I'll... I'll... I'll pretend this
conversation never happened.
Okay? Just...
keep my wife and kids out of it.
I'm... I'm begging you.
Please.
Please!