Oh, God.
Toner
Gotham City Coroner
Hell of a way to start the day.
I mean, I just cleaned this.
Harvey.
Hey. Uniforms found the body.
No wallet, no ID, no watch.
He got beaten up pretty good.
I'm guessing the cause of death
is that gigantic gash
on the side of his neck.
You think?
What's all the black on him?
Ink? Paint?
- Good morning, Ed.
- Detective.
Going by overall coagulation,
I'd say time of death is midnight.
But he's only been here
for a couple hours.
Rats have just started on his ears.
Sneaky little buggers.
So not a mugging.
Muggers don't move the body.
Abrasions on his knuckles?
Put up a fight.
Yeah. Look at his suspenders.
I'm guessing
he's some kind of finance guy.
Maybe it was an abduction-ransom
thing gone wrong.
He resists, ka-chunk...
You wanna talk to the uniforms
who found the body?
You do it.
We should canvass the area, though.
A lot of homeless around here.
- I'll get some units on it.
- I'll handle it myself.
Hey, Joe. Go smoke somewhere else.
Come on, Jim, that's what we got
uniforms for. Let them do it.
And I'd rather handle it myself.
Detectives. I'm guessing I should run
all the prints.
- Yeah, Ed, run the prints.
- This one too?
Yeah, Ed. That one too.
It wasn't even a proper yacht.
It was more like a dinghy.
Can I help you?
- What a lovely brooch.
- Thank you.
May I have it?
I have a friend who would love that.
Excuse me?
I'm sorry.
May I please have it?
- You shouldn't have.
- I wanted to make a gesture.
I hope in time, we can be friends.
Friends?
Sure.
Why not? What's done is done.
I'm so glad you feel that way.
Don Maroni wants us
to clarify terms.
Well, it's business as usual.
Maroni still has his drugs,
his unions.
He pays tariff for the ports.
If he needs favors from the cops
or the mayor
Don Falcone will consider it.
And of course the families
still share Arkham.
And there's to be no blood spilled
on either side.
Not a drop.
Maybe just a drop.
Look at you.
Timothy, do you know this fellow
used to have your job?
Carried my umbrella
and thought it an honor.
Now look at him.
Has a seat at the table.
Things change, eh?
I've been blessed.
Perhaps I should open your gift.
My goodness.
That is beautiful.
Now I feel awful.
- I didn't get you anything.
- No.
Thank you.
- Sweet.
- That was uncalled for.
I brought you into my family
and I treated you like a son.
- And you betrayed me.
- For which I suffered.
Not enough.
When I order some fool killed,
I expect him to stay that way.
Your boss, Don Falcone
- expressly said...
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. He wants peace.
He's the only reason
why your ass is still alive.
And if I were you, I would pray
for his good health.
Oh, I do.
- I do.
- Good.
Because remember...
things change.
Convey my respects to your don.
Likewise.
Peace...
friend.
Come now, Master Bruce.
Had to happen sooner or later.
Is this really necessary?
Homeschooling is just as effective.
I can show you the data.
You need to be around children
your own age.
- Why?
- Because you do.
You know I despise
that sort of answer.
Don't you miss your mates?
Not really.
I've always found them
kind of childish.
That's what they're meant to be,
aren't they? It's what they do.
Don't you wanna be like a normal kid?
I'm not sure.
Define normal
and make a good case for it.
You're going to bloody school.
Now, start walking.
Good luck, lad.
Very sorry for your loss, ma'am.
Can you think of anyone
who'd wanna hurt your son, Coleman?
No, sir. Nobody.
He was a good boy.
Yes, ma'am. I can see that.
No arrests, an honest young man.
- What did he do for a living?
- He worked in a coffee shop.
When we found him, he was in a suit.
Suspenders.
He was looking for a job in finance.
He was very ambitious.
First in our family to go to college.
Who would do this, sir? Why?
We'll do our best to find out, ma'am.
Gordon's finishing up
with the mother.
So far,
nothing off the severed thumb.
And none of the city's ERs have
seen any thumb-less guys.
- You think he went black market?
- That's next on my list.
- How's Gordon?
- Angry.
How would you feel if every cop
in the building ran out on you?
Now they treat him
like he's got the plague.
Seeing him reminds them
of what cowards they all are.
I'm sorry, Cap. I...
I didn't mean you.
Nope. You're right.
But he's gotta get over that.
Can't do this job alone.
Lucky he's got you.
Yeah.
So beautiful.
As soon as I saw it,
I thought of you.
Such a good son.
Put it on, put it on.
Wha... What happened? Who did this?
Nobody. It's just a scratch.
Is your mother a fool? No.
Someone is being mean to my boy.
It's a tough business.
The restaurant business
is so tough these days.
Why is that?
My success makes other
people envious.
So tell the boss on these people.
This person isn't scared of the boss.
Not like they should be.
- I don't know why.
- I know.
When I was in school,
Magda Himmelfarb was so mean to me
and teacher did nothing.
Why?
Because such a good dancer, I was.
And Magda, with her nice hair
and her big bosoms, a cart-horse.
I meant,
why did the teacher do nothing?
Why you think?
Private lessons, they said.
I put stop to that.
You told on them.
Oh, no.
I denounced Magda's father
to secret police.
Three weeks he's been turning
up his nose at my traps.
And now, now today,
a smidge of camembert
and Mr. Rat, he cannot resist.
No. Oh, can you?
Can you, my little greedy baby?
I found out your secret.
Yes.
Everybody has a secret.
Rat
Morphine! Morphine!
They teach you that in med school?
Bullock.
Is that Kenny Suffield?
Smash-and-grab guy.
Also a real hound with the ladies.
- Who shot him?
- I don't ask.
Well, me and my partner
are doing all the rounds
of you black-market sawbones.
Guy we're looking for would've
come in early this morning,
- missing a thumb.
- Sorry.
You'd tell us if you knew,
wouldn't you, Doc?
I mean, that's the deal, right?
You give us info
and we let you keep operating.
That's a pun. Operating.
Bullock, black ink?
Just like on the victim?
Oh, Doc...
Fine.
He came in about 3.00 this morning.
Didn't give a name
but this dropped out of his pocket.
- Sionis Investments.
- What did he look like?
Mid-20s, suit, suspenders.
Just like our dead guy.
Sorry, Doc.
This is Gordon.
I need an ambulance and
a black-and-white at 1856 Wilton...
Wait. Just a second.
Just get me Alvarez, will you?
Bullock. Bullock, what the hell, man?
I got a deal with that guy.
- Deal's off.
- But I told you everything.
Yeah, after we caught you in a lie.
He always lies. You just squeeze him.
- You're screwing the rest of us.
- Oh, yeah?
- How's that feel? You like it?
- Hey, enough! Enough!
I get it, I get it, huh?
None of these sons of bitches
had your back when it mattered.
But where was I?
I was there, remember?
With Falcone, the Mayor,
blaze of glory?
- Be nice for my sake.
- I am being nice.
Haven't you learned your lesson?
We're only alive
because Falcone let us live.
You gotta go along to get along, Jim.
No, I don't.
You think locking up Doc Scumbag
there is gonna make a difference?
I'm on your side, I proved that.
Yeah, you did.
So I'm asking you, please,
let the Doc out, and tomorrow
you and I will go check out
this Sionis Investments together.
All right, partner?
Sorry, Harv.
- This ain't right, Harvey.
- Alvarez, put a zipper on it!
- Jim.
- Barbara, what are you...
I heard someone come in.
You didn't turn on the lights.
- So you got out my spare?
- You were late. I got nervous.
I... God.
Not the best idea to be handling
a firearm when you've been drinking.
I'm sorry.
Look, you've been through a lot.
It's over now.
I am scared, Jim.
Everywhere I go, I can...
I can feel that monster Zsasz
stalking me, and I...
He's not a monster.
He's just a man.
I won't let anyone hurt you.
How can you promise me that?
Tell me it'll be okay.
Please tell me
there really aren't any monsters.
Just...
lie if you have to.
There aren't any monsters.
When are we gonna get out of here?
That's up to you.
Morning.
Hey...
I didn't think you were up.
That last night was just nerves
and way too much to drink.
I said I wanted half your life,
and I've got it.
Leave the gun.
- I wish it wasn't like this.
- Do you really?
Ignore me. I'm just tired.
Go. Catch some bad guys.
Go get them.
Forensic examination by Edward Nygma.
8.42am. GCPD morgue.
The room is approximately 19°C.
I ate half a cranberry muffin
earlier, saving the rest.
What do a dead man, a cruise ship,
and an emu have in common?
Correct. Nothing.
Ever more curious.
He what?
Nygma, how many times have I told you
to stay the hell out of here?
But I discovered something...
You'll discover your butt on
the street if you keep doing this.
Out.
Your loss.
You sloppy ignoramus.
- Hi, Bruce.
- Hi.
Brucey, how you doing?
Tommy, hey.
- I'm well. How are you?
- You know, chilling.
So your mom and dad got killed, huh?
Yes.
Did you see the whole thing?
The blood and everything?
- I'd rather not talk about that.
- I was just interested.
Never seen a real dead body.
Was there guts?
I'll be going to class now.
Forgive me, Mother,
for I have sinned.
Funny.
Feels weird meeting here.
You don't want anyone
to see us together.
Falcone has his eyes everywhere.
So where are we?
I cook for him. I sing to him.
We go on walks.
I don't know whether I'm his maid,
his lover, or his mother.
Or all three. He cares about you.
Yeah.
Have you been inside
his private office?
Yeah, a few times.
Inside the right bottom desk drawer
is a ledger.
Copy the last two pages.
It'll be locked. You'll need a key
off of his key ring.
How do I get that?
Behind you is a vial.
Give it to him. He'll sleep like
the dead for two hours.
It won't kill him, will it?
Liza... you haven't got feelings
for the old man, have you?
Not at all.
No, it won't kill him.
Killing him now
would only create chaos.
I need to siphon his strength.
So when the time is right
taking over his organization
will be like slipping on a glove.
What if one of his men
catches me snooping?
Then you're probably dead.
You leave first.
Right, right, right.
I'm under a lot of pressure.
Success Today Ready For War
Something tells me
we came to the right place.
- You think?
- Mr. Sionis will see you now.
Richard Sionis.
James Gordon.
This is my partner, Harvey Bullock.
How can I help you, detectives?
I don't have much time.
You know this man? Coleman Lawson?
He might have interviewed for a job.
Sorry.
Any of your employees
miss work yesterday?
Any of them show up
today with an injured right hand?
I don't take roll call, Detective.
You mind if we check?
Perhaps you can tell me
what this is about.
Coleman Lawson was killed
two nights ago.
The man who did it
had your firm's card in his pocket.
There's a thousand ways
he could have gotten that.
What's with all the warrior baloney?
It inspires me.
High finance is a tough business.
In order to succeed,
you have to be a warrior.
No, you don't.
You have to be a good businessman.
Warriors fight wars. It's different.
So you fancy yourself a killer.
Have you killed people, Mr. Sionis?
Only metaphorically.
So all this is just juvenile
play-acting.
Exactly. Thus speaks a man
who's seen actual combat.
You've killed people for real,
haven't you?
True killers are easy to spot.
Yes, they are.
Why all the masks?
A shrink would say
you're hiding something.
To the contrary.
A mask hides the face,
but frees the soul.
A mask speaks the truth.
Deep.
How come so many of your employees
have scars and injuries?
Our touch football games
get very rough.
You're a liar, Mr. Sionis.
Such fire.
You must miss the battlefield
desperately.
I imagine killing gets
quite addictive.
You murdered Coleman Lawson,
didn't you?
Prove it.
We will.
I'd give you a "good cop" routine,
but it's not in my tool kit.
GCPD. Turn around slowly.
Let me see those hands.
Don't move.
Should have waited for me.
Hey, Brucey.
It's Bruce.
No Y.
No parents either,
so I can call you what I like.
Please get out of my way.
Snobby little jerk, isn't he?
For an orphan.
You're being very unkind.
I don't understand why.
Boy, you're a weirdo.
Your mother must have...
Don't talk about my mother.
Oh, really?
Oh, is that Timothy?
We met at Fish Mooney's.
I'm the fellow
who used to have your job.
I was hoping to ask you
a few questions.
I don't know anything...
There'll be time for that.
First things first.
Most killers leave their prints
at the crime scene. But not you, no.
You left your whole thumb
in the dead guy's mouth.
You got style. I like you, kid.
This is your last chance.
Once we walk out that door,
it's over.
- It was self-defense.
- Of course, it was.
Wasn't that what I said, Jim?
Didn't I say
it was probably self-defense?
Talk.
Gordon's getting the rest
of his statement.
Apparently, it was part of
the hiring process.
Sionis told the top
three candidates to fight it out.
They weren't supposed to fight
to the death but...
This is unbelievable.
They all signed confidentiality
agreements.
So they're accomplices
to whatever happens.
Do we know where the fight was held?
Some old office building.
The windows were boarded up.
And he was taken there blindfolded.
Yes, Ed.
Printer toner.
Do you know what he's talking about?
The medical examiner's report said
it was black ink...
but I did my own examination
and it was printer toner.
Also, I pulled staples
from his shoulders
and found graphite chips
between his ribs.
Your man was killed in an office.
Yeah, we're kind of past that, Ed.
But thanks.
Is there something else?
Yes, it made me think of a case
from a year ago.
Young man, business suit.
Esophagus lacerated from index cards
shoved down his throat.
So I did some digging.
How many other bodies were killed
with office supplies?
Four. In the last three years.
Get that man to sign a confession.
Now.
I think we have a problem.
I explained to Detective Gordon,
as counsel to Mr. Adams
I advised him against
speaking further.
Also, any statements he has made
will be considered having
been made under duress.
And how much is Sionis
paying him to take the fall?
Good day.
He showed up before
Adams could sign his statement.
Gotta figure out
where Sionis is staging his fights.
I'll run all the buildings he
or his company owns in Gotham.
- This make any sense to you?
- No.
But how is it any worse
than the Goat or Balloon Man?
When did this become normal
for this city? What changed?
Maybe nothing. It was always
just below the surface
only needed a spark.
What? Thomas and Martha Wayne
being killed?
I'm not blind, Gordon.
I know you're still looking into it.
But how could their deaths
have caused all this?
Why were they so important?
I think it's what they represented.
A different Gotham.
Decent. Hopeful.
Whatever it was, it's gone now.
When Zsasz came for you,
I should have stayed.
I told you to go.
That doesn't matter.
I should have stayed.
- Let's get this guy.
- Yeah.
Tad late, Master Bruce. Oi.
- Oi, what happened to you?
- I'm perfectly fine.
What happened?
Someone spoke disrespectfully
about my mother.
Oh, did they, now?
Well, I hope you broke their bastard
teeth for them.
No.
He's much bigger than me, and I...
I'm not good at fighting.
Didn't hurt him at all.
Not at all.
Don't tell the school.
Not bloody likely.
Take a look at this.
Sionis owns half of Gotham.
All right. We'll split up.
Focus on the buildings
that are abandoned
or under construction first.
This son of a bitch
is not getting away.
I'll say one thing.
He has your number.
- What are you talking about?
- Sionis.
You may not have put down
Cobblepot, Jimmy boy
but you've got a demon in you.
You can call yourself a soldier
but all this fighting Falcone,
fighting other cops, you love it.
So when you find something
that seems remotely possible,
call me.
Barbara. Everything all right?
Fine. I just... I wanted to check in.
Look, can we talk later? I'm kind
of in the middle of something.
Of course. I love...
Hey.
Boss wants his tea.
It's almost ready.
GCPD.
Anybody else here?
That... would be a yes.
Collette
Hey.
Hi.
Girl's gotta shop.
This is your father's watch.
Don't you lose it, now.
Tommy Elliot's house.
- Don't you be scared.
- I'm not.
I'm visualizing what I'm going to do.
Because if you don't want to do this,
there's no shame in it.
There would be immense shame in it.
What the hell are you doing here?
We have unfinished business.
Listen, if you think
you're gonna tell my parents...
- Are you crazy?
- Don't talk about my mother.
Master Bruce!
Point well made, I think.
You all right, mate?
Any broken bones?
He... he tried to kill me.
That's right.
He did. He tried to kill you.
Just you remember that
next time you see him.
And you remember that I let him try.
Now, let's get some ice
on those knuckles.
What do you fancy for your dinner?
- Pizza.
- Pizza?
Superb choice, Master Bruce.
Jim, where the hell are you?
My list crapped out. Call me.
Nygma, Gordon hasn't called in,
has he?
No.
But if the detective becomes
the mystery, then...
Wake up.
Detective Gordon. Wake up!
So, three of you
applied for a position at my firm.
I explained then, you can use
anything here as a weapon.
The last man standing gets the job.
However, tonight is special.
You see the man without the mask?
Whoever kills him is the victor.
Listen to me. I'm a cop.
So far none of you
have broken any laws.
Let the games begin.
One last chance. Nobody move.
Oh, and I'll throw in
a million-dollar signing bonus.
Oh, crap.
Alvarez, I need help checking
these addresses.
- Gordon might be in trouble.
- Busy.
I'm gonna remember
that next time your wife calls
asking where you are, you putz.
Collins, listen up, man.
Can I have some help?
Now listen up, you sons of bitches!
So you don't like Gordon.
Fine. He can be a total ass hat,
but he is still a cop!
And not one of you, not one,
stood up when he needed it.
That ain't happening twice.
I need help
checking these addresses. Now.
Give me a couple.
Okay.
- But you cover with my wife, right?
- Yeah.
It's over.
I knew you had a killer in you.
So, where are your brother police?
Did they abandon you?
I don't need them.
Seems like I'll have to
give myself the million dollars.
Jim?
Jim!
Thanks.
You're welcome.
If I die
And my soul be lost
Ain't nobody's fault but mine
If I die and my soul be lost
You better have a good reason
for being here.
Did you get what I asked for?
I want out.
No.
He's gonna find out.
Maybe not today, but soon.
Is it worth it?
You are rich.
People are afraid of you.
- Is that not enough?
- No.
It's not.
I grew up not too far from here.
One bedroom, cold water,
just me and my mama.
I used to sleep in a bed
behind a curtain.
It's where I would hide
when she entertained men.
And that's where I was
when he killed her.
One of Falcone's men.
They didn't like the service.
I hid there, silent, until morning.
With my mama two feet away from me.
That night I made a promise.
To get revenge.
To never again be powerless.
To never let any man,
any man be over me.
This is about keeping
that promise to that little girl.
So what's this about?
This is a thread.
I pull this and Falcone comes undone.
You're scared.
But I won't let anything happen
to you, and that's a promise.
I want you to say,
"I believe you, Mama."
I believe you, Mama.
That's my girl.
The thing is, when I had your job
I had someone asked me
what is Ms. Mooney's secret
I could have answered.
Timothy.
I think you're holding back on me.
Okay. I...
- I might have heard her with Butch.
- Talking about what? Whom?
Fal...
Falcone.
She said our...
"Our friend with Falcone." That's it.
She was whispering. Please...
She has someone close to Falcone.
Of course.
Thank you.
- No one can find the body.
- No.
We are at peace after all.
No. No, please. No, no!
Alvarez and Collins
are bringing in Sionis' minions.
Pansies tried to rabbit when
they saw you cuffing their boss.
You okay?
- Essen told me you made a speech.
- I wouldn't call it a speech.
- She said you called me an ass hat.
- I did call you that.
Thank you.
For having my back.
Now and before.
Just try not to be such a pain
in the neck.
Makes my day harder.
You know, you were wrong.
What you said earlier.
It's not that I love fighting,
but I'm not afraid to either.
And if we don't fight for this city,
who will?
I'm not gonna stop, Harvey.
Falcone, the Mayor, every cop I know
that's dirty, I'm gonna get them.
You should know that.
Go home, Jim.
You were listening tonight,
weren't you?
You gonna get in trouble, old woman.
Heard you telling that girl stories.
A lie with a heart of truth
is a powerful thing.
Go on. It's late.
Incoming: Jim
Jim
Hey, it's me. I'm coming home soon.
Everything's gonna be better.
I promise.
I love you.
Hey, Gordon. You got a minute?
Can it wait?
Kind of on my way out of here.
Some uni's brought in a perp.
Claims to know you.
- Oh, yeah? What's the charge?
- B & E. Some fancy store uptown.
Pretty professional job.
Kid didn't even trip the alarm.
Kid?
- A boy or a girl?
- Girl.
Said to ask if you'd been down
any sewers lately.
Hey, Detective.
Miss me?
I enjoyed it.
I enjoyed hurting him.
Of course, you did.
He deserved it.
I'm so angry all the time.
Will it ever go away?
That I don't know.
Alfred...
can you teach me how to fight?
Yes...
Master Bruce.
Yes, I can.