NYGMA:
Previously on Gotham...
GABE: Cops aren't gonna let you
within 100 feet of Galavan.
Let us whack him for you.
No.
He's mine.
Shoot him, Detective.
He killed my mother, Jim.
(gunshots)
You have the Wayne boy.
THEO:
Not yet.
There are some practical matters
that have to be resolved first.
See this finger?
I've got little Bruce
wrapped tight around it.
NYGMA:
I had to kill him.
'Cause he hit you.
I love you.
Kristen? Kristen?
(sobbing):
No!
Within a year, Jim and I
will be back together.
(chuckles)
Want to know why?
Because we're both the same.
We both have
a dark side.
(bell tolling)
(organ playing)
Ready for the practice run?
I'm ready to skip this
and get married.
Me, too.
Let us rehearse the vows.
Barbara Kean...
Mmm.
do you take James Gordon
to be your unlawfully
wedded husband
to have and to hold...
I'm sorry, Father.
You said "unlawfully wedded."
(whispering):
Barbara,
just answer him, for God's sake.
(gasping)
I'm waiting.
GORDON:
Barbara,
what's wrong?
(bird tweeting)
(laughter)
How did you do that? (laughs)
(guns clicking)
(gasps)
(panting)
(sighs)
Bad dream.
♪ ♪
(sighs)
Doesn't being mayor mean
you can sleep in?
Jim Gordon has forced us
to accelerate our plans.
About time.
I'll meet with Bruce Wayne
this morning.
If all goes well, I'll have his
company by the end of the day.
I still don't see how
you can get Bruce Wayne
to turn over
his family's legacy.
You're not that charming.
I'm going to offer him the thing
he wants most in the world.
Still,
it will be delicate.
Jim Gordon must
not be allowed to interfere.
But his sudden death
would upset Bruce.
So we need him distracted,
occupied,
and then...
Have you told her?
Told me what?
(whispering):
I love my present.
Does it mean
what I think it does?
Yes, my dear.
Today is the day
you get to kill Jim Gordon.
(sighs)
GORDON:
The breakout at Arkham,
the massacre of the GCPD,
the gala, the arsons,
it was Galavan.
He's behind everything.
And you have proof of this?
I have Penguin,
and I have Gilzean.
Both criminals.
Both in the wind.
Given the circumstances
under which
I obtained the information,
I think it's safe to say
they were telling the truth.
Maybe they are.
But you have no legal evidence,
no proof,
not a single hard lead to go on.
You bring in Galavan
with what you have now,
and he'll just laugh at you.
He won't laugh long.
Are you gonna rough him up
a little?
Lawless thuggery,
is that your plan?
You want to arrest Galavan?
You do the police work
and you bring me back
some real proof.
THOMPKINS:
Can you blame him?
You're going after a man
who was elected mayor yesterday.
The most popular figure
in Gotham.
Galavan is dirty.
I'd bet my life on it.
Well, don't.
Don't what?
Don't bet your life on it.
I know that look
in your eye, Jim.
Be cool.
Do not make this personal.
Well, it is personal, isn't it?
Only if you make it that way.
OFFICER: Suspect! Suspect! Put
your hands where I can see them!
Right there!
♪ ♪
Hi, Jim.
Long time no see.
♪ ♪
You said you'd
only talk to me.
I'm listening.
BARBARA: Yes.
Here it is.
Is there any chance
I could get a latte
or something?
This is not a game, Barbara.
Oh.
Of course it is.
It's a game you've been losing.
Big-time.
It is not a game.
(chuckles)
It must be killing you.
All that righteous indignation
with no place to go.
Why are you here?
Don't act all calm
and businesslike.
Rough me up a little,
if you want.
I don't want to do that.
I don't want to hurt you.
I want to help you.
I know...
you want to hurt me,
just a little.
I've been a very bad girl.
No.
You're a good woman.
You're just sick, is all.
(crying)
Oh. (chuckles)
I knew it.
I knew you still had
feelings for me.
Of course I have feelings.
(laughs)
Talk to me.
I will.
But first I want
to show you something.
It's not far away,
won't take long.
Well, what is it?
What do you want to show me?
It's a surprise.
Don't worry,
it's a good one.
And then after that,
I will tell you everything.
Everything about what?
Is it about the breakout
at Arkham?
Was it Galavan?
(chuckles)
Wouldn't you like to know?
(knocking)
OFFICER:
Detective Gordon?
(sighs)
Okay, that's someone telling you
that my lawyer is here.
Why don't you take five minutes
to think about it?
(knocking)
Detective Gordon,
time's up.
♪ ♪
BARNES:
What is she playing at?
GORDON:
Not sure, sir.
I suggest we play along
and find out.
I'll go see this thing
she wants to show me.
Jim, she's mentally ill.
Like hell.
She's sharp as a nail.
This is a trap.
Yeah. Either way,
it's too risky.
What choice do we have, huh?
She won't talk.
And kissing her
didn't work out, did it?
That was a judgment call, sir.
Judgment? Really?
Let's focus
on the issue at hand.
It's my official opinion
as chief medical examiner
that Miss Kean
is seriously mentally ill
and should be in a hospital,
getting treatment.
Yes. Tomorrow.
Look, I suggest we play along,
let her think
she's in control.
I can still work on
her inside the car.
Maybe I can find out
something useful.
She's our only link to Galavan.
It's worth the risk.
All right, do it.
(car engine humming)
(engine shuts off)
(birds chirping)
(insects trilling)
♪ ♪
(grunting)
Oh, sorry, Miss Kringle.
(door closes)
You have a visitor,
Miss St. Cloud.
Hi.
BRUCE:
Hello.
My uncle will be just a moment.
He wanted me to apologize
for keeping you waiting.
(short laugh)
It's fine.
Do you have any idea
why he wanted to see me?
He told me he had
something for you.
He seemed excited.
It was totally goofy.
I can't picture him goofy.
I am so sorry
to keep you waiting.
I'll see you later.
Bye.
Please.
♪ ♪
Meet the new crop
of Strike Force members.
We're throwing them in
the deep end, but they're ready.
They'll be shadowing you
in a TAC SUV.
I'll be monitoring
from here.
The second
I don't like something,
I'm pulling the plug--
agreed?
TWO OFFICERS:
Yes, sir.
Gordon?
Agreed.
He's too wrapped up
in this thing emotionally.
I need to know that one of you
isn't gonna get sucked into all
these mind games that Ms. Kean
is gonna be pulling out there.
Not to worry--
no one's ever accused me
of getting sucked into
mind games.
Just follow my orders,
understood?
Understood, Captain.
I'm glad we had
this chance to talk.
GORDON:
Hey, look.
I don't like this
any more than you do.
But it is the only way.
No, this is you, Jim.
This is all you.
She sucked you
right back in, didn't she?
Because she still
has a hold on you.
Her sickness and yours
feed off each other.
What do you mean, my sickness?
I'm not sick.
You see an abyss,
and you run toward it.
That's not healthy.
I'm just doing my job.
BULLOCK:
Moving out!
Hey, Lee.
You don't mind if I borrow him
for a little while, do you?
(laughing)
I want to ask
you a question.
If you could have
one dream come true,
what would that be?
I would find the man
who killed my parents.
What would you do
if you found him?
I would kill him.
What a young tiger you are.
My dream?
I would save this city.
I would rid Gotham
of corruption,
crime
and poverty.
Sounds good.
How would you do that?
Oh, I have plans, schemes,
ideas aplenty.
But... I need help.
I need your help.
Of course.
And perhaps in return,
I could help you
with your dream.
How so?
(chuckles)
MAN:
Get those vehicles
out of the way!
You good?
Anything that makes Captain
Barnes' tight ass nervous,
I'm all for.
Watch your head.
So, you want to tell us
where we're going?
Head downtown.
(tires screech)
Bruce, your family
helped build this city.
The Wayne name is synonymous
with growth, strength
and prosperity.
It's also a lie.
Please explain what you mean.
I've been investigating Wayne
Enterprises for quite some time.
You know what I found?
Toxic waste dumps.
Illegal weapons contracts.
Use of banned chemicals.
Nightmarish experiments.
It can't continue.
Please, understand
this isn't about corruption.
It's about saving
innocent lives.
You have my word.
I will look into all of it.
And I will stop
whoever's responsible.
No, Bruce, you won't.
You can't.
People often underestimate me.
Wayne Enterprises
is a multi-billion-dollar
conglomerate,
with a board that will kill
to protect its secrets.
Who's underestimating who?
Why are you telling me this?
You obviously have a solution
you want to propose.
(chuckles)
You control 51%
of the voting shares
of Wayne Enterprises.
If you sell me
your shares,
I could take control,
do what needs to be done.
You would be
a cash billionaire with freedom.
You want my company?
I want to clean up Gotham.
Protect its citizens.
Return the city to what it was.
But I can't do it
without your help.
Wayne Enterprises
is my responsibility.
It's all I have
left of them.
I'm not just
offering you money, Bruce.
The night your parents
were killed,
you weren't supposed
to be there, were you?
No.
Your parents were headed
for the theater.
Your father changed his mind.
Suggested a movie.
Invited you along.
You got there late.
Uh...
I've never told anybody that.
He was following
your father that night.
Before the alleyway.
I'm a man
of considerable resources.
Even then,
it took some doing.
It's why I didn't want
to say anything last night.
I couldn't confirm it
until today.
If you sell me your company,
I will give you this
as a signing gift.
This is the name of the man
who killed your parents...
with documentary proof--
accomplices, motives,
why, how and who.
I will fix your company,
protect your legacy
and give you closure.
It's what your father
would've wanted.
And what Gotham
desperately needs.
I need your answer
by the end of the day.
(sirens wailing in the distance)
BARBARA:
Hey, Jim?
Cheer up.
Where's your spirit
of adventure?
Next right.
(tires screech)
I know it's a trap.
And Galavan's using you
like a puppet.
It is Galavan who's
behind all this, right?
Mm-mm-mm...
He's a psychopath,
Barbara.
He's using you.
He's laughing at you.
And when he's done with you,
you're just a loose end.
He'll kill you.
You really don't like
this Galavan guy, do you?
She's not
talking, Jim.
We need to turn
this car around now.
Just give me a little more time.
(grunts)
(sighs)
(liquid pouring)
Well, I'm afraid this
is as proper a burial
as circumstances allow.
But I thought we could have
one last meal together.
♪ ♪
I was a broken man,
Miss Kringle.
Two halves at war
with each other.
But thanks to you,
I am whole.
I will not forget you.
I take you by night,
by day take you back.
None suffer to have me,
but do from my lack.
What am I?
That some sort
of riddle?
You know, you really shouldn't
sneak up on people;
that's not polite.
Not usually any people
out here.
Can I interest you
in a tea sandwich?
A what?
What heck is in there?
Aah!
(sighs)
Great.
Now I've got to improvise.
Don't go anywhere.
Barbara, listen to me.
Are you listening?
You have a lifetime
ahead of you.
Don't throw it away
on madness.
BARNES:
Gordon, Bullock...
come in.
Go ahead, Captain.
I don't like this.
You're boxed in.
There's lots of cover,
high vantage points all around.
Perfect spot for an ambush.
Yeah, I gotta pull you out.
Turn around, you get nothing.
GORDON:
Not yet.
You hear me?
I'm pulling you out.
What was that, Captain?
You're breaking up.
Bullock! I swear to God,
if you disobey...
(radio shuts off)
Barbara, think hard.
Don't throw away your life.
What life?
You and me...
we had a life.
We had real love.
You asked me to marry you.
I booked a church.
I bought a damn
wedding dress.
Jim...
fool that I am,
I still love you, even now.
And I know
you still have
feelings for me,
'cause you said so.
We can talk about
our feelings later.
There's more at stake here.
I love you, Jim.
And I think, deep down,
you still love me.
Oh, for God's sakes,
Barbara, I don't give a...
(tires screeching)
Move, move!
(gunfire continues)
(shell casings clattering
on pavement)
(groans softly)
(echoing):
You gonna shoot me, Jim?
(groaning softly)
I want a 20-block perimeter,
with hard target searches
of every building,
business and bodega.
We kick down everything
with four walls and a roof.
Nobody sleeps
until our boy gets home.
Hey!
I told you to get
out of here.
You did?
Still a lot of ringing
in my head.
I must've missed it.
This is a direct order.
You don't belong here anymore.
Go home.
(insects trill quietly)
(panting)
Okay.
Well, let's see.
If I can't make the hole bigger,
then I'll make you smaller.
(chuckles)
♪ ♪
Who has eaten my sandwich?
For a secluded forest,
this place sure has
a lot of foot traffic.
(exhales)
Looks like it's gonna get
a tad crowded in there.
I'll be back.
Ah, there you are,
Master Bruce.
Been looking all over
the gaff for you.
Bit dreary down here,
isn't it?
Fancy something
to eat?
What's up?
I need to ask you a question.
And I need your word
that you're going to be
honest with me.
I always am.
All right, you have my word.
My training...
the skills that I need
to take down the corruption
at Wayne Enterprises.
How long will it take?
Well, there's no set timeline.
It doesn't really work
like that, does it?
Alfred. A year?
Two years?
Five?
Well, a lot longer than that,
for you to be the man
that you need to be.
But you will get there,
I promise you that.
Yeah, well, how many will suffer
in the meantime?
How many will die
because of the crimes
committed by my family's
company?
What...
Who...
Where's all this coming from,
Master Bruce?
Eh?
(bat chirping)
I spoke to...
Mayor Galavan this morning.
And...?
He wants me to sell him my
shares in Wayne Enterprises
so he can...
fix the company.
Clean up Gotham.
I see.
And what aren't you telling me?
He says...
that he knows the identity
of the man
who killed
my parents.
Which he's offering in return
for the company, right?
Yes.
Yeah, well, that's...
not an offer, is it?
That's bloody extortion.
Yeah, well, I can't help
but consider it, Alfred.
Well, you shouldn't.
There's a fine line
between extortion
and negotiation.
Yes, there is, Master Bruce,
but there's still a line.
My parents were killed
because of
the corruption
that my father
was trying to stop.
As of now,
their...
their deaths have been in vain,
but if Mayor Galavan
can truly...
if he can truly fix
Wayne Enterprises,
isn't it my moral... duty
to allow him to do so?
For my father's legacy?
Wayne Enterprises
isn't Thomas
and Martha Wayne's legacy.
That legacy is standing
right here.
With me.
Alfred, am I wrong if
I just want it all to be over?
(crying):
I just want...
I just want it to be over.
No, no. No, you're not wrong.
Come here.
You're not wrong.
(Bruce sobs)
(gasps)
(footsteps approaching)
(Barbara humming
"Bridal Chorus")
I know.
Can you believe it still fits?
Do you remember
when we first visited
this place?
How excited I was
to get married here?
How long do you think you have
before the GCPD finds us?
So typical.
I'm talking about us,
and your head...
(clicks tongue)
...is in work.
There is no "us."
What is all this?
Well, this is
my wedding dress.
The tailor still
had it in storage.
I mean, can you
believe the luck?
Or fate.
That's Father Callahan.
(muffled grunting)
You remember him, of course.
And these bozos...
(whimpering)
Oh!
Who knows?
But you can't have a wedding
without witnesses.
That's the law.
Barbara...
Jim...
please don't act all surprised
and aggrieved.
You knew,
from the start,
that this was a trap.
But you thought, "Hey,
"let the bad guys
take their best shot.
"I'm Jim Gordon.
"I'll find a way to win.
(laughs)
Or die."
It's option B, baby.
Your fondest wish come true.
I don't want to die.
Oh.
Hey.
Sure you do.
Aren't you tired of hiding
your true self?
Tired of lying to yourself?
To Lee?
I don't lie to Lee.
Really?
Let's ask her.
(wheels squeaking)
Lee!
(whimpering)
Savor every moment.
Hey, girlfriend.
We really need to talk
about this bad boy.
(gasps)
BARBARA (over speaker):
We had real love.
You asked me to marry you.
I booked the church.
I bought a damn wedding dress.
Jim...
fool that I am,
I still love you even now.
I booked the church.
I bought a damn wedding dress.
I want updates every 15 minutes.
Hang on.
Turn around
and get the hell out of here.
She's taking him to church.
Church? What church?
She talked about the wedding
they never had.
She wants a do-over.
Gotham Cathedral
is nearest to the snatch site.
That's where they are.
That's thin.
I know I am right.
I'll call you back.
Let's go.
(humming, chuckles)
So, Lee, how do you think
your relationship
with Jim is going?
This doesn't concern Lee.
Let her go.
This is between you and me.
Oh.
This...
is about all of us.
She deserves to know
exactly who you are.
I know who he is.
Oh, how could you
when he doesn't even know?
He is incapable
of being honest
with himself,
let alone anyone else.
What about you?
This entire day
has been a lie.
You were never going to
give up proof on Galavan.
Who?
Oh.
You want some honesty?
Fine.
Mayor James is alive and well
at a stash house
on China Docks.
Hmm, see?
Honesty.
Now you.
Who put him there?
Boring, Jim.
The Jim Gordon you know
is an act.
He's like an addict
who thinks he can dabble
in darkness
as long as nobody sees
the needle marks.
Everyone has an act.
(scoffs)
Did he tell you how
he got reinstated at the GCPD?
He killed a man for Penguin.
Wow!
Very good, Jim.
You did tell her.
We don't have secrets
between us.
Mm-hmm.
He's done a lot of things
that he's not proud of.
Everyone has.
Oh.
But you love him anyway,
is that right?
Despite all his faults.
Yes, I do.
Cute little do-gooder
Dr. Lee,
hmm... in love
with a cruel, cold,
death-obsessed sadist.
(laughs)
That's not Jim.
Do you think you know him
better than I do?
Hmm?
I love him, too, you know.
I know him
better than you do.
Okay, Barbara, I hear you.
You love him. We both love him.
That's okay.
But I love him more.
Okay, listen, Barbara.
I know that now. Please...
I'm gonna prove
that I love him more.
I am going to carve
your pretty face
off your skull.
And then you will
both understand
what true love is.
Okay, just one more thing.
What?
Your dress.
I-I love your dress.
I just want to know
where you got it.
Hmm.
Oh, um...
Drop the knife.
There he is.
My little monster.
Don't make me kill you.
Make you?
Jim,
you long
to kill me.
Do it, Jim.
Do me.
(sirens approaching)
Don't take another step.
(tires squealing,
sirens wailing)
Kill him!
(gunshots)
Go get her!
Jim!
It's over.
Not yet.
(wind whistling)
Hold on.
I'm sorry, baby.
I've been kind of
a bad date, huh?
I love you, baby.
No!
Some hedges and bushes
broke her fall,
but she's got
half a dozen broken bones
and a concussion.
She's critical.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
(door closes)
(engine starts)
Not now,
but when this is over,
we need to talk.
I know.
Tell me you got something
from her.
She didn't give up Galavan,
but she did say
Mayor James is alive.
Stashed in a safe house
on China Docks.
All mobile units, China Docks,
right now!
OFFICER (over radio):
Ten-four, Captain.
♪ ♪
GCPD!
(softly):
Help.
What is wrong
with these people?
Help me.
Mayor James?
Help me, please.
Oh, thank God.
Who did this to you?
Who do you think?!
BRUCE:
All the papers
seem to be in order.
You're making
the right decision.
Sign,
and the file is yours.
I...
I changed my mind.
I can't sell you my company.
Not for any price.
Alfred, get Bruce
away from him now.
Detective Gordon?
You're under arrest.
Surprised to see me?
(scoffs)
May I ask what the charge is?
The kidnapping and torture
of Aubrey James.
Cuff him.
(scoffs)
GORDON:
Get him out of here.
Where?
No!
Tell me who killed them!
Please.
I'll do anything.
(birds calling,
insects chirping)
NYGMA:
Finally.
(dogs barking in distance)
Oh!
(groaning)
Oh, my.
(panting) Mr. Penguin?
Help me, please.