Previously on "Gotham"...
GORDON: I'm arresting you
for the murder of the boy you blew up
under the Crown Point Bridge.
ZSASZ: You blew that kid sky-high.
You are lying.
You are a lying traitor.
I need you at the head of the GCPD.
Let them think you're a hero.
I screwed up, Harv.
Sofia hired the Pyg,
and I covered it up.
SOFIA: We all have to make sacrifices.
THOMPKINS: Thought it was
all about family.
SOFIA: Never said it was a happy family.
(THOMPKINS SCREAMS)
IVY: My friend thinks
we're here to rob you.
But I know
- you torture plants
- (GRUNTING)
in the name of science, Roland Charles.
Lee Thompkins may have made Ed strong,
but I see the other you...
- the Riddler.
- (NYGMA LAUGHING)
I'm back.
(LAUGHS)
(MAN LAUGHING)
(LAUGHING)
_
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
(CLEARS THROAT)
(CHUCKLES) _
_
(COUGHS)
(GRUNTS)
_
(TOILET FLUSHES)
(SNIFFS)
What's that smell?
_
(HIGH-PITCHED WHISTLING)
(CAR ALARMS RINGING IN DISTANCE)
Uncle Penguin sent me to get you.
Come on, let's get ice cream.
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com
(PUNCHES LANDING, MAN GRUNTING)
The Narrows is under new management.
(GRUNTING)
The Narrows is Sampson's turf.
(GRUNTS)
And Sampson...
well, collects protection.
(GRUNTING)
And people need to find out
what happens when you don't pay.
(GROANS)
(CRYING)
(GUN COCKS)
Please, my family.
Do I look like an animal to you?
I wouldn't hurt your family.
(SCREAMS)
Unless they don't pay me.
(SAMPSON LAUGHING)
Before Don Falcone died,
he warned me I had no idea
what I brought to the city.
I now know he was talking about the Pyg.
Somebody must have told him.
My guess, that person has evidence
that links Sofia to the Pyg's murders.
Why not come forward with what you know?
It has to be more
than just my word against hers.
Or are you afraid the truth
is gonna drag you down, too?
(GROANS) Harvey, we've been over this.
- When did you know?
- I swear,
I had no idea
until after it was too late.
And you can be pissed,
but this is bigger than both of us.
I need to know I can count on you.
Yeah, Jim.
I'll help you take down Sofia.
But then you're gonna have
to pay for what you done.
I personally guarantee it.
I know an ex-Falcone assassin.
Might have beans to spill.
Went by the name
of Scandinavian Skinner.
Sit tight.
I have history with the Skinner.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(CLATTERING)
SELINA: You know you have,
like, no food in here, right?
Selina?
What are you doing here?
What's-what's wrong?
Why does something have
to be wrong for me to come by?
Seriously?
I need help.
You mean money.
(SIGHS)
I stole something, fenced it,
and now I want to get it back,
and I'd steal it, but the fence
is difficult, so I need money.
Why don't you just ask
Barbara Kean for the money?
'Cause I don't want to get her involved.
Look, I'll-I'll pay you back.
I just... I don't have time,
because if the fence sells
what I gave them...
But you still haven't told me
why you want to give it back.
Because it's what I stole
from Roland Charles.
The... Wayne scientist...
That Ivy killed.
(SIGHS)
I didn't know
she was gonna do that, Bruce.
And I-I just...
You feel bad.
Look, if you don't want to help me,
then I'll just find another way.
Let me get some cash.
There's oatmeal raisin cookies
in the blue tin.
- (LOCK BUZZES, LATCH CLICKS)
- (BIRD CAWING)
- Why are you dragging me here?
- (ROARS)
Cobblepot.
Guy called, wanted me
to give you a message.
Finally.
"I could lend you a hand,
but you won't find me helpful.
My name may sound tasty,
but the flavor is dreadful."
Is it "knuckle sandwich"?
(CHUCKLING): Yeah.
No.
(OSWALD SHOUTS)
(BELL JINGLES)
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
(CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
Hello, Agnes.
Or should I say the Skinner?
Detective Bullock.
I don't go by that name anymore.
I'm retired.
- You kids, don't spoil your dinner.
- Okay, Grandma.
I'm looking for someone
who might have been
Don Falcone's eyes and ears
when he was down south.
Why would I tell you that?
Because we have history.
That history got me four years
in the Gulag.
Either you help me,
or I tell your beautiful
grandchildren how their meemaw
used to skin people alive.
CHILD: I wonder if they
come in double chocolate...
Hey, kids, you want to hear
- a really funny story?
- All right.
It's-it's all right. (CHUCKLES)
Never mind.
Falcone only really trusted
the bookkeeper.
The one who
always smelled of fish.
Mr. Penn?
Yeah. Penn.
But good luck finding him.
I heard he vanished.
Poof.
(DRUMMING COUNTER)
(SHOUTS)
How is Martin gone?
(SIGHS) Never mind.
Penguin is coming.
Go to Arkham and kill him now.
Okeydokey.
Oh, by the way,
a buddy of mine
just got out of the hospital
is looking for work.
You mind if he tags along?
Hi-ya.
Just make sure Penguin dies
choking on his own blood.
Why is Cobblepot in the infirmary?
Heard he mouthed off to a guard.
Then slipped and hit his head.
(WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(LOCK BUZZES)
(GASPS)
Bullock.
- This is a surprise.
- Hey, Oswald.
Good to see you, too.
I just had a few questions about
a former employee of yours.
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
- WOMAN: They got guns!
- Open that door!
(LOCK BUZZES)
(CLAMORING)
Get out of the way.
Clear out!
Move, move, move!
Hey!
You two! Don't come any closer.
Bullock?
Dude, I thought you stopped being a cop.
Guess it didn't take, huh?
Not so much.
- You remember Wendell, don't you?
- Howdy.
BULLOCK: I don't know
why you two are here,
and I don't care!
- Walk away.
- ZSASZ: See,
I'm afraid we can't do that.
We're not leaving here
without the Penguin.
ZSASZ: Harvey, do yourself a favor.
Give us Penguin, and...
live to get drunk another day, hmm?
As tempting as that sounds, no.
(ALARM BLARING, SIREN WAILING)
Let's go, let's go.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
It's okay.
We'll come back.
MAN: He's escaped!
Oswald Cobblepot has escaped!
(LOUD, OVERLAPPING CHATTER)
(GUNSHOTS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Nygma.
BRUCE: What?
You're just... different.
Different how?
You were a complete douche
bag to me at the club.
And now... you're not.
Listen, Selina, about that night...
Oh, no, you're not gonna try
to apologize to me, are you?
No, I just wanted to say...
Save it.
Because you're probably
gonna be a douche bag
to me later anyway.
Missed you, too.
Kitty cat.
Back so soon?
'Sup, Floyd?
I'm gonna need that stuff I
brought to you the other day.
Oh. You mean this stuff?
The stuff you tried to break in
and steal last night?
You think I wouldn't check the camera?
Great.
You remember what I said
about being a douche bag?
I'll pay double what you gave me.
This your bank?
How about I take the money...
...and I keep your stuff?
(GRUNTING)
(GUNSHOT)
Next time...
(GROANS)
- ...take the deal.
- (GROANS)
(GRUNTS) Got it.
I knew that as soon as I rescued Martin
that she'd send her hit men.
How is Martin?
Snug as a bug in a rug.
Here, will you hold this?
So, do you want to know how I found him?
So, it turns out, Zsasz...
huge fan of the disco.
So, I dress up as an old Polish woman...
Perhaps another time.
Now that Martin is safe, we need
to focus on killing Sofia.
- We need a power base.
- I know.
That's why we're here.
(UNLOCKING)
Hello. (CHUCKLES)
Ed. You're back.
- Mm-hmm.
- How are you doing?
Worlds better, honestly. Thank you.
I...
Oh, no. What happened to your hand?
Sofia Falcone
smashed it with a hammer
and then threw me out on the street
and put Sampson
in charge of the Narrows.
I see.
But, together, we can
get that bitch back.
We could show her she can't just
take everything we've built.
Yeah, Oswald, she can't help.
What is this?
What is going on? What's wrong with you?
I let him out of his cage,
and he, in turn, helped
me get out of mine.
You're him.
The Riddler.
Hi, Lee.
You know, I was really hoping
that you were still
running the Narrows,
maybe could help us, but...
guess not.
Yeah, so what's your
next brilliant idea?
Sofia will have turned
the Falcone mansion
into a stronghold.
It will be impossible to get at her.
Oswald, you think I don't
have a backup plan?
I'm gonna have Victor Fries
put you in a block of ice.
I'm gonna take you to Sofia
like a chilly Trojan horse,
- pretend to hand you over.
- (LAUGHS)
Are you kidding me?
It's a fantastic plan.
Try again!
- (CHUCKLES)
- All right.
Let me help.
Look, all of your capos have
pledged their loyalty to Sofia.
Do you think I can't handle it?
I know you can't.
Look what she did to me.
I will pull the trigger
on that bitch myself.
That's some tough talk, but
we both know that's just talk.
Enough! Both of you.
If we want to fight Sofia,
we need muscle!
I agree.
I can tell you where to look.
Don't you think he misses you?
Who is she talking about?
NYGMA: Grundy!
You down here, big fella?
It's your best friend and pal,
Edward Nygma.
Hey, guess what.
I'm smart again! (LAUGHS)
(FOOTFALLS APPROACHING)
(LIGHT SQUEAKS)
(WATER DRIPPING)
There he is.
Pale skin, nobody upstairs.
Who's my buddy?!
Correct. You.
Oh, boy. So we're corralling allies.
Penguin and I are gonna kill
Sofia Falcone, and we need
a big galoot like you for cannon fodder.
How's that sound?
(GROWLS)
What's your problem? Why are you
looking at me like that?
(GROWLS)
- (GASPS)
- (GROWLS)
Oh, dear.
You're not the only one who got smart.
- (GROANS)
- Okay, Butch, I helped you.
You remember? Hot.
Hot arm. Yeah. Ed put out fire.
- But you're not Ed anymore.
- (GRUNTS)
And I'm not Grundy.
PENGUIN: Where the hell is Ed?
He'll be here.
No. No, he's betrayed me, too.
I know it. I should...
never should have trusted him!
Calm down.
No, do not tell me to calm down.
You have no idea what I've been through!
Calm down. Ed will be here.
He will bring Grundy, and
we will make Sofia pay.
I can't wait any longer.
How did Nygma get in touch
with Penguin anyway?
- I don't know.
- Nothing's ever easy with you, is it?
It's always like, "Find Lee,
and then she'll point us to Ed,
"and then we'll find Penguin,
and he'll tell us where to find Penn."
Or we could just talk
to Oswald right now.
Huh?
- (GLASS BREAKING)
- Hey, you son of a...
(OSWALD BREATHES HEAVILY)
What are you doing here?!
We're looking for an
Arkham escapee, about yea tall,
walks with a limp, mommy complex?
Those trumped up charges you used
to put me away have lost their teeth.
Martin is still alive.
- So produce him.
- Nope. He is not safe
until Sofia Falcone
has been dealt with...
permanently!
I think you and I want
the same thing, Oswald.
We both want Sofia to go away.
Then turn around and walk away.
Let me do what I do.
No. I want her in jail,
and for that I need evidence.
I want your bookkeeper Mr. Penn.
What would he know about...?!
That little weasel was working for her!
BULLOCK: Yeah, he was working for her,
for Don Falcone, everybody!
You might want to check
your management style, pal.
(GROANS)
I'm gonna kill him. I'm gonna kill him.
Oswald? Oswald?
Calm down. You show us
where we can find Mr. Penn...
...and I'll let you walk away.
- I don't believe you.
- BULLOCK: Sofia sent Zsasz
to Arkham to kill you.
Her goons run the Narrows.
How long do you think it's gonna
take till she finds you?
(PANTING)
(GUTTURAL GASP)
(SNIFFLES)
I overheard Mr. Penn talk
about a place just out of town,
near the Tricorner...
the Spa Bo'sh Sumka.
(LAUGHS) Offers special therapy.
If he's hiding, he's probably there.
Oswald.
Thank you.
BULLOCK: That's really nice.
- Now put your hands behind your back.
- (GRUNTS)
- BULLOCK: Thank you.
- Aah!
- No, we had a deal!
- Harvey, what are you doing?
If you want to look
the other way, Jim, fine.
I didn't agree to squat.
- Come on.
- OSWALD (CRYING): No! No!
- I will not forget this!
- Relax.
If your information on
Penn is good, at least
- you'll be free of Sofia Falcone.
- (GRUNTS)
Well, well, well.
Sofia's gonna be very curious
to know why you're looking for Penn.
Hey, Penguin.
You remember me?
Oh, God, no.
Wait. Is Penn important or something?
That's a yes. You see that?
- That's his "yes" face.
- Get him in the car.
(GRUNTING)
Guess I'll have to go dig him up myself.
Now, you boys want to come quietly?
Or do you want to do it the fun way?
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
The fun way. Nice.
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
- Lee?
- Shut up and get down.
- (ENGINE STARTS)
- (GRUNTS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Lee!
Come on!
Let's get out of here.
We need to get to Penn
before Zsasz does.
We need a car.
(SIREN WAILING)
(FOOTFALLS REVERBERATING)
(SIGHS)
Migraines, still?
It's like I've been hit
in the head with a brick.
What is that stink?
(MUFFLED SHOUTING)
Should've known.
Grundy smell like old dentures.
TABITHA: It's him.
I know.
I can smell him.
(SNIFFS)
Hey there, Barbara.
Scary.
Nygma tried to recruit me against Sofia.
He's working for Penguin.
(LAUGHS)
I figured after all Ed did to you,
you should be the one to kill him.
Wait, Butch.
- Don't just walk away again.
- Tabby,
I'm gonna find a way
to get back to the old me.
I promise.
(MUFFLED SPEAKING)
(SHOUTS)
(GROANS)
NYGMA (DISTORTED): I'll remove
your spleen with a claw hammer!
Any ideas?
(GASPS)
You okay?
I'm fine.
We send Nygma back to Sofia.
She will torture him to get to Penguin.
Lee has no more allies, boom.
Rebellion quelled, we're heroes.
Then what about Nygma?
- He just gets to walk away?
- Yes!
When Sofia doesn't need him anymore,
she'll kill him.
Same end result, none of the headache.
Well, we did find Penguin,
but then he got away.
So why aren't you looking for
him instead of wasting my time?
Because I also found out that
Gordon is looking for Mr. Penn.
(HANGS UP PHONE)
Find Penn before Gordon does.
Yeah, so, Penn, Penguin...
I mean, where are we, priorities-wise?
Do both.
Thank you for coming to my rescue.
Don't bother. Without you,
I can't get to Sofia.
Hmm, touching.
I cannot believe I'm doing this.
Believe it. No Ed, no Grundy,
we're running out of time.
You know this cockamamy scheme
will probably get me killed?
If it puts Sofia in the ground,
I'm okay with that.
(GASPS)
Last time you came to me
with one of your schemes
to regain the city,
you promised every resource I needed
to reverse my condition.
So that didn't happen.
An omission I regret
and will rectify if given the chance.
Uh-huh.
(AIR HISSING)
(SCREAMS)
(HISSING STOPS)
God!
You cannot honestly tell me
you are happy here.
Tinkering away on whatever...
Don't touch that.
You need money for your research.
Sofia wants Penguin.
So you deliver him to her,
you can name your price.
I may have something.
Keep this on you; it's on a timer.
Best I can do on short notice.
If being frozen affects my
brain the way it did Nygma,
- I cannot afford...
- Ready?
- Not yet. I...
- Don't care.
So, now are you going to return it?
Selina, you said...
Can you do it?
That's really why you came to me.
It wasn't about the money.
You did not kill Roland Charles.
I was there, though.
And what, uh, what am I supposed to say?
"I... I stole your jewelry.
Sorry."
Sometimes that's enough.
- (DRILLING)
- (NYGMA SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
His strength of mind is impressive.
(GROANS)
You are going to tell me
where to find Penguin.
Or I will make
all of this look like a pleasant dream.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay.
I can be done with the teeth,
the eyes or the mind.
What am I?
I can be humorous
but I'm never funny! (LAUGHS)
What am I? (LAUGHS)
(SCREAMS)
(SHOUTS)
Tell me where he is.
I am telling you!
(LAUGHING): You're just
too stupid to figure it out.
(LAUGHS, SCREAMS)
Ms. Falcone, you got a visitor.
Kind of in the middle of something.
Guy's got Penguin.
(GROANS)
Bring him in.
(CART ROLLING)
(SOFIA CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHS)
Well, this is unexpected.
Heard you were looking for Penguin.
He never was a great boss.
(QUIETLY): Well, well, Oswald.
Is he alive in there?
VICTOR: Maybe?
I want a hundred thousand.
Pay him.
I'm not even gonna ask.
Oh, by the way,
I found out where Penn is.
(GASPS)
(CHUCKLES)
Take him to the docks.
Shoot him and throw him in the river.
Watch Penguin.
Let's go get Mr. Penn.
(ICE CRACKLING)
MAN: Lovely, Ms. Gonzalez, well done.
Uh, Ms. B, pull a little harder.
That's, that's it, Mr. King, come on.
You can do it.
(LAUGHTER AND INDISTINCT CHATTER)
What fresh level of hell is this?
Who is hungry?
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
GCPD!
GCPD.
We're looking for Arthur Penn.
What are you doing?
Anonymity is a strict edict here
at the resort.
I bet.
WOMAN: What is going on?
- That's him.
- Penn.
Penn!
Oh, no.
Let's take a walk.
As you were.
(LAUGHTER AND GIBBERISH)
(BEEPING)
(ICE CRACKING)
Mr. Cobblepot.
You're working for her, too. (LAUGHS)
- I assure you...
- O-Of course you are!
- Where is she?
- You don't understand.
Where is she?!
(SCREAMS)
(PHONE RINGING)
Is it done?
Sofia left before I could kill her.
She's on her way to stop Gordon.
Meet me at the Spa Bo'sh Sumka,
and we will kill her together.
(GASPS)
Nygma was here.
Miss Falcone tried to get him
to turn on you.
What?
He endured a tremendous amount of pain.
He wouldn't give you up.
Where is he now?
Her thugs took him to the docks.
To kill him.
(GRUNTS)
I'd worked for Don Falcone for years.
Uh, before Mr. Cobblepot.
When Sofia came to Gotham,
Don Falcone asked me
to keep an eye on his daughter.
She found out.
So you made another deal with her?
You weaselly triple agent, you.
It's how you stay alive
in this business.
And she let me live,
as long as
I informed to her about Mr. Cobblepot.
So that's how she was able to
stay one step ahead of Penguin,
with inside information.
Then what?
She asked me to put her in touch
with Lazlo Valentine.
The Pyg.
So I did.
- But I told Don Falcone right away.
- All right.
You're coming with us.
We need your statement for the record.
(WHIRRING)
Get down!
(PEOPLE SCREAM, GORDON GROANS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Get Penn out of here.
He's all that matters.
We got to get you to the hospital.
Gunshot will draw attention.
Cops will be here soon.
I can make it till they arrive.
SOFIA: James Gordon.
We could have had a good thing,
you and I.
You just had to go and ruin it.
Go.
That's an order.
Get Penn.
Get Gordon.
Get out!
(CLAMORING)
(GRUNTS)
(GORDON GRUNTS)
(GUN CLICKING EMPTY)
(GROANING)
Police!
Where's Sofia?
In there with Jim.
Take the car.
He's hurt. Bad.
Get in.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SIRENS WAILING)
Can't catch a break today.
Let's go get a milkshake.
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
Jim, you really are
such a disappointment.
(GRUNTS)
Would it have been so bad being
in the palm of my hands?
Having me chip away at your
soul little by little?
Was it so important
to rob me of my revenge?
(WHEEZES)
(GUNSHOT)
(GRUNTS)
It wasn't about me.
I wasn't gonna give you the GCPD.
Of course it was about you.
Your pride, your arrogance.
Do you think that what I was asking for
was any different than
what my father had for 30 years?
You mean your father who you killed?
Yes.
I killed him.
Because he disappointed me.
Just like you.
You know, Jim,
oddly enough, I still care for you.
Beg me for your life.
Ask for forgiveness...
and we can start over.
Sofia.
Go to hell.
James Gordon...
...this is where our story ends.
(GUNSHOT)
(PANTING)
You.
Yeah.
Me.
(ECHOING): Stay with me, Jim.
Jim.
Can you hear me?
(NYGMA SNICKERING)
Come on, come on.
Hey, I got a riddle for you.
What's got a bullet in its head
and sinks to the bottom of the river?
You. (LAUGHS)
The real torture
is that those idiotic words
will be the last I ever hear.
Just do it!
(GUNSHOTS)
(GUN CLICKS)
Oswald.
How?
Did you already kill Sofia?
No.
She left the mansion
to pursue Jim Gordon.
Why didn't you just stay at the home?
Wait till she came there and killed her?
Then I wouldn't have been here on time.
You gave up your revenge for me?
(SIGHS)
Trust is so very hard to find in Gotham,
but I trust you, Ed.
(EXHALES)
I have a strong desire to never,
ever see this pier again.
(SIGHS)
I agree.
(SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE)
(MONITOR BEEPING)
(WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY OVER P.A.)
(GASPS)
Hey.
Surprised you're alive?
Oh...
Yeah.
How?
How do you think?
Lee.
She kept you alive till
the medics got there.
Even one-handed, she's
a damn good doctor.
Sofia?
In a coma.
Amazing she's not dead.
Harvey.
When I get out of here,
I'm gonna confess.
My connection to Sofia,
my role with the Pyg, all of it.
I got to come clean.
No.
What do you mean?
Who would benefit from that? You.
You get to be the martyr,
feel better about yourself.
The GCPD loses its hero. No.
You want to pay your debt?
You live with it.
Just like I do.
So Sofia wins after all?
It's what the city needs.
Where's Lee?
She went back to the Narrows.
Said she had unfinished business.
(DOOR OPENS)
- (DOOR CLOSES)
- (YELLING, CHEERING)
(PUNCHING)
Get him, get him some more! Come on!
(PANTING)
All right.
I'll go... I'll go.
Oh, I know you'll go.
Just not yet.
Hold his hand.
No! No!
No!
What are you doing? No!
No! No!
(SCREAMING)
(GRUNTING)
♪ Fire ♪
(DISTORTED CHATTER)
With Sofia gone, Penguin's gonna try
and take control of Gotham again.
Maybe even try and kill us.
Can you just give me a second?
Barbara, we have to act.
We can't just stand around
here doing nothing.
I said shut up!
(PANTING)
♪ To a fuller love, child ♪
♪ Yes, it does ♪
♪ The way you squeeze and tease ♪
♪ Knocks me to my knees ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm smokin', baby, baby ♪
♪ The way you swerve and curve ♪
♪ Really wrecks my nerves ♪
♪ And I'm so excited, child ♪
♪ Whoo, whoo ♪
♪ The way you push, push ♪
♪ Lets me know that you're good. ♪
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com