Previously on Gotham:
(grunts)
BULLOCK: The guys call him the Ogre.
He's a serial killer.
Whoever did this is a monster.
The blood of his next
victim is on my hands.
If you don't drop it,
that blood could be Lee's.
Because the Ogre retaliates against any cop
who investigates and
kills the people they love.
BRUCE: The man who stabbed
Alfred, he's in Gotham.
You need my help to find him.
Who sent you?
You want me to tell Bunderslaw
that you're onto him?
(screaming)
(train clacking, bell
clangs, ship's horn toots)
(car horns honk, siren wails in distance)
Hey!
You look far from home.
Get away from him.
Or what?
(scoffs)
Whatever.
SELINA: Come on.
Did you go back?
Yeah. The cops are there.
And?
What do you think?
He fell out of a five-story
window. He's dead.
(voice breaks): Why'd you do it?
He told us what we wanted.
He told us about Bunderslaw.
You didn't have to go and kill the guy!
Yes, I did! 'Cause the moment we'd left,
he was gonna go tell his boss!
Who works for you, by the way.
He's the one who tried to kill me,
who tried to kill your butler...
who probably killed your parents.
I saved your life.
Besides... you wanted to do it, too.
You just didn't have the guts.
- Wait...!
- Just go home.
We still have to find out who
Bunderslaw is and what he wants.
You mean you do.
You really think this is
over? He's gonna come after us.
So what's next? Hmm?
- His safe.
- What?
Every senior executive at Wayne Enterprises
has a safe in their office.
A-Any secrets Bunderslaw
has, that's where they'll be.
Key or combination?
Key. My dad had one.
He'll probably keep it on him, then.
Figure out a way to get me
close, and I'll steal it.
- Can you do that?
- I think so.
And what happened tonight, you tell no one.
Not your buddy Detective Gordon,
not your butler.
No one.
- Sync and corrections by madhatters -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Punctures on test subject
are consistent with those
on the victim, indicating
the killer was right-handed.
Yum.
Where's Thompkins?
Detective Gordon, Dr.
Thompkins said I was free
to use this room. She's very nice.
She's not like the old medical examiner.
Ed, just tell me where she is.
- No riddles.
- Home. She went home.
Hope you find her.
(phone buzzes)
- (glass breaks in distance)
- (gasps)
Jim?
Jim, is that you?
- (meows)
- (gasps)
- (meowing)
- You're lucky I don't skin you.
Go on.
(dials phone)
(phone rings)
- I... slow down.
- Lee, please.
Start over.
This case you caught, the dead woman,
she was murdered by a serial killer?
Yes. Who's killed a
dozen women, maybe more.
And Loeb gave you this on purpose?
He wants to hurt me.
And how am I in danger?
He murders the loved ones of any cop
who investigates him.
It's how he's been able
to get away with it so far.
Anyone who comes after him,
he's killed someone they love
and the investigation's been buried.
Bullock knows a cop...
Came home and found his wife.
Her throat had been cut.
Oh...
That's why Loeb gave me the case.
Either I give up, like everyone else...
and live, knowing I let a killer go free...
or I keep on,
and someone I love is killed.
You're not giving up, are you?
I can't.
That's why I need you to
get out of Gotham right now.
Tonight.
No.
You want to protect me? Find him.
I'm gonna stay here and do my job.
But I do like that you think of me
as a loved one.
I do.
Love you.
And it only took a serial
killer to get you to say that.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Hi.
(door opens, closes)
This is it.
Home sweet, you know.
This is a great space.
Selina?
Hmm.
- Sort of a roommate.
- Hmm.
She comes and goes.
Wayne Enterprises Charity Ball.
Didn't you know I'm a member of society?
I go every year.
Get my picture taken in a pretty dress.
Smile.
Aren't you scared of my being here?
Should I be?
Are you dangerous?
I don't know... is your
boyfriend gonna come home?
I never said I had a boyfriend.
I assumed a woman as beautiful as you...
You assumed I had a boyfriend
and you assumed I would
be the kind of woman
who would cheat on him.
Well, I'm not.
And I don't have a boyfriend.
And if a bus hit me tomorrow,
no one would care.
That change things?
- Yes, actually, it does.
- Make it more illicit?
Or would there be less chance
of us getting attached...
One night and done.
Only that would happen anyway.
Because once you saw the real me,
you would run screaming,
like everyone else.
I have to say, you're not
who I imagined you'd be.
Surprise.
You can let yourself out.
♪ Love, love ♪
♪ Love... ♪
But you promised to dance with me.
- And I will.
- (laughs)
But first I have to
finish with that gentleman.
Who knew running
a nightclub was so much work?
My poor darling.
As I was saying,
you and your crew are the best
gun and knife men in the city.
Your hit on Councilman Klein...
A thing of beauty.
- And I'm a fan, so...
- Cheers.
What do you want?
For you to help me kill Don Maroni
and all of his lieutenants.
You're having a laugh.
I'm fairly certain I'm not.
And Falcone's good with this?
He will be. When it's done.
Thank you. No, thank you.
So you like being number two.
Falcone gives Victor Zsasz
first dibs on every new contract.
You bring him the bullet-riddled
corpse of his enemy
and all of that will change.
This is your chance to move up.
(wry chuckle)
You're a mad fella, aren't ya?
Fair enough.
Come by the bar tomorrow.
We'll talk details.
What's this about, Harvey?
BULLOCK: Have a seat.
This is my partner Jim Gordon.
Detective.
Eight years ago, you
investigated the murder
of a woman named Julie Kemble.
- That was a long time ago.
- It was the Ogre.
Julie Kemble was his first victim.
But you dropped the investigation,
and because of that,
11 more women have been murdered.
(chuckles) Seriously, guys, you know...
Stop.
We also know the Ogre
kills the loved ones of
the cops that hunt him down.
That pattern started with you.
We think you found
something that spooked him.
Your notes from the investigation.
The last page,
something's been scratched out.
I want to know what.
He killed my wife.
I still got a daughter, Harvey.
Beth Tudor.
Katherine Wood.
Jessica Parker.
11 women.
Each one was someone's daughter.
It has to stop.
Yeah. I was doing background
on the dead girl. Someone
told me she was a nurse
for a private medical clinic uptown.
It was on Grant and 80th.
Some cosmetic place.
We'll put cops on your
daughter until this is done.
(camera clicks)
So you forgive me?
Mm-hmm.
- I'll see you tonight.
- Mm-hmm.
How's it hanging, Riddle Man?
Uh, it's hanging...
fine.
(trembling sigh)
Mr. Nygma,
did you need something?
Oh. Yes. Uh...
Detective Gordon wanted me to
go through the forensic evidence
- of these old murders.
- Okay.
- Are those bruises?
- Uh...
Did Officer Dougherty do that?
Um, he was... upset, and he didn't mean to.
I-I said some things
I shouldn't have, and...
Miss Kringle, this is not
right. He can't just...
Mr. Nygma, it is none of your concern.
Now, I-I need to get started
on these files, so...
Alfred.
Should you be up?
Oh, thank you, Master Bruce. I feel...
I feel much better.
Can I get you anything?
Yes, actually. I've decided to attend
the Wayne Enterprises Charity Ball tonight.
All the senior management will be there,
and I think people should see
that a Wayne is still at
the head of the company.
I shall set your tux out for you.
Alfred...
Yes, Master Bruce.
Wh-When you were in the army...
you had to kill people, right?
Yes.
Yes, I did.
And it was necessary?
Oh, I see... so you
overheard the conversation
that Reggie and I had
that was best left unsaid.
But in answer to your question, yes.
Yes, it was necessary.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I better go and find my good cufflinks,
if we're stepping out.
No, but, uh, you're-you're
still recovering.
What, I'm supposed to let
you walk into that nest
of vipers on your tod?
There'll be hundreds
of people there, Alfred.
I won't be in any danger.
So you say. But you're not gonna go alone.
I won't be alone.
I've invited Selina Kyle.
Selina Kyle?
To the Wayne Enterprises Ball?
I see.
What do you see?
Nothing. I mean, you
know... I mean, you're...
a healthy young lad and
she's a very pretty young girl
with a penchant of wearing,
well, a little too much leather.
- Alfred, it's not like that.
- Then what's it like?
Well...
well, what if it is, huh?
What's wrong with that?
Absolutely nothing.
So, I will wait in the car outside,
so you don't feel my watchful eye,
but I will be close by, if there needs be.
That is the deal.
Fine.
Could you call around and send
some dresses and shoes
to where she's staying?
This is the address.
It's a charity ball, Alfred.
I'll be fine.
Freaky, huh?
You wonder how they
recognize themselves after.
Doc Thompkins is fine.
No one's gonna touch her
at the precinct. Relax.
You do understand it's because
of me that she's in danger.
Anything that happens is my fault.
You can't hold yourself responsible
for the actions of a psychopath.
Sure, I can.
Detectives... I'm Dr. Cushman.
How can I help you?
We're looking into the murder
of a woman named Julie Kemble.
She worked here about eight years ago.
Of course. Terrible thing.
Julie was a talented nurse.
But she'd only just started
here when it happened.
She'd been recommended
by one of our patients.
- The patient's name?
- (scoffs): Well, I'm afraid
I can't give you that. Confidentiality.
Really?
You're gonna make us get a warrant?
Yes.
"I specialize in fake
boobs, but I got ethics.
I need a warrant."
We'll talk to Judge Harkness. I'm sure...
That car was in front of the precinct.
Jim, wait up.
(starts engine)
(tires screeching)
(car horn blaring)
- You sure about this?
- It was him.
You saw his face?
No. I should've been looking for a tail.
It's obvious he tracks our investigations.
BULLOCK: Called in a description
of the car and a partial plate,
but I'm not too hopeful.
So what's the next move?
Gordon, you got a call. Says it's urgent.
- Gordon.
- JASON: Detective.
I didn't get a chance to say
hello properly in the alley.
Listen to me...
Don't bother tracing this. I won't be long.
I'm giving you one chance
to turn yourself in.
You make me come after you,
and I will put you down.
Something tells me you've begun
to buy your own press, Detective.
The hero cop who's gonna clean up Gotham.
The rising star of the GCPD.
I'll stop you, that's for damn sure.
No, Detective, you won't.
But keep on your present course,
and I will kill someone you love.
This is your only warning.
(click, dial tone)
BULLOCK: Oh, no.
Tell me that wasn't him.
He's used to intimidating cops.
We have to show him we're not afraid.
And how do we do that?
You're okay with this? You're sure?
Yes. It's the right thing to do.
(cameras clicking)
I called you here today...
because the people of
Gotham deserve to know
that there's a serial
killer in their midst.
For years, he's killed with impunity,
aided by a culture of silence
and fear among the police.
That ends now.
We'll be providing the names
and photos of all of the victims.
Please call with any information.
And to the man who committed
these horrific crimes,
(on TV): your days of hiding are over.
I'm coming after you.
And I'm not gonna stop.
- (sighs)
- What are those for?
The Wayne Charity Ball.
It's boring but good for
the gallery's business.
Well, I'll probably see you there.
- (knocking on door)
- What?
I'm going with Bruce Wayne.
Wait, what?
- MAN: Delivery for Selina Kyle.
- SELINA: Oh.
Uh, over there.
MAN: Thank you. Enjoy.
(man speaks indistinctly)
(door shuts)
(sighs)
Am I really supposed to wear these?
Okay...
we have a lot of work to do.
Got it.
That was the doctor. Harkness
sent over the warrant.
The dead girl came to the clinic
by way of a Miss Constance van Groot.
Van Groot... that's one of
Gotham's oldest families. Shipping.
Yeah. We thought the Ogre might be rich.
- Could be the old lady had a son.
- You got an address?
Right here.
Well, Butch, Connor and
his crew are on board.
They hate Maroni even more than I...
Shut up. Maroni and his crew are here.
I couldn't turn 'em away.
- No, of course. No matter.
- No.
She was already here.
MARONI: Is that my buddy Oswald?
- (gasps)
- Come here.
Oh, Oswald.
(Maroni chuckles)
There he is.
Mother, what are you doing?
I'm having a drink with Mr. Mar...
Uh-uh-uh-uh.
I told you... Sal.
With Sal.
But we shouldn't impose
- any longer...
- Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh-uh.
No, you're not taking my Gertrud.
Oh, his Gertrud.
(Gertrud chuckles)
- Sit. Join us.
- (gasps)
GERTRUD: Oswald, sit.
Sit, Oswald.
(knocking on door)
Hello.
I'm Bruce Wayne.
- Barbara Kean.
- Oh.
Selina never said you're
who she's staying with.
Detective Gordon spoke of you.
Well, Selina can be a little guarded.
(chuckles) Yes, I know.
Stop talking about me.
Selina.
You look very nice.
The shoes hurt.
Have fun.
BARBARA: Look for me at the ball.
It was nice meeting you.
Think she's here?
(echoing): Miss Van Groot!
GCPD!
I need to say this is not exactly legal.
We're running out of time.
(clanking, man gasping)
(gagging)
GORDON: Over here.
(man grunts, gasps)
Oh!
He's good.
Call it in. I'm gonna go
check the rest of the house.
(weakly): He told me...
but I was too slow.
(doors creaking)
Hello?
Miss van Groot?
I'm a police officer.
Ugh...!
(distant): Gordon!
Now!
Jim Gordon,
Constance van Groot.
(classical music playing,
indistinct conversations)
(indistinct chatter, light laughter)
Everyone's staring at us.
Well, I am Bruce Wayne.
Well, I am.
Anyway, I don't see Bunderslaw anywhere.
He's probably not coming.
But he's on the guest list.
Just keep dancing.
And smile, maybe?
Name's Jacob Skolimski.
He's not talking, but near as we can tell
he was the old lady's butler.
And you're thinking the
Ogre's this guy's son,
not the dead woman's?
Yeah, yeah. Coroner said the
old bird's been dead for years.
My guess, Ogre killed her,
daddy pretends she's still alive,
so crazy serial killer son
can keep living off her money.
He tried to kill himself.
He knew you were closing in.
- He has to be in contact with his son.
- BULLOCK: Yeah.
Listen, Gordon's running
pretty hot on this one, Cap.
Can you blame him?
Thinks Thompkins is the next victim.
Still, watch him.
Alvarez called.
Nothing on the son in the system.
We have to make him talk.
Make this simple.
Give us your son's name and address.
JACOB: Or what?
I'm not afraid of you.
Only because you don't know me.
Listen, I get wanting to protect your son,
but how many more women
is he gonna have to kill
before you realize he
needs to be locked up?
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me. You were hiding
a rotting corpse upstairs for years,
but no, no, my son's an angel,
he didn't murder close to
- a dozen women that we know of.
- My son...
He made one mistake.
One.
Anything else is lies.
So tell us the truth.
Hear, hear. Cheers.
Selina, what happened last night...
That can never happen again.
I told you I didn't have a choice.
I don't accept that.
(scoffs)
I knew you wouldn't be able to handle it.
You're right. I did want to kill him.
Keep your voice down.
But there's a line, Selina.
And you can say I don't
have guts, but the fact is
I will never cross it.
I guess that's where we're different, then.
'Cause if I had to do it again, I would.
And it wouldn't bother me one bit.
That's Bunderslaw.
- (chuckles)
- (clears throat)
Riddle Man.
Officer Dougherty, a word.
I can start a war or end one.
I can give you the strength of heroes
or leave you powerless.
I might be snared with a glance,
but no force can compel me to stay.
What am I?
Got me.
Love.
Miss Kringle has given hers to you.
And in return, you hurt her.
- I saw the bruises.
- And?
And you cannot do that.
The next time you do that, I'll...
Whoa! Calm down.
You'll give yourself a girly fit.
Have you ever been with a woman?
(clicks tongue) Didn't think so.
They need a firm hand.
That goes double for Kringle.
Girl's got a tongue.
I won't let you hurt her.
(laughs) Oh, yeah?
What are you gonna do?
(clicks tongue)
That's what I thought.
Later, Riddle Man.
Care to dance?
- You.
- Me.
It was not a place for a boy to grow up.
Miss van Groot kept herself sealed off
from the world, but she doted
on my son.
Treated him as her own. Still, I...
I didn't realize how deep it went.
This kid's own mom was out
of the picture, so it seems
he started thinking he was this
van Groot woman's secret son.
SKOLIMSKI: I tried to tell him
it wasn't true, but he had
built this fantasy, and...
Miss van Groot led him on.
She was deranged. Cruel, even.
BULLOCK: So, about ten years ago,
he confronts her, he demands
that she acknowledge him,
give him her last name,
put him in the will.
She laughs at him,
said it was all just a big joke.
So he kills her.
His dad feels guilty,
helps him cover it up.
So the old woman rejects him,
he kills her... bang,
you got a serial killer
with a "Mommy didn't love me" complex.
But there's a wrinkle.
I don't know where my son is.
He called me today, told me
the police would be coming.
But I haven't seen him
since the day he killed Miss van Groot.
My son is not a bad man.
Your son has been
seducing and killing women
for almost a decade.
(wheezing laughter)
Why is he laughing?
My son... seducing women?
Oh, let me show you my son... two pictures.
It's all I managed to save.
You've heard "a face
only a mother could love"?
Well... his mother couldn't.
She left us after he was born.
(chuckling): Oh, yes... my son,
the seducer.
Now you can see why it makes sense
he scratched his face
out of those pictures.
But that means this can't be the Ogre.
- We're chasing the wrong guy.
- Jim had an idea.
Judge Harkness's warrant was very specific.
I don't have to say anything.
Then nod.
Did you operate on this man?
I need to know what he looks like now.
Or the next woman he
kills will be on your head.
Never, never,
would he play with the other children.
You know, even then,
he was too good for them.
And now, he is a respectable
man of business...
My Oswald.
Well...
this has been a delight.
But it's late.
One thing...
- Gertrud, my love.
- Aw...
A question that's been bothering me.
Oh, no. Oh... no, no.
Is this an act?
(both laughing)
Are you pretending
that he's just a nightclub owner?
Or are you really that stupid?
- Stop!
- I don't understand. I...
- Your son...
- Don Maroni, I am warning you!
Is a cold-blooded psychopath.
No, no, no, no, no...
I can't count how many men he's killed.
My own friend, Frankie Carbone,
he stabbed him a dozen times.
What kind of person plunges a knife
into someone over and over?
He is a filthy liar, Mother!
He's just angry because
I played him for a fool!
(gasping): Oh! Oswald...
You know, don't you? Oh, I can see it.
(whimpering) Let go of her!
Did you catch him, one night,
washing the blood from his hands?
When did you realize that you had
given birth to a monster?
(shouts, sobs)
You are going to pay for this!
Maybe.
Or maybe this ends with me
dumping your lifeless body into the river.
Either way, you and Momma
Gertrud can stop pretending.
Place is looking good.
(door opens)
- Shh, shh...
- (sobbing)
(door closes)
The other night, when
you saw my invitation,
why didn't you tell me you were coming?
I wasn't.
I didn't get invited.
Oh, so you're crashing.
Oh, no, I'm... on the list.
It's amazing what a
$10,000 donation will do.
You donated $10,000 to this?
Why?
I was hoping that would be apparent.
And what if I decided not to come?
Well, then, I'd have been making
a generous donation to charity,
and I would've been very... disappointed.
The way things ended last night,
it was my fault.
But I felt something.
I couldn't let it slip away.
Well, that's very sweet, but...
You said that when people see the real you,
they run screaming.
Someone said the same thing to me once,
that no one would ever love me.
Who?
The woman I thought was my mother.
Barbara...
I know what it's like...
to be one person on the inside,
and have the world see another.
I lived like that.
And it almost destroyed me.
I can see it destroying you.
I don't want to dance anymore.
The person that I am now, I created.
I brought him into being.
I can do the same for you.
Aren't you tired of playing games?
Of hiding?
Yes.
- (laughing) Good-bye.
- See you soon.
Hello. I'm Bruce Wayne.
Sid Bunderslaw.
(quiet click)
BRUCE: I'm going around,
trying to get to know everybody
who works for the company.
You do work for Wayne
Enterprises, don't you?
I do.
I'm the Director of Physical Operations.
Which, I'm afraid, is a bit dull.
There are many much more
interesting people here.
Ah, yes, well, I'm sure I'll
get to meet everyone, eventually.
If you'll forgive me, Bruce,
I have an early flight tomorrow.
It's been a pleasure.
It was, um...
it was nice meeting you.
SELINA: Sorry.
(Bruce sighs)
See? Nothin' to it.
What is it?
Nothing.
(siren wails in distance)
Stop right there, buster!
(car door opens)
Riddle Man?
What the hell are you
doing, creeping around here?
You need to leave Miss Kringle alone.
What?!
I'm not gonna let you hurt her.
Ever again.
I think you need to leave Gotham...
tonight.
(chuckling)
I get it now.
You got a thing for my girl.
That's too funny.
Don't take this personal.
(yells in pain)
Aw... (scoffing laugh)
You want some more?
Upsi-daisy... oh!
Oh, dear.
(gasps)
(grunting)
(train clacking)
Riddle Man...
Oh, dear.
Oh, no.
(gasping, laughing)
Oh, dear.
(laughing)
(gasps)
Oh, dear.
Oh, dear...
- Oswald.
- Feeling better?
I made tea. (laughs)
I'm afraid you had...
well... (laughs)
a little too much to drink.
Mr. Maroni, he...
he has a strange sense of humor...
Oswald...
I am not some bumpkin from the country,
with hay in my brains!
No...
I am your mother...
and I will love you, no matter what.
But lie to me now...
you will break my heart.
Oswald...
have you done things...
you should not?
I...
Mother...
I'm a nightclub owner.
That's all.
(shuddering breaths)
(sighs)
I'm tired now.
I'm tired.
(crying quietly)
(sobs)
(knocking on door)
(Oswald sniffles, knocking continues)
Yeah, I got a delivery
for Gertrud, from Sal.
Tip's not included.
You tell Sal it's over.
The guns are bought.
The killing room is waiting.
He doesn't know it, but he's a dead man.
On second thought...
I'll tell him myself.
(delivery man groans)
(gasping)
GERTRUD: O-Oswald?
Who was that?
It's Mr. Yatsko, from next door.
He needs help taking out some trash.
You, you... please, you help him, then.
(broken glass clinking)
Jason van Groot?
His real name is Jason Skolimski.
He used the old woman's name
when he went to the clinic.
But there's no Jason van
Groot or Skolimski in Gotham.
- The guy's a ghost.
- So, the old woman
rejects him, he goes to the doctor,
gets himself a pretty new face.
That's where he runs into the nurse.
And we're off to the races.
I don't suppose you got a picture.
Missing from the file. No surprise there.
But the good doctor was kind enough
to do a sketch.
It's been ten years since he last saw him,
but at least it's a start.
So we have his real name,
but not what alias he's using,
or what he looks like
beyond a decade-old sketch.
Did he say anything
else on the phone today?
Anything we might've missed?
GORDON: Nah, just warned me to back off.
Told me not to believe my own press
as the rising star of the GCPD.
What is it?
The paper that said that...
They ran an old photo of
me, from a charity gala.
I wasn't alone.
(pounding on door)
GORDON (muffled): Barbara!
- Is Barbara here?
- No. Why?
Where is she?
- When's the last time you saw her?
- At the Wayne Ball.
She left with some guy.
- Was this the guy?
- It's kind of a crappy drawing.
(firmly): Was this the guy?
Yeah, I think so.
Why? Who is he?
What's through there?
See for yourself.
- Sync and corrections by madhatters -
- www.addic7ed.com -