ED: Previously on Gotham...
Who were those people
you were speaking with?
You keep your nose out of my business.
Come now, Butch. Play nice.
If a person comes into contact
with my blood, it changes them.
My brother, if he gets in your mind,
you're doomed.
Good-bye, Mr. Gordon.
- Ivy's missing.
- She'll turn up somewhere.
This time she fell.
It was a long way down into water.
BRUCE: Then maybe she survived.
- MAN: What's your name?
- My name is Ivy.
Barnes asked me
to put you on a 48-hour suicide watch.
I've already signed off on it.
BUTCH: He just cost you the election.
Give me one reason why I shouldn't
let Butch kill you where you stand.
There's that.
REPORTER: Oswald Cobblepot has won
the mayor's office by...
I believe in you, Oswald.
You never believed
I could win this election on my own.
Maybe you're not cut out for this
after all.
What?
Jervis. Let her go now.
No! I'll never go with you!
No!
(SCREAMING)
JERVIS: You killed her!
I would like to introduce you
to my chief of staff,
Mr. Edward Nygma!
(CROWD CHEERING)
MAN: (OVER PA)
Welcome your new mayor of Gotham,
Mayor Oswald Cobblepot.
Building Gotham safe again.
Welcome your new mayor of Gotham,
Mayor Oswald Cobblepot.
Building Gotham safe again.
(INAUDIBLE)
(CHEERING CONTINUES)
MAN: You're an angel.
Oh, thank you so much.
Thank you.
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
(CROWD WHOOPING)
(CROWD CHEERING)
Thank you.
COBBLEPOT: There's something
I've been wanting to ask you.
Am I a good boy?
Have I made you proud?
I hope I'm not interrupting.
Ah! Ed, you never met my mother.
Wasn't she beautiful?
A fine figure of a woman.
She was my whole world.
The only one that was always there for me.
Well, I believe the answer is yes.
She would be proud.
- Do you really think so?
- Oswald,
look at everything you've achieved.
The people love you.
Gangs fear you.
And tomorrow night, the creme of Gotham
will be gathering to celebrate,
You.
What more could someone ask for?
Someone to share it with.
My mother was the daughter of immigrants.
A humble cook.
We did not have much,
but when she was by my side,
I felt loved. Protected.
As promised, I have rid Gotham
of its villainous monsters.
With my mother as my witness,
I vow to you from this day forward,
every man, woman, and child
in our great city will be safe!
(CROWD CHEERING)
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (ALL SCREAMING)
RED HOOD: Spread out!
No one is safe. Not from us. Drop it.
Put it down!
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(GASPING)
You will pay for this! Dearly!
RED HOOD: Now, now, Mr. Mayor.
Don't go losing your head.
(EXPLODES)
Have a nice day!
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
I can't come over tonight.
Okay.
I mean, that'd be three nights in a row.
That'd almost make it a thing.
Yeah. The neighbors might talk.
Exactly. And I have a dinner.
It's not a date.
None of my business.
Uh-huh.
So, whatever happened with Tetch?
I told you.
He broke his sister out of the GCPD.
Bullock and I chased him down.
She died. He escaped.
'Cause I heard a rumor
there's something strange about her blood.
Do you like this?
I think I've made that pretty clear.
- Then why are you pressing?
- Because I want to know.
And are you asking as a reporter,
or as yourself?
- Is there a difference?
- There should be.
When you were a cop, did you stop
being one when you came home?
Maybe that was my problem.
Hmm.
The guy I'm having dinner with
is a hematologist
in charge of analyzing
Alice Tetch's blood.
I'm free after 10:00, if you wanna call.
- Thanks for the coffee.
- (DOOR OPENS)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
We found the truck.
(GRUNTS)
BULLOCK: They ditched it in The Narrows.
We've got forensics going over it,
and teams doing a 10-block sweep.
We already found this.
The Red Hood Gang?
I thought those idiots were dead.
My guess is they're copying the look.
The original Red Hood Gang
were bank robbers.
Whoever they are,
they got a beef with Penguin.
Expand the search to 15 blocks.
Everything goes through you.
ED: You mean through me.
Wow!
(LAUGHS)
It is good to be back.
I have missed all of you.
(CHUCKLES)
Harvey, still a stranger to a haircut
and a shave, I see.
What are you doing here, Nygma?
As Mayor Cobblepot's chief of staff,
I'm gonna be your liaison
on the Red Hood investigation.
I wanna see all reports.
And I'm going to need access
to your forensic lab.
You think I'm gonna just let you
waltz into my precinct?
You're a cop killer
who should be in the loony bin.
- I'll be damned...
- You'll be fired.
The Mayor can't fire me.
No, but he can appoint
a police commissioner who will.
So, you will carry out the Mayor's orders,
without question,
or the GCPD has a new captain.
How does that sound?
Every dog has his day, Nygma.
Enjoy yours.
And where is our lord mayor?
Hiding under his desk?
He's meeting with constituents.
(COBBLEPOT SNIFFLES)
"Anything for you, my little Cobblepot.
"You can count on me."
(SNIFFLES)
Those were the words
my mother used to whisper to me
every night before I fell asleep.
She was a saint.
Yes, a saint whose only desire
was to love me.
And what was her thanks?
Not only did she take a knife in the back,
but even in her death,
her memory is being desecrated.
Seriously? This is the reason we're here?
A little glue. Some paint.
Momma will be good as new, huh?
- (LAUGHS)
- (GROANS)
No! That is not the reason you are here.
The Red Hoods
have challenged my authority.
They will be made an example of.
Tonight, I am celebrating
my historic victory...
At The Sirens. It's gonna be fabulous.
None of you are invited.
I want them found, and their leader's head
brought to me on a spike before nightfall.
What're you waiting for? Find them!
RED HOOD: All right.
Five card draw, gentlemen.
Someone didn't ante up.
Come on, you cheap bastards.
(SIGHS)
How long are we supposed to wait?
Long as it takes the boss man to get here.
You need a lookout.
(GUNS LOADING)
Ah, relax, fellas.
Hey, uh, you want us to deal you in, boss?
We don't have time for games, boys.
We got work to do.
- (KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- (DOOR OPENS)
Hello, Jim. Is it a bad time?
I should've called.
No.
Please, come in.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(SIGHS)
Right. Can I get you something to drink?
A glass of water?
I'm fine.
I heard you were back.
I've been meaning to come see you.
Everything okay?
Yes. Alfred and I are both well.
I hear you're a private investigator now.
I'd like to hire you.
(SIGHS)
Bruce, if this is about corruption
at Wayne Enterprises...
It's not. I've put my investigation
into my father's company aside.
It's time I moved on.
Why the sudden change of heart?
It's far from sudden.
I've given it a great deal of thought.
I can't live my life
if I keep looking back.
For what it's worth, I think that's wise.
So, what can I do for you?
Ivy Pepper's gone missing.
I didn't realize you two were close.
We're not. She's a friend of Selina's.
And does Selina know you're doing this?
No. I don't want to get her hopes up
if you don't find anything.
Well, we'll start with the GCPD.
See where we go from there.
And I think it's chivalrous,
you doing this for Selina.
How long have you two been a thing?
Uh, no, no, no.
Selina's a friend. That's all.
- Mmm-hmm. Yeah.
- No. Really. She's just a friend.
Yeah. Yeah.
(ED WHISTLES)
Mr. Fox, just the man
I've been wanting to see.
Oh, joy. Mr. Nygma.
Heard you were stopping by.
I have questions.
Hopefully, you have answers.
Or what? You'll poison me with gas?
(LAUGHS)
That gas was a sleeping agent.
And, to be fair,
I was not in the best place in my life.
(BLOWS)
To be fair, if you ever threaten my life,
or the life of Bruce Wayne again,
I will find a way to end you.
Mr. Fox, we both know
you're not a man of violence.
No, I'm not.
If I was, I would have laced
some piece of lab equipment,
one which you were sure to touch,
with a toxin.
Ricin, maybe.
I'd use saxitoxin. Harder to trace.
But I like your style.
You are insane.
Was insane. I have a certificate.
So, the Red Hoods?
See for yourself.
Mmm?
(WHIRRING)
The gang's getaway vehicle
was abandoned in The Narrows.
As you'll notice, its carpet fibers
has elements of dirt, oil,
and, oddly, potassium chloride.
A halide salt.
Fascinating.
So, nothing on Ivy Pepper.
But an odd report came in a few weeks ago.
Okay, a construction worker claimed
that a redhead knocked him out,
robbed him.
And she left this.
That's Ivy's sweater.
How do we find this man?
I already called.
All right, the guy's down south on a job.
But he swore up and down that the redhead
who rolled him was in her 20s.
So'? He's probably covering
for being with a young girl.
Doubtful he would come forward
in the first place.
Yeah. Most pervs don't wanna
call attention to themselves.
So, it wasn't Ivy.
It seems unlikely.
But why would she have Ivy's sweater?
- (FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
- Dr. Thompkins.
Bruce. It's good to see you again.
You got taller.
Like I said, right?
The kid's growing like a weed.
Nice to see you, too.
Uh, Jim, could I have a word?
I wanted you to hear it from me.
Um, my engagement announcement
is coming out in the Gazette tomorrow.
And it will feature Mario's name.
I think that's customary.
His family name.
You mean Falcone.
You knew?
You knew and you didn't say anything?
Sure I did. I said congratulations.
Don't be cute.
Lee. People talk.
Was I surprised? Sure.
But it's also none of my business.
Your life is your life.
And I meant what I said.
I'm very happy for you.
So, that's it?
That's it.
Okay. Um, well, I just wanted to tell you.
(SIGHS)
Dr. Thompkins.
I had heard that you were back.
I'm so glad...
(GLASSES CLATTERING)
- That's for Kristen.
- You shouldn't have done that.
Or what? I'm supposed to be scared of you
because you work for Penguin?
My fiance’s father is Carmine Falcone.
I so much as whisper to him,
and you disappear.
Tell the Mayor, whatever I can do as ME,
I'm happy to help.
It's bad enough
we're throwing Penguin's party.
- It's good for the club.
- Now we're his errand girls?
Sweetie, we find the Red Hoods,
he'll owe us.
We can ask for a favor.
Say, him not killing you?
Well, it would be nice
not to have to watch my ass all the time.
- (MAN WHIMPERING)
- (GASPS)
Well, well. Who do we have here?
Guy calls himself The Ballistic Bomber.
My contact at The Merc saw him
buying smoke grenades last week.
Just like the ones
the Red Hoods used on Penguin.
Groovy. Reckon he'll talk?
Of course.
(WHIMPERS)
Maybe give him a moment.
Now, remember, kids, you tell the press
this is all Penguin's fault.
SISTER: Leave us, please!
- Good.
- Leave us in peace, please!
Okay, sir.
- Light it up.
- Have mercy.
PRIEST: Please. Don't. No!
Better run, Sister.
Before the Padre goes boom!
SISTER: No! Jesus! No!
Don't.
PRIEST: Wait, wait.
The grenade, it's slipping.
- (EXPLODES)
- (SCREAMS)
BUTCH: Seriously? The priest?
(CHUCKLES)
You should've seen it.
Ka-boom!
But you told 'em what to say?
"This is all because of Penguin"?
Yeah, boss. But I don't get it.
You wanna take out Penguin,
let's take him out.
This Red Hood stuff is fun,
but it's a lot of work.
How about you just do what I tell you.
Now, I got you these,
so you'll blend in at the party tonight.
- Huh? Huh?
- Nice suit!
And that's when we kill him?
No!
No one kills Penguin!
TABITHA: You should.
'Cause he's gonna murder you!
(GRUNTING)
(GASPS)
Time to have a heart to heart, Butch.
Alone.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
You don't have to buy lunch.
I know you're a billionaire.
But I can buy you a sandwich.
Do you miss it? Being a cop?
Sometimes. Yeah.
It gave a sense of mission.
True. There's more to life
than having a mission.
Look, I'll keep asking around
about Ivy. But, uh...
You want my advice, talk to Selina.
Tell her how you feel.
Does that actually work?
Sometimes.
It's definitely better than being silent.
Before you know it, the moment passes.
And are you taking your own advice?
I'm afraid that ship has sailed.
I'm not talking about Dr. Thompkins.
I'm talking about the woman
- you're seeing now.
- Excuse me?
There was lipstick on a coffee mug
on your table.
You've become quite the detective.
- (SIGHS)
- So, are you?
It's complicated.
So is Selina.
That I believe.
I just wish sometimes I had a sign.
Unfortunately,
life doesn't usually work that way.
REPORTER: We're hours away from
Mayor Cobblepot's victory celebration.
But people are asking,
will the Red Hood Gang
put a damper on the festivities?
Sounds like Penguin's having a bad day.
I'm supposed to go to his party tonight.
Part of my re-engagement
with being a Wayne.
Hmm.
Well, give the Mayor my best.
(CHUCKLES)
Someone is testing me, Ed.
They're thinking, "He's mayor now.
He has to play by different rules."
No, they'll see, when I'm roasting
their entrails over a fire.
Perhaps I'm thinking about this all wrong.
Perhaps, this is not about you at all.
What if this is about the statue?
Of course it's about me!
- Yes, you're probably right. Oh, dear.
- (GRUNTS)
- Wonderful.
- Oswald, take a breath.
(GRUNTING)
What are you doing?
It's an old trick I learned in the lab.
Most solvents have as their base...
I am the son of water,
but if water touches me, I die. What am I?
Again with the riddles?
Salt. Most people think of it
as a food additive.
But potassium salt
is found in detergents, soaps...
What is your point, Ed?
I know where the Red Hoods are.
BARBARA: I say we give him to Penguin.
Knowing Penguin will gut him like a fish?
Ladies. Come on.
After all we've been through...
It's his life for yours. Simple.
I don't get it. Why'd you turn on him now?
I wasn't gonna hurt Penguin, honest.
I was gonna take down
the Red Hoods myself.
Tonight, at the party.
All this so you could play the hero?
Ever since Nygma got out of Arkham,
Penguin treats me like I'm nothing.
That pencil neck's trying to push me out.
Let me ask you. We figured out
you're the man behind the Red Hoods.
How long do you think it'll take Penguin
and his lapdog?
It's your life, baby. You make the call.
Let me see this through.
I get my place beside Penguin back,
I'll protect you.
Oh, you'll do more than that.
You'll owe me.
And one day, I'm gonna collect.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Gilzean.
- Butch, where are you?
The Red Hood Gang
is at a detergent factory in The Narrows.
We're on our way.
I gotta go.
Get your things. We're done.
I'm breaking up the band.
I'm serious. Go. Get out of Dodge.
Yeah, well, not for nothing, Butch,
you promised us a payday.
We're not leaving till we get it.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(CAR DOORS SLAMMING)
Well, guess it was gonna happen
sooner or later.
What?
Sorry, boys.
(ALL GRUNTING)
I did it, boss. I got 'em for you.
(GASPING)
(CHUCKLES)
Peace and order have once again
been restored to Gotham.
The Red Hood Gang is no more.
My very own man, Butch Gilzean,
risked life and limb
to face down the bandits.
(REPORTERS CLAMORING)
Was your life ever in danger, Butch?
I can honestly say
that if I'd had hesitated,
I'd have been a goner.
(COBBLEPOT CHUCKLES)
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
All right, people, listen up.
It's happy hour.
Finish up those reports,
and let's call it a day.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
Hey, uh, Ed.
Even before you went crazy,
I never liked you.
Your zipper's down.
(SIGHS)
Listen, Butch did us all a favor.
Red Hoods go bye-bye. Case closed.
Look at the way the bodies fell.
It's as if they were just standing there,
waiting to be killed.
Butch comes all the way in the room.
But only one man pulled out a gun.
I guess they weren't threatened.
By a 300-pound gorilla?
Whose side are you on anyway? Hmm?
No one's losing sleep
over a bunch of dead crooks.
Least of all me.
I said wrap it up!
What have we here...
Burning the midnight oil?
I was just finishing up.
I'm guessing you're here to reprimand me.
Reprimand you? For what?
Punching Nygma in the jaw.
I just couldn't help myself.
First I'm hearing of it.
Well done, Doctor.
(CHUCKLES)
Actually, I'm here to ask about,
uh, Alice Tetch's blood.
If you've heard anything.
As it happens, I just received
the preliminary results back from the lab.
- Fascinating.
- What is?
They injected samples
into a group of rats.
After three days, two of the rats
were showing marked increases
in strength and stamina.
Well, that doesn't sound so bad.
But the study ended after one of the rats
killed all the others.
I'm guessing that's not normal.
It chewed through a dozen wire cages
to get at them.
No.
Why would one of the rats go psycho
and not the others?
Perhaps the others hadn't had a chance
to show any symptoms.
Or they were immune.
Sometimes people live with a disease
for years without any adverse effects.
The lab is starting a new study now.
Well, keep me informed.
Oh, and, uh, don't stay too late.
I'm sure that fiancé of yours
would like to see you once in a while.
And was the captain of the GCPD invited
to our new mayor's victory party'?
You know, I lost my invitation.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
I can feel it...
(MUSIC PLAYING)
My beautiful Oswald.
Heard you took down
the Red Hood Gang single-handed.
- So to speak.
- Very funny.
Don't forget. You owe me.
(SIGHS) I know.
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
How long do we have to stay?
As long as it takes for you
to be seen in the world, Master Bruce.
Being Bruce Wayne. And smiling.
So this is our life now?
Fake smiles and mingling.
I miss the old days.
So do I.
- It's so nice.
- Oh, excuse me.
Bruce, Mr. Pennyworth,
I'm so pleased you made it.
Yeah, well, you know, we're trying
to get out a bit more, Mr. Mayor.
Oh. Oswald, please.
We never got the chance to thank you
for saving our lives from the ex-Mayor.
- (CHUCKLES) That was nothing.
- ALFRED: Not at all.
I found it very fortuitous you turned up
when you did with that bazooka.
I just felt a bit sorry for Stan,
the gardener,
'cause he was picking up bits of Galavan
for weeks.
(CHUCKLES)
And now here you are, the new mayor.
Sometimes life has a way of working out.
Yes, that's true.
What is it, Master Bruce?
A sign.
Please excuse me.
ALFRED: All right, well,
I'll just go and wet my beak.
Congratulations again, Mr. Mayor.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
- Hey!
- Hey yourself.
Funny, I never realized how short you are.
Who the hell are you?
Not yet.
This is too fun. Run along, little kitty.
Go steal some more wallets.
Hey.
So sweet.
There he is, the man of the hour.
I have a surprise for you, Butch.
Not in the mood.
What's in the box?
Open it.
(EXHALES)
Thanks, already got one.
Oh, of course you do.
And you certainly wouldn't need this one,
as it's so similar
to your very own pocket square.
This is from the Red Hood crime scene.
It turns out that your suit
and the Red Hood suits
were all made
by the same tailor, Mr. Fuji.
That's some coincidence.
I thought so myself,
which is why I called Mr. Fuji.
And he said that a large man
with a metal hand,
not many of those running around,
bought all six of the suits.
Which means, ta-da,
you're the architect of the Red Hood...
- (GRUNTS)
- I should snap your neck right now.
(CHOKING)
You haven't heard my offer.
(EXHALES)
We kill Penguin together.
(CHUCKLES)
What are you talking about?
You're his guy.
Oh, please.
You fell for that act?
Yes, he broke me out of Arkham.
Very appreciative.
But I was not cut out to be number two.
I've simply been waiting for my moment.
Which you have graciously provided.
How would you like to run Gotham with me?
(LAUGHS)
The two of us? Working together?
You have proven yourself far more cunning
than I imagined.
Now, I assume this little drama of yours
was meant to climax tonight.
So, put on the hood, kill Penguin.
I'll help you escape.
Tomorrow, we divide up the city.
You'd really turn on him?
After all he did for you?
- Mr. P.
- In a heartbeat.
No.
Okay.
Then I guess it's time
for surprise number two.
You got to Zsasz?
I got to Zsasz.
And he got to Tabitha.
Penguin 's history.
Question is, are you?
Can I see your invitation?
- (SIGHS) What are you doing here?
- I was invited.
Of course you were.
You recognize her?
Should I?
I don't know.
Hey. Are you, you?
I'm me.
Uh-huh. (CHUCKLES)
Well, I'm working, so...
Actually, there was something
I wanted to tell you.
Could we go somewhere more private?
Fine. But make it quick.
Can't believe you'd turn on Oswald, too.
Uh, hello. Pot-kettle-black.
No. It's not the same thing. You...
Never mind.
I swear, your goons hurt Tabitha,
so help me...
Just do your job.
- (APPLAUSE)
- Huh.
Showtime.
Put one in the Mayor
before I put one in Tabitha.
Ladies, gentlemen.
Welcome to The Sirens.
Tonight we're here to celebrate
the honorable Mayor Cobblepot.
Our savior from the monsters,
and the captain of our fair city.
And now, the Mayor would like to say
a few words.
Ed, where've you been?
I've been looking for you all evening.
Oh, just tying up loose ends.
I just wanted to say
good luck.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay. Thank you.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Tonight is a celebration,
not of my victory,
but of Gotham's.
This is a new day!
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (GASPS)
I wouldn't celebrate yet, Mr. Mayor.
Red Hoods ain't finished yet.
- (GASPS) Ed! What are you doing?
- Wait!
Sorry, boss.
Butch!
- (GRUNTS)
- (CROWD EXCLAIMING)
(GASPS)
- Huh?
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (CROWD EXCLAIMING)
(GROANING)
The Mayor, our mayor,
vowed that all of the Red Hoods
would be destroyed.
And now we have the real leader caught.
Red-handed.
(GROANING)
You really thought
I'd give you real bullets?
You are an idiot.
(CROWD EXCLAIMING)
I will kill you for this!
Sounds like we're missing all the fun.
Got plenty of fun left for you.
You know, if you're gonna
take a girl hostage in her own place,
you might wanna search it first.
(GRUNTS)
After all that I've done for you!
I gave you a job!
I gave you everything!
I used to be somebody in this town,
and then you and that sniveling little...
- (GRUNTS)
- (LAUGHS)
Shut up!
(GASPING)
I am shocked, and grieved,
that one of my dearest friends
has betrayed me.
But let it be known that Oswald Cobblepot
will prosecute anyone
who threatens Gotham.
Hear, hear.
- Yeah!
- (CROWD CHEERING)
- Upsy-daisy.
- (GROANING)
- (GASPs)
- Oh, my God!
(LAUGHS)
Showtime.
(GUN CLATTERS)
(GLASS SHATTERING)
Oswald, move!
(GRUNTING)
I am gonna enjoy this!
(GASPING)
Best party ever.
(BOTTLE SHATTERS)
- Wait, not now.
- COBBLEPOT: Ed!
(GRUNTS)
Ed! Ed!
Ed!
(COUGHING)
So, what's up?
I hired Jim Gordon to help me locate Ivy.
And?
There was a redhead that had her sweater.
But it wasn't Ivy.
Saying it out loud, I realize
it doesn't sound that impressive.
No. It doesn't.
That's really why you brought me up here?
(SCOFFS)
You are the real Bruce,
'cause nobody else would be this boring.
Great work, Detective.
That's not all.
We've been friends a long time, Selina.
And ever since you've known me,
I have been dedicated to one thing.
But that's done.
I don't know what's next. But I know...
Would you please just say what you mean?
I like you.
As more than a friend.
It would be nice
if you said something back.
How many girls have you dated?
- What do you mean?
- (CHUCKLES)
It's not a trick question.
How many girls have you dated?
- None.
- None. Hmm.
Have you ever thought
that maybe you only like me
because I'm, literally,
the only girl you know?
That's not true. I feel something.
And I know you do, too. We're the same.
In what universe are we the same?
- The money doesn't matter!
- Try not having it.
It matters.
There's something between us.
I know there is.
You have to see that.
Rule one,
don't ever tell me what I have to do.
So, you do have feelings for me?
I'm confused.
Good.
Come on, just tell me.
I got all dressed up,
I even put on lipstick.
I could lose my job.
What are you offering?
Fine. Then I'll say something.
If I'm right, you just nod.
You ran tests on Alice Tetch's blood?
You found something in her blood.
A virus or infection or something.
Do I have to go over the rules again?
Let's have new rules, sweetie.
I'll tell you what we're doing
with Alice Tetch's blood,
and in return you...
Okay.
Excuse me, what are you doing?
(SIGHS)
Two whiskeys
and a pineapple juice for this guy.
- MAN: What's going on?
- To go.
What's going on?
I think you were just leaving.
Forget this.
Trust me, I'm gonna try.
(SIGHS)
What are you doing here?
Just walking by.
Saw you through the window,
took it as a sign.
Like hell.
You tracked me here.
And for the record, I could've gotten
what I wanted from that creep
without compromising my honor.
I know.
But you don't have to.
I'll tell you what you wanna know.
I thought you wanted to keep the woman
and the reporter separate.
- Is that an option?
- No.
Well, then.
You are gonna
have to buy me dinner though.
What's good here?
(COUGHING)
It's ginger tea with honey.
It's my mother's remedy for a sore throat.
You sure you don't need a doctor?
No. I'm fine.
(COUGHS)
I still don't understand why
you didn't tell me what you were doing.
Your shock, when seeing Butch,
had to be genuine.
The people had to believe it.
And they did.
And once again, you're the city's hero.
(CHUCKLES)
You were almost killed.
And you saved me. Again.
(COUGHS)
I hope you know, Oswald,
I would do anything for you.
You can always count on me.
Thank you.
Need a hand, kitten?
I got it.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(GUN LOADING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
Hold on, Butch.
Sir, the ambulance carrying Butch Gilzean
was just hijacked.
Damn it! Put out a BOLO.
I'll call the Mayor.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Yes.
WOMAN: (STAMMERS) Mister, please.
(JERVIS SHUSHING)
My dear, sweet sister.
Just look at what he did to you.
He took you from me!
We belonged together.
And he killed you.
But, mister, I'm not dead.
If only that were true.
(GASPING)
Those who hurt you
will feel my pain,
when my sweet and terrible vengeance
upon them rains.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English - SDH