Previously on Gotham...
Taking a life will
lead you down a darker path
than you can ever imagine.
I know. I've been down it.
I'm not the hero Gotham needs.
And it's gonna be a
long, bumpy journey back.
You've met Martin, I see.
You and I, we're
more than friends.
We're conspirators.
Got him!
Oh, oh, no.
You are relieved
of duty, Harvey Bullock.
As of this moment, I'm assuming
the captaincy of Gotham Central.
What did you have to do
to get it?
Gotham finds
itself in the hands
of a ritualistic cop killer,
being called Professor Pyg.
It doesn't stop until
I've butchered every single
swine on Penguin's payroll.
I'm gonna find you.
I hope you do.
It's a spectacle.
And you're my muse,
Jimmy Gordon.
My poor lost lambs.
I come to you today
with an offer for this evening.
Fresh biscuits
and a hearty bowl of soup.
Wait. Mm.
I have place settings for six.
Nobody wants some
fresh pumpkin pie?
Smile.
My children,
there are two Gothams:
The Haves and the Have Nots.
I know what it is
to feel like a Have Not.
But...
I say, enough.
Here's to giving the Haves...
...a taste of
what it is like to be...
a Have Not.
Let's begin.
Shall we?
I'll be out of your way
in just a second, Captain.
Harvey, this isn't how
I wanted things to go down.
And yet, here we are.
You know what I was
thinking about today?
Our first case.
When I told you to walk Penguin
to the end of the pier,
put a bullet in his head,
and dump him in the water,
and you wouldn't.
You thought it was wrong.
It was.
Well, maybe if
you would've done it,
Falcone would still be
running things,
and a lot of people who are dead
would be alive today.
If I could go back,
I'd do the same thing.
Because you still
don't understand
how this city works, Jim.
You want to be a hero.
And Gotham doesn't need heroes.
It needs people who will
do what is necessary.
You're wrong.
If you show 'em the way,
the people will follow.
Guess we'll just have to wait
and see, huh?
When your leave is up,
there'll be a desk here
waiting for you.
Sit around and
watch you all day?
No, thanks.
Right there is perfect.
Thank you.
Beautiful.
I predict this evening's
fundraiser will be
a smashing success.
If I want Gotham's
wealthiest families
to support the orphanage,
things have to be perfect.
I appreciate you
taking part, Oswald.
Yes.
Sadly, a situation has arisen.
No.
That thing in the Narrows,
with your former chief of staff?
No, no.
This is far more serious.
It has to do with Mayor Burke
promoting James Gordon
to captain of the GCPD.
You're not really worried
about James Gordon?
Please.
The issue is the person
who ordered his appointment.
I see. Do you?
Oswald, we both know
the mayor is a weasel.
Someone must have paid him off.
But I don't see why that means
you can't attend my dinner.
Because, my dear,
the mayor has vanished.
But I will find him,
I will learn the name
of my enemy,
and there will be a reckoning.
And that is why I might not
be able to make it this evening.
Very well.
But a few of the children
are doing a song.
Martin is taking part.
It would mean the world
to him if you could come.
Of course.
Now, don't let me keep you.
If you think she's the one,
we could have Victor...
talk to her?
You do realize she is...
literally my only friend.
I need the mayor. I need proof.
But, sir, what if Ms. Falcone...
Not to say it is her...
Has seen to it that the mayor
is missing, well, permanently?
I could be chasing a ghost while
she prepares her next move.
I wish I had a spy,
close to her, someone quiet.
Bring me Martin.
Who?
The boy with the pad
around his neck.
The one who can't talk.
I thought I was clear.
We're done.
Penguin suspects something.
What are you talking about?
He was just here,
saying that he couldn't come
to the party I'm having tonight
for the orphanage.
He knows someone paid the mayor
to make you captain.
I think he suspects me.
Have you warned the mayor?
I'm not a fool, Jim.
I had him leave town
after your appointment.
Sounds like you have
your bases covered, as usual.
Thanks for the heads-up
about Penguin.
Don't call me again.
This is Harper.
Gordon, line one.
Says it's private.
Sofia.
Wrong. Try again.
You son of a bitch.
Yeah, attaboy, Jim.
Or should I say Captain?
Congratulations, by the way.
So, do you remember
when you said
the rot in Gotham
went from high to low?
You've hit the nail on the head.
Police were low.
Now it's time for Gotham's elite
to feel the pain.
Enter Phase Two.
I won't spoil the reveal.
Hurry outside for a little taste
of what's to come.
Ciao, mon ami.
He's outside. Let's go.
GCPD.
GCPD! Make way.
GCPD. Excuse me. Back up.
Are they dead?
Get forensics here.
And I want this whole area
closed off. No press.
That pig's eating that guy.
Now, Harper.
Excuse me.
Where's breakfast?
Breakfast was produced
and consumed by yours truly
at breakfast time.
It is now fast approaching
luncheon, Master Bruce.
Whatever, just give me a coffee.
Enjoying the benefits
of another night out
on the tiles with Tommy Elliot
and his band of miscreants,
are we?
How absolutely delightful.
I know what you're going
through, you know, Master Bruce.
Yeah.
I went out with my friends.
I'm hungover.
Doesn't take a genius
to figure it out.
You're lost is what you are.
I've seen that
countless times... young men,
going off to war
with a clear purpose,
only to return home to a normal
life, unable to assimilate.
Confused, angry.
And they make
a complete tosh of it.
I don't really care.
You killed Ra's al Ghul.
Vengeance for
your parents' death
has been your driving force
for so long.
You are completely lost
without it.
I need to call Tommy.
Have you forgotten
what day it is today?
Give me my phone.
You have, ain't you?
Today is the day
my father took me camping
and we put a rock on
top of Mount Bristol.
We did it every year.
Now give me my phone.
You are Bruce Wayne,
son of Thomas Wayne.
And the sooner you start
remembering that, the better.
So, you drink your coffee.
You go upstairs, you put
your kit on, 'cause you and I...
...are going for a walk.
According to
the medical examiner,
both victims had been
living outdoors for some time.
Most likely homeless.
Now, see these incisions?
He removed their organs.
Any idea why? Not yet.
Pyg all but announced
that his next victims
would be the rich and powerful,
the high in Gotham.
So why is he killing
the homeless?
You're asking for logic
from a psychopath.
From him, yeah.
Everything he's done has been
thought through carefully.
There was a card
on the table in French,
said, "Long Live
the Revolution."
Maybe he's using them
to make a statement.
He wants the city's attention.
For what?
He said this was just
a taste of what's to come.
There's a piece
that's still missing.
The homeless are densest
in the Narrows.
I'm gonna start there.
Hell of a first day
to be captain.
Yeah.
Call me, you find anything else.
We checked all buildings
in a three-block radius,
Captain. Nothing.
All right, widen it out
a couple of blocks.
Focus on buildings with
protected loading docks.
Captain, that was Lucius Fox.
Final tox came back.
Both victims had sodium sulfide
and chlorine residue
on their skin.
He says it's common in
paper manufacturing.
There's an old paper plant
few blocks from here
that closed down a while back.
Let's check that out.
Backup's still incoming.
Should we wait?
No.
Over here.
What is he doing to them?
Taking their organs.
A smoker oven?
He's cooking them.
Harper?
Drop the gun,
Captain.
Shoot this bastard.
Drop it!
Thank you.
You found me too soon, James.
The table's not yet set,
and no meal should be served
before its time.
You want a hostage, take me.
No, no, no, no, no.
That won't do at all.
You must see my final act.
Along with all of Gotham.
Right, well,
it's a lovely day for it.
Best foot forward.
Very distinguished.
Sofia tells me
you're taking part
in a performance this evening.
Oh. She's quite a lady,
isn't she?
She's been a friend
to both of us.
Or has she?
Martin,
I worry Sofia is only
pretending to be my friend.
And worse,
I fear she may be using you.
Now... I've been
running this over in my mind,
and there are two ways
this might have gone.
One, Sofia chose a
specific orphan... you...
To place in my path.
She groomed you.
She told you how to act.
Or...
Sofia simply collected
a group of children,
hoping one would gain my trust
and make me easier
to manipulate.
In this version,
you are innocent.
Martin...
this is the version
I very badly want to believe.
But I need proof.
Of our friendship.
I need to know
if my suspicions are correct.
And if so,
what Sofia is planning
and who she is planning it with.
I need you to be my
eyes and my ears.
Do you think you can do that?
Don't let me down, Martin.
Please.
I want a city-wide BOLO
on that van.
I want every cop in Gotham on
the streets, looking for Harper.
She will not be
the Pyg's next victim.
Go.
Captain Gordon! Captain Gordon!
Is it true that the serial
killer known as the Pyg is back?
That he's responsible
for the scene
outside the GCPD this morning?
We believe so, yes.
We've also heard he's kidnapped
a GCPD detective.
How can you keep the
people of Gotham safe
when you can't protect
your own officers?
We remain hopeful for
Detective Harper's safe return.
Let me be clear.
The GCPD will stop this monster;
That's a promise.
And if you fail, will you be
pushed aside like
Harvey Bullock was?
We're done here. Thank you.
What about the rumor that the
Pyg is now cooking his victims?
Who told you that?
Is it true?
As I said, the GCPD will
bring the Pyg to justice.
That's all.
Captain Gordon!
Someone leaked to the press that
the Pyg is cooking his victims.
Maybe it was the Pyg.
We know he wants attention.
Look, Jim, everyone in
the department is on your side.
Yeah.
There's something
you need to see.
"I grant this food
will be somewhat dear,
"and therefore very proper
for landlords, who,
"as they have already
devoured most of the parents,
seem to have the best title
to the children."
It's Jonathan Swift,
"A Modest Proposal."
He made an argument
for cannibalism,
about the rich eating the poor.
The poor are the homeless.
Who are the rich?
Swift didn't just talk about
the rich eating the poor.
He specifically
mentioned the orphans.
I know where he's going.
He left this for me.
He's doing exactly what he did
with Harvey. It could be a trap.
And I won't lead more officers
to their deaths.
You're going alone?
I'm sorry, Lucius.
Where's Chef Louis?
Ici, mademoiselle.
Such a pleasure
to meet you in person.
Hmm. I was
expecting you earlier.
Apologies.
I was detained.
But I've made a small change
in the menu.
I have steered us
away from haute cuisine
to something
a bit more... mundane.
Et voilà.
I am calling them
Gotham Meat Pies.
Your guests will die for them.
I've made us a delicious
brown English stew
with herb dumplings,
Master Bruce.
Your father used to love it
when I made stew.
Did I ever tell you
how I met your old man?
In London. He was doing
postgrad work there.
He told me.
Yeah, but no details.
Well, I was just out
the army, two months.
Don't remember any of it.
All a bit of a blur, really...
Booze, drugs, brawling.
A sucking great black cloud.
One day, I wake up and
I'm lying in this alley,
and I'm covered in
blood... don't know how.
So I picked myself up,
I took myself straight down
to the police station,
turned myself in,
hoping that they would
chuck me into the big house
and throw away the key.
And they told me to shut up,
sit down and wait.
And there was this
really annoying Yank
wandering about,
dressed like he was
ready for a game of tennis,
and it was your dad.
Anyway, he bowls up to me,
asks me what I done.
Asking me questions.
Eventually, you know,
I found myself
telling him stuff that I was too
frightened even to think about.
But I guess it'd
just been building.
Anyway, that point, the desk
sergeant called him over,
and your dad turned
around to me and he said,
"Alfred, last night, I was
being attacked in that alley,
"and you started
fighting this geezer.
I headed on my toes,
and I ran away."
And I said, "Yeah, but
that's not what happened,
is it, Thomas?"
And he says, "It is now."
Your father saved my life.
His friendship saved me.
You see, I know what it's
all like, being lonely.
Hoping that the world
will punish you.
I can help you.
Bruce...
Alfred, I hear you.
I just don't want to talk
about this right now.
All right.
Well, this looks lovely.
The rocks are gone.
They must've
fell out in the car.
Oh, the keys are in
the bag, just there.
Beautiful.
So nice to see you, dear.
Thanks. Yes.
Oswald, you came!
Look at you two.
So handsome.
I know how important
tonight's party is to you.
And I wouldn't have
forgiven myself
if I missed Martin's
performance.
Why don't you go find
the other children.
Did you locate the mayor?
Unfortunately, no.
Hmm.
But I have not given up hope.
Well, I, for one, am happy.
This way, you get to
come to my dinner.
I need to go check on the chef.
He seems a bit odd.
Please try and enjoy yourself.
Let's go. Straight ahead,
down to the left.
Hello, Martin.
What are you writing?
Don't make a noise.
Shh.
I'm a cop.
Who are you?
A-A waiter.
I'm looking for a man,
Caucasian, about five-foot-ten.
He would've brought the food.
Maybe the chef.
Uh, the chef's in the kitchen.
Look, I just got hired tonight.
Whatever the dude's into, I
have no idea. I'm just here...
You're okay, you're okay.
Do me a favor, find
Ms. Falcone, bring her to me.
Can you do that for me?
Yeah. All right.
What's that in your jacket?
Jim Gordon really is
an impressive policeman.
Is he alone?
Seems so.
But, man, whatever
it is you're into,
my partner and I?
Our rates just doubled.
Harper.
My friends,
the Falcone orphanage
is the realization
of a long cherished dream,
and one that would not have been
possible without your support.
- So thank you. Cheers.
- Cheers.
Now, if you could please take
your seats in the next room,
a few of the children
have prepared a song.
Where's Martin?
I wanted to wish him luck.
Ah. Off getting ready, no doubt.
Oswald, I've been thinking.
Maybe things happen
for a reason.
Licensing crime was a bold move,
but it would've destroyed you.
Whoever had Jim Gordon
appointed captain
may actually have saved you.
By attempting to destroy
everything I ever created?
Oswald... Enough.
If you're going to confess,
confess.
And face the consequences.
So sorry to interrupt.
The servers are
getting everyone seated.
We don't want the food
to get cold.
Shall we go in to dinner?
Chop, chop.
All right.
I stopped the bleeding, I think.
That's the best I can do
until I can get you out of here.
Got to get that door open.
Gordon. Maybe I can
get the hinges off.
Gordon.
Idiots forgot to search me.
Was this another
one of your plans?
No.
Ladies and gentlemen,
as you by now have surmised,
there's been a change
in the program.
Tonight, we are proud to present
the six merry Gothamites
of Squatter's Row,
and Martin,
from the Falcone
Home and School for Orphans,
in our rendition of...
the "Meat Pie Tango."
Enough! Where are
the other children?
If you hurt them, I swear...
Rude.
I'm not finished.
Sit down.
Pull it out,
and the next one's in her eye.
Oswald, no.
Now, to answer your
question, my dear,
the other children
and your staff
are safely locked
in the kitchen.
Despite appearances,
I'm not an animal.
Martin.
May we continue?
You have all fed upon
the poor of Gotham for years.
Now you're going to know
what they taste like.
Please, open your envelopes and
look at the photographs inside.
Oh, come on.
Open them!
Who is Trish?
Well, I thought you should
see who you're eating.
Bob, Fricks,
Trish, Nunuh, Cyrano and Vincent
all deserve our gratitude.
So these pies are...
People. Yep.
They're people pies.
People.
And you're all
going to eat them.
Oh, no.
Absolutely not.
Okay.
Let's try this again.
No!
Eat, or I kill the boy.
But he's just an orphan.
What did you say?
Well, these are made of people.
For God's sake,
you can't expect us...
I mean,
so they kill some urchin, hmm?
What a waste of a good pie.
But I do applaud the sentiment.
Especially as you,
Mr. Cobblepot,
are the reason I'm here.
Me? Why?
Oh, I could've chosen any
gathering of wealthy Gothamites
who've gotten fat upon the poor.
But you,
with your Pax Penguina,
you are the biggest
glutton of them all.
You have gorged yourself
on this city's heart,
its lungs, its liver.
Why should today
be any different?
Now eat, little Penguin.
Eat.
Eat the pies, or the boy dies.
If you don't eat,
I will hunt you down
and kill you all!
Now, that's what I like to see.
And as Mother
always used to say,
"Nobody leaves until
every plate is clean."
It's a compliment to the chef,
and I love compliments.
And, Ms. Falcone...
...mangia, signorina.
Only if you don't hurt him.
Can you help me?
Yes.
No!
He'll kill the kid!
Get off of me!
Martin!
Jim!
Get out of here!
Go!
Come on, Jim.
Don't give up.
You'll ruin everything.
Should be good.
How is your hand?
I'll be fine.
How's Martin?
He is stronger than he looks.
You paid off the mayor
to make Jim Gordon captain.
Yes.
And you want me to believe
that you did this
out of friendship.
To save me.
I tried to talk you
out of the license program.
You wouldn't listen.
There seemed no other way.
Of course,
it's equally plausible
that you are my enemy,
intent upon my destruction.
You could choose
to see it that way.
Choice is yours, Oswald.
Well, whatever
your actual reasoning...
...you went behind my back.
I would be justified
in killing you.
But what you were
going to do for Martin...
...that was real.
Don't ever betray me again.
Never.
I will abandon the licenses,
but Jim Gordon
cannot be captain.
Pick someone else, then.
Gordon's less than nothing
to me.
♪♪ Bye-bye, Piggy, bye-bye... ♪♪
Captain Gordon!
Captain Gordon! Captain Gordon!
Captain Gordon?
Is that the Pyg?
Did you really catch him?
The suspect known as
the Pyg is in custody.
Detective Vanessa Harper is
on her way to Gotham General,
and is expected to make
a full recovery.
The GCPD kept its promise.
Captain Gordon?
Yes?
Thank you.
Oh.
Hey, hey, Alfred!
How was your walk?
Everybody out now.
Nobody move.
This is not your house.
If I want my friends to stay,
they're staying.
Like hell they are.
Dude, your butler is
a little out of line.
Have you been hitting
the sherry, Jeeves?
You have no idea
what extreme danger
you are now in, son.
If I was you, I would walk away.
Yeah, whatever.
Meet us at the club.
Come on.
Driver will take us.
Well...
...you've certainly shown
a new side of yourself today,
haven't you, Master Bruce?
Save it, Alfred.
You tell me a story
about you and my dad,
and I'm supposed to get
all weepy?
You don't know
what I'm going through.
You and I are nothing alike.
Then talk to me.
Let me know
h-how I can help you.
You can't.
Like you said, I did what I did.
I killed Ra's.
I avenged my parents' death,
and guess what.
Nothing changed.
It made no difference.
So then what did I do it for?
How can you help that?
I can help with the way
that you're feeling.
But you need to talk to me.
You have to face up
to who you really are.
Stop telling me who I am.
I know who I am.
And if you really
want to help me,
you can stop trying
to be my father,
and you can be my butler.
Clean this place up.
Tommy!
You're the hero of the day.
I was just doing my job.
I know you hate me
for what I did,
but you deserve to be captain.
I went to your father for help.
I knew what I was getting into.
Doesn't mean I have to like it.
But you accept it.
Because I do deserve it.
Just like Gotham deserves
law and order.
And I'm gonna make sure
it gets it.
You don't think
I want that, too?
I'm not your enemy, Jim.
I never will be.
Did you find anything out?
"I saw Sofia
kissing the policeman."
Is this true?
Martin, you are a good friend.
As for Sofia...
she will answer
for what she's done.
I swear it.