[indistinct chatter]
Come on, people. Time's a wastin'.
[Lee] The filtration system
that Lucius designed is working.
What you're doing is both unnecessary
and it's reckless.
Our supplies of drinking water
are at critical levels.
Every day the gangs grow
more aggressive.
If I can get a ceasefire,
even a temporary one,
then when reunification does happen,
at least there will be
people left to save.
They deserve that much.
And does your child deserve a father?
You have no problem
taking care of the entire city.
What about focusing on just one life?
Why are you always so ready
to put yourself in the crosshairs?
It's like you won't be satisfied
until you sacrifice yourself.
-You really believe that?
-I do.
And it scares me.
How is this gonna work?
Am I supposed to just stay at home
and raise this child with Barbara
while you go cowboying off all the time?
It won't always be like this.
-After reunification--
-Nothing will be different.
-Unless you stop being--
-Me?
[Harvey] Hey, Jim.
-I have to go. We'll talk after.
-If there is an after.
[yelling]
[Barbara] Oswald, where the hell is Nygma?
Shouldn't we have left the city already?
Miss Kean, this may come as a surprise,
but building a submarine from scratch
by yourself takes time.
-Patience.
-Easy for you to say.
You're not a walking egg timer.
Tell 'em to get a move on.
And why exactly are you hosting
Gordon's gangland get-together?
Keep your friends close
and your enemies closer, my dear.
If we're really going to leave Gotham,
we need to keep Gordon happy.
You know all about that, don't you?
It was a momentary slip.
The world was on fire.
[banging on door]
Jim, it's your show.
[speaking Spanish]
I'll make this short.
Gotham is running dry.
Our supply of clean water
will only last a few more months.
So you have a choice.
You can keep killing each other,
fighting over what little water is left,
maybe eke out a few more months, then die.
Or we can all agree right now
to an immediate ceasefire.
[clamoring]
Government will not annex a war zone.
If we can show them that
we deserve to rejoin the mainland,
the supply chain will be restored and
we will all survive until reunification.
That's the choice.
Life or death.
Your call.
[man] No way!
[all clamoring]
-[woman 1] Yeah?
-[woman 2] Yeah.
-[woman 1] All right.
-[woman 2] All right, do it.
[gunshot]
Weapons down!
Get back!
Jim, you see where the shooter was?
Jim!
Oh, my God!
[gasping]
[Harvey] Get back!
You're gonna be all right.
It's bad. We gotta move him, now.
Clinic's too far.
ME's office. Alvarez, come on, help.
[Alvarez] On it.
[groans]
[Harper] All right, get back.
[crowd clamoring]
[Harvey] Get back!
Well, did not see that coming.
[Selina] What made you choose this,
of all places, for a scavenging mission?
Just trust me, okay?
[Selina] What the hell?
[ballroom music playing]
[Bruce] Sit.
[scoffs]
[chuckles softly]
Wow. Candles.
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say this was a date.
Maybe it is.
That okay with you?
Maybe.
Good.
So, let's eat.
[Harvey] Lee, it's Jim.
He's lost a lot of blood.
Can you save him?
Come with me.
Doc says he's gonna be okay.
He's gonna pull through.
But until then, I'm acting captain.
Now, the gangs in this city
think this is their time,
that they can run wild.
They are dead wrong.
I want us to take to the streets.
It is show of force time.
We ain't gonna give them an inch.
Harper, I want you
to organize patrol teams.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna find out who shot my partner.
[Lee] The bullet shattered against a rib.
We have to get all the fragments out.
I haven't done general surgery
since med school.
There.
There's an exit wound,
so the rest must have gone through.
I need to sew him up. Can you get my kit?
[woman] Right away.
[Lee] Come on, Jim.
You can do this. You have to fight.
You hear me?
You have to fight.
[gavel pounding]
[judge] Order in the court.
James Gordon.
You have been brought here
to be judged for your many crimes,
and your very life hangs in the balance.
Do you understand?
No, I--
The defendant understands
and waives his right to appeal.
The trial of James Gordon will now begin.
No! Wait!
That was the best canned meal
I have ever had.
And if this was a date,
I don't know how you're gonna top it
when everything gets back to normal.
I don't think things
are ever gonna be normal.
For me, anyways.
What do you mean?
Wayne Manor is gone.
And I know that a lot of people
lost a lot more,
but part of me wonders if it wasn't fate.
[sighs] It wasn't. It was Jeremiah
blowing up your house.
Maybe it's time to move on.
You mean, like, leave Gotham?
Bruce, forget Wayne Manor.
This city is your home.
And how many terrible things have
happened to it because of me?
Galavan,
Ra's al Ghul...
If this city really is my home,
then maybe the best thing I can
do for it is leave.
I have to say,
I kind of agree with you on that one...
Billionaire Boy.
[Penguin] Jim Gordon's blood on my floor.
Ugh. Olga! Why is the help never around
when you need them? [chuckles]
This could be good for us. You especially.
Are you serious?
Your baby daddy is the top cop in Gotham.
A dead Jim Gordon is the only way you can
hold on to your little bundle of joy.
Harvey, how is our dear--
[groans]
Who the hell did it?
If I find out it was you, I swear to God--
It wasn't me! I merely supplied the venue.
At your boss's request!
That doesn't mean squat.
Fine! You wanna know who's to blame?
James Gordon!
He invited every criminal in Gotham.
What did he think was gonna happen?
[groans and coughs]
How about you, huh?
When did you two become so buddy-buddy?
Maybe when you hatched up a plan
so you could keep that baby for yourself.
Harvey, whatever you think of me,
I did not plot to kill my child's father.
Well, someone here did!
Someone in this room shot Jim Gordon,
and I'm not leaving
till I find out who it was.
Wrong! The shooter was not here.
Look at the window, stupid.
The shot came from outside.
If the shooter was there,
the trajectory was here,
Jim was...
Then the bullet...
Uh-huh.
I'm gonna find out who this was.
And when I do,
there's gonna be hell to pay.
Harvey...
Is there anything I can do?
Yeah. You can keep the gangs
from tearing the city apart.
[door closes]
-What do you want?
-You, I will deal with later.
I'm here for you.
I need you to come with me.
Why would I do that?
Because you love me so much.
Not yet, but you will.
-Don't mess with him, Ivy.
-[Ivy] Protecting your boyfriend?
That's cute.
But I thought that might happen, so...
I brought a friend.
I stumbled across this charming man
on the way over here.
And apparently, you two know each other.
[Bruce] Leave her out of this!
I know I heard you talking
about the future of Gotham.
But Gotham will be what I decide.
A green world.
Won't that be beautiful?
[softly] Gorgeous.
[Ivy chuckles softly]
Bruce and I have to go.
You always did think
you were better than me.
But without my plants,
you never would have left your bed.
I made you strong again.
Think about that
while my friend is cutting out your heart.
There are so many things I wish
I could say to you.
[monitor beeping]
So many things I wish we could do.
This can't be the end.
Come on, Jim.
Talk to me.
Say something.
Speak...
[gavel pounding]
No.
This isn't right. I shouldn't be here.
You have to listen to me.
-[chains clanging]
-[judge] Silence!
The prosecution will now
give its opening remarks.
Your Honor, Jim Gordon's crimes are
a matter of public record.
He's failed Gotham at every turn.
He failed to clean up the city.
Failed to stop the bridges
from being destroyed.
Failed to protect those
poor, innocent souls
in the refuge he himself created.
Haven.
I tried.
-I did the best--
-[judge pounds gavel] Silence!
One more outburst
and you will be held in contempt.
I'm hurt.
I need help, please!
Continue.
The issue here
is not how many people have died
because of Jim Gordon,
but how many more must die in order
to satisfy his need to be a hero.
Therefore, we pose one simple question.
Are the people in Jim Gordon's life
better off with him alive,
or dead?
I think I'm dying.
[Gordon 2] Prosecution would like to call
its first witness, Your Honor.
Dr. Lee Thompkins.
[irregular beeping]
Come on, Jim. Hold on.
[door opens]
[Harvey] How is he?
Touch and go.
He's stable for now.
I removed all the bullet fragments,
but something keeps pulling him down.
Where are the fragments?
What is it?
[Harvey] "VZ."
Victor Zsasz.
Okey dokey.
Time to boogie.
Hey, I'm only here for Gordon.
All of you, stay down.
I see anyone, and, you know...
Bang.
-[shouting]
-[groans]
Now, I heard you were
looking for Jim Gordon.
[Zsasz] Uh-huh.
[Selina] Listen, I know we have history.
Let's just let bygones be bygones.
Yeah, right.
You did this to my face.
Whatever.
It's not like you were
much of a looker before anyway.
[grunts]
Ivy says you hurt her feelings.
Why would you do that?
She's so sweet.
[roars]
Ivy didn't make me strong.
I made me strong.
[grunts]
Tell me where she took Bruce.
[Harvey] The only reason
I'm not ending you right now
is the thought of the look on your face
when Jim Gordon walks through that door,
because he's alive, you son of a bitch.
[exclaims in disgust]
What did you eat?
You smell like a butcher.
You know, I'm vegan now.
Why kill Jim now?
Makes no sense.
He saved your miserable ass.
He prevented Penguin from executing you.
If anyone, you should be
going after Cobblepot.
Yeah, that's a good point.
Maybe I'll do him next.
It's kind of not up to me.
You're working for someone.
Sorry.
[grunts]
-I want a name!
-[exhales deeply]
What's in a name?
A rose by any other name
would smell as sweet.
You know, I'm really taking the time
to stop and smell the roses these days.
Like, actual roses.
They're great.
-Are you high?
-On love.
But like I said,
my lips are sealed.
[snaps fingers] Ivy Pepper.
You said it, not me.
Uh, I'm technically not allowed
to say it, her name.
Which is such a bummer, because it's
the most beautiful name in the world.
-You watch him.
-I could say it all day.
Maybe I will say it all day.
Ivy. Ivy Pepper.
Mrs. Ivy Pepper Zsasz.
Oh, that sounds good.
[Alfred] Here you are, Ms. Thompkins.
Careful. It's a little bit hot.
Forgive me, but I heard on the grapevine
that you and Captain Gordon had a rather
heated exchange this morning.
[Lee] Oh, God.
Was it that bad?
Apparently, it was like a session
at the Italian Parliament.
[sighs]
You have misgivings about the arrival
of this child, don't you?
What am I getting myself into, Alfred?
How am I supposed to raise a child
alongside a psychopath like Barbara Kean?
I mean, how the hell is this gonna work?
But that's not all of it.
If Jim and I are gonna do this,
then we have to do it together.
You know how he is.
I don't know what's going on inside
that man's head sometimes.
I think you'll find that he needs you
a lot more than he's letting on.
Well, I need to hear it from him.
I never thought that this was how
my life was gonna be.
I had no interest
in being a father myself.
I always presumed that I was
unfit to be one.
And then I found myself,
one night, staring down an alley
at this little boy
quite literally shaking with fear.
I don't know,
it's funny what life throws at you.
I'm keenly aware that I am not
Master Bruce's flesh and blood,
but it's the moments,
the little things like...
Like when he uses a skill
that I once taught him.
Or we laugh at a joke
that only he and I share.
Those have been some of the most
ecstatic moments of my life.
Nothing can possibly
prepare you for that joy.
The hows and the whats,
you'll figure that stuff out.
What matters is this.
You'll be an exquisite mother.
And that child, he or she,
will be extraordinary,
because of you.
[sniffles]
Thank you, Alfred.
[inhales sharply]
Jim, can you hear me?
I'm right here, right next to you.
Can you feel me?
-Lee...
-Dr. Lee Thompkins.
You suffered at this man's hands
more than anyone.
Broken heart,
broken engagement,
a lost child.
And yet, you're still with him.
I love him.
[Gordon 2] For all the pain
he's caused you,
would your life be better,
could it not still be better,
without Jim Gordon?
Answer the question.
-Lee?
-[Gordon 2] I'll ask it a different way.
Would you, Dr. Lee Thompkins,
be better off if Jim Gordon were dead?
I'm sorry.
Everything he touches dies.
Prosecution rests, Your Honor.
You made her say that.
[Gordon 2] I didn't make her say anything.
Ask them.
[Gordon] Who are they?
[Gordon 2] More people who trusted you.
Who believed you when you said
you would protect them.
They're from Haven.
I think I'm dying.
And isn't it about time?
The verdict's in.
You're guilty.
Hey, Jeff, listen to me.
One day you're gonna meet someone
who's gonna totally change your life.
And it's gonna make you happy.
And you deserve it.
Or not.
Is she here? She's here, isn't she?
Sweetie...
All I asked of you
was to kill Jim Gordon.
You're not angry, are you?
'Cause I'll do it. I'll do it right now.
I'll do it.
You keep the cops busy.
Luckily, the other part of my plan
is coming together nicely.
[Bruce] Lucius!
[Lucius] Bruce!
I had no idea you were stopping by.
I wanted to check on your progress.
[Lucius] Well, the toxicity levels
in this river continue to drop.
At this point, we'll be under
the threshold mandated by the government
sooner than expected.
It's not glamorous work,
but we are helping to save the lives
of thousands of people.
People. Ugh.
I'm sorry, did you just say,
"People. Ugh"?
Lucius, what if I were
to tell you I have in my possession
the most intoxicating perfume
you'll ever smell?
I would tell you that's
an abrupt change of topic.
Can we go back to the part where
you said, "People. Ugh"?
[clears throat]
Mmm.
[distorted] Oh, my goodness!
Lucius, Ivy sent me here
to get you to shut down the plant.
Can you do that for her?
[distorted] For Ivy?
Anything.
She is so great.
[rock music playing]
Raise your glasses.
I called you all here today
because Jim Gordon is at death's door.
[cheering]
For years, he has hounded us, beaten us,
shot us, and today he got his due.
To Jim Gordon. May he rot in hell!
[cheering continues]
What exactly are you doing?
I'm trying to keep the city
from ripping itself apart.
So, this has nothing to do
with your feelings for Jim?
What if Ed fails and we are stuck here?
This will put us in Gordon's good graces.
Consider it a backup plan.
[Barbara] Listen up.
Now to the real reason
I brought you all here.
I want you to agree to an immediate truce.
[all snickering]
And what if instead, we shoot you
and take your club?
I don't think so.
See, those drinks I just gave you?
They're poisoned.
And you had two shots before
everyone got here.
So that should be taking effect around...
[choking]
Now.
The rest of you have 48 hours
before you'll need the antidote,
which I will deliver to you,
provided you go back to your territories,
play nice, and send me all your guns.
Deal?
I said, deal?
[mumbling in agreement]
Now get out of here!
[Penguin] Hmm.
Jim will be so pleased.
Keep your friends close
and your enemies closer.
Isn't that right, Pengy?
Once I reverse the system,
all the toxin we pulled from the river
will be re-released,
and the overload
should destroy the filters.
In a matter of minutes,
the entire facility will be inoperable.
[alarm buzzing]
Perfect.
Ivy's gonna be so happy.
You think so?
[automated voice]
Security breach. Zone one.
That's odd.
[Bruce] Selina.
I'll take care of her.
Okay.
All right, listen up.
I know you're probably familiar
with Ivy Pepper.
In fact, you were probably here when she
hypnotized the whole freaking precinct.
Okay? She is on the loose,
and we've got to find her
and take her down.
Actually, fellas, she's already here.
That's right. Ivy came to free me.
That is true love for you.
She really understands what makes me tick.
Don't worry, though.
-[officer screams]
-I'm just a distraction
so she can finish off Jim
once and for all.
You know, that's how great couples work.
Maybe I shouldn't have told you that.
Oh, well.
I'm sorry, Ms. Thompkins.
I know. Go. Thank you, Alfred.
Come on, Jim, can you hear me?
Stay with me.
[voice fades] Stay with me, Jim.
[Harvey] Jim.
[laughing]
You want a drink?
Alvarez makes a hell of a Mai Tai.
I can barely feel my face.
Harvey, what is this?
It's your wake.
Pretty nice turnout, huh?
[all] ♪ For he's a jolly good fellow ♪
♪ For he's a jolly good fellow ♪
[giggling]
♪ Which nobody can deny ♪
Wake?
I'm not dead yet.
Well, it'd be a little bit of a bummer to
have it after you die, don't you think?
I'm gonna have a kid, Harvey.
How do I protect that child
when everything around me dies?
Harvey?
[boy] That's a good question.
-Will.
-You said I'd be safe in Haven.
I trusted you.
I know. I did my best.
Your best never seems good enough.
It's time to go.
[monitor beeping rapidly, flatlining]
No, no, no. Jim.
Where's my adrenaline?
[panting]
Well, it looks like Victor
succeeded after all.
I guess I'll have
to settle for killing you.
I can tell you one thing.
I am sick and tired of getting
shot at in my own precinct.
What the bloody hell's going on?
I thought you had this lunatic locked up.
Ivy broke him out and gave him an arsenal.
But I have an idea. I got to get
to the storeroom. Give me cover.
Alvarez! Go!
[both grunting]
Why are you doing this?
What has Jim ever done to you?
Gotham has a chance to be born anew.
To return to what it was,
before people ripped down the trees
and paved over the earth.
He's trying to reunify with the mainland
to save all these people.
A return to filth.
Pollution.
He's fighting for death.
While I promise life
in its purest form.
[shrieks] Is that your plan?
To have the plants take over Gotham
by killing Jim?
Killing Gordon's just the first part.
Bruce Wayne is taking care of the rest.
-For what it's worth, I'm sorry.
-For what?
[gasps]
This pain is nothing
compared to what you are about to feel.
Say goodbye to Jim Gordon for me.
No, no, no! No!
Jim!
Selina, you're wasting your time.
Bruce, you have to snap out
of Ivy's spell. This is not you.
You're wrong. Ivy's given me a purpose.
[Selina grunts]
Stop! Stop! I don't wanna fight you.
What are you gonna do?
Kill everything in Gotham?
The toxins will only kill all the people.
The plants will adapt. They always do.
Can you hear what that sounds like?
Yeah. It sounds great!
[grunts]
[coughs]
[breathing heavily] I guess
I shouldn't be surprised.
You don't care about Gotham.
You're gonna leave anyway.
What about the rest of us, huh?
The ones who are gonna be
stuck here without you?
Selina.
[both panting]
Selina, I'm okay.
Bruce, I'm so sorry.
-We gotta stop Lucius. Come on.
-Okay.
Lucius, you have to stop the shutdown.
Oh, no, I can't do that.
Ivy would be so mad.
Listen to me.
I used Ivy's perfume to hypnotize you.
-She's using you.
-No!
Ivy would never do that.
We're perfectly bonded,
like carbon and oxygen,
or hydrogen and oxygen.
We do not have time for this.
I'm sorry.
[grunts]
There.
-Ugh, you kicked me in the head!
-I didn't have a choice, Lucius.
Bruce, where's Ivy?
She was headed to the GCPD.
I wonder what Ivy's doing right now.
[Harvey] Hey, lover boy.
Are you serious right now?
[Harvey] As a heart attack.
[laughing fiendishly]
What an idiot.
-[Harvey yells]
-Oh...
[Harvey grunts]
[exhales] Oh, that felt good.
[Lee] Come on, Jim! You fight for
everyone else, you never give up.
Fight for yourself, Jim. Come on.
[thunder cracking]
It's time.
[Lee] Jim.
[Gordon] Lee.
-Is that...
-Yes.
Do you wanna...
I don't know.
I don't know that I can.
Oh, I see.
No!
Goodbye, Jim.
No, I wanna live! I wanna live!
I wanna live!
It's too late.
No, I wanna live!
[baby crying]
[gasps]
-Lee...
-[Lee] Don't move.
Don't move.
How do you feel?
Like I almost died.
Well, you didn't.
-You're fine. You came back to me.
-'Cause I need you.
Lee, this child...
It's okay.
It's okay to be scared.
The only thing scarier than doing this
is doing it without you.
Can I ask you something?
[inaudible]
-[Bruce] He seems nervous.
-[Selina] I know.
He should be thrilled.
Marrying a woman who's smarter
and better looking than him.
Selina, while we were fighting,
when I was hypnotized,
you talked about me leaving Gotham--
Quiet.
Here she comes.
You may sit.
[chuckles]
I'm just gonna say, this isn't gonna be
some long, drawn-out tearful affair
like you all are used to. Okay?
This is gonna be a short wedding.
I'm gonna try and make it quick,
-so we can all get to the bar. Okay?
-[all laughing]
I first met a young Jim Gordon when he was
a pain in the ass, moralistic
rookie detective.
[Lee chuckles]
In the years since, he'e evolved into
a pain in the ass, moralistic captain.
[Gordon chuckles]
[Harvey] I'd say he's my best friend.
But in truth, he's my only friend.
So we'll skip that.
Uh, on to Lee.
Lee's always had his back.
Except for the time when she was infected
with the crazy-making virus
and she tried to kill him.
But that's love.
[laughing]
[Harvey] But I will say,
if there's one beautiful thing that's
happened over these last few crazy years,
it's that these two people met each other.
And that truly is a beautiful thing.
Jim, will you please take Lee's hand?
[clears throat]
Do you, Jim Gordon,
take Lee Thompkins to be
your lawfully wedded wife,
to have and to hold,
from this day forward,
for better, for worse,
for richer, for poorer,
in sickness and in health,
to love and cherish
till death do you part?
I do.
And you, Lee Thompkins?
Do you do the same?
Sure, Harvey.
I do.
By the power vested in me
by absolutely no one,
[people laughing]
I now pronounce you husband and wife.
[cheering]
What?
And now Jim Gordon and Lee Thompkins
are man and wife.
Thank God you held this city together so
that this blessed event could take place.
It was never gonna work.
What?
Controlling the gangs
was not a backup plan.
You saw a chance to convince James Gordon
that you had changed.
But he will never see you as anything
but a dangerous woman
keeping his child from him.
Then I'd best be long gone before
he can do anything about it.
He will hunt you
till the ends of the earth.
[snickers]
Let him.