Previously onGotham...
General Wade's landing craft docked.
His convoy's on the way here now.
Reunification day is today.
- Captain Gordon.
- General.
Welcome to Gotham.
Incoming! Get back!
- Eduardo. What did Walker do to you?
- Eduardo's dead, Jim.
There is only Bane now.
Everything I have done here
is about punishing Gotham
for the sins of Bruce Wayne.
I'm not leaving.
And I don't think
I can let you leave either.
What are you doing?
Ra's al Ghul.
This is revenge for his death.
- And who am I?
- You're his daughter.
- Barbara Kean.
- Run!
My name is Nyssa al Ghul.
I believe you knew my father.
- Where's Nyssa?
- I don't know.
But she's planning on using
the military to wipe out Gotham.
I can order them to stand down.
Now let's get you out of here.
This is General Wade.
- Begin your bombing run on my order.
- Wait, wait.
- Let's go, let's go, let's go!
- Back.
We need to get a hold of Barbara.
Nyssa al Ghul is coming for her.
The sooner she and Lee get back
here with the baby, the better.
We've got refugees coming in
from all over Gotham, Jim.
People are scared.
I know you're not one to quit
but if there's ever a time
to wave the white flag, now is it.
Nyssa al Ghul doesn't wanna
just conquer Gotham.
She wants to destroy it,
kill everyone she finds.
The only thing standing between her
and these people is us.
Gather the team.
Get every able-bodied refugee down
to the bunkers beneath the GCPD.
Why do I get the feeling
he's concocting
an elaborate plan
to get us all killed?
You better gather up these refugees.
Look at him.
The medics did everything
they could to stabilize him.
Now all we can do is wait.
This is my fault.
I sent him on this mission.
Alfred knew what
he was signing up for, Bruce.
We all did.
Nyssa and Bane are coming
after me and Barbara.
Coming after Gotham.
Because of what we did to Ra's.
What you did was stop him.
Twice.
We'll stop his psycho daughter
together.
I'm sure you recognize this knife.
You touch my baby
and I will turn you into a pile
of ash just like I did your father.
A bit cruel, don't you think?
Don't let this little one
get too attached
when you won't be around much longer.
Soon, you and Bruce Wayne
will see Gotham and Jim Gordon's
precious Green Zone destroyed.
Then I'll allow you to die.
My father made his name
destroying empires.
Now it's my turn.
- Hello.
- Listen to me.
There was this submarine in the docks
full of Gotham's gold. It's yours.
Just leave the city.
Let me and my baby go.
No.
I think I'll keep this little one
and raise her as my own...
as an al Ghul.
- I take it the army has landed.
- They're just awaiting my orders.
Then what are you waiting for?
Cute little baby.
Wait, what?
You're ordering us to destroy
the Green Zone?
Anyone still in Gotham
is an enemy of the state.
I won't be party to the murder
of civilians, General.
Then you're relieved of command.
Who the hell are you?
I'm your new commander.
Does anybody else have a problem
with the General's orders?
Good. Let's get started.
What's the matter?
Can we really be so cavalier
about the destruction of Gotham?
Let me think about that.
Yes!
- Darn it!
- Oswald.
Where are you going? Oswald.
This is my city and I will be damned
if I'm gonna let those
bastards take it.
I cannot let you do this.
You of all people should wanna
stop those monsters.
They forced you to destroy Haven,
to murder hundreds
of innocent civilians.
You're just gonna let them
get away with it?
I was kind of planning on it, yeah.
Very well.
I'm going to follow my heart.
Oswald!
You have been down this road before.
Following your heart
has never worked out for you.
Perhaps.
But perhaps you could learn something
if you listen to this
instead of this.
I'm gonna miss you, Edward.
I'll miss you too, Oswald.
I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to the...
God!
Come on, baby.
Okay. Good boy.
Go with the man in green.
You'll be safe.
Oswald?
If you walk off this dock,
I'm taking the submarine.
And the treasure!
Nyssa al Ghul wants to kill
everyone in Gotham.
But to get to us, the army
has to follow the western corridor.
That's where we'll make a stand.
We got a handful of men.
How are we gonna take on an army?
We just have to slow the army
down long enough
to get General Wade out
from under Nyssa's control.
Then he can reverse
the invasion order.
We're trying to reach the Sirens.
Still no luck.
- All right. I'll go.
- Jim.
I need to get Barbara
and Lee back here.
I'll meet you at the barricades.
I know you haven't seen your kid yet
but the GCPD needs a leader
and they're looking to you.
I'll go to Sirens.
Okay.
You sure you wanna do this?
It doesn't take the two of us
to track the General's signal.
And if Jim's making a stand,
that's where I should be.
Okay.
Wayne Enterprise's EMP,
smoke bombs, signal jammers.
Not enough to even the odds
but it may buy you some time.
What's this?
You remember the Nightwing Project?
Portable, next-gen stealth tech.
Put it on any aircraft
and it's invisible to radar,
but unfortunately,
it also seems to serve
as a beacon to certain animals.
You never know.
Might find a use for it.
Oswald, come in.
You still have those eyes
in the back of your head, Jim.
No.
You just have a remarkably
recognizable odor.
Part dandy, part snake.
For all these years,
it hasn't changed.
Drink?
No, thank you.
It dulls the senses.
That's what I was going for.
Surprised you're still here.
I figured you'd be long gone by now.
That storm you've warned me about
for so long, it's finally here.
We've shared some turbulent times,
you and I.
That we have.
When you spared my life
on the pier that day,
banished me from Gotham,
that was the most lost
I've ever been.
Because I was away
from the city, you see.
It's part of me.
You know what I'm talking about
because it's part of you too.
Sure, I could escape with money,
I might add but then what?
Stand on the shores of the mainland
and watch the army burn it
to the ground?
Then watch tasteless industrialists
and vapid politicians rebuild it?
No.
My life is etched
on the walls of every alley
and dirty warehouse here.
My blood lives
in its broken concrete.
I'm staying to fight.
- For my legacy.
- Hey.
The army just busted through
the GCPD checkpoint.
They're heading to the barricades.
Bane's leading them.
- How many men?
- Six, 700.
Still wanna fight?
- How many do we have?
- Maybe 30?
Thirty-one.
It takes two men to pilot
that submarine, Oswald.
The dog can't do it.
Ditto on that blood
and concrete thing.
I kind of like this city
the way it is.
Shall we?
I believe time is of the essence.
Gentlemen?
Remind me to talk to you
about that full pardon.
Alvarez, Harper, Bruce,
take the left flank.
Harvey and I will take the right.
Holy Mary Mother and Joseph.
Captain Gordon.
I always knew you had
savior complex,
but this is too much.
What happened to you, Eduardo?
There was a time when you would've
been up on these barricades with me.
Yes.
But that was before
I found my true purpose.
Stand by.
Fire on my command.
Jim, there's a lot of innocent
soldiers down there
just following orders.
Target Bane and Nyssa's commandos.
Fire on my command.
For Gotham.
Lee?
- Selina.
- Hey.
Come on. We gotta get out of here.
Where's Barbara and the baby?
Nyssa al Ghul took them.
- We have to tell Jim.
- Yeah.
The Narrows.
They never stood a chance.
The ones who could
escape to the GCPD...
Then that's where I'm needed.
Target Jim Gordon.
Oh, I'm sorry,
I don't think he can hear you
through the bullet in his ear!
Eddie!
They're only delaying the inevitable.
Jim, that thing's pointing
right at us!
Go, go, go!
Find me, Jim Gordon and Bruce Wayne.
If the army gets to the barricades,
they'll have a straight shot
to the GCPD and the people there.
We need to find another way
to slow them down.
I think I have a way.
Gather all the ammunition you can,
fall back to the GCPD!
Go, go, now!
We gotta go.
Well, that was a disaster.
Come on, Oswald,
we have to keep moving.
Where? There is nowhere to hide, Jim.
Wherever we go,
the army will find us.
- Get me Gordon.
- It's Lucius.
Tell me you were able to track
the General's signal.
It's coming from City Hall
but there's a problem.
Selina radioed.
Barbara and the baby
were kidnapped by Nyssa al Ghul.
If General Wade is at City Hall,
chances are Nyssa,
Barbara and the baby are too.
Our best bet is for me
to sneak into City Hall alone.
One good electrical zap should
short out the General's chip,
then you can get them
to reverse the invasion order.
See you back at the GCPD.
Get Barbara and the baby back safe.
Come on.
Hey, move!
Upsy-daisy, Oswald.
- We're running out of time.
- Just give me one minute.
- Oh, God.
- I'm so sorry.
I saw the grenade and I froze. I'm...
It's the least I could do.
But tell me...
does it look bad?
No, it's just a...
It looks fine. Let's go.
Where did everybody go?
She's gonna need some morphine.
And his bandage needs changing.
Lee!
- Bruce, is Jim...
- He's okay, for now.
We need to get Jeremiah's battery
from the basement.
After the bridges went down,
Lucius remodified Jeremiah's bomb
to be used for its original purpose.
As a battery.
It's been powering the GCPD.
Right.
We need to make it a bomb again.
You gotta be kidding me.
Jeremiah knew exactly
where to put his bombs
to topple buildings and turn
Gotham into a maze.
We stopped him.
But if we can use
just part of his plan,
we can trap the army
and slow them down.
By knocking buildings down
like dominoes.
But for that to work, we need
to put a bomb in this building.
Ground zero for the blast.
Wayne Enterprises.
Bruce?
There's no other way.
Okay.
How do we get this thing out of here?
To use it as a bomb,
we don't need the whole thing.
All you need is the core...
and the activator.
That's it?
It may look modest
but all it took is one of these
to blow up an entire bridge,
not to mention
the Gotham Clock Tower.
- Bruce, you can't do this alone.
- He's not alone.
I know where to place the bomb.
And you and Lucius are needed here.
I can't believe
we're letting them do this.
Well, add that to the list of things
that I cannot believe are happening.
- Hey.
- What?
The key is there.
Where is she? Is she okay?
Yeah, she's upstairs in the office
with Nyssa and the General.
Nyssa is not gonna stop until
she's killed everyone in Gotham.
One thing at a time.
Let's go save our baby.
Hello, Captain Gordon.
You're seeing your baby
for the first time.
I wish I had a camera.
- Hand her over.
- No.
I don't think I will.
Put down your guns.
Unless you want the little one
hurt in the crossfire.
Even now, the army is making
its way to the Green Zone
while Bane is hunting down
Bruce Wayne.
Only question is,
what to do with you?
This is it.
The bomb will weaken
the support column
and topple the entire building.
This is crazy.
We've spent this entire time
trying to stop Jeremiah,
and now we're actually using
part of his plan?
Believe me...
if there was any other way...
You sure you wanna do this?
First, Wayne Manor gets destroyed
and now Wayne Enterprises.
This building is the heart
of my family's company.
There are things above us my parents
spent their entire lives on.
Some of my earliest memories
are playing with Alfred in this lobby
waiting for my parents
to get down these escalators.
But my parents built this company
to make Gotham a better place.
They would've sacrificed
everything for this city.
They did sacrifice everything.
And if that's what it takes...
so will I.
So remind me how this works?
Pulls energy from the air
and magnifies it.
- And when it does that?
- We run!
I knew you would come for your child.
I just didn't think you'd be foolish
enough to come alone.
I don't need help to take you down.
Don't you see?
It's over.
Gotham will burn
and I'll achieve
what my father couldn't.
Including killing you.
She likes to be held upright.
Barbara, I'll deal with you once
Gotham has been destroyed,
but I'd like you to see this.
I was expecting a little more gusto.
You want gusto?
Is that all you got?
It's Lieutenant Angel.
- They did what?
- No. No.
Is there another way around?
Then tell the army to blast through.
Hey, I'm not done with you yet.
Your friends may have
bought you some time,
but the Green Zone's
destruction is only delayed.
And now, to meet your fate.
Let's meet it together.
Barbara!
You think you can defeat me?
Better men and women
have tried and failed.
I am an al Ghul.
You'll never beat me.
I have my father's blood in my veins.
I am his one true heir.
Do you ever stop talking?
You two do share one thing.
You both love getting
stabbed by this knife.
General Wade...
execute fail-safe.
No.
I'm going to enjoy watching
Gotham be destroyed.
And then, my legacy will be complete.
We gotta hurry.
It's only a matter of time
before the army breaks through.
We need to get back to the GCPD.
Bruce!
Impressive.
You blow up your father's
building to stop the military.
It'll take more to stop me.
- Go on ahead, Selina, warn the GCPD!
- No, we're doing this together.
You shouldn't have hurt Alfred.
Collateral damage. It happens in war.
I'm sorry you weren't there
to see me break your butler.
But I'm so glad you won't miss me
killing your little friend.
Let her go.
In war, there are no attachments.
Only then can you fight
without your hands tied.
You see,
just a little ounce of pressure.
That's all that separates
the living from the dead.
- What is that?
- Wayne cloaking device.
But it had some glitches.
Apparently, it's a beacon
for certain winged mammals.
What winged mammals?
Bats.
There's no way to reverse
the invasion order.
We have to find another way.
- Is she all right?
- She is now.
There, there.
Mama's here.
And your father.
Try not to get blood on her.
- Sir.
- Come on.
We're almost at the Green Zone.
Lee?
Jim.
- The baby?
- I checked her over. She's fine.
Though she could use a feed.
Where's General Wade?
The army's broken through.
General Wade's dead.
Nyssa al Ghul escaped.
There's no way to order
the army to stand down.
So now what?
The army blew up Wayne Enterprises
and knocked down two other buildings.
We don't stand a chance.
Actually, that was Bruce and Selina.
- What?
- The army's blocks away.
- From what direction?
- Every direction.
We're surrounded.
Jim, I need to get her out of here.
All right.
The tunnels underneath the GCPD,
there's a vent shaft
that connects to a subway line.
Take the baby and the refugees
down to the subways,
get them behind enemy lines.
- Don't stop till you get to safety.
- Okay.
But what about you?
I'll hold them off outside,
buy you some time.
- Jim...
- These refugees,
most of them are from the Narrows.
They know you and they trust you.
They know you'll protect them.
Go.
Oh, there you are, Master Bruce.
Rest, Alfred.
All this time,
I tried to protect you.
Here you are, a soldier.
A soldier for good.
You've spent your life protecting me.
Now, it's time for me to do the same.
It's time for me to protect Gotham.
Even if there's nothing
left to defend.
All right, everyone,
let's move, okay?
All right, you'll walk about
five blocks underground,
and then you'll get to a subway vent.
Go.
Thank you.
You're not coming with us?
Jim and our friends are out there,
making a stand.
That's where I belong.
Wait, what are we going
to do without you?
Survive.
Make sure this was all worth it.
Go.
What was that for?
Everything you've done for me.
And for her.
Just get them to safety.
It's over, Jim.
Our war has come to an end.
This isn't a war.
This is a firing squad.
- I told you to go.
- And I didn't listen.
Ready.
Aim...
Shoulder to shoulder.
- Stand together.
- What the...
They're here for us, Jim.
Fire.
I said fire!
You have a choice.
You can stand with us,
or you can stand with them.
Yes!
We are Gotham!
We are Gotham! We are Gotham!
That bitch was telling
the truth after all.
We managed to raise the mainland
on the radio.
They know everything.
As of right now,
the army is being repurposed
for the humanitarian mission
of rebuilding Gotham.
These refugees will get food,
water, medical treatment.
They're setting up a crisis
center in Federal Square.
I'll be damned.
Hey.
So...
this whole not listening thing,
it's not gonna become a habit, is it?
You're welcome.
Go.
This is gonna make one hell
of a bedtime story someday.
- Can I?
- Of course.
I don't even know what to call her.
Barbara.
Barbara Lee Gordon.
In this city, it's important
she know who she can rely on.
Bruce, what's wrong?
We won.
Nyssa al Ghul is still out there.
And she and Bane were right.
All this happened because of me.
Because people were trying to hurt me
and the people I care about.
When Bane had you...
I thought he was gonna kill you,
Selina
and there was nothing I could do.
Hey.
I will be here whenever you need me.
What?
That's what my parents
used to tell me.
Come here.
- That bitch stole our submarine!
- And our gold.
And by now she's probably landed
somewhere on the mainland,
impossible to track.
After all we've been through
these last months,
we are once again left with nothing.
Nothing!
Back to square one.
Common criminals.
We saved this city
from certain damnation,
but will we see any credit
for our loyalty?
Our selfless bravery? Of course not!
I don't want their thanks.
Or their respect.
You know what I felt
standing shoulder to shoulder
with those people out there?
Nothing.
I feel...
absolutely nothing for those drab...
boring people.
That was me once.
Minimum wage at a thankless job
at the GCPD.
Yes, sir. No, sir.
Thank you so much, sir.
Pick up scraps
from my master's floor.
Shy, awkward,
pathetic.
Ed.
Common criminals.
Never again.
I've shown this city
who I truly am once before,
and I will do it again.
They will bow to The Riddler,
and they won't get up
until I permit them to.
Yes.
You're right.
Our accomplishments have been erased,
our brilliant minds underrated.
If they had let me run this city
the way I wanted to,
it would not be in ruins now.
I have the men,
the money, the guns...
Gordon took them.
Why? Because he still sees you
as Fish Mooney's umbrella boy,
and he always will.
Yes.
I only came back to help him
save this city
so that I could take it for myself.
We would be stronger together.
No one could stop us.
Yeah, perhaps.
Let's make a pact.
Here and now.
We will take what we want
from who we want,
and we will suffer no fools.
Together.
Shall we shake on that?
Please.
We're brothers.
A hug.
A hug it is.
Life begins anew.
Shall we head to work?
Thank you all for coming here today.
It is my great honor
to introduce Mayor Chang.
With reunification underway
and the bridges being rebuilt,
it is my honor to bestow
upon Captain James Gordon
the title of Commissioner.
We're gonna miss you
around the bullpen.
I won't be far.
And the mission doesn't change.
Trying to make this city
a better place.
Be careful.
You're swimming with sharks now.
If you need anything ever...
I know who to call.
You deserve this, Jim.
You really do.
I'm gonna go get a drink before
you get all teary-eyed on me.
What do you mean you're leaving?
Bane's in prison. It's over.
My life here...
it's too public.
You've made up your mind.
Gotham's in good hands.
Commissioner.
Thank you, Bruce
for everything you've done for me
and for the city.
Gotham will always be your home.
Bruce is all grown up.
That he is.
Well, now you have another
little one to look after.
Where's Bruce?
He left you this.
You know how to reach me,
if you need anything?
Yes.
Well, you know me, Master Bruce so,
I'll be very self-sufficient.
Busy, actually, you know,
we start the reconstruction
of Wayne Enterprises
and Wayne Manor tomorrow.
You'll remember everything
I told you, won't you?
Of course.
Good. That's...
that's good.
I never tried to replace
your parents, you know.
I couldn't. I never would.
But I want you to know, Master Bruce,
that you are the only son
that I will ever have.
And I could not be more proud.