Previously on Gotham...
Monsters are coming, Mr. Mayor.
Six criminally-insane inmates
busted out of Arkham Asylum.
They want mass panic.
Hello, Jim. How do I look?
Barbara!
- Yo, Commish.
- Yeah.
Don't move.
You should probably
get back to work.
Who knows what went wrong
while you were gone.
It's a new day, Jim.
Jerome Valeska.
The attack on the G.C.P.D.
Someone on the streets is talking.
Somebody knows something.
Valeska has red hair. Crazy laugh.
Might be rolling with the blonde number.
I don't know anything. Honest.
- You believe him?
- Nope.
Me neither.
It's the truth!
But, hey, I can help you guys.
- You know, spread the word and stuff.
- Valeska killed a friend of ours.
Anybody hides him, anybody protects him,
they go down, too.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
- Now spread the word.
- No. No!
Sneaking out?
Just like a guy.
There are loose ends that need tying.
Need this?
Bring back bagels.
No need for that.
I thought Miss Kean and I could have
a little chat. Good morning.
Jerome's waiting outside.
Try and keep him focused.
You be nice.
You two seem to be getting along.
I'm so glad.
She needs a friend.
My sister is a very special person.
She seems so strong,
but yet she's quite fragile. Sugar?
Sure.
You acquitted yourself very well
at the adventure at the G.C.P.D.
Jim Gordon escaped the carnage unscathed.
- Top marks.
- Thank you.
Did you know my family built this city?
We carved the bedrock
upon which it stands.
But there is not a bridge, an alley,
a ditch that carries our name.
My forefathers were betrayed.
Their legacy erased.
And I am here to punish those
who wronged us,
and reclaim what is ours.
Strawberry?
I didn't ask.
So you're gonna take over Gotham
by unleashing a bunch of loonies.
Awesome plan.
That's only part one.
- So what's the second part?
- Oh, you're gonna love it.
There's a starring role for you.
You'll be famous and powerful.
And your fondest dream will come true.
You know my dreams, do you?
When Jim Gordon has
outlived his usefulness,
I'm gonna help you destroy him.
Not kill him.
Destroy him.
Body and soul.
Bang.
Shocking images.
Gotham is on high alert today after--
Look,
I'm just saying, I'll chuck mopes
out of windows
until the cows come home,
but at some point,
we gotta go see Penguin.
Why would he break Jerome out of Arkham?
Or attack the G.C.P.D.?
He wouldn't.
But that weasel's running things now.
- If there's chatter, he'd know it.
- I'll think about it.
- Jim--
Alvarez, where are you with
Jerome's circus contacts?
- Circus is upstate. I'm just waiting--
- Follow up.
His father's probably with him.
He covered for him once before.
He might have some information. Do it.
You, Detective.
Which escapee are you tracking?
Helzinger. No one's seen him.
He's 6'7", two-seventy-five
with the mind of a five-year-old.
Somebody's seen him.
Hey!
What are you doing?
That stays up until we have her killer
in custody, you understand?
Yes, sir.
Sarah Essen and nine of your brothers
were killed in this house.
In our house.
Their murderer stood right there
and he laughed at us.
Never forget that.
What?
- So how are you?
- I'm fine.
Really?
Look, I know Essen was your friend.
Lee, whatever you're about to say,
I know it's coming from a good place,
but I can't hear it right now.
So, the Gotham Children's Hospital gala
is tonight,
which I helped organize.
I can't.
- You can't go?
- No.
Even though a few hours away
from all of this might actually help.
Lee.
Okay.
I just have to tell you something,
because if I don't
and you find out, you're gonna be pissed.
There's gonna be a magician.
Yeah, you're right.
- Stop beating yourself up.
- I'm trying.
- I know you are.
- I should have been here. I wasn't.
Stop it.
Kiss me.
Better?
Not to interrupt your
weirdly-timed make-out session,
but Alvarez got in touch
with the circus manager.
The blind fortune teller,
Jerome's dad, bailed on him.
Stayed in town. Got an address.
- I'll call you.
- Okay.
Who's there?
I know someone's there.
Hiya, Pops.
Long time, no see.
So, how you doing?
Ah, silent treatment, eh?
Here, I'll tell you a story.
Ah.
You remember Kansas City, Dad?
The circus went through town every spring,
right around my birthday.
There was this guy.
Him and my mom used to drink and fornicate
and beat the crap out of me.
They would make a whole night out of it.
And I remember one time.
It was my ninth birthday.
Him and my mom had just finished round one
of boozing, boning, beating up Jerome,
and were deciding to take a little break.
Anyway, hmm,
I was outside the trailer,
and you were there.
And you said,
"Why are you crying, Jerome?"
"It's my birthday,
"and my mom and the snake guy
are beating me."
And then you said,
"This world doesn't care about you
or anyone else, Jerome.
"Better to realize that now."
And that was it.
Well, you see, there's this guy, Dad.
He believes in me.
He thinks I'm gonna be a star.
And tonight,
all of Gotham will see that, too.
Except for you, 'cause you'll be,
you know, dead.
- Jerome--
- Oh, is this the part where you say
how sorry you are? Hmm?
How you should have believed in me?
How it's not too late to start again?
News flash, Dad, it's too late.
You don't have to do this.
No. I'm pretty sure I do.
I was a bad father. But I did love you.
To kill me for that--
It's not why I'm gonna kill you.
Plans to Arkham Asylum.
And look at these.
Letters between you and your troubled son.
Innocent at first glance,
but Detective Gordon--
You remember him, right?
He'll feel little bumps,
a secret message written in braille
between you and your son
discussing my escape.
Finally, the knockout gas
used to disable the orderlies.
'Cause you see, Dad,
this guy I was telling you about,
he's the one who broke me out of Arkham.
He doesn't want anyone to
know about that, obviously.
So, the police will find
these letters. Hmm.
They'll think,
"The blind old fool really loved his son.
"What a wonderful father."
There won't be a dry eye in the house.
They'll never believe it.
Ah, sure they will. Cops are dumb.
There's nothing to eat in this dump.
Finish up and let's go.
Sorry you're gonna miss my big night, Dad.
But, hey, you're psychic,
so tell me, do I kill?
You will be a curse upon Gotham.
Children will wake from sleep,
screaming at the thought of you.
Your legacy will be death and madness.
Well, say hi to Mom for me.
G.C.P.D.
Mr. Cicero, it's Detective Gordon.
We need to speak with you about your son.
Mr. Cicero?
Harvey. Window.
Harvey.
Detective Gordon, old pal,
that gas sure packs a wallop, huh?
That's cute.
I'm sensing anger.
You killed Sarah Essen,
now I'm gonna kill you.
Mmm-mmm.
Don't shoot him.
How about a little flesh wound?
No, no.
My dibs.
This is a waste of time.
We had a deal, didn't we, Master Bruce?
Part of which was
you resuming a normal lifestyle.
Your parents were both patrons
to the Children's Hospital,
therefore, it makes you a patron.
Besides, there's gonna be a magician.
And you like magicians, don't you?
No, I don't.
I hate magicians.
You know what I said about being normal?
Excuse me.
I'm Lee Thompkins.
I work with James Gordon.
He's mentioned you.
- I saw you and thought--
- Of course.
- It's very nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
This is my guardian, Alfred Pennyworth.
- It's an absolute pleasure.
- Thank you.
How is Detective Gordon doing
since the attack on the precinct?
I was thinking I should call him.
He'd appreciate that.
Can I get you
something to drink?
Uh, just water. Thank you.
So, I hear there's gonna be a magician.
Hello, Selina.
Hey.
I didn't expect
to see you here.
Well, you wanna steal stuff,
it helps to go where the rich people are.
You do know this is a benefit
for Children's Hospital.
So?
So these people are here for a good cause.
Me eating is a good cause.
Besides, didn't I steal something
for you once?
Selina, that was different.
Right.
How'd that go?
You get into that guy's safe?
Yes. Though things didn't turn out
quite like I planned.
A lot's happened since then.
- Alfred says there's gonna be a magician.
- I'm working, and hate magicians.
See you around, Bruce.
So, you wanna share your plan?
Remember I told you I could divine a thing
a person truly wants?
What Gotham wants is a hero.
And tonight, I'm going to give them one.
Shall we? Jerome and Tabby went on ahead.
Great cape.
Thank you for filling in
on such short notice.
But how did you hear
our magician dropped out, Mr...
Rudolpho.
Well, you know, magic.
Oh, I won't be needing that.
- Come on.
- I'm sorry,
but really there is no mystery.
Tabitha, have you met Deputy Mayor Kane?
Harrison, this is my Tabith.
Ah, nice to meet you.
Oh, and could you please tell your brother
that when a handsome billionaire
appears out of nowhere,
people get curious?
"Where'd he come from?
How'd he make his money?
"Who's he dating?"
My wife would kill me if I don't
get something. A tidbit.
He's a monster in the sack.
Do you have any news of Mayor James?
No, no. It's a real mystery.
We don't know where he is.
How intriguing.
Harrison, would you mind?
A little family business.
Of course. Miss Galavan.
Everything's ready.
See you at home.
So how do you go from being
in the Royal Marines to a butler?
Well, it's a bit tedious,
really, after a while.
You know, parachuting into
one global hot spot after another,
warlords putting ridiculous bounties
on your head.
Gets a bit boring, really.
You have amazing stories.
Yeah, well, you know, one or two.
You know, I don't really get nights off,
but if ever you'd like to
pop by Wayne Manor
for dinner one evening, I'd--
Oh, that's very kind of you,
Mr. Pennyworth.
No. "Alfred." Please, "Alfred."
Alfred, that's very kind of you, but--
Now having said that,
I don't see why I can't take a night off.
And I... I happen to know
the head chef at Chez Parnasse.
Well, I'm afraid, I--
Did you say Chez Parnasse?
I've been trying to eat there
for quite some time.
You have the most beautiful eyes.
Oh, wow. Okay, look--
Thank you, but, uh...
Alfred, I'd like to leave.
Yeah, um...
What about Dr. Thompkins' water?
And, of course,
you're gonna miss the magician.
Sorry, I must have forgotten your water.
Alfred, I still want to leave.
- Are you not feeling well?
- No, no, he's abso-- He's absolutely fine.
He's fine. Why don't you just
pop off to the bar, Master Bruce, and...
Show's about to start, Miss Thompkins.
Is it time?
I've roped myself into emcee duties
for the night.
I hope you'll stay for the show.
I wouldn't miss it for the world.
What?
Good evening.
I am Dr. Lee Thompkins.
For the past five years,
I've had the honor of being part
of the Children's Hospital.
Thank you for your support,
and thank you so much
for coming out tonight.
Over the years,
we've had magicians
come and entertain our children.
And so tonight,
we have one of the magicians here for you.
Without further ado,
please allow me to present to you
the Great Rudolpho.
Ha!
Greetings, ladies and germs.
I am indeed the Great Rudolpho.
Please ogle my lovely assistant.
Ooh!
For my first act,
I'll require a volunteer.
Let me see...
Duck, duck, duck, duck, duck, duck, duck,
goose.
Who's the goose?
Go on, Master Bruce. Be a sport.
Don't keep the lady waiting.
Fine.
Hello, young man. Please.
Does this handsome gentleman have a name?
Bruce.
Bruce!
Well, Bruce, this won't hurt a bit.
Is there a doctor in the house?
No, just, excuse--
Just wait, wait, wait one second.
Go home.
I'm fine.
Been running this since last night,
and you got a face full of that gas.
Go home.
You going home?
I didn't think so.
- Maybe I will go get some sleep.
- Yeah? Good idea.
But we got somewhere, right?
At least now we know
who broke Jerome out of Arkham.
Yeah, crazy old blind man
that lived alone.
A clever crazy old blind man.
If his father broke him out,
why'd Jerome kill him, huh?
He was probably planning this
Maniax shtick since you sent him away.
He was just a kid.
Every evil bastard in the world
was just a kid once.
Yeah.
But I don't think it was his father
that broke him out.
Cool. Back to square one.
You're right, I will go
and get some sleep.
For the record, I knew Essen
a hell of a lot longer than you.
She saved my ass hundreds of times.
You really should go home.
First thing tomorrow,
we'll go see Penguin.
You're right,
he's got his ears on the street.
Jim.
Never mind.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Give them a wave.
Some people say
Bruce has a split personality.
- Very good, Master Bruce.
- Mmm.
For my next illusion,
I'd like to call to the stage
esteemed Deputy Mayor Harrison Kane.
Is there something familiar to you
about those two?
Oh, my God.
- Lee, I was just ab--
- Jim, it's Barbara. She's here.
And I think maybe Jerome--
By the way,
nobody here is getting out alive.
Really?
- He's really...
- Oh, my God!
Whoo!
All right, Master Bruce, time to leave.
Ta-da!
Don't shoot!
- Selina!
- Bruce!
You!
- What's going on?
- Hostage situation.
The magician just killed the Deputy Mayor.
It's Jerome Valeska. The same man
that killed Commissioner Essen.
- Who's in charge here?
- I guess you are.
Lee, thank God. I've been--
Sorry, Jimbo,
it's just little old me.
Jerome.
Are you outside?
You are, aren't you?
Oh, goody.
I swear to God, if you've hurt her--
Breathe, James. I haven't touched
a hair on your girlfriend's pretty head.
See for yourself.
This is live television,
after all.
However, the police are here.
They are trying to...
- The feed just came back.
- Ooh!
You son of a bitch.
True. But not the point.
Hey, let's talk about what I want.
Excuse me.
$47,000,000,
a helicopter, obviously,
the dry cleaning I left at Mr. Chang's,
be careful, the man is a crook,
and, I don't know, a pony.
Uh, you got 10 minutes
or I start killing people.
Remember, this is being broadcast to
every home in Gotham, so,
you know, don't let people die.
Bye.
- I think that went well.
- Enough.
You need to pack up your
pathetic little sideshow and leave.
Is that right?
It may be presumptuous
to speak for all the citizens of Gotham,
but we are sick of you.
You're a small, vicious man
with a pathetic need for attention.
Enough, man.
For God sakes, enough.
I'm curious what your leverage
is here, Mr...
Theo Galavan.
Well, Mr. Theo Galavan,
if you don't sit down, uh,
I'm gonna shoot you in the face.
I know there is some
human decency left in you.
If you need to take a hostage, take me.
But let these people go home.
To their families, to their children.
- Boring.
- Right.
Get your men. We're going in.
I used this to sneak into the party.
We're lucky those dummies
didn't know about it.
- Wait--
- We're almost outside.
Wait! I have to go back.
Are you crazy?
That guy was killing people.
Yes. And Alfred's back there.
I'm not going back.
I don't expect you to.
Selina...
I miss you.
I just wanted to say that.
You're refusing a direct order?
I could have your stripes.
That maniac killed the commissioner.
Not my men, we're not equipped for this.
Fine. I'll go it alone.
Oh.
Hold very still.
I can't look.
Someone tell me how it turns out.
Damn. Turn around.
Whoo!
Well, clap!
So, Lee, how's Jim doing?
I hope he's not blaming himself for this
whole "Essen being killed" thing.
You are one crazy bitch.
So rude.
You know, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna make a prediction.
Within a year,
Jim and I will be back together.
Wanna know why?
Because we're both the same.
We both have a dark side.
And one day,
we will tell our grandchildren
about how this man-eating harpy
almost tore us apart.
But in the end,
love conquered all.
- You're...
- I'm sorry, what's that?
Hasn't been 10 minutes.
We need to buy you a watch.
Well, I think it's time
for tonight's first official victim.
You all know and love.
Poor rich boy,
parents murdered in an alley,
and my favorite volunteer.
Where is Bruce Wayne?
You know I'm an orphan too, Bruce?
I killed my parents, though.
Where are you hiding?
Bruce!
Where are you, buddy?
Kill his butler.
Come on, move it, butler.
All right, last chance, Bruce,
but it's about to get
very butler-brainy out here.
Detective Gordon.
He's gonna kill Alfred. I have to help.
Brucey!
No. It's you he wants.
Bruce, he just wants you.
I will not let him hurt Alfred.
I'm bored. Shoot the butler.
Stop!
What the bloody hell are you doing, Bruce?
There's a gun in my jacket.
Detective Gordon's behind the curtains.
Let's get this started, huh?
You, check behind the curtain.
Make sure no one's playing
silly buggers.
Drop the knife!
I don't have a clean shot.
Stay calm, Bruce.
It seems like
we've got ourselves a pickle.
What do you say, Brucey boy?
Wanna boost our ratings, huh?
Smile.
I said enough.
I know, I know.
This is not what we rehearsed.
I'm so sorry, Jerome.
You have real talent.
But now you see, the plot thickens.
Enter the hero.
You said
I was gonna be...
Jim! Stop her!
A pony.
Uh...
See, someone like that
has no interest in building things.
He's not part of a tradition. Hmm.
It's chaos for chaos' sake.
Perhaps I could use a new laugh.
Huh?
Wow!
Dude!
Color me impressed.
You know, if I close my eyes,
I can still see you
holding Fish's umbrella.
"Yes, Miss Mooney. No, Miss Mooney.
"Whatever you say, Miss Mooney.
"That wig looks great on you,
Miss Mooney."
Seriously, the worm has turned.
Detective Bullock,
I heard you rejoined the force.
I'm so happy.
But aren't you missing
all of the excitement?
Yeah, I got the word too late.
Besides, I want to talk to you.
Of course.
Always happy to help.
See, there's talk on the street
that Jim Gordon did a favor for you.
Collected a debt
and the guy ended up dead.
Rumors.
Well, then again, where there's smoke...
Jim shouldn't worry about that.
He and I are good friends.
Well, see, that's the problem, Oswald,
I think he is worried.
Because something happened today
and you were
the obvious person to come to,
and I sensed Jim was a little reluctant
to come down here.
Like I said, he shouldn't worry.
As long as you two remain friends.
- Exactly.
- Yeah.
I've got a half a mind to take you outside
and beat you senseless with a garbage can.
Maybe some other time.
Call yourself whatever you want, man.
"The King of Gotham."
But to me,
you'll always be that little umbrella boy.
And if you come after Jim Gordon,
you gotta come after me.
And I still owe you for Fish.
But seriously, this place is amazing.
Give me another drink.
You were very brave.
You helped save the lives
of everyone in here.
Your parents...
They would've been proud.
That they would have been.
They also would have given me the sack
for letting you do something so idiotic.
It was all of us. We were a team.
Yeah, I guess we were.
Is he okay?
Fine. Though I'd still like him
to get checked out at the hospital.
Barbara gave him quite a knock.
Any word on her?
I don't know.
She went through a trap door in the stage.
They must have always been planning
to use that as their exit.
Don't worry, we'll find her.
Uh, Mr. Galavan, sir.
Alfred Pennyworth.
I'd just like to thank you for saving
young Master Wayne's life.
Oh.
If there's anything
I can ever do for you, sir.
Or I.
I really just did what any citizen
of Gotham would have done.
I wish that were true.
Jim Gordon.
Theo.
Well, if you ever need anything,
please call.
We're all in this together, right?
Thank you, sir.
Right, well, I suppose I better be
getting this young man home.
It's been much more of an
exciting evening than originally planned.
I never did like magicians.
Good night.
It was very nice meeting you,
Dr. Thompkins.
And you, Bruce.
Good night's sleep,
you'll be right as roses.
I do hope we get to see you again soon.
Thank you.
Alfred.
- You're sure you're okay?
- I'm fine.
Kiss me?
- Jim...
- Kiss me.
- Oh, bugger.
- Alfred.
- You knew, didn't you?
- I didn't know, Alfred.
You did.
You let me make a right mug of meself.
Alfred. No, I didn't.
- You did.
- I didn't know.
Well, I didn't know.
Despite the presence of the G.C.P.D.,
it was billionaire Theo Galavan,
newly arrived in Gotham,
but already making his name,
who stood up to the escaped lunatic.
- Am I a hero?
- Hmm.
Apparently.
...greeted him with rapturous applause.
I think tonight,
the people of Gotham have said,
"Enough. The reign of tyranny is over."
Now the real fun begins.
Poor Jerome.
Yes, very sad.
Such a compelling character, but limited.
No, he was never gonna last long.
I don't know about that.
The kid had a way about him.
Oh, poor baby,
did you get a bump?
... G.C.P.D. Commissioner Sarah Essen.
...the killer, Jerome Valeska, is dead,
his murderous escapades
left a deep impression on Gotham.
Nobody here is getting out alive.
Coming through.
Bang.
You will be a curse upon Gotham.
Children will wake from sleep,
screaming at the thought of you.
Your legacy will be death and madness.
English - SDH