- Previously on Gotham...
- Everybody,
raise your glasses
to the killer
of Jeremiah Valeska.
(cheering)
A lead on a guy selling RPGs.
Get out of here, Barbara.
(gunshot)
Eduardo?
Nice shot, right?
Tell me what you did!
I put a chip in your brain.
Better talk, now.
A contract came along.
A contract from who?
(beeps)
Walker wants Ed Nygma
taken out now.
Walker was behind this?
She's been controlling Nygma
the whole time?
- (gasps)
- Ouch.
Stitches still sore, huh?
I told you I had to let
Selina thrust the knife
into my flesh at least once.
(beeps)
You know Jim Gordon.
You know this city.
Find him. And kill him.
(panting)
(gunfire)
(grunts)
Your chances of survival
are astronomically low, James.
Continuing to run
is ill-advised.
(door opens)
(thudding)
(whirring)
♪♪
Hope you're well rested, Edward.
We have a lot of work
ahead of us.
(sighs)
Edward?
(chuckles)
(sniffing)
Edward, what is it?
Is someone down there, boy?
(Edward whimpers)
MAGPIE:
♪ Cash and jewels aplenty ♪
♪ Sparkle in the sky ♪
♪ Five and ten and 20 ♪
♪ Time to say bye-bye. ♪
Ooh, pretty, pretty.
I'll call you Charlotte.
(giggles)
Ooh, you're a handsome devil.
What's your name?
Oswald Cobblepot.
But I'm guessing
you already knew that.
Stop!
Penguin. Didn't think
you'd miss a couple things.
Couple things go missing
all the time.
How did you know
about this place?
All of the thieves I used
are dead.
Yep, yep.
Was on a job.
Someone got there first.
Followed them
back here.
Saw you. Bang, bang.
Then you know what is in store.
I do hope whatever you came
here for was worth your life.
(both laugh)
The Russifer Diamond.
Not Russifer. Charlotte.
What's in your other hand?
Wait, how did you...
(groans)
Bye-bye.
(panting)
Who the hell was that?
(grunts)
Oh, God...
Oh!
(panting)
Oh, God. It happened
again, didn't it?
What did I do?
You tried to kill me.
Oh. Is that all?
I need answers, Ed.
I know Walker gave the orders
to destroy Haven
and the supply helicopter.
What is she planning next?
I don't know.
Jim, I don't remember anything
once I go under.
You're bleeding.
You have to let me go.
I'm not responsible for this.
That chip in your head
could be evidence.
So unless you want me
to rip it out,
- you're coming with me.
- Okay.
(grunts)
(gunfire in distance)
(indistinct chatter)
ALFRED:
Bruce.
There you are.
So, go on, then.
How'd it go with Selina?
Oh, dear.
Well, I am sorry, Master Bruce,
but perhaps it's for the best.
Maybe. That's not why I called
you here. You see this?
Yeah, I know, right?
Looks like Captain Gordon's
finally getting the help
this city so desperately needs.
Is he?
What the people desperately
need is food and medicine.
Not just more guns.
What is it?
No, it's just this unit.
Their motto is "Born of Blood."
You know them?
Yeah, by reputation only.
They're a horrible bunch
of bastards.
They specialize in military
coups, assassinations.
They're certainly
not the vanguard
for humanitarian relief.
Excuse me.
When's the supply
shipment gonna be here?
Supplies?
These people are
desperate for food,
clean water, medicine.
Oh, yeah. It's on its way.
Where's Captain Gordon?
We lost sight of Gordon.
But don't worry. Eduardo's out
there looking for him right now.
Unless you know
where we might find him?
Logically, he'd come here.
Unless there's some
reason he can't.
Tell you what, kiddo.
I'm gonna find you and your
friend a quiet place in the back
where you can
wait for Gordon.
Ah, don't you worry
about it, mate.
We'll just catch up
with him later.
I insist.
We need to find Jim.
So the government is behind
Haven and the supply helicopter,
and they did it with a chip
in this one's head?
Is that really
the craziest thing
you've ever heard, Barbara?
Bruce hit me up on the radio
a little while ago,
looking for you.
Said things are amiss
in the GCPD.
I'll reach out, see if we
can meet up somewhere safe.
Can you pull in some of your
people, see if they can help?
No. I need them
guarding my territory.
But you have me.
And me.
I don't trust you.
With or without
that chip in your head.
Jim.
They used me as a pawn
to murder innocent people.
They messed with my brain.
The thing that I want
is revenge.
How do I know that chip
can't be reactivated?
Well, when you found
me at Strange's lab,
he was fixing it after a...
car battery mishap...
I-It's safe to say
that I think you shorted it out.
Let me look at that.
- What?
- Your neck.
That's gonna need stitches.
I have a first aid kit.
I need to keep moving.
Just name your fee.
Can't I just want to help?
Not you, not usually.
Friend of mine just
tried to kill me.
I don't want anyone else
waiting for an excuse
- to stab me in the back.
- I gave you Gerry the Jerkwad,
and I'm letting you
hide out in my club.
If I wanted to betray you,
I would have done it earlier.
So, where's that first aid kit?
Gonna make myself useful.
What's it gonna take
for you to trust me?
After everything you've done,
I honestly don't know.
EDUARDO:
I'd listen to her, Jim.
I hear trust is in short supply.
EDUARDO: You forget your
PSYOPS training, Jim?
Lesson one: when a person
is in trouble,
they go to a familiar place.
Your ex-fiancée's bar was
just a stone's throw away,
so it's nice to finally
meet you, Barbara.
Screw you.
Hmm.
It seems
you've lost your tail.
You mean the psychopath
you ordered to kill me?
You had your chance.
It could have been
like old times, buddy.
You, me, together,
making the world a better place.
- By murdering civilians?
- Civilians?
This hellhole is infested
with criminals and terrorists.
Sometimes you just have
to clean house, you know?
I won't let you.
It's not your call, Jim.
(guns clicking)
I'm not dead yet.
James Gordon,
I've been ordered to kill you.
Well, looks like you haven't
lost that tail after all.
(straining):
If I die,
you'll never get the evidence!
Stand down.
I have evidence that you
and Walker are behind Haven.
If I die, it gets out
to the entire country.
It's time to make a deal.
You don't have any evidence.
Is that a risk
you're willing to take?
It is.
Nygma, kill them both.
(bell tolling in distance)
(screaming)
(door closes)
Bad time?
(sighs) What
do you want?
Depends.
What did they want?
Oh. A shot at me.
I killed Jeremiah Valeska.
(laughs softly)
So the rumors are true.
Yeah.
And now, every scumbag in town
wants to take me down
to make a name
for themselves.
So I got to find a new squat.
How about, in exchange
for helping me find someone,
I let you crash in my citadel?
It's seen better days, but...
(laughs):
...then again, right?
Who?
A miscreant I caught in the act
of stealing from me.
She was going to replace
the stolen item
with an exact replica,
except the replica was a bomb.
- (chuckles)
- Ring any bells?
White hair, feathered collar,
kind of of resembles
a goth chicken?
You do know her.
(chuckles)
She goes by the name Magpie.
What'd she steal?
The Russifer Diamond.
What makes you think
I would help you
after you
killed Tabitha
in cold blood?
Because you believe
in an eye for an eye.
Hard as it may be to swallow,
Tabitha made her bed
when she killed my mother.
Tell you what.
I will help you
if I get to keep the diamond.
(laughs)
What?
Not a chance.
Ha, ha, ha.
Then you'll never find her.
And every person in Gotham
will think it's okay
to steal from Penguin.
Is that what you want?
You know me too well.
Fine.
Good.
- What happened?
- EDUARDO: I want every soldier
in the field looking
for Jim Gordon.
Sir, we maxed out
the holding cells.
We may need to keep men here
to control the overflow.
Ethan, Sumiko.
We're moving to phase two.
(grunts)
What in the hell's going on?
Listen up.
I am not here to play nice.
I am not here
to hold anyone's hand.
I am here on a simple mission.
Any questions about the nature
of that mission?
Are you insane?
You can't just execute people.
Do not question me.
This is the mission.
If you don't like it,
you'll be locked up,
you'll remain locked up,
until we purge
the criminal element
from the streets of Gotham.
Sir, Secretary Walker's
on the radio.
(cell door closes)
We've moved on to phase two,
but we've lost track
of Gordon and Nygma.
I think Gordon found a way
to fry the chip.
WALKER:
We can't have Nygma
in the wind with all that
evidence in his head.
Just trust me.
Once we find them...
Don't bother.
I have an idea that will bring
Jim Gordon and Nygma to us.
Thanks for getting
everyone here.
And for the Wayne R and D.
Are you sure about including
Barbara Kean and Ed Nygma?
War makes
for strange bedfellows.
It's good to have
a friend nearby, Bruce.
Ow! Would you be careful?
If you'll stop moving,
this will go a lot faster.
NYGMA: Well, if you would be
more careful, I wouldn't potato
all the long legs
from the hidden spoon.
What just happened?
I believe the chip is installed
against his speech center.
Huh. Do it again.
The human brain is not
a plaything, Ms. Kean.
Please don't habituate
the curtain rod.
(chuckles)
And... ah.
Stay.
There. How does that feel?
(grunts)
Peter Piper picked
a peck of pickled peppers.
Oh, God.
Thank you, Lucius.
LUCIUS: So what exactly
are we looking for?
Anything tying Walker or Eduardo
to the destruction of Haven.
Why would Walker
kill all those people?
That's what we
have to find out.
Oh, yes.
It appears the chip
retains an audio log
of every verbal communication
with Nygma while he was under.
There's some damage, but...
if the command to attack
Haven is still here,
I can trace it back
to the computer
from which it originated.
It has to be Walker.
They won't be able to sweep
this under the rug anymore.
Are you out there, Jim?
What do you want?
We have someone here...
...who wants
to say hello.
THOMPKINS:
J-Jim? What's happening?
Lee?
We found the Queen
of the Narrows
in a run-down hidey-hole
on the north side. Tell me,
how many ex-fiancées
do you have, anyway?
Leave her out of this.
She's not involved.
Ah, but she's a criminal,
and all criminals in Gotham
are now under a death sentence.
But what happens next
is up to you.
A trade, perhaps.
Lee Thompkins for Ed Nygma.
Fine.
Good. Bring Nygma
to the GCPD now.
No, we meet at Haven.
I want you to see
the carnage you've caused.
Always so emotional.
That's not how wars
are won, Jim.
Those are my terms.
Take it or leave it.
(radio crackles)
Okay. I'll play your game.
What are you doing?
He's never gonna
let you walk out of there.
I don't recall volunteering
as a trading chit!
He doesn't want Ed.
He wants the chip.
So I'll give him
the chip. Bruce,
do you have any contacts
in the mainland press?
Several.
What would it take to broadcast
the information from the chip
- to the mainland?
- A transmitter, which I have,
and a very large antenna,
which I do not.
I know where there's an antenna
in the Green Zone,
but you're not gonna like it.
The roof of the GCPD.
(whispering):
Lee.
- Harvey.
- Where the hell have you been?
You've been gone for months.
I don't know.
I can't remember anything.
What happened to me?
I don't know.
We're gonna figure it out.
I promise.
Let's go.
BULLOCK:
It's gonna be okay.
(beeping, clicking)
GORDON (over radio):
Eduardo just arrived.
He brought backup,
like we expected. Time to move.
Copy that.
Let's go.
(birds squawking)
THOMPKINS:
Jim!
Who are these people?
I'm gonna get you
out of here, Lee.
I'm not sure that's true, Jim.
It seems you forgot
to bring someone.
It's hard to make a swap
when you have nothing to trade.
We both know this
is really what you want.
Proof that you and Walker
are responsible
for the destruction of Haven
and the murder of hundreds
of innocent people.
Now let her go.
Let me guess, you made a copy
so you can do this little bit
of theatrics for me.
I expected more from you, Jim.
Three soldiers against one man
without a gun.
You sure you brought
enough help?
I don't need any help.
Is that why you sent Nygma
to do your dirty work?
So he could pick up your slack
like I used to?
Still dining out on pulling me
from that burning truck.
I carried more
than my fair share.
I was always the first man in.
Your recklessness
got people killed.
I don't know what the hell
you're talking about.
Ramirez?
No.
Johnson.
Bolton.
Their deaths were not on me.
Yeah.
Put a bullet in my mouth
and shut me up.
No.
Not a bullet.
But I am gonna shut your mouth.
Once and for all.
Come try.
(creaking)
You sure this
is the place?
Yep.
This is the place.
Stop her!
Ouchie. You're quick.
I know you?
- Doubt it.
- Uh-huh.
You killed Jeremiah.
You're famous.
(laughs)
Not so scary.
I could be famous.
You want a shot at me, too?
Unfortunately, you won't
have the opportunity.
Careful.
This is my workshop
where I make my boom-booms.
Anything here, boom, boom.
Then more boom
and more boom,
then the whole room...
- Boom, boom. We get it.
- You're bluffing.
Catch.
Ooh! No, no!
- (watch ticking)
- MAGPIE: Whoops!
(laughs) That watch
must have been an original,
but other stuff
in there, boom, boom.
Good luck.
We tie our
shoelaces together,
then we lasso the keys
off the desk.
And then what, Roy Rogers, huh?
They surrender in awe?
No harebrained scheme is
gonna get us out of here.
Hello!
Hope you don't mind, I...
borrowed some cop stuff
from the garage.
Oh, boy, you can
put your guns down.
Kevlar in this thing
is designed to withstand a blast
that can tear down a building
twice this size.
What is that?
Is it not obvious?
It's a bomb!
Okay.
Let's play a game.
- Clear out.
- Ah, ah, ah, ah.
If anyone leaves this building,
this thing blows.
You gomers messed with
the wrong super genius,
and now it's time
for a little payback.
Nygma, you're a son of a bitch!
Oh, not now, Bullock.
The body count at Haven
wasn't big enough for you, huh?
Shut up!
What's your game?
The only way
to deactivate this bomb
is to put a four-digit code
on the keypad there.
What's the code?
(clears throat)
The pallid beach mouse
can give birth every four weeks.
Assuming we start
with two mice,
and that the size
of an average litter is 12 mice,
and that they are equally
split male to female,
how many pallid beach mice
would we have
at the end of one year?
The answer to that question
is the code.
Oh, I almost forgot.
- You have two minutes.
- (beeps)
After that,
everyone in here goes splat.
Except for me, of course.
(panting)
I'm in position.
Copy. Plug the recorder
to the transmitter.
Next, you'll connect
the transmitter to the radio.
There should be a black box
at the base of the antenna.
Let me know
when you get it open.
- Nygma's bomb ploy won't last forever.
- We just have to
wait for the exhaust
fans to come to
a complete stop before
you can use the gas.
What are you doing?
(grunting and groaning)
(both grunting)
(both groaning)
You want to take responsibility
for people dying?
Look around.
This is all on you.
What the hell does that mean?
Walker spent months
trying to convince
her superiors that Gotham
was overrun by criminals.
We were this close
to being sent in
when you set up Haven.
The fact that
one man was able
to safely house
and rescue hundreds
of innocent civilians
showed the military higher-ups
that the criminal element
of Gotham
must not be so big
and scary after all.
They were ready
to send in relief,
so it had to come down.
Why? What the hell
does she want?
They were innocent
people, children.
They were an acceptable loss
for the mission.
What mission, damn it?
(laughs)
That's enough.
(grunts)
Take her out back and shoot her.
He doesn't need to see this.
It's my gift to you,
a small mercy.
You never should have
brought her into this, Eduardo.
(groans)
Can we speed things along,
please, Mr. Fox?
The exhaust fans
have to wind down
before they can
change directions.
If you throw the canisters in
now, the gas will blow outside.
Bruce, status?
One second.
I'm here. The box is open.
LUCIUS: Two dark green wires
right in front.
Attach those to the transmitter.
The message will send.
(whirring, beeping)
It's done.
One minute left.
Everybody hear that?
One minute before
this thing explodes.
I know the answer.
Uh... (chuckles) Nope,
don't think you do, Bullock.
My high school zoology class is
still rattling around up here.
High school was
a long time ago,
so let's just take
the full minute, shall we?
Really think about it.
I don't need to.
The pallid beach mouse
is extinct.
It disappeared
in 1959.
The number you'll have at
the end of the year is zero.
The number is zero.
Trust me on this.
I got in trouble. I had to
write an essay about it.
I swear to God.
Oh, dear.
(indistinct chatter)
(groans)
I got a math problem for you.
- Count these bullets.
- (inhales)
Yes!
- (grunts)
- You want to know why
Ramirez and the rest
didn't make it out?
After your tour
of duty was up,
we were caught
behind enemy lines,
taken to the darkest
hell on Earth...
Peña Duro.
Have you heard of it?
Prison? I didn't know.
No one did,
'cause it's where we were
left to die by our government.
I was the only one
that survived.
Walker...
Walker, she found me
in that place.
She pulled me out.
She gave me a
new purpose.
She made you her killer.
No, no, Jim.
She's the killer.
And you have no idea.
- (gunshots)
- Lee?
You and your stupid revenge.
The diamond isn't even worth
anything in Gotham anyway.
Unless...
The diamond is worth
something on the mainland.
And I bet you have
way more where that came from.
You're leaving Gotham.
Congratulations,
you're a genius.
Why?
"Alexander the Great
"then looked upon his land
"and wept.
For there was nothing left
to conquer."
I've done all I can in Gotham.
Some things twice.
(chuckles lightly)
There's nothing left
for me here anymore.
I want in.
I can't even walk
around the city
without some lowlife
trying to take me out.
Just so he can
up his cred.
I don't want to be the person
who killed Jeremiah Valeska.
I just want to be myself.
And I can't do that
in Gotham anymore.
My heart weeps for you.
But no.
- What if I could get us out of here?
- (Oswald laughs)
You do that, I will cut you in.
50-50.
Ten percent,
and I won't murder you
- once we reach the mainland.
- Deal.
Selina, wait!
She said, "Anything in the room
could be a bomb."
Not the room itself.
Did you know that
the whole time?
Just thought of it.
We should hurry before
she gets away with
all our stuff.
Don't worry.
She won't get far.
Alvarez, take Lee
to my office.
Be right there.
I got to be honest
with you, man.
I don't know how many more
of these close calls
this old heart can take.
We were able to transmit
the audio logs,
but until I hear back
from my contacts,
I won't know
if they received them.
Well, if they did,
probably have
a lot of questions.
We'll spend the night
and help out.
Alfred, can you go back to the
apartment and grab what you can?
Certainly,
Master Bruce.
Thanks, Bruce.
The next time I
get a short straw,
I'm just gonna
walk into traffic.
Where has Lee been
this whole time?
I don't know.
I'm not gonna
wait around
to watch their
touching reunion.
What is happening here?
I don't know where to start.
When I didn't hear from you,
I'd hoped you'd
gotten out of Gotham.
The last thing
that I remember
is Jeremiah destroying
the bridges.
That was over
three months ago.
Three months?
Oh, my God.
You don't remember anything?
I'm trying, and...
Right before the bridges
came down,
you said you were
leaving the city.
Why didn't you?
I don't know, Jim.
None of this
is making any sense.
We're still cut off.
There's no help.
It's been hard.
Actually, that's not true.
It's been hell.
People needed hope,
so I put on a
brave face.
Pretended I knew
what to do.
But you know me, Lee.
I'm just a cop.
And now I'm really lost.
Hey, it's okay.
(distant siren)
We're here now.
We'll just try to put
the pieces back together again.
Maybe we can help each other.
Let's start with my memory.
I went back
to the Narrows.
I saw Ed.
We fought. We...
Oh.
He stabbed me.
- What?
- Wait, let me remember.
I stabbed him.
There was
so much blood.
Then I was... (exhales)
somewhere...
A hospital, maybe?
- (scoffs)
- (man groans)
Eduardo. (clicks tongue)
So much potential,
but not quite up
to the task.
- (beeping)
- Walker.
(case opens)
How?
We've been burned.
The press have
recordings of me
instructing Nygma
to take down Haven.
I thought I might
accomplish my task
without setting foot
in this foul city,
but that's not to be.
- You won't die yet, my warrior.
- (groaning)
There is so much more
for you to do.
Professor Strange will have you
fixed up in no time.
(device beeps, clicks)
(respirator powers up)
(sharp inhale)
(distorted):
Jim Gordon.
Don't worry
about Gordon.
Nygma was never alone.
There was a
second operative.
(sharp inhale)
You okay?
You cold?
(brief whir)
The hospitals were
all out of commission.
Just the one clinic
in the green zone.
Lee?
Time to die, Jim Gordon.
(Jim grunting)
(both grunting)
- (electricity crackles)
- (exhales)
(owls hooting)
(faint clanging)
(leaves rustling)
♪♪
- (grunts, groans)
- Ah...
(thud)
Wanted: one butler.
Military background a plus.
References required.
Yes, Mr. Pennyworth.
I have a job for you.
(distant foghorn)
(rapid gasping)
SELINA: Well, you weren't
lying when you said
she wouldn't get far.
(dog panting)
Pretty crown's...
(chuckles) booby-trapped.
Ouch.
Ouch, indeed.
I couldn't have you
coming back here
and making off with
all of my belongings.
Our belongings.
Cut my wings, let me go?
Bang, bang.
- What the hell?
- (dog whines)
The buckshot in her gut
wasn't enough punishment?
Just a little reminder
of what happens
when people try
to steal from me.
(shuddering breath)
Good to know.
Partner.
(sirens wailing)
BULLOCK:
So Lee has a chip, too?
GORDON: I don't know how,
but it seems that way.
Walker must have
been holding onto her
as some sort of
plan B this whole time.
Three months? That's a hell
of a long game she's playing.
Which means she probably has
other tricks up her sleeve.
(moans)
Hey.
(grunts)
- Welcome back.
- Oh, hell.
This is gonna keep happening.
What's wrong with me?
The good news is, I think
I can actually answer that.
- (exhales)
- (door opens)
BARBARA:
Jim.
I need to talk to you.
Now is not a good
time, Barbara.
Don't you remember the good time
we had the other night?
- Over there?
- Say what?
You need to leave now.
I'm pregnant.
Good to see you, Lee.
Long time.
Congratulations?
(buoy bell dinging)
(labored breathing)
You.
You're supposed
to be dead, mate.
Sorry to disappoint.
You hurt my boy...
and I will bite your face off.
(manic giggling)
(laughing):
Yeah. Yeah.
Ah... Bruce will be
along shortly.
In the meantime...
This place is in desperate need
of some good, old-fashioned
butlering.
How did you even find a way off
the bloody island anyway?
How? One if by land,
two if by sea,
three if by digging
a tunnel under the river.
But enough questions.
Today is the big day.