Previously onGotham...
Who were those people you
were speaking with?
You keep your nose
out of my business.
Come now, Butch, play nice.
If a person comes into contact
with my blood, it changes them.
My brother, if he gets in your mind,
you're doomed.
Goodbye, Mr. Gordon.
- Ivy's missing...
- She'll turn up somewhere.
This time she fell, it was a long way
down into water.
Then maybe she survived.
- What's your name?
- My name's Ivy.
Barnes asked me to put you
on a 48 hour suicide watch.
- I've already signed off on it.
- He just cost you the election.
Give me one reason why I shouldn't
let Butch kill you where you stand.
There's that.
Oswald Cobblepot,
has won the mayor's office by...
I believe in you, Oswald.
You never believed I could win
this election on my own.
Maybe you're not cut out
for this after all.
- What?
- Jervis. Let her go now.
- No! I'll never go with you!
- No!
You killed her!
I would like to introduce
you to my Chief of Staff.
Mr. Edward Nygma.
Welcoming our new Mayor of Gotham,
Mayor Oswald Cobblepot.
"Building Gotham Safe Again."
Welcoming our new Mayor of Gotham,
Mayor Oswald Cobblepot.
"Building Gotham Safe Again."
You're an angel.
Oh, thank you so much. Thank you.
There's something
I've been wanting to ask you.
Am I a good boy?
Have I made you proud?
I hope I'm not interrupting.
Ed... you never met my mother.
Wasn't she beautiful?
A fine figure of a woman.
She was my whole world.
The only one that was always
there for me.
Well, I believe the answer is yes.
She would be proud.
Do you really think so?
Oswald, look at everything
you've achieved.
The people love you.
Gangs fear you.
And tomorrow night the crème
of Gotham will be gathering
to celebrate, you.
What more could someone ask for?
Someone to share it with.
My mother was the daughter
of immigrants.
A humble cook.
We did not have much,
but when she was by my side
I felt loved. Protected.
As promised, I have rid Gotham
of its villainous monsters.
With my mother as my witness,
I vow to you from this day forward,
every man, woman, and child in
our great city will be safe!
Spread out!
No one is safe. Not from us. Drop it.
Put it down!
You will pay for this! Dearly!
Now... now... Mr. Mayor.
Don't go losing your head.
Have a nice day!
I can't come over tonight.
Okay.
I mean, that'd be three nights
in a row.
That'd almost make it a thing.
Yeah. The neighbors might talk.
Exactly.
And I have a dinner.
It's not a date.
None of my business.
So, whatever happened with Tetch?
I told you.
He broke his sister out of the GCPD.
Bullock and I chased him down.
She died. He escaped.
'Cause I heard a rumor there's
something strange about her blood.
Do you like this?
I think I've made that pretty clear.
- Then why are you pressing?
- Because I want to know.
And are you asking as a reporter
or as yourself?
- Is there a difference?
- There should be.
When you were a cop, did you stop
being one when you came home?
Maybe that was my problem.
The guy I'm having dinner
with is a hematologist
in charge of analyzing
Alice Tetch's blood.
I'm free after 10.00
if you wanna call.
Thanks for the coffee.
We found the truck.
They ditched it in The Narrows.
We've got forensics going over it,
and teams doing a ten block sweep.
We already found this.
The Red Hood Gang.
I thought those idiots were dead.
My guess is they're copying the look.
The original Red Hood Gang
were bank robbers.
Whoever they are, they got
a beef with Penguin.
Expand the search to 15 blocks.
Everything goes through you.
You mean through me.
Wow.
It is good to be back.
I have missed all of you.
Harvey, still a stranger
to a haircut and a shave, I see.
What are you doing here, Nygma?
As Mayor Cobblepot's chief of staff,
I'm gonna be your liaison
on the Red Hood investigation.
I wanna see all reports.
And I'm going to need access
to your forensic lab.
You think I'm gonna just let you
waltz into my precinct?
You're a cop killer who should be
in the looney bin.
- I'll be damned...
- You'll be fired.
The mayor can't fire me.
No, but he can appoint
a police commissioner who will.
So, you will carry out the mayor's
orders, without question,
or the GCPD has a new captain.
How does that sound?
Every dog has his day, Nygma.
Enjoy yours.
And where is our lord mayor?
Hiding under his desk?
He's meeting with constituents.
Anything for you,
my little Cobblepot.
You can count on me.
Those were the words my mother
used to whisper to me
every night before I fell asleep.
She was a saint.
Yes, a saint whose only desire
was to love me.
And what was her thanks?
Not only did she take a knife
in the back
but even in her death, her
memory is being desecrated.
Seriously?
This is the reason we're here?
Little glue. Some paint.
Momma will be good as new, huh?
No! That is not the reason
you are here.
The Red Hoods have challenged
my authority.
They will be made an example of.
Tonight, I am celebrating
my historic victory...
At The Sirens.
It's gonna be fabulous.
None of you are invited.
I want them found and their leader's
head brought to me on a spike
before nightfall.
What're you waiting for? Find them!
All right. Five card draw, gentlemen.
Someone didn't ante up.
Come on, you cheap bastards.
How long are we supposed to wait?
Long as it takes the boss-man
to get here.
You need a lookout.
Oh, relax, fellas.
Hey, you want us to deal you in,
boss?
We don't have time for games, boys.
We got work to do.
Hello, Jim.
Is it a bad time? I should've called.
No.
Please. Come in.
Right. Can I get you something
to drink?
- A glass of water?
- I'm fine.
I heard you were back.
I've been meaning to come see you.
Everything okay?
Yes. Alfred and I are both well.
I hear you're
a private investigator now.
I'd like to hire you.
Bruce, if this is about corruption
at Wayne Enterprises...
It's not. I've put my investigation
into my father's company aside.
It's time I moved on.
Why the sudden change of heart?
It's far from sudden.
I've given it a great deal
of thought.
I can't live my life
if I keep looking back.
For what it's worth,
I think that's wise.
So what can I do for you?
Ivy Pepper's gone missing.
I didn't realize you two were close.
We're not.
She's a friend of Selina's.
And does Selina know
you're doing this?
No. I don't want to get her hopes
up if you don't find anything.
We'll start with the GCPD.
See where we go from there.
And I think it's chivalrous
you doing this for Selina.
How long have you two been a thing?
Oh, no... no... no.
Selina's a friend. That's all.
- Yeah.
- No. Really. She's just a friend.
Yeah. Yeah.
Mr. Fox, just the man
I've been wanting to see.
Oh, joy. Mr. Nygma.
Heard you were stopping by.
I have questions.
- Hopefully, you have answers.
- Or what?
You'll poison me with gas?
That gas was a sleeping agent.
And, to be fair, I was not
in the best place in my life.
To be fair... if you ever threaten
my life,
or the life of Bruce Wayne
again, I will find a way to end you.
Mr. Fox, we both know you're
not a man of violence.
No, I'm not.
If I was, I would have laced
some piece of lab equipment,
one which you were sure to touch,
with a toxin.
Ricin, maybe.
I'd use Saxitoxin. Harder to trace.
But I like your style.
You are insane.
Was insane. I have a certificate.
So, the Red Hoods?
See for yourself.
The gang's getaway vehicle
was abandoned in The Narrows.
As you'll notice, its carpet fibers
has elements of dirt, oil,
and, oddly, potassium chloride.
A halide salt.
Fascinating.
So nothing on Ivy Pepper.
But an odd report came
in a few weeks ago,
okay, a construction worker claimed
that a redhead knocked
him out, robbed him.
- And she left this.
- That's Ivy's sweater.
- How do we find this man?
- I already called.
All right, the guy's down
South on a job.
But he swore up and down
that the redhead who rolled him
was in her 20's.
So? He's probably covering
for being with a young girl.
Doubtful he would come forward
in the first place.
Yeah. Most pervs don't wanna
call attention to themselves.
- So it wasn't Ivy.
- Seems unlikely.
But why would
she have Ivy's sweater?
Doctor Thompkins.
Bruce. It's good to see you again.
You got taller.
Like I said, right?
The kid's growing like a weed.
- Nice to see you, too.
- Oh, Jim, could I have a word?
I wanted you to hear it from me.
Oh, my engagement
announcement is coming out
in the Gazette tomorrow.
And it will feature Mario's name.
I think that's customary.
His family name.
You mean Falcone.
You knew?
- You knew, you didn't say anything?
- Sure I did.
I said congratulations.
- Don't be cute.
- Lee. People talk.
Was I surprised? Sure.
But it's also none of my business.
Your life is your life.
And I meant what I said.
Very happy for you.
So, that's it?
That's it.
Okay. Oh, well, I just
wanted to tell you.
Doctor Thompkins.
I had heard that you were back.
I'm so glad...
- That's for Kristen.
- You shouldn't have done that.
Or what? I'm supposed to be
scared of you
because you work for Penguin?
My fiancé's father
is Carmine Falcone.
I so much as whisper to him,
and you disappear.
Tell the mayor, whatever
I can do as M.E.
I'm happy to help.
It's bad enough we're throwing
Penguin's party.
It's good for the club.
Now we're his errand girls?
Sweetie, we find the Red Hoods,
he'll owe us.
We can ask for a favor.
Say, him not killing you?
Well, it would be nice not to have
to watch my ass all the time.
Well... well. Who do we have here?
Guy calls himself
The Ballistic Bomber.
My contact at The Merc saw him
buying smoke grenades last week.
Just like the ones the Red Hood
used on Penguin.
Groovy. Reckon he'll talk?
'Course.
Maybe give him a moment.
Now, remember, kids,
you tell the press
this is all Penguin's fault.
No, please!
- Please leave me!
- Good.
- Light it up!
- Yes, sir.
- No, have mercy.
- Please. Don't. No!
Better run, Sister.
Before the Padre goes boom!
No! Jesus! No!
Don't. Hey, hey.
The grenade, it's slipping.
Seriously? The Priest?
You should've seen it.
Ka-boom!
But you told them what to say?
- This is all because of Penguin?
- Yeah, boss.
But I don't get it, you wanna take
out Penguin, let's take him out.
This Red Hood stuff is fun,
but it's a lot of work.
How about you just do
what I tell you.
Now, I got you these, so you'll
blend in at the party tonight.
Huh? Huh?
Nice suit!
And that's when we kill him?
No! No one kills Penguin!
You should.
'Cause he's gonna murder you!
Time to have a heart to heart, Butch.
Alone.
You don't have to buy lunch.
I know you're a billionaire.
But I can buy you a sandwich.
Do you miss it?
Being a cop?
Sometimes. Yeah.
- It gave a sense of mission.
- True.
There's more to life
than having a mission.
Look, I'll keep asking
around about Ivy.
But you want my advice,
talk to Selina.
Tell her how you feel.
Does that actually work?
Sometimes.
It's definitely better than
being silent.
Before you know it,
the moment passes.
And are you taking your own advice?
I'm afraid that ship has sailed.
I'm not talking
about Doctor Thompkins.
I'm talking about the woman
you're seeing now.
Excuse me?
There was lipstick on a coffee mug
on your table.
You've become quite the detective.
So are you?
- It is complicated.
- So is Selina.
That I believe.
I just wish sometimes I had a sign.
Unfortunately, life doesn't usually
work that way.
We're hours away
from Mayor Cobblepot's
victory celebration.
But people are asking,
will the Red Hood Gang
put a damper on the festivities?
Mayor Cobblepot...
Sounds like Penguin's
having a bad day.
I'm supposed to go to his party
tonight.
Part of my re-engagement
with being a Wayne.
Well, give the mayor my best.
Witnesses say the Red Hoods blamed
Cobblepot for their act.
Someone is testing me, Ed.
They're thinking, he's mayor now.
He has to play by different rules.
No, they'll see, when I'm roasting
their entrails over a fire.
Perhaps, I'm thinking
about this all wrong.
Perhaps, this is not
about you at all.
What if this is about the statue?
Of course, it's about me!
Yes, you're probably right. Oh, dear.
- Wonderful.
- Oswald. Take a breath.
What are you doing?
It's an old trick I learned
in the lab.
Most solvents have as their base...
I am the son of water,
but if water touches me, I die.
- What am I?
- Again with the riddles?
Salt. Most people think
of it as a food additive.
But potassium salt
is found in detergents, soaps...
What is your point, Ed?
I know where the Red Hoods are.
I say we give him to Penguin.
Knowing Penguin
will gut him like a fish?
Ladies. Come on.
- After all we've been through...
- It's his life for yours. Simple.
I don't get it.
Why'd you turn on him now?
I wasn't gonna hurt Penguin.
Honest, I was gonna take down
the Red Hoods myself.
Tonight. At the party.
All this so you could play the hero?
Ever since Nygma got out of Arkham,
Penguin treats me like I'm nothing.
That pencil-neck's
trying to push me out.
Let me ask you, we figured out you're
the man behind the Red Hoods,
how long do you think it'll take
Penguin and his lap dog?
It's your life, baby.
You make the call.
Let me see this through.
I get my place beside Penguin back,
I'll protect you.
Oh, you'll do more than that.
You'll owe me.
And one day, I'm gonna collect.
- Gilzean.
- Butch. Where are you?
The Red Hood Gang is at a
detergent factory in The Narrows.
We're on our way.
I gotta go.
Get your things. We're done.
I'm breaking up the band.
I'm serious. Go. Get out of Dodge.
Yeah, well, not for nothing,
but you promised us a payday.
We're not leaving till we get it.
Well, guess it was gonna happen
sooner or later.
What?
Sorry, boys.
I did it, boss.
I got them for you.
Peace and order have once again
been restored to Gotham.
The Red Hood Gang is no more.
My very own man, Butch Gilzean,
risked life and limb to face down
the bandits.
Mr. Gilzean...
Was your life ever in danger, Butch?
I can honestly say that if I'd
had hesitated, I'd been a goner.
All right, people, listen up.
It's happy hour.
Finish up those reports
and let's call it a day.
Hey, Ed.
Even before you went crazy,
I never liked you.
Your zipper's down.
Listen, Butch did us all a favor.
Red Hoods go bye-bye. Case closed.
Look at the way the bodies fell.
As if they were just standing
there waiting to be killed.
Butch comes all the way in the room.
But only one man pulled out a gun.
I guess they weren't threatened.
By a 300lbs gorilla?
Whose side are you on anyway?
No one's losing sleep over
a bunch of dead crooks.
Least of all, me.
I said wrap it up!
What have we here...
Burning the midnight oil?
Oh, just finishing up.
I'm guessing you're here
to reprimand me.
Reprimand you? For what?
Punching Nygma in the jaw.
I just couldn't help myself.
First I'm hearing of it.
Well done, Doctor.
Actually, I'm here to ask about,
Alice Tetch's blood.
If you've heard anything.
As it happens, I just received
the preliminary results
back from the lab.
- Fascinating.
- What is?
They injected samples
into a group of rats.
After three days, two of the rats
were showing marked increases
- in strength and stamina.
- Well, that doesn't sound so bad.
But the study ended after one
of the rats killed all the others.
I'm guessing that's not normal.
It chewed through a dozen
wire cages to get at them. No.
Why would one of the rats go psycho
and not the others?
Perhaps the others hadn't had
a chance to show any symptoms.
Or they were immune.
Sometimes people live
with a disease for years
without any adverse effects.
The lab is starting a new study now.
Well, keep me informed.
Oh! And, don't stay too late.
I'm sure that fiancé of yours would
like to see you once in a while.
And was the captain
of the GCPD invited
to our new mayor's victory party?
You know, I lost my invitation.
I can feel it...
Looking for Oswald...
Walking down the street.
Kicking cans...
Heard you took down
the Red Hood Gang,
single handed.
So to speak.
- Very funny.
- Don't forget. You owe me.
I know.
How long do we have to stay?
As long as it takes for you to be
seen in the world, Master Bruce.
Being Bruce Wayne.
And smiling.
So this is our life now?
Fake smiles and mingling.
I miss the old days.
So do I.
- It's so nice.
- Oh! Excuse me.
Bruce. Mr. Pennyworth.
I'm so pleased you made it.
Yeah, well, you know, we're trying
to get out a bit more, Mister Mayor.
Oh. Oswald, please.
We never got the chance to thank you
for saving our lives
from the ex-Mayor.
- That was nothing.
- Not at all.
I found it very fortuitous
you turned up when you did
with that bazooka.
I just felt a bit sorry for Stan,
the gardener,
'cause he was picking up
bits of Galavan for weeks.
And now here you are the new Mayor.
Sometimes life has a way
of working out.
Yes. That's true.
What is it, Master Bruce?
A sign.
Please excuse me.
All right, well, I'll just go
and wet my beak.
Congratulations again, Mister Mayor.
I... I... I knew that I'm onto you
I've got my plans
And they needn't you
- Nothing you can say to me
- Hey!
Hey, yourself.
Funny. I never realized
how short you are.
Who the hell are you?
Not yet.
This is too fun.
Run along, little kitty.
Go steal some more wallets.
Hey.
So sweet.
There he is, the man of the hour.
I have a surprise for you, Butch.
Not in the mood.
What's in the box?
Open it.
Thanks, already got one.
Oh. Of course you do.
And you certainly wouldn't
need this one as
it's so similar to your very own
pocket square.
This is from
the Red Hood crime scene.
It turns out that your suit and the
Red Hood suits were all made
by the same tailor, Mr. Fuji.
That's some coincidence.
I thought so myself,
which is why I called Mr. Fuji.
And he said that a large man
with a metal hand,
not many of those running around,
bought all six of the suits.
Which means, ta-dah!
You're the architect
of the Red Hood...
I should snap your neck right now.
You haven't heard my offer.
We kill Penguin together.
What're you talking about?
- You're his guy.
- Oh, please. You fell for that act?
Yes. He broke me out of Arkham.
Very appreciative.
But I was not cut out
to be number two.
I've simply been waiting
for my moment.
Which you have graciously provided.
How would you like to run
Gotham with me?
The two of us? Working together?
You have proven yourself far more
cunning than I imagined.
Now I assume this little drama of
yours was meant to climax tonight.
So, put on the hood.
Kill Penguin.
I'll help you escape.
Tomorrow, we divide up the city.
You'd really turn on him?
After all he did for you?
- Mister P.
- In a heartbeat.
- No.
- Okay.
Then I guess it's time
for surprise number two.
You got to Zsasz?
I got to Zsasz.
And he got to Tabitha.
Penguin's history.
Question is, are you?
Can I see your invitation?
- What're you doing here?
- I was invited.
Course you were.
You recognize her?
Should I?
I don't know.
- Hey. Are you, you?
- I'm me.
Well, I'm working, so...
Actually, there was something
I... I wanted to tell you.
Could we go somewhere more private?
Fine. But make it quick.
Can't believe you turned on
Oswald too.
Oh, hello. Pot-kettle-black.
No. It's not the same thing. You...
never mind.
I swear, your goons hurt
Tabitha, so help me...
Just. Do. Your job.
Showtime.
Put one in the Mayor,
before I put one in Tabitha.
Ladies, gentlemen.
Welcome to The Sirens.
Tonight we're here to celebrate
the honorable Mayor Cobblepot.
Our savior from the monsters,
and the captain of our fair city.
And now the mayor would
like to say a few words.
Ed, where've you been?
I've been looking
for you all evening.
Oh, just tying up loose ends.
I just wanted to say good luck.
Okay. Thank you.
Tonight is a celebration,
not of my victory, but of Gotham's.
This is a new day!
I wouldn't celebrate yet,
Mister Mayor.
Red Hoods ain't finished yet.
- Ed! What are you doing?
- Wait!
Sorry, boss.
Butch!
- Huh?
- Oops.
The Mayor.
Our Mayor.
Vowed that all of the
Red Hood would be destroyed.
And now we have
the real leader caught.
Red handed.
You really thought
I'd give you real bullets.
You are an idiot.
I will kill you for this!
Sounds like we're missing
all the fun.
Got plenty of fun left for you.
You know, if you're gonna take
a girl hostage in her own place,
you might wanna search it first.
After all that I've done for you!
I gave you a job!
I gave you everything!
I used to be somebody in this town
and then you and that sniveling
little son-of-a-bitch...
Shut up!
I am shocked, and grieved...
that one of my dearest
friends has betrayed me.
But let it be known,
that Oswald Cobblepot
will prosecute anyone
who threatens Gotham.
Here. Here.
Yeah.
Upsy-daisy.
Oh, my God!
Showtime.
Oswald, move!
I am gonna enjoy this!
Best. Party. Ever.
- Wait. Not now.
- Ed!
Ed! Ed! Ed!
So, what's up?
I hired Jim Gordon to help me
locate Ivy.
And?
There was a redhead
that had her sweater.
But it wasn't Ivy.
Saying it out loud, I realize,
doesn't sound that impressive.
No. It doesn't.
That's really why you
brought me up here?
You are the real Bruce...
'cause nobody else
would be this boring.
Great work, Detective.
That's not all.
We've been friends
a long time, Selina.
And ever since you've known me,
I've been dedicated to one thing.
But that's done.
I don't know what's next.
But I know...
Would you please just say
what you mean?
I like you.
As more than a friend.
It would be nice
if you said something back.
How many girls have you dated?
What do you mean?
It's not a trick question.
- How many girls have you dated?
- None.
None.
Have you ever thought
that maybe you only like me
because I'm literally
the only girl you know?
That's not true. I feel something.
And I know you do too.
We're the same.
In what universe are we the same?
- The money doesn't matter!
- Try not having it. It matters.
There's something between us.
I know there is.
You have to see that.
Rule one... don't ever tell me
what I have to do.
So, you do have feelings for me?
- I'm confused.
- Good.
Come on, just tell me.
I got all dressed up.
I even put on lipstick.
I could lose my job.
What are you offering?
Fine! Then I'll say something,
if I'm right, you just nod.
You ran tests on Alice Tetch's blood?
You found something in her blood.
A virus or infection or something.
Do I have to go over the rules again?
Let's have new rules, sweetie.
I'll tell you what we're doing
with Alice Tetch's blood,
and in return you...
Okay.
Excuse me? What are you doing?
Two whiskeys.
And a pineapple juice for this guy.
- What's going on?
- To go.
What's going on?
I think you were just leaving.
Forget this.
Trust me. I'm gonna try.
What're you doing here?
Just walking by.
Saw you through the window.
- Took it as a sign.
- Like hell.
You tracked me here.
And for the record,
I could've gotten what I wanted
from that creep without
compromising my honor.
I know. But you don't have to.
I'll tell you what you wanna know.
I thought you wanted to keep the
woman and the reporter separate.
- Is that an option?
- No.
Well, then.
You are gonna have to buy me
dinner, though.
What's good here?
It's ginger tea with honey.
It's my mother's remedy
for a sore throat.
You sure you don't need a doctor?
No. I'm fine.
I still don't understand why you
didn't tell me what you were doing.
Your shock when seeing Butch
had to be genuine.
The people had to believe it.
And they did. And once again,
you're the city's hero.
You were almost killed.
And you saved me. Again.
I hope you know, Oswald.
I would do anything for you.
You can always count on me.
Thank you.
Need a hand, Kitten?
I got it.
Hold on, Butch.
Sir, the ambulance carrying
Butch Gilzean was just hijacked.
Damn it! Put out a BOLO.
I'll call the Mayor.
Yes.
Mister, please.
My dear, sweet sister.
Just look at what he did to you.
He took you from me.
We belonged together.
And he killed you.
But, Mister, I'm not dead.
If only that were true.
Those who hurt you will feel my pain.
When my sweet and terrible vengeance
upon them rains.