There's a war coming.
A terrible war. There will be chaos.
Rivers of blood in the streets, I know it.
I can see it coming.
It's time. Somebody has to take over.
It might as well be me.
- My name's James Gordon. A detective.
- My name is Bruce Wayne.
I will find the man who did this.
Stop or I'll shoot!
Mario Pepper was framed
by Fish Mooney and the cops.
Why snitch on your own boss?
You want to push Fish out.
I told you this is important.
I ain't looking for no girl.
I'm looking for a weapon.
The old man has to go.
If he figures out we're working together,
we're cooked.
You're under arrest for the murder
of Oswald Chesterfield Cobblepot.
- Holy crap.
- I am Oswald Cobblepot.
You son of a bitch.
He's alive? Alive!
No.
Boss, what's wrong?
Gordon didn't kill
Penguin like he was told.
- What?
- Penguin...
...is alive and working for Maroni?
No.
You go find Gordon
and you bring him to me.
Still breathing.
I wanna talk to that son of a bitch.
Hey. Leave a message.
Barbara, if you're at home, listen to me.
I need you to get out right now.
- I thought we were friends.
- Harvey.
Shut up. Game's over.
Now I gotta kill you, take your body back
to Falcone and beg-- Beg him for mercy!
Listen to me. I screwed up.
But I have a plan to make things right.
Don't kill me. Help me.
You think I'm an idiot?
Walk away.
Help me.
- We don't have to go out like this.
- You better hope you never see me again.
Wow.
What a place, huh?
A beautiful home...
...for a beautiful lady.
Please tell me what you want.
I guess there's no harm in the truth.
See, your boyfriend was supposed to kill a
certain person for somebody, only he didn't.
And now that somebody is real mad. Heh.
- Cobblepot.
- What?
He didn't kill Cobblepot.
There you go!
You're hip.
You are hip.
That Jim Gordon
is one lucky son of a gun.
What, are you like 100 pounds?
One-ten?
I bet that's your real hair color too.
What are you gonna do to Jim?
You ever been with a criminal?
Some ladies find it a turn-on.
- Jim.
- Hey.
Speak of the devil.
I was getting to know your lady.
You're trespassing. Get out.
Slow down. You're misreading
the situation. I'm the shot-caller here.
You've been told to bring me in alive or I'd
be dead. I'm happy to kill you right here.
Don't be such a hard ass.
Come on, you know the rules.
You play nice. You take your lumps.
Nobody else gets hurt.
Tell your friend to drop his gun
or I'll blow his brains out.
- Oh, my God. Jim.
- It's under control.
Drop your gun.
Okay. Have it your way.
But now, after we kill you,
we're gonna kill blondie too.
Nice and slow.
We've gotta go. Right now.
Barbara.
Westbound interstate
express departs in five minutes, Bay 12.
Barbara.
- What?
- Listen.
No. No.
- Just a couple of days and I'll join you.
- No.
There are things I need to do.
Fine. Then if you stay, I stay. Okay?
Because I love you, Jim. I cannot leave you.
I love you too.
That's why you need to leave.
If I know you're safe,
there is nothing they can do to me.
I'll make things right.
And then I'll come join you.
And what if you don't?
Don't come back.
Don't come back to Gotham.
No, Jim.
Gordon's here. He's nuts.
What's he doing?
You believe this guy?
Hey, Alvarez.
You got any of those blank warrants
that Judge Barn Barn signed?
Uh...
Yeah.
This cannot stand.
Gordon must die. Bullock must die.
Penguin must die. Today.
- And Maroni too, I suppose?
- If need be.
You're overreacting, my dear.
This Penguin's a nobody.
You want to start a war over the guy
that carried your umbrella?
He was on my hip everywhere with me.
He knows things.
Like what?
Too much. He knows too much.
Go to Maroni and ask him politely
to hand over your little man. Politely.
If he refuses,
we can talk about stronger measures.
Boss, this is weak response.
I hate to agree with Fish,
but we need to show strength now.
We need to hit back hard.
No talk. Penguin dead. Gordon dead. Done.
Relax, Niko. I know what I'm doing.
Where is Gordon?
You were bringing him with you.
No. He wouldn't come without a struggle.
I don't know if he's playing tough or crazy,
but he's at work like nothing's wrong.
I'll send Victor to fetch him.
No need. My guys can handle him.
I'll send Victor.
That's a nice handsome bird, huh?
I don't know chickens.
- Ugh.
- Fall back. The old man is right there.
Screw him. He's done.
Now's the time to strike.
- Not yet.
- "Not yet." "Not yet." If not now, when?
Look at him. Maroni clan are laughing
at us and he plays with chickens.
That's what has me worried.
The chickens.
He's happy, relaxed,
as if he doesn't have a care in the world.
- That girl of yours is doing her job, then.
- No.
She says he hasn't even touched her.
She cooks and she cleans for him.
- He likes to watch her do chores.
- Weird.
- But if that's his thing...
- No.
He's acting as if he knows something
important that no one else knows.
What the hell are you doing here?
I work here. It's my shift.
Where else should I be?
How about Alaska?
Arrest warrants? For who?
Mayor Aubrey James, Carmine Falcone,
and their close associates.
On charges of conspiracy and perversion
of justice in the Wayne case.
- Are you insane?
- No.
Maybe a little. Feels good.
They're gonna try and kill me anyway.
Might as well make them pay for it.
You're gonna arrest
the mayor and Don Falcone. How?
My testimony is attached to the warrants.
That's enough to indict on a dozen counts.
True. If you could execute
the warrants, which you can't.
If the DA would prosecute, which he won't.
There's not a cop or lawyer
in the city who'll help you.
There are people willing to help
once they see it's possible to fight back.
You're dreaming.
Nobody will help you. I won't help you.
You don't think I want change,
just like you do?
I have a family.
I understand.
Gordon...
...get out of town.
This is my home.
It was my father's home.
I'm not leaving.
Hello, everyone.
My name is Victor Zsasz.
I'm sent here personally
by Don Carmine Falcone himself...
...on a matter of deep concern to him,
so please be respectful.
I'm here for Jim Gordon.
Only him. Everybody else,
mind your business and we're cool.
So where's Jim at?
Thank you.
Hey, Jim!
Jim.
Hi, Jim.
Relax. I'm supposed to take you in alive.
Don Falcone wants to talk.
Tell Falcone we'll talk, but not today.
Don't be that way.
Alive is a very broad category.
A man with no hands can still be alive.
There are 50 cops in here. Try something.
Everybody out.
Please!
Go, boss. Get out of here.
- Jim--
- Go.
I can handle this.
Well, how now, Jim?
Jim?
Why are you hiding from me, Jim?
Hey! What the--?
There.
You need a ride?
Go. Go. Go.
No. Please.
Twenty-eight.
Ah. You're back.
How do you feel?
Terrible.
Where am I? Who are you?
I'm a friend of Montoya and Allen.
I took two bullets out of you, sewed you up.
Now I'm checking to see how you're doing.
So who are you? What city are we in?
And what day of the week is it?
I'm James Gordon. We're in Gotham.
It's Friday. Why are there rats?
It's the dissection lab at the university.
I gather you're a fugitive from the mob.
"Can't go to the hospital," said Crispus.
Very exciting, I must say.
- How long have I been out?
- Just a couple of hours or so.
You're very lucky no vital organs were--
Whoa. Lie back down.
Okay, you were hurt.
Just a week or so in bed--
- No, I have to go.
- James, you have lost a lot of blood.
You have to do as I say and lie back down.
If you don't, you could die.
I have to stand. Can you help me?
Okay. Okay. Crispus.
- He said he's leaving already.
- I have to go. Now.
Sure.
Some clothes would be good though.
This is about tradition. Values.
Snitches get stitches.
That's how it's always been.
You need to hand him over, Sal.
I know. I should.
But what can I say?
- The little guy amuses me.
- Heh.
Don Falcone is going to be very unhappy.
You wanna start a war over this punk?
War? Whoa.
- He's that important to you, is he?
- Oh, no.
He means nothing to us.
Respect is what matters here.
Respect, I understand.
Penguin, come on out here.
Don't be scared. She won't bite.
You won't bite him, will you?
Hello, Penguin.
Hello, Ms. Mooney.
Penguin, Ms. Mooney
and her boss, Mr. Falcone...
...feel disrespected by you.
Oh, dear.
That certainly has never been my intention.
Well, respect is very important to them.
Now, I want a sincere apology
from you for making them feel that way.
Oh. Gosh, of course.
If I've, in any way, caused anyone
to feel a lack of respect, I apologize.
Sincerely.
There you go. Can't say fairer than that.
Bloodshed then. I'm glad.
Jolly fat men are so tiresome.
And you.
You little scaly-faced bitch.
Oh.
What I'm gonna do to you.
Torture's far too nice of a word.
I'm sorry you feel that way, Fish.
Ungh!
Only my friends call me Fish.
Hey, Sisters.
How's it hanging?
Holy--!
Tell your boss Falcone won't let any
of Maroni's trucks over the bridge.
Not till he gives up Penguin.
Listen, you gotta get hurt a little.
- You want a beating or a bullet?
- Why we gotta get hurt?
Because we're sending a message
this is a serious issue.
We'll tell him it's serious.
No problem.
Eh, you know what?
How did they find out
about the gun truck, huh?
That's 3 mil per week, right there.
Son of a bitch!
Four and a half mil per, gross. Cash.
A very aggressive move, isn't it?
An overreaction. They want to scare you.
You think that they think
that Don Maroni can be scared?
Of course you're right, no.
But why then would they
react so ferociously?
- Why do they want me back so badly?
- I know why.
Because they know I got
a stone money-maker here.
A golden goose. They know it and they
don't want us to have him. Right, Penguin?
Honk, honk. Heh, heh.
- What?
- Honk, honk.
- It's what geese say.
- Right, right. Honk, honk.
So fine. He's a goose. Maybe we can
negotiate a price. Pay him off.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Caution is wise.
The Falcone clan still is number one.
Paying them off is the safe thing to do.
Screw safe.
They wanna push me?
They think I'm gonna fold?
I'll push right back. Harder.
Hit them where it hurts. Today.
You know best.
If that's how you wanna play it...
...I think I know just
the spot to hit them.
I owe you an apology.
You were telling the truth
and I wouldn't believe you.
Maybe my personal feelings towards
Barbara got tangled up in there.
- That was wrong.
- Forget it.
Anyhow, I'm sorry for misjudging you and
I'm glad that we're on the same side now.
Yeah, me too.
So Barbara's safe though?
You sure she's safe?
I'm sure.
Unh! Agh.
Gordon, is that you?
It's all right, Alfred. He's a friend.
We couldn't risk a direct approach.
People are looking for me.
- All right.
- Agh!
Sorry about that, mate.
Can't be too careful.
In a spot of bother, are we, sir?
Renee Montoya and Crispus Allen.
- Pleased to meet you.
- Bruce.
I promised I would find
your parents' killer.
I'm not sure I'm gonna be able
to keep that promise.
It's a long story,
but I'm kind of in a tight spot.
I've upset some powerful people.
Stop treating me like a child.
- Explain.
- You are a child. You don't need to know--
You expect to die!
I'd like to know why.
Is it connected to my parents' murder?
Yes. It's all connected.
Somehow.
Bruce.
I will do my best to work
this thing out, but if I don't...
...Montoya and Allen here
will take over your parents' case.
I've told them everything I know.
You can trust them, 100 percent.
One hundred percent.
Bruce, these are good detectives.
If anyone can find the truth, it's them.
Thank you.
Sir, what can we do to help you now?
Nothing.
From here on in, I have to go it alone.
I don't want anyone else caught up in this.
- I have to go.
- You can hardly walk.
I'll be fine.
This way.
Not much further.
It's there.
Told you. Easy as pie.
There must be a million
dollars' worth here.
Yeah, you told us, all right.
You're clever.
You're very clever.
I sense a sarcastic
and hostile edge to your tone.
Hostile?
You got that right.
You ain't no golden goose. You're a yellow
rat snitch and you got Maroni all twisted.
I'm so glad
we're finally clearing the air, at last.
That's it. Act smart, okay?
Because all I gotta do right now
is put a bullet in your brain right here:
bang.
See, then I go back and I tell the boss...
...that one of Nike's men shot you.
Gee, that's too bad. End of story.
Yes, that's clever enough.
I never doubted your intelligence.
That's not your problem.
Oh, I got a problem, huh?
I got a problem.
No. You got a problem.
What's my problem, shmo?
What drives you?
What's your passion?
When you know what a man loves,
you know what can kill him.
Do you believe this guy?
For you, it's money.
You love money.
More than power and respect.
You're a skinflint, Mr. Carbone.
A cheapskate.
What are you guys 'May-mg an
Let me gm!
- Sorry, Frankie.
- What?
- As I say, a Cheapskate.
- Hey, come on!
And consequently,
you don't pay your people enough.
Oh, no. You don't want to do this.
- It is a sad fact...
- Stop, you don't want to do this.
- ...that there is no loyalty among thieves.
- No, no. No!
The simple offer of a substantial pay raise
is all it took to sway these fine men.
So you see, that's your problem.
Your greatest passion
becomes your greatest weakness.
Love...
...Mr. Carbone.
Love conquers all.
Shh.
My friend.
My good friend, today is a sad day.
Nikolai was like a son to me.
Just as Frankie was a son to you.
We've both lost precious family members.
- My condolences to you.
- And mine to you.
I want this violence to stop.
Business is good.
The Arkham Project is a gold mine.
Wayne Enterprises is back in play.
Life is good for all of us. Why risk
all of that to go to war over trifles?
Your little man there is
obviously very valuable to you.
We'll let you have him, unharmed.
Our gift to you.
And as a show of mutual respect,
you give us something in return.
Like such as what?
How about real estate?
One of your warehouses
on the river, maybe.
That's not gonna work.
I mean, I like this fella, but we're
talking about a warehouse on the river.
Yeah.
Indian Hill. I'll give you Indian Hill.
I'm not familiar with the name.
It's in Arkham. It's a toxic waste dump
on an Indian burial ground. It's worthless.
Oh. Nothing is worthless.
Even nothing is worth something.
We'll take it.
As a token of our mutual respect, yes?
You got it, my friend.
It's all love. Heh, heh.
It's a pleasure seeing you all.
Um, I heard Vic Zsasz tore up
the G.C.P.D. tracking down Gordon.
Did you catch him yet?
We're working on it.
Well, good luck with that. There's nothing
more dangerous than an honest man, huh?
Jimbo, it's me. Open up.
- Hey.
- Don't worry. I'm not gonna kill you.
I should, but I ain't.
Glad to hear it.
You figured you'd go
to the last place they'd look...
...because it'd be the first place they'd reject
as being too obvious. Sorry, I'm being rude.
This is the Duchess of Devonshire.
Duchess, Jim Gordon, putz.
- Marsha. Hi.
- Hi.
Baby, why don't you explore a little bit?
Find the bedroom.
Put on your birthday suit
and I'll find you in a jiffy, okay?
So I've been thinking,
you're still a douche bag.
But you have the moral high ground. So
I'm gonna back your play, whatever it is.
I figure I'm doomed anyhow.
I might as well join the good guys.
Thank you.
So, what is your play?
You got one, right? You said you did.
Tomorrow morning, I'm arresting Falcone
and the mayor for framing Mario Pepper.
For conspiracy, P.O.J., RICO, the works.
Wow, that's a hell of a plan.
You sit down with chimpanzees and
a bucket of crack and come up with that?
Whatever else happens, we'll stir things
up. We might even make the papers.
We'll make the papers, all right. We'll
be dead in time for the evening edition.
The people will know the truth. We'll
go out doing our jobs. Enforcing the law.
That's the best inspirational speech
you got? Doing our jobs?
- You don't have to join me.
- No, I'm game.
Like I said, I'm doomed anyhow.
Now, if you'll excuse me for one minute.
Just gonna take care of some business.
Duchess!
Marco.
Polo.
Jumping catfish.
Good morning, Mayor James.
Gordon, you scared
the bajeebers out of me.
Almost spilled my coffee.
Sorry. Sir, you're under arrest.
That's not funny.
Depends where you're sitting.
Might wanna take a look at this.
How you doing, guys?
I'm here to have a chat with Mr. Falcone.
Sure thing, Mr. Mayor.
Carmine Falcone, you're under arrest.
Move.
Lie down right over there. Stay quiet.
What on earth are you thinking?
We'll take you both to jail and charge you
with conspiracy to pervert justice.
Try and take me in,
you won't make it to the end of the street.
- Exactly what I said.
- This is a lawful arrest.
- If you resist, you will be shot.
- I see.
We all die together in a blaze of glory.
If that's how it works out, that's fine.
How about you, Harvey?
- Fine by me.
- Oh, God.
I envy you boys.
Having nothing to lose must be liberating.
- Must feel pretty good.
- Yes, it does.
Suppose you did have something to lose.
What would you do then? Suppose...
...I had a knife
to Barbara Kean's throat right now.
Would you still be so brave?
- You don't.
- I'm telling you I do.
You're a liar.
I have many faults, but I'm not a liar.
Victor Zsasz has Barbara. You know Victor.
- You're lying. She's far away.
- She came back.
Came right to me to plead for your life.
You have a good woman there.
She loves you very much.
Too much.
Prove it.
Prove you have her.
I could.
But I won't.
I want you to believe me.
It's obvious, Jim. He's lying.
Am I?
If you think so,
go ahead and try to bring me in.
You'll be dead, so you won't know
what happens to Barbara.
But it won't be pretty.
Lying.
On my mother's grave.
Drop your gun and Barbara
won't be harmed in any way.
Those muffins smell good.
None for you, creep.
She can have one if she wants.
No, thank you.
Got it.
What a shame.
Oh, this is embarrassing.
He straight-up bluffed you into folding.
We could have gone out like heroes.
Now we're fish food.
Okay, so it wasn't a bluff.
Sorry if she was mistreated a little.
We needed to be sure
she had nothing useful to tell us.
Untie her, Victor.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's okay.
What am I gonna do with you?
By rights, you have to die.
Whoa, hello. Um, late for work.
Quite an adventure. I'll be on my way.
Such a waste though.
Gotham needs men like you. Both of you.
Strong men with principles.
I wish I could show you I'm not the enemy.
The system is not the enemy.
The enemy is anarchy.
But I told you that before, didn't I, Jim?
- Yes, you did.
- You didn't listen though.
Do we get a last meal or a smoke
or anything? Or just talk?
But today, you believed me.
You trusted my word.
That's a good first step.
Perhaps there's still hope for you.
Yes.
Go. Get out of here
before I change my mind.
- Wait a minute.
- Quiet.
It's been a pleasure, Barbara.
I do admire a brave woman.
- What's the catch?
- He said we could go. Let's not haggle here.
What's the catch, Mr. Falcone?
I want you to think about what I said.
I want you to understand the truth.
That's all I ask.
The catch is...
...someday soon, you'll see I'm right.
Barbara.
I'm sorry.
I was just trying to help. And...
...I don't know, I--
I love you so much.
Mm.
Excellent. Delicious.
Yes. I followed the recipe.
You're right, Mr. F. Cooking is easy.
I'm sorry you had to see all that earlier.
Not pleasant.
I understand. Business is business.
Yes, it is.
I'll go see to the chickens.
Bawk-bawk-bawk.
Any eggs, my dears?
Don Falcone.
My friend. Good to see you.
I was just thinking about the night we met.
Cut them down.
Where's the snitch? I wanna speak to him.
Cobblepot, is it?
Condemned men are honest men, I find.
What can you tell me before you go?
Don Falcone. It is a great honor, sir.
Indeed, I can tell a secret
of great value to you...
...if you grant me one last request.
Which is what?
Give the job of killing me to James Gordon.
Why him?
He's the only man under your sway
who has a conscience.
The only one who might be
persuaded to spare my life.
Why would I agree to that?
I want you dead. You're a snitch.
If you agree and Gordon spares me...
...then I will become your snitch for life.
I will come back to Gotham
under a different name.
I will work my way into the Maroni family,
and I will snitch for you.
I'm excellent at this sort of work.
I have a gift for it. I really do, sir.
Deal.
Gordon will get the job of killing you.
Thank you, sir.
What is the valuable secret?
Oh, yes.
Fish Mooney and Nikolai the Russian
only pretend to hate each other.
They're lovers.
And Fish is pushing Nikolai
to take your place.
- Is that so?
- Yes, sir.
But only so Fish can take over from him.
That is a good secret.
It's almost uncanny.
Everything played out
exactly as you said it would.
We got rid of Nikolai painlessly
and Maroni thinks you're a wizard.
You really do have a gift.
But I think we're making
a mistake letting Gordon live.
He's trouble.
Thank you so much for sparing him.
I appreciate the favor.
Don't worry. He'll see the light.
One way or another, I guarantee it.