Previously on
Gotham...
You can still run.
Find Lee, have a life.
- I have to clear my name.
- But how?
You're sane.
It would be unethical
and illegal to keep you confined.
If you keep releasing lunatics,
you're going to get a bad reputation.
- Matches Malone.
- We've met before?
You killed my parents. Who hired you?
You'll never know their name.
Bruce.
He's in there.
Hello, Kristen.
How did you become this?
This is who I am.
That's what made it so easy to frame you.
Drop the gun!
Oh, crud.
So, when are you coming back to work?
I promised Bruce Wayne
I'd solve his parents' murder.
I have to do that first.
The Wayne case is closed, Jim.
The perp is dead.
But who hired him?
I need to find out.
Good morning, Victor.
How is it I'm not dead?
Anything above freezing will kill you.
But never fear,
you won't be locked in there forever.
You do know that Mr. Lucius Fox
fixed your old man's computer?
But I will not have you put that
little girl's life in danger.
It's either the work or it's her.
- I'm not going back.
- What?
My place is here.
Have a great life, Bruce Wayne.
Hi, Jim.
Hands up. Hands up!
Okay. Look.
Better?
Inside.
Keep them up. Face the wall.
What are you doing here?
You're supposed to be in Arkham.
And you're supposed to be in Blackgate.
I cleared my name. I'll ask you again.
What are you doing here?
I was released.
Call them. You'll see.
I'm telling the truth. It's what I do now.
That's hard to believe.
Which part?
I swear to God, after the day I've had,
I have no problem shooting you.
Hey, look, I believe you.
Look, when I came out of the coma,
the memories I had were horrifying,
like waking up from a nightmare.
But the person who did those things,
that's not me.
So they released you, just like that?
Well, not right away.
I mean, I had some issues
to work through, obviously.
But yes, I'm better, Jim.
I'm totally sane.
I really am.
I'm happy for you.
Please, go.
You don't believe me, do you?
Frankly, I don't care.
- What? And that's it?
- I have work to do.
The Lady. You're investigating
the Wayne murder, huh?
I've heard of her.
You think she's involved?
'Cause I could help you with this.
No, thanks.
Okay, well, maybe
it was a mistake to come,
but listen, could you just
do one more thing for me?
Could you say my name?
Goodbye, Barbara.
Hey, Harvey.
Jim will catch you up.
Jim!
You've been at it all night, Master Bruce.
I need to try
and get some food down your neck.
Do I smell sausage?
Chipolatas, dear Mr. Fox.
I've prepared a full English upstairs.
I have no idea if that's a "yes,"
but I'm starving. Let's eat.
I think I found something.
Your father's files are still running
through the decryption program.
It could take weeks
before we know what we have.
Yes, but his calendar
was only password protected.
It was "Bruce," just like the lock.
Here, the week of his murder,
he was supposed to meet a woman
named Karen Jennings
about something called Pinewood Farms.
Oh, Pinewood Farms?
Sounds, uh, rather quaint.
Or not.
Most of Wayne Enterprises' black op
programs had code names like that.
Running Brook, Windy Ridge.
A bland name covering up a nasty business.
This could be what my father
was investigating when he was killed.
I think we might be getting a tad ahead
of ourselves here, Master Bruce.
I mean, how covert could it possibly be
if it's on your old man's calendar?
I'll run Karen's name through HR
when I get into work,
see if there's even a connection.
My father had her address.
She lives somewhere
right outside the city.
I think we should just wait and see what
Mr. Fox comes up with first, Master Bruce.
I'm done waiting, Alfred.
I'm going up there, with or without you.
Imagine my surprise.
You are going to eat something on the way!
Now that we know Matches Malone was
the trigger man, we can work backwards.
His file has him working primarily
with two contractors.
One's dead.
The other one's known as the Lady.
Her? She's the one that sent the assassins
after you at Galavan's penthouse.
Yeah, her. You know where she's at?
In the wind.
She went out of business
after you killed her A-team.
Put her rep in the toilet. Ironic, huh?
At least I have a list of her known
associates. It'll have to do for now.
Someone must know where she is.
Look, her known associates
are professional hit men.
Come back to GCPD.
You'll have resources,
not to mention, you know, me.
Yeah, and I'd have Barnes
looking over my shoulder.
I need to be able to do things my way,
at least for now.
All right, but don't take
too much time, okay?
I'm supposed to be training Alvarez.
It's like trying to teach a halibut
how to put on socks.
Yeah.
Is that it?
You don't carry a badge anymore,
partner, remember, hmm?
I think you need to grab a few items
from the whammy drawer.
Can you believe
they let Barbara out of Arkham?
First Penguin, then her?
What, they don't have locks on the doors?
Good choice.
Hey, Jim?
Be careful out there.
Always.
It's gonna be a bad day
for the hit men of Gotham.
I said, where's the Lady?
No one knows!
Wrong answer.
- Someone knows.
- I don't! I swear!
Where is she?
She might be at a club called the Artemis.
Thank you.
The moment has arrived, Ms. Peabody.
Our success here could finally free
humanity from the shackles of mortality.
As you said the first dozen times
we attempted reanimation, Professor,
and failed.
Oh, but I have a very good feeling
about Patient 44.
You need to be more positive.
Someone at Wayne Enterprises
ran a search for Karen Jennings.
Do you think she's been found?
I don't see how. We've never been able to.
But someone is looking.
She was our first.
One small stroke
on the canvas of possibility.
Such promise, do you remember?
I remember the orderlies she maimed
and the two she killed.
Creation is always so violent.
She could expose us.
Oh, Karen, who's looking for you?
Do they know what you've become?
What I turned you into?
Nope. No joy, never mind.
Still kind of nice to get out the manor,
have a little drive in the country.
Oh, that's terrific, isn't it?
She's made a bloody tea leaf out of you.
"Street smarts"? Streets smarts, my eye.
Shush, Alfred.
These are merely technical skills.
- Oh.
- Morally neutral.
What is it?
Careful, Master Bruce.
She's got some kind
of weird hunting knife.
We don't wanna hurt you.
What're you doing?
Raise your gun. Raise your gun.
My name is Bruce Wayne.
I just wanna talk to you.
Bruce Wayne?
You're Bruce Wayne?
That's far enough.
Drop the knife.
It's not a knife.
Whatever it was you used to do this to me,
just drop it right now.
I can't.
- Listen to me--
- That's far enough.
Alfred!
Look around you, Master Bruce.
Listen, I have no idea what you are,
but whatever that thing is,
it's bloody dangerous.
Do you know who I am?
You seemed to recognize me.
How did you find me?
My father, Thomas Wayne, came here
the week before he died.
He had it in his calendar.
His calendar? Great. Were you followed?
No. I don't know. By who?
No, no, we weren't followed.
Good.
Then you can leave.
Not until you answer my questions.
I know my father came to talk to you
about something called Pinewood Farms.
What is that?
God. You don't know anything, do you?
So tell me.
Do you not understand
that these people will kill you?
I've been trying to tell him that.
I'm not afraid to die.
Not if it means doing the right thing.
Yeah? How'd that work out for your dad?
You have to go.
It's not safe for you here.
I don't care.
Whatever my father was investigating
got him and my mom killed.
You're the first person I've found
who might know why. Please.
You have to tell me what he was doing.
The Artemis is a private club, sir.
I need to see if someone's inside.
It'll just take a minute.
Members only.
Jim?
What a coincidence.
Can I borrow him a moment?
Did I not make myself clear last night?
Oh, you did.
And I wanted to respect your boundaries,
but I was wondering if you knew
that this is a women's-only club.
Plus, its members are, shall we say,
of a criminal persuasion.
Hmm?
Didn't think so, which is why I'm here.
Let me guess.
You're gonna talk to the Lady for me,
get the information I need
if I just, what, trust you?
No one likes a smarty pants.
So what's your plan, then?
- My plan?
- Mmm-hmm.
My plan is to stick a gun
in the Lady's face
and have her beg me
not to pull the trigger
until she tells me
everything I want to know.
The Gordon special. I remember it well.
Problem is you're not a cop anymore.
Why is that by the way?
The point is,
if you go in there guns blazing,
the Lady will disappear,
probably for good.
I can go inside and get you what you want.
What do you have to lose?
Why are you doing this?
I was there, remember?
When you first caught the Wayne case?
I know what it means to you.
You think that if you can solve it,
you can close the door on the past
and maybe, just maybe, it will stay shut,
and then you'll be able to start over.
And you really have to ask me
why I'm doing this?
Buy a girl a drink?
Have we met?
No, but I'm kind of famous.
Oh...
The notorious Barbara Kean. Please.
Sorry about your hand.
I don't get many visitors.
You, uh, spooked me.
Wait, what, we, we spooked you?
How long have you lived here?
Ten years. Ever since Pinewood.
Is that where you got that?
Pinewood Farms was a bioengineering
program at Wayne Enterprises,
the kind that was kept off the books.
I was one of their first volunteers.
What? You volunteered for that, did you?
I didn't have many options at the time.
I was at Blackgate.
Blackgate? Nice.
I take it you weren't a guard, then?
I was born with a crippled arm.
Growing up, my father liked two things,
booze and beating his deformed daughter.
One night, I fought back.
He fell down the stairs
and broke his neck.
I went to Blackgate for murder.
But that's self-defense.
Well, people are scared of different.
Jury sent me away.
One day, these men show up,
tell me they're gonna fix my arm.
Not only fix it, make it better.
Instead, they turned me into the monster
who everybody thought I was.
Did my father know what was going on
at Pinewood Farms?
No. No.
When he found out what was going on,
when he saw what they were doing to us,
he shut it down.
Paid to put us into hiding.
So how many were there of you?
I'm not sure. I know
most didn't survive the experiments.
It started up again, didn't it?
That's why my father came to see you
after all those years.
He wasn't sure, but he had his suspicions.
He came to warn me.
Whoever was running Pinewood,
whoever started it up again,
I know that's who killed my parents.
Do you remember any names?
None of them ever used their names
around us,
but the man who was in charge,
I can still see his face
every time I close my eyes.
Then you need to take us there.
You need to take us to Pinewood Farms.
My father risked his life to save you.
I'm asking you to repay that favor.
I promise, nothing will happen to you.
Okay.
Yeah, it didn't go quite to plan,
but whatever.
I look incredible in that wedding dress.
I just bet you did.
And how did you get out of Arkham?
Well, that was easy,
with a lot of...
"Oh, my God, I can't
believe I killed all these people."
Boo-hoo.
Well, what's your plan now?
Well, I'm thinking about
getting into the assassination business.
Only I need a partner.
What do you have to offer?
I'm rich, fabulous,
and, in your case, I may have
just the thing to restore your reputation.
Really?
All right, see you next week.
Let me help you with that.
Thanks.
Stubborn.
I need to speak to the Lady.
She's expecting you.
Hey, Jim. Guess what.
You were right.
Wow.
Is anyone getting major déjà vu here?
Only wait, oh, we're missing Lee. Shame.
That would've been a real family reunion.
So that's what this has been about?
Delivering me to her?
Well, when I saw her picture
in your file,
I figured you'd go after her,
so I did some digging.
Saw you two had some history,
and it all kind of came together.
So did I deliver or what?
When you said he was looking for me,
I assumed this had something to do
with the men I sent to kill him?
No, he knows you contracted
Matches Malone for the Wayne murders,
and he is just obsessed with finding out
who hired you. It's like his thing.
That's why he's here?
I have absolutely no idea
who is behind the Wayne murders.
You didn't take the contract?
Oh, no, I mean I did,
but we did it all over the telephone.
I never met the client.
Well, you must have got a name.
- He went by a nickname.
- Oh...
Poor Jim.
So close.
It's almost sad you have to die.
Oh.
You know, should we just tell him?
You always this sentimental?
Fine. He called himself the Philosopher.
Here you go, Jim. Now you know.
Told you I had a plan.
It doesn't exactly scream, "top secret
bioengineering lab," does it?
This is it.
All right, you two sit tight.
I'll have a shifty.
Honestly.
She's here. Right.
I'd wager nothing's been touched in here
for a decade.
Are you okay?
Seeing all this,
it feels like yesterday that I was here.
I'm sorry.
Uh, it looks like your father was wrong.
Maybe it's for the best.
You can move on now.
You knew this place was shut down,
didn't you?
Is that why you brought me here,
hoping I'd give up?
Steady on, Master Bruce.
No, she's hiding something.
I can see it in her eyes.
I don't understand.
What won't you tell me?
Hey!
Hey, this is private property.
I'm gonna call the cops.
The girl comes with us,
and no one gets hurt.
Run, Master Bruce.
Run!
Come on.
Drop the gun! Now!
You go down Fourth,
and I'll look this way.
Got it.
What the hell was that about?
Don't be mad.
I was tied to a chair
and nearly killed, again.
What should I be feeling?
Gratitude?
I'm not feeling that.
I needed the Lady to trust me.
It's called a plan.
- "A plan"? What if I'd stayed outside?
- Mmm.
Really?
Look, we got the name.
We should be celebrating.
Hey, we kind of make a pretty good team.
This doesn't change anything.
I got you the information
that I said I would.
Everything I did in there, I did for you.
You have to see that.
Honestly, I don't know what I see.
Then look.
Please.
What do you care?
After everything that's happened.
Let's say you've changed.
What do you care what I think?
Because when I woke up from that coma,
the first image I saw was your face
as you were holding onto me
from the church window.
You were trying to save me.
Because in that moment,
you didn't see the monster.
You just saw me.
That's what I've been holding on to.
Because I feel like, if you
could just look at me like that again,
I'd be okay.
I'd make it.
You wanna be a better person?
Yes.
It's your choice to make.
I can't be that for you.
You tried to kill Lee.
I can't forgive that.
I won't.
Just get it.
Bruce.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Slow down. Slow-- Slow--
I'll be right there.
Alfred!
About bloody time, mate.
Not my call, pal, how about you
stop getting arrested so much?
- Where's Bruce?
- In with Barnes.
Bullock!
Prep Karen Jennings to travel.
I want her at Blackgate today. No contact.
You! You're free to go.
I suggest you do so
before I change my mind.
What did you tell him?
The truth. He didn't seem to like it.
All right. How about you tell me?
Your father found out
about this program,
where Karen Jennings was a subject,
and shut it down.
When it was restarted, he tried
to stop it, and they had him killed.
And you think Karen can identify
the men involved?
Doesn't know their names.
Says she can remember the faces.
The man who contracted Matches Malone
to kill your parents
called himself the Philosopher.
Hold on. How do you know this?
I've been conducting my own investigation.
I found out today.
And I'd be willing to bet that this
is the man who is behind Pinewood.
What do we do?
Have Lucius Fox put together
the files of all the scientists
who've worked for Wayne Enterprises
over the past 15 years.
If Karen can pick this man out,
if he is the Philosopher,
we can tie him to your parents' murder.
Well, that's assuming, of course,
that Karen Jennings is still alive.
I mean, it's obvious
these guys mean business.
She's gonna be dead
the minute she hits Blackgate Prison.
That's why we're gonna break her out.
How much money
can you put together quickly?
How much do you need?
Patient 44's EEG patterns
confirm paradoxical sleep.
We're getting close.
He's getting close.
Karen Jennings was arrested
and is being sent to Blackgate Prison.
Pity.
It seems we should abandon our efforts
to bring her back.
She cannot be allowed to talk.
I'll send a team.
Actually, I was thinking this would be
the perfect opportunity
to let our sub-zero guest
try out his new suit.
You sure?
Whatever that gas did to him,
he's not the man he was before.
He seems very angry.
Oh, I know.
I was listening to that.
Hello, Victor. How are you feeling?
How am I feeling?
I'm locked in a freezer.
How do you think I'm feeling?
That's why I'm here.
How would you like to go
on a little field trip?
What the hell?
Damn.
Yo, Marty, you're never gonna believe it.
You have a decision to make.
You can keep the money, toss us your gun,
and tell your supervisor
you were disarmed,
or be a hero
and wake up like your friend here
with nothing to show for it
but a massive headache.
I'd say it's a bit of
a no-brainer, wouldn't you, sweetheart?
Give me your tool.
You can go.
Go ahead.
Enjoy your cash. Let's go!
Bruce, what is going on?
Who is this?
A friend.
Nice to meet you.
He's gonna help us get you out of town.
I have a car, cash, and a new identity
waiting for you back at Wayne Manor.
I can't believe you would do this for me.
I made a promise
nothing would happen to you.
I intend to keep it.
Karen, do you know a man
who goes by the nickname
"the Philosopher"?
That's, uh, the man who ran the program.
That's what the others called him,
something about some game they played.
And you can identify him?
- Yeah.
- Good.
We have someone tracking down the files
of all the scientists
who've worked for Wayne Enterprises
over the years.
After that, you can disappear.
No one will ever hurt you again.
You sound just like him.
I have been hiding something
from you, Bruce.
Your father did more
than just rescue me from Pinewood.
What do you mean?
After what happened, I was so angry,
but he never gave up on me.
He kept visiting, gave me books to read,
a music box for my birthday.
He kept reminding me that I wasn't alone,
that I wasn't a monster.
I never knew what a real father should be
until Thomas Wayne.
That's why
I didn't want you to pursue this.
I didn't want you to see him differently.
Your father started Pinewood, Bruce.
His intentions were good,
but the man in charge
took advantage of him.
He didn't realize the truth
until it was too late.
Pinewood was his burden,
but it doesn't have to be yours.
It's not a burden.
It's who I am.
Hold on!
Victor?
You.
Put down the gun!
Go! Get on Bruce!
You both all right? You all right?
Go! Go. Run. It's me he's after.
We're not leaving without you.
I'm so glad I met you, Bruce.
Your dad would be so proud of you,
of the man that you've become.
- Hey, Karen!
- Stay here!
No! No! No!
Get back! Get back!
Sorry I'm late.
I did get you
that salt water taffy you like, so--
Shh.
You'll wake her.
I thought she was in Arkham, in a coma.
Not anymore.
She showed up
a couple of hours ago, poor thing.
What is she doing here?
She's come home.
Huh.
My father risked his life to protect her.
He cared for her, and now she's dead
Because of me.
Not because of you, Master Bruce.
Because of what you're pursuing.
Is there a difference?
Yes.
And if you can't make your peace
with that, then you're not ready.
There will be others, Master Bruce.
Karen was the only one who knew
what the Philosopher looked like.
How are we going to find him now?
You need to have faith, Bruce.
I know what you risked today.
- If Barnes finds out you were involved--
- He will,
if he hasn't already.
Pretty sure my days at the GCPD are over,
but I knew that going in.
Then why'd you do it?
You're not the only one
who made a promise.
- Oh, Mr. Fox.
- I let myself in.
I think I might have something.
When I was compiling
the personnel files on scientists,
I also ran a cross-reference search
on Pinewood Farms and the Philosopher,
and found this.
It's from a company newsletter
taken 12 years ago.
The photo lists team nicknames.
Look at the man next to your father.
"Hugo Strange, the Philosopher."
He runs Arkham now.
A friend.
Someone he trusted.
That's not fair.
That's not right.
Oh, Karen, what a shame.
You held such promise.
Victor said he recognized Jim Gordon,
said he was with a boy.
Bruce Wayne.
So he and Jim Gordon are working together.
Well, well.
I think life is about to get
very interesting for us, Ms. Peabody.
It's coming from downstairs.
Patient 44.
But the reanimation
should take another 12 hours.
- Grab him. Grab him.
- Stop!
Oh, Peabody, we did it.
We brought someone back.
We actually did it.
What? What is it now, Sister?
What's he saying?
Heathen dogs, huh?
What now, Sister?
Oh, the holy city. Oh, I see.
The saint will deliver us.
No, don't leave. Don't leave.
Should I gas him?
Azrael.
Azrael!
English - SDH