Previously on Gotham:
How I ever let him
lay a hand on me...
(grunting)
I'm glad he's out
of your life.
ALFRED:
Keep that guard up--
jab, jab.
Lead... jab, jab, right.
What you doing?
Alfred's teaching
me to fight.
I need you to take me
to the Pike brothers.
The firebugs from the Narrows?
I used to hang
with their sister, Bridgit.
GILZEAN:
Hey, boys.
We need the best
and you guys are the best.
JOE:
Bridgy, you just got
a promotion.
GCPD!
Run!
I got her! Drop it!
Drop it!
(Bridgit screams)
(Garrett screaming)
THEO:
One moment, Mr. Penguin.
OSWALD:
Mother.
GERTRUD:
I don't know nothing.
You are going to go to Galavan.
Once you're inside
his organization,
you will find my mother
and rescue her.
He'll buy it
if we sell it right.
(screams)
...and then Penguin
just went crazy.
I mean, like... crazier
than I've ever seen him.
He said it was me that set up
the count house raid,
said I was a traitor and a rat.
(rope creaking)
Then he...
he came at me with a cleaver.
I tried to protect myself
and he did this.
(low grunting)
Sick bastard.
Hmm.
How'd you get away?
GILZEAN:
There was a lot of blood.
A lot.
And he... he tried
to take another swing
and he slipped and fell
and so I just ran.
I ran and I ran and then...
the next thing I knew,
I woke up in the hospital.
Huh.
Give me a shot, Mr. Galavan.
Let me show you what I can do.
Well, I'd like
to help you out,
Butch,
but I already have several
capable, two-handed thugs
in my employ.
They don't know Gotham
like I do.
I got brains, you ask anyone.
What do you think, ladies?
I think he's cute.
Like a sad bear.
I suppose
he's telling the truth.
The little man was cracking up
last time I saw him.
He was very mean
to me once.
Held me hostage in
my own apartment.
Said some
nasty things.
Isn't that right, stumpy?
That's right, ma'am.
And I'm sorry for it.
Business is business,
you know?
Please.
Let me work for you,
Mr. Galavan.
I got nobody else to turn to.
(gasps)
Oh, yes!
We can put cool things
on his stump,
like knives
and mallets and stuff.
Ooh!
How about a little
tiny chain saw?
Yes.
Huh.
Well, that settles it.
Welcome aboard, Butch.
Thank you, sir.
(cries out)
THEO:
Oh!
(laughs) Oh.
Bravo, Congressman.
Well saved.
You really are
quite spry
for a big man.
Have you reconsidered
your position?
Can I count on your
support this election?
Yes.
Yes, you have my full support.
Thank you so much.
(grunting, panting)
(panting)
(grunting)
Freeze!
Man, I didn't do nothing!
Why you chasing me?
A police officer
died last night,
killed by a firebug crew
on a spree.
You're a firebug, aren't you?
No, man! I been out
of the game a long time!
(grunts)
Don't lie to me, Nino!
I swear!
Sir, that's a violation
of officer conduct regs.
Luke Garrett burned to death
in front of me 12 hours ago.
I'll conduct myself
as I see fit.
This crew's working
with a kid.
A girl.
Wears a homemade fire suit.
Hey, for real! Never heard of
a female firebug before.
It's mad rare,
like a... like a unicorn
or something.
(grunts)
(Nino groaning)
Sir?
Captain Barnes says we must
report any infractions.
Even by superior officers.
You do that.
What are you doing?
Can't sleep.
I don't know what
to do with myself.
(sighs loudly)
That's the point
of being free.
You get to do
whatever the hell you want.
What am I gonna do?
I killed someone last night.
I can't go home.
I can't go
to the police...
You gotta get out of town.
How?
I got no money.
No problem.
We'll get some.
You mean, like, crime?
(laughs)
Man, you are square.
(sighs)
I guess I got no choice.
Why are you helping me?
Maybe you remind me of me.
If I was a doofus.
(laughs)
This crime...
what exactly you got in mind?
♪ I'll fight for... ♪
AUCTIONEER:
Ladies and gentlemen!
Or should I say,
pimps, hoes and thieves!
Do I have some product
for you today!
Do you like what you see?
(customers cheer)
Come on, now let me hear you!
Do you like what you see?!
(cheering)
All right.
Oh, check it out, check it out!
Yeah, it's nice and it's dirty!
I want her!
Bidding will start at $800.
Apiece.
Have we got $800? Come on!
$850!
(voices and music muffled)
Those girls
are for sale?
Told you this place
was freaky.
We need to help them.
We're here to help you.
'Cause you killed
a cop, remember?
We get the money, we go.
But...
Listen!
Listen.
You go down the stairs.
The lock on the back door
is busted.
I know, 'cause I busted it.
You go in,
wait for me
to make my move.
How will I know when?
Pay attention.
Sold for $2,500 to the gentleman
in the burgundy hat!
Come on, ladies.
Found you a nice new home!
Oh, you'll be very satisfied.
Very, very satisfied.
Next up!
Check her out as she walks
down the stage;
see how graceful she is.
Look at this one! Whoo!
I'm going to start the bidding
here at $900!
Can I get $900?!
(grunts)
SELINA:
Hey, pervs!
This is a robbery!
Milo! Kill that punk.
She's with me.
Now, each of you
put all your cash in the bag.
Or what?
I ain't
scared of you.
Yeah.
All right.
Anybody else got a problem?
Yeah, didn't think so.
(women shouting)
And for the record?
All y'all suck.
Help!
Come on, come on!
Get me out of here!
MAN:
Hey, stop!
(screams)
(laughing):
Oh, my God.
I know, right?
Let's go.
A note in my file?
Are you serious?
Do I look like I'm joking?
We do not beat suspects! Ever!
(garbled radio transmission)
I get it.
Luke was a good kid.
We took him out of the academy,
told him he was ready.
Now he's dead.
You lose people in war.
You know that.
Make no mistake,
this is war.
But that doesn't give you or me
the license to break the law.
There's a line.
I learned that the hard way.
Respectfully, sir,
this is Gotham.
There are gray areas.
I've learned that
the hard way, too.
And did you
even get a lead
while you were
out avenging Luke?
No, sir.
No, sir?
Well, you got one now.
Bodega owner called this in.
His security camera
caught it.
She's our firefly.
We don't know who
the other one is.
(squealing)
I do.
Damn it.
(Bruce grunting)
Focus. Focus!
Head down!
Distractions will be the
death of you, Master Bruce.
Now, get on your toes.
On your toes.
Move!
Well, don't...
dance around like
a bloody showgirl.
Come on.
(grunts)
That's better. Better.
Now, big left,
big left. Go on!
I got you. Now, your enemies
Hey.
are gonna fight a lot dirtier
than that.
Ow. Ow!
(panting)
Bloody
hell.
(chuckles)
Very good, Master Bruce.
Eh?
Have you spoken to Mr. Fox
about the computer?
That I have, yeah.
How much longer
until it's fixed? (grunts)
I'll tell you when it's done,
won't I? Patience.
I'm tired of patience, Alfred.
I'm ready to begin.
I'll tell you when you're ready,
Master Bruce.
I'm ready now. I know I am.
(grunting)
Oh, by the way,
by the way,
Miss Silver called.
She wants you to go
for dinner this evening.
Silver called?
Yeah.
(shouts)
Told ya.
Not ready.
Let's go.
KRINGLE:
Well, he just up
and moved out of town.
It was rude
and inconsiderate
and perfectly in character
for Tom Dougherty.
Do you ever wonder
where he went?
He could be dead in a ditch
for all I care.
Kristen.
And I mean it, too.
He, um...
he wasn't very nice to me.
That's awful.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
But... it all worked out
for the best.
THOMPKINS:
I know. You and Ed
seem to be getting along.
(Kringle
chuckles)
He is so gentle and kind.
Almost too gentle.
I-I think a man needs
to have a little...
a little fire, a little danger
in him, don't you think?
Oh, I don't know about that.
(chuckles)
And sometimes I-I feel like
he's holding something back
from me.
THOMPKINS:
Like a secret?
I don't know.
I just... I guess I just wish
he would open up a little more.
Good morning.
Miss Kringle,
Miss Thompkins.
Hi.
What do you call
a three-legged cow?
I am terrible...
Lean beef.
Or supper. At my place.
Oh... Ed.
Aw.
(both chuckle)
Ginger to ginger,
we both know
you know
where Selina Kyle's at,
so why don't you tell me now
and save us the hassle.
Who's Selina Kyle?
Cat.
Cat?
Look, Ivy,
want me to call
the children's home
and have 'em come get you now?
Or should I get
a candy bar and forget
to have someone watch you?
Candy bar.
I struck out.
None of the street kids
I talked to have seen Selina.
Relax. Your Uncle
Harvey has you covered.
She's in a squat off
Jenkins. Condemned SRO.
I know it.
Hey. Last time
we saw this chick, she had
a shotgun pointed at us.
Maybe you should take
the Fascist Youth, huh?
Nah.
With Selina,
it's best to go quietly.
When you get
to the bus station,
take the first bus
south.
Stay on till the end
of the line.
Well, what do I do then?
You got plenty of money.
You can do what you like.
Thank you.
For everything.
You've been
a really good friend.
I got my cut.
(chuckles)
No biggie.
(vehicle approaching)
(tires screeching)
Bridgit, you need to run.
Bridgit, run!
Run! Run!
No...
Selina! No!
Selina!
No! No!
(Bridgit shouting)
(grunting)
BRIDGIT:
Help me!
(Bridgit shouting indistinctly)
Hey!
(panting)
Hands in the air!
Drop the gun.
Like hell I will.
Where's your
girlfriend?
Who?
We got both of you on tape.
Don't know what you're talking
about, Gordon.
She's burnt down
half a dozen buildings.
Killed a cop.
You're running
with a bad partner, kid.
You don't understand.
She was forced
to do all of that.
Okay.
Let me help her.
Who is she?
Who's forcing her
to do this?
Look, there's a lot
of angry cops out there.
She's gonna get shot on sight,
unless I get to her first.
Her name is Bridgit Pike.
Her brothers took her back.
Joe and Cale Pike.
They, like... kidnapped her.
They're the ones
who made her start burning stuff
in the first place.
It's their fault the cop died.
The Pike brothers?
Why'd they burn down
Wayne Enterprises' buildings?
Who paid them?
Why the hell should I know
why the Pikes do anything?
They're freakin' nuts.
They treated Bridgit like a
slave, chained her to the wall.
And you're angry about it.
Is that why you're armed?
You're gonna go
after the Pikes?
Rescue your friend?
No.
That's a yes.
Look, you're gonna get
your friend and yourself killed.
Let me handle the Pikes.
No offense, Jim,
but I like my chances better
than yours.
Why get involved?
Why risk your neck?
Who is this
girl to you?
No one. Just...
a girl in the neighborhood.
I give you my word.
I will do everything I can
to keep her safe.
But you have to
stay out of it.
Tell me where she is.
(grunts)
Damn.
She's got six grand here.
Little Bridgy put
on her big girl pants.
You can take all of it.
I don't care.
Oh, I'm taking it.
That's not the issue.
The issue
is you thinking it's cool to
just ditch your brothers, hmm?
CALE:
Oh, snap.
Bridgit's gonna get it.
Joe, please.
Did you even think about us,
hmm?
Did you even think
how we would feel?
(bang)
No, don't!
Joe,
I didn't mean anything by it!
I'm a sensitive guy,
and you hurt my feelings.
(gasping)
(bang)
You know, without family,
what do you got?
You-you got
nothin', right?
You want to be part
of the family again?
(bang)
(gasps, panting)
I said...
do you feel like being part
of this family
again?
(Bridgit whimpers)
Yes!
(bangs)
(screams)
Damn! (laughs)
Damn, that hurts.
Bridgit's back.
(whimpering)
(chains rattling)
If you try anything like
that again, I'll kill you,
and I'll skin that little
cat bitch, too. You hear me?
You're never leaving.
Yes.
Good.
Go make our supper.
All right,
let's pack it up.
(Oswald sputters)
Dear me.
A mallet.
That's, um... useful.
Don't even start.
Tell me you bring good news.
I'm in.
I'm in good.
And? And?!
I'm asking questions.
But it's dangerous.
If I push too hard,
Galavan'll be onto me.
I told you,
he's a smart guy.
Look at me, Butch.
Are you my servant?
(sniffs)
Yes.
Do you obey me in all things?
Then why do you
bring me excuses?
Go find my mother.
Before I chop off
your other hand.
(slurping)
Yes, boss.
Come on.
Harder.
(laughs)
(gasping,
laughing)
Come on, Joe.
What are you gonna do,
kill us?
Yep.
(screaming)
Oh, God!
(sizzling)
I'll check
the other room.
(door opens)
(groans, sniffing)
Clear!
(groans)
She's not
here.
Damn.
I hate how it smells
like good barbecue.
(gasps)
(screams)
Bitch.
(grunting)
Bullock, hey!
What?!
Scared the hell
out of me!
(gasping, exhales)
And now he's dead.
Nice work, Bullock.
Oh, yeah.
My kicks did it?
Maybe it's because he's fried
like a taquito!
It's not on me.
Uh-huh.
Looks like Selina was telling
the truth.
Look, I don't want to speak ill
of the dead, but these asshats
had it coming.
These asshats were
professional arsonists.
Somebody hired them.
Why Wayne
Enterprises?
Who cares, all right?
There's a freaky
firefly chick
on the loose with
a flamethrower.
Let's start there.
(groans)
(whimpering)
Hallelujah.
Hello, Butch.
Sorry to keep you
waiting.
I just wanted
to check in,
see how things
were going.
Any complaints?
No. No, sir. I'm fine
like a bottle of wine.
(chuckles)
Good.
You have a real future here.
You are a hard worker,
and you're loyal to a fault.
Thank you, boss.
If only you were loyal to me.
I, uh...
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Come on, Butch.
Have some dignity.
I know what you were doing.
You were looking for
Penguin's mother, weren't you?
The hand was a nice touch.
Almost fooled me.
How on earth
did Penguin get you to do that?
I'm his servant.
I have to obey him
in all things.
Penguin's done a number
on you, huh?
Tinkered
with your wiring.
Perhaps we can help.
Tabby?
Tabby, could you come
here, please?
Penguin has brainwashed
this poor soul.
Can we help?
Be my pleasure.
All right, let-let's...
let's talk about this.
Can we talk about this?
Take it easy.
What are you doing?
Relax.
We just want to help.
(grunts)
(panting)
(shouts, pants)
(grunting)
(grunts, shouts)
THEO: I'll leave
you two to it.
Uh, remember,
dinner's in an hour.
(gasps, gags)
(Tabitha sighs)
We've set up a perimeter.
She can't have gotten far.
And we're sitting
on Selina Kyle's place.
Keep me posted.
Bridgit Pike
was abused her whole life,
forced to set
those fires.
I promised my informant
I would keep her safe.
Uh,
weren't you the one saying that
Luke Garrett was just a kid?
That we owe him justice?
I know that's what I said.
And you were right.
And now she
killed him.
Now she has
two more dead bodies on her.
So I don't care about the hows
and the whys and the boo-hoos.
You don't make promises
you can't keep.
You find her
and you take her down.
Clear?
Yes, sir.
(pigeons cooing)
We must've spent
years up here,
watching these birds.
Remember when Mickey Slattery
called us orphan bastards
and we tried to throw him
off the roof?
The cops are
outside my place.
You need to get
out of town.
I'm not scared of them.
Bridgit, I know what you did
to your brothers.
Not that they didn't
deserve it, but...
whoa.
I was surprised.
Cale flamed up good, but it was
Joe who burned the brightest.
You don't sound like yourself.
I'm not myself anymore.
I'm free.
Just like you told me I was.
So what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna go after
the rest of them.
The rest of who?
The pervs and the bullies.
The ones
who hurt people like us.
No one's ever
gone after me or hurt me.
Yeah, right.
Rule number one:
look after number one.
That's you.
Don't be crazy, or you'll
get yourself killed.
Don't worry about me, Selina.
This is what I was meant to do.
Bridgit, please,
don't do this.
It's nice to have someone
who cares about me.
Thank you.
I don't care.
I just think you're
being dumb. But...
hey...
good luck.
I'll see you around.
A toast.
TABITHA:
I'm so sorry.
Something came up last minute.
(clears throat)
As I was saying:
To family.
In the end,
it's all that matters.
Family.
I hope, in time,
you'll come to think
of us as family, Bruce.
Thank you.
It's-it's been some time
since I had a...
a meal like this.
You mean with girls?
You should come over more often.
We can, like,
hang out or whatever.
I'd like that.
Look how cute they are.
Don't you
just want to eat them?
Tabitha,
leave the young people alone.
Well, they are cute.
And they know it.
(Peggy Lee's "Sugar" playing)
KRINGLE:
These were
the best mashed potatoes
I have ever had.
I swear, I'm gonna get plump.
I like that you have
an appetite.
Stop it, you're spoiling me.
I won't stop it.
I want nothing more
than to spoil you.
Oh. Ed.
So forceful.
There's something else
I want to tell you.
I just...
I don't want to scare you away.
Please, tell me anything.
Do not hold back.
♪ That sugar baby of mine... ♪
(instrumental interlude)
Kristen...
...I like you very much.
I... I feel the same way
about you.
And, um...
And...
shh.
(thunder rumbling)
♪ ...trips to his lips ♪
♪ If I was a bee ♪
♪ Because he's sweeter than ♪
♪ Sugar candy to me ♪
♪ He's confectionary sugar... ♪
Mr. Nygma,
is that your bedroom over there?
♪ I'm too sweet on my sugar ♪
♪ That sugar baby of mine... ♪
Why, yes, it is.
♪ That sugar baby of mine! ♪
(thunder rumbles)
(song ends with a flourish)
Gordon, phone call for you.
This is Gordon.
Do you remember your promise?
Yes.
I think I know
where she's going.
(man screaming)
(gasping, shouting)
BRIDGIT: Go, go, go!
Go, go, go!
Go, go! Go!
(shouting)
Come on!
(officers shouting indistinctly)
(siren wailing)
All right,
no one gets hurt tonight.
We follow protocols
and stay safe.
UNIT ALPHA:
Yes, sir.
Freeze!
Hands in the air!
Hold your fire!
Bridgit Pike!
Stay away!
My name's Jim Gordon.
I know what
your brothers did to you.
(gasping)
I know you didn't mean
for any of this to happen.
You don't know anything!
You put your weapon
down and come with me,
I can help you.
There are places
you can go.
I'm not going to jail!
You're a juvenile.
We can work something out.
Wait, wait!
I said hold your fire!
Bridgit!
Stop!
Take cover!
Bridgit!
Wait!
(screaming)
I'm glad we have a moment
alone. There is something
I need to discuss.
Oh.
An executive at
Wayne Enterprises
has been
reported missing:
Sid Bunderslaw.
Do you know him?
Yes.
We've met several times.
What happened?
No one knows.
But it doesn't
look good.
How did you hear?
Let's just say I have
friends in high places,
and I've been following
the goings-on
at Wayne Enterprises
very closely.
What have you learned?
That your father
was a good man.
A great man, even.
But in spite of that,
bad things happened
at his company.
Unfortunately,
I think you're right.
I can tell you're very
mature for your age.
Ready to tackle the problems
of your company head-on.
But you'll need help.
Once I'm mayor,
I would very much
like to be that person.
Thank you...
Mr. Galavan.
I-I appreciate it.
(clicks tongue)
Butch.
What has happened?
I found your mother.
Where?
In a warehouse
down by the port.
But they caught me looking.
You half-wit!
If they kill my mother...!
Look, they don't know I'm here.
The tigerlady, she wanted
to take her time with me,
so she chained me up
and I got out.
We gotta go now.
(laughing)
Yes. Yes, yes.
Good, Butch.
You've done well.
Your loyalty
will be rewarded handsomely.
I swear it.
Yes, boss.
Rest here for a minute,
and I'll go gather the troops.
THOMPKINS:
How old are you?
Old enough to shoot you,
if that's what you're thinking.
No, that's not
what I was thinking.
You don't have to point
the gun at me.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Damn right you're not.
My name is Lee.
I know what your name is.
What's your name?
You're cute.
For a doctor.
Thanks. You're cute.
For a gangster.
Hi, Selina.
Sorry about this, Lee.
Oh, hey, no problem.
(sighs heavily)
So...
is Bridgit okay?
I'm sorry.
She's not gonna make it.
You said that you'd help her.
I tried, Selina.
I tried.
But she didn't
want to go quietly.
I think she wanted it
to end this way.
Look...
Selina...
Don't touch me.
I know you were telling
the truth about Bridgit.
That her brothers
put her up to this.
I need to know who hired them.
I already told you I don't know.
And I still don't believe you.
What do you care?
You don't care about people
like us. It's not like
you're really gonna go after
your little friend.
My friend?
Do you mean Penguin?
Why would he set those fires?
That doesn't make any sense.
Ask him yourself.
I'm done talking to you.
I should have never
trusted a cop.
I tried to help her,
it just went a different way.
Is that what you call it
when someone dies?
Is that what you tell yourself?
I'm sorry.
(scoffs)
Whatever.
(both laugh gently)
You're so sweet.
Kristen, what's the matter?
Um... I'm scared.
Of what?
Of Tom Dougherty.
He used to tell me...
if he ever saw me
with another man,
he would kill me.
I'm terrified of what will
happen when he comes back.
You don't need
to worry about that.
No...
you don't know him.
He is... (exhales) a monster.
Listen to me.
You do not need to worry
about Tom Dougherty.
You are sweet.
But... you're not a fighter.
You couldn't possibly
take him on.
Trust me, it's been
taken care of.
What does that mean?
Um...
Some time ago,
he and I had an altercation.
I asked him to treat you
with more respect.
Oh, my God.
And he said he would treat you
any way he liked
and he assaulted me.
Oh, my God!
So, anyhow,
long story short...
I killed him.
(laughing):
Oh, Ed, that's...
You had me going
for a minute, there.
It was outside of your apartment
under the elevated train.
I stabbed him and he died.
Ed, that's not funny.
I'm not being funny.
"T. Dougherty."
Do you believe me now?
Oh, my God.
What's wrong?
Uh...
How could you?
Where are you going?
No, please, sit down.
Don't touch me!
Would you please let me explain?
There is nothing
to explain.
I don't even know who you are.
No, that's wrong.
You are a murderer.
He was a monster! You said so!
He was abusing you.
I can't believe I even
fell for you, you sicko.
I'm not sick. I love you.
I did it for you.
Everything I ever
thought about you, I was right.
I should have my head examined.
Don't say that.
Wait, what were you
doing outside my house?
I was worried for you.
You were stalking me.
You are a psychopath.
That is not true!
That's not who I am.
Don't say that about me.
You are going to prison
where they will
do horrible things to you.
Things that
you deserve.
Don't say that to me.
No, let go. Don't touch me!
(grunts)
Let go of me, you freak.
Please don't call me that.
Oh!
Help!
Listen to me.
I am not the man
that you think I am.
I would never
do anything to hurt you.
I had to kill him
because he hit you.
Do you understand that?
I did it for you.
I promise I will never do
anything to hurt you ever again.
I love you.
I've loved you
since the first moment
that I saw you.
Kristen? Kristen?
Oh, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no... no, no.
Oh, no, plea...
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
Please.
(sobs):
Please, no.
No. No.
(screams):
No!
♪ ♪
(dogs barking in distance)
MAN: Damn, this girl
looks rough.
They tell people she dead.
But that's a lie.
I heard the suit
she was wearing melted to her.
Say she's fireproof.
Come on.
Yeah, man-- fireproof.
That's why they sent
her down here,
with the rest
of the monsters.
For testing.
(quiet, muffled groan)
(quiet clicking)
(screaming)
(eerie, distant groan)
(quiet moan, gasping)