Previously onGotham...
On the count of three,
instead of telling me who you love
- tell me who to kill.
- Kill Lee.
You chose Lee because you love Vale.
If a person comes into contact
with my blood, it changes them.
Listen to me! I would never do
anything to hurt you.
Kristin. No!
You wanted to save Lee.
You knew he would do the opposite.
You love Lee. Which means we're done.
I have found someone.
I have no choice
- to confess my feelings to Ed.
- Duh!
Is this about the tests they're
running on Alice Tetch's blood?
Yes. The rats were exhibiting
manic tendencies. Violent rage.
- I assume they're working on a cure.
- Yes, but it could take years.
Nobody moves!
- What is going on?
- I'm afraid your evening
- has been hijacked.
- Glasses down!
Is that my dear sister I see?
She's in you, isn't she?
- Miss Kringle?
- No, my name is Isabella.
You remind me of someone
that I used to know.
I met someone. I think I'm in love.
I want to re-join the GCPD.
Welcome back, detective.
GCPD! Hands in the air!
Back away! Slowly.
This ain't what it looks like.
Explain it to me
down at the precinct.
For now, you'd be wise
to keep your mouth shut.
Listen, can we talk about this?
Be reasonable, man.
Look, I didn't kill anybody. Okay?
I'm the cleaner. That's it.
- You're just the cleaner.
- Yeah.
You're just the guy
that chops up the bodies
and dumps them in a vat of acid.
That's it.
What're you doing, man?
Just take me in, okay?
I bet that's what you want.
Me to read you your rights.
Make sure you get a lawyer.
In two, three years from now,
I'll see you on some corner
free as a bird.
Any other night, yeah.
It would eat at me,
but, yeah, I'd do it.
Not tonight.
The Toad, he's the one you want!
He gave me the job!
See, something got into me.
Now, I see a scumbag like you
and my blood starts boiling
in my veins.
I just want to punish you.
Make you suffer.
But until now,
I've been able to control it.
But it's growing stronger
inside of me.
Please.
The Toad! I told you! He's the one!
Just arrest me! Arrest me!
- We're past that.
- Please.
Morning.
We knew what we were
getting into, right?
When we agreed to let my dad
throw us an engagement party?
- Oh, we knew.
- I mean, who are these people?
He's very proud of you.
And he wants all of Gotham
to know that.
Well, he's succeeded because
he invited most of the city.
- How are you so okay with this?
- Because I agree with him.
He should be proud. As am I.
How did I get so lucky?
What is it?
Jim Gordon's returning to the GCPD.
- When?
- He starts today.
- How long have you known this?
- A few days.
I'm sorry,
I should've told you sooner.
It's fine.
Is it?
I don't know, Lee.
We agreed
he wouldn't be a part of our lives
and now you're going
to be working with him.
- That's a part of our lives.
- Do you trust me?
Because if you do,
then nothing else matters.
Of course, I trust you.
And you're right, you're right.
It's all gonna be okay.
It's just...
When I think about what happened
with Tetch.
And the things that Gordon said, I...
So don't think about it.
I'll try.
But if you accidentally shot him,
I'd be okay with that, too.
No promises.
I'll see you tonight.
Yeah.
- Lock this bummer.
- Shut up.
Come on!
Finish it at this moment!
Hey, hey, hey.
There you are. We got a call.
Warehouse district.
You coming?
- That's it? No "welcome back?"
- Please.
If we had a big to do every time
you came back to the GCPD
we'd never catch any bad guys.
Andale, partner.
Oh, and I believe this
belongs to you.
You coming or what?
Yeah. I'm coming.
What must be broken
before it can be used?
- Eggs!
- Correct.
As always.
Edward, you spoil me.
You make it easy.
I'm going to miss you.
I'm only gone for two days.
Actually, your conference ends
at 1:45 on Monday.
With traffic,
I put you in 5:30 in the Gotham.
If you leave on time today,
which I'm sure that you will...
you'll be gone 44 and one-half hours.
Less than two days.
I will hold onto that thought.
Cream! I'll got you cream.
So what does one do
at a librarian conference?
Oh, it would bore you.
Nothing that you would say, do,
or think would bore me.
In that case,
let me read you my schedule.
Where did those glasses come from?
These? These are my back-up pair.
I normally wear contacts.
I thought you knew that.
Is something wrong?
Edward, what is it?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
Excuse me.
They're just a pair of glasses.
I remember
you loved that style on me.
Oh, dear.
I haven't upset you, have I, Ed?
I would've thought
you would've been used
to seeing people in mirrors.
You're just in my head.
Like that makes a difference.
But honestly, besides the fact
that she looks just like me
you went from someone
who files papers in a police station
to someone who files books
in a library.
Not super original.
You and Isabella are...
just somewhat, different.
Well, I'm dead, and she's alive.
But how long will that last?
Until you...
I...
I would never hurt Isabella.
I bet you would've said
the same thing about me.
Face it, Ed. You're a killer.
It's only a matter of time
before you...
Okay, so, the UNI ID'd the Vic.
One Paulie Penopolus,
aka Paulie Pennies.
Clean up guy
for the Gotham underworld.
Bingo. I'm thinking it's some
kind of business thing.
Maybe an unhappy customer?
- Perhaps a competitor.
- Good places to start.
Hey listen, seriously, Jim,
I'm glad you're back.
Me too, Harv. Feels good.
This wasn't just business.
We should call Barnes.
You know why I'm here.
Oh, yes.
Yes, indeed.
She's in there, isn't she?
Inside of you.
Hello, sister dear.
Just tell me.
You grew up with your sister.
You've seen this virus first hand.
How do I beat it?
I believe the way this works
is you give me something
I give you something. Tick-tock.
How about I let you keep your teeth?
Or...
My sister's virus
is a beautiful thing
it makes the darkest part
of a person sing.
What darkness in you
has Alice brought to life?
Tell me that,
and I'll tell you everything I know.
Criminals.
The guilty.
My anger at them.
Oh, but it's not anger I see.
Rage.
Violent, bloody rage.
All right, Tetch, my turn.
Is there a cure?
Yes.
There is a cure.
What is it?
You give in,
and let my dear sister win.
- You think I'm playing?
- Have you heard the voices?
What voices?
The virus, even as it grows stronger,
waxes and wanes
you may have the illusion
you're winning.
Then you hear the voices...
those dark voices
from deep within you
whispering, whispering.
And finally you'll see the world
as it really is.
And there'll be
no more Captain Barnes.
Only Alice, my dear Alice.
You don't know me.
You've dirtied your hands,
haven't you?
And now you're desperately trying
to make it right.
I can make it right.
You're back.
I'm back.
I suppose
it was only a matter of time.
Once a cop, always a cop.
For better or worse,
this is where I belong.
- How's Vale?
- Good. I think.
She was on a hospital anyway.
- You two are not...
- No.
I'm not trying to make this awkward.
Why would it be?
We're both adults.
There's no reason
we can't work together.
I'm glad you feel that way.
Mario agrees?
He will. Eventually.
Right.
Our engagement party is tonight.
I'll only bring it up
because a few people here are going.
- It's awkward now, isn't it?
- A little.
So you want to know
about the two bodies
- that you found this morning?
- Yes.
I've only had time
to do a preliminary examination.
But that John Doe in the acid?
His face had been removed.
- Removed how?
- Scalpel? Razorblade?
Whoever did it knew exactly
what they were doing.
I'll have more for you soon.
Jim...
I think you made the right decision,
coming back.
I noticed there was exactly,
was just business
but, right now, we're thinking
whoever paid Paulie Pennies
to dispose of the body in the bathtub
then also might have killed him
to tie up loose ends.
Uh-huh.
Jim, good to see you
with a shield again.
- And a tie.
- Captain, good to be back.
Bullock was just filling me in.
Hell of one a catch
in your first day.
Yeah.
It's the preliminary report from Lee.
John Doe had had his face removed.
- Trying to cover up his identity?
- I don't know, maybe.
But the acid would've done
that anyway.
I'm gonna run point on this one.
- Honestly, cap...
- That's cool.
Look, I know I've been away...
Maybe that's why you forgot
how things go around here.
I give you an order,
and you follow it.
Which for the record, Captain,
I totally support.
I'm taking point on this.
Not giving you the day off.
File the physical evidence,
Bullock. Report back to me.
Aye-aye.
Jim.
I didn't mean to bite your head off.
Just sometimes the ugliness here
gets to me.
No need to explain.
Let me know if you need anything.
And...
don't let those bastards
haze you too hard, rookie.
Yes, sir.
Gordon.
Here's one you wanted, Captain.
Mid-level felon.
- Goes by "The Toad?"
- Yeah, that's him.
Thank you.
Maybe she's right?
What if there's something
about Miss Kringle
Kristen's, Isabella's face
what if there's something
about her face that
unlocks that side of me?
What if I do hurt her?
Oswald?
- Yes?
- You're smiling.
- I was?
- Yes.
Well...
I was just thinking...
how darned lucky Isabella is.
You love her, yet to protect her
you're willing to break up with her.
Beautiful.
Sad, but beautiful.
So you think I should break up
with her.
I'm sorry. I thought that's
what we were talking about.
Certainly,
I would never pressure you...
No, you're right.
If I did hurt her,
I would never forgive myself.
That life would put her
in your path again
only to snatch her from you.
- Why?
- I can't do it.
- What?
- I can't break up with her.
- But, you said yourself...
- I need you to do it for me.
Would you do that?
I would be forever in your debt.
Just be gentle.
Of course.
I'm looking for a punk
who's supposedly frequent
this rat hole.
Goes by "The Toad."
Who's asking?
Captain Nathaniel Barnes of the GCPD.
How about you and I go on
to the precinct
and you can answer some questions.
Blow, pig.
I want to know about Paulie Pennies.
The body he was getting
rid of last night.
Where'd it come from?
Maybe you want me
to open up that mouth for you.
Stop!
I'm... I hired Paulie!
But I'm just the go-between!
I'm getting so sick of hearing that.
Nobody's responsible for anything.
Everyone's a middle man.
I want a name!
Symon. Okay?
Dr. Symon.
He's a big-time plastic surgeon!
So what?
He likes cutting people's
faces off for kicks? Try again.
No! He's got a side business.
You get in trouble.
You need a new face.
He gives you one!
New face? Whose?
I don't know. I just get rid
of the bodies that's all!
You think you're not guilty,
but you are.
Stop. Stop it, Symon!
He's the one you want!
You're a cop!
Symon?
Take me to him.
Mayor Cobblepot?
Hello, Isabella.
May I?
Of course.
Going somewhere?
Just for a couple nights.
But, I was hoping to talk to Ed
before I left.
I've tried calling him. Is he okay?
Yes.
How shall I put this?
It's over.
Excuse me?
He's not going to see you anymore.
Don't try to contact him.
That door is closed.
Have a nice life.
Oh, my.
It's a shock.
But really, besides your odd
resemblance to his ex
a certain facility with riddles
compulsion for order
what is it that you two
really have in common?
Edward is a person
of exceptional intelligence
and imagination.
He deserves to be appreciated
by someone on his own level.
And you, my dear, are simply not.
Best end things now.
You're right.
I don't deserve him.
Glad we agree. Bye.
But I'm not going to let him go.
He loves me, and I love him.
Do you know how rare that is,
Mr. Mayor?
Of course, you do
because you love him too.
I can see it.
I'm not even jealous.
I don't think you understand
It was my glasses this morning.
They reminded him of Miss Kringle.
He's afraid he's going to hurt me
like he hurt her.
Listen to me, you little idiot
I'm telling you one last time
Let. Ed. Go.
No.
I'll write to him.
I'll make him understand
he has nothing to fear.
I'm not gonna let him go.
Very well.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
You better not have been lying to me.
I'm not! This is his place.
You're not gonna kill me, are you?
I'm trying.
I'm about to take the face.
Be here in an hour,
and we can do the transplant
you haven't eaten today, have you?
Very good.
I have to thank you, my dear
for taking such care of your skin.
Excellent elasticity.
Now hold still.
Who's there?
Quiet.
Or we will forgo any anesthesia.
- I said, who's there?
- GCPD.
You're under arrest.
Go for it.
Please.
I surrender.
Ma'am?
You all right?
How many?
- Excuse me?
- How many have you killed?
How many faces have you taken?
I have the right to an attorney.
I wish to invoke that right now.
Guilty! Guilty!
Who's there?
No one. It's only me.
Guilty! Guilty! Guilty!
What is wrong with you?
What are you doing? Arrest me!
Guilty! Guilty!
I am not resisting!
Guilty!
The point Dr. Thompkins hopes
you pay particular attention to
is the level of strength required
to sever Paulie Pennies' head
from his torso.
And what level would that be, Lucius?
- Extreme.
- Extreme strength, got it.
As with the other victim
in the bathtub
we haven't gotten any hits
on his prints
but a puncture mark in his arm
suggests he was drugged
prior to having his face removed.
I'll run toxicology,
let you know what I come up with.
- Thanks, Lucius.
- Yep.
It's good to have you back, Gordon.
Lucius, you're in forensics,
not the M.E.
Is there a reason
Lee didn't bring this herself?
Dr. Thompkins has already gone
for today.
Her engagement party?
Right.
I heard it's gonna be
quite the affair.
Beautiful women.
Free booze. Canapes.
- Harvey, you can go if you want.
- What? No.
I'd much rather spend time
here with my old partner.
Much more fun.
Besides, I wasn't invited.
Captain!
Bullock, book this piece
of human garbage
for the murder of the John Doe.
You got it, Captain, come on.
He's a plastic surgeon.
Face man for the underworld.
He had a girl on the table.
If I'd been there five minutes
later...
But you weren't.
You did it, Captain.
Yeah. Today.
You know the feeling, Jim,
when you've won a battle
but know you're going
to lose the war?
Wars are fought one battle
at a time, sir.
You said he killed the John Doe.
Not Paulie Pennies?
No. His killer is still out there.
I'll get him tomorrow. I promise.
My father and I have not always
seen eye-to-eye
but I think, Dad, will agree of that
marrying Lee is the best decision
I've ever made.
Without a doubt.
And Lee, you're a doctor
a member of our city's
police department
you're funny,
compassionate and brilliant
despite insisting all dogs are boys
and all cats are girls
It's hopeless,
I've tried to correct her.
I loved you since the moment
I saw you.
You're so wonderful. He's sweet.
- You're so lucky.
- Lee!
Congrats.
You look gorgeous, no surprise.
- Barbara? How did you...
- Get in?
As a plus one.
With that guy there. Hey.
- Or it might've been him.
- You need to leave right now.
Can't we bury the hatchet?
So I came at you with a knife,
kidnapped you, whatever.
I've forgiven you
for beating me unconscious.
Water under the bridge.
You just stay right here.
I'm gonna get someone.
I'm leaving.
I just wanted to ask.
As someone else
who was once with Jim Gordon
- don't you miss it?
- Miss what.
The heat.
Being so close,
so much darkness and light.
To someone always a warm in himself.
Let me think.
Tormented Jim Gordon.
Or Mario, who I know is a good man.
Who'll be a wonderful father
to my children.
And whom I love.
No, I don't miss it.
Wow.
I think you actually believe that.
It's kind of sad.
Tell my dates I've left, would you?
Don't let her ruin your night.
Captain, I'm so glad you came.
I can't stay.
I came to congratulate you.
You deserve to be happy.
Thank you.
But you have to stay
for at least one drink.
If nothing else to save me
from these people.
One drink.
- But no work talk.
- Deal.
So among the materials
confiscated in Symon's lab
I came across a unique
anesthetic cocktail.
Let me guess,
the same cocktail toxicology
- found in the John Doe.
- Exactly.
Hey. I got some bad news.
Symon walked.
- What?
- The girl he had tied up
refused to press charges
they've probably paid her off
and we just got an order
from Judge Bam-Bam
demanding his immediate release.
The botoxed son of a bitch
is uber-connected.
The toxicology definitely Ties Symon
to the John Doe murder.
We gotta get him back here.
Captain Barnes?
Carmine Falcone.
I don't believe we've met.
No. But I was just leaving.
I see. Is my company so odious?
You belong behind bars.
I'm retired.
After running Gotham's underworld
for 30 years.
This city was built
because of men like me.
People have jobs
That whiskey you're drinking,
paid for through my work.
So you did some good, so what.
Doesn't mean you're above the law.
Nobody is.
You know, whenever I hear a man
possessed of such certainty
I always think he's trying mostly
to convince himself.
I wish you a pleasant evening,
Captain.
- Me, Captain.
- Alvarez?
Tell Gordon I'm bringing him the man
responsible for Paulie Pennies'
murder.
No backup.
He's coming in of his own accord.
Sure thing Captain,
but you should know
the judge release Dr. Symon...
Guilty!
Guilty! Guilty! Guilty!
Guilty.
Isabella?
Isabella, I got your note.
I thought you needed to leave
for your conference.
I can be late, Edward.
This is more important.
Oswald...
Oswald, the Mayor,
he informed me of your position.
But believe me, I think...
our breaking up is for the best.
No, Edward, it's not.
I understand your fear.
It comes from a place of love.
I know you won't hurt me.
You never could.
I don't think that you...
Oh, my...
Kristin...
I found old photos in newspapers.
- You have to, No, no, no.
- I need to leave. Now.
No, look at me. Look at me.
You don't know what you're doing.
I'm forcing you to face your fear!
You won't hurt me!
Even when I look like this!
Edward!
Edward...
Don't. No, no, don't, don't, no.
Should I take the glasses off?
Keep them on.
Seal off the exits.
But do it quietly.
Last thing anyone wants is a scene.
- Yes, sir.
- A little late for that.
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry,
but we have to make an arrest
in the Paulie Pennies case.
We tried to get the guy at his home.
But his housekeeper said he was here.
Just makes you realize what a small
town Gotham is, doesn't it?
Couldn't you wait?
If he's here,
he's not exactly running.
Which make a good point, Jim.
You wanna take that one?
Good evening, everyone.
Jim.
- What's going on?
- Apparently,
there's a murder suspect
among our guests.
Can I ask who?
- Dr. Maxwell Symon. He's...
- A plastic surgeon.
You arrest him, you gonna have
to fight off every women here.
He's a favorite.
He's also a murderer.
I'd be curious to know
how your father knows him.
I'm sure that their relationship
is completely above board.
While you two hash this out.
I'm gonna go and grab Symon.
- Harvey.
- What?
I can handle a plastic surgeon
on my own.
Don't worry,
discretion is my middle name.
Lee. I'd like a word with Jim.
- Mario...
- It'll be fine.
Okay.
Look, Mario, I have a job to do,
so whatever this is...
When you told Tetch to kill Lee
you knew he would do the opposite.
You sacrificed your girlfriend
- for my fiancé.
- That's insane.
Would you just admit
you still love her?
- I don't have time for this.
- Hey.
You once told me that
if I ever hurt Lee, you'd kill me.
Well now it's my turn.
I love Lee and I'll do whatever
I have to, to keep her.
Then word of advice,
lose the jealousy.
It's weak.
Gordon!
For Lee, I'll give you that one.
Oh, Captain,
if you keep frowning like that
you'll never get those wrinkles
out around your mouth.
Come down to my office tomorrow,
I'll give you a free evaluation.
How surprised you can even feel that?
Through that thing you call a face.
What are you doing?
What I should have done all along.
You're insane.
Oh no, Doc,
I'm saner than I've ever been.
I'm seeing things clearly
for the very first time.
All these years,
I've put my trust in the system
my trust in the law
held myself back from doing
what I really wanted to do.
And then I saw the truth.
It's not just you that's guilty.
This whole city is guilty.
Stop!
You're a police officer
for god's sake!
You have to follow the law!
I don't have to do anything.
I am the law. I am judge...
jury...
and executioner!
Sentence served.
Ed!
- How'd she take it?
- What?
Everything is wonderful.
Isabella showed me
that I was worried over nothing.
I'm so happy for you.
But why are you back?
Well, she had to go
to her conference. I insisted.
You're a good man.
But you look done in.
I will hear all about it tomorrow.
Get some sleep.
You got to give her credit.
She fought for him.
Too bad she underestimated
her opponent.
- I'm assuming it's done.
- Yup.
Feel kind of bad though, boss.
I always liked librarians.
You?
What about poor Ed?
He'll be heartbroken.
Luckily, he has a shoulder to cry on.
Come on. Oh, no.
Oh, come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Help me! Help me! Somebody, help!
Oh, dear.
Jim, you and Mario
have a heart-to-heart?
Yeah. Where's Symon?
No luck. He must have skedaddled.
I thought he might be at the bar.
Look, keep a perimeter
in case he shows back up.
I'm gonna head to his house.
And Harvey, take it easy.
It's good to have you back again,
Jim.
I'm really glad.
- Captain, did you hear?
- Everything.
I saw Symon here earlier.
- You managed to pick him up?
- Not yet.
He must've skipped out
when we showed up. We'll get him.
Alvarez said you were bringing in
the guy who did Paulie Pennies?
Turns out to be a dead end.
I'll let you know when I find Symon.
Jim.
Things are going to change
around here.
You and I are gonna make
a difference in this city.
We're gonna clean it up.
Yes, sir.
Guilty, guilty, guilty.
Guilty.
Guilty, guilty.
- GCPD!
- Sir!
Dr. Symon.
Who did this?
Barnes.