- Previously on Gotham...
- You can trust me.
We don't work for you
- and we don't work with you.
- Your captain
says otherwise.
So, Penguin's guys
are gonna beat and torture
their way through the city?
Get off of him.
You better pray
I can clean up your
mess on this one, Harvey.
It has to be a trap.
Hey!
Oh, no, Patel.
The Demonz.
They have a chop shop across town.
Let's hit it.
We've got a business to run.
I came here with Grundy.
Make some money to get me smart again.
Hey, I'm looking for the
person in charge here.
You're looking at her.
Go get the doc.
Fight!
Grundy fight now?
Yes! Grundy Ed's best friend.
And now...
the most hated man in Gotham:
The Penguin!
I'm so happy to be here.
You love me. I knew you loved me.
You don't love me?
Get out of here.
You've asked for it.
I'm going to sic my lackeys onto you.
My hoods and the GCPD!
Get 'em, boys.
Get 'em!
You awful Penguin. You awful Penguin.
You've got to do what I want
or they're gonna enter your homes
and terrorize your families.
Get 'em! Get 'em!
You do what I say.
Grundy. Grundy.
- Let's see some blood!
- Yeah!
No! You leave me alone, you monster.
- Tear him apart!
Stupid, lame...
Birdbrain!
He'll never learn.
You can't mess with the Narrows!
It is time...
for the main event!
Get him, Grundy!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
A title defense.
No refs.
No rules.
No rules!
Our challenger:
Mr. Murder Face.
Yeah!
And our champeen...
Straight from the Slaughter Swamp,
it's Solomon Grundy.
They really ate it up tonight.
I think they hate
Penguin almost as much as I do.
You know what, I may or
may not find a cure for you.
At the rate you're going,
may not have a chance.
What does that mean?
You don't just have
these people laughing.
- You have them ready for a fight.
- So?
So? So, what happens
when Penguin hears about all this?
Well, let that bird waddle in here.
I have Grundy. I'm gonna be fine.
And what about them? Your fans?
Not my problem.
Ed, you've put yourself on
the front line of something.
- You can't just bail when fighting starts.
- Okay, Doctor.
If you would like to
stop hiding from your past
and do some leading, you go right ahead.
That's not what I'm here for.
Well, then, case closed.
Neither of us are willing
to put our necks out.
Oh!
Hey, Butch.
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah!
Stop hitting yourself!
Stop hitting yourself.
I love this.
I love it!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans
- TBS resynced by Se7enOfNin9
Congratulations, Captain Gordon.
A promotion.
Harvey Bullock is
captain of Gotham Central.
Bullock's lost the rank and file, Jim.
The debacle in the Narrows.
Teaming up with Penguin's goons.
Sending cops into the Pyg's trap.
You know, he's...
he's a disgrace.
What does that make you?
Excuse me?
Last time I checked, you signed over
the entire GCPD to Penguin.
Wholesale.
What does he think of this?
Well, perhaps I've earned
that kind of cynicism, Jim,
but I want to assure you,
with hand on heart,
that this has nothing
to do with Mr. Cobblepot.
I won't take Harvey's job.
Someone is going to.
And, trust me,
none of our other candidates
share your misgivings about Penguin.
Just take it with you.
When you decide, all you have to do
is sign on the dotted line,
and you'll be the new captain
of Gotham Central.
Nobody steals from
the Demonz, Mr. Penguin.
Why do I pony up for
a license if some crook
can just swoop in and rip off our swag?
Your swag might as well have been
a lollipop in a baby's hand.
You admit it. She
admits it, Mr. Penguin.
Oswald.
What say we resolve
this like professionals?
The ladies and I will take out
the rest of these so-called Demonz
and split their goods
with you fifty-fifty.
Uncivilized is what these girls are.
Outside the bounds
of a proper criminal society.
What?!
Repeat that for my guests.
Uh, Ed Nygma,
who-who owes his life
to Mr. Cobblepot's mercy,
is repaying that generosity
by aping his benefactor
in a crude commedia dell'arte.
What?
He is making fun of me
in a clown show
in the Narrows!
Pretty funny.
The Riddler's doing a Penguin act.
That is not his name.
His name is Ed.
Plain, dumb Ed.
And you don't know him,
so you don't get to laugh.
Well...
thank you, Oswald, for...
clearing our account.
Not cleared, Babs.
The debt you owe him,
you now owe me.
Of course. What'll it be?
Seeing as you love a good laugh,
I would like you to go to the Narrows
and see Ed's act for yourself.
Then I would like you
to bundle him up
and bring him back to me by nightfall.
We're not your toadies.
Dear child, what was that you said?
What do we get
if we bring you Nygma?
Very well.
In exchange, I will...
not set every criminal
in the city after you.
I will not let them cut out your eyes
and feed 'em to you,
along with your ears,
and then your noses,
and then your tongues.
That is what you get!
Acceptable?
Yes, Oswald.
That is acceptable.
- Well...
- Ladies.
Mr. Penn will put you in contact
with my Narrows informant.
If those three do not
have Ed in hand promptly,
you will go down there and
burn them all to cinders.
What about feeding them
their eyes and all that?
Trust me, it's a great idea
but far too messy to be practical.
So, give me the
scoop on this Cherry's joint.
It's mainly crazy prize fights.
Chain saw matches and stuff.
But back in the day
we'd settle our beefs in the ring.
Winner takes all.
The code of the Narrows.
Right. Well, I want to get in, grab Ed,
deliver him to his doom,
and then go find a martini.
Okay?
Hello? Earth to Tabby.
Sorry. Thinking about
getting my hands on him.
Yeah. As much as I hate
doing Penguin's dirty work,
this job is like a
little dream come true.
Gonna be Ed's nightmare.
Aren't we worried about
him setting a trap, though?
He's a genius.
Well, word is...
Ed lost a step when
Penguin put him on ice.
But we should be ready for anything.
You insist on persisting
in this misbehavior,
you leave me no choice
but to scold you.
You've asked for it!
I'm going to sic
my lackeys upon you. Get 'em, boys.
Get 'em.
Grundy! Grundy!
No! No, no, no, no! No!
Butch?
Stop hitting
yourself! Stop hitting yourself!
Butch.
It's Butch. Do you know what this means?
Yeah.
It means you owe me an
apology for electrocuting me.
I got to find a way to go talk to him.
Have fun.
Tell him it was nothing personal
when I shot him in the head.
Wow.
I have got to know what
is up with this outfit.
Grundy!
Grundy! Grundy! Grundy!
Could've sworn we had a job to do here.
- Grundy! Grundy! Grundy!
- Yeah, Grundy!
Morning, Harv.
Where have you been?
Ah, sorry. Got stuck in traffic.
What you got there?
It's the Bullethole Club today.
These are the slugs they pulled
from the wounded cops
in the Narrows raid.
It was the Pyg that set the trap.
But I was the one who
sent those cops in.
Yeah. You did.
But now we got to move on.
And we got to catch the Pyg
before he can hurt somebody else.
Yeah.
Right.
Captain Bullock. Detective.
What's the word, Lucius?
The word is "absence," as in
all of Professor Pyg's
crime scenes demonstrate
a marked absence of
useful physical evidence.
How is that possible?
He's a loony.
But a crafty one.
We have to dig deeper,
try and get ahead of
whatever he's planning.
I'm at your disposal.
Hey, Jim.
Uh, about the Bullethole Club today.
I'd really appreciate it
if you could be there, too.
- It'd just help me a lot...
- Of course.
I know you have my back, partner.
Of course, Harv. I got your back.
The Bullethole Club?
Cops shot in the line of duty.
New members joining today.
How's that work?
It's unofficial. Little
ceremony at a bar.
Commanding officer hands them
the bullet they were shot with.
This batch, cops wounded in Pyg's trap.
And Harvey has to
give 'em their bullets?
Yeah. Including the officer he shot.
No wonder he wants a friend there.
Yeah. No wonder.
Leave it to Ed Nygma to
find a way to turn his idiocy
into a tool for revenge.
And everything was running so tidily.
Now I have nothing but headaches.
No one appreciates how hard
it is to be a crime lord.
I did actually spend my
childhood being raised by one.
My very point.
In fact,
I thought we would have lunch together
and talk over the vagaries
of this capricious calling.
I'd love to help, but I
have to see the caterer
for the orphanage fund-raiser.
Of course.
I can't expect you to
be at my beck and call.
You need a different source
of relaxation, Oswald.
Um...
You need chickens.
I'm sorry?
Do you remember my father's chickens?
I seem to recall the don's
predilection for poultry.
He understood that life
couldn't just be about business.
When his troubles were greatest,
he spent time with his birds.
You think I need...
chickens?
An interest outside the
business. Give it some thought.
We'll talk about it when I get back.
Chickens.
Chick, chick, chickens.
Loser!
- Wedgie!
- Aw!
Aw! That must've hurt!
Grab him! Martin!
Squeeze his arm harder!
Boy!
Come here this instant.
What do you think you're doing?
You cannot do things like that.
Your enemies
will know it was you.
Grundy! Grundy!
Butch.
You're alive.
Huh?
Oh, Butch.
What happened to you?
Guess who.
Psycho-killer stalker?
Got it in one.
Please.
If you were gonna pop,
you'd have done it already.
Whew, that felt good.
Been waiting a long time to do that.
Other cheek?
I'm good, thanks.
So what are you doing
down here, Barbara?
This is a low-rent neighborhood for you.
Yeah. If it wasn't for Penguin,
you wouldn't catch me dead
- in a place like this.
- Oh.
You're working as Penguin's flunky.
That suits you.
Yes, and you seem to be thriving
with your current life choices.
We don't all make decisions
based on what it can get us.
There are other people in the world.
Wow.
Sexy and self-righteous.
What does Jim think of this new you?
Jim who?
Well, I have to go see a man
about a kidnapping. But this...
has been interesting.
Toodles, poodle.
Kidnapping. Oh, crap.
You play
a great Penguin, mister.
Yeah. Sure, sure. Thanks, kid.
Oh, crud.
I thought you were supposed to be smart.
Relax, Jim, no one followed me.
I have Oswald wrapped around my finger.
If you have such a good
grip on him, explain that.
Why would he want me
promoted? What's his plan?
Oswald has nothing to do with this.
The commissioner and the mayor
can feel the winds changing,
and they want to be out
ahead of it before it blows.
It was you.
You put them up to this.
You must have made a
hell of a contribution
to get the mayor to defy Penguin.
No contribution necessary, Jim.
Just the Falcone name and...
everything that it implies.
Well, I won't do it.
Not like this.
And not at Harvey's expense.
Harvey is weak.
How much longer do you
plan on propping him up?
And how many more cops need to
die because of his incompetence?
I need to go.
And you need to stop pretending
like you're not taking that job.
I'm not pretending.
So you say, Jim,
but I don't see you rushing
to throw that piece of paper
in the trash.
Come see me tonight.
After you take command.
We will celebrate.
Revenge is never as simple
as a mere tit for a tat.
Revenge must be specific in nature. Now,
when you imagine revenge against
your two juvenile tormentors,
what do you see?
That might be a little overly ambitious.
We must be crafty.
For instance,
friendship can be an
especially deadly tactic.
How do you think you might
use friendship to drive a wedge
between your two antagonists?
"They're both flunking math."
And you, I imagine,
are very good at math?
Excellent.
Tell me more.
Psst.
Hey, Martin!
Thank you.
What's wrong, Martin?
Who did that to you?
Hey.
Why you picking on Martin?
You like that dummy so
much, go play with him.
He's not a dummy!
Yes, he is.
Well done.
Feels good, does it not?
Minions are so much better than friends.
"But I'm your..."
The greatest friend I ever had
turned into my worst enemy.
Shun friendship.
You and I...
we're more than friends.
We're conspirators.
Are you not gonna fight back?
Peekaboo.
Well, look at the little go-getter.
Yeah. Well, you and Tabby
decided to freak out,
so someone had to be the professional.
Teenagers, Ed.
Don't you love 'em?
Do you remember anything, Butch?
Do you remember anything about us?
Doesn't this mean anything to you?
Ed!
Butch!
Tell zombie Butch to back off.
Grundy kill everyone!
Butch!
Ed is not your friend.
Rip 'em to pieces!
Butch!
All right. Everybody just take it easy.
Selina, what are you
doing with these two?
Looking for trouble.
Well, you found plenty
of it, trying to take Ed.
Let him go.
You're such a bleeding heart, Lee.
I thought you'd change, but turns out,
just got a new hairdo.
Code of the Narrows.
Let's settle it in the ring.
Champion against champion.
The winner would take Ed.
So your best fighter
against my fighter?
Yeah, let's do that.
Honk-honk. Honk-honk.
You Narrows trash
have been very, very naughty.
You've been hiding someone from me.
Don't listen to him.
He's not my friend.
No, Ed. No one's gonna save you.
Ed. Grundy.
No one can save you. Save me!
Oh, no. Help.
Help. Save me.
Ladies and Grundy fans.
Tonight is a special edition
of fight night.
A good old Narrows grudge match.
Winner takes...
me.
And featuring your champeen
Solomon Grundy...
versus...
Tabby...
the Tigress.
Tabs, I know this was my idea, but...
No, it's okay.
Butch is still in there. I know he is.
He loves me too much to hurt me.
Grundy kill!
Babe, I love your faith,
but I really think you should take this.
No. He won't hurt me.
I'll just choke him out, no problem.
Tabitha and Grundy were lovers
before he got this way.
What if he goes easy on her?
Grundy will win.
Not that it makes a difference, anyway.
What does that mean?
The Penguin wants Ed.
He's gonna get him.
Come on, Butch.
I know you could never forget me.
You're still in there, I know it.
Grundy!
Tabby, come on,
Tabs. Come on, get up.
Get up.
Tabby, get up.
No. No, Butch.
No, Butch!
Tabs!
Oh!
Hey, Butch.
Tabby?
Oh!
Butch?
No! No!
- I'll get you one more.
- Yeah.
I don't know what to tell you.
Come on, buddy.
You Detective Gordon?
Yeah.
Harvey said as how I
should give this to you.
Said you'd know what to do with it.
When was he here?
Uh, a couple hours ago.
Before you all started coming in here.
Thanks.
Get up! Come on!
Come on, Butch. Come on, baby.
Wake up. Come on, Butch.
- Tabitha, we've got to go, now.
- Come on, baby.
Ladies, let's amscray.
- Come on. Come on.
- I'll come back for you, Butch.
What happened to
the code of the Narrows?
Give me up, Bra-Bra.
You're getting out
of here empty-handed.
In the name of Penguin,
everybody back the hell off.
Well,
look at that... cavalry.
Not so fast.
Boss gave you a deadline.
You missed it.
So what? We got Ed.
We are literally champions here.
What you are is four
courses of barbecue.
Crispy skin.
Grundy, wake up.
Grundy!
Get up, big guy, come on.
Grundy kill!
What's the matter, gruesome?
Afraid of fire?
Come on, Bridgit.
Don't do this. You're from the Narrows.
Yeah. And I couldn't
be happier to be out.
Penguin's right about this place.
It's a sewer.
Only way to kill the stink
is to burn it.
Hey, Firefly.
You're the only thing
that stinks around here.
You know what you've done?
Firefly's Penguin's enforcer.
And who's the one who got
Firefly down here, Cherry?
She informed on Ed to Penguin.
What?!
- You're a snitch, Cherry.
- Shut up.
You're over. It's done.
Shut up.
This is my club. It's my turf.
You guys just do as you're
told like the scum you are.
They're the ones that are the problem.
They work for Penguin.
Oh!
I would like to announce
that we just quit working for Penguin.
Yeah! Do it!
God, they sure love
their cold-blooded
murder down here, huh?
Yeah, well, we better split
before they decide they want more.
Hey.
It's okay, big guy.
Fire lady... she can't hurt you.
Ah. Grundy safe.
Where were you, Harvey?
Hey, Jim.
I was just having a...
little drinky-poo.
Why don't you join me?
Not right now.
Come on, Jim. Don't be like that.
Come on, sit down and
have a drink with me.
Those cops were waiting for you.
Yeah, to spit in my face.
If that's what they wanted to do,
you owed it to them to be there,
to stand in front of 'em,
look each one in the eye.
If you'd have done that...
maybe you could have
gotten their respect.
I don't deserve their respect.
Jim, I shot Officer Patel.
What the hell was I supposed to do?
Stand in front of her
and hand her the bullet
that I shot her with,
that came from my gun?
That's the job.
Take responsibility for what happens
to your cops... that's the job.
Oh.
So now...
you're telling me what the job is?
Yeah.
Well, today, Jim...
I just couldn't do the job.
So I sent you
because I knew...
you could.
It's not good enough.
Not today.
They needed you there.
Well...
ain't nothing I can do about it now.
You got a pen?
For what?
Harvey Bullock, you
are relieved of duty.
As of this moment, I'm assuming
the captaincy of Gotham Central.
Well, well.
Look who finally got
what he always wanted.
But what I'm wondering is,
what did you have to do to get it?
All I did was my job, same as you.
Nothing in Gotham is free...
Captain Gordon.
You just better hope you can
pay up when your bill's due.
And it'll come due.
Huh? Now you try.
Uh...
Ah. You've met Martin, I see.
Shh. He's practicing.
No. It's up.
Upward, Martin, so that way you drive
the blade under the
ribs and into the heart.
Oswald?
Entirely theoretically
speaking, of course.
Mr. Penn?
Urgent matters, Mr. Cobblepot.
It seems that Ms. Kean and
her associates have failed
to retrieve Mr. Nygma.
Did you dispatch Firefly?
I did.
And Ms. Firefly was
herself, in turn, disabled.
What?!
There's more.
Yes?!
The mayor,
at his own discretion, has seen fit
to promote Detective Gordon
to the rank... of captain.
That is...
That is... quite a lot
to go awry in one day.
Very good, Mr. Cobblepot.
You see, Oswald?
Business is not the end-all of life.
There are other rewards to be had.
Companionship, peace of mind.
Friendship.
Oh, I have to get back to the estate.
I still have so much to
do for the fund-raiser.
Will you be joining me later for dinner?
I think not.
Martin needs some more practice.
Okay.
Martin,
remind me.
What did we learn today?
What did we learn about friendship?
Exactly. Sometimes,
if you're not very careful,
friendship can blind you
to what is staring
you right in the face.
"Hey, Firefly.
You're the only thing
that stinks around here."
I get melodramatic under pressure.
How you feeling, big fella?
- Grundy confused.
- Yeah.
Tell me about it.
What's with them?
They're, uh...
They're acknowledging their new leader.
Well, like I said, they love you.
Uh, Lee, I'm supposed
to be the stupid one.
You heal their children.
You stitch up their warriors.
You've slain a fire-breathing monster,
and you helped topple the queen.
This is your turf now.
No, no, no, no, no, I am not a leader.
Okay, well, if you don't do it,
somebody else will,
probably worse than Cherry.
Where do I start?
I don't know. Just...
make 'em happy, give 'em
something to cheer for.
Drinks on the house.
Good move.
Why, Captain Gordon,
you came to celebrate after all.
I'm not here to celebrate.
What's wrong? I made
you captain, didn't I?
You made me?
Is that what you think?
Jim.
You can toy with Penguin all you want,
but I am not your puppet.
No, you're not.
You're my partner.
Your partner?
I just stuck a knife
in my partner's back.
A mercy killing if you ask me.
Grow up. You wanted
a gangster to help
you get rid of Penguin.
This is what that help looks like.
Harvey.... had... to go.
I don't need your help anymore.
I think it's time you left Gotham.
I'm not going anywhere, Jim.
I came to restore the Falcone name,
and that's exactly what I'm going to do.
So, do you want to come in
and celebrate... Captain?
Think I'll stay out
here where I can breathe.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
TBS resync by Se7enOfNin9