Previously on Gotham...
Listen to the watch.
Its ticking synchronizes
with your heartbeat.
Stand upon the back of the chair.
So you could get him to do
anything you wanted?
I want you to find my sister.
Her condition...
Some poison in her blood.
I announce my candidacy for mayor.
Hugo Strange made another you.
- He's gone.
- He cut his hair, too...
To look more like you.
- Does Alfred know you have his car?
- Would you like to go for a ride?
The ticking synchronizes
with your heartbeat.
Deep down, you want to die, Jim.
- Step off the ledge...
- Stop!
You, you don't understand.
My, my brother will find out I'm
here, and he'll come for me.
Nothing will stop him.
This is the brother that took you
to Strange to try and fix you?
What? No.
Jervis kept me a prisoner most
of my life,
and when I finally managed to escape,
I ran as far away
from him as I could.
And landed in Gotham.
It seemed like a good place to hide.
Until Strange found me
and locked me in Indian Hill.
I'll admit, not the best luck.
For you or your future landlord.
That was an accident.
The infecting part,
or the lighting him on fire part?
I'm not a monster!
But if you want to see one,
just wait until my brother
comes for me.
You don't know what he's capable of.
This isn't over.
For either of us.
It's perfect.
Oh, my sister used to love
amusement parks.
The rides. The food.
The tents with amazing acts.
That's why I became a performer.
Are you a family man?
Yes. I am a family man.
The day I lost her was the saddest
of my life.
The only thing that got me
through, that kept me sane...
was the hope of one day
being together again.
Reunited.
And if all goes well
that day is today.
Of course, a reunion like this
needs to be a private affair.
You understand.
It's Election Day in Gotham
with former mayor, Aubrey James,
and former criminal kingpin,
Oswald Cobblepot,
running toe to toe for the hearts
and minds of Gotham.
Why don't you take care of that?
Appreciate it.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- To you too.
- Butch. Your phone call.
I must say, you are looking quite
the dapper fellow.
Hold on.
I had to guess on the jacket size.
I hope it fits.
Perfectly...
I cannot thank you enough.
It's just a suit...
No. No, if it weren't for you,
I would still be falling asleep
to the screams of the insane.
It becomes almost a white noise
after a while, doesn't it?
It does.
I do believe, Oswald,
Arkham has made us both stronger.
I couldn't agree more.
Which is why I had
our release certificates framed.
A reminder of past struggles
and new beginnings.
If I didn't know better, I'd accuse
you of being a sentimentalist.
Guilty.
You all set, boss? Busy day today.
Who were those people
you were speaking with?
- Don't worry about it.
- Come now, Butch, play nice.
We're all on the same team here,
right?
My team.
Yeah. Sure. Whatever you say.
You keep your nose out
of my business.
Yeah. Sure.
Whatever you say.
Why is it that every time something
hits the fan around here
I inevitably find you
at the center of it?
I was just working a job.
Her brother asked me to find her.
Yeah, you're some sort of PI now?
Is that it?
- I'm whatever pays the bills.
- Right.
What do we know about this
girl's blood?
Not much. She claims infecting
the landlord was an accident.
Have Thompkins draw some samples.
See if she can find out what
we're dealing with here.
And pick up the brother
for questioning.
Any idea where we might find him?
No. But when I do, I'll let you know.
We have some unfinished business.
Not anymore.
This is an active investigation.
You go anywhere near him,
I'll have you arrested.
For what?
No law against two private
citizens having a chat.
I'll come by later to pick up
my check.
I bet that I'd make a kick-ass PI.
Get out.
Have you had this condition
since birth?
Tell me about it.
If a person comes into contact
with my blood it changes them.
It affects every person differently.
My brother believes it brings out
a person's true nature.
Is your brother infected?
Is that why you're
so terrified of him?
Jervis isn't infected.
He believes we're connected.
Two sides of the same coin.
My way is the blood and his the mind.
Hypnosis.
It goes way beyond that.
He preys on fear, anger, regret.
And if he gets in your mind...
you're doomed.
Vote for Oswald Cobblepot.
- Your next Mayor of Gotham.
- Here you go. Cobblepot for Mayor.
- And Make Gotham Safe Again!
- Good, Sir. Sir, vote for Cobblepot.
Vote for Oswald Cobblepot
your next Mayor of Gotham...
You are so very tired of life,
aren't you?
Do you hear my watch ticking?
Hard road for you, Jim Gordon.
Listen closer.
You are so very tired of life,
aren't you?
Now you can rest, Jim.
Hey, pal!
You got a death wish
or something?
Right. Yes, sir, will do.
Thank you very much.
Goodbye.
Well, that was the impound yard
from downtown.
It appear the Rolls was towed only
this morning, Master Bruce.
This doesn't make any sense.
Why would he leave?
But he cut his hair to look more
like you, if that's even possible.
You think he went to the city
to pretend to be me?
Yeah, absolutely, bloody-yes.
So where would he go?
Take in a show? Do a little bit
of shopping? Have a facial?
I mean, where do pain-resistant
clones of multi-billionaire
teenagers normally go?
- Alfred.
- Well, I don't know.
Oh, the car was found
at Eleventh and Dillon.
- Wasn't it?
- That's in the Narrows.
So, I suppose, we should be thankful
there's anything left to tow.
What the Dickens was he doing
down there in the first place?
Selina.
Eleventh and Dillon
is near her apartment.
Sorry again for the way I acted
when you came by yesterday.
Any word on your friend Ivy?
No.
I even braved a beat-down
from Sonny to see if she
was growing magic mushrooms
for him again.
- Magic what?
- Mushrooms?
Sonny Gilzean?
Pounded you to within
an inch of your life?
Yeah. Sonny. Right.
Well, this is it.
Time to earn a living.
- You work here?
- No. I rob here.
What?
The Bang, Bang Room
is a betting parlor.
Should be flush today
with the mayor's race.
Meet me around back in five minutes.
Selina.
Yeah.
Pay up.
Hey, I got twenty five points for it.
Yeah, that's true.
Oswald Cobblepot.
Hey. That guy at the end of the bar
said you're buying the place a round.
What?
Oh, and your mom sucks.
Or something.
Really?
Hey. Wise guy.
He's your drink.
Get him on the face and...
Come on, you messed up the face!
Who the hell are you?
Sorry... My first day.
Can you help me find the cherries?
No? Probably behind the bar. Right.
Oh, I'll go check.
Hey, Squirrel, what's the odds
of a person getting out of here
in one piece?
Not good, boss.
My beloved mother always
believed in me.
Even when I doubted myself,
she held firm.
Seeing all of your bright
faces reminds me
that there is nothing you cannot
do if you put your mind to it.
And when I am Mayor,
I believe...
no, I know...
that together we will
Make Gotham Safe Again!
Excuse me.
- Are you on the election board?
- Yeah.
I work for Mr. Cobblepot.
He just wanted me to
confirm what Butch gave you.
May I? Thank you.
It's all there. Thank you.
Follow him for the rest of the day.
Don't let him leave your sight.
Well, look who's back.
I saw you last night.
You didn't even say hi. Rude.
I need to find Jervis Tetch.
Oh, you mean The Great Jervis Tetch
Hypnotist Extraordinaire!
Can you believe it actually says
that on his business card?
His number's been disconnected.
Where is he?
I don't know. Magic shop? Bunny farm?
Some place where everyone
wears top hats and drinks tea?
Barbara.
You know? I'm not sure I like this
new thing of you storming
in here every time
you need something.
It's almost like we're married.
Scary thought.
I need a favor.
Then you must be monumentally
screwed.
What happened?
Did he hypnotize you?
Make you bark like a dog?
He's dangerous, Barbara.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Okay.
He came in here earlier.
Said he wanted to hire some muscle.
- "Muscle"?
- Yeah.
For some performance he's planning.
Said he needed them to have flair.
What'd you tell him?
It's Gotham, baby.
We've all got flair!
Thanks.
Always a help.
Excellent!
Deever and Dumfree, I presume?
The Terrible Tweeds.
Your reputation precedes you.
And you are?
Jervis Tetch.
I have a job that might
suit your particular skills.
My sister has been taken by the GCPD.
I need to get her back.
You wanna break someone
out of the GCPD?
Not someone. My sister.
I assumed men like yourselves
understood the bond of family.
What's in it for us?
Does he ever speak?
Regardless, if you'll do the courtesy
of listening to me,
I think you'll find I can be
quite persuasive.
Place is packed to the gills.
It's running two-to-one for Penguin.
Sounds like you're busy.
Maybe I should go, huh?
No. This won't take long.
I hate people with sticky fingers.
Okay, wait. What do you,
what do you need? Huh?
Money? Information?
I could be useful.
Oh, you will be.
You'll send a message.
But maybe...
I don't got to do this?
That maybe you learned your lesson?
Yeah! Totally! I...
You're screwing with me, aren't you?
Yeah. Do it.
Bruce?
Let's go.
And although some have criticized
Mr. Cobblepot
for running a campaign based
largely on name-calling
and fear mongering.
His simple message
of "Make Gotham Safe Again" has...
You believe Penguin
might win this thing?
This city is going to hell in
a hand basket.
You okay?
Fine.
I assume you didn't come here
to ask about my health.
- I need to speak with Alice Tetch.
- No.
Five minutes. That's all I'm asking.
She's scheduled to be moved
to a facility upstate.
I'm sure she'll have plenty
of time then.
This can't wait.
What's going on?
You can talk to me, son.
Her brother, I had a run in
with him last night.
I think he may have done
something to me.
Like what?
I don't know.
I'm having thoughts.
Look, you've caught some bad breaks.
Blackgate. Lee.
I don't know what happened
when you went to see her,
but I can take a pretty good guess.
But at some point,
you're gonna have to make peace
with the decisions you've made.
And what if I can't?
Take it from me, you don't wanna
wake up one day
and realize that 20 years
has gone by.
We're keeping Alice in interrogation.
Five minutes.
What was that back there?
- What?
- You.
Remind me to give props
to Alfred on his training.
I did not think you had that in you.
Me neither. You okay?
You?
A little light headed.
Bruce...
- Oh! You need a hospital.
- No. No hospitals.
- Are those scars?
- Nothing, they're nothing.
- You're not Bruce.
- Selina, just...
- Just, just listen to...
- What the hell are you?
- I won't hurt you. Just let me...
Just let me explain.
I assume you know Butch
is paying campaign officials
to buy the election.
You don't approve?
My dear, Ed, this is Gotham.
This is how things are done.
And in theory, I support that.
But, Oswald, do you see how
these people are cheering for you.
Yes, they do seem very excited.
You can win this on your own.
Why risk it? There is no upside.
I want this, Ed. I want this like
I've never wanted anything.
I know, which is why you need
to call off Butch.
Mr. Penguin...
Hello, there.
I wanted to thank you for getting rid
of all the monsters.
Do you see?
People look at me differently now.
For the first time
in my life I feel wanted.
Nice doing business with you.
And how do you feel now?
I feel like I've misjudged someone
who was supposed to be my friend.
I am your friend.
I can't be bought
but I can be stolen with a glance.
I'm worthless to one
but priceless to two.
- What am I?
- I don't care!
I do not need
a stupid riddle, right now.
I know what I want.
I want to be Mayor.
Stay out of it, Ed.
I'm warning you.
I need to find your brother.
You turn me in
and now you want my help?
I was hoping we could help
each other.
He's still in your head, isn't he?
- How do I stop it?
- I don't know.
Most of the time, once
the trance is broken that's it.
You should have been fine the
moment you stepped off the ledge.
Then why is it still happening?
Jervis has tapped into something
you're struggling with.
Something a part of you
would do anything not to face.
Then give me something to fight
this until I find him.
There's usually a trigger
that brings on the hypnotic state.
What's the last thing you remember?
He pulled out his watch.
Asked if I could hear it ticking.
That's it then.
His watch, anything resembling
the ticking will trigger the impulse.
He's made you a prisoner
in your own skin.
He did it to you.
When we were kids.
At first, he did it
to control me, keep me with him.
But then he started putting other
thoughts in my head.
Thoughts a...
Thoughts a brother should never have.
That's why I wanted to kill him.
I won't go back to him.
Not ever.
Yeah! Everybody!
Come on.
Ladies and Gentlemen.
It is with great excitement
that we welcome you to our show!
That's him. He's come for me.
- I'd like to introduce you...
- I'm getting you out of here.
...to wrestling's most notorious
family here to entertain and amaze!
The Terrible Tweeds!
Let the show begin!
Harvey, look out!
Hello, sis.
We both know you can't kill me.
Not until I remove that nagging
little impulse I planted.
Turn around. Hands in the air.
Alice, go! Now!
Goodbye, Mr. Gordon.
- No!
- I doubt I'll be seeing you again.
Get off me! Let go! Mr. Gordon!
It really doesn't hurt?
No.
Whatever they did to me
at Indian Hill I don't feel pain.
So why'd they make a Bruce Wayne
look-a-like anyhow?
I don't know.
I didn't even know I looked like him
until a few days ago.
I went to his house thinking he might
have some answers about who I am.
He didn't.
So you ran off
and pretended to be him.
Why?
- You'll laugh.
- I doubt it.
Neither of you has a sense of humor.
When you came to see him the other
night I was watching from the hall.
I saw the way you looked at him.
No one's ever looked at me like that.
I wanted to know how it felt.
You should have your eyes checked.
I didn't look at him like anything.
All I mean
that I've never had a friend.
I've never had anyone.
You have no idea what it's like
to spend your whole life alone.
You're actually better off.
People are overrated.
You don't believe that.
My mom left
before I could ride a bike.
Never knew my dad.
I had two friends.
One ended up barbecued,
and the other's
at the bottom of the river.
What about Bruce Wayne?
Forget about him.
He's even more screwed up than you.
You're more normal than you think.
Hey. You're up.
What's going on?
Barnes told me what happened
during the attack.
Nothing happened.
I heard the tape from the
interrogation room with Alice.
- Listen to me...
- Whatever Jervis is doing to you...
You need to uncuff me.
I can't do that.
I don't know what I would
do if something happened to you.
You'd be fine.
Do you really believe that?
You seemed to have moved on okay.
Yes, I moved on, Jim.
What choice did I have?
I went through the most painful
period of my life alone.
I cried myself to sleep every night
and like an idiot, I would wake up
thinking, hoping, that the next day
you would show up at my door.
But you never did.
Mario was there for me
when I needed someone.
He was there as I tried to put
myself back together.
But I'm the one who doesn't care?
After everything that's happened,
you really have nothing to say to me?
The past is the past and there's
nothing I can do to change that.
Alice told me that her brother
preys on anger and regret.
I really don't want that to be
all that's left of us.
You mean all that's left of me.
Barnes asked me to put you on
a 48 hour suicide watch.
I've already signed off on it.
I know that we can't change the past,
but there's a difference between
moving on and letting go.
Most of you guys have been
with me for a while.
You know me.
And I know Gotham
like the back of my hand.
Penguin, when he's Mayor,
boys, I promise you...
we are gonna run this city. Huh?
- To Butch!
- Hey.
- What?
I lost track of the guy in
the glasses.
Nygma?
That skinny loon gave you the slip?
Yeah.
No. No, no, that's not possible.
Let's go! We gotta go, guys!
Two of your brothers are dead.
The other two escaped
with Alice and Jervis.
And I need to know where
they're taking her.
Jervis gains a sister
and you lose two brothers?
That don't seem too fair?
I bet you were close growing up, huh?
Wrestling around the house.
Driving your mom crazy.
Five little kids all dreaming
of stardom.
Yeah.
I'm a fan.
My dad used to always take me
down to the wrestling matches
at the Garden.
I also happen
to know most luchadores...
request to be buried
in their masks...
...as a sign of honor and respect.
I really, really hope that wasn't
the case with your brothers.
This freak, Jervis, did something
to my friend.
And I need him to undo it.
Where are they taking her?
Okay! Okay! I'll tell you!
Well...
do you like it?
I know you were surprised
to see me last night...
And I want you to know
that I forgive you.
For everything.
But, I want you to understand
the consequences
if you ever leave me again.
I need you to understand
how important you are to me.
Don't. Please.
Now, you might feel a little prick.
Your escorts agreed to take
a long lunch.
- You know where they took Alice?
- Yeah.
But it's only a matter of time
until Barnes finds out
and sends in the cavalry.
- How'd you find me?
- Lee.
- Lee?
- Yeah!
She also told me if you check
out on my watch it's my head.
Well, I guess you're gonna have
to trust me.
Remember to chisel
that into my tombstone.
Let's go.
Thanks, Francisco!
- Took you long enough.
- Where's Selina?
She's not at her squat.
If you did anything...
- She's fine.
- Where is she!
She left a little while ago.
I don't know where she went.
I take you in
and this is the thanks I get?
You run around with Selina,
pretending to be me?
Is that why you're angry?
Because I was pretending to be you,
or that I spent the day with Selina?
For someone who has everything, you
have no idea what you actually want.
Or maybe, you're just too
scared to take it.
At least I know who I am.
Cool your boots, Master Bruce.
Let's all just take a breath,
shall we?
Don't worry.
You won't be seeing me anymore.
Neither will she.
I don't know why I was created,
but I know I don't belong in Gotham.
Say goodbye to Selina for me?
And thank her for the kiss.
What're you going to use that for?
Oh, I imagine I'll...
mix it into some public
drinking fountain.
Create a few dozen monsters.
Please, Jervis. Please.
I'll do whatever you want.
You will now.
Because you know the price
other people will pay if you don't.
I don't know what
I would ever do if I lost you.
That connection.
It keeps me sane.
It always has.
Tetch! Jervis!
Don't move!
Mr. Gordon.
I can't say I'm entirely surprised.
So stubborn.
Let her go, now!
You know I can't do that, but if you
let me leave with my dear sister,
my dear Alice, then I'll free you
from that nasty little impulse.
Maybe you can live a long, happy...
Well, a long life.
Let her go and you live.
That's the deal.
One question...
Do you hear that?
Jim!
We both know what you really want.
I saw it in your eyes
the first time we met.
You want to be free.
Free from the pain.
And you can be.
Stop fighting and let go.
Past is the past.
There's nothing
I can do to change that.
There's a difference between
moving on and letting go.
No!
Well, well, Mr. Gordon breaks
my spell!
I dare say it's time we bid
this foul city our good-bye.
- No!
- Alice!
I'll never go with you!
Why do you say such things?
We belong together.
You know that. I love you.
- You're insane!
- Oh, no!
No!
You killed her!
You want to explain yourself?
I was following a lead.
You were following some misguided
notion about friendship.
James Gordon is gonna
get you killed one day.
Do you get that?
Maybe.
But until that day, I will never
turn my back on him.
The night that all of Gotham
has been waiting for.
Final results should
be coming in shortly...
This is it.
The moment I've been waiting for.
Indeed.
You! You, you ruined everything!
Butch! Release him this instant!
What is going on?
I'll tell you what's going on.
He just cost you the election.
He went to every district official
and took the money back.
Said you wanted to run
a clean election!
Tell me this is not true.
I'm afraid Butch is right. For once.
Why?
After everything I've done for you.
Everything we could have
done together.
You betrayed me.
Butch...
Give me one reason why I shouldn't
let Butch kill you where you stand.
Well, there are
about thirty witnesses.
I don't care!
And there's that...
In what can only be viewed
as a seismic shift
even by Gotham standards,
former underworld kingpin,
Oswald Cobblepot, has won
the mayor's office by a landslide...
momentum based largely on
his outspoken criticism...
I still won?
...of how city officials
and the GCPD mishandled
They really want me as Mayor?
Yes.
I can't be bought but I can be
stolen with one glance.
I'm worthless to one
but priceless two.
Cobblepot! Cobblepot!
They love me.
If you would have bought the election
you would have never known.
And now you do.
Feels good, doesn't it?
How did you know I would win?
I believe in you, Oswald.
Even when you don't believe
in yourself.
You!
You never believed I could win
this election on my own!
I think maybe you're not cut out
for this after all.
What? You've gotta be kidding me.
This guy...
Don't worry!
I still need someone to crack skulls.
Come, Ed.
We have plans to make.
You think we'll ever see him again?
Well, that I very much doubt,
Master Bruce.
I reckon he is gonna try
and get as far away from Gotham
as he possibly can.
I still wonder why Hugo Strange
made him.
Long lonely nights in the laboratory,
probably needed someone to talk to.
Or some other, nefarious reason.
Perhaps.
There is one thing...
Yes, Master Bruce?
Do you think Selina really
kissed him?
Oh, bloody hell.
I mean, you've had training
in interrogation right?
- You can tell when someone's lying.
- I'm not...
You know, I'm not gonna
have this conversation.
And if she did kiss him, do you think
she thought he was me?
Good night, Master Bruce.
I bet she thought it was me.
Hey.
Hi.
You're here late.
The Tweeds really
did a number on this place.
Guess I'm Medical Examiner
slash-medic.
Slash-resident-therapist.
I wanted to thank you
for telling Bullock where to find me.
I heard about what happened
with Alice. You okay?
- Yeah.
- No. I mean, are you okay?
Whatever Jervis did to me,
it's over now.
I'm glad.
Guess I should get going.
Lee?
There's something I need to tell you.
Something I should have told you
the moment I saw you back in Gotham.
- Everything you've said today...
- I'm sorry about that.
Don't.
You were right.
And after everything
that happened today.
This is harder than I thought.
What is it, Jim?
I'm happy for you.
You are?
Trying to be.
Maybe we can start there?
Yeah. I think we can do that.
Bruce Wayne?
- No.
- But you could be.
In fact, you could be so much more.
Who are you?
You might think
of us as your parents.
We've been looking for you
for a long time.
It is with a humble heart
that I accept the trust placed
in me by this great city
to become your Mayor.
The people have spoken,
and I have heard their call!
- Yeah.
- That's right!
And as my first act as Mayor,
I would like to introduce you
to my Chief of Staff.
Mr. Edward Nygma!
Congratulations!
No.