COBBLEPOT:
There's a war coming, a terrible war.
There will be chaos.
Rivers of blood in the streets. I know it.
I can see it coming.
FISH: It's time. Somebody has to take over,
it might as well be me.
[SCREAMS]
- My name's James Gordon. I'm a detective.
- My name's Bruce Wayne.
I promise I will find the man who did this.
Stop or I'll shoot!
He was framed to cover up for the real killer.
Don't ever come back to Gotham.
MONTOYA: He's killed a man
on the orders of Carmine Falcone...
...biggest crime boss in Gotham.
The death of the Waynes would bring
troubled times for our family and Gotham.
The Maroni family senses weakness.
Jim, it's for you.
BARBARA:
Jim.
Hello, James. Old friend.
- You must be Barbara.
- Yes, please come in.
COBBLEPOT:
James, hi.
I'm Peter. Peter Humboldt.
Heh. Lovely to meet you at last.
You're even more beautiful than I imagined.
Shush. Nice to meet you, Peter.
I never meet Jim's friends.
He never tells me anything.
- Men.
- Don't I know.
- Would you like a drink?
- No. Uh...
He's a work friend. It's a work thing.
I'm just recently back in Gotham
and I had an idea to pop by.
Out of the blue.
But now is clearly not a good time.
I'll walk you out.
I told you never to come back here.
I know. I know, I-- I apologize.
But I just wanted to speak with you.
No. If Falcone finds out you're alive,
he'll kill us both.
I got no place else to go.
Gotham is my home.
I should have killed you.
I should put a bullet in your head right now.
And you would have every right to do so.
But you won't, Jim Gordon.
You're a good man.
You may very well be the last good man
in Gotham. That's why I want to help you.
- I don't want your help.
- No, no, but you need it.
That vile creature Fish Mooney...
...Don Falcone, the police.
Not even your own partner trusts you.
They will always hide the truth from you.
But not me.
Never.
- You saved my life.
- God knows I wish I hadn't.
Kill me now. Or trust me.
I told you there's a war coming, Jim.
There will be so many deaths. So many.
You wanna save Gotham?
I can help you. I can be your secret agent.
Until Falcone finds out you're alive.
Nobody looks for a dead man. Hm?
This war, what are you talking about?
Why will there be a war?
Uh, as you know,
war is just politics by other means.
And isn't politics just money? Talking?
Talking about what?
Arkham, of course.
MAN 1: Ready for some prime rib tonight?
MAN 2: I am, sir.
MAN 3:
Excuse me.
Councilman Jenkins?
- Can I help you?
- Yes, uh, I'm one of your constituents.
Voted for you every time.
Thank you very much, my friend.
I don't want to take up too much of your time.
I just want to show you something.
I'm always happy to help constituents,
but perhaps you can come by my office.
Sir, please. Just one second.
Now, I got the idea for this years ago.
Designed and built it myself.
Here. Take a look
Go ahead. You just put your eye
on the end there.
That's it.
- What is that thing?
- You'll see.
[GRUNTS]
No, no, no.
You're next.
[YELLING]
Honestly, sir, I really did vote for you.
Hey, I'm working.
Caught a double homicide. You're up.
No way. Alvarez hasn't done
a case all week. It's his turn.
Alvarez put in double overtime last week.
Hey, Gordon.
Captain.
Councilman Ron Jenkins
and his aide were found dead...
...in a parking structure this morning.
Still waiting on the ME's report.
Their wallets and jewelry were missing.
Councilman? Maybe it's a political hit.
No one hits councilmen.
It's cheaper to bribe them.
You kill them and another bum
with his hand out takes his place.
ESSEN:
Sniff around City Hall if you want.
Smart money says
this is wrong place, wrong time.
- Go work it.
- Ugh. Slave driver.
Don't worry, Jim. I know just where to start.
WOMAN [SINGING]:
O, at sea again
And now my hurricanes
Have brought down this ocean rain...
- She's got talent.
FISH: Hm.
- She's not bad-looking.
- That's plenty.
Come to me so I can take you in.
You sing well.
For this job I need more than a pair
of nice pipes and a pretty face.
I'll do whatever it takes.
I like hearing that.
So you like boys or girls?
Boys.
Fine. Pretend I'm a boy.
Seduce me.
[FISH GRUNTS]
At least you can sing.
Butch, put a pin in this one.
We'll call you.
Not bad, but keep looking.
Really, boss? That's a good-looking girl.
[SNAPS FINGERS]
Look at me. I ain't looking for no girl.
I'm looking for a weapon.
Come on, Nicky, don't be modest.
You're the crown prince of parking lot
muggers. No one's got a bigger rep.
I'm on sabbatical. I didn't kill no one.
That's not my thing.
- Then Why'd you have a shank in your bag?
- Protection.
BULLOCK:
Councilman Jenkins was murdered.
- We know it was you. We got witnesses.
- I swear to God, I didn't do it.
BULLOCK:
Hey.
- Hey!
- He's not our guy, Harvey.
- Alvarez, what's this?
- Yo.
Evidence from your crime scene.
A couple unis just dropped it off.
GORDON:
Arkham?
JAMES:
Forty acres. Twenty-six city blocks.
The last major undeveloped district
in the city of Gotham.
Arkham.
Now, before their untimely
and tragic deaths...
...Thomas and Martha Wayne
had a plan for their city.
A progressive development plan...
...that would raze Arkham's shanty towns,
and in its place...
...build new, affordable housing
for Gotham's less fortunate.
- What about the old asylum, mayor?
- Torn down.
Brick by brick if need be.
In its place, a cutting edge...
...state-of-the-art mental health facility.
This is a vision for the future of our city.
An opposing plan
is gaining support recently.
Then it would do away
with the asylum all together.
Use the surrounding land
as a waste disposal site.
No. No, the Wayne plan is best
for this city...
...and more importantly,
for the people of this city.
This is why I am endorsing it.
[DOOR OPENS]
[BELL JINGLES]
Don Maroni.
- Heh. Pleasure to see you.
- Thank you. How are you?
Please, please, have a seat.
I'll bring wine and bread.
MARONI:
Today is a day of celebration.
A very lucrative deal is coming my way.
Land, my friend. Land.
That's where the big money is. Huh?
I need information about
the Wayne plan for Arkham.
Ah, it's the Wayne plan
in name only now.
When the Waynes died, Falcone stepped in.
He's back in the plan now.
And he stands to make
quite a chunk of change if it passes.
But Councilman Jenkins
was backing Falcone's plan.
That's right.
- Then he was killed because...?
- Because, detective...
...there is an opposing plan.
Maroni.
He's the only one strong enough
to oppose Falcone.
He's making a play at Arkham.
BRUCE:
Are they related?
Bruce. How are you?
BRUCE:
"The new Arkham Asylum...
...will serve the mentally ill of Gotham
in ways the present asylum never can.
Those poor, sick souls deserve our help."
My mother wrote that.
She and my father fought for years
to get a new asylum built.
They thought that if they can help
the city's least fortunate...
...it would show
there was hope for everyone.
I just don't want
my parents' dream to die with them.
I understand that, Bruce.
But this isn't just about the asylum.
If there is a fight
between Falcone and Maroni...
...this could be the spark
that ignites a city-wide gang war.
Innocents will die.
And whatever little faith people have
that police can protect them...
It will be crushed.
So you have to stop it.
[PHONE BUZZING]
- This is Gordon.
BULLOCK: Hey, it's me.
We got a call.
Councilman Zeller's been abducted.
Listen, Gordon,
Zeller's one of Maroni's guys.
Be right there.
[GRUNTING]
Please, don't. I'm begging you. Stop.
You know...
...if it were up to me, this would
be over quick without all the fuss.
My father used to say,
simplicity is the ultimate sophistication.
But it's not up to me.
My customer specifically
asked me to send a message.
And you know what they say.
The customer is always right.
Please. You don't have to do this.
Help, somebody!
No, wait!
Tell Falcone I'll change my vote.
I'll back the mayor!
I'll do anything he wants!
Please, please! Please, help. Please! Plea--
[ZELLER SCREAMING]
ESSEN: Two councilmen dead
in as many days. Can't be a coincidence.
Gotta be politics driving this. He was right.
Never said he was wrong.
I just wanted him to be.
All right, genius. Any other insights?
Yeah, this is about the Arkham vote.
- How so?
- Arkham is more than just a land deal.
It's a war between Falcone and Maroni.
These councilmen were on opposite sides.
So who did who?
The way I see it, Maroni struck first.
He had Jenkins killed to change
the vote his way. Then Falcone retaliated.
Had Zeller killed to change the vote back.
Burning the body was Falcone's message.
I'll have guards put on other councilmen
and the mayor until this plays out.
So you wanna tell me?
Come on. Falcone, Maroni, Arkham.
How the hell do you know so much
all of a sudden?
BULLOCK: Ed, what you got?
- I have a paradox for you.
- What?
- Well, a paradox, detective, is when you--
I know what a paradox is, smart-ass.
What paradox?
These are the medical examiner's reports
on the murders...
...of Councilman Jenkins and his aide.
Both victims sustained fatal puncture
wounds to the skull via the eye socket.
The weapon was some kind of metal spike.
- Okay, so?
- Councilman Zeller...
...also has wounds from a metal spike.
It's an extremely unlikely coincidence,
don't you think?
You're saying Zeller, Jenkins and the aide
were killed by the same person?
It would appear so, wouldn't it?
Same killer
working for both Maroni and Falcone?
- That's nuts.
- Heh-heh.
Only in Gotham. Come on.
- Where we going?
- Go see a friend of mine.
- What the hell do you think you're doing?
- Uh, uh, uh--
You were snooping, you little worm.
I told you when I gave you the job...
...that in here, you don't see nothing,
you don't hear nothing.
I'm sorry, sir. I beg your pardon.
You keep that sniveling nose of yours
to yourself, understood?
Yes, sir.
Two cartons. Must be important.
- We're looking for a hit man.
- Yeah? Which family's he work for?
A few. He's an independent type, like you.
Not too many of them still around.
- Who'd they hit?
- Two city councilmen and an aide.
He uses a special weapon to kill.
A steel spike? About so big?
Could be.
- You know him?
- I heard of him.
His name is Gladwell. A real pro.
- You know where we can find him?
- Word was...
...he works out of the Lansky building
in Midtown.
Coming or what?
We got 12 more floors to check.
What's got you so wound up?
Maybe I'm just doing my job.
You've been acting weird lately,
like you got something to hide.
G.C.P.D., ma'am. We're looking
for someone who may work here.
- Last name Gladwell.
- Oh, you mean Richard.
He works in Human Resources.
- Richard's not in any trouble, is he?
BULLOCK: Which desk is his?
Third one from the back.
Gladwell. Richard Gladwell.
Has anyone seen him?
- You just missed him.
- Where'd he go?
He was just here.
Maybe he headed out the back?
I'll go check it out.
Stay here in case he comes back?
[DRAWERS OPENING]
BULLOCK:
Jim, I found something.
Look what was in his desk.
Jenkins and Zeller. We got him.
Man, I love the easy ones.
- Freeze.
- Ah!
It's just a box of paper clips.
I didn't think anyone would mind.
- Sorry. I'm sorry. You okay?
- Ah!
GORDON:
CLM?
What do you think it means?
I don't know.
[GASPING]
You all right?
I'm fine. Ahem.
- Why?
- Well...
I heard screaming.
Bad dream.
Oh.
Was I in it?
Not this time.
- There any more files on the Arkham plan?
- Yeah.
Absolutely untold piles
of the bloody things.
I'd like to see them, please.
All of them.
And may I ask why?
I'm looking for a connection.
Between the councilmen murders
and the murders of my parents.
I see.
[TIRES SCREECH]
Nobody move. This is a robbery.
[PATRONS SCREAM]
Money's in the back. Go, go!
What do you think you're doing?
Get over there.
[GUNSHOTS]
MAN:
Let's go. Move! Move!
[TIRES SCREECH]
MAN:
Move. Out of my way.
Out of my way.
Check the back.
They got the money, Frankie.
I got eyes, don't I?
Ah! Oh! Oh.
Oh, thank goodness you're here.
They had guns, and Lou--
Lou was hit in the stomach. ls he--?
Forget about Lou. Who did this?
Uh, they had masks. I couldn't see.
- But you got the money.
- Oh, yeah.
I managed to hide this bag,
but they got the rest.
- I'm sorry, I--
- Hey, relax, kid.
Save it for the boss.
You're off early for a change.
Missed you.
You all right?
Long hours and late nights, Jim.
They make me worry.
- About what?
- All kinds of things.
- Just doing my job.
- Are you?
What is that supposed to mean?
It means I think you have secrets from me.
And I hate it.
What do you want me to say, Barbara?
Yeah, I have secrets.
- It's part of my job. It's how--
- Who's Oswald Cobblepot?
- How do you know that name?
- Doesn't matter. Who is he?
- I can't even begin to answer that.
- Can't or won't?
Montoya.
She came to see you, didn't she?
Yes.
Why does she keep coming to you?
What is it between you and her?
Years ago, before I was with you...
...she and I were in a relationship.
What?
It only lasted a year.
And then I ended it and moved on.
And what? She didn't?
I don't know.
I don't care, okay? Because you are the one
that I want to spend the rest of my life with.
- What? You're angry?
- What do you think?
- Because she's a woman?
- Because you lied to me!
Okay, I'm sorry. I should have told you.
MARONI:
Falcone thinks he can hit me...
...in my place of business
and get away with it?
He's got another thing coming, Frankie.
I want to hit him back.
This time where it hurts.
I wanna hit the Mouth.
His time's up.
FRANKIE:
I'll take care of it.
Then there's the other thing.
Send him over.
You know, I'm a man that shows
appreciation when appreciation is due.
Yes, Don Maroni.
What you did for me yesterday
did not go unnoticed.
Thank you, sir.
I only wish I was able to retrieve the other--
Ba-ba-ba. Ba.
How long you been washing dishes?
- Not long.
- That ends today.
You've been promoted
to restaurant manager.
The position recently became available.
Thank you, Don Maroni.
I won't let you down.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. You're welcome.
Frankie, get the kid a suit.
He's dead.
- Who?
- Richard Gladwell.
At least, the real one.
Sent some unis by his apartment,
found a moldy old corpse sealed inside.
Puncture wound through the eye.
Been dead five years.
- And no one found him until now?
- Landlord said he paid rent on time.
Kept quiet. The ideal tenant.
So our hit man killed this Gladwell
to use his identity as cover.
And it worked too.
Employee records, payroll,
contact information, all fake.
We got nothing but a face.
Damn.
All right, there's gotta be something to this.
CLM. You got any ideas?
It's a complete waste of time.
It's a lead. Our only lead.
- Says you.
- You can't be this lazy.
Lazy? Maybe I just work smarter than you.
Ever consider that?
Yeah. I considered it.
This Arkham vote is tomorrow.
If we don't find this guy by then...
What? What happens?
Worst case? A major gang war.
People will die. Maybe a lot of people.
We find this guy, we can stop it.
And where are you going?
To work the case.
You got your ways, I got mine.
Hey, Harvey...
...tell her I said hi.
WOMAN [SINGING]:
You hear laughter
Cracking through the halls
That sends you spinning
You have no choice
Following the footsteps
Of a rag-doll dance
We are entranced
Spellbound
What's your name?
Liza.
How long have you been singing, Liza?
Not long.
Do you like boys or girls?
Boys.
So you want the job or what?
Well, you haven't told me what it is yet.
You want to be a woman with power,
money and respect like me?
I guess. Yeah.
Are you willing to do
whatever it takes to have it all?
Yes, I am.
That's the job.
Seduce me.
Heh. What?
You think I'm kidding.
[LIZA MOANS]
Harvey. You see something you like?
I do now.
I need your help.
City councilmen are dropping like flies.
- I heard.
- Bad for business.
- You're not wrong.
- Button man's called Gladwell. Know him?
- Only by reputation.
- Think you can find him?
I can find anyone if I have the time.
The question is, what's in it for me?
I'll owe you.
Okay, but I still think
it's a waste of time, if you ask me.
Falcone will just get someone
to take his place.
- He's not gonna let this bone go.
- Why's that?
Falcone cannot afford to lose that vote.
If Maroni gets even a piece of Arkham,
it'll only prove what we already know.
And that is, Falcone is old and weak.
You seem kind of pleased about that.
How come?
Falcone goes down, so do you.
Harvey, don't you worry about me.
I always have a plan B.
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
[PHONE RINGS]
Detective Gordon.
COBBLEPOT:
Hello, old friend.
What do you want?
To offer you help.
To prove that you can trust me.
There's gonna be another murder.
- Maroni has put out the hit.
- Who's the target?
Someone backing Falcone's plan.
Who it is, I can't be certain.
All the councilmen
are under police protection tonight.
Heh. There are many ways
around the police.
But the hit will happen tonight.
That much I can be certain.
How do you know this?
I told you, detective. Gotham is my home.
I need a list of the officers
working police protection tonight.
Campos, Lazenby, Martins.
CLM.
[PHONE BEEPING]
BULLOCK:
Hey, it's Harvey.
Bullock, I found out
who Gladwell's next target is.
It's the mayor.
- Detective, what's going on?
- I think you're in danger.
- I need to get you out of here.
- What?
I'm not going anywhere.
I got police protection.
- They're gone.
- What?
I just checked. No one's out there. Sir,
I think someone's coming here to kill you.
I gotta get some things from my safe.
Sir, we need to go. Now.
- I'll move as fast as I can.
- Is there someplace safe I can take you?
- We're not going to the police station?
- Not sure you'll be safe there. Police...
- What the hell's this town coming to?
- Sir...
All right, all right.
My sister's house. It's across town.
Let's go.
Go. Go. Go.
- Is there another way out?
- Here.
JAMES:
He's trying to get in.
- Shoot him. Why don't you shoot him?
- He's got my gun, I can't. Go. Go. Go.
[GUNSHOTS]
[GRUNTING]
Drop it!
Drop it, or I'll shoot.
You know why they hire a professional?
Because he finishes the job.
BARBARA: How are you?
GORDON: I'm okay.
Jim, I should've told you
about Montoya a long time ago.
- And why didn't you?
- I don't know.
Because she works with you.
Because she's a woman.
Are you sure there isn't another reason?
No. There's nothing else.
Jim, I don't want there to be
any secrets between us.
- Neither do I.
- Good.
So you'll tell me who Oswald Cobblepot is.
Damn it, Barbara. Why can't you drop this?
- Why can't you just tell me who he is?
- Because...
...it's work.
I know.
But you told me about your work before.
And that was a mistake.
One I am not going to make again.
All right, well...
I'm not gonna live like this.
I can't live like this.
You're gonna have to make a choice, Jim.
You either let me in or you let me go.
All right, I'm going to cut to the chase.
I like you both, but I only have one opening.
You've got the talent.
And you've got...
...something else.
I can't decide. So you two are going
to have to do it for me.
You want us to fight for it?
[GRUNTING]
So when do I start?
It's you. Heh.
Scared us there for a second.
We do good, or what?
Excellent work, my friends.
You were very convincing.
Yeah, I bet that manager thought so, huh?
Ain't that right, Dickie?
[ALL LAUGH]
Got any other joints you want us to rob,
let us know.
- There's good money in this.
- Good money.
What's that?
Oh, I brought cannoli.
Hell, yeah. Ha.
Eat up. You guys deserve this.
- Yeah.
- Check this out.
- Mmm.
- It's really good.
Real good.
MAN [ON TV]: The Arkham development vote
has been a topic of controversy for weeks.
Today we have the results.
We go live now
to Mayor James's press conference.
- Mind turning that down? Head's killing me.
- Oh, shut up.
This is what we worked for. We did this.
WOMAN: How is today's outcome
not simply a failure of the Wayne plan?
This is not a case of either plan failing.
This is a case of compromise...
...for what's best for the people of Gotham.
The Arkham district will be developed
into both low-cost housing...
...as well as a much needed site
for waste disposal.
This is the best of both plans.
Together in one.
Yes. Yes.
For years, this city's been
giving us nothing but scraps.
But from now on...
From now on, we feast.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Mayor James, what about the asylum?
What's going to happen to it?
JAMES: Arkham Asylum will be retrofitted
to meet today's standards and reopened.
Gotham needs-- No, Gotham deserves...
...a world-class treatment facility
for the mentally ill.
Falcone took a shot to the body today.
Maybe a few more will put him on his back.
Looks like I got you just in time.
And I know that the Waynes,
were they still alive...
...would be proud of what
we've been able to accomplish today.
The mayor's making this new plan
sound like it's good for Gotham.
- But it's not, is it?
- No, it's not.
Then why's he doing it?
He was caught between
two very powerful opposing forces.
Falcone and Maroni.
Maroni threatened the mayor's life.
Out of fear, I'm guessing,
the mayor made a compromise...
...and gave Maroni a huge piece of Arkham.
What piece?
Maroni gets to build a waste disposal site.
And he gets the contract
to refurbish Arkham.
Falcone gets to build
a low-income housing project.
Look, Bruce...
I know it's not the outcome
you had hoped for.
But this compromise...
...it may have prevented a lot of bloodshed.
May have even stopped a war.
My parents believed a new asylum
would bring hope to Gotham.
Now that's gone.
Everything they worked for
is now falling into the hands of criminals.
Not everything.
You're alive.
It's not too late.
Do you really believe that?
Do you believe Gotham can be saved?
I believe it's worth trying.