Bad guys in this town are changing.
Hi.
Welcome, everyone.
The world sees criminal lunatics.
I see brilliance.
Theo Galavan, the new mayor of Gotham!
No! Mother.
Any last words?
I am going to kill you.
They're going to pay
for what they've done.
Hello, Jim. Please step aside.
This is the name of the man
who killed your parents.
- You're under arrest.
- No! Tell me who killed them!
Hello, sleepyhead.
My mother was a saint!
A man with nothing to love is free.
Silver is bad news, Bruce.
What are you doing? Stop!
Malone! It's Malone. That's the name.
Goodbye, Silver.
Bruce, you can't do this. It isn't you.
That's what you think.
But you're wrong.
You're right about my uncle.
He's everything everyone says.
I don't know how bad it's gonna get.
There is no line. There's just the law.
Jim, you see an abyss,
and you run toward it.
I'm pregnant.
We need every method at our disposal.
If there was ever a time for us
to work together, now is that time.
Gotham needs him dead!
Think of the greater good.
Think of Gotham.
Goodbye, Jim Gordon.
After searching the premises,
I, along with Alfred Pennyworth
and Selina Kyle,
was able to locate the abductee,
Bruce Wayne.
Where was he?
Theo Galavan's residence.
- That's when you opened fire?
- Yes.
We eliminated the threat posed
by Father Creel and his men,
and were able to recover Bruce Wayne.
Sacrilege!
You then left to search
for Galavan on your own?
That's correct.
Did you find him?
Yes.
Theo Galavan, you're under arrest.
- Did you detain Galavan?
- No.
Why not?
Captain Barnes and Officer Vargas arrived
and placed me under arrest.
Jim. Jim! Put your gun on the ground
and put your hands on top of your head.
That's because at the time
of this incident,
some four weeks ago,
you were a fugitive from the law.
That was a misunderstanding.
What happened next?
Oswald Cobblepot
and two of his associates arrived,
rendered Officer Vargas
and Captain Barnes unconscious.
Cobblepot and his associates
escaped with Galavan.
Are you 100% sure that he won't beat this
and walk free again?
You then pursued Cobblepot
and his men, correct?
Yes, but I was unable to locate them.
You're a man of conscience, Jim.
You'll regret this.
I have many regrets.
This won't be top of the list.
At which point you decided
to flee the city
before law enforcement could question you?
Yes. For that, I have no excuse,
other than to say
I was concerned
for the safety of my fiancée.
She had informed me earlier that day
that she was pregnant.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Detective Gordon,
within hours of your encounter,
Theo Galavan was found beaten
and shot to death.
Were you present
at the time of his murder?
Oh, well. Here we are.
No, I was not.
Do you have any information
regarding the case
that you have not shared with us?
This is for my mother.
No, I do not.
Detective, did you have anything to do
with the murder of Theo Galavan?
Detective, answer the question.
Were you involved
in Theo Galavan's murder?
No, I was not.
Charges are lifted.
I'm cleared of all wrong-doing
and reinstated.
I knew they would see sense.
I didn't.
You told the truth.
What choice did they have?
Yeah.
Are you sure this is what you want?
After everything
this job has put us through?
Positive.
Then what's wrong?
Nothing. Long day.
Promise?
Promise.
Barnes.
Dent.
Captivating story.
Yes, it was.
Do you believe him?
I believe your investigation has found
no evidence of criminal wrongdoing.
Careful. You're starting
to sound like a lawyer.
Any leads on Cobblepot?
His men have deserted him. He's all alone.
It's only a matter of time
before we find him.
It's now day 27 of the manhunt
for the crime lord, Oswald Cobblepot.
G.C.P.D. officers
continue to comb the city
in search of the man they say
killed controversial mayor Theo Galavan
in cold blood.
With public enemy number one on the lam,
the question remains,
just who is running Gotham's underworld?
Take him away.
Hello, Butch.
Hey. How you doin'?
Your security stinks.
People are usually trying to get out
of this place, not in.
Why so glum?
You're the king of Gotham now.
I'm not glum. I'm just thinking.
I got a lot of responsibilities.
Not as much fun
as you thought it'd be, huh?
Yeah.
What do you want, anyway?
You got a lot of nerve showing up
after what you did to me.
Ooh.
Is that your mean face?
What are you gonna do? Kill me?
Maybe I will.
What I did for you, Butch,
is make you a free man.
If it wasn't for me, you wouldn't be king.
I bet that was your plan all along, huh?
You're just that fond of me.
Strangely enough,
I am kind of fond of you.
I mean, normally, I go for handsome,
intelligent men, not brutes,
but you have an amazing animal vitality
about you.
I'm smarter than I look.
Oh, you must be.
A funny lady.
What do you really want?
I wanna be your partner in crime.
Lonely, huh?
You and I would make a good team.
I'm not looking
for a relationship right now.
Honeybun, look at me.
We have history.
And you and I both know,
deep down in your heart,
that whatever I want,
you want.
All units, all units,
reported armed abduction near
the 300 block of Kearny Avenue.
Any and all available officers
in the area, please respond.
G.C.P.D.
Is there a problem, Officer?
There's been an abduction in the area.
How awful.
Have you seen anything tonight?
Anything out of the ordinary?
No. Can't say that I have.
Do you live in the area, sir?
- Not far.
- What's your address?
Well, what I mean to say,
I used to live in the area. I moved.
Would you open
the back of the van, please, sir?
Sure thing.
Happy to.
What the--
Somebody get me a glass of water!
Hey! Mitch, separate those two.
It's a good thing you're here.
We caught a weird one last night.
That's it? No hug? No kiss?
No welcome back?
You don't deserve these lips.
Way I see it, you finagled yourself
a month-long, paid vacation, you bastard.
Besides, Captain's pressing me
on this case.
Oh, yeah? What is it?
You didn't hear?
Last night, some psycho froze a cop
to death.
Froze her?
Yeah. Told you it was weird. Come on.
Nygma's waiting for us.
Frozen.
Interesting. It took nearly five seconds
to freeze this rose
- using liquid nitrogen.
- So?
Well, so, it'd take a human body
significantly longer,
depending on mass and body fat, of course.
So why would a cop stand around
for hours waiting to get frozen?
She wouldn't.
Which means your suspect
wasn't using liquid nitrogen.
He was using super-cooled liquid helium.
It's one of the most effective substances
in the world
for rapid temperature reduction.
This liquid helium, where do you get it?
Why do you need it?
He doesn't, dummy.
He just wants to know where it comes from
so we can track down the guy
that blasted our colleague with it.
I don't like
being called names, Detective.
Easy, Ed.
I'm sure Harvey was just being colorful.
Yeah.
I was just being colorful, Ed, I'm sorry.
It's extremely rare and expensive.
Can't imagine there's more
than one or two producers in Gotham.
I could research manufacturers,
if you would like.
That'll be really nice. Thank you, Ed.
You coming?
Uh, gimme a minute.
Listen, Ed, there's something I wanted
to talk to you about.
- Penguin.
- Yes.
You want to know
the nature of my relationship with him.
Yes.
Because you're concerned I aided
and abetted a known criminal.
Did you?
I found Mr. Cobblepot wounded
and dying in the woods.
I nursed him back to health.
He owed me his life which is why I trusted
him when he said he had changed his ways.
It was an innocent mistake.
Got him! We got him!
Wonder what that is.
Silence!
What are you, a bunch of cheerleaders?
This is not a game! This is our job!
And this specimen,
this is just one sad, pathetic skell.
There are plenty of scumbags out there.
Plenty.
So stop waving your pom-poms
and go catch some!
Yes, stare all you want. Big whoop.
- You got me. I'm cool.
- Get in there!
It's all good.
I said I'd catch him, and I did.
Yes, sir.
Now we'll learn the truth
of what really happened to Galavan.
All right, Cobblepot.
Tell me what happened at Galavan's
that night.
Well, a lot of things happened.
Why don't you start with the moment
right after you knocked me out
with that vase.
I'm sorry for that.
Such an exquisite vase.
This is my amused look.
Keep talking.
I took Galavan to the river
and I killed him.
Slowly.
You confess to murder?
Yes, I do. Proud of it.
I'm not a criminal, you know.
I'm just insane.
- What did James Gordon do?
- What did he do when?
What did he do after you knocked me out?
What does he say he did?
I'm asking you.
You have something you wanna tell me?
No, sir.
Cobblepot backed your story.
You mean, he told the truth.
Yeah.
That's what I'm gonna choose to believe.
It's the right thing to do.
- Good to have you back.
- Good to be back, sir.
Jim, I'm trusting you.
Don't make a fool out of me.
Yes, sir.
I was having a dream about you.
We were at that little red cabin
by the beach. Remember?
I remember. Six summers ago.
You looked like a movie star.
You look tired.
Work.
How's it coming?
Good. Good.
Slower than I'd like, but good.
Tell me.
I'm having trouble with reanimation.
I need to find the correct ratio of
liquid helium to glycerol cryoprotectant.
Now tell me what that means
in English, honey.
It means
I can freeze you, like we planned.
I can bring your temperature down
to 200 degrees below zero,
and I can stop this disease
from killing you.
But?
I can't bring you back.
Not yet. But I will.
I'm sorry.
No, it's not that.
I'm just thinking of all those poor mice
you're experimenting on.
They don't feel anything.
I just need more time. A little more time.
Hey.
I'll find a way. I promise.
- Got some good news and bad news.
- Good news.
Nygma did some digging and found
one company in all of Gotham
that makes liquid helium.
Wayne Enterprises.
- That's the good news?
- It's not,
but I thought bad news and more bad news
didn't have the same ring.
What's this?
Three abductions in the past month
all tied to a blue van,
same as our suspect's.
Three abductions? They find any of 'em?
Not a one.
Which makes you wonder what's this guy
doing with all those people.
Nora? I'm going to work for a few hours.
Knock if you need anything.
Okay.
Psst.
- Ed?
- Shh.
Don't look at me.
I'm not supposed to be talking to you.
You doing okay? You look kind of funky.
I confess I've felt better.
Is there anything I can do to help?
I'm beyond help.
Forget me, my friend.
But if you would take care
of my mother's grave,
I'd be very grateful.
If you'd visit occasionally,
tell her I'm thinking of her.
I will.
She likes lilies.
Occasional visits, lilies, check.
Thank you.
On your feet, Cobblepot.
What's going on? Where are you taking me?
Arkham. You are insane, right?
It is now Thursday,
February 21st, 2:44 p.m.
Test subject 014 is in his 40s,
appears to be in good health,
and shows no signs of damage sustained
during vitrification.
I'm now ready to commence
the reanimation experiment.
You are correct.
Wayne Enterprises does manufacture
liquid helium.
For years it was used
as part of our cryogenics program.
Cryo-whatics?
It's the branch of physics dealing
with the production and effects
of extremely low temperatures.
My understanding is that
there were some promising experiments
being carried out in the program.
But, alas, it was shut down.
When was that?
Two or three years ago.
Thomas Wayne killed it,
along with a few other odd programs.
Any idea why?
No idea. It was all kept very quiet.
Thanks, Lucius.
Detectives.
Penguin pie!
There seems to be some confusion.
My name is Oswald Cobblepot.
Many of you, no doubt,
will have heard of me.
Some of you, clearly, have not.
For those poor ignorant souls,
I offer illumination.
I am not a man to be trifled with.
No.
I am powerful. I am vicious.
I'm King of Gotham.
I am King of Gotham!
I'm the King of Gotham!
I am! I am!
Look at me! I'm the King of Gotham!
I'm King! I'm King! Here ye, here ye!
The subject's core temperature
is now 39 degrees.
We are approaching the critical threshold.
41 degrees.
We hit 41 degrees.
Solution A14, I knew it would work,
I knew it!
Ha!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
No.
No, no, no, no. Not again, please.
Not again, no.
Nora?
Breathe, Nora. I'm right here. Look at me.
Where's the formoterol?
That was the worst one yet.
That was the last pill.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm sorry. I forgot. I have so many.
There's so many.
If you have another attack
and you don't have this medication,
you could die.
You can't let this happen again, Nora.
Why does it matter?
It matters.
I'll be back.
I need to get this refilled.
Next.
Do you have the prescription?
I have the bottle.
That's not the same thing, is it?
Please. I just need it refilled.
The original prescription
doesn't have a refill order.
If it doesn't have a refill order
I can't refill it.
This medication is for my wife.
She's sick. She's in pain.
Everyone that comes in here is sick
or in pain.
Have your doctor write a new prescription,
then I can refill it.
Just give me the medication.
- No.
- You son of a bitch!
Get out! Get him outta here!
Get outta here before I call the cops,
you kook!
You shouldn't have done that.
I'll be back.
Goodbye, Nigel.
Oh, and remember what I told you.
See no evil, do no evil.
Yes, sir. I will.
Mr. Cobblepot. My name is Hugo Strange.
Chief of Psychiatry here at Arkham Asylum.
Please come in.
You're not listening.
Maybe you should get a new hearing aid
while you're here.
Hey!
- Formoterol. Now!
- Okay. Okay.
Take it all.
Please, don't kill me. Please.
I'll do anything you want.
You and your friend here
are going to help save my wife.
No! No!
Excuse me!
Going to need some help out.
Yeah?
Our guy just hit a pharmacy on 9th.
That's it.
Just slide him in there.
Hey, careful.
Blue van.
- Go, get out of here.
- Thank you.
- Go, go, go, go!
- I got it, I got it!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, slow down!
What is this, anyhow? Am I being punished?
No.
I make it a point to meet all new inmates.
It's part of the intake protocol.
Though I will ask you to refrain
from making speeches
atop cafeteria tables in the future.
I'll do my best.
How has your adjustment been so far?
Fine, I suppose.
Oh, come now, Oswald.
Periods of great transition
can bring on great stress.
Surely this must be a traumatic experience
for you.
Please.
This is a pillow fight
compared to what I've been through.
Yes. I have read
of your tribulations of late.
Attempts on your life,
having to survive being a fugitive.
The death of your mother.
Troubled times.
Is that your clinical diagnosis?
I know that if I were in your position,
I would be feeling some strong emotions.
Anger, grief, regret even.
For what?
The murder of Theo Galavan.
My mother died in my arms
because of Galavan.
The only thing I regret is that I couldn't
kill him more than once.
I see.
Perhaps we could pick it up
right there next time.
I so look forward to our work together.
And don't worry.
Here at Arkham, we have a number
of intensive treatment programs.
I am more than confident that we'll be
able to facilitate your rehabilitation.
My what?
Rehabilitation.
That's why you're here, after all.
To be cured of your sickness.
You are sick, aren't you?
Victor?
Honey? You down here?
My God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Surveillance system wasn't even on.
What's that?
Some witnesses saw our guy
throw this at the pharmacist.
It's probably his prescription bottle.
"Fries, Nora Fries." His wife, maybe?
Yeah, maybe, but it's "Fries."
- What do you mean?
- It's pronounced "Fries."
- How do you know?
- I'm really good with names.
Yeah, whatever. There's an address
on here. Come on, let's go.
G.C.P.D., we have a search warrant!
Ma'am, don't move.
Holy moly.
He told me they were mice.
Get her out of here.
Ms. Fries.
Nora.
You all right? Nigel?
See no evil, do no evil.
No, no.
We need to find your husband, Nora.
Before he hurts someone else.
I was asleep.
I woke up when I heard him leave.
That's all I can tell you.
If you don't cooperate, we'll be forced
to charge you with obstruction of justice.
You're going to jail, Nora.
You get that, right?
My husband did terrible things.
But he did those terrible things
for my sake.
I'm dying. He wants to save me.
I can't tell you how sorry I am.
But I can't betray him.
Oh, one more thing.
What's the correct pronunciation
of your last name?
It's Fries.
Fries. Thank you.
Told you.
Excuse me.
Yeah, what can I help you with?
I'd like to speak
with Detective Gordon, please.
What for?
I'd like to make a confession.
I'm the man that's been freezing people.
You too, huh?
That makes five in one night.
Must be a full moon.
Tell you what.
Why don't you have a seat with the others.
Detective Gordon,
he'll be out in a minute.
- No, no. You don't understand. I'm--
- I understand. Have a seat.
Huh.
Am I dead?
Hello?
- Don't touch me! Don't touch me!
- Take it easy, come on! Down!
A16. It worked.
Go get a blanket.
I can't believe it worked.
All right. I got him.
I got him.
You? You!
I'm coming for you, Nora.
I'm coming to save you.
New inmate Oswald Cobblepot exhibits signs
of extreme narcissism and megalomania.
Also seems to have had
a rather unhealthy relationship
with his deceased mother.
Treatments will include immersive aversion
therapy and radical psychotropics.
How are we this evening, Ms. Peabody?
Busy. The formaldehyde pump in silo F
needs replacing.
Our young lady arsonist refuses
to co-operate with our experiments.
And I had to reschedule your appointment
with Councilman Carter.
- Again?
- It's the third time.
- How very rude.
- Indeed.
And there's this.
Seems someone has solved the problem
of post-cryonic reanimation.
Nonsense.
I'm still years from solving that.
Fascinating.
Do you realize what this could mean
for our program? Who is this man?
His name is Victor Fries.
But the newspapers have already
given him a nickname.
Hello, Mr. Freeze.
English SDH