COBBLEPOT: Previously on Gotham...
But you are my only
true blood relative, Oswald.
That vermin has to go.
But, how can we persuade him to go?
How do you get rid of rats?
- (GLASS SHATTERING)
- (GRACE GASPS)
- Did he, did he drink that?
- Yes.
Why? Why? He's not supposed to.
No!
(MONITOR BEEPING)
Awake at last.
Well, hello, dear.
Someone call Professor Strange!
ED: We'll see about your
clever little plan, Jim Gordon.
I can make plans of my own.
- Hello, Officer Pinkney. Can I come in?
- Sure.
Murder weapon was a crowbar.
Your fingerprints were on it.
I was set up!
WARDEN: Being convicted for murder
has its downsides.
It was good to see you, Harv.
Don't give up hope.
What the hell are you doing here?
What's it look like?
We're getting you out of here.
BULLOCK: Come on. Let's go.
I have to clear my name.
And to do that
I have to go to back to Gotham.
(PANTING)
MALE GANGSTER: You little thugs!
Don't you take that bag!
Do you have any idea
who you're stealing from?
(GROANS)
Leave it!
(PANTS)
That's my money!
Boo-hoo! You stole it.
Now you got stole, chump.
(CHUCKLES)
I catch you, you're dead! Both of you!
By the way, you're a terrible crook,
letting two kids rob you.
You really don't deserve this money.
What the hell are you doing,
you little freak?
What the hell are you doing?
You're both dead!
Nobody's ever gonna touch my money!
(GRUNTS)
I'm not a thief.
I don't steal for the money.
This is research.
I can't understand Gotham,
- until I understand its criminals.
- Okay.
This whole "understanding criminals" thing
is getting on my nerves.
That was your half you threw out.
I saved enough for burgers.
Gotham is on high alert today
after former GCPD detective
and convicted murderer, James Gordon,
escaped from Blackgate Prison last night.
Detective Bullock,
have you heard the news?
Yeah, Ed, I heard.
So what do you think he'll do?
Knowing Jim Gordon,
I'd say he's not gonna rest
until he finds the son-of-a-bitch
who framed him for murder.
Good luck with that.
Bullock. This is your one and
only chance to tell me where he is.
Hand to God, Cap, I have no idea.
Oh, stop it. You're not smart enough
to play dumb.
We both know Jim did not kill Pinkney.
I know that the court found him guilty.
He wants to prove his own innocence,
great, I hope he does.
The public, the people of Gotham,
the ones you and I serve...
They have to know. They have to see
that we're impartial, you understand?
The people of Gotham can eat my socks.
Hey! Hey! Nice try.
Walk away in a huff.
Now I know you know something.
If you're providing aid and shelter
to Jim Gordon,
anything, a glass of water,
I will bust you like a bum I never met.
Cap, I wish I knew where he was,
but I don't.
Go.
(SIGHS)
- Everything okay?
- Yeah. Let's get to work.
I've been going over and over this
a thousand times in my mind.
It all has to be connected.
The theft at the art museum,
the bombing at the train station,
the IA tipoff, Pinkney's murder...
It's all a part of an elaborate frame.
So, he's smart, meticulous,
got technical skill, and access.
- An active cop?
- Has to be.
Only way that he could have access to
a crowbar after it was put into evidence.
That doesn't really narrow
the suspect list too much.
I mean, come on, Jim, be honest,
you probably got 500 cops
who have beef with you.
- Yeah, but enough to frame me for murder?
- Maybe 10.
You got to admit,
you do have a little bit of a knack
for, uh, making enemies.
My number was 12.
- Hmm.
- Mainly Loeb loyalists.
Who knows?
Maybe Loeb himself is behind this.
Before you go down that rabbit hole,
I've gotta say something
to you as a friend.
You can still run.
Go to an island. Buy a banana boat.
Grow a beard. Find Lee. Have a life.
Look, I've been working this thing
since you went away,
and I'm not saying it's hopeless,
but Barnes is on the hunt.
- You don't have much time.
- Did he threaten you?
Hey, I'm the one who busted you
out of jail, remember?
I made my choice.
All right, let's say, I run.
I find Lee. I somehow convince her
to take me back. What then?
I get her to live as a fugitive?
I have to clear my name.
Otherwise, I might as well be in jail.
But how? Starting where?
Dent once told me IA
secretly records and archives
all their incoming calls on tape.
Which means, the eyewitness,
who called into IA,
the one they assumed was Pinkney?
There could be a tape
with his voice on it.
(BULLOCK EXHALES)
It's a hell of a long shot, brother.
And if... Okay.
Just saying if a tape like that exists,
it's gonna be locked up tighter
than a duck's ass in IA evidence.
That's why it's lucky for you,
Uncle Harvey has connections.
Hey, Ginny. (LAUGHING)
How's my favorite IA sugar plum, huh?
Well, why do you think I'm calling, baby?
(BULLOCK GRUNTS)
- Heard you're getting married?
- No, she changed her mind.
Smart girl. (CHUCKLES) Oh.
You're an animal, Bullock.
You know that?
Oh, yes, ma'am, I do, I do.
- (GRUNTS)
- Oh!
- Come on, Bullock.
- Yeah, baby! I'll be right there.
Just hold on for me for a second.
(DOOR OPENS)
Hey, an hour. Slip 'em under the door.
- Come on, Bullock, I ain't got all night!
- Don't say a word.
Mmm?
BULLOCK: Daddy's coming!
(WHOOPS)
MALE COP: Is that what he said?
FEMALE COP: Yeah.
Julian had his arm all twisted up.
(CONVERSATION CONTINUES
INDISTINCTLY)
(DOOR CLOSES)
- MALE THUG: Give me that!
- (WOMAN WHIMPERS)
Oh, what's up, sweetheart,
what are you doing, huh?
- Where are you going? Give me your purse.
- WOMAN: What, no, no!
- Come on, do it! Just, come on, do it.
- Somebody help!
- Just do it.
- Hey!
WOMAN: (SCREAMS) No!
(GRUNTING)
Get out of here. Go!
(THUGS PANTING)
Ma'am, are you okay?
(SCREAMING)
- You're welcome.
- Hands up! Or I'll blow your head off.
GCPD. You're under--
You're Jim Gordon.
Listen to me.
This is Barkley over on Fifth and Spring.
I got Jim--
(GROANS)
- Don't kill me!
- I'm innocent, you hear me?
(COP GRUNTS)
All units, it's Jim freaking Gordon!
I need backup now!
(SOBBING)
Father, I only knew you a short time.
But you came to me
when I was alone in this cold, dark world.
You gave me a family.
I will never forget you as long as I live.
(SOBBING) Oh, Father.
(MOUTHING)
(SIGHS) What a bore that was.
Yeah, but the house is ours now,
and we're rich.
Quiet.
- (SOBBING)
- Oh.
- He loved us all so much.
- Indeed.
But, Oswald, Oswald...
(CHUCKLES)
As painful as this is,
we need to talk practicalities. Um...
Can I call you a cab,
or will you take the bus?
I don't understand.
Well, you're not returning
to the house with us.
- But where shall I go?
- Anywhere, but there.
Oswald, I'm so happy that you
and your father reconnected,
but he left the house
and the estate to me, and I'm...
Well, I'm simply not comfortable sleeping
under the same roof
as a notorious murderer.
But I'm not like that anymore.
I couldn't hurt a fly,
even if I wanted to.
Please, my father was all that I had.
We shared the same blood, and--
And he wanted us to be together.
He told me.
Let me stay. I'll do anything.
You are his blood.
We do need help around the house.
- Mother.
Why waste good money on servants
when we have Oswald?
I'll do anything.
Well, you can start by getting rid
of those disgusting flowers.
- I've always detested lilies.
- (LAUGHS) Yes, of course.
You're not really letting him stay?
He's Elijah's only natural son.
If he found the right lawyer,
he could make things difficult.
Especially if people look into
how his father died.
So, we just live with him, then?
Yeah, we keep him close and
after a suitable amount of time goes by,
poor Oswald, overcome with grief,
will take his own life.
Till then, we have a free servant.
I can fire the maid.
I murdered my parents.
I cut their throats.
Um...
I joined a gang of psychopathic killers.
I tried to kill Jim Gordon
and Lee Thompkins.
I was a puppet
of these demons in my head
and, uh, they were forcing me
to do these terrible things.
I wish I could go back
and undo what I've done.
Only I can't.
I don't feel insane, now.
I just...
I feel sad.
Thank you, Barbara.
That was very brave.
What do you suppose
made this healthful change in you?
Maybe I just really needed some sleep.
(DOOR BUZZES)
It's a good act.
HUGO: You're so sure it's an act, are you?
- Aren't you?
- I have no idea.
One way or the other, she intrigues me.
Well, if you would allow us to apply
rigorous dream therapy,
we would know for sure.
No, no, no.
We do have a very useful hammer,
Ms. Peabody,
but not all of our patients are nails.
(GRUNTS AND SIGHS)
- Thank you.
- (SIGHS)
- What the hell happened last night?
- Ah...
Stumbled on to a mugging.
And Jim Gordon couldn't just walk by.
Where'd you sleep?
(GRUNTS) I didn't. I just walked around.
How's Barnes?
He's on the warpath.
Governor announced a $10,000 reward
for anyone who helps catch you. (SNIFFS)
$10,000. You should turn me in.
If he doubled it to 20,
I'd give it some thought.
Okay, here.
MALE OPERATOR: Internal Affairs.
MALE CALLER: (IN DISTORTED VOICE) I--
(CLEARS THROAT) I want to report a crime.
- You recognize that voice?
- Sounds like it's been disguised.
I saw Detective James Gordon
shooting Mayor Theo Galavan
on the Southside Docks.
The Penguin was beating him with a bat,
but it was Gordon that pulled the trigger.
(DISTORTED NOISE ON TAPE)
Is that a bird?
Run it back.
(DISTORTED NOISE PLAYING)
Yeah.
We gotta find somebody
to clean up the tape.
Isolate the sound.
Maybe do something to the voice.
(SNIFFS)
I gotta get going.
Barnes is watching me like a hawk.
Yeah. All right.
Hey.
You've done more than
any partner could ask.
From now on, stay away from me.
For your own sake. If Loeb is behind this,
you don't wanna be mixed up in it.
What're you gonna do?
I still have some friends
I could ask for help.
Where're you going? Jim!
- Hi, Ed.
- (GASPS)
- Please. Please, don't hurt me.
- No, relax. I'm not gonna hurt you.
- I need your help.
- My help?
I didn't kill Pinkney.
You have to believe me.
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
I need to find the man who framed me.
Whoever it was,
he covered his tracks well.
But I have something.
A recording of his first call to IA.
IA secretly records everyone who calls in.
They do? (CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Those sneaky little buggers.
Uh, and what did-- What did you hear?
If you don't mind my asking.
Not much. He disguised his voice.
But there are other sounds on the tape.
I figured, you work with audio.
I was hoping you could help me.
Jim. (CHUCKLES)
My friend, you've come to the right place.
Please, have a seat.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I will get my stuff and make some tea.
(CHUCKLES)
Mmm.
Well, let's pray Helga hasn't signed on
anywhere new yet.
- It's a family recipe.
- (SIGHS)
I'm sorry you don't like it.
I'm sure my cooking
will improve over time.
(GULPS) Mmm, it's not that bad.
(SPITS)
Tomorrow, you need to go
to the butcher.
I'd like a nice roast for Sunday dinner.
Not your slut mother's goulash.
(LAUGHING)
A nice roast. Yes, ma'am.
Oh, and clean up this mess tonight.
I can't stand the sight of dirty dishes.
Oops.
- (GROANS SLOWLY)
- (SASHA LAUGHS)
Oops.
Good shot, Charles.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(LAUGHING)
Okay. I must get to these dishes.
But, this has been delightful. Really.
(DISTORTED NOISE ON TAPE)
Yes, it does sound like a bird.
And he's doing his best to mask his voice.
It's too bad the quality's so poor.
(WINCES) Uh...
Well, I'm afraid it's a dead end.
We should at least clean the tape.
Right.
(CLEARS THROAT)
You need some more tea. (CLEARS THROAT)
So, the person who killed Pinkney
and framed you,
is the same person
that attacked the art museum
and planted the bomb in the train station.
Amazing. And you don't have any leads?
I think Loeb was behind it.
Payback.
He still has lackeys in the GCPD.
- Is that so?
- Everything points to a cop.
Or someone who worked
with the police, had access.
(CLATTERING)
You all right, Ed?
Right as rain. Just thinking.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Surely, you don't think
that Loeb killed Pinkney himself?
No. He had some psychopath do it for him.
"Psychopath" seems a strong word.
He bludgeoned a man to death
with a crowbar in cold blood.
He's sick.
You say that, yet, you've killed
lots of people, haven't you?
That was in the line of duty.
And a person who would kill
in cold blood is a psychopath.
See, I-- I knew the rumors weren't true.
What rumors?
About you killing Galavan.
You would never do that.
That would make you
like the people that you're hunting.
Sick. Diseased.
(KETTLE WHISTLING)
Thar she blows. (CHUCKLES)
Shut up, you're talking too much.
Ed, did Penguin ever say
anything about that night?
Hmm?
Did Penguin ever tell you anything
about the night that Galavan died?
No. Remember?
I nipped that friendship in the bud.
And you didn't talk to him in the GCPD?
When Barnes brought him in?
Yes. No. I-- Just to say hi.
Oh, tape's finished.
I'm gonna give that a listen.
Let's both listen.
Swell idea.
MALE OPERATOR: Internal Affairs.
MALE CALLER: I--
(CLEARS THROAT) I want to report a crime.
I saw Detective James Gordon
shooting Mayor Theo Galavan
on the Southside Docks.
The Penguin was beating him with a bat,
but it was Gordon that pulled the trigger.
(CUCKOO CLOCK CHIMES)
It's not a bird.
It was mechanical.
Without fingers I point,
without arms I strike,
without feet I run. What am I?
- You're a clock.
- Correct.
I know it was you, Ed.
- Me?
- You.
(CUCKOO CLOCK CHIMES)
(LAUGHS)
Guess what?
I knew that you knew, that I knew.
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
That's why your chair's
wired to the mains.
(LAUGHING)
Over the pavement and down the alley
But why this wind is cold
(GRUNTS)
It bites my toes and nips my nose,
as over the ground that we go
(PANTING)
I hope you like the outdoors, Jimbo.
I know just the spot.
(GUN COCKS)
(JIM GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
Come out, come out wherever you are.
I bet you're wondering,
"Why would Ed do this to me?
"Set me up.
"Ruin my life."
I'll give you a hint, Jimbo.
K.K.
- Kristen Kringle.
- (GUN COCKS)
(DOOR OPENS)
ED: Rats.
SELINA: Hey, have you seen my jacket?
(PANTING)
It's freezing outside.
Sorry. I was fixing the sleeve.
You'd ripped it.
You know how to sew?
Alfred says it's an important skill
for young bachelors.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay.
Hmm.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
(DOOR OPENS)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
- SELINA: What the--
- Detective Gordon.
Bruce? What are you doing here?
I could ask the same about you.
I found the man who framed me.
(PANTING)
I need a phone-- (GRUNTS)
Great, a dead cop in my crib now.
GRACE: Don't forget the cherries, Oswald.
Oh. Right, cherries,
cherries, cherries, cherries.
GRACE: Oswald!
(SIGHS)
Oswald.
- (GASPS)
- My drink?
I'm sorry. There's no cherries.
No cherries?
The next time I ask for cherries,
there better be cherries.
Yes, Grace. Ma'am. Of course.
(GAGS)
(COUGHS)
(DOG WHIMPERS)
(SLURPING)
Mother said to remind you
of tomorrow's dinner.
- What's wrong with him?
- Who knows?
- Mother wants a roast.
- And make it good this time.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Yes, I will.
(DOG WHINING)
(THUD)
(LAUGHS MANIACALLY)
BRUCE: He's still sleeping.
Best thing for him.
Thank you for coming
when I called, Alfred.
Of course I came. No question.
You're looking thin.
- I'm getting plenty to eat.
- That I very much doubt, Master Bruce.
But there are things that we must discuss.
- I'm not coming back.
- I understand that--
- Not yet.
- But we need to talk--
- Alfred!
- JIM: Good morning.
Detective Gordon, should you be up?
- I'm fine. You stitched me up?
- Actually, it was Master Bruce.
He called from Selina Kyle's
when you passed out.
So I thought I'd bring you here.
Safest place for you.
Master Bruce,
I'm wondering if you might go
and get the detective his clothes
from the laundry room, please.
I'm glad you're okay.
So, I'll make you some breakfast.
Take a seat.
- Like some coffee?
- Yes, please.
- There we go.
- (SIGHS)
How long has Bruce
been living with Selina Kyle?
Ever since the Matches Malone debacle.
Turns out staring into the
cold, dead eyes of the man
that killed your parents
doesn't bring the right amount of closure.
Bruce never should've been in that room.
I should've gotten to Malone first.
Yes. You should've done.
But you didn't, did you?
Eh?
You can't un-fry an egg.
As my dear old mum used to say.
So, why don't we leave
Master Bruce's situation alone,
and why don't we discuss yours, eh?
It's a long story.
Right, so you were framed for the murder
of that other police officer.
You escaped from the prison,
you then tracked down
the man that framed you,
and you're promptly shot in the leg.
Right, so, answer me this, Detective.
Do you have any idea
how you're gonna get out
of this awful pickle?
Yes, I do.
HUGO: Come, my dear.
Your future awaits.
You're sure?
I run a hospital, not a prison.
You're sane.
It would be unethical and illegal
to keep you confined.
- What if I--
- Hush, now.
Life is full of uncertainty.
And if something does happen,
we're always here.
Off you go.
If you keep releasing lunatics
so liberally,
you're going to get a bad reputation.
I'm not looking for a good reputation.
We're releasing Barbara Kean into the wild
to observe her behavior.
- She's a beautiful experiment.
- MS. PEABODY: Hmm.
You know what she's going to do,
don't you?
I don't, actually.
But I do know it will be interesting.
Nygma was right about one thing.
I can't just go to the cops.
They'll never believe me.
- I need hard proof.
- Cops, right? Jerks.
Nygma said he met Penguin
for the first time in the woods.
That's right around the same time
his girlfriend went missing.
I think he was burying her.
Just like he was going to bury me.
What? You wanna find her body?
Touch of the old "needle
in the haystack," isn't it?
Nygma knows where she is.
What? You think he's gonna, what?
Straight tell you?
That's exactly what he's gonna do.
But I need help.
Whatever we can do.
Thanks. But I need someone
Barnes knows will betray me.
(CRUNCHING)
What?
Who do I talk to about the reward
for Jim Gordon?
Hey! Psst. Come here. Come here.
- Come here. Come here.
- Let go of me! I'm here for my reward.
- I'll give you a reward.
- BARNES: Bullock!
- Have you seen Jim Gordon?
- Depends. There really a ten grand?
Depends on your information.
He was at my place a couple of hours ago.
He'd been shot.
Shot? Who shot him?
Didn't say.
He wasn't making a lot of sense.
- Is he still there now?
- No, he took off.
I don't know where,
but he was just looking for a place
to lie low for a while, I guess.
That's not worth $10,000.
(SIGHS) Fine.
Before he left he said he'd found out
where the Penguin was hiding
and he was gonna go see him.
BARNES: Why would he go see the Penguin?
I don't know. Something about,
"Penguin knows where the body is buried."
- What bodies?
- I don't know!
- Where's the Penguin now?
- No one knows.
- You're gonna pay me or what?
- Or what?
(EXHALING HEAVILY)
Relax. Relax.
Maybe Gordon won't even find Penguin.
You idiot. He's a detective.
He finds people for a living.
Penguin won't tell him.
He's my friend.
Who am I kidding?
You idiot. Stupid. Stupid!
Okay, okay.
Okay, calculate, cal-- Calculate.
Chances of Gordon finding Penguin,
let's say 80%.
Chances of Penguin telling Gordon,
also 80%.
So that's a 60% chance
of Gordon finding Kristen.
That settles it.
- (WIND HOWLING)
- (BIRDS CHIRPING)
(GRUNTS)
Hello, Kristen.
I know, didn't expect to see me again,
but circumstances.
Now, I'm afraid
I'm gonna have to move you.
- Now--
- (TWIGS CRACKING)
Jim Gordon.
So you did find Penguin.
And that little bird sang.
No, I just followed you.
(LAUGHS)
You fed information to that little
miscreant assuming that I'd hear.
Or no. No, no, no.
Of course, you were in cahoots.
Well, either way, bravo, Jim.
I'd clap, but I have your gun in my hand.
How did this happen to you?
How did you become this?
You dummy, this is who I am.
It was just finally admitting
the truth to myself.
Well, that and murdering some people.
- I don't believe that.
- You don't believe it. Why, Jim?
'Cause it would make you incompetent?
To know that I was right
under your nose the whole time?
Or you don't wanna admit
that there's a monster in all of us,
because you, of all people,
should know that.
That's what made it so easy to frame you.
(LAUGHS)
I was your friend.
Were you, Jim?
Were you my friend?
Or did you just pity me?
"Oh, poor, weird, little Ed.
"With his little, silly wordplay
and his little riddles."
You're completely insane.
Yeah. It's probably easier
for you to think that.
How about one last riddle
for old time's sake?
"A nightmare for some.
"For others, a savior, I come.
"My hands, cold and bleak,
"it's the warm hearts they seek."
Death.
Right again.
Goodbye, Jim.
- BARNES: Drop the gun!
- (GUN COCKS)
- Drop it!
- (GUNS COCKING)
(STAMMERING)
Captain Barnes, I'm arresting Jim.
Stop it, Ed. We heard everything!
Now, drop the gun and get on your knees!
No, this is-- This-- I'm-- He's-- He's--
Last chance!
(GRUNTS)
Oh, crud.
How is it? Not too gamey?
Hmm. Overcooked.
Try the other joint.
It is much more tender.
Hmm. It's the same.
Mmm.
Still, beats my slut mother's goulash, no?
Where are the children?
Ring the bell again.
Hmm. I doubt they'll hear it.
You look different.
(CHUCKLES) You noticed!
Yes. I'm doing my hair a different way.
Charles! Sasha! Where are they?
I found the sherry decanter, Grace.
The one with poison in it
that you used to kill my father.
What on Earth are you talking about?
You should've thrown it away.
Guess you're a little too mean
to waste good poison, huh?
(GASPS)
Don't go.
Charles! Sasha! Help!
- They won't come.
- Where are they?
You thought they tasted the same.
But Sasha--
(SMACKS LIPS) Mmm.
- No. No. No.
- Definitely more tender.
- No!
- In my opinion.
- No! No!
- (SCREAMS)
BARNES: You said you were innocent.
And you were.
I'm glad.
I guess I owe you an apology.
No. You were doing your duty.
Can't fault you for that.
Ah, well, I owe you one.
Not necessary. But I'll take it.
Can you do me a favor,
and take it easy on Bullock?
- (SIGHS)
- Thanks.
So, when are you coming back to work?
- I'm not coming back. Not yet, anyhow.
- No?
There's something I have to do first.
Lee Thompkins' number.
She's working for
an M.E. Department down south.
I promised Bruce Wayne
I'd solve his parents' murder.
I have to do that first.
Then, I'm free.
The Wayne case is closed, Jim.
The perp is dead.
But who hired him? Why?
I need to find out.
Sometimes we never find out.
It happens.
I need you to give me the Wayne files.
You take this
and I'll give you the Wayne files.
Call her.
I'll go get 'em.
It was nothing that you did
or didn't do, Alfred.
Why I went away.
I want you to know that.
I do.
Thank you very much.
I'll be going back to the city
as soon as Selina's ready.
She's just taking a hot shower.
Hmm.
You do know that Mr. Lucius Fox
fixed your old man's computer
a couple of days ago, don't you?
And when were you going
to tell me, Alfred?
Well, I tried telling you this morning.
I'm telling you again now, aren't I?
- Don't--
- What're you doing?
She could walk in here.
Have a word.
- I trust her.
- It's about trust, is it?
Look, whatever your father was doing,
he did it in secret for a reason.
To protect those he loved.
And it's got--
It doesn't matter about
my personal opinion about that young girl.
But she has been a bloody good friend
to you and she's been loyal.
So, I'm gonna let you go ahead.
Continue your father's work.
I can't stop you.
I mean I've tried, haven't I?
But I will not have you put that
little girl's life in danger.
It's either the work or it's her.
Can't have both. Do you understand?
Ugh! Man, rich people
have great water pressure.
(SELINA SIGHS)
So, Jeeves, any chance
we can get a ride back to the city?
Right, well, I'll be in the...
In the kitchen, Master Bruce.
Miss.
What's with him?
Bruce, what's going on?
I'm not going back.
What?
I'm grateful for everything
that you taught me.
My place is here.
(SCOFFS)
So, that's it?
Wow.
I don't expect you to understand.
Right, 'cause you're Bruce Wayne
and I'm street trash.
- Selina, it's not like that.
- Yeah, it is.
It is.
(SIGHS)
It's fine.
Have a great life, Bruce Wayne.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(WOMAN GRUNTS)
(SHOUTING CONTINUES)
(EXHALES)
(BEEPING)
AUTOMATED VOICE: System enabled.
Thompkins.
Hello? Hello?
(HANGS UP)
Hi, Jim.
English - SDH