Previously onGotham...
My forefathers were betrayed.
Their legacy erased.
I'm here to punish those
who robbed us.
- We have a deal.
- We do.
I'll do whatever it takes,
I'll train every day.
Yeah, well, you said that before,
ain't you?
I'll even go back to school.
I saved your life.
You wanna do it, too,
you just don't have guts.
Selina, I missed you.
This is not what we rehearsed.
I'm so sorry, Jerome.
Enter the hero.
Gentlemen, ladies, others.
Let us discuss the future
with a little civility, shall we?
So not one of you knows
who orchestrated
and/or executed the Arkham breakout?
I find that hard to believe.
I mean, the cop's only lead
is an old blind man, for God's sake.
A blind man!
Then, who here is to be trusted?
Because someone knows.
We thought it was you.
Why would I do that?
We've never had it better.
I gave you all of the freedom
in the world and business boomed,
for all of us.
A new generation.
Then that ginger maniac
had to spoil everything.
Even now he's dead,
the public's still terrified,
business is in the can.
And what are we doing?
Fighting among ourselves.
Is this how any of us want to live?
Squabbling, brawling, running,
hiding?
This city belong to us now.
But kids,
that brings responsibilities.
We need to restore confidence
in our brand, if you will.
We need discipline and unity, yes?
There will be no more chaos,
no more gang wars.
No more blood in the streets
scaring decent folk.
From now on,
if you want to kill someone,
blackmail, steal or kidnap anyone,
I need to hear about it first.
Understand?
Hey, boss, there's a new girl.
Bravo.
Quite the King Solomon.
You have them nicely in line.
Who are you?
My brother would very much like
to talk to you.
- Alone.
- Why you looking at me like that?
You don't know me.
Relax, Butch. He has issues.
Bipolar.
She doesn't know me, I have to say.
- Your brother?
- Theodore Galavan.
There's a car waiting for you
outside.
I'm sick and tired of your
"Holier than thou" crap, Gordon.
Yeah, then do some police work.
The last arrest you made
was your bookie.
My name is Nathaniel Barnes.
Captain Nathaniel Barnes.
That's right, I'm your new boss.
Ten hut!
You, clean that up.
You know when this place was built?
Over a hundred years ago.
Can you imagine how many perps
have been booked in here
since that time?
All the murderers, rapists,
thieves have been locked up?
They don't make them like this
anymore.
Strong, sturdy.
And yet...
just days ago...
an escaped convict just strolls
in here, in to our house.
Our house.
And murders your commissioner,
and nine of your fellow comrades.
I wasn't even here, and I'm ashamed.
Are you all ashamed?
I hope so.
Anyone is here that's not ashamed
and angry should resign.
Right now.
Some of you are lying to yourselves.
I've got your files here.
I've read them all.
Step forward if you hear
your name called.
Pollard.
Guthrie, Coulson, Dowler, Brooks,
Perez, Hightower.
You aren't ashamed.
You have no shame.
You're not police...
you're low-life criminals.
Bribery, drug abuse, extortion,
racketeering.
Sons of bitches! You're all fired!
Drop off your badges and your guns
with the desk sergeant
on your way out.
Hey, you can't do this.
We got rights.
Yes, you're right,
you do have rights.
You have the right to remain silent,
you have the right to an attorney.
Take him.
From now on any officer,
detective, rookie or clerk
who breaks the law
will not just lose their job,
they will go to jail.
If you turn a blind eye to a crime,
I will bust you.
If you fail to help a fellow officer
because of cowardice or apathy,
I will bust you!
What the hell you still doing here?
Don't make me mad.
Anyone who didn't hear
their name called,
get back to work.
I like to see you in my office,
please.
Well, what do you think
about what I said out there?
I agreed with every word, sir.
Every word, huh?
You a sycophant, Gordon?
No, sir.
I've read all your files.
Army, academy, G.C.P.D.
You're a troublemaker.
A fighter.
Is that an accurate assessment?
Yes, sir.
Good.
You're now my second command.
Starting now, Jim.
We're gonna fix this department
and bring respect for law
and order back to this city.
Yes, sir.
We're kind of short-handed.
Well, you think I cut too deep?
You could have thrown out 20 more
guys and not hit bottom.
Fixing this department
is gonna be tough.
Maybe tougher
than you think, sir.
Welcome to my unit,
you sad-ass army hump.
Tough is what we eat for breakfast.
A jarhead, huh?
Who would have guessed.
Sir.
I hope you told him
he made a huge mistake.
I don't think he did.
Come on, Jim.
We've seen his type come and go.
Idealists, always looking
to walk a straight line.
Gotham doesn't have straight lines.
It's got twists and turns
and dead ends.
Yeah. It doesn't have to be that way.
With Mayor James still missing
and the deputy mayor
recently murdered,
the need for leadership at City Hall
is of paramount concern
to Gotham's citizens.
Today, two more hopeful candidates
have thrown their hats into the ring.
Janice Caulfield is a city councilor
who began her political career
as an environmental activist.
Randall Hobbs, the longest
serving teamster boss
in Gotham's history
is another candidate
with a strong base.
In the latest polls, though,
a surprise surge for a man
who has not even declared
his candidacy.
Theo Galavan.
The dashing billionaire businessman
has not ruled out a bid
for the mayor's job.
But he is considering his options
according to his spokesman.
Mr. Cobblepot, finally, we meet.
Call me Penguin.
I thought I heard you hated
that name.
It grew on me.
Penguin it is. Please sit.
How's your head?
Healing, thank you.
Gave me quite the scare.
You were lucky to get out
of there with your life.
Wasn't I just?
Was it luck?
You are a clever man.
Perfect timing, dear.
Do you two know each other?
We've met.
Oh, my.
The Arkham breakout...
the G.C.P.D massacre,
Jerome and the Maniax.
All you.
Of course.
Guilty.
It was foolish of me to think
I could trick The King of Gotham.
Here, you need this more than me.
I'll make another.
My sister tells me
you're doing a stellar job
of organizing your new empire.
I try.
You're not The King of Gotham,
you're the King of Garbage.
A year ago I held Fish Mooney's
umbrella.
Now she's dead by my hand.
Along with Maroni.
Falcone is in hiding
and all of their businesses are mine.
They all underestimated me.
I suggest you not make
the same mistake.
My sister is too blunt.
But she is honest.
The foundations of this great city
were laid 200 years ago
by some very dedicated people.
Now, it's an old, crumbling pigsty,
full of human waste.
It's time to move into the future.
A cleaner, brighter...
future.
Those are all residential areas,
so thousands of homes would have
to be destroyed, wouldn't they?
Yes, so?
Here's the rub.
In order to rebuild,
I need first to destroy.
But I can't do that.
I mean, watch the news,
I'm a hero.
But you have a certain flare
for such a task.
You, Penguin...
you will be my destroyer.
Truly, I'm flattered.
Thank you so much for thinking of me.
But, my dear sir,
you have me all wrong.
I have no flare for destruction,
I'm a builder, a problem solver.
Besides, such a huge project
would need the support
of hundreds of city officials.
Yes. Only the highest authority
could see it through correctly.
Say, a mayor
with a landslide mandate.
- But you're not a candidate.
- Oh, I will be.
By popular demand.
Alas, some of my fellow
candidates
actually stand a chance of winning,
so, they'll have to go.
- Go?
- And I'm gonna need you
to take a crack of me also
and miss, of course.
Don't want anyone to think
that I had anything to do
with my fellow candidates demise.
That's smart thinking.
However, all due respect,
Mr. Galavan, I'm not your man.
You need an assassin.
This is Gotham, you can find them
in the phone book.
Under A.
One moment, Mr. Penguin.
I'm sorry.
I took you for a man of vision.
Tabitha, do you wanna get
the remote, dear.
Yeah, yeah.
Before you leave,
my sister would like to show you
her favorite reality show.
She's addicted.
She's being kind of dull right now,
but sometimes she cries
and bangs on the door.
- Please.
- Mother.
I swear, I swear, I don't do nothing.
You'll pay for this.
That's the spirit.
They die, your mother lives.
Simple.
Where is my boy? Please!
I swear, I swear, I don't do nothing.
- Thompkins.
- Good morning, Dr. Thompkins.
Captain Barnes, GCPD.
Captain Barnes, hi.
I hear great things about you, Doc.
Get ready to get real busy.
We're gonna be sending you
a whole lot of dead bad guys.
Okay, okay?
May I speak to Jim.
He wants to talk to you.
This is Gordon.
Meet me at the Police Academy
at 0700.
The academy? Yes, sir.
If you don't mind me asking, sir.
Everybody knows
you're banging the M.E.
See you in an hour.
Oldest in your class.
Not the strongest or fastest
or even the most
academically gifted either,
and yet you finished the top
of your class.
How did you do that?
I'll tell you how.
You were a soldier.
You saw combat
while your classmates
were still playing with themselves
in their parent's basements.
You got blood on your face.
You could say that.
You're a warrior, Jim.
So am I.
But you can't carry on
the way you been.
Going after everyone on your own.
You need help that you can rely on.
With all the respect, sir.
What if there were a team
of young cops
who haven't been bought yet?
Not jaded, not corrupted,
still filled with hope and faith
in the system.
Cadets?
This is the greatest academy
in the country,
graduation is next week.
We can grab a group
of their finest
before some precinct kills
their spirit.
Wouldn't hurt to look into it, right?
- Gus!
- Captain Barnes.
This is Gordon.
Sure, I remember this guy.
He argued a lot.
I'd like to think
I was raising questions.
- What you got for us?
- This way.
Keep your eye on the little one.
The one getting her ass handed
to her?
Wait.
Patience.
Not your strongest virtue,
if I remember, right, Gordon?
State wrestling champ,
academy running back.
Why this place
and not a sports scholarship?
People from my neighborhood
don't get scholarships.
They join gangs and sell drugs.
I needed to change the direction
my life was going.
Mr. Martinez,
says you're the best shot
this school's ever seen.
Where d'you learn to shoot?
Gotham gun range,
one of my mother's three jobs
was cleaning it.
When she died,
the owner let me go there
after hours and practice,
until I worked out my anger.
I still go there.
You're way too smart
to be here, Garrett.
- Don't tell me, your father's a cop?
- Negative.
My father's family business
was destroyed by armed thugs
who demanded he pay them
protection money.
When he refused they beat him
half to death.
I'm here to make sure
that doesn't ever happen again.
Garrett.
Pinkney.
Josie.
Martinez.
Do you swear to honor that badge
with your life?
Yes, sir!
Congratulations.
You are now Unit Alpha
of the GCPD Strike Force
under the command
of Detective James Gordon.
You will answer only to him,
and him only to me.
Dismissed.
Strike force?
Got a nice ring to it, doesn't it?
They're good kids...
but facing what's out there
at their age?
That's a big risk, sir.
True, but what have we got to lose?
Yes, sir.
For your acts of courage
in the face of overwhelming
uncertainty,
the City of Gotham would like to
give you this token of appreciation.
The Medal of Valor and Bravery.
Mr. Galavan.
Please, Theo.
Theo, for Pete's sake,
why aren't you running for mayor?
Get down!
Everybody stay where you are!
Everyone okay? Everyone?
You know what?
Gothamites don't buckle
under pressure.
And neither will I.
We will not be intimidated
by the scum
that seeks to reduce this
great city of Gotham to ruin.
If the bad guys wanna stop me
running,
well, then, I guess I got no choice.
I will run for mayor.
Yes.
Hello, Caulfield for mayor.
Yes, will do!
Excuse me, you can't go in there.
Miss Caulfield, what a pleasure.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I can see what you are.
How did you get in?
I know it's late,
but I'm afraid there's no time
for delay.
Someone tried to kill
Theo Galavan this morning.
Are you here to kill me?
Actually, yes.
Please, no...
I'm a mother.
Wait.
I have a mother too.
Steady now, folks.
Just think of blue sky
and cornfields.
That's what I do.
Why are you doing this?
Darling, I've got no freaking idea.
We've been doing crazy stuff
all day long.
Well, we're away, then.
Sorry to ruin your evening.
Now remember...
yeah, I got your names
and addresses.
So think about your families
and keep mum, eh?
Are waiting for someone?
No.
That's your job.
That's for Reggie.
I know you killed him.
Now I don't know what you want
with Master Bruce,
but I'm certain
that his life is gonna be damn
slight better without you in it.
So you do yourself a favor,
trickle...
jog on.
All good.
Oh, Master Bruce.
You know, I could always pull up
front if you want.
No, I... Alfred, I don't want
the other kids to see...
To see that you've got a butler,
yeah, I completely understand that.
I made dinner reservations
as requested for tomorrow night.
Mr. Galavan suggested
the Regal Hotel, very posh.
You're gonna be forking out serious
dosh for that, I'll tell you that.
He saved my life,
dinner is the least I can do
to repay him.
Master Bruce, where are you going?
Now I clocked Wayne Manor
at exactly six and a half miles.
It should take you 90 minutes
to two hours,
depending on how many times
you stop, of course.
Now you said you wanted to train,
to prepare.
And this is it.
Wait, you...
You expect me to walk?
No, Master Bruce.
I expect you to run.
Ms. Kringle...
ever since I first laid eyes
on you,
I've felt this deep connection.
Perhaps you've felt it too.
Cheesy.
Ms. Kringle, you've perhaps felt
my affections from afar.
Afar? Really?
God.
Ms. Kringle...
Be quiet.
I don't need your opinion.
What you need is to stop mumbling
and fumbling and tell her what's up.
Well, she's been bullied
and taken for granted for too long.
- I want her to understand...
- You saved her life for God's sake!
She owes you.
Take what you deserve.
Ms. Kringle.
Dinner, tonight.
Chez Moi. Eight o'clock.
Okay.
- I'd like that.
- You will.
A wise cop once said,
if you catch a kid smashing
a window, even a small one,
bust him.
You let it slide,
and he'll smash another one.
Then he'll tag a wall
or steal a bike,
rob a store, maybe hold someone up.
Crime unpunished
is a crime in itself.
This city is bleeding to death...
from the amount of free passes
we hand out.
Time to put a tourniquet
over that wound.
And from now on,
no one gets a free pass.
What is this strike force for?
To send a message
that this epidemic of lawlessness
will no longer be treated
but extinguished.
With extreme prejudice.
Gentlemen, lady, your new uniforms.
Sir, got a caller
says Councilor Caulfield
has been attacked.
Says she's dead.
No security cameras.
Galavan and now her.
Looks like a damn pattern.
Only she's dead.
Come on, people.
Who knows what.
Just give us a name, a description.
You will not have to testify.
They have our names and addresses.
Ms. Caulfield was stabbed repeatedly.
Probably drowned in her own blood.
Forget it, Jim.
The man with the knife was short,
fancy clothes.
Walked funny.
Mr. Galavan, thank you
for meeting me.
Oh, it's an honor,
pleasure's all mine.
I'll meet you in the lobby,
Master Bruce.
Oh, why not dine with us?
That's very kind of you, sir,
but I don't think it's appropriate.
And I know that Master Bruce
want to speak to you on his own.
Sir.
Thanks, Alfred.
Enjoy.
Do you like this place?
I've never been here before.
To be honest, I don't go out much.
Well, I hope I can change that.
There's always some tedious function
I could drag you to.
I just, I wanted this opportunity
to thank you in person
for saving my life.
Oh, you're very kind.
The truth is, I don't know
what came over me.
I don't think I was in
complete control of my faculties.
I also wanted to speak with you
face to face.
Regarding your parent's passing.
I find it astonishing
that the police have failed
to produce any evidence
or any real suspects
in all this time.
It is disappointing.
Even your father's own company,
Wayne Enterprises,
has failed to advance
the investigation in any way.
It's shocking.
Yes, Mr. Galavan,
it's very disappointing.
That's Silver.
- I'm sorry?
- Silver St. Cloud.
Her father was my step-brother.
He passed, sadly.
She's my ward now.
Would you like to meet her?
Yes.
Hello, my dear.
Uncle.
I'd like to introduce you
to Bruce Wayne.
- Nice to meet you, Bruce.
- Hello.
I was early so I came out here,
it's such a warm day.
Do you know, I do believe
that you two will be sharing
a school soon.
Anders Prep, yes?
Silver just got back to Gotham
after two years abroad.
Switzerland, Geneva.
Yes. We have a house there.
So, what's it like?
- Switzerland?
- No, Prep, silly.
I think it's fine.
I've been homeschooling
for quite a while now.
So I'm virtually a new boy too.
Then we shall brave it together.
I was kind of expecting a restaurant.
Ms. Kringle, I'm so sorry, I've...
I'm sorry, I should have been
more clear,
I like to cook.
I'm a good cook. Is that okay?
It is, it is, and perhaps
you should call me Kristen.
Kristen.
Hobbs' campaign office
is the entire second floor.
You sure about this?
Don't worry, I've got it
under control.
Okay, you gotta tell me
what the hell is going on...
I know I gotta do
whatever you say.
But at least tell me
why the hell we're doing it.
They have my mother, Butch.
- Who?
- Galavan and his sister.
They have her.
They're making me do this.
Holy smokes.
We gotta find your mum.
If they find out we're looking,
they'll hurt her.
Don't worry, we'll find her.
He's here.
Let's go.
Got it. Thanks.
I still think we should move you
somewhere a little more secure.
Forget it. Anyone has the guts
to come for me,
they'll find out real soon
who they're messing with.
Who the hell are you?
I came here to volunteer.
Well, run back and whoever hired you
tell them I'm not going anywhere.
This city needs me.
Cool pins.
Count, idiot, there's five of us.
I know, hardly seems fair.
Move, move, move, move, move! Go!
Keep going!
There you go. Right there!
Go!
G.C.P.D! Put down your weapon!
We should fan out.
Flank him from both sides,
catch him in our crossfire.
Yeah, do that.
I'll cover you, go!
Okay, so they move well.
Unexpected.
Move! Move, move, move!
Let's go!
Shooter got away, sir.
You just met Victor Zsasz.
Works for Penguin these days.
What the hell is Penguin playing at?
No, I feel like I owe you an apology,
I feel as though I've been nothing
but mean to you.
No, I don't think that's fair.
I feel like all I've ever done
is annoy you.
I've been consistently inappropriate.
No, no, no, it's me.
You've been nothing but sweet.
And I ignored your card
and your gift.
Ms. Kringle, I can honestly say
that our interactions
are always the highlight of my day.
Please, Kristen.
Oh, my God, I even accused you
of writing Dougherty's goodbye note.
Right, crazy.
I mean, who knows
what that jerk was thinking?
Jerk.
How I ever let him lay a hand
on me, I'll never know.
I'm glad he's dead.
Well, he just left town,
he's not dead.
Right, yeah, I know.
Figure of speech.
He's dead to you.
Out of your life. Not dead dead.
I'm gonna use the restroom.
You blew it, dummy. Nice work.
Leave me alone!
Are you talking to me?
No.
Honestly, Kristen,
I wasn't talking to you.
Who else is there?
I talk...
to myself.
It's crazy, I know, I just,
I have this...
I have this voice inside my head,
a sort of stronger version of me,
that keeps this me in line,
because I'm such a klutz.
I can understand that.
I think that we all have
a voice like that.
You think?
What was your inner voice saying?
He was mad at me
for spoiling the mood.
It was, it was a really nice mood.
But my inner voice is telling me
that I think maybe
we can get back there.
You killed Caulfield.
We have a witness.
And the attempt on Galavan,
was that you too?
- Not now.
- And Hobbs,
- you sent Zsasz there?
- It's complicated, okay?
What does it profit you
to mess with the election?
You have your own sordid empire
to rule over.
Walk away, Jim. Let me be.
The GCPD has new leadership,
no more deals, no more favors.
If they find out
you're behind these attacks,
we will come after you
with everything...
Rousing speech, really!
Goosebumps.
But you came here alone, Jim,
with no warrant, no cuffs,
no back-up, and why?
Because you would hate
your new captain
to find out about how you gunned
down Ogden Barker in cold blood.
Over a debt.
A debt to me.
He was trying to kill me.
Where are your witnesses?
And just that day before,
I suppose you did not ask me
to run Commissioner Loeb out of town
so that you can get
your old job back?
I'll face whatever's coming to me.
As will I.
Goodbye, Jim.
- Obviously.
- I don't think so.
- I think...
- I'm serious.
Hey, you shouldn't be joking
about near misses.
Next bullet might get stuck
right in your eye.
Yes, sir.
No joking.
All right, gather around.
Today I'm giving the strike force
its first real mission.
Build a case to put away Gotham's
enemy number one.
Time to take down The Penguin.
Bruce?
Hey, Selina, come on, let's go.
I don't know what you want
with Master Bruce,
but I'm certain that his life's
gonna be a damn sight better
without you in it.
So, what do you think? Red...
or blue?
- Red.
- Blue.
- Blue it is.
- I want some fun.
I'm sick of staying indoors.
Patience, Barbara.
Your time will come.
The wheel is turning.
While the GCPD chase The Penguin
I'll steal the mayor's office right
from under their noses.
Did you find her?