Previously on Gotham...
I'll find my way out.
'Cause this place is just one big puzzle,
and puzzles are my forte.
Oh, my.
I don't know who you are anymore.
Please. That is such a ridiculous cliché...
It's time for me to look out
for number one.
The man who contracted Matches Malone
to kill your parents
called himself the Philosopher.
"Hugo Strange, the Philosopher."
I was one of the ones who forced
Thomas Wayne to shut down the program.
You're lying. I needed to be sure
you were behind all this.
And now I am.
Our creations need new personae
to give their minds focus.
That sword was made yesterday.
Our replica is central to his acceptance
of his new identity.
I am Azrael.
My Lord Dumas...
Command me.
A murderer walks the streets
of the city a free man.
By your blade, he must be destroyed.
- Tell me his name.
- James Gordon.
That is not possible.
You?
You're dead.
Not anymore.
What is the meaning of this?
You are upsetting the inmates.
Where's your boss, darling?
We got a warrant to search his office
and everything in it.
He's busy with patients.
That's quite all right, Ms. Peabody.
We're gonna tear this place apart,
Strange. We're gonna get answers.
Answers to what?
Records indicate Theo Galavan's dead body
was brought here, that it was cremated.
Seems likely.
Then why the hell
was he at the GCPD last night
running our captain through
with a sword, huh?
I'm surprised as you are.
And while you're at it,
explain to me this.
Why Victor Fries, also last seen here,
very dead, is alive and kicking
and dressed like a spaceman.
You stink, Strange.
This whole damn place stinks.
Excuse me.
- Is this your office?
- Yes.
But, Detective, please.
What the...
Shredded? Son of a...
Spring cleaning.
You are free to look around.
I'm just not sure
there's much more to see.
Do you think shredding a few documents
is gonna save you? It won't.
We're onto you.
Bad guys come in and monsters come out.
Just like Pinewood, right?
Seeing as how you no longer work
for the police department,
I'm not required to speak with you.
Mr. Gordon.
You have a lot of anger, James Gordon.
I can help you with that.
We're gonna tear this damn building apart.
Every square inch.
Check your warrant, Detective.
It clearly states that you have permission
to search my office. Nothing more.
Of course, I am more than happy
to accommodate you.
If you come back with a different warrant.
Just know
that I will also be calling the judge,
and telling him how disruptive it is
to have the GCPD
and others,
traipsing about this place of healing
and disrupting the patients unnecessarily.
This ain't over yet.
Has Azrael returned?
Nope.
Troubling.
Hey. Hey.
What are you doing out of your cell?
Big mistake. Sorry. My bad. Just got lost.
Escort me back, would you?
Thank you.
Thank you. Have a nice day.
I've gotta get out of here.
Damn kids.
Did you break the lock?
Hey, you.
This is God's house, a place of worship.
Not a homeless shelter.
Get out before I call the cops!
I need a weapon to fulfill my holy quest.
I don't have any weapons.
Oh.
Then what good are you?
Captain Nathaniel Barnes
remains in critical condition
at Gotham General
after suffering a violent attack
by a masked assailant late last night.
So far, no arrests have been made,
but reports coming from
within the locked down GCPD
have confirmed that the masked man
is, in fact,
former Gotham mayor, Theo Galavan.
Search parties
continued throughout the night,
but as of yet,
Galavan's whereabouts remain a mystery.
There's nowhere to hide, Galavan.
I'm coming for you.
Alvarez, any sign of him yet?
No, but we've got
six choppers in the air
and every sniffer dog in the state
out there looking.
Call the brass upstate,
tell them to get more men down here.
That freak couldn't have gotten far.
Tom, get Judge Bam Bam on the phone.
Tell him I need a new warrant
to search Arkham.
Every frigging room, all of it.
What are they all doing?
They don't have a captain, Harvey.
Guess you're it.
I ain't no captain.
- Say something to them.
- I don't work here anymore. You do.
All right, everyone, listen up.
I know we're all a bit freaked out
right now.
It's understandable, hmm?
Some nutjob in a Halloween costume
and cape comes in to our house,
and takes out four of our brothers.
He does this to our captain.
Now, I've been around a long time.
It's like the bad guys in this town
just keep getting weirder and weirder.
But under that mask,
he's just a man, and he can bleed.
Just like you and me.
And if he bleeds, he can be beaten.
So let's do what the cap would tell us
to do if he were here.
Let's go out there
and let's find that son of a bitch.
And let's get him, whatever it takes!
All right.
- I'm not one for speeches.
- No, no, no. You did fine.
But?
If that was Galavan that I saw,
he'll know how to stay out of sight.
We gotta think outside the box.
Like what?
Who knows him best?
Who's still in the city?
His sister.
Alfred, pull over.
Master Bruce, are you out of your tiny,
bloody mind?
There's a madman loose on the streets.
Now is not the time to go running around
on your own, is it?
I don't plan on being on my own.
With all due respect, sir,
what good will a 15-year-old little
girl do, even if Galavan does turn up?
Strange lied to the police.
I know and so do you.
- I can't stay at home and do nothing.
- We need to trust Jim Gordon.
I'm tired of trusting Jim Gordon.
Aren't you?
I am your guardian, Master Bruce.
And it's my job to protect you.
Is it your job to watch me sit on my hands
and do nothing?
Alfred, please.
Let me go.
- Hey, buddy. Move your car.
Just... Just be careful, all right?
I will.
- Hey! Let's go!
- Yeah, all right, mate. Keep...
Just keep your bloody hair on.
Don't go, baby, come on.
Let's talk about this, huh?
- Is this because I kicked Barbara out?
- Just let me go, Butch.
Come on, I'll do whatever you want.
I'll eat more fruit.
I'll work on the snoring.
I swear to God, whatever you need...
Catch you guys at a bad time?
Seriously?
How do people keep getting in here?
Do I have no security at all?
Why the rush?
- Just time to move on.
- Oh, yeah, is that it?
Or are you worried
Galavan's coming after you, too?
Don't worry, Butch.
It's not about you.
She's just scared of her brother.
Come on, help me find him.
You two hardly left on the best of terms.
Must have been weird
to see your dead brother
show up dressed like a ninja
from Medieval Times.
That thing that stabbed your captain
last night?
It wasn't my brother.
That was a 300-year-old
assassin called Azrael.
Azrael?
That image I saw on the news, his clothes,
the way he moved...
It was Azrael.
A mythical figure worshipped by the monks
who raised my brother.
A cold-hearted killing machine sent into
the night to kill his master's enemies.
And he wants you.
An ancient assassin?
A legend.
My family used to tell stories of him.
He was real?
Who knows?
It was 300 years ago. Probably, yes.
So your brother's gone nuts?
You tell me.
Theo convince you that he was Azrael
last night, or was he acting?
Someone got inside my brother's head.
It's not a safe place to be.
If you're right, I wanna find this person,
but first I have to find your brother.
So, help me.
If a search team finds him,
they're gonna kill him.
He is still your brother, after all.
He's blood.
The sword that was used last night?
The one that broke?
- It was fake.
- And you know this how?
The real one belonged to my grandfather.
He was an antiquities collector,
obsessed with Dumas history.
I saw it once. It was beautiful.
Forged by the monks themselves.
It's said to hold supernatural powers.
Theo knew this.
It's possible
he'll attempt to steal it back.
Does your grandfather still have it?
And where is he?
Gotham Cemetery.
He's been dead for 20 years.
But he was buried with his treasures.
Selina?
What's up?
I remember you telling me you were
still feeding your friend's birds.
Someone has to.
Why are you here?
- Have you seen the news?
- Walking zombies in Gotham?
What's new?
Strange worked for my father
on a project designed to help people.
He perverted it
and now I believe he's found a way to...
Bring back the dead?
- A little far-fetched, don't you think?
- Perhaps.
But he's hiding something.
The police have failed to find out what.
I think I can do better.
That so?
When my father shut down Strange,
he was killed.
Selina, I just want the truth, that's all.
You just won't be happy
until you get yourself killed, will you?
Victor Fries and Theo Galavan
both went to Arkham as dead men.
Both returned.
- I don't care.
- So did your friend Bridgit.
Wait, they sent her to Arkham?
She may still be there right now.
- Alive.
I told her to leave town.
To run, but she didn't listen.
It's my fault she's there.
Selina, we can put this right.
Strange was ready for the police.
He may even have been tipped off.
The only way we're gonna find out
what's really going on in there,
is if we break in ourselves.
Break in?
To Arkham?
A highly guarded place
that's packed with crazy people?
If that's too dangerous for you,
I'll just go myself.
I didn't say that.
Prisons are meant to stop people
from breaking out, not in. It can be done.
It's a looney bin.
Not a prison.
I know it can be done.
But I go alone.
Why?
I get caught, they'll just toss me out.
Nobody cares about me.
But you? They see you coming,
and they'll shut that whole thing down
quicker than you can say rat.
And then you'll never find out
what they've been up to.
That, or they'll just kill you.
Besides,
I already know a way in.
This is it.
The Dumas crypt.
Dozens of my relatives are buried here.
So, does someone have a key?
All right. Key. Crowbar.
This one. My grandfather's.
Wait, wait, wait.
I'm sure we're breaking
more than a few laws right now.
Really? This is where you draw the line?
Come on.
This doesn't creep you out
even a little bit?
- It's frigging grave robbing.
- Whatever it takes, Harvey.
Little help?
Oh!
That was said to be Azrael's sword
up until the end.
- He died?
- No, he disappeared.
Azrael's thought to be immortal.
It's beautiful.
I will take that.
James Gordon.
Time. To. Die.
Step aside. He must die.
It's me, brother.
Don't you recognize me?
My quarrel is not with you. Step aside.
Tabitha. Your sister.
I have what you're looking for.
Tabitha?
That's right.
You remember where we grew up?
The estate by the sea?
Before the monks took you.
Our dogs, the horses?
We were happy once.
You are Theo Galavan.
My brother.
Theo?
Yes.
Theo Galavan, the new mayor.
Do you remember now?
Death to the Son of Gotham.
Bruce Wayne.
We were sent to kill him.
Yes. Yes, but...
He dishonored our family name.
Yes.
Death to the Son of Gotham.
Thank you for reminding me.
Traitor.
Go through the folding iron.
There you go.
Come on, let's go.
- Harvey?
- He's gone.
This is Bullock.
I need a backup down at the cemetery.
Galavan's in the wind, again.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
- I made him remember.
- Remember what?
Bruce.
Death to the Son of Gotham.
Stay with her. I need to find Bruce.
Hey!
Stop!
- I need this car.
- You ain't a cop anymore.
I need the damn car.
It's okay.
- What do we got here?
- Looks good.
Put that with the other one.
All right. This looks good.
Ugh.
Come on, come on.
- Master Bruce?
- No, it's me. Where's Bruce?
I don't know, he was in the city.
Where in the city?
Well, to be perfectly honest,
I haven't got the foggiest.
He's got a mind of his own at the moment,
that one, ain't he?
All right, well, we need to find him.
Galavan could be coming after him.
Well, you having a laugh, ain't you?
I thought he was after you.
He was.
Tabitha must have jogged his memory.
Reminded him of his original mission.
To kill Bruce Wayne.
- Right, well, I'll get the motor.
- No, no, no. You stay there.
In case he comes back. Where was the last
place you saw him in the city?
Uh, Collins and Delaney.
Last I saw of him, he was headed
for the roof to see that Selina, I reckon.
All right, I'll head over there.
Till then, be safe.
Right, so. Will do.
Oh, for Pete's sake, Master Bruce.
Creeping up on someone like that,
I could've filleted you.
I'm sorry.
- What's wrong?
- Galavan, Master Bruce.
Theo bloody Galavan is what's wrong.
Okay. Okay.
Holy cow!
Forensic guy?
- Street trash girl?
- You framed Gordon.
And you tried to get a reward
by turning him in.
Mmm, yeah.
- What the hell are you doing here?
I gotta get out of here.
This place is crazy.
They'll be looking for me.
Which way is out of here?
I'll help you if you help me.
Where's Strange right now?
Okay.
Look, I barely know you.
But that is the last person
that you wanna be looking for.
Why is that?
The basement here. It's horrible.
Just trust me. Stay away.
He is a very dangerous man.
Basement?
Alive people.
Dead people.
Dead-alive people. It's horrible.
Okay, how do I get there?
It's like I'm saying things
and you're just not hearing them.
He has a friend of mine
and I'm here to get her out.
Now, how do I get there?
- You'll tell me the way out?
- Yes.
Okay.
There's an elevator.
I'll tell you where it is,
but can you pick a lock?
Why'd you have to be brave, huh?
I just got used to you being around.
Partners, right?
How am I supposed
to keep people in line now, huh?
I don't think I can do this without you.
You're one of the only people in the world
who looks me in the eye
when they talk to me.
You know that?
You laugh at my jokes.
And you actually like the way I look.
I didn't think
I'd ever feel like this again.
I guess what I'm trying to say is...
Well, don't stop now,
I was just getting misty.
What are you doing here?
Paying my respects.
She's looked better, I must say.
You will not hurt her.
Why would I do that?
Oh, I know.
Because she stabbed my mother in the back!
If you touch her, I will kill you.
I like this new side of you.
Soft. Sentimental.
He has to pay, Butch.
- Who? Azrael?
- No!
Galavan!
See, I will not buy
this whole über-villain nonsense.
I mean, if he wanted to wear leather,
he should just wear leather.
This is Gotham City. No one cares, right?
We have all suffered by his hand.
Me. You.
My mother.
And now, his own sister.
Galavan must die.
And when he does,
you'll leave us alone?
Mmm. I suppose.
Promise.
Jeez. Fine. Yes. Whatever.
Where is he?
- Yeah?
- He's here.
And he's safe.
Thank God. I'm coming.
You're more to me
than just a guardian, Alfred.
You're my friend.
Your timing really is quite impeccable,
Master Bruce.
But we haven't got time
for sentimental nonsense right now.
We need to make sure
that all the doors are locked,
all the windows are closed,
and the lights are off.
To make it hard as possible
for Galavan to find us. Do you get me?
Detective Gordon's sure he's coming here?
Nothing's certain, is it?
So we need to be ready.
Okay.
It's a big house, we should split up.
Fine.
But just you be quick.
So, you take the upstairs.
I will take the downstairs.
You make sure the windows are closed,
you make sure the doors are locked.
You make sure the skylights are closed.
And then you meet me down here, as quick
as you can, in the study, all right?
Now go.
Alfred! Alfred!
Ingenious.
You.
You will show me to the boy.
Over my dead body.
As you wish.
Let's check it out.
What's that noise?
Hey, Ed, what's that noise?
Nygma?
Son of a gun.
Sound the alarm. We've got a runner.
Go.
Come on, come on, come on.
Oh. Okay.
Alfred! Alfred!
Alfred!
Take one more step, mate,
I will put a bullet
right between your bloody eyes.
You think that'll stop me, you manservant?
I'd like to give it a go,
if you don't mind.
You think I am flesh and blood?
I am immortal,
and I have grown tired of you.
Alfred!
Run, Bruce!
Immortal? Let's see, shall we?
Alfred.
Come on, come on.
Hey, just gonna need someone
to come down here and take a look.
Give us a minute, please.
I think we can safely say
Azrael has gone rogue.
I'm not comfortable
making that assumption just yet.
But it's been more than 24 hours
since he's made contact.
Perhaps that's because
Jim Gordon still breathes.
But if the police
catch him first, how do we explain?
Something that cannot be explained?
We don't.
Theo Galavan is no more.
Azrael is his new creation.
A killer. A madman.
The GCPD will fail
if they try to capture him.
They'll have to kill him first
and when they do,
they'll be successfully
covering our tracks for us.
In the meantime,
this facility needs to be shut down.
All subjects moved to the new location.
Already happening.
That's my girl.
Damn it.
Don't hide, little boy.
Face me.
Face death.
You know the Waynes were a blight
upon the city.
A selfish, arrogant family.
A family with no beliefs.
No honor.
No respect.
You are your father's only son, Bruce.
When I kill you,
I eradicate the Wayne name forever.
It will be as though
you had never existed.
Enough of fun and games.
Prepare to die.
Unexpected.
You okay?
Sorry I couldn't get here sooner.
Seems like I missed all the fun.
Where have you been?
I slowed him down for you, didn't I?
I'll call Bullock.
It's time I taught you
how to drive, Master Bruce.
You should know by now
that bullets don't kill this monster, Jim.
My last one got stuck in your throat, so,
I'm thinking about shoving this one
somewhere else.
Jim, a little tip for next time.
Always bring the right tools for the job.
See you in hell, Theo.
Oh.
You're welcome.
Let's go, Butch.
Night, fellas.
Oh, God!
Oh, the little sprite was right.
Freeze!
Remain where you are.
Oh, dear.
Are you my human subject?
What?
Were you sent here to test me?
- Bridgit?
- Who's Bridgit?
- It's me, Selina.
- What?
You burned yourself when the cops
tried to bust you, remember?
I don't remember anything before this.
Professor Strange told me I have amnesia.
No, don't trust him.
Your name is Bridgit.
He told me he'd send people to test me.
Well, I'm not here to test you.
I'm here to take you home.
That's what he said you'd say.
Bridgit, no. Bridgit, no. Bridgit, no.
Bridgit, no! Bridgit, no!
Bridgit, no.
Don't call me that.
My name is
Firefly.
English - SDH