Previously on Gotham...
General Wade's landing craft docked.
His convoy's on the way here now.
Reunification day is today.
- Captain Gordon.
- General, welcome to Gotham.
- Incoming!
- Get back!
Eduardo.
What did Walker do to you?
Eduardo's dead, Jim.
There is only Bane now.
Everything I have done here
is about punishing Gotham
for the sins of Bruce Wayne.
I'm not leaving. And I don't think I can
let you leave... either.
What are you doing?
Ra's al Ghul.
This is revenge for his death.
- And who am I?
- You're his daughter.
Barbara Kean.
Run!
My name is Nyssa al Ghul.
I believe you knew my father.
- Where's Nyssa?
- I don't know,
but she's planning on using the
military to wipe out Gotham.
I can order them to stand down.
Then let's get you out of here.
This is General Wade.
Begin your bombing run
- on my order.
- Wait, wait.
We need to get ahold of Barbara.
Nyssa al Ghul's coming for her.
The sooner she and Lee get back
here with the baby, the better.
We got refugees coming in
from all over Gotham, Jim.
People are scared.
I know you're not one to quit,
but if there was ever a time
to wave the white flag,
now is it.
Nyssa al Ghul doesn't want
to just conquer Gotham...
she wants to destroy it,
kill everyone she finds.
The only thing standing between
her and these people is us.
Gather the team.
Get every able-bodied refugee
down into the bunkers beneath the GCPD.
Why do I get the feeling he's concocting
an elaborate plan to get us all killed?
Better gather up these refugees.
Look at him.
The medics did everything
they could to stabilize him.
Now all we can do is wait.
This is my fault.
I sent him on this mission.
Alfred knew what he was
signing up for, Bruce.
We all did.
Nyssa and Bane are coming
after me and Barbara.
Coming after Gotham.
Because of what we did to Ra's.
What you did was stop him.
Twice.
We'll stop his psycho daughter together.
I'm sure you recognize this knife.
You touch my baby,
and I will turn you into a pile of ash,
just like I did your father.
A bit cruel, don't you think?
To let this little one get too attached
when you won't be around
much longer.
Mmm.
Soon, you and Bruce Wayne
will see Gotham
and Jim Gordon's precious
Green Zone destroyed.
Then I'll allow you to die.
My father made his name
destroying empires.
Now it's my turn.
Hello.
Listen to me. There is a submarine
in the docks, full of Gotham's gold.
It's yours.
Just leave the city.
Let me and my baby go.
No.
I think I'll keep this little one
and raise her as my own.
As an al Ghul.
I take it the army has landed.
They're just awaiting my orders.
Then what are you waiting for?
What a cute little baby.
Wait, what?
You're ordering us to
destroy the Green Zone?
Anyone still in Gotham is
an enemy of the state.
I won't be party to the
murder of civilians, General.
Then you're relieved of command.
The hell are you?
I'm your new commander.
Does anybody else have a problem
with the general's orders?
Good.
Let's get started.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --
What's the matter?
Can we really be so cavalier
about the destruction of Gotham?
Let me think about that.
Yes!
Damn it!
Oswald!
Where are you going?
This is my city, and I will be damned
if I'm gonna let those bastards take it!
I cannot let you do this.
You, of all people,
should want to stop those monsters.
They forced you to destroy Haven,
to murder hundreds of
innocent civilians.
You're just gonna let
'em get away with it?
I was kind of planning on it, yeah.
Very well.
I'm going to follow my heart.
Oswald!
You have been down this road before.
Following your heart has
never worked out for you.
Perhaps.
But perhaps you could learn something
if you listened to this
instead of this.
I'm gonna miss you,
Edward.
I'll miss you, too, Oswald.
I'm not talking to you.
I'm talking to the...
God!
Come on, baby.
All right.
Okay. Good boy.
Go with the man in green.
You'll be safe.
Oswald, if you walk off this dock,
I'm taking this submarine.
And the treasure!
Nyssa al Ghul wants to
kill everyone in Gotham.
But, to get to us, the army has
to follow the Western Corridor.
That's where we make a stand.
We got a handful of men.
How are we gonna take on an army?
We just have to slow the
army down long enough
to get General Wade out
from under Nyssa's control.
Then he can reverse the invasion order.
We're trying to reach the Sirens.
Still no luck.
All right. I'll go.
Jim.
I need to get Barbara and Lee back here.
- I'll meet you at the barricades.
- I know you haven't seen
your kid yet, but the
GCPD needs a leader,
and they're looking to you.
I'll go to Sirens.
Okay.
You sure you want to do this?
It doesn't take two of us to
track the general's signal.
And if Jim's making a stand,
that's where I should be.
Okay.
Wayne Enterprises EMP,
smoke bombs, signal jammers.
Not enough to even the odds, but...
it may buy you some time.
What's this?
Ah. Remember the Nightwing Project?
Portable, next-gen stealth tech.
Put it on any aircraft, and
it's invisible to radar.
But, unfortunately, it also
seems to serve as a beacon
to certain animals.
Never know. Might find a use for it.
Oswald, come in.
Still have those eyes in the
back of your head, Jim.
No.
You just have a remarkably
recognizable odor.
Part dandy, part snake.
After all these years,
it hasn't changed.
Drink?
No, thank you.
Dulls the senses.
That's what I was going for.
Surprised you're still here.
Figured you'd be long gone by now.
That storm you've warned
me about for so long,
it's finally here.
We've shared some turbulent
times, you and I.
That we have.
When you spared my life
on the pier that day,
banished me from Gotham,
that was the most lost I've ever been.
Because I was away from
the city, you see.
It's part of me.
You know what I'm talking about,
because it's part of you, too.
Sure, I could escape...
with money, I might add...
but then what?
Stand on the shores of the mainland
and watch the army
burn it to the ground?
Then watch tasteless industrialists
and vapid politicians rebuild it?
No.
My life is etched on the
walls of every alley
and dirty warehouse here.
My blood lives in its broken concrete.
I'm staying to fight.
For my legacy.
Hey.
The army just busted through
the GCPD checkpoint.
They're heading to the barricades.
Bane's leading them.
How many men?
600, 700?
Still want to fight?
How many do we have?
Maybe 30?
Thirty-one.
Takes two men to pilot
that submarine, Oswald.
The dog can't do it.
Ditto on that blood and concrete thing.
Kind of like this city the way it is.
Shall we?
I believe time is of the essence.
Gentlemen.
Remind me to talk to you
about that full pardon.
Alvarez!
Harper, Bruce!
You take the left flank.
Harvey and I will take the right.
Holy Mary, Mother and Joseph.
Captain Gordon...
I always knew you had a savior complex,
but this is too much.
What happened to you, Eduardo?
There was a time when
you would have been up
on these barricades with me.
Yes... but that was before
I found my true purpose.
Stand by.
Fire on my command.
Jim, it's a lot of innocent soldiers
down there just following orders.
Target Bane and Nyssa's commandos.
Fire on my command.
For Gotham.
Lee?
Selina.
Hey. Come on, we got to get out of here.
Where's Barbara and the baby?
Nyssa al Ghul took them.
We have to tell Jim.
Yeah.
The Narrows.
They never stood a chance.
The ones who could escaped to the GCPD.
Then that's where I'm needed.
Target Jim Gordon.
I'm sorry!
I don't think he can hear you
through the bullet in his ear!
Eddie!
They're only delaying the inevitable.
Jim, that thing's pointing right at us!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Find me Jim Gordon and Bruce Wayne.
If the army gets through the barricades,
they'll have a straight shot to
the GCPD and the people there.
We need to find another
way to slow them down.
I think I have a way.
Gather all the ammunition you can.
Fall back to the GCPD.
Go, go now!
Fall back!
We got to go.
Well, that was a disaster.
Come on, Oswald, we have to keep moving.
Where? There's nowhere to hide, Jim.
Wherever we go, the army will find us.
Get me Gordon.
It's Lucius.
Tell me you were able to
track the general's signal.
It's coming from City Hall,
but there's a problem.
Selina radioed.
Barbara and the baby were
kidnapped by Nyssa al Ghul.
General Wade's at City Hall.
Chances are Nyssa, Barbara
and the baby are, too.
Our best bet is for me to
sneak into City Hall alone.
One good electrical zap should
short out the general's chip,
then you can get him to
reverse the invasion order.
See you back at the GCPD.
Get Barbara and the baby back safe.
Come on. Hey, move!
Upsy-daisy, Oswald.
We're running out of time.
Just give me one minute.
I'm so sorry.
I saw the grenade and I froze.
- I'm sor...
- Shh.
It's the least I could do.
But tell me...
Does it look bad?
No, it's just a scr...
Looks fine. Let's go.
Where'd everybody go?
She's gonna need some morphine.
And this bandage needs changing.
Lee.
- Bruce. Is Jim... ?
- He's okay.
For now.
We'll need to get Jeremiah's
battery from the basement.
After the bridges went
down, Lucius re-modified
Jeremiah's bomb to be used
for its original purpose...
as a battery.
It's been powering the GCPD.
Right.
We need to make it a bomb again.
You got to be kidding me.
Jeremiah knew exactly
where to put his bombs
to topple buildings,
turn Gotham into a maze.
We stopped him.
But if we could use
just part of his plan,
we can track the army
and slow them down.
By knocking buildings down like dominos.
But for that to work, we need
to put a bomb in this building.
Ground Zero for the blast.
Wayne Enterprises.
Bruce...
There's no other way.
Okay. How do we get
this thing out of here?
To use it as a bomb, you
don't need the whole thing.
All you need is... the core...
and the activator.
That's it?
It may look modest,
but all it took was one of these
to blow up an entire bridge.
Not to mention the Gotham Clock Tower.
Bruce, you can't do this alone.
He's not alone.
I know where to place the bomb.
And you and Lucius are needed here.
I can't believe we're
letting them do this.
Add that to the list of things
that I cannot believe are happening.
Hey.
What?
The key's there.
Where is she? Is she okay?
Yeah, she's upstairs in the office
with Nyssa and the general.
Nyssa is not gonna stop
until she's killed everyone in Gotham.
One thing at a time,
let's go save our baby.
Hello, Captain Gordon.
Ah.
You're seeing your baby
for the first time.
I wish I had a camera.
Hand her over.
No.
I don't think I will.
Put down your guns.
Unless you want the little
one hurt in the crossfire.
Even now, the army is making
its way to the Green Zone
while Bane is hunting down Bruce Wayne.
Only question is,
what to do with you?
This is it.
The bomb will weaken the support column
and topple the entire building.
This is crazy.
I mean, we've spent this entire
time trying to stop Jeremiah
and now we're actually
using part of his plan.
Believe me...
if there was any other way...
You sure you want to do this?
First Wayne Manor gets destroyed
and now Wayne Enterprises.
This building is the heart
of my family's company.
There are things above us
my parents spent their entire lives on.
Some of my earliest memories
are playing with Alfred in this lobby,
waiting for my parents to
come down these escalators.
But my parents built this company
to make Gotham a better place.
They would have sacrificed
everything for this city.
They did sacrifice everything.
And if that's what it takes...
... so will I.
So remind me how this works.
Pulls energy from the
air and magnifies it.
And when it does that?
We run!
I knew you'd come for your child.
I just didn't think
you'd be foolish enough
to come alone.
I don't need help to take you down.
Don't you see?
It's over.
Gotham will burn.
And I'll achieve what
my father couldn't.
Including killing you.
She likes to be held upright.
There.
Barbara, I'll deal with you
once Gotham has been destroyed.
But I'd like you to see this.
I was expecting a little more gusto.
You want gusto?
Is that all you got?
It's Lieutenant Angel.
They did what?
No, no.
Is there another way around?
Then tell the army to blast through.
Hey.
I'm not done with you yet.
Your friends may have
bought you some time,
but the Green Zone's
destruction is only delayed.
And now to meet your fate.
Let's meet it together.
Barbara!
Shoot him.
No.
You think you can defeat me?
Better men and women
have tried and failed.
I'm an al Ghul.
You'll never beat me;
I have my father's blood in my veins.
I am his one true heir.
Do you ever stop talking?
You two do share one thing.
You both love getting
stabbed by this knife.
General Wade.
Execute fail-safe.
No.
I'm going to enjoy watching
Gotham be destroyed!
And then my legacy will be complete.
We got to hurry.
It's only a matter of time
before the army breaks through.
We need to get back to the GCPD.
Bruce!
Impressive.
You blew up your father's building
to stop the military.
It will take more to stop me.
Go on ahead, Selina!
Warn the GCPD!
No, we're doing this together.
You shouldn't have hurt Alfred.
Collateral damage. It happens in war.
I'm sorry you weren't there
to see me break your butler,
but I'm so glad you won't miss
me killing your little friend.
Let her go.
In war, there are no attachments.
Only then can you fight
without your hands tied.
You see... just a little
ounce of pressure.
That's all that separates
the living from the dead.
- What is that?
- Wayne cloaking device,
but it had some glitches.
Apparently, it's a beacon
for certain winged mammals.
What winged mammals?
Bats.
There's no way to reverse
the invasion order.
We have to find another way.
- Is she all right?
- She is now.
There, there. Mama's here.
And your father.
Try not to get blood on her.
- Sir...
- Come on.
We're almost at the Green Zone.
Lee?
Jim.
- The baby?
- I checked her over, she's fine.
Though she could use a feed.
Where's General Wade? The
army's broken through.
General Wade's dead.
Nyssa al Ghul escaped. There's no way
to order the army to stand down.
So, now what?
The army blew up Wayne Enterprises
and knocked down two other buildings.
We don't stand a chance.
Actually, that was Bruce and Selina.
What?
The army's blocks away.
- From what direction?
- Every direction.
We're surrounded.
Jim. I need to get her out of here.
All right. The tunnels
underneath the GCPD.
There's a vent shaft, it
connects to the subway line.
Take the baby and the refugees
down into the subways.
Get 'em behind enemy lines.
- Don't stop till you get to safety.
- Okay.
But what about you?
We'll hold 'em off outside,
buy you some time.
- Jim...
- These refugees,
most of them are from the Narrows.
They know you, they trust you.
They know you'll protect them.
Go.
Oh, there you are, Master Bruce.
Rest, Alfred.
All this time, I tried to protect you.
There you are, a soldier.
A soldier for good.
You've spent your life protecting me.
Now it's time for me to do the same.
It's time for me to protect Gotham.
Even if there's nothing left to defend.
All right, everyone, let's move. Okay.
All right, you'll walk about
five blocks underground,
and then you'll get
to a subway vent. Go.
You're not coming with us?
Jim and our friends are
out there making a stand.
That's where I belong.
Wait, what are we going
to do without you?
Survive. Make sure
this was all worth it.
Go.
What was that for?
Everything you've done for me.
And for her.
Just get them to safety.
It's over, Jim.
Our war's come to an end.
This isn't a war. This
is a firing squad.
I told you to go.
And I didn't listen.
Ready.
Aim.
Shoulder to shoulder.
- Stand together.
- What the... ?
They're here for us, Jim.
Fire.
I said fire!
You have a choice.
You can stand with us,
or you can stand with them.
We are Gotham!
We are Gotham! We are Gotham!
So that bitch was telling
the truth after all.
We managed to raise the
mainland on the radio.
They know everything. As of right now,
the army's being repurposed
for the humanitarian mission
of rebuilding Gotham.
These refugees will get food,
water, medical treatment.
They're setting up a crisis
center in Federal Square.
I'll be damned.
Hey.
So...
this whole "not listening" thing.
It's not gonna become a habit, is it?
You're welcome.
Go.
Well, this is gonna make
one hell of a bedtime story some day.
Can I?
Of course.
I don't even know what to call her.
Barbara.
Oh.
Barbara Lee Gordon.
In this city, it's important
she know who she can rely on.
Bruce, what's wrong?
We won.
Nyssa al Ghul is still out there.
And she and Bane were right.
All this happened because of me,
because people were trying to hurt me
and the people I care about.
When Bane had you...
I thought he was gonna kill you, Selina,
and there was nothing I could do.
Hey.
I will be here whenever you need me.
What?
That's what my parents used to tell me.
Come here.
That bitch stole our submarine!
And our gold.
And by now she's probably landed
somewhere on the mainland,
impossible to track!
After all we've been
through these last months,
we are once again left with nothing!
Nothing!
Back to square one.
Common criminals.
We saved this city from
certain damnation,
but will we see any
credit for our loyalty,
our selfless bravery? Of course not!
I don't want their thanks.
Or their respect.
You know what I felt,
standing shoulder to shoulder
with those people out there?
Nothing.
I... feel...
absolutely nothing
for those drab...
boring people.
That was me once.
Minimum wage at a thankless job
at the GCPD. "Yes, sir. No, sir.
Thank you so much, sir."
Picking up scraps from
my master's floor.
Shy, awkward...
pathetic Ed.
Common criminals?
Never again.
I've shown this city who
I truly am once before,
and I will do it again.
They will bow
to the Riddler, and they won't get up
until I permit them to.
Yes.
You're right.
Our accomplishments have been erased,
our brilliant minds underrated.
If they had let me run this
city the way I wanted to,
it would not be in ruins now.
I have the men, the money,
- the guns...
- Gordon took them.
Why? Because he still sees you
as Fish Mooney's umbrella
boy, and he always will.
Yes.
I only came back to
help him save this city
so that I could take it for myself.
We would be stronger together.
No one could stop us.
Yeah, perhaps.
Let's make a pact,
here and now.
We will take what we want
from who we want,
and we will suffer no fools.
Together.
Shall we shake on that?
Please,
we're brothers.
A hug.
A hug it is.
Life begins anew.
Shall we get to work?
Thank you all for coming here today.
It is my great honor to
introduce Mayor Jones.
With reunification underway
and the bridges being rebuilt,
it is my honor to bestow
upon Captain James Gordon
the title of commissioner.
We're gonna miss you around the bullpen.
I won't be far.
And the mission doesn't change.
Still trying to make this
city a better place.
Be careful.
You're swimming with sharks now.
If you need anything, ever...
I know who to call.
You deserve this, Jim.
You really do.
I'm gonna go get a drink before...
you get all teary-eyed on me.
What do you mean, you're leaving?
Bane's in prison, it's over.
My life here... it's too public.
You've made up your mind.
Gotham's in good hands.
Commissioner.
Yeah.
Thank you, Bruce,
for everything you've done
for me and for the city.
Gotham will always be your home.
Bruce is all grown up.
- That he is.
- Well,
now you have another
little one to look after.
Where's Bruce?
Um...
he left you this.
You know how to reach me
if you need anything?
Yes.
Well, you know me, Master Bruce,
I'll be very self-sufficient.
Busy, actually. You know,
we start the reconstruction
of Wayne Enterprises and
Wayne Manor tomorrow.
You will remember everything
I taught you, won't you?
Of course.
Good, that's... that's good.
I never tried to replace
your parents, you know?
I couldn't, I never would.
But I want you to know, Master Bruce,
that you are the only son
that I will ever have,
and I could not be more proud.
- Synced & corrected by MementMori -
-- www.addic7ed.com --