Previously onGotham...
- The Doc. You know him?
- Oh, I know The Doc.
Sometimes we search for things
we don't wish to find.
I'm enjoy being the queen of Gotham.
Glad we understand each other.
There are other ways for me
to hurt you.
Something's eating in you, Jim.
And you're not gonna feel clean
until you get it off your chest.
That's done now.
I'm at Sofia Falcone's.
I just shot and killed the Pyg.
I see Arkham's treating you well.
Good-bye, Oswald.
I am held captive
of my brilliance locked away.
You're still there.
And you're gonna help me
find a way out of here.
- I need a name.
- Ivy Pepper.
- I know Ivy.
- No, Gordon, she's changed.
Like, a lot.
Called Lazarus Water.
What are you going to do with it?
I'm going to make miracles happen.
You reel it in a little?
Or should I call your keeper?
Call Alfred. He won't answer.
- Why?
- Because I fired him.
Where is the other guy
who works here?
You mean Harvey? He's out sick.
You wanna leave him a message?
I do.
Alright. What should I say?
Nothing.
Because all of you
with your blood and your flesh
and what you will become...
you are the message.
He was a good man.
It doesn't matter that Mario's gone
you'll always be my sister.
For Falcone, it's all about family.
Appreciate that.
So, sister to sister...
we're not really here
look at photographs.
There's only one neighborhood
in Gotham
that hasn't bend the knee.
The Narrows is never submitted
to an outside boss.
There's never been
someone like me ruling Gotham.
Okay.
- What do you want?
- A tax.
Thirty percent in all income coming
for The Narrows legal and illegal.
Every family there lives
hand to mouth, they'll starve.
But we all have
to make sacrifices.
I'll need the answer
by the end of the day.
You want me to kiss the ring,
I'll do it. To keep the peace.
But what you are asking for
is impossible.
You'll find a way.
I thought it was all about family.
Never said it was a happy family.
Thank you.
Thank you for meeting me.
My parents foundation is having
their annual dinner tonight.
- I thought we...
- Somehow I don't think you called me
all the way down here to talk
about a fundraiser, did you?
Bruce, what exactly is it
that you want from me?
Help.
Figuring this out,
I can't do it alone, I...
Alfred, I need your help.
No.
- What?
- Listen, you can't just waltz
back in here and expect me to go and
clean your s'mores and cook your tea.
- After what you've done...
- Alfred, I'm not asking for that
- I've changed.
- Oh, you have, have you?
So, it's one thing saying
that you changed
and another actually changing so...
show me.
Show me how you changed
and I might reconsider.
Show you how?
That's for you to figure out, innit?
I'm asking as a friend.
I'm not your friend.
I was your butler.
And you fired me.
He'll pay for the tea, miss.
Sure hope Lee is gonna
figure something out with Sofia.
Leaving the love of your life
and all.
We're friends.
You know, those koo-koo pills
aren't gonna make me go away.
Well, they have stopped you
from getting out
and trying to kill Lee again
so works for me!
Mail arrived.
Who's it from?
Oswald.
"I want to apologize.
Can we be friends again?"
What? What does he...
I'm never gonna forgive him.
Oh, I think it's a nice letter.
Oh, shut up!
Hey, Ed.
What has two eyes but can't see?
What has two...
Good Lord.
This is new. More aggressive.
The plants are literally bursting
through their flesh.
You.
Get away from that. Now. Now.
Same flower growing out of
these bodies.
That's a weapon?
Gordon, this must be what Ivy do
with the Lazarus Water.
Used it to increase
the potency of a toxic plant.
The seeds made it airborne...
- Where is Bullock?
- What?
He works here.
Harvey killed Ivy's father.
Clear.
- Too late.
- No, we're not.
Hey.
Damn it, Jim.
Jim, what the hell?
Hey, someone's paying for that door.
Ivy Pepper.
- Who?
- Mario Pepper's kid.
She's been working on some biotech.
She attacked your bar.
It's bad.
Donnie, the bartender?
I'm sorry.
- Oh, God.
- Look.
I gotta think
that you were the target.
Jim, I only shot Ivy Pepper's Dad
because I was saving
your stupid hide.
You can't put this on me!
- I'm not putting in on you!
- Guys!
Public safety we have to decide
to share the footage.
So in a moment the video
we're about to show you
is form a tape received this morning.
And again let me warn you
it is very disturbing.
Plants love us.
They gave us food, shelter
the very air we breathe.
And what we do in return?
Kill them.
Because that's our nature.
We cause pain.
Everyone I've known
has only hurt or betrayed me.
Maybe I've always known in my heart
when I needed to do.
But I finally had the power
to do so.
I'm giving your city
back to the plants.
Starting with the people
who hurt me.
So, if that's you...
your time is coming.
- Guess we know what she's up to.
- Yeah.
She's gonna kill everyone
in Gotham.
Starting with me.
Preliminary reports indicate that
similar tapes have been delivered
to multiple news organization...
Wait a minute.
What's that there?
Sully's eatery.
That's in Ives Square.
House must be right across.
You should go to the precinct.
Hey, I'm not hiding like
some freaking coward, all right?
Four people are dead
because she wanted me.
Okay, then we'll work on it together.
You can wear the badge.
Get this straight, Jim.
I ain't working for you now.
Or ever.
I got more contacts
in the Narrows than any of you.
I'm gonna find her. Alone.
Once I've found my pants.
It doesn't make any sense.
- There's no money here.
- Okay, so it's about power.
I offered to bend the knee.
She's asking for something
she knew I couldn't give.
She wants...
she wants to punish me.
For what?
I don't know.
But you can't fight an enemy
whose motivations
you don't understand, Lee.
You are the greatest spies
in all of Gotham.
You have eyes and ears everywhere.
The survival of the Narrows
depends upon you.
Whoever learns why Sofia Falcone
wants to destroy Lee Thompkins
will receive...
a complete set of encyclopedias.
Minus the T.
- Plus 20 bucks.
- Yeah.
- Yes.
Go get them.
Incoming.
- Eyes for movement.
- Clear.
She wasn't bluffing.
With this many plants, she could kill
hundreds if not thousands of people.
Search the other room for any signs
of where she's heading.
What are you gonna do to her?
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
I just saw the news.
She killed four more people today.
You knew where she was staying.
If you had told me,
we could've saved lives.
Or not.
I mean, you couldn't even stop her
from hypnotizing your own cops.
So why'd you come here?
To try to reason with her?
Have you heard a word she said?
- She's a fanatic.
- She's my friend.
I mean, what do you expect me to do?
She contacts you again, call me.
I'll try and find her
and bring her in quietly.
Otherwise, stay out of her way.
- Harvey?
- Hey.
- I got a lead.
- Great.
I knocked some heads.
Heard a hot redhead was poking around
in that dive bar next door.
That is the place in The Narrows
for low-end muscles
so I figured if she was planning
something big,
she might've gone there to recruit.
That's the back entrance.
That's where my contact said that...
Hello, Detective Gordon.
On the ground now.
Harvey, call it in.
She's beautiful,
don't you think, Jim?
Drop your weapon.
You don't look good.
I think you might be exceeding
your recommended dosage.
You're experiencing
trembling extremities?
Check.
Cognitive impairment? Definite check.
Though, to be fair,
how would you know?
Shut up!
Take all the pills you want, Ed.
I'm only getting stronger.
Soon, I'm gonna be out,
and the fun begins!
No. I won't let you.
Because I know what you'll do.
Oh, you mean kill Lee?
Yeah, I guess I will do that.
And you can't stop me.
- There are things that I can do.
- Like what?
You need to face it, Pal.
The only way you'll get rid of me
is to kill yourself.
I guess you're smarter than me.
- You would actually...
- Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I said drop the gun, Jim.
Do you believe in fate,
Detective Gordon?
I went out today to test my plants
on the man who shot my father.
He wasn't there.
It's disappointing.
Then, he found me.
And I realized I could make him
deliver his partner as well.
- Fate.
- Stay strong, Harvey.
- She's controlling you.
- I kinda like it, Jim.
Sweet surrender.
You need help, Ivy.
Let me find Selina,
she wants to help.
Quiet.
I have to go.
Big plans tonight,
lots of people to kill.
- Detective Bullock.
- Ma'am.
After you kill your partner...
be sure to shoot yourself
in the head, okay?
Copy that.
- Harvey.
- Don't even try
and talk your way out of this.
I wouldn't. But...
Quick question.
Is Ivy's hair more auburn or scarlet?
I... That's a good question.
Think I didn't come prepared?
You always underestimate me.
That's not why I'm shooting you.
I just think we should clear the air.
What do you want to talk about?
I'm all ears.
How you stole my job, for starters!
Was it really your job, though?
I mean, you only got it
'cause one captain died
and the other one went nuts.
Like hell!
I paid my dues. I earned that job
and you took it!
You mean like the time
you gut-shot Officer Patel?
That was... a mistake.
Hey, give yourself some credit.
You did shoot her
from across the room.
Although you couldn't face her later,
remember?
You didn't have the courage to meet
her the next day, did you?
- Coward!
- Screw you!
- We're not open.
- I wanted to see you.
Why? Because you weren't
big enough of an ass
the last time I saw you?
- Selina...
- I don't have time for this, Bruce.
Something happened.
- I need to talk to someone.
- Okay, then go find Alfred.
Oh, you did.
And he wanted nothing to do with you.
Smart guy, Alfred.
- Will you at least hear me out?
- No, Bruce.
Because Ivy's out there
killing people
and I need to find her and stop her.
So whatever problem you have
going on right now
you need to figure it out.
I mean, say sorry to Alfred.
Because I'm sure whatever happened
was your fault.
According to my spies...
Sofia and Jim
were carrying out an affair.
Till Jim ended it.
So technically,
your ex has been sleeping
with your dead husband's
mafiosa sister.
Okay, I get it.
If Sofia was sleeping
with the captain of the GCPD
it was a power play.
And it failed.
I'm her next step.
Why don't I just give her
what she wants?
Power over Jim Gordon.
You would do that?
I'm not trying to get back at Jim,
though he deserves it.
My job is to make sure that
the people of the Narrows are safe.
And I will do everything
in my power to ensure that.
What?
Lee, I...
I...
have to leave.
She's here...
Harvey.
- Harvey, come on.
- Where am I?
You were hypnotized.
I need you to focus.
Did Ivy give you any clue
about who she's targeting next?
I can't believe I let her get to me.
Hey, you wanna help? Here's how.
Did she say anything?
Something about,
"They get rich by murdering plants?"
So, she's targeting a group
of rich people?
At her place, she was trying on
fancy clothes, fancy shoes.
Party?
She said she had big plans,
couldn't be late.
- Yeah. Black tie. Fancy schmancy.
- No, no, come on, you gotta know...
Charity for hobos or something.
Wayne's Foundation Annual Dinner
is tonight, over at Gotham Square.
All right, give the strike force.
I want full body armor,
gas mask, non-lethal rounds.
To fight plants?
When Ivy got me, she was hypnotizing
a bunch of low-end muscle.
Go.
I could really use you there, Harv.
Jim, she got in my head.
I really... I just don't trust
myself right now.
All right, you can help out here.
Man the phones.
Hey, Jim...
I spent too long putting this
all on you.
What happened between us.
Fact is, I only got myself to blame.
I'll call.
And now, ladies and gentlemen
please welcome to the stage,
our host, Bruce Wayne.
Good evening.
Welcome to the third Annual Dinner
for the Thomas and Martha Wayne
Foundation.
This year, we disburse
four million dollars in...
We disbursed four million dollars
and...
My parents spent their lives
helping people.
I was so proud of them
and I always wanted them
to be proud of me.
And then I saw them get murdered.
I survived because someone
in my life kept me going.
He's been everything to me.
A teacher.
A protector.
He's been a father to me.
I hope...
I hope he can see that...
and give me another chance.
Thank you.
That meant a great deal.
But I can't help you.
Not until you accept
who you really are.
I know who I am,
I've seen what's inside of me.
Darkness and anger.
But what was beneath that...
it's a heart that feels pain.
Your heart is what makes you
want to help other people.
Your heart is your strength.
Deny the darkness,
and you deny that.
But accepting that is something
you must do on your own.
Do you understand me?
I was stupid for reaching out.
That was quite a speech.
Hello all.
I'm Ivy Pepper.
No, no, no, please.
Stay seated.
Can I just say...
this is crazy!
Look, this whole thing
was it your idea?
And you're the smart one,
as you always tell me?
Oh, very funny.
Okay, fine! Fine!
You win!
- What?
- You win.
You beat me.
Is that what you wanna hear?
That is very nice.
But I still have to do it.
Wait!
Wait, wait.
What if there's a way to do this
where nobody gets hurt?
I don't believe you.
So, you just gonna kill yourself
without hearing me out?
I'm telling you, Ed,
there was a way to save Lee
without killing yourself!
Or killing us.
I'm listening.
Aren't these crimson flowers lovely?
You're a handsome man.
But you want more from life.
I can feel it.
Bruce, is Ivy Pepper in there?
Ivy? No, I mean, I didn't see her.
Get out of here. Let's go!
Breach that door!
We are going to turn this room
into the most gorgeous garden
the world has ever seen.
All you have to do...
is take a deep breath.
A volunteer.
GCPD!
Drop your guns! On the ground now!
Kill everyone.
You got this, I'm going after Ivy.
I'm getting you out of here.
Come on, let's go.
Listen, listen...
people need your help.
This is who you are.
Watch the door,
I'm gonna go look left.
Where'd you go, punk?
You can run, but you can't hide.
Hey! Hey!
- Drop it!
- No.
Hey. Hey.
You hear the news?
"Crazy Ivy Pepper attacks
the Wayne Foundation dinner."
I'll be honest the evening didn't
turn out quite the way I'd hope.
You mean you didn't get to kill
everyone in there?
Something like that.
You got out, made it back here.
You always were the survivor.
Hey, you tell me that, Selina.
What's in the bag, Ivy?
It's the last the Lazarus water
I stole from Wayne Enterprises.
So you can go and make more plants
to kill people?
Yeah, that ain't gonna happen.
Are you gonna stop me, Selina?
Are you gonna remind me the old days?
Tell me I'm not this person.
No, I think we're past words now.
Well, Selina Kyle
turns out to be the hero.
I'm no hero.
One scratch is all it takes, Selina.
And there's no antidote this time.
And there's no more jumping across
rooftops for little dead Selina.
I'll keep that in mind.
You're gonna have to fight me,
Selina.
You can't run forever.
I wasn't running.
I was getting this.
This is what you're gonna use
to make all your little plants?
So, I guess it's safe to say
that I shouldn't drop it...
Stop, Selina.
- I will let you live.
- Let me?
You're not gonna turn me
into some geranium-type thing?
That's so generous.
No!
How can you side with them?
All the people who hurt us.
You think they're innocent?
They're guilty.
Every person in this city...
they spew out poison.
How are you not choking on it?
The only thing that I'm choking on,
Ivy, is your insanity.
No...
You shouldn't have done that.
- Now you're gonna die.
- Ivy, look down.
- Well...
- Yeah.
So what happens now?
- We kill each other?
- That's an option.
You always did think
you were better than me?
That's not true, I was your friend.
We were friends, Ivy.
You said so yourself.
That's a long time ago.
I'm a different person now.
This isn't what I want.
Don't get in my way again.
Lift your hands up.
You got any weapons?
I'd almost think this wasn't going
to be a friendly conversation.
Just being careful.
- They're clean.
- Okay.
Smart lady.
So you said you wanted 30 percent
of everything in the Narrows.
What if I told you I had something
more valuable to offer?
Such as?
Jim Gordon.
I know crimes he has committed
no one else does.
It would give you control over him.
Surely that's worth more
than 30 percent of this.
I have my own dirt on Jim Gordon.
But you can't use it.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be sitting
there threatening me, would you?
Sofia...
take my deal.
I have a better way
to bring Gordon around.
No! No!
Stay with me! Stay with me!
You are never gonna get out
of here alive.
My people are gonna kill you!
Your people? Who do you think
planted these guns?
You can come out.
How are you doing, Doc?
I'm having Sampson run the Narrows.
You know, you should've killed me
when you had the chance.
The fact that you didn't told me
everything I needed to know.
Since we're family,
I'm only going to do one hand.
Throw her on the streets.
Let the Narrows see their queen.
The scene here remains largely
under control.
But Ivy Pepper remains at large.
Now inside we have
a team of investigators...
Yeah.
What?
Where is she?
Sir?
Sir? Excuse me.
Are you family?
I'm a cop.
She wouldn't tell us who did it.
She didn't have to.
Arkham doesn't get many volunteers.
You do know who I am, right?
Criminally insane pretty much
covers it.
Read and sign.
I'll be back.
Hate that you were right about this.
It'll keep her safe.
Hey, Ed.
What has two eyes but can't see?
This again.
Two needles.
Half of Mississippi, who cares.
You should, Ed.
I knew you'd come.
- I knew you'd understand my letter!
- How did you know I'd be?
- What are you talking about?
- I'm not talking to you, Ed.
I'm talking to him.
He read my letter!
Read the first word of each sentence.
"Please bring Ed to Arkham
so I can set you free."
What has two eyes
but can't see what's happening
in front of him?
- Ed Nygma!
- No!
I came here to save Lee.
He read my letter!
You...
You're wrong! I am Ed!
Edward Nygma, that is it!
Lee believes in me!
She sees me for who I am!
But I see him, Ed!
No.
Lee Thompkins may have
made Ed strong...
but I see the other you.
One whose name I wouldn't speak.
But because he has earned it
and because I need him,
- I'm saying it now.
- No, please. Please, don't!
- I need you...
- Please.
Riddler.
Shall we get to work?
So...
how'd you make it off the roof then?
A fire escape on the next building.
Why'd you run from Gordon?
I mean, you could've told him
it's you.
I don't know.
I just...
couldn't.
I want to help people, Alfred.
And if that means accepting
every part of myself
the good and bad...
then I will.
I do.
It's what my parents would've wanted.
Your parents would have been
very proud of you.
I'm proud of you.
Alfred.
If you...
need a ride back to Gotham,
I can drive you.
I'm not going anywhere, sir.
I'm home.
Congratulations.
I heard you saved the day.
Good job.
It's the reason you're captain
and I'm a 50-year-old screw-up
pouring shots for barflies.
There's a reason, all right.
But it's not what you think.
I screwed up, Harv.
I screwed up bad.
And I'm gonna need your help
to make it right.
Sofia hired the Pyg...
and I knew.
I knew...
and I covered it up.
And now I'm gonna take her down.