Previously on Gotham...
WOMAN:
Welcome to Wayne Enterprises.
I have some questions
regarding Wayne Enterprises'
business affairs.
Where's Jim?
Don Falcone thinks you don't
know how to run a club.
(whistles)
Hi.
He'll help you out.
Those people out there
are using us as spare parts.
Unless we do something
about it.
Alfred, can you teach me
how to fight?
Yes, I can.
BULLOCK:
Pretty handy for a valet.
ALFRED:
Butler, mate.
I'm a butler.
(tires screeching)
♪ ♪
What the hell is that?
I made it. Yeah.
You made it?
So what is it?
It's a hood.
Thought it would, uh,
you know, spice things up.
When did we start
wearing hoods?
We didn't.
W-Was I supposed to get one?
No!
(panicked shouting, gasping)
Ladies...
And gentlemen,
we are not here for your money!
We're here for the bank's money!
So just stay cool
and no one will get hurt!
Don't be brave!
Don't be frightened!
Just do
what you're told!
This will all be over
quicker than that time
I hooked up with a cheerleader
on prom night!
(man chuckles)
What are you doing up there?!
Getting 'em fired up.
90 seconds.
Nice and easy,
ladies and gentlemen!
You know, banks like this one--
who are insured
to death, by the way--
steal from us every single day!
'Bout time a few of us returned
the favor, don't you think?
60 seconds.
You're being great, folks!
Almost done!
40 seconds.
(gunshots)
(people gasping, shrieking)
(gun clicking)
(chuckles)
Nothing!
Not a scratch!
(cackling)
Th-Thirty seconds.
Let's get out of here!
You've been great, ladies
and germs, but we got to go!
(chuckles)
Did you see that?
That guy missed me
with, like, six shots.
He was, old, nervous.
(sirens wailing)
No, no, no, it's the hood.
I'm telling you.
Damn it.
We're cooked.
(sirens wailing)
Attention, citizens of Gotham!
What the hell are you doing?!
There you go, everybody!
(cheering, shouting)
Take back
what's yours!
(cheering, shouting)
Follow me! Come on.
(clamoring)
(indistinct chatter,
cameras clicking)
BULLOCK:
Well,
we'll never know
how much cash was lost,
but I just saw a bum
eating oysters at Madeline's.
Another freak in a mask.
Awesome.
Is that guard blind or wasted?
Clyde refused
to wear his glasses.
Said they made him look old.
Missing a man standing 20 feet
in front of you with six shots
makes you look old.
Who tripped
the alarm?
I did.
Why aren't you out there,
Detective?
This brazen audacity
cannot be tolerated.
They didn't go for the vault...
just the cash
in the registers.
And the crew was in and out
in under two minutes.
The red-hooded man seemed nice.
Nice?
He wasn't stealing our money...
just the bank's.
Then he gave
a lot of it
back to people in the street.
Like...
...Robin Hood.
Oh, great.
This bank hires Communists.
Robin Hood stole from the rich
and gave to the poor.
These armed thieves
only threw cash away
to guarantee
their escape.
It's very different, ma'am.
The thief
in the back here, was he always
checking his watch?
Yes.
He was counting down.
They knew what our
response time was.
They'd done their homework.
Has the alarm been triggered
for any other reason recently?
No.
Well,
there was that time
with the smoke bomb.
Smoke bomb?
A week or so ago,
a small flare or firework,
or something, was set off
by the Mortgages desk.
It tripped the alarm.
We thought
it was just a kid's prank.
We're gonna need you
to find the surveillance footage
from that incident.
(thunder crashing)
(knocking on door)
(knocking continues)
Yes, sir. How can I help you?
Reggie?
Sorry for calling
so late.
Forgive me.
Oh, my God, mate.
How long's it been?
20 years.
I got picked up by the GCPD
last night
for trying to sleep
under the Westbury Bridge.
Here, mate.
Cheers, mate.
One of the officers
was a Marine, back in the day,
so we got to talking.
I told him
I was with Her Majesty's Special
Air Service back in the day.
So he took pity on me.
He says, "Why don't you look up
some of your old regiment,
you know, see if one of the guys
can... help you out."
Well, you know...
I'm pleased
you looked me up, Reg.
If anyone
would've told me
this is where I'd find you,
I wouldn't have believed them.
I like it here.
It's good for me.
I can see that.
I've missed you,
mate.
Missed your ugly mug.
Cheers.
What happened, Reggie?
Vanessa died.
11 years ago now.
I just couldn't find the energy
to get back out there
after that, you know?
A year later, I lost the house.
Moved back
to Gotham.
I've had a few jobs.
Nothing I'm proud of.
It was the drink, Alfie.
It was the drink.
BRUCE:
Alfred?
Um, Master Bruce.
This is, uh,
Reginald Payne.
We served together, sir.
Very pleased
to meet you, sir.
You were caught in the storm?
Reggie's had a run of
bad luck, Master Bruce.
I-I don't wish to be a nuisance.
I just...
I hadn't seen Alfie
in a very long time.
N-No, I'm glad you found us,
Mr. Payne.
Please, feel free to stay
with us a few days.
That's very kind of you, but...
I insist.
Please.
MOONEY:
Where are you taking me?
MAN:
This way, Miss Mooney.
(moaning, shouting in distance)
Who chose these people?
Where'd you get them from?
(door shuts)
(lock clicks)
Sit, please.
Sit.
There you are, Mr. Red Hood.
Armed robbery perps
dating back ten years.
I took out the dead ones
and the ones in prison.
A who's who
of scumbags.
They were casing the place
a week before they took it down.
Set off the alarm
then timed the response.
He looks pretty young.
He might not be in here.
You see that?
No, 'cause you took my glasses.
Right there,
underneath his coat.
He's wearing a work shirt.
"Kleg's Auto."
Idiot.
(chuckles)
(music blaring)
"The Red Hood Gang"!
(chuckles)
It's got a ring to it.
No, it doesn't.
See those people?
They loved me.
They loved the money
you threw at 'em.
Thanks for that,
by the way.
Shall we take it out
of your share?
You guys don't get it.
We're not just five mooks
with shotguns anymore.
We're the Red Hood Gang.
Taking from the rich
and giving back to the poor.
Mark my words,
the people in this town,
they're gonna get me.
Us.
Will you shut up?
All that prancing around
could have gotten us killed.
You're wrong. That guard,
he was 20 feet away from me.
Not one shot got close.
Luck!
He looked
r-real nervous.
It's the hood!
It's good luck.
I'm telling you.
I feel like a totally
different person with it on.
Eh, sit down, will ya?
We need to go over
tomorrow's score.
Nah, this sets us apart.
It's a piece of cloth--
two holes cut out of it.
It's a symbol!
Whoever wears
the hood
should lead!
(gunshot)
(grunts)
(grunting)
He's right.
Any objections?
So...
you're the one causing
all of the fuss.
The one with
the knife now.
This is your facility?
I manage it, yes.
But do you own it?
The doctor owns it.
Where are you going?
Back to the basement.
We're done here.
Miss Mooney...
Take a seat.
I will talk to the doctor
and the doctor only.
He's away on a consultation
in Gotham.
Then call me when he returns.
He expressly asked me
to attend to your demands.
His name.
I'm sorry?
The doctor. His name.
Dulmacher.
You tell Dr. Dulmacher
that the basement is mine.
No one will leave
unless I say so.
It will remain that way
until he sits with me
and negotiates terms.
Perhaps...
you and I got off
on the wrong foot, Miss Mooney.
When was the last time
you had a shower?
A new set of clothes? Hmm?
(lock buzzes, latch clicks)
(door opens)
Take Miss Mooney to
my private bathroom,
and then pick up
some fresh clothes for her
from storage.
Freshen up.
Come back to me.
And then perhaps we'll talk
some more.
COMEDIAN:
So the mortician says
to the waitress... No, the
waitress says to the mortician,
(clears throat)
"He was always stiff."
MAN 2:
That's it.
Let's go.
Wait. No.
Have a good night.
See you next week, sir. Okay.
(patrons groaning, moaning)
It's fine. We got, uh...
What do we have? We got, um...
MAN 3: Check, please.
(whispering)
COMEDIAN: ...cards.
Oh, okay. Um...
What's wrong?
Ah, Mr. Penguin.
I mean the Penguin. I mean...
I...
What is it?
We're out of booze.
What? Hello? Behind you,
there's a wall of booze.
Just colored water, sir.
Always has been.
We keep the real stuff
down here, but we're out.
So, duh, order more.
We did.
It's just that...
GILZEAN:
It's Maroni's booze.
And he's a little grumpy
with you these days.
He was hardly a fan
of Fish, either.
Why did he sell her booze?
Business is business.
But he hates you with a passion.
But he can't kill you, so...
That's...
This is ridiculous. There's
a thousand places to buy booze.
That's where
it gets complicated.
See, Maroni, he supplies
this whole side of town.
No one would dare cross him
to help you.
(patrons booing,
glass shattering)
Help...
WOMAN:
Get outta here!
Thank you.
Bye. Sorry.
MALE PATRON:
You're not funny.
(patrons murmur, catcall)
(snickering): You must take
great pleasure watching me fail.
On the contrary.
I was with Fish
when we took this place off
a Chinese bookie nine years ago.
It was used for cock fighting.
Took forever
to get the smell out.
My blood, sweat, and tears
are in this dive.
Well, if you'll excuse me,
it seems as though I need
to procure some alcohol
for my dwindling clientele.
Be careful.
You've seen what happens
when you cross Maroni.
GCPD!
Looks like they were here
last night.
Hey.
Your hot doctor friend,
Thompkins...
Leslie.
Whatever.
Give me the double D--
"dirty details."
Don't leave anything out.
(chuckles)
Gotta hand it
to you, partner.
You don't sit
around moping.
You got right back up
on the hobby horse.
Let's just hope you can
keep your head straight
whilst up there.
You had the purse.
Now you got yourself a nurse.
(chuckles)
Well, looks like I found
our friend Floyd.
What? If I don't drink it,
Forensics will.
GORDON: All right. This was
the guy with the hood.
He's wearing
the same coat.
I wonder what he did to
piss off the rest of his crew.
Maybe they knew
we'd catch up to him.
Well, he was the leader,
so it looks like we've seen
the last of the
Red Hood crew now.
(people screaming)
Good morning, everyone!
(grunting)
Get off me! I got it.
Okay.
We're not here
for your money.
We're here for the insurance!
I mean the bank's insured money!
60 seconds.
MAN: Hey! You gonna
share a little bit
of that cash with us, Hood?
(others agreeing)
Th-Thirty seconds.
(grunts)
MAN:
Come on. A lot of us
are hurting here.
(others agreeing)
Ten seconds. L-L...
L-Let's go!
Aw, fine.
(laughs)
(cheering, shouting)
So long, Gotham!
Sayonara!
(indistinct chatter)
And then there were four.
People are gonna hang out
in banks waiting for handouts
from these idiots.
We're never gonna catch a crew
no one wants us to catch.
Call me old-fashioned,
but when crooks
become more popular
than cops,
that's anarchy.
Think about it.
As long as somebody's willing
to put that red hood on,
this gang can go on forever.
ALVAREZ:
Hey, guys.
Got somebody here
you might want to meet.
This is Mister...
Chaing.
Chaing, right.
He's an eyewitness.
From the bank?
I work at a restaurant
a block away.
The Red Hood Gang parked
their van there this morning.
I was throwing out
the trash
when they ran back to it.
You see their faces?
Just one-- the fat
one with the hood.
He took it off to drive.
I'll get the sketch artist.
Well, wait a minute.
Got the armed robbery
files already opened.
Maybe he can look through them,
see if he recognizes someone.
Maybe that someone is
a known associate of Gus Floyd.
Only problem is records are
kind of old-- he might
look different now.
We could pull a few based
off Chaing's description.
Get ourselves a good
old-fashioned lineup.
Wait. Wait a second.
What's in it for me?
I got all these parking tickets
because my ex-wife
is a crazy bitch.
We'll see what we can do.
(panting)
Training
for a fight?
Just training.
Who's helping you?
Alfred.
Good choice.
Show me your stance.
Good.
Hit me.
(grunts)
Again.
And don't hold back.
You have a go at me, son.
(grunting)
(shouts)
Come on.
It should take more than that
to piss you off, son.
Come on.
Again.
(grunts)
(shouts)
(Reggie laughing)
(grunting)
Now, now.
Never lose your cool.
It'll get you killed.
Now, you want to hit me, right?
You want to hit me, right?
Okay. Take a swing.
Take a swing.
Go on. Do it.
(grunts)
Somebody gives you
a free shot,
you got to make it count.
You hit me
as hard as you can.
(grunts)
Oh. Better.
Put your shoulder behind it.
Put your full
body weight behind it.
Go on. Do it.
(shouts)
(grunts)
Harder. Again.
(shouts)
(grunts)
Again.
Come on.
Do it again.
Put me on my back, son.
Come on, you can do it.
Come on. Again.
You're so much bigger than me!
Then use that to your advantage!
You hit me low.
Hit me in the knee, the ankle.
Forget
about the gloves!
Use whatever's around you.
Here. Here.
Go on.
ALFRED:
Right!
That's enough
of that.
Perhaps a shower's
in order, Master Bruce.
M-Mr. Payne was just showing me
some alternative methods.
Yeah, I can see
that, can't I?
Not methods that fit into our
curriculum, though, are they?
No, they're not;
but they're effective.
Discipline, skill,
and hard work are effective.
How 'bout I start that shower
for you, sir?
No.
(door opens upstairs,
then shuts)
You ever raised
a child before, Reg?
No.
Me neither.
Hardest job
I've ever had to do in my life.
Nothing prepares you for it.
Listen, I'm sorry
if I overstepped the mark.
I was just...
It was obvious
how much you've helped him s...
No, he helped me.
I'm a better person
for knowing him, Reg.
Let's keep our past
where it belongs.
In the past.
(snickering):
That's it? Just two workers?
This'll be easy.
Make it quick, guys.
(sirens wailing)
Well, this is inconvenient.
WORKMAN:
Whoa, Officer.
Nothing going on here.
That so?
Eh, your liquor license
is out of date.
We're gonna be
confiscating the shipment.
Hey, does Don Maroni
know you guys are here?
Walk away...
before I run you downtown.
This town is truly
going to the dogs.
Evening, fellas.
(Oswald gasps)
(gun cocks)
(mutters indistinctly)
(panting)
Why the smile, Butch?
First Maroni blocks
our liquor,
and now the cops?
Oh, who, them?
They're with me.
I always keep a few
uniforms in the closet.
A lot cleaner than going in
guns blazing, don't you think?
You're welcome, Oswald.
(chuckles)
(siren wailing in distance)
Nice work there.
How you doing,
Mr. Gilzean?
GILZEAN:
This over here, this...
OFFICER:
Nothing to worry about.
(music playing over headphones)
You okay?
Of course.
Thank you for
letting us stay here.
Sorry it got
a little messy.
I was just about to go.
I like having
you guys here.
(coughs)
Selina...
Come here.
You know, you're turning into
quite the beautiful woman.
No, I'm not.
Remove the dirt...
that old hood...
these ratty clothes...
I bet we find
a princess undernea...
I have an idea.
Holy moly.
Take anything that
fits you guys.
This is all stuff you've worn?
Most of it.
You sure must go out a lot.
I used to.
Come with me.
You're a true beauty.
Something you can use
to your advantage.
Your appearance
can be a weapon,
as powerful
as any knife or gun.
Yeah?
What good's it done you?
(door opens)
BULLOCK (over speaker):
All right, backs to the wall.
Hold your numbers up.
No talking.
I thought they were going
to be similar types.
They are.
Uh-huh.
Look closely, Mr. Chaing.
I know how this works.
There, number four--
the short, fat one.
You're sure?
That's your Red Hood.
Threw all that money away,
and I didn't get a cent.
Clyde Destro,
47 years old, conviction
for assault and armed robbery
of a convenience store
three years ago.
Let's book him.
Wait a minute.
All we have is one witness
outside of the crime scene,
that's it.
Now, Floyd was killed,
so we know they're
turning on each other.
Let Destro go?
And tail him.
He takes us to the
other gang members.
We use them
against each other.
We catch the Red Hood Gang
red-handed.
That's right.
Can I get a ride home?
My girlfriend will freak out
if I turn up in a patrol car.
(door opens)
Well...
don't you look lovely?
(door closes)
There's still business
to discuss.
Of course.
The basement.
How do I resume operations?
We do have a business to run.
Yes, you're stealing body parts.
For who?
Oh!
We have clients...
all over the world in
need of such things.
Also, there's the doctor's
personal experiments.
You have such
a presence,
Miss Mooney.
Such a gaze.
Your eyes...
will fetch quite a penny.
You will take nothing from me.
Really?
Because the way I see it,
you have two choices: One...
we kill you and your little
friends in the basement.
That's an inconvenience
but an acceptable one.
Or, two...
...we take your eyes now
and see how long a blind girl
can survive in the basement.
You forgot option three.
(grunts)
Stop her!
(both scream)
No!
(spoon clinks)
(thud)
(thunder rumbles; Alfred and
Reggie converse quietly)
I picked something out
from the cellar.
I hope that's okay.
Well, that's, uh,
extremely kind of you,
Master Bruce,
but I don't think that we...
...that I'll be, uh,
drinking this evening.
I'm sure it's perfectly fine
to have
a glass of wine occasionally,
Alfred.
I-I picked an old one.
Seems a shame to let them
gather dust down there.
Domaine de la Romanée-Conti.
It's a rather nice Burgundy,
actually, it's 1966.
Yeah.
It's one of your
father's favorites.
(chuckles)
Why not, eh?
Take a pew.
That's very kind of you.
There you go.
Cheers, mate.
Now, the idea,
of course,
is to let it breathe
for at least an hour.
Or not.
(slurps)
(laughs)
Ah.
Delicious.
(laughter)
So he eventually
opened his backpack
and he found the
bloody snake.
We'd been waiting
for it all night.
He didn't even flinch.
What'd you do?
Oh, you know,
I chopped its head off
and we ate the bloody thing.
(laughter)
He did.
What did it taste like?
ALFRED:
Uh, a bit like, um,
fast food.
(all laugh)
ALFRED:
It was horrible.
It was disgusting.
BRUCE:
So, um...
so, Mr. Payne,
you were in the Air Force?
Special Air Service-- SAS.
Best soldiers
in the world,
if I'm being honest.
So that means covert missions?
That's right.
Before a conflict,
they dropped us
behind enemy lines.
We were quiet,
precise, and deadly.
We never lost a man
and we always completed
our missions.
Except that once, I guess.
Yeah, well,
that's enough
of the old war stories, eh, Reg?
What one time?
REGGIE:
There was a sandstorm.
We got separated.
Two of us were captured.
You?
He fought 12 of them off
before they cut him down.
Didn't you, Alf?
I'm here now, aren't I?
That's all that matters.
(sniffs)
All right, gents,
while I have to say
this has been
absolutely lovely,
I'd like to,
I'd like to tidy up
before I go to bed.
(scoffing):
T-T-Tidy up?
Mr. Yes Sir, No Sir.
Mr. Queensberry rules
and discipline.
Thank you, that's enough.
Alfred's right...
it's time for bed.
Good night,
Master Bruce.
BRUCE:
Good night. Good night.
Sleep well, son.
Why are you hiding from him
what you really are,
who you really are?
You're a war dog, Alfie.
You're a cold-blooded,
lethal war dog, is what you are.
I found some fresh clothes
for you, Reg.
I folded them
and I put 'em on your bed,
and I've taken the liberty
of packing you
a lunch for your travels
tomorrow.
It's been really nice
to see you, Reggie.
I see them, at night...
when I'm alone.
The faces...
the faces of those we killed.
Do you?
I don't have to look
for them, Reg.
They find me.
(startled shout)
(gasps, chuckles)
Holy crap.
You scared the snot out of me.
H-Had to see you.
I c-couldn't wait.
Where were you?
Out.
J-Just out?
What's it to you?
I need the hood.
What?
No.
M...
My-my girlfriend, sh-she
wants... she wants to leave.
She... she called me
a loser last night.
Her ex is back in town.
He's a b-bouncer.
I figured
she-she sees me
in the hood, she's got... she's
got to take me s-seriously.
Did you ransack my place
looking for it?
I need it, Destro.
They're talking about it
on the streets
and in the news.
She sees me in it, and I'm...
No!
We have one last job before
we split up and skip town.
(gun cocks)
You have it on you, don't you?
You better use that thing
before I make you eat it.
(gunshot)
(door creaking)
(gasping weakly)
He's alive.
(stairs rattling)
Who shot you, Destro?
Give us the name
of the guy.
I need an ambulance.
We'll get to that. Give us the
names of the guys in your crew.
I'm bleeding out.
Yeah, you're dying.
And, unfortunately, I'm not
getting cell reception.
You know what might help?
Giving us the names of the guys
in your crew!
GORDON:
I need an ambulance.
Java Heights and Homewood,
apartment 466.
I might need some pressure
on this wound.
Knock yourself out.
(panting)
What do you got there,
partner?
A stack of loan rejection
letters from the banks
that were robbed.
"Dear Mr. Destro, we regret
to inform you your application
for a loan has been denied."
"Mr. Destro, once again,
we must deny your application,
due to inadequate collateral."
What the hell
would he need a loan for?
Pastry shop.
Get out of here.
You're a baker?
A damn good baker.
And they all turned you down.
So these are revenge robberies.
Banks don't care
about people like me.
Or you, probably.
You have to force people
to see you.
Otherwise, you're nothing.
There's a third letter here.
International Savings Bank
of Gotham-- this was
the next target.
Where's my ambulance?
♪ ♪
To new beginnings.
(sniffs)
I'm not trying
to poison you, son.
Forgive me
if I'm a little cautious.
If this club tanks,
Falcone's not gonna trust
either of us again.
I don't know about you,
but I'm done
playing the sidekick.
To no longer being a sidekick.
Do you miss her?
I do.
(chuckles)
Even after everything
she did to me.
Perhaps it's not
our friends but...
our enemies that define us.
To Fish.
She got what she deserved.
(thunder rumbling)
(rattling, clattering)
(rattling, clattering continue)
You're stealing
from us?
You could have just asked me
for money, Reg.
You don't know how hard that is,
Alfie... do you?
We gave you somewhere to sleep.
We put food in your belly.
I'm in trouble.
Real trouble.
I don't need a lecture
right now.
What kind of trouble?
You don't want to know.
Right.
Well, you put the bag down
and you leave.
Now.
Did you bring a gun, Alfie?
No.
If there was any other way...
Oh, come on-- there's
always another way, mate.
I'm sorry.
Sorry f...
(grunting)
I'm so sorry.
(coughs)
♪ ♪
(no voice)
(dialing phone)
Th-This is Bruce Wayne.
I need immediate help
at Wayne Manor!
My friend has been stabbed.
Alfred... Alfred, Alfred, look
at me-- you're gonna be okay.
Alfred, stay with me.
(voice breaking):
Please.
Alfred!
(tires screech)
There's only three
of us.
I'm worried. If someone makes
a move in there...
Don't be.
I have this.
(tires screeching)
GORDON (over bullhorn):
GCPD!
We have you surrounded!
This doesn't have
to end badly!
Put down your guns!
Suck it, coppers!
(gunfire)
(laughing)
OFFICER (echoing):
Man down! Man down!
(clicking)
GORDON:
Hold your fire!
OFFICER:
Drop it!
It's over.
Yeah?
Don't be so sure.
(gunfire)
(sniffs)
I need a Danish.
(phone ringing)
Yeah.
Which hospital?
(monitor beeping steadily)
(voice breaking):
I can't lose him.
He's all I have.
(crying)
REGGIE:
He has nothing concrete.
Just faces, some dates,
some newspaper articles.
There's no grounds
for an investigation.
Just... suspicions...
some cobbled-together
theories...
Nothing.
WOMAN:
Has he had outside counsel?
I don't think so.
WOMAN: And his caretaker,
Mr. Pennyworth?
He's in the hospital.
WOMAN:
For how long?
If he lives,
a few weeks, give or take.
Now's the time
to make a move on the kid.
Thank you for your service,
Mr. Payne.
I doubt we'll meet again.
He's just a kid.
A good kid.
Good-bye, Mr. Payne.
(mimics gunshot)