Previously onGotham...
I'm arresting you
for the murder of the boy
you blew up under
the Crown Point bridge.
And how can you help me?
What do you say, Pal?
You need a smile.
I'm not who my parents
might've wanted me to be.
- And I'm okay with that.
- I'm not okay with it.
I went to my lawyer to had them
drop emancipation papers.
Alfred, you're fired!
Now get the hell out of my house.
I am in control!
But why would you want that?
We had so much fun when we were me.
Surprise.
I needed the police
to turn on Penguin
So you sent this monster
to my city?
I need you at the head
of the GCPD.
Let them think you're a hero.
Mrs. Gordon.
I just shot and killed the pig.
Ivy?
What happened to you?
I've been reborn.
And I will never be underestimated
or ignored ever again.
Let's make Gotham our bitch.
Can I help you?
You're so beautiful.
Thanks. Now move.
Yeah, let me tell him.
Oh, my God, you're gonna love this.
- Let me just tell him.
- Wait, no. Can I tell him?
- Just let me tell him.
- Nice score.
Cindy? Who are these...
Well, what a charming young lady.
- She's so beautiful, mom.
- It's cool.
So, your perfume turn people
into your super fans?
Like all good things, it'll fade.
But until then, they're mine.
Freeze.
Not bad.
I'll check out the rest of the house.
My friend thinks
we're here to rob you.
But I know who you work for
Roland Charles PhD.
How you torture plants
in the name of science.
Do you ever wonder
how those plants feel?
Soon...
you'll share more with them
than you ever could've imagined.
What did you do to him?
I gave him what he deserves.
Captain. Captain Gordon. Yoohoo.
Captain. Captain Gordon.
Chaz Carmichael
Congratulations.
Boss ain't gonna be happy
I'm in here.
Let's say I got a lot
of responsibility
in my organization.
Well, you seem like a real
responsible guy.
My boss is Sofia Falcone.
Oh, yeah?
What's that got to do with me?
Easy.
Well, I know she told me
if I ever got pinched
to tell you to give her a call.
- Is that so?
- You can't do this.
- I got rights.
- Oh, yeah?
How about you exercise your right
to remain silent?
Hey, Cap.
Got something.
Victim was Roland Charles
were an RnD
Wayne Enterprises Biotech.
Did you know him
from any work to Wayne?
I met him in passing, not that
I recognize him right away.
It's like the twig
we found last week.
The toxin entered the bloodstream
through the cuts on the neck.
If it is the same as the last victim.
The toxin creates vines
that feed off in the victim's body.
while also attacking the hippocampus
like some plant-based psychedelics.
So it kills you
and makes you hallucinate.
Any witnesses?
The family saying
it was two women.
Redhead and a brunette?
The redhead used some kind
of hypnosis on them.
The brunette wore leather whip.
Selina Kyle?
Murder's not really her thing.
The family says
the redhead killed Roland.
She left with his briefcase.
Well, if his briefcase is missing
maybe this is related
to his work at Wayne Biotech?
Doubtful.
He oversaw standard projects.
Pharmaceuticals, pesticides.
What?
Nothing.
I'll track down Selina.
This is Bruce. Leave a message.
Bruce, I know we haven't talked
in a while
but someone just killed
Roland Charles.
We may have a problem.
Roland Charles asked for clearance
for some top secret
biotech experiment.
Project M.
Ivy, do you think
I care about that?
You just killed a man
in front of his family.
He had it coming.
You have no idea
what these people do.
We need to find out everything
we can about Project M.
And whatever it is
all access would've had
to have been approved
by Bruce Wayne.
You know I... I... I really thought
that doing a crime spree with you
would be fun
but I was wrong.
- Selina!
- Leave me alone.
Enjoy your shrubs.
We don't need her.
Now let's show everyone
just how strong we are.
Pour me another shot.
Party time. Party time.
Gonna throw up.
You know, I've had some crazy nights
but I've never bought a talking bird.
Sorry. Party's over.
I was not at the party.
I've seen you before.
At the Sirens. What are you...
what are you doing here?
I'm here
to speak for those who can't
speak for themselves, Bruce.
I'm here to speak for the plants.
Okay.
My head hurts.
Please get out.
First.
Tell me about Project M.
How do you know about that?
You know, I know a lot of things...
billionaire boy.
Ivy?
You're so...
beautiful.
Now Project M.
Hi, there.
Giddy up!
Is this seat taken?
If I say yes
would it make a difference?
You know, I've always been a fan
when you got locked up
in this loony bin
I expected great things.
Murder or two. Maybe a...
prison break.
But all you've done is mope
for the last six weeks.
You must know I cannot escape.
Why?
None of your business.
Because Sofia Falcone's holding
someone important to me captive
and if I escape, she will kill him.
Wow, what a boring story.
If there's one thing I can't stand
it's someone boring.
The last person who bored me
was Deidric.
- Deidric.
- I had to sneak into
his shock therapy session
and boost the juice.
Now he pees himself
10 times a day and sometimes...
poos himself.
Well, that's very sad.
I'm gonna cure you this attitude,
Oswald.
I'm gonna find that entertaining guy
I know is inside of you.
And when I do ooh...
we are gonna have
so much fun together.
Alright?
That's quite a story.
Not what I was expecting.
You're just so easy to talk to.
Normally, I would make this quick,
like I did with Roland.
But it's your name
on the company
that murders my little green friends.
I'm so sorry, Ivy.
I would never want to upset you.
But you have, Bruce.
I know what you really want.
Bury your head in the sand.
You're still guilty.
It will be slow.
And it will be painful.
But it's what you deserve.
I'm just sorry I won't be here
to see you bloom.
Nope.
No.
None of this will do.
Where's Ivy?
What is she doing to me, where am I?
- Just the thing.
- Ra's al Ghul?
Ra's al Ghul.
Nope, never heard of him.
I'm Dr. Greenthumb.
Just here to do
a little light pruning, really.
No!
There.
That's better.
Mummy always used to say.
a little pruning encourages growth.
Where are you taking that?
Thanks, poppet.
Where are you taking my face?
Please, what's happening to me?
My dear boy.
You're dying.
Just hold still
while I put this in place.
Good lord.
Jim. What a pleasant surprise.
- I'm looking for Selina.
- Haven't seen her.
She's more of an alley cat
than a house cat.
Now I'm just in the middle...
Let him in.
Hello, James. It's been a while.
Barbara, can you give us a moment?
Sure.
Have fun, lovebird.
What is your business
with Barbara Kean?
You worried that I told her
about our arrangement?
I know how to keep a secret.
Now, I want my man, Carmichael,
released from GCPD custody.
That wasn't the deal.
You run the underworld,
I run the GCPD
your guy got arrested.
That's on him.
Let me make something clear...
our deal is whatever I say it is.
Unless you want people to know
you're responsible
for bringing the Pyg to town.
You brought him to Gotham
I was just trying to stop Penguin.
But, you covered it up
and took credit for killing him.
Word gets out, you're destroyed.
Along with your beloved GCPD.
And if I go down...
so will you.
And I think you like being
the Queen of the underworld.
You still think you know
what I will and won't do.
I know a bluff when I see one.
I have a job to do.
Selena!
Oh, hey Jim. I found Selena,
she went that way.
No! No! No!
Shut it, Penguin.
No! No!
Don't!
- What do you want?
- I told you Pengy.
I'm gonna cure you
of the sad-sack mopey act.
And the best cure,
is the laughing cure.
Make me laugh.
Make him laugh! Make him laugh!
So, what are you be performing?
Contortionism,
juggling act, the tight five?
What's that?
You want to do a clown dance?
- Yeah!
- Wonderful.
I will not!
No.
I refuse it! No!
Make him dance! Make him dance!
Make him dance!
In your own time.
You have no idea how I have suffered.
The betrayals I've been do into.
Just leave me alone.
- Leave me alone.
- Cut!
Oswald, Oswald, Oswald.
You are trapped in a prison. In here.
And I'm offering you the key. So...
- dance.
- Make him dance!
Make him dance! Make him dance!
Now we're talking.
So I can feel funny from it.
Here it come.
Here comes the bunny. Okay.
Afraid to stare you are not.
We'll try again tomorrow.
What the hell, man?
Why were you running Selena?
'Cause a jerk with badge
was chasing me.
So not because you're in roll
in Charles' house last night
when he was turned into a tree?
His family saw
a redhead and a brunette
the brunette was carrying
a leather whip, just like yours
tell me I'm crazy.
I swear, I was only there
to rob the place.
So what about the redhead?
She kill some tweaker
in the narrow the same way.
I need a name.
Ivy Pepper.
Try again, I know Ivy.
No, Gordon, she's changed.
Like a lot.
She can use plant to hypnotize people
and poison them.
So why'd she want to kill Roland?
'Cause he work for Wayne Enterprises.
Wayne Enterprise?
She's obsessed with the super-secret
project they're doing.
I know she's lying.
Come on, let's go.
Admiring my handiwork?
Excuse me?
Look how beautiful he became.
And all it took...
was a little...
scratch.
What do you want from me?
I want to know about Project M.
What is Project M?
Bruce Wayne told me everything.
Now, he didn't even trust himself
with the location
but then you know where it is.
And you're going to take me to it.
But first...
you probably want to tell me
I'm beautiful.
Yes.
No!
Help! Somebody, help me!
Jim. Jim, I need you to help me.
Looks like you got yourself shaving,
old man.
Jim, it's me, it's Bruce.
I'm Bruce Wayne.
Honey, I think we'd know
if you are Bruce Wayne.
He's the one throwing this shindig.
That's him, younger.
Bruce, you're incorrigible.
I may have bust a gut.
Luckily, I am a doctor.
I need the guest pajamas.
Come on.
Easy there, sport.
It's Italian Velvet.
What did you do?
Where's Ra's al Ghul?
Ra's al who?
It's my face. He gave you my face!
That's my face!
I think you've been hitting the gin.
Give me back my face!
I'm Bruce Wayne!
Get off of me! You ruining my mind!
Everything all right, Master Bruce?
Yes, thank you.
Just getting rid of a riffraff.
Dude, what is it with you
and arm grabbing?
Harper, I need keys to lockup,
and is Lucius in his office.
Lucius? No, he left with Ivy
a little while ago.
- Ivy Pepper? She was here?
- Yeah.
She asked me
to introduce her to everyone.
Doesn't she the coolest?
She's a psycho who turn a guy
into a potted plant.
What's going on with you?
Did he just say that Ivy is a psycho?
But Ivy is the best.
Is this the hypnosis
I've been hearing about?
I'm gonna say yeah.
Until it fades,
they'll do anything for her.
And think she's the coolest.
What do you mean by Ivy is a psycho?
Hold that thought, Harper.
We'll be right back.
You hear what the captain said
about Ivy?
- But Ivy is awesome.
- Yeah, she is the coolest.
No more! No more!
You have a visitor.
Hello, Oswald.
I see Arkham is treating you well.
I take that you're here to gloat.
You are correct.
And why not?
I'm in an insane asylum.
Being pummeled by lunatics.
Then again, at least I'm not a moron.
I may not be the man I once was...
but I have many things
that you do not have.
A purpose...
friends, your manifest.
And I wanted you to see that.
No.
I know who you are.
There's something else going on.
Something else brought you here.
There's nothing else.
I wanted you to see
how well I am doing.
And I wanted to see
how miserable you are.
Mission accomplished.
Ed...
I'm gonna be out of here soon.
And once I am...
I am going to wipe
that smile off your face.
Preferably with the chainsaw.
Now, how are you gonna do that?
You have no friends.
No one to help you escape.
You are utterly alone.
Goodbye, Oswald.
If I... if I don't put too much stuff
into your brain
you're just a simpleton!
"I am held captive all day,
my brilliance locked away
this prison must be broken,
the key...
my name which must be spoken."
You are still in there.
That's why you came.
You're still there.
And you gonna help me
find a way out of here.
Hello, we should be leaving.
Not until we find out
where Ivy took Lucius.
There has to be something.
You know where it is
and you are going to take me to it.
You're so incredible.
Where is project M?
Wayne Bio-Tech has a secret facility
outside the city
at the edge of Kane Park.
Good man Lucius.
In here.
Hey, cap, the boys and I were talking
and we didn't really like
the way that you are talking
about Ivy.
I told you we should've left.
Look, I think you misinterpreted
what I was saying.
You called Ivy a psycho.
That's a term of endearment.
I love Ivy, I think she's great.
What about you?
Do you love Ivy?
Yeah, I love Ivy.
How much?
I love Ivy so much
that I wish I could be her.
You're not really selling it.
And you think you did?
Run.
Get them.
Selena!
All right, Oswald.
Old buddy, old pal.
Tonight we're gonna cure you.
Make me laugh or else.
Let's call this
the sudden death round.
Dietrich?
Okay, that was clever... ish.
Yeah, that's a spoon.
This is also a fork!
Looks like you got
some fire in you still.
But it just too little,
too late, too...
boring.
Lobotomized the little burn.
Wait! Wait.
You said,
this prison is all in my mind.
Maybe, I've been to prison right now.
A prison, where you can't get to me.
Okay.
You really are nuts.
Try laughing now you ginger sap!
Yes!
See? I told you I kill you!
Don't flatter yourself!
One more.
And so I said to the guy.
You wanna know what I said?
I said, what is this?
A three-ring circus?
And keep them coming.
How long do you think
you can hide in here?
Look.
Out there.
He's going to find you eventually.
I don't understand.
Who's gonna find me?
- Alfred?
- Special agent Pennyworth
to you too, scumbag.
Package secured,
requesting extraction.
No!
Just be careful here.
We to go this way.
This way.
So, this is it?
Project M.
Also called Lazarus Water.
It belongs to a man
known as Ra's al Ghul.
It stimulates cell growth
at an alarming rate.
We get to figure out how.
I assume Project M killed plants.
But it's the opposite.
Just like humans lock up
something so beautiful.
What do you gonna do with it?
I'm going to make miracles happen.
Release me!
Listen to me, I'm Bruce Wayne
I can pay you whatever you want,
you need to let me go, now!
Sorry, I can't do that more enough.
You see, I have a mission.
What mission?
For me to bring you to him.
What is that?
Oh, giddy up, son.
What do you want?
Why did you bring me here?
This is where my parents were killed!
No.
This is where I was born.
No!
That's far enough.
Jim Gordon.
Ivy Pepper?
It's been a long time.
I'm not the same kid you remember.
The kid whose father,
you and your partner killed
all those years ago?
How was this possible?
First, I was a seed...
then sprout...
now I've bloomed.
Drop your gun.
Or your friend Lucius
becomes a flower arrangement.
Lucius, you okay?
I'm in the sweet embrace of one
of my favorite people, Jim
never been better.
Now, I know you're tenacious.
Jim Gordon gun or no gun
you'll come after me.
But then...
Bruce Wayne will die.
What have you done to him?
I went to Wayne Manor
and planted a seed.
I imagine he's about to bloom.
But if you let me go...
he may have a chance...
to get him the antidote.
This isn't over.
You have no idea how right you are.
I love you.
Lucius, give me the antidote.
Let's just wait until
Ivy is at a safe distance.
Give me the antidote, come on.
- Don't make me hit you.
- Jim...
I must warn you,
I'm a black belt in Jiu-jitsu.
- Since when?
- Night classes.
- The Lazarus Water.
- Come on.
We gotta get to Bruce Wayne.
Help!
Somebody help!
Who's there?
Show yourself!
Who are you?
I am the one you cannot escape.
The one you cannot kill.
You're me.
- Please.
- You're scared.
You should be.
It's okay Bruce, it's all right.
You're safe now.
According to Lucius
Ivy's toxin attacks the brain
like hallucinogen.
So, whatever you went through
I doubt it was pleasant
but it wasn't real.
I think I saw who I really am.
I know what you're gonna say
but what I saw, it was real.
Well, then you're lucky.
Most people go their whole lives
not ever knowing who they really are.
I'm not lucky.
You didn't see it.
I've seen my own darkness.
I say this...
you have people around you
who care for you.
Don't fight this alone.
Trust us.
I'll leave men outside tonight.
I'll come by tomorrow,
check in on you.
Jim.
When I was under...
I saw you.
You had a mustache.
Well, clearly
that's a very dangerous toxin.
Alfred, it's...
it's me, it's Bruce, I...
I need your help, Alfred.
Please call me.
We're not hypnotized.
Just embarrassed.
Good to have you back.
All right, listen up!
I want an APB on Ivy Pepper.
Finding her is our top priority.
All right, you heard him people,
let's get to work.
- What do you want?
- I thought about what you said.
How if I use the pic
to destroy you
I'd also destroy myself.
And?
And, you're right.
I've come to enjoy
being the queen of Gotham.
Glad we understand each other.
Not quite, you see, I also realized
I don't need the pic.
There are other ways for me
to hurt you.
Thank you so much for coming.
Without we're overdue for a chat.
How could I say no
to my sister-in-law.
Cowards. Oh, I strangle them if...
Relax, buddy.
You gave me what I needed.
The laugh of the century.
Tell me something.
You appear to have
everyone here under your thumb.
The guards, the inmates...
What can I say,
I'm a charismatic guy.
You could escape anytime.
Why stay?
Why indeed?
- You're planning something.
- Righty-o, boy.
Something spectacular.
See, I'm in this funny form
because I need
to find the cram deal are crazy.
Which is why I need you.
You get it.
But when we're done
the world out there
that'll be the asylum.
What do you say?
Thank you for your kind offer.
I don't expect to be here very long.
You'll come around.
They always do.
Nope.
Where did these plants come from?
Get out.
Before we call the police.
Oh, friends,
you're all so beautiful.