Previously on Gotham...
I had a meeting
with board of Wayne Enterprises.
To tell them I was
investigating them,
they sent someone
we trust to spy on us.
Alfred was stabbed.
It was a friend of his from the Army.
- What was he looking for?
- Some of my files missing.
I could find out who hired him.
He's the key to everything.
I have a plan.
I promise you,
I will get some of us
out of here alive.
- Who are you?
- Dr. Francis Dulmacher.
The people in the basement trust me.
Put me in charge and I promise you
a dependable flow of healthy product.
- And if I fail?
- Those who fail me
still have their uses.
What are they doing?
I'm sorry, honey, you're on the list.
Half the cops on the G.C.P.D.
have a Cobblepot
and Loeb has the goods on
all of them.
That is what Loeb does.
- Well, it ends now.
- So, what do you want?
With the coming election
for president
of the policeman's union
there's no man I'd rather support.
It's a new day in the G.C.P.D.
- Looking good, Ms. Cavanaugh.
- Thank you.
- How's that swelling?
- Fine.
If you need more ice packs,
I'll let Denise know.
Mr. Douglas,
I know you don't like your view
and as soon as
a recovery suite is open
I'm going to move you.
Is there a problem?
- You're outside.
- You're observant.
I'm the new assistant for the doctor.
I'm Fish.
And you are?
Inside, you're free to roam,
that's Dr. Dulmacher's prerogative.
But once you step outside,
you're in my world.
I'm the man who catches
the poor souls
brave enough to try to escape.
You're the catcher.
I've heard a lot about you.
So, have there been many?
Poor souls, I mean.
No.
The water does most of the work.
But every so often, someone gets
stupid and gives it a go.
I didn't know
I wasn't supposed to be outside.
My mistake.
Make that mistake again
and it'll be your last.
I saw the papers the other day.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks.
So, what does president
of the policeman's union do exactly?
Depends on the president.
- I see.
- How's Alfred?
Whinier than I thought.
No, he's getting better.
Glad to hear it.
You two lied about who stabbed him,
didn't you?
That's why you're here?
Is it?
Yes.
Did you...
lie to me?
No.
If we don't have a description
of the culprit
we won't find him.
I wish I could help you, detective.
Alfred wants to go after him
on his own,
that's why you lied to me.
No.
Bruce, look at me.
Whatever Alfred is up to,
you have to stay out of it.
It's dangerous.
And it's not your fight.
I cut this bread way too thick,
didn't I?
Bruce...
I understand what you're saying.
Okay, then.
Detective Gordon.
Len Moore.
- Officer. What can I help you with?
- You're a man with a reputation.
- Yeah?
- A Gotham detective
who actually closes cases.
I try.
That's actually why I'm here.
- Yeah?
- See a few weeks ago
I was the first responder
to a homicide.
Victim's name was 'Grace Fairchild'.
They found her body stabbed
to death.
The detectives who caught the case
they got nowhere with it
and moved on.
I'm sorry to hear that
- but it happens.
- I'm wondering if you'd pick up
where they left off.
You want me to take over the case?
Yeah.
Look, Len, I got a full boat here.
This victim's family,
they deserve justice.
- Yeah.
- Her killer deserves to pay
for what he did.
This was a nasty one.
They're all nasty.
What's your angle on this?
There's no angle. It's just...
A few of us younger guys,
and we've been watching
what you've been doing
to clean up Gotham and the G.C.P.D.,
and I wanna be a part of it.
And bringing you this case...
is my way of trying to do that.
I'll look into it.
Ready to go?
Ready?
I have been dreaming
about the carbonara
at Luccio's all day.
New case?
Sort of. It's an unsolved homicide
a uni asked me to look into.
- It's an odd one.
- How so?
Thought you were hungry.
What can I say?
You had me at "homicide."
The victim, Grace Fairchild,
was found two weeks ago.
But she was reported missing
four months earlier.
The last anyone heard,
she called her mother
said she was having a drink at a bar
in the South Village.
That's my neighborhood. What bar?
Detectives canvassed the area,
nobody knows.
No leads, no tips.
I'm starting to see
why the case was dropped.
God, we were almost the same age.
We could've been friends.
You know, they have a few
speakeasies in the South Village.
It's a new thing.
You walk in through a dry cleaner's
or a shoe store to get inside.
Easy to miss
if you're not in the know.
Thanks. I'll check it out.
Good.
I'm glad you're looking into this.
Whoever did this, he's a monster.
Kelly.
God.
Still bad.
What do you want?
I have a plan, but I need your help.
What plan?
We're going to escape.
I'm getting off of this hell
of an island
or I'm gonna die trying.
Alfred?
Where are you going?
Into the city, Master Bruce.
If I know Reggie,
he's probably drunk himself
half to death by now
and is moving swiftly
onto the harder stuff.
I'll probably find him
holed up in a shooting gallery,
totally off his maracas.
Alfred, you can't go.
- You're not well.
- No choice, Master Bruce.
He'll only be here for a few days.
Enough time to get his fix,
then he'll be off.
Well, then we'd better get going.
If you think I'm gonna take you,
Master...
Oh, dear.
Good day, Lidia.
Have you thought about my offer?
I told you already,
my place is not for sale.
Please.
I beg of you, think again.
I will serve strictly
as a silent partner.
You will continue
to run the day-to-day operations...
I told you already!
Madam, please, I meant no harm.
Okay, ma'am. You made your point.
Madam, I assure you...
I have a sincere interest
in your establishment.
If money is not what you seek...
surely there is something you want.
My granddaughter, Antonia...
She's beautiful...
Virtuous...
An angel.
And she has been seduced
by a silver-tongued guitar player.
Lucifer himself.
A tragedy.
You make her come home...
leave this baboon...
then I'll consider your offer.
Madam...
She'll be home for Sunday Mass.
You have my word.
This place is a dump.
Real nickel-and-dime.
It's worth far more than that, Gabe.
You just don't see it yet.
- No.
- I'm not saying
we officially take over
the investigation.
Just help me look into it.
No.
Harvey, the victim deserves justice.
Yeah,
and I deserve a mute supermodel
who likes pasty Irish guys
and loves to cook.
It's not happening.
Besides, we both know that justice
isn't the real reason
you want this one.
Hello, detectives.
Ed, question.
Would you rather work more or less?
- Is this a riddle?
- Exactly.
You're helping. What's up?
List of establishments
in the South Village
with a liquor license.
- Including speakeasies?
- Yes, sirree.
Four of which,
you'll be pleased to know,
were missed
by the original detectives.
That's great, Ed.
Thanks. One more thing.
I was going through
the crime scene evidence
from the Fairchild murder and...
there's a piece of evidence missing.
- Any idea what it is?
- No, but it's labeled "3A."
Think you can find it?
Detective, I will solve this puzzle.
You coming?
Let me say it in Spanish. No.
Okay, look, you're right.
I'm ambitious.
I wanna show people around here
that things are gonna change.
But, Harvey,
I can't do that without your help.
Look, I know you're riding high
with getting over on
Loeb and all
but there's one thing
you should always remember.
Fly too close to the sun,
you're gonna get burned.
- You done?
- Yeah.
Good. Then get your ass up.
So that's it.
So you're trying to tell me
you actually think
we can get out of here?
That's what I said, didn't I?
- How?
- With cunning and guile.
But it won't work without your help.
Why us?
Why not your friends?
There's no telling
how this is all going to go down
during the breakout.
Just in case it goes south.
I need some stone-cold killers
by my side
not some whipped-ass victims.
That's fair. What's the plan?
Outside, there's a boat
down by the shore
big enough to carry the six of us
off of this island.
A boat?
You have a better idea?
I heard a chopper land the other day.
Thumped like a son of a bitch.
Why don't we fly out of here?
Do any of you know how to fly
a helicopter?
That's why.
All right, this boat.
You got the keys to it?
No. Not yet, but I will.
So, are you in or out?
We're 0-3 and
my dogs are barking.
I'm hardly one to complain
about going to a bar,
but this is getting ridiculous.
It's grunt work.
Just like any other case.
Except it's not just like
any other case, it's a hobby.
Everybody needs a hobby.
G.C.P.D. Homicide.
Yeah, she was in here.
A while ago,
maybe three or four months.
You remember her?
Yeah, she mentioned
she went to a rival college of mine.
- Plus...
- Plus what?
To be honest with you,
her date was hot.
Her date,
remember what he looked like?
Just that he was good-looking,
but classy, you know?
Okay, your turn.
How is a successful, funny,
mildly good-looking guy like you
still single?
Mildly?
Maybe a little bit more than that.
Come on.
Something has to be wrong with you.
Maybe you're right.
I've had plenty of relationships
but in the end they...
never seem to work out.
Why not?
I think what I'm looking for
frightens people.
Okay.
No, it's, it's nothing weird.
What, then?
It's gonna sound cheesy.
I won't laugh. I promise.
What I'm looking for...
is unconditional love.
Unconditional, real,
intense love.
Cheesy, right?
Totally.
You like it?
It'll do.
There's some wine in the kitchen.
Open anything you like.
May I take your jacket?
This place must work well.
What do you mean?
The women that you bring back here.
Actually it's...
Been a while,
since I've had anyone over.
Lucky me.
I'm the lucky one.
Thank you for taking a chance on me.
Are you kidding me?
Look at this place.
I could definitely stay here.
For a night.
Look, if he...
Comes back in or you think
of anything else, give me a call.
Sure.
He was right here, Harvey.
Yeah.
You're not dropping this one,
are you?
Not a chance.
So...
Are we in agreement?
Not quite.
Pagliaccisays
he still loves the girl.
He won't leave her.
Antonia and I are destined
to be together.
And nothing you can do
will make me stop loving her.
See what I mean? True love.
You want me to put a slug in him?
- See if that loosens him up?
- No.
He's a guitar player.
Lose the fingers.
- You want me to shoot his fingers?
- Don't shoot them.
Lose them.
Just the man I wanted to see.
Don't say that.
You're gonna make Jim jealous.
I finished the Fairchild autopsy
and the results are strange.
Strange how?
Grace Fairchild was missing
for over four months.
Usually with these kind
of abductions there's a lot of...
trauma and abuse to the body,
not this time.
Other than the stab wounds
to her heart and her throat,
her body was mostly pristine.
That doesn't add up.
Unless...
- Unless what?
- Have you ever consider
if she ran off on her own?
That her going missing has
nothing to do with her murder?
The findings would certainly
support that.
Maybe.
No.
No. Fairchild had a good job,
a mortgage.
Hell, she called her mother
the night she went missing.
No, she didn't run away.
She was taken.
And whoever took her
kept her locked away
'til he was good and ready.
And then he killed her.
I know it.
Morning. How'd you sleep?
Like a baby.
So, I thought after breakfast,
we could go to the Palick exhibit.
He's only in town another week.
I would love to, really,
but I am already late
and I've got a morning meeting
and a work lunch.
- So reschedule it.
- I can't.
I had a really good time
with you last night.
And I hope that
I get to see you again.
At least have some breakfast.
I still have to go home and change,
and I'm so late.
Next time.
Call me tonight.
I can come over after work.
If you want.
Jason, please. I really have to go.
No.
You don't.
Ms. Mooney.
What a surprise.
Is there something I can do for you?
Well,
supplies were running low
for the inmates.
Those are in the storage room.
But then, of course,
you already knew that.
The one thing
I won't tolerate is dishonesty.
You were trying to escape,
weren't you?
No.
I'll tell you what
I'm gonna shoot you in the stomach.
You'll feel pressure at first.
Then you'll feel an intense burning
like you've never felt in your life.
Maybe that will properly motivate you
to be honest with me.
I ask you again.
Were you trying to escape?
- No.
- How disappointing.
Wait. Stop. Wait, wait.
I was lying,
but I wasn't trying to escape.
You were going to kill me?
Slit my throat, perhaps?
No, I swear.
Not yours.
Every night when I close my eyes,
I pray to God...
that nightmare doesn't come.
That...
living, breathing man
stitched together with...
arms and legs that weren't his.
That nightmare you created...
I've faced dangerous men
but none like you.
Dollmaker.
So, you'd rather take your own life
than end up one of my creations?
Yes.
Well,
Miss Mooney.
Try anything like this again
and your nightmare will come true.
I will bring you back
from the dead if I have to.
And make you into something
the world has never seen.
Was there something else?
No.
I could've smashed your head
with a brick, you know.
Why would you do that?
Why'd you even say that?
Just thought you should know.
What's up?
Why are you looking for me?
Reggie Payne,
the man who stabbed Alfred,
he's in Gotham.
And you need my help to find him.
Okay.
Alfred said he'd be at a gun range
for a few days.
But I checked every one in the city.
Nothing.
Who stays at a gun range
for a few days?
Doesn't make any sense.
That's what he said.
He said Reggie would be
at a shooting gallery.
That's not the same as
a gun range, silly.
You really need to get out more.
All right, all right, all right.
Now, go get yourself cleaned up.
I'll be back in a minute.
So...
Shall we discuss terms?
- So, what is it?
- Well, to be clear.
This isn't an actual piece of crime
scene evidence.
It's gone, as far as I can tell.
What I was able to find
is a photocopy buried
deep in a logbook.
It's a broken heart.
Hand-painted, I guess.
This was at the crime scene?
- You sure?
- Well, not this, exactly.
You see, a photocopy is a replica...
Damn it, no, Ed. Not now.
- What's wrong?
- I warned you
but, no.
You had to go
and get both of us burned.
- What are you talking about?
- This guy you're after.
This is not his first rodeo.
He's a serial killer.
This looks delicious.
Thank you.
I...
I think I might have overcooked
the lamb a little bit.
But I... I...
I'm sure it's fine.
How was your day?
Wonderful...
Darling.
And how was yours?
Good.
Thank you for asking.
I think you might have been right.
About the lamb.
I am so sorry.
It's fine.
I checked it twice
when it was in the oven
and I think it might be hotter
than it says that it is.
You know.
I don't think this is working out.
It's not you.
It's me.
We could've had something special.
Please. Please, don't hurt me.
You know,
I really thought you were the one.
Please.
Don't worry, sooner or later.
I'll find her.
I still don't get it.
Why all that trouble
for this pile of bricks?
This was never about money, Gabe.
Not about money? What else is there?
All kinds of things motivate people.
Lust, ambition, envy.
Okay, what motivated you?
Why do you want this place so bad?
It's simple.
This is where,
I'm gonna kill Don Maroni.
It's time. Are you ready?
Let's go.
Now, as soon as this door opens,
an alarm will go off
and we will not have much time.
- What about the gate?
- Unlocked last night.
Take these.
Get the boat started as soon as
- you get there.
- You're not coming?
I'm coming. I'll be right back.
I need to get Kelly.
He can barely walk. Let's go.
Call me sentimental,
but I cannot leave him here.
And you better not leave me.
You lied to me, Fish.
I warned you what would happen
if you lied to me.
What wonders I'm going to make
of your parts.
See you around, doc.
Leave him there.
We don't have much time. Let's go.
Go.
This way.
They're headed for the boat.
What are you doing, man?
Open up the gate.
I can't. It's locked.
What? Fish said she unlocked it.
- That bitch.
- What?
Fish.
She set us up.
- Kelly, other side.
- Over here, come on.
- Hurry, hurry.
- Come on.
You told them you couldn't fly,
didn't you?
I lied.
The chopper.
Hold on.
Fish.
He abducts young, single,
attractive women
and he keeps them
sometimes for a week,
sometimes for months.
Then he dumps
their bodies around Gotham.
- How many has he killed?
- A dozen. Maybe more.
Every time he makes a kill,
he leaves one of these
at the crime scene.
It's his calling card.
So, who is he?
No one knows.
Thinking is he's educated,
decent-looking, rich,
but that's just a profile.
Some of the guys call him
the Don Juan Killer.
Most call him the Ogre.
So, why haven't I heard
about this guy before?
Why hasn't the public?
- It's the G.C.P.D.'s...
- Hey, fellas.
Dirty little secret.
Only a handful of senior detectives
know anything about this guy.
And they sure ain't leaking it
to the press.
Why not?
Because the Ogre retaliates
against any cop who investigates him.
He kills the people they love.
That's why this lunatic
hasn't been caught yet, Jim
because no one's been stupid enough
to investigate.
Until I came along.
Which makes me wonder,
how did you catch this?
I told you, a fellow officer asked me
to look into it.
Who?
Which one?
Okay.
- Other side.
- That's him.
Give me some of that stuff.
Relax, old man.
We're not gonna rob you.
- What are you doing here?
- We came to talk to you.
- Who's she?
- Never mind.
Who sent you to my house?
Who sent me to...
Just go home. Go home, Bruce.
You'll be in more trouble
than you are already.
Hey! That's my medicine.
Give me that.
My friend just asked you a question.
I said, give me that.
Or you'll what?
- Hey! Don't!
- Answer the question.
Listen, I didn't mean any harm.
I just was to take some documents.
But Alfred walked in...
is he all right?
Is he?
You stabbed him.
What do you care?
I care. He's all right, isn't he?
Who sent you?
Throw them out.
- No!
- Tell me who sent you.
Who sent you?
You shouldn't be doing this, Bruce.
Only Alfie can deal
with these people.
What people?
It's a woman named Mathis,
and a guy called Bunderslaw.
Sid Bunderslaw.
He's the guy I dealt with.
But you've go...
You've got to let
Alfie take care of this.
Not you, Bruce.
It's no business for a child.
This man, Bunderslaw.
What did he want?
Just to know what you knew.
To see how far your investigation
had gone.
But he was scared.
And that's why he sent me.
Now, can I have my bag back, please?
Please?
Give it back to him.
You.
You're a sick man, Mr. Payne.
You need help.
Don't you patronize me.
I may have vices, yeah,
but I'm a professional.
You want me to tell Bunderslaw
that you're onto him?
Because he'll come after you.
And there's nothing that you can do
to stop him.
You're just silly little children.
I'm going to tell on you.
No, you won't.
It wa... it wasn't my idea. I swear.
I was ordered to get you
to take the case.
- Ordered by who?
- Loeb.
It was Commissioner Loeb.
He told me to tell you that...
I looked up to you,
that you inspired me.
I mean, he told me to say that
I wanted to help clean up Gotham
and the G.C.P.D,
and that this case...
this case was part of that.
He knew you couldn't say no.
So you followed orders
like a good soldier.
I didn't have a choice.
I mean, you know what Loeb can do.
All too well.
Jim, listen,
you're still in the clear on this.
In the clear?
He could come after Lee.
Only if he thinks
you're investigating him.
Think about it.
It's not on your docket.
There's been no press
linking you to this case.
All we've done is ask questions,
so you gotta drop it now.
This is no time to be a hero.
If I drop it,
I'm letting a serial killer go free.
The blood of his next victim
is on my hands.
If you don't drop it,
that blood could be Lee's.
Hi, you've reached Lee.
Go ahead and leave a message.
Lee, call me as soon as you can.
It's very important.
You!
- You son of a bitch.
- Excuse me?
You set me up.
- Detective, I don't know what...
- Don't talk.
- Listen. Back off.
- Hey.
Don't you...
I tried to work with you.
But now you crossed a line.
You come after the one I love?
From here on, we're playing my way.
No more games. No more deals.
I'm gonna find the Ogre,
and I'm gonna put him behind bars.
And when I've done that,
I'm coming after you.
I'm coming after you, commissioner.
You're done.