There's a war coming, a terrible war.
There will be chaos!
Rivers of blood in the streets.
I know it! I-I can see it coming!
MOONEY: It's time.
Somebody has to take over.
It might as well be me.
(screaming)
GORDON: My name's James Gordon, a detective.
- My name is Bruce Wayne.
- I promise I will find
the man who did this.
Stop or I'll shoot!
(gunshot)
OSWALD: Mario Pepper was framed
by Fish Mooney and the cops.
Why snitch on your own boss?
You want to push Fish out.
(grunts)
I told you this is important.
I ain't looking for no girl.
I'm looking for a weapon.
The old man has to go.
He figures out we're working
together, we're cooked.
ALLEN: You're under arrest for the murder
of Oswald Chesterfield Cobblepot.
Holy crap.
I... am Oswald Cobblepot.
You son of a bitch!
MOONEY: He's alive?!
Alive?!
No!
Boss, what's wrong?
Gordon didn't kill
Penguin like he was told.
What?
Penguin is still alive
and working for Maroni?
No.
You go find Gordon,
and you bring him to me.
Still breathing.
I want to talk to that son of a bitch.
BARBARA (recorded): Hey,
guys. Leave a message.
Barbara, if you're at home, listen to me.
I need you to get out right now.
- I thought we were friends.
- Harvey!
Shut up! Game's over.
Now I got to kill you and
take your body back to Falcone,
and beg, beg him for mercy!
Listen to me. I screwed up.
But I have a plan to make things right.
Don't kill me. Help me.
You think I'm an idiot?
Walk away!
Walk away.
(groans)
Help me.
We don't have to go out like this.
You better hope you never see me again.
(phone vibrating)
Wow.
What a place, huh?
A beautiful home for a beautiful lady.
Please tell me what you want.
I guess there's no harm in the truth.
See, your boyfriend was supposed to kill
a certain person for somebody.
Only, he didn't.
And now that somebody is real mad.
Cobblepot.
What?
He didn't kill Cobblepot.
- There you go!
- (gasps)
You're hip.
You are hip.
That Jim Gordon is one lucky son of a gun.
What are you, like, a hundred pounds?
110?
(sniffs)
(sighs): Oh.
I bet that's your real hair color, too.
What are you gonna... do to Jim?
You ever been with a criminal?
Some ladies find it a turn-on.
- Jim.
- Hey!
Speak of the devil.
I was just getting to
know your lovely lady.
You're trespassing. Get out.
Whoa. Slow down, hoss.
You're misreading the situation.
I'm the shot caller here.
The situation is you've been
told to bring me in alive,
or I'd be dead already.
But I'm happy to kill
you right here and now.
Don't be such a hard-ass.
Come on, you know the rules.
You play nice, you take your lumps...
nobody else gets hurt.
Tell your friend to drop his
gun or I'll blow his brains out.
- Oh, my God, Jim.
- It's okay. It's under control.
Drop your gun.
Okay.
Have it your way.
But now, after we kill you,
we're gonna kill blondie, too.
Nice and slow.
We gotta go. Right now.
Barbara.
MAN (over P.A.): The
Westbound Interstate Express
departs in five minutes, Bay 12.
Barbara.
- What?
- Listen.
No, no. No.
Just a couple of days and I'll join you.
There are things I need to do.
Fine. Then if you stay, I stay.
Okay? Because I love you, Jim.
- I cannot leave you.
- I love you, too.
That's why you need to leave.
If I know you're safe, there's
nothing they can do to me.
I'll make things right,
and then I'll come join you.
And what if you don't?
Don't come back.
Don't come back to Gotham.
No, Jim.
(door closes)
(officers chattering)
(chatter quiet)
MAN: Gordon's here.
Is he nuts?
What's he doing here?
You believe this guy?
Hey, Alvarez.
You got any of those blank warrants
that Judge Bam Bam signed?
Uh... yeah.
(chicken clucking)
This cannot stand.
Gordon must die, Bullock must die,
Penguin must die today!
And Maroni, too, I suppose?
If need be.
You're overreacting, my
dear. This Penguin's a nobody.
You want to start a war
over the guy that carried your umbrella?
He was on my hip everywhere with me.
He knows things.
Like what?
Too much. He knows too much!
Go to Maroni
and ask him politely to
hand over your little man.
Politely.
If he refuses,
we can talk about stronger measures.
Boss, this is weak response.
I hate to agree with Fish, but
we need to show strength now.
We need to hit back hard. No talk.
Penguin dead, Gordon dead, done.
Relax, Niko. I know what I'm doing.
Where is Gordon?
I thought you were bringing him with you.
No. He wouldn't come without a struggle.
Now, I don't know if he's
playing tough or crazy,
but he's at work like nothing's wrong.
I'll send Victor to fetch him.
No need. My guys can handle him.
I'll send Victor.
That's a nice handsome bird, huh?
I don't know chickens.
(chicken squawking)
(sighs)
Fall back.
The old man is right there.
Screw him. He's done.
Now's the time to strike.
- (clicks tongue) Not yet.
- Not yet, not yet.
If not now, when? Look at him.
Maroni clan are laughing at
us, and he plays with chickens.
MOONEY: That's what has me worried.
The chickens. He's happy, relaxed,
as if he doesn't have a care in the world.
- That girl of yours is doing her job then.
- No.
She says he hasn't even touched her.
She cooks and she cleans for him.
He likes to watch her do chores.
Weird.
- But if that's his thing...
- No.
He's acting as if he
knows something important
that no one else knows.
What the hell are you doing here?
I work here. It's my shift.
Where else should I be?
How about Alaska?
Arrest warrants? For who?
Mayor Aubrey James, Carmine Falcone
and their close associates.
On charges of conspiracy
and perversion of justice
in the Wayne murder case.
- Are you insane?
- No.
Maybe a little.
Feels good.
They're gonna try and kill me anyway.
Might as well make them pay a price for it.
You're gonna arrest the
mayor and Don Falcone. How?
My testimony is attached to the warrants.
That alone is enough to
indict them on a dozen counts.
Sure, if you could execute
the warrants, which you can't.
If the D.A. would
prosecute, which he won't.
There's not a single cop or lawyer
in the city who will help you.
I think there are plenty
of people willing to help me
once they see it's possible to fight back.
You're dreaming. Nobody will help you.
I won't help you.
You don't think I want
change just like you do?
I have a family.
I understand.
Gordon...
get out of town.
This is my home.
It was my father's home.
I'm not leaving.
Hello, everyone.
My name is Victor Zsasz.
I'm sent here personally by
Don Carmine Falcone himself
on a matter of deep concern to him,
so please be respectful.
I'm here
for Jim Gordon.
Only him.
Everybody else, mind your
business and we're cool.
So where's Jim at?
Thank you.
Hey, Jim!
(singsong): Jim.
- Hi, Jim.
- (door closes)
Relax.
I'm supposed to take you in alive.
Don Falcone wants to talk.
Tell Falcone we'll talk.
But not today.
Don't be that way.
"Alive" is a very broad category.
A man with no hands can still be alive.
There are 50 cops in here.
Try something.
Everybody out.
Please?!
Go, boss.
Get out of here.
- Jim...
- Go.
I can handle this.
Well, how now, Jim?
(grunts)
(panting)
Jim?
(whistles)
Why are you hiding from me, Jim?
OFFICER: Hey!
What the...?
(screams)
There!
(tires screeching)
You need a ride?
Go, go, go, go, go!
(groaning)
No.
No, please.
Twenty-eight.
(grunts)
Ah, you're back.
How do you feel?
Terrible.
Where am I? Who are you?
I'm a friend of Montoya and Allen.
I just took two bullets
out of you and sewed you up.
Now I'm checking to see how you're doing.
So... Who are you?
What city are we in and
what day of the week is it?
I'm James Gordon. We're in Gotham.
It's Friday. Why are there rats?
It's a dissection lab at the university.
I gather you're a fugitive from the mob,
Can't go to the hospital, said Crispus.
It's very exciting, I must say.
- How long have I been out?
- Just a couple of hours or so.
You're very lucky. No vital organs
were... Whoa, whoa, lie back down.
Okay? You are hurt.
Just a week or so in bed...
- I have to go.
- James, you have lost a lot of blood.
You have to do as I say and lie back down.
If you don't, you could die.
I have to stand. Can you help me?
Okay, okay.
Crispus?
He said he's leaving already.
I have to go. Now.
Sure.
Some clothes would be good though.
This is about tradition, values.
Snitches get stitches...
that's how it's always been.
You need to hand him over, Sal.
I know.
I should.
But what can I say?
The little guy amuses me.
Don Falcone is going to be very unhappy.
You want to start a war over this punk?
War? Whoa.
He's that important to you, is he?
Oh, no.
He means nothing to us.
Respect is what matters here.
Respect I understand.
Penguin!
Come on out here.
Don't be scared. She won't bite.
You won't bite him, will you?
Hello, Penguin.
Hello, Ms. Mooney.
MARONI: Penguin, Ms. Mooney and her boss,
Mr. Falcone, feel disrespected by you.
Oh, dear.
Well, that certainly has
never been my intention.
MARONI: Well, respect is
very important to them.
Now, I want a sincere apology from you
for making them feel that way.
Oh, gosh, of course.
If I've in any way
caused anyone to feel a lack of respect,
I apologize. Sincerely.
MARONI: There you go.
Can't say fairer than that.
Bloodshed, then.
I'm glad.
Jolly fat men are so tiresome.
And you...
you little scaly-faced bitch.
(inhales sharply)
Oh... what I'm gonna do to you.
"Torture" is far too nice of a word.
I'm sorry you feel that way, Fish...
(grunts)
Only my friends... call me Fish.
(laughing)
(church bell tolling)
Hey, sisters!
How's it hanging?
- Holy...!
- (horn blaring)
(women screaming)
(tires screeching)
Tell your boss Falcone won't let
any of Maroni's trucks over the bridge.
Not till he gives up Penguin.
So, listen, you got to get hurt a little.
You want a beating or a bullet?
Why we got to get hurt?
Because we're sending a
message this is a serious issue.
We'll tell him it's serious. No problem.
Ah, you know what?
(men screaming)
How did they find out
about the gun truck, huh?!
That's $3 mil per week right there!
Son of a bitch!
$4.5 mil per, gross. Cash.
Very aggressive move, isn't it?
An overreaction.
They want to scare you.
Oh, is that right? You
think that they think
that Don Maroni can be scared?
Of course, you're right. No.
But why, then, would
they react so ferociously?
Why do they want me back so badly?
I know why.
Because they know I got
a stone moneymaker here.
A golden goose.
They know it, and they
don't want us to have him.
Right, Penguin?
Honk, honk.
(chuckles)
What?
Honk, honk.
It's what geese say.
(laughs): Oh, right, right.
Honk, honk.
So, fine, he's a goose.
Maybe we can negotiate a price,
- pay them off.
- Yeah.
Yes. Caution is wise.
The Falcone clan still
is number one, after all.
Paying them off is the safe thing to do.
Screw safe.
They want to push me?
They think I'm gonna fold?
I'll push right back, harder.
Hit them where it hurts. Today.
You know best.
If that's how you want to play it,
I think I know just the spot to hit them.
MONTOYA: I owe you an apology.
You were telling the truth,
and I wouldn't believe you.
Maybe my personal feelings towards Barbara
got tangled up in there.
- And that was wrong.
- Forget it.
Anyhow, I-I'm sorry for misjudging you,
and I'm very glad that
we're on the same side now.
Yeah, me, too.
So Barbara's safe though?
You're sure she's safe?
I'm sure.
(Allen groans)
Gordon, is that you?!
It's all right, Alfred.
It's all right. He's a friend.
We couldn't risk a direct approach;
there's people looking for me.
- Ah, right.
- (groans)
Sorry about that, mate.
Can't be too careful.
In a spot of bother, are we, sir?
GORDON: Renee Montoya and Crispus Allen.
Pleased to meet you.
Bruce, I promised I would
find your parents' killer.
I'm not sure I'm going to
be able to keep that promise.
It's a long story, but I'm
kind of in a tight spot.
I've upset some powerful people.
Stop treating me like a child.
Explain.
Bruce, you are a child.
You don't need to know...
You expect to die!
I'd like to know why.
Is it connected to my parents' murder?
Yes, it's all connected.
Somehow.
Bruce...
I will do my best to work this thing out.
But if I don't,
Montoya and Allen here will
take over your parents' case.
I've told them everything I know.
You can trust them, one hundred percent.
One hundred percent.
Bruce, these are good detectives.
If anyone can find the truth, it's them.
Thank you.
Sir, what can we do to help you now?
Nothing.
From here on in, I have to go it alone.
I don't want anyone else caught up in this.
- I have to go.
- You can hardly walk.
I'll be fine.
(men chattering in Russian, laughter)
This way.
Not much further.
It's there.
(chatter continues)
(men screaming)
(gunfire stops)
OSWALD: Told you.
Easy as pie.
There must be a million
dollars' worth here.
Yeah, you told us, all right.
You're clever.
You're very clever.
I sense a sarcastic and
hostile edge to your tone.
Hostile?
You got that right.
You ain't no golden goose,
you're a yellow rat snitch,
and you got Maroni all twisted.
I'm so glad we're finally
clearing the air at last.
That's it.
Act smart, okay?
'Cause all I got to do right now
is put a bullet in your brain right here.
Bang.
See, then I go back and I tell the boss
that one of Niko's men shot you.
Gee, that's too bad.
End of story.
(chuckles)
Yes, that's clever enough.
I never doubted your intelligence.
That's not your problem.
Oh, I got a problem, huh? I got a problem.
No, you got a problem.
What's my problem, schmo?
What drives you?
What's your passion?
When you know what a man loves,
you know what can kill him.
Do you believe this guy?
For you, it's money.
You love money.
More than power and respect.
You're a skinflint, Mr. Carbone.
A cheapskate.
What are you guys playing at? Let me go!
Sorry, Frankie.
- As I say, a cheapskate.
- CARBONE: Hey, come on!
Hey... Consequently,
you don't pay your people enough.
No, you know me. You don't wanna do this.
- It is a sad fact...
- You don't want to do this.
No. No. No, no!
That there is no loyalty among thieves.
(grunts)
(groaning)
The simple offer of a substantial pay raise
is all it took to sway these fine men.
(screaming)
So, you see, that's your problem!
Your greatest passion
becomes your greatest weakness!
(chuckling)
Love, Mr. Carbone.
(chuckles)
Love conquers all.
Shh.
My friend.
My good friend, today is a sad day.
Nikolai was like a son to me,
just as Frankie was a son to you.
We both lost precious family members.
- My condolences to you.
- And mine to you.
I want this violence to stop.
Business is good.
The Arkham Project is a gold mine.
Wayne Enterprises is back in play.
Life is good for all of us.
Why risk all of that and
go to war over trifles?
Your little man there is
obviously very valuable to you.
We'll let you have him.
Unharmed. Our gift to you.
And as a show of
mutual respect, you give
us something in return.
Like such as what?
How about real estate?
One of your warehouses on the river maybe.
That's not gonna work.
I mean, I like this fella,
but we're talking about
a warehouse on the river.
MARONI: Yeah.
Indian Hill.
I'll give you Indian Hill.
I'm not familiar with the name.
It's in Arkham.
It's a toxic waste dump
on top of an Indian burial ground.
It's worthless.
FALCONE: No.
Nothing is worthless.
Even nothing is worth something.
We'll take it.
As a token of our mutual respect, yes?
You got it, my friend.
It's all love.
It's a pleasure seeing you all.
Um, I heard Vic Zsasz tore up the GCPD,
tracking down Gordon.
Did you catch him yet?
We're working on it.
Well, good luck with that.
There's nothing more dangerous
than an honest man, huh?
(knocking)
BULLOCK: Jimbo, it's me. Open up.
Hey.
Don't worry, I'm not gonna kill you.
I should, but I ain't.
Glad to hear it.
Obviously, you figured you'd go
to the last place they'd look,
because it'd be the
first place they'd reject
as being too obvious.
I-I'm sorry, I'm being rude.
This is the Duchess of Devonshire.
Duchess, Jim Gordon, putz.
Marsha. Hi.
Right.
Baby, why don't you explore a little bit.
Find the bedroom, put
on your birthday suit.
(laughs)
And I'll find you in a jiffy, okay? Hmm?
So I've been thinking.
You're still a douche bag.
But you have the moral high ground.
So I'm gonna back your play,
whatever it is.
I figure I'm doomed anyhow.
I might as well join the good guys.
Thank you.
So what is your play?
I mean, you got one,
right? You said you did.
Tomorrow morning, I'm
arresting Falcone and the mayor
for the framing of Mario Pepper.
Conspiracy, POJ, Rico, the works.
Well, that's a... that's a hell of a plan.
You sit down with a panel of chimpanzees
and a bucket of crack
and come up with that one?
I figure whatever else
happens, we'll stir things up.
We might even make the papers.
Oh, yeah, we're gonna
make the papers, all right.
We're gonna be dead in the streets
in time for the evening edition.
Well, at least the people
will know the truth.
And we'll go out doing our jobs,
enforcing the law.
That's the best
inspirational speech you got?
Doing our jobs?
- You don't have to join me.
- No, I'm game.
Like I said, I'm doomed anyhow.
Now, if you'll excuse me for one minute,
just gonna take care of some business.
Duchess!
Marco!
MARSHA: Polo!
Jumping catfish.
Good morning, Mayor James.
Gordon, you scared...
scared the bejeebers out of me.
Almost spilled my coffee.
Sorry.
Sir, you're under arrest.
That's not funny.
Depends where you're sitting.
Might want to take a look at this.
How you doing, guys?
I'm here to have a chat with Mr. Falcone.
Sure thing, Mr. Mayor.
(door opens, closes)
Carmine Falcone, you're under arrest.
BULLOCK: Move.
Lie down right over there. Stay quiet.
What on earth are you thinking?
We're thinking we'll take you both to jail
and charge you with conspiracy
- to pervert the course of justice.
- Try and take me in,
you won't make it to the end of the street.
That's exactly what I said.
This is a lawful arrest. If
you resist, you will be shot.
I see.
We all die together in a blaze of glory.
If that's how it works
out, that's fine with me.
How about you, Harvey?
Fine by me.
- Oh, God.
- FALCONE: I envy you boys.
Having nothing to lose must be liberating.
Must feel pretty good.
Yes, it does.
Suppose you did have something to lose.
What would you do then?
Suppose, for instance,
I had a knife to Barbara
Kean's throat right now.
Would you still be so brave?
You don't.
I'm telling you I do.
You're a liar.
I have many faults, but I'm not a liar.
Victor Zsasz has Barbara.
You know Victor.
You're lying. She's far away.
She came back.
Came right to me to plead for your life.
You have a good woman there.
She loves you very much.
Too much.
Prove it.
Prove you have her.
I could.
But I won't.
I want you to believe me.
It's obvious, Jim. He's lying.
Am I?
If you think so,
go ahead and try to bring me in.
You'll be dead,
so you won't know what happens to Barbara.
But it won't be pretty.
Lying.
On my mother's grave.
Drop your gun,
and Barbara won't be harmed in any way.
Those muffins smell good.
None for you, creep.
She can have one if she wants.
No, thank you.
(ringtone playing)
Got it.
What a shame.
Oh, this is embarrassing; he straight-up
bluffed you into folding.
We could've gone out like
heroes; now we're fish food.
Okay, so it wasn't a bluff.
FALCONE: I'm sorry if she was
mistreated a little. We needed to be
sure she had nothing useful to tell us.
Untie her, Victor.
I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's okay.
What am I gonna do with you?
By rights, you have to die.
Whoa, hello. Uh, I'm late for work.
Quite an adventure. I'll be on my way.
FALCONE: Such a waste though.
Gotham needs men like you, both of you.
Strong men with principles.
I wish I could make you see
I'm not the enemy.
The system is not the enemy.
The enemy is anarchy.
But I told you that before, didn't I, Jim?
Yes, you did.
You didn't listen though.
Do we get a last meal or a
smoke or anything, or just talk?
FALCONE: But today, you believed me.
You trusted my word.
That's a good first step.
Perhaps there's still hope for you.
Yes.
Go. Get out of here
before I change my mind.
- Wait a minute.
- Quiet.
It's been a pleasure, Barbara.
I do admire a brave woman.
What's the catch?
Jim, he said we could
go. Let's not haggle here.
What's the catch, Mr. Falcone?
I want you to think about what I said.
I want you to understand the truth.
That's all I ask.
The catch is...
someday soon, you'll see I'm right.
Barbara...
I'm sorry.
I was just trying to help, and...
I don't know what...
I love you so much.
(thunder rumbling)
Mmm.
Excellent.
Delicious!
Yes.
I followed the recipe.
You're right, Mr. F., cooking is easy.
I'm sorry you had to see all that earlier.
Not pleasant.
I understand. Business is business.
Mm-hmm.
Yes, it is.
I'll go see to the chickens.
(chickens clucking)
(Falcone clucking)
Any eggs, my dears?
Don Falcone.
My friend.
Good to see you.
I was just thinking
about the night we met.
Cut them down.
Where's the snitch?
I want to speak to him.
Cobblepot, is it?
Condemned men are honest men, I find.
What can you tell me before you go?
Don Falcone.
It is a great honor, sir.
Indeed, I can tell a secret
of great value to you...
if you grant me one last request.
Which is what?
(sniffles)
Give the job of killing me to James Gordon.
Why him?
He's the only man under your sway
who has a conscience.
The only one who might be persuaded
to spare my life.
Why would I agree to that?
I want you dead. You're a snitch.
If you agree and Gordon spares me,
then I will become your snitch.
For life.
I will come back to Gotham
under a different name,
and I will work my way
into the Maroni family,
and I will snitch for you.
I am excellent at this sort of work.
I have a gift for it.
I really do, sir.
Deal.
Gordon will get the job of killing you.
Thank you, sir.
What is the valuable secret?
Oh, yes.
Fish Mooney and Nikolai the Russian
only pretend to hate each other.
They're lovers.
And Fish is pushing Nikolai
to take your place.
Is that so?
Yes, sir.
But only so Fish can take over from him.
That is a good secret.
It's almost uncanny.
Everything played out
exactly as you said it would.
We got rid of Nikolai painlessly,
and Maroni thinks you're a wizard.
You really do have a gift.
But I think we're making a
mistake letting Gordon live.
He's trouble.
Thank you so much for sparing him.
I appreciate the favor.
- (thunder rumbling softly)
- Don't worry.
He'll see the light.
One way or another, I guarantee it.
Sync & corrections by madhatters
www.addic7ed.com