Last season on Gotham...
It's in here.
It's in this room.
My father's secret,
it's in this room.
Going after Loeb is suicide,
plain and simple.
As usual,
wrong place, wrong time.
You're a disgrace, Loeb.
What's black and white
and red all over?
Stop talking like that.
Why did you kill
your mother, Jerome?
(cackling)
Barbara, Jason Lennon
killed your parents.
You didn't kill them.
Yes, I did.
Surprise, Fish!
(Oswald yelling)
(Fish screaming)
(thunder rumbles)
I'm the king of Gotham!
What is it,
do you think?
(rumbling)
(thunder crashes, rumbles)
Bloody hell.
No, wait, wait, wait!
(thunder rumbles in distance)
(harsh beeping)
(bangs door)
There must be a million possible
combinations, Master Bruce.
(harsh beeping)
(frustrated sigh)
(thunder rumbles
in distance)
(sirens wail in distance)
("Perfect Day" by Lou Reed
playing)
♪ Just a perfect day ♪
♪ Drink sangria in the park ♪
♪ And then later,
when it gets dark ♪
(snores)
♪ We go home ♪
♪ Just a perfect day ♪
♪ Feed animals in the zoo ♪
♪ Then later a movie, too ♪
♪ And then home ♪
♪ Oh, it's such a perfect day ♪
♪ I'm glad I spent it with you ♪
♪ Oh, such a perfect day ♪
♪ You just keep me hanging on ♪
♪ You just keep me hanging on. ♪
(horns honking in distance)
Drink it all.
Thank you, Master.
(groans)
(hissing inhale)
(chuckles)
Now go.
(continues chuckling)
Come on through.
Let's go, let's go.
♪ ♪
(police whistle blowing)
I am Zaardon...
MAN:
Shut up!
...the Soul Reaper!
ZAARDON: Foolish slaves!
You cannot escape me!
Sir, drop the guns!
(chuckles)
(hearty laugh)
You! You!
WOMAN: Hey!
(grunts)
Come on...!
Your primitive
weapons
cannot hurt me!
(woman sobbing)
Prepare to die, insect.
(Zaardon roars)
Hey...
listen, I don't want
to shoot you, man, all right?
Too much paperwork.
So why don't you just...
put the sword down.
(fierce yell)
(sword clanging)
(yelling)
(Zaardon yells, grunts)
Stay down. Relax.
(grunting)
(handcuffs clicking)
OFFICER:
Yo, Gordon.
What's up? Busy shift?
You're late.
Geez, relax, will ya?
What's the matter
with you, man?
(clattering nearby)
Hey!
Bad idea.
How can this be?
Zaardon drank dragon's blood
from the master's chalice.
"Zar-don"-- that
spelled how it sounds?
Two A's.
Close enough.
You dare send me
to prison?
Oh, no-- you're
a cinch for Arkham.
Hear me, Gor-Don.
You might have won this battle,
but the war has just begun.
(chuckling): The master
will unleash hell upon you.
Dark days are coming.
Thanks for the heads-up.
(knob squeaks,
water runs, pipes creak)
Ed.
You okay?
Never better.
MAN (over P.A.):
Officer Gordon 23611,
report to the captain's office
immediately.
I'm up.
See ya.
(door closes)
He's gone. Relax.
(soft gasp)
Holy moly, look at you!
Everyone's gonna think
you're going nuts.
I get nervous
when you talk to me
with other people around
like that.
Stop doing that.
What?
That!
Copying me.
Dude... it's a mirror,
that's how they work.
You know what
I think we need?
I think that
we need...
a little more fun.
(chuckles)
Some romance.
Stop.
I know where this is going.
I told you, leave...
Miss Kringle alone.
Imagine her in our arms.
Those big eyes
looking up at us,
and soft, trembling flesh.
Be quiet!
(chuckling)
It's a simple question,
Officer Gordon--
did you or did you not put your
hands on Officer Franks here?
Yes. I did.
Mm-hmm.
(door opens, closes)
LOEB:
From the first day
on the job, you've been
an insubordinate troublemaker.
I hoped demotion to uniform duty
would suffice to make you quit.
It worked for your
partner, Bullock.
However,
you've now confessed
to violation of section 12.
Immediate dismissal
is mandatory.
Commissioner, this is not just.
Officer Frank
sustained no harm,
and Officer Gordon showed
admirable restraint
in defusing
a dangerous
hostage situation.
Thank you so much
for your input, Captain.
The facts speak for themselves.
The facts say he
deserves commendation,
not dismissal.
You're letting
gutter politics...
(whispers):
That's enough, young lady.
Take Officer...
Mister Gordon's
badge and gun.
That's an order.
(quiet sigh)
All good.
Let it go.
Thanks, though.
It's been an honor
working for you.
This is all
for the best, you know.
Some men are
just not meant
to be cops.
(clasps hand)
I told you I'd break you.
I will.
(snoring quietly)
(snores)
(belching)
(men groaning
in disgust, coughing)
What did you say to Loeb?
Did you get mad?
Well, I disagreed
with his decision.
Come on.
You know I need the details.
I said I'd break him.
Words to that effect.
Hey, you went out
with a bang.
(heavy sigh)
Maybe it's for the best.
That's what Loeb said.
I should have walked away.
I just hate to quit.
You didn't quit.
You were fired.
What can you do?
Oh, there's things I can do.
I thought you said you didn't
have any legal moves left.
I don't.
You want to be
a cop so bad,
you're willing
to break the law?
I'm willing
to bend it a little, yeah.
You're happy I got fired, huh?
You got me.
But only because
I know that you'll
never quit.
And I love that about you.
But they have you
directing traffic, Jim.
Why keep beating your
head against a wall.
I'm a cop, Lee.
I'm a cop.
(crows cawing,
dogs barking in distance)
(door rattles, clanks shut)
(whistling a tune)
Hi, gorgeous.
I'm Jerome.
Keep moving, ginger.
Just being polite.
So, what-cha in for?
Killing my parents.
Oh. Me, too.
Well... Mom, anyhow.
Liberating, right?
Oh... what a rush!
Yeah, all righty, then.
You see the big handsome fella
staring at you like
you're fried chicken?
Richard Sionis.
He's a millionaire.
Mm, got his own airplane.
Got a boat with
a hot tub on it.
And he killed 25 people...
(snorting laugh)
...just for fun.
So what?
So... he likes you.
He wants to be
your friend.
Hmm. Let me think. No.
A girl needs
a good friend in here.
See, the guards,
they don't care.
They figure bad things
happen to bad people.
And they happen
all the time.
All the time.
Hey, you.
Hello?
(whistles) Baldy!
Here, here. Hello, yes.
Hi. Come here.
Hi.
My name is Barbara.
Would you be my friend?
Yes.
Hey, if someone here
tries to hurt me...
...would you protect me?
Yes.
Thank you so much.
(both chuckle)
Cutie. (chuckles)
Now I have a friend.
You're bad.
Yeah, so why don't you go
make me a sandwich.
Your friend is a gorilla.
My friend runs
the joint.
And he can get you things
that other people can't get you.
Things like what?
Anything you need.
I need a telephone.
Ogden Barker, in for 70 grand,
plus two months vig,
250 and change.
Says he owes Falcone.
Falcone's gone,
so his debt's forfeit.
Well, we can't have him
saying that.
What if everybody started
saying that?
There'd be anarchy.
What is it?
(whispering)
Oh.
Splendid.
Jim!
Come on in!
My dear old friend.
We need to talk.
Oh. Leave us.
GORDON:
Hey, Selina.
Moving on up, huh?
Tryin'.
OSWALD:
Isn't she darling?
It's like having a cat
around the house.
But no horrid
dead mice.
I need a favor.
I figure you owe me one.
(scoffs)
I do?
I'm always happy to help you,
Jim, but I-I, I don't recall...
The hospital.
I saved you from Maroni's men.
But I was only there
because you arrested me.
For attempted murder.
Remind me again
why I let you go.
Enlightened friendship.
I'd call us even,
but... (chuckles)
let's not quibble.
I'm so happy
you came to me for help, Jim.
The answer is yes.
Your wish is granted.
You don't know what it is yet.
You want Loeb fired,
and your old job back, no?
Yes.
For a good friend like you,
it can be done.
If you're sure
that's what you want.
I'm sure.
May I ask why?
Police work in Gotham
is such a thankless job.
Good pension.
What does Lee think?
Who?
Are you gonna help me or not?
Relax.
I already said I would help.
(chuckles)
He is so brusque,
isn't he?
(chuckles)
No, thank you.
Oh... while I think on it,
perhaps there's a small favor
you could do for me in return.
I know how you hate
to owe favors.
I am having a small business
dispute with a friend of mine.
Ogden Barker.
You have
a persuasive personality.
Perhaps you could talk to him.
You want me
to collect a debt for you?
I want you to prove to me that
our friendship is a real one,
based on trust and equity.
That's fair.
No. Sorry.
Can't help you.
Congratulations on
all your success.
Be good, Selina.
Always.
Don't say no now, Jim.
Sleep on it.
(door opens)
(door shuts)
(siren wailing in distance)
♪ The Cadillac... ♪
Screw Penguin,
screw the GCPD,
and screw this city.
Amen. You're doing the
right thing, brother.
Walk away, Jim,
just walk away.
You'd do
the same thing, right?
Me? I'd serve a sandwich
to Beelzebub,
but that's just me.
You are a moralist.
You could never
work for Penguin.
The shame
would eat away at your guts.
Yeah...
Yeah.
Ooh, slow down, slurpy.
Mm...
You're not joining me?
I've been sober 32 days.
32 days, huh?
Eh, it's no biggie.
Once I quit the job,
quitting drinking was easy.
It's the job, Jim.
Makes us angry.
Makes us hard.
Yeah, it does.
It's hard to walk away,
but it can be done.
I just couldn't
carry that badge anymore.
Look at me now.
Right? I'm sober...
I have a woman who
does not dislike me,
I live in a house,
I sleep at night.
I've never been happier
in my life.
Here's to civilian life.
♪ He never had no time for reds,
for drink or dice or whores ♪
♪ And he never threw
a fight... ♪
(grunts)
I'm proud of you, brother.
Got to go.
ALFRED: I really am
most frightfully sorry
it took so long
to answer the door, sir.
Strange.
Normally a buzzer sounds when
a car comes through the gates.
GORDON:
I walked.
You two are dirty.
What have you been doing?
I imagine
you have something
important to say.
Yes.
I've been fired from the GCPD.
I won't be able
to keep the promise I made you.
I wanted to apologize.
Your apology's accepted,
of course, but...
you didn't need
to walk here.
A phone call
would've been fine.
I needed the air.
No hope
for reinstatement then, sir?
No.
Well, there is a way, but...
it's too ugly.
I would have to collect a debt
for Penguin.
To prove
our friendship.
Ah.
And you can't do
that, because...
he's a bad man.
And the task would be demeaning.
Well, yes.
You were going
to find my parents' killers.
You were going to
fight for justice.
You were going
to clean up the GCPD.
Change Gotham.
I had hoped to do that.
If you remained
at the GCPD,
you might still be able to do
all those good things,
but first...
you must do something ugly.
And your personal honor
forbids that.
Yes.
Are you not sacrificing
the greater good
for the sake of your dignity
and self-esteem?
For vanity?
Steady on, now,
Master Bruce.
Manners.
He walked all the way here
to discuss the issue, Alfred.
I'm simply asking
a question.
Surely, sometimes,
the right way
is also the ugly way.
Sometimes a man can't take
the right way.
He's dealing with
all kinds of business you can't
possibly understand yet,
because you're still a child.
Yes, Alfred,
there is still a great deal
I don't understand yet.
Please forgive me
if I've offended you, Jim.
No, no.
That's okay.
I'll show you out, sir.
(remote beeps)
(rumbling, clanking)
(harsh beeping)
(keypad beeping)
(harsh beeping repeats)
(Bruce grunting)
(panting)
Screw it.
(gate clanks, rattles,
screeches open)
(indistinct chatter)
(gate screeches,
clanks shut)
Ooh!
(lock buzzes)
Jerome says
you can get me a telephone.
I try and help my friends.
What do your friends do for you?
Well, that depends...
on how much...
you want...
a telephone.
("Slow Dive" by Siouxsie
& the Banshees playing)
(indistinct chatter, laughter)
♪ Get your head to the ground ♪
♪ Shake it all around,
a dirty sound... ♪
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold it right there.
Ogden Barker.
Penguin asked me to talk to you.
Damn, boy.
(chuckling):
You had me worried there
for a minute.
I know you. You're Jim Gordon.
Cop. Supposed to be
a cold stone hard-ass.
But you're
Penguin's bitch, huh?
Who the dickens can
you trust anymore?
He wants his money.
How many times
I got to tell you people? No.
To Don Falcone,
I'll pay.
To that fruitcake leprechaun?
Nish.
Not a penny.
Falcone's retired.
Times change.
Penguin's boss now.
Like hell.
The freak won't last the year.
Don't underestimate him.
Advice now.
I'm trying to be nice here.
Let's work this out.
Yeah?
Let's not.
Walk away.
Walk away...
before I kick your ass,
you crooked punk bitch.
How much money you got there?
Looks like a lot.
What is your problem?
I don't have a problem.
Give me the money you owe.
How about I put a hole
in your face?
I'm gonna count
to three.
You're crazy.
One...
(grunting)
Put the money
in the bag.
Do it!
(groans)
Oh-ho-ho, get him, man.
(sirens wailing in distance)
(panting)
Stop! Thief!
Out of the way.
Hey, cop...
(grunting)
(siren wailing in distance)
Fertilizer? What is your game?
I would've thought
that's obvious
to a man of your perception.
(sighs)
It occurred to me
to follow my own advice.
Sometimes the ugly way
is also the right way.
I mean, a bomb,
inside the house?
I mean, you're having a laugh,
ain't ya? A bomb?
I was going to tell you.
I wanted to present it
as a fait accompli.
Don't start
talking French to me.
You don't know
the first thing
about bomb-making anyway,
do you?
I read a book, Alfred--
it seems simple enough.
A book.
I mean, you're gonna
blow your bloody head off
before you put a dent
in that thing.
You know, maybe that door's
trying to tell us something.
Maybe you're not ready to
find out what's behind it.
Maybe we should wait
until you're older.
I mean, who knows
what your dear old dad
was up to down there, anyway.
Like what?
Like things I wouldn't want...
to describe to a child,
which is exactly
what you are.
I'm building a bomb
to blow down that door.
You may assist me...
or not,
as you wish.
But i-if not,
some tea would be nice.
Right, well,
you're gonna need ten more...
sacks of that gear,
for starters; three more
dairy cans, too;
and extra timber; a...
heavy tarpaulin.
And I'll put the kettle on.
(siren wailing in distance)
Excellent.
I'm so sorry
things got messy.
What a foolish fellow.
Never mind.
I will make sure that there's
no follow-up
from your colleagues.
Don't worry about a thing.
You knew.
You knew Ogden would go off.
What a devious mind you have.
I had no idea.
We have a deal.
We do.
You okay, Jim?
(sighing):
Oh, yeah. Daydreaming.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
(phone ringing)
Hello.
BARBARA:
Hello? Jim?
Hello? Are you still there?
I'm here.
Hi.
How are you?
How did you get to a phone?
Who cares?
We're talking at last--
that's the important thing.
What do you want?
(whispers): Jim, there's been
a terrible mistake.
I...
never told Lee
that I killed my mom and dad.
And I never attacked her.
She attacked me, Jim.
(trembling breath)
She's completely insane!
That's enough.
Don't call again.
Who was that?
Sales call.
They can drive you crazy, huh?
Sales call?
(phone ringing)
(sighs)
(ringing continues)
Don't.
Wh-What?
Don't answer it.
Jim, you're scaring me.
It's Barbara.
LEE (recorded):
Go ahead and leave a message.
BARBARA:
Hey, girlfriend.
(chuckles):
Guess who.
Sorry I missed you.
Bummer, eh?
I just wanted to say
that I hope
you die screaming, bitch.
(chuckles)
(mockingly sweet):
Bye.
(hangs up, tone beeps)
(answering machine clicks off)
Nice.
All right, look...
she's safely locked up
at Arkham.
She can't hurt you.
I know, I know.
She's just
a sick person spreading sadness.
Screw her.
Let's be happy.
Let's go away someplace.
We can't let a crazy woman
drive us out.
Why not?
Pride? Who cares?
We could go away
and never come back.
What's keeping us here?
I can't leave.
Why not?
Jim...
I did a bad thing.
(siren wails in distance)
(door unlatches, creaks open)
(door closes)
(clattering in distance)
(thunder rumbles, crashes)
Hi.
Do you have
any peanut butter?
(scoffs)
What?!
Peanut butter.
Smooth, for preference.
Guards, help!
Help!
Oh, hi, boss.
How about a bottle of beer?
(laughs)
(thunder crashes, rumbles)
Let me share
a dilemma with you.
May I?
I need you to do
something for me
that I know
you won't want to do.
What is it?
With most people,
there's no problem.
I find their weak spots
and use violence
or blackmail to
persuade them.
But you...
...you are a man
of monkish virtue.
You have no vices
to expose.
So threats of personal
violence will only
harden your resolve, huh?
No, that...
Come, sir, don't be modest.
You... are a rare animal.
But... that does lead us
to this sad pickle.
Since I can't persuade you
to do as I ask,
the only rational option
is to kill you
and negotiate with whomever
replaces you as commissioner.
Now, chief?
One moment, Victor.
The commissioner
deserves time
to process all this...
say a prayer or what have you.
What do you want me to do?
It's not worth talking about.
You wouldn't do it.
Tell me.
I need my friend Jim Gordon
reinstated as a detective.
(scoffs)
(giggling):
See? You hate that idea.
No, I'll... I'll do it.
Mm-mm, I can tell
that you're not sincere.
Even if
you do as I ask,
someday, down the line,
you'll change your mind,
and you'll turn on him again.
Want me to kill him now?
No, make him
a nice cheese toastie.
Yes, kill him now, please.
Just wanted to be clear.
No, wait!
Let's talk about this.
Sorry.
Least worst option.
Unless, of course... uh...
No, you would never agree.
To what? Agree to what?!
♪ So long, farewell ♪
♪ Auf Wiedersehen, good-bye ♪
♪ Good-bye ♪
♪ Good-bye... ♪
♪ Good-bye. ♪
COMPERE:
Lovely, lovely, bravo.
Mayor James regrets
he's unable to attend today,
but he's sent a dear friend
in his stead.
Please welcome
distinguished businessman,
visionary scientist,
acclaimed philanthropist
and new chairman of development
at the Gotham Chamber
of Commerce, Mr. Theo Galavan.
(audience applauds)
Thank you so much. Uh...
What an honor it is
to be here today,
to help bid farewell
to a great man
and a faithful servant
of this city.
What can I say
about Gillian Loeb?
(sighs)
Someone tell me a funny story.
I have a good one.
So when I was in college,
I played
for the varsity polo team
and I had a...
a string of ponies.
Greetings!
I am Zaardon,
the Soul Reaper.
So I had these ponies...
I'm an adopted son
of this city.
I haven't lived in Gotham
very long,
but I already love her
like a native.
It just...
it just kind of
grabs hold of you,
doesn't it?
There's magic here.
Magic.
And that is down
to everyday heroes
like Gillian Loeb.
Mr. Commissioner,
thank you
for your service.
Thank you very much, everybody.
My best wishes to...
...Commissioner Essen.
...and the maître d' says,
"You can't bring them in here."
Hear me, slaves.
My patience is
wearing thin.
Surrender your souls
to my mercy,
or I swear
by the master,
I shall feast
on your pain.
I shall gorge
on your torment.
I shall crush you like a bug.
(laughs, coughs)
(gagging)
(alarm ringing)
GUARD:
Backup to area five!
Area five!
(alarm continues ringing,
klaxon whooping)
ESSEN:
Welcome back, Jim.
I don't know how
you pulled this off,
but I'm glad you did.
He's a resourceful man.
Congratulations,
to both of you.
Thank you.
And it is a new day, Jim.
We're going to do
great things.
Yes, we are.
(whispers)
It is a new day.
Things are gonna be all right.
I promise.
I hope it was worth it.
I hope so, too.
Jim...
What's wrong?
There's been an incident.
At Arkham Asylum.
Six inmates
have escaped.
Barbara Kean was one of them.
Oh, my God.
What the hell
is this place?
Ain't Arkham, anyhow.
Things are looking up.
Welcome, everyone.
My name is Theo Galavan.
This is my sister Tabitha.
(all clamoring)
Oh, my God,
look at that.
Yeah, I got to get
my hands on that.
(clamoring quiets)
I understand.
You're feeling
confused, scared...
a little groggy...
but please, relax.
Today is the first day
of a wonderful future
for all of you.
If you want it.
Who are you?
Well, now, the question is
who are you?
The world
sees criminal lunatics.
I see brilliance.
I see charisma.
And power.
I see power.
JEROME:
Yes.
Exactly, my man.
Oh, that is so spooky.
That is me to a T.
These other bozos,
oh, I don't know, but...
you're singing my song.
Quiet,
Jerome.
Keep talking.
Imagine a group
of brilliant outlaws
like yourselves,
each selected
for their unique ability,
all working together
as a team.
Imagine the synergy.
Imagine the impact.
Gotham would tremble before you.
BARBARA:
Well, that sounds
fabulous, but I am not
a brilliant outlaw.
I just have...
mm... issues.
You have ferocity
and beauty and desire
and that's enough.
Come with me, Barbara.
Whatever you want
in the world,
it's yours.
Theo?
That's your name,
right-- Theo?
You're getting way ahead
of yourself, here.
First of all,
keep your hands off her.
Second,
this whole "magic team"?
I gotta pass.
I don't take orders.
Good luck on
everything, though.
It's an intriguing concept.
This is very disappointing.
Oh.
Fair play.
You want a reward
for busting us
out of Arkham.
I am grateful.
How's a million bucks sound?
Pretty good, huh?
I can get it
for you today,
as soon as I hit the street.
Money's not the concern.
Oh...
I had such high hopes for you.
I didn't anticipate
sexual jealousy.
That always poisons the well.
You have to go.
Tabitha
will see you out.
Miss Kean is coming with me.
Oh, she doesn't want
to go where you're going.
(grunts, gags)
(blade slicing)
(laughs)
(gasping)
Anyone else want to leave?
Now...
you're absolutely sure
about this, Master Bruce?
I strongly advise...
Alfred.
I need to know.
Let's do this.
Right, sir.
Yes, we're in!
Yes, yes!
(laughs)
(coughs)
(switch clicks)
"Dear Bruce,
"these last weeks
I begin to feel very mortal,
"which prompts this note to you.
"Perhaps I'm being
paranoid.
"I hope so.
"In any case, if you're
reading this, then I'm dead,
"and you figured out that
the entry code is... BRUCE.
"I'm sorry
"I had to hide this part
of my life from you,
"because this place
only exists because of you.
"Becoming a father made me want
to be a better man,
"and I started asking
hard questions
"about the
family business.
"So here we are.
"As I write this, you're 12
(voice breaking):
"and a fine, good-hearted boy.
"So I'm sure you'll be
a fine, good-hearted man.
"But that's all I know.
"I don't know what happened
to me or your mother,
"or how life has
turned out for you.
"I don't even know
how old you are.
"So I'll resist giving you
much fatherly advice.
"Only this:
"You can't have both happiness
"and the truth.
"You have to choose.
(clicking)
"I beg of you,
"my son,
please choose happiness.
"Unless...
"Unless you feel a calling.
A true calling."
♪ ♪