Previously on
"Gotham"...
The infected are being
killed all over the city.
I'm the one you seek.
I am Ra's al Ghul.
This man is your past.
Now embrace your future.
Use the waters, Bruce.
You were the one time
I let love weaken me.
I want you around as
a constant reminder to never
make that mistake again.
I heard about Alfred.
Is he gonna be okay?
You don't give a damn
about Alfred,
and you sure as hell
don't care about me.
I know you
better than that.
I thought you did.
Jonathan Crane's father
made a toxin
from the adrenal glands
of his victims
while they experienced terror.
What do you want?
I'm tired of just surviving.
I want more.
I'm sorry, Alfred.
I've been trying to find
who I am for so long.
Who am I supposed to be?
Money! Now!
You need to find
your true north.
And let that guide you.
♪♪
Money! Now!
Hurry up, huh?
Give me the ring.
You have one chance.
Walk away.
Who's this?
License.
I got a license.
♪♪
*GOTHAM*
Season 04 Episode 01
Title: "A Dark Knight: Pax Penguina"
♪♪ Never gonna give you up
♪♪ Never gonna let you down
♪♪ Never gonna run around
♪♪ And desert you
♪♪ Never gonna make you cry
♪♪ Never gonna say good-bye
♪♪ Never gonna tell a lie
♪♪ And hurt you
♪♪ We've known each other... ♪♪
Nobody move.
Jewelry, watches, wallets.
You know the drill.
Let's go.
We want it all.
- All your money.
- Thank you.
Come on. Ah, nice.
Ah.
Jackpot!
Let me see that.
Ah.
Cheapskate, huh?
Come on.
Excuse me.
Hi.
That's Victor Zsasz.
I know who it is.
What do you want?
Oh, I was just passing by.
Heard the ruckus.
You know you can't commit
a crime in Gotham now
without a license
from Penguin, right?
Is that right?
Well, we just started it,
so word's still getting out.
We ain't kicking half our take
to that little creep.
Well... that's a problem.
Maybe you ain't noticed,
but there's, uh,
four of us,
and only one of you.
My finger!
No license.
No crime.
Now, drop the loot
and blow.
You tell Penguin
he hasn't heard
the last of this.
And stay out!
I can't thank you enough.
Don't bother.
Because you see those guys?
They do have a license.
Mazel tov.
Seriously?
Best wedding ever.
You know, we appreciate
all you've done.
Do you?
Three months ago, following
the Tetch incident,
this city was in flames.
I came to you and offered
to cut crime in half,
and I delivered.
Violent crime is down 57%.
But now
you want to, uh,
literally, unionize crime.
I mean,
but we can't possibly...
Quiet!
I remember when I sat there,
in the mayor's chair.
I do not envy you.
Nor you.
Commissioner of police in
a city notorious for crime.
That's why I want to help.
But, uh, we are fully aware
of all you've done.
Are you?
What do you think
really happened
to those hordes of criminals
who once prowled our streets?
I'll tell you.
- I hunted them down...
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
I made Gotham safe.
Me.
But this is Gotham City;
there will always be crime.
What I am offering is crime
in the hands of professionals.
And held to
agreed-upon terms.
From which you'll profit.
God bless America.
You have a choice:
an era of calm
and prosperity...
or a return
to the good old days.
And they will return.
With a vengeance.
We deny everything to the press.
Hmm.
What you need to worry about
is the GCPD.
When one of your officers finds
someone committing a crime,
if that person has a license,
they walk away.
Three percent each.
Uh, from the take.
Two
to split between you.
- Two and a half.
- One!
- You...
- Yes. Fine. Done.
Excellent.
Well, if you'll
excuse me,
I have to go prepare for the
grand opening of my new club,
the Iceberg Lounge.
Good luck.
Smile, gentlemen.
It's a new day.
Hey, Frank.
Morning, Jim.
I'll get you coffee in a second.
Sure.
Morning.
Everything okay, Frank?
Everything's
fine, copper.
I got a license.
Penguin approved.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
I'll take that coffee to go.
Man, what the hell
are you doing?
- Look, I-I got a license!
- Yeah.
And unless you shut up,
you're also gonna
get a fat lip.
We got a problem?
Penguin guarantees
these numbers?
Mr. Cobblepot
has negotiated them
with the mayor
and commissioner.
These are damn
good numbers.
But I already heard
from the commissioner.
We have to play ball. What the
hell are you doing here?
Compliance with
the licenses is key.
Mr. Cobblepot worries
about Detective Gordon.
He has a history.
My men will honor the licenses.
You let me worry about Gordon.
Now, get the hell
out of my office.
Hmm.
Who was that?
A, uh, dung beetle.
What's up?
I pulled this off of some guy
robbing my corner bar.
You're a homicide detective.
Isn't, uh, a stickup
a little JV?
I'm a cop. I see
a crime, I stop it.
This is the second one of
these I've come across,
- and I'm not the only one.
- Yeah.
Harvey.
Harvey, we cannot
let this slide.
Word's come down
from the commissioner,
you find someone with
one of those, they walk.
And before you
get on your high horse,
three months ago,
this city was in a tailspin.
We survived because
Penguin took control
of the underworld.
I am not giving the city
over to Penguin.
I don't care
what the commissioner says.
What about
your fellow cops, huh?
The past month,
how many have been shot? None.
I know the stats.
Jim, we will bust Penguin
one day, I promise you.
But this city has to get
back on her feet.
Please?
Harvey, I get that.
But every day the citizens
of Gotham look to Penguin
and not the GCPD
to keep them safe,
the harder it's gonna be
to win them back.
You want people to trust cops,
there are better ways
of doing it
than spitting in Penguin's eyes.
You see one of these,
you walk.
Bloody Penguin.
There must be some way we
can turn this against him.
Oh, just-just stop.
Stop right there.
How does this fit in
to what we're doing?
What was the initial reason
that you popped on that mask
and you went out there?
We agreed that
I have to be ready
for when Ra's al Ghul returns.
You yourself said
there's no substitute
for real-world encounters.
But my point is
if that is our mission,
we must hold to it.
My finger was on the button
that released the virus.
Oh, I see.
I know I didn't press it,
but I feel responsible
for what happened.
And more than that, I can make
a difference in Gotham, Alfred.
I know I can.
And that is what we call
"mission creep," Master Bruce.
You're trying to achieve
not one but two objectives.
So, go on, then.
Which one is
your priority?
It's messy, sir.
It's dangerous.
I hear you, Alfred.
But I can prepare myself
for Ra's
and make Gotham safer.
You have to trust me.
All inmates,
last call... in five minutes,
make your way to the door
and the nearest...
This way.
Hey, Warden Reed.
Warden Reed's
the boss here.
Where is he?
This way.
Back when I was
an orderly in here,
he'd always talk about his dad
and this formula he'd made.
Some sort of
scare juice.
Make you see your
greatest fear.
We get ahold of that,
we don't got to worry
about Zsasz or Penguin,
or nobody.
What's wrong
with him, anyway?
The toxin his father
injected him with
overloaded Jonathan's
fear response.
His mind created
a sort of boogieman figure.
Now it haunts him.
I find it very useful for...
controlling him.
Jonathan, you're going
with these men.
What? What? Wait.
Where are you taking me?
We just want to give
someone a little scare.
Excellent.
♪♪
Yeah.
That's all, that's
all my dad's stuff.
Look, I can't be here
after dark, please.
I real... I cannot
be here after...!
You were your daddy's
little assistant, weren't you?
You helped with
the experiments.
Some, but I don't
know everything!
Now, you're gonna take
your daddy's notebooks
and make as much of
that fear juice as I say.
And so you don't
get lonely,
the boys here
brought you a friend.
No.
No!
No, don't! Please, stop!
No, you don't understand!
Good morning,
ladies and gentlemen.
May I have your
attention, please!
All the money, now!
Give it to me! All of it!
Hey.
You have a license?
Look at me.
Fiery demons. Demons.
Fiery demons.
- Demons.
- Demons. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, we'll catch them.
Get him out of here.
- Go, go, go, go.
- Fiery demons.
Hey.
Did Penguin issue
a license for this?
Why you asking me?
Best of my
knowledge, no.
Then why do something so public?
Unless you're trying
to send Penguin a message.
I hope the message was "Please
send Victor Zsasz down here
to kill me," because that's
exactly what's gonna happen.
- Not if I find them first.
- Hey!
You asked me to stop busting
crooks with licenses.
This gang didn't
have a license.
And you're gonna
find them before Zsasz
just to prove
that GCPD still matters?
That's not thumbing
your nose at Penguin?
Fire me.
Hey, don't tempt me.
You got a lead?
The victims,
the way they're acting,
their terror reminds me
of Crane's formula.
You think someone's using
the fear juice?
It ain't him.
He's dead, remember?
Not that that matters much
in this town anymore.
He's dead. His son isn't.
Jonathan Crane's condition
is fragile.
I'm afraid he can't see anyone.
Certainly not the two men
who killed his father.
Yeah, so, uh, how many loonies
you got in this joint?
436 total.
We mustn't
call them "loonies."
Course not.
How about staff
that had access to Crane?
Any of them
not show up for work?
All present and accounted for.
You don't want to check?
- I don't need to.
- See, that's impressive.
'Cause I run a precinct,
and if half my cops
didn't show up,
I'd be none the wiser.
It's true. He wouldn't.
Clearly we have different...
professional standards.
Jonathan Crane's father
created a toxin
that makes people see
their greatest fear.
This morning,
it was used to rob a bank.
How is that my problem?
Let me explain
it to you.
See, whoever
robbed the bank,
they challenged Penguin.
And all we have to do
is tell Penguin
that you're involved,
and he'll send Victor Zsasz
down here to talk to you.
Jim, how would you
describe Victor?
Victor Zsasz?
A homicidal maniac and sadist.
A homicidal maniac
and sadist
of the highest
professional standards.
So you can talk with us
here and now,
or you can
talk to Victor.
They threatened me;
I had no choice.
We want a name, putz.
I knew it rang a bell.
Grady Harris.
Ran a crew
a few years back.
Him and his
cousin Merton.
Couple of cowboys
from the sticks.
Grady!
GCPD!
Well, well.
Look at what we got here.
What's wrong with you pigs?
Harassing honest fellas like us,
when there's real criminals
out there.
You robbed a bank
in broad daylight.
That don't make you a criminal?
I'm an outlaw!
Outlaws have a code.
Criminals,
they'll take everything.
They'll take
a man's livelihood.
Like the Penguin.
And his licenses.
But we're gonna show him,
you'll see.
Penguin wouldn't give you
a license
if you begged him
till the cows came home,
you stupid hick!
You're lucky
I'm not the Penguin.
We would gut you right here.
We're better than them!
Take care, pigs.
They see him anyway.
Hey, check it out.
Ooh.
Looking for company?
She all by herself.
Just let me go, okay?
Not a chance.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Don't turn your back on a guy
unless you're sure he's down.
Otherwise, not bad.
Does this mean we can get pizza?
I'm just saying,
you steal my pepperoni again,
I'll break your fingers.
So you're saying... do
steal your pepperoni again?
I come in peace.
You ladies were not
easy to track down.
Then again,
I can see why you don't advertise.
Didn't you used to be rich?
That was before
your boss stole my club.
Well, you murdered his mom
and tried to kill him.
So... call it even?
There a reason you're here?
You know about these?
The boss can't have you
operating on your own.
Now, he could just kill you,
but he figures it's time
to let bygones be bygones.
How big of him.
Tomorrow night's
the opening of his club.
Come by, kiss the ring,
get your license.
Is that pepperoni?
Goes without saying,
this is one of those...
"or else" kind of deals.
Later.
We got to find a new place.
Why? We join Penguin,
we can at least get work.
I came to you because
I wanted to move up.
And look around.
We're barely making it.
I'm not working for him.
Now, pack.
Detective Gordon.
Bruce.
I didn't hear you.
What happened?
Uh, nothing.
Harvey and I
were tracking a gang.
We let ourselves get surprised.
What brings you
down here?
I found this
when I was in the city.
Wasn't sure what
to do with it.
One of
Penguin's licenses.
Apparently,
crime is legal now.
And you're going along
with that?
Not really.
There's a number on the license.
I was thinking
Penguin must have
some sort of
master list.
Connecting the crime and the
criminal to the license issued.
List like that would tell you
not only who committed
that crime,
but crimes that haven't
even happened yet.
Unfortunately, the judges are
going along with
the licenses.
I'm trying to track down
who in Penguin's organization
keeps the list.
It would set off
too many alarms.
I see.
But you haven't
given up.
You just said
you were out tracking a gang.
That's different.
This gang isn't licensed.
But...
Penguin will come after them,
if he hasn't already.
And when he catches them,
it'll be more proof that Gotham
doesn't need the GCPD.
Sorry, it's been
a long day.
So why not use Penguin
to lead you to them?
If I could figure out
how to do that, I would.
It was good to see you,
Detective.
You should come by
the house for dinner.
Yes.
I'd like that.
How about we grab a bite...
tonight?
Exclusive, but welcoming.
Urbane and edgy.
Tonight's opening will establish
the Iceberg Lounge
as Gotham's newest place to see
and be seen.
And you say you acquired
the club from Barbara Kean?
Is that a question?
It's just, no one's
seen her for months, and...
Well, Barbara Kean's whereabouts
are not my concern.
This was The Sirens club.
It is now mine.
Mr. Cobblepot,
there's a rumor going around
about criminals
being given licenses.
The rumor is
you're issuing them.
Tell me, what is
the crime rate in Gotham?
We're at historic lows.
Historic lows.
You know, Augustus Caesar
once presided
over the longest period
of peace and prosperity
the world has ever known.
It was called the Pax Romana.
Perhaps one day,
this will be known as
the "Pax Penguina."
That's not a denial.
We're here to talk
about my club.
Your readers will
find this interesting. Ivy?
That's Edward Nygma.
Turns out Ed had
a very rare brain disease.
There was only
one option:
to freeze him and
wait for the cure.
In his final lucid moments,
he begged me,
"Oswald, do not hide me away.
Put me out with the people."
It was the least I could do.
Anyone tell him
he was being frozen?
I have affidavits
from his doctor,
if you would like to see them.
No, thanks.
Well, Jim,
I'm rather busy.
So whatever your business is...
I came to tell you
you're a fraud.
The gang that has
Crane's fear toxin,
they're not afraid of you.
Others will find out.
That's how it begins.
You've had a nice run, Oswald,
but it's over.
Oh, Jim,
it's so hard to admit when
you've become irrelevant.
Let me tell you
what's gonna happen.
I'm going to find this gang,
and I'm going
to crush them.
And everyone will see
that it is Oswald Cobblepot,
the Penguin,
who keeps Gotham safe.
Always good to see you,
old friend!
As he prepares for the opening
of the Iceberg Lounge,
Oswald Cobblepot announced
that he would destroy the gang
that attacked Gotham
First National Bank yesterday.
He described them as cowards
and pond scum.
Penguin's going down tonight.
You finish that
new batch yet?
Yes.
Now, can you please,
can you please
get rid of that, please?
What, you and him
ain't getting along?
Please, just get rid of it!
Listen, I got to do
some things tonight,
but I think you guys should
spend some time together, huh?
No, please.
We all have our fears to face.
Stop, stop! Please!
Stop, please!
No!
Stop!
Let me out!
Remember how you accused me
of being a slave to my emotions?
No more.
I have banished those feelings.
And look how I have risen.
But at what cost?
I wonder which
of us is frozen.
Him.
He's, like,
totally frozen.
Ivy, go somewhere else.
All right, I want two
unmarked units at street level,
and another two teams
with me and Harvey
watching the entrances
to the club.
The moment that gang arrives,
we move.
You heard the man.
Suit up! Let's go!
Can we count on them?
Let's see, you tricked Penguin
into baiting the gang
to attack his club,
hoping to arrest them
before they cause mass panic,
only so you could
embarrass Penguin,
so I would say yeah,
they're about as dependable
as any other part
- of this cockamamie plan.
- Thanks.
I'll get the gas masks.
♪♪
Please, let me out!
Jonathan.
Let me out!
Jonathan!
So you guys work
for Penguin, huh?
It ain't like that.
- Sure.
- Come on, Gordon.
Since Penguin's
been cracking down,
life's been good.
Why you got to
rock the boat?
What happens when he starts
giving out licenses for murders?
Huh?
What then?
I'm wasting my breath, aren't I?
Pretty much.
All right, then.
Who wants it first?
♪♪ Dance music playing...
♪♪
Mr. Wayne,
Mr. Pennyworth.
I am so glad
you could make it.
It's our pleasure.
Congratulations.
We were
just admiring
your frozen mate.
Is he still alive in there?
I fear we may never know.
Well, you'll know when
you finally thaw him out.
When they discover
a cure for his disease.
Oh, yes. Then, of course.
I wanted
to personally thank you
for everything
you've done for this city.
Thank you, Mr. Wayne.
So...
can I ask about
the licenses?
Uh, a little discretion,
if you would, Master Bruce.
Everybody's talking
about it, Alfred.
I just want to know
how it works.
So, does someone
come to you and say
"I want to rob a bank"?
Now, Bruce,
if I didn't know any better,
I would think that you wanted me
to implicate myself.
Anything you say
stays between us.
First, let me ask...
you would be agreeable
to the idea of licensed crime?
If crime had been licensed
and controlled three years ago,
my parents would still be alive.
Exactly so.
Well, between us,
I have nothing to do with
the licenses directly.
I provide the guidelines
while Mr. Penn
handles all of
the details.
Now...
would you excuse me?
Well done, sir.
Thank you.
Now we know who
has the list.
The next step is...
Selina.
Where's your babysitter?
It's kind of a package deal.
Yeah. Well, he's got me.
Is that good enough or not?
Actually,
we're both in.
I should...
pat you down for weapons.
Sure.
- If you want to lose a hand.
- Was worth a shot.
I'll tell the boss.
See ya.
You were worried about me.
Hey, man, I been looking
all over for you.
Ooh, ouch.
Think we can forget
about backup.
I see you talked to some
of your fellow officers.
Probably not a bad thing.
How's that?
Guys get to let off steam,
resentments don't fester.
Next time, you can
get punched in the face.
This beautiful mug?
No one would dare.
Let's go.
♪♪ Dance music playing...
All right, once inside,
gas Zsasz and Penguin first,
and then go crazy.
I still don't see Penguin.
Hello!
I'm guessing that gas
isn't faster than a bullet.
What do you think?
Jim Gordon and his
ham-fisted manipulation.
He thought he fooled me.
You want to
do 'em here or downstairs?
Might be a little loud
in here.
Neither.
I have something special
planned for them.
What do you
want, Bruce?
You knew I'd follow you.
Just like I knew
you'd come up here.
You don't know
anything about me.
I wanted to apologize
for what I said at the hospital
when you came
to visit Alfred.
You were making a kind gesture.
You want to talk to me,
come up here.
My point is I'm sorry.
Yeah.
You were a jerk.
I saw you arrive
with Tabitha Galavan.
I'm not sure
I'd choose her
as a mentor.
Wow.
That means
absolutely nothing to me.
Selina...
Oh?
You... you want
to say something?
That's a lovely dress
you're wearing tonight.
Honestly, you two.
Why can't you just go to the
cinema like normal teenagers?
Uh, Master Bruce,
we got a bit of a...
bit of a situation downstairs.
What sort of situation?
Miss Kyle.
For the past three
months, I have given this city
a tranquility
it has never known.
Now I would like to ensure
that peace for the future.
In the weeks to come,
you will hear whispers
about what's happening
in the streets of Gotham.
All you need
to know is
without me...
this is what you get.
Men who want to bring fear
back to our city,
who promise a return
to the old days.
So... tell
your families,
tell your friends,
it is Oswald Cobblepot
who keeps them safe,
not the GCPD.
You're welcome!
I have my things in the car.
We can stop them
in the parking garage.
Absolutely not, Master Bruce.
Alfred, Penguin is gonna take
those men out and kill them.
Undoubtedly so...
But as you said before,
you can make a difference.
There is a time for masks,
and there is a time
for Bruce Wayne.
What's going
to be done to you...
Wait!
I want to know what you're
going to do with those men.
You need not concern yourself
with that.
Are those men going to be
turned over to the police?
Earlier tonight, you thanked me
for making the city safer.
Now, how do you think
that happened?
I do the dirty work
no one else will.
I understand.
But I'm asking you,
turn those men over
to the police.
You're young.
You have a good heart.
No.
Enjoy your party, Penguin.
You little twerp.
What's wrong?
You scared?!
Hey!
You're under arrest,
by order of the Gotham City
Police Department.
Cuff him.
Help me!
Help me! Help me!
Penguin ain't
gonna be too happy.
Screw him.
I'm just worried about
finding Jonathan Crane.
If he's out there, with access
to his father's formula...
Relax. We'll find him.
I wouldn't expect too much help
from these parts, though.
There's good cops out there.
They just need reminding.
You have a list
of all the licenses
you've given; I want it.
I... I can't.
Penguin, he'll...
♪♪
What about the alarm?
Forget it.
We got a license, remember?
Guys, come on.
Oh, no.
What the...?!
GCPD!
Gotham Police!
You're under arrest!
Crane! You got to make more
of that fear gas.
We got to get Merton
out of jail! Crane!
Crane?
Jonathan Crane
isn't here anymore.
Just the Scarecrow.
Sync corrections  by  srjanapala
♪♪