Previously on Gotham...
- Is it loaded?
- Ain't no point in an unloaded gun.
It's Kristen Kringle's final paychecks.
She never picked them up. I don't like it.
Oswald,
you are making progress.
By the laws of Gotham City,
he is hereby declared sane.
You are a free man.
I was wondering if you'd heard
from Kristen Kringle lately.
Do you think
that something bad has happened?
- We have no idea when she might wake up.
- Bitch.
So, that's the game is it, Jimbo?
Gonna try to outsmart me?
I don't think so.
We've met before?
Yes. You killed my parents.
Who hired you?
You'll never know their name.
I'm a monster. You need to kill me.
- You're just a man.
- Bruce.
He's in there.
Alfred,
I have left home for a while
to live on the streets with Selina.
Trust me, and honor my wishes.
Don't try to bring me back.
Welcome to the Gotham Museum of Art.
The museum offers hundreds of new events
and programs each month,
including lectures,
performances, tours,
family activities and more.
The Gotham Museum cafe and gift shop
is located on the fourth floor...
Keep moving!
Stop!
Solo robber hit the museum
about an hour ago.
Scared people away
with a bomb that never went off.
- Anybody hurt?
- Nope.
Why us, then?
Isn't it a Robbery Squad case?
Bomb threats are you guys,
whether the bomb goes off or not.
So, get on it.
Gordon, you stay.
Internal Affairs is reopening the file
on Galavan's murder.
Why?
Anonymous tip.
Someone called in, claims they saw you,
not Penguin, kill Galavan
that night at the docks.
IA gets a dozen crank calls a week.
They're probably just bored.
This tip came with a detail
we didn't put out to the public.
The umbrella.
So someone in the GCPD
is trying to make trouble for me.
By spreading lies.
Been known to happen.
Lies, huh?
Tell me the truth again.
I didn't kill Galavan.
I wasn't there.
What was that all about?
Later.
- Detective Gordon.
- Hey, Ed.
I'm ready for our sit-down.
Our what?
You wanted to interview me
about Ms. Kringle leaving town
with Officer Dougherty?
Oh, right. Yeah, sorry. Rain check.
We got to get to Gotham Museum.
Oh, the art heist.
Yes, I heard about this.
Very bold.
Uh, yes, rain check.
Tally-ho, chaps. Go get that bad guy.
We'll talk later this afternoon.
And Ed?
Don't worry. I'll find out
what happened to Ms. Kringle.
I have the utmost faith in your abilities,
Detective Gordon.
Believe me.
Boss?
You'll never guess
who just knocked on the door.
If I'll never guess,
then why not just tell me, jackass?
If you say I have three guesses,
well, then that's a game.
It's an annoying and stupid game,
but at least it makes sense.
Son of a...
Hi.
Well, well, well.
I heard they let you out of Arkham.
Yes.
Happy day.
I'm sane.
I have a certificate.
Whoa.
Uh...
But... But I... I hope I'm not intruding.
I just got back in town,
and thought it'd be rude
not to say hello to an old friend.
An old friend?
Well, yes.
I mean, we had our ups and downs,
but on the whole,
I thought we were friends.
Weren't we?
That's what I recall, anyhow.
Cupcake?
You killed my brother.
You messed with his mind
and made him your slave.
Hello?
I guess I was pretty terrible, huh?
I want to apologize sincerely.
I wasn't thinking straight.
Apology accepted.
Let's kill him.
Wait. What?
Uh, Butch, listen, I've changed.
You have no reason to fear me. I'm...
I'm a good person now.
I was thinking about
visiting your mother's grave.
- Oh?
- Mmm.
Miss the old bird.
Her sobs would often lull me
to sleep at night.
"Oswald!
"Save me."
That does sound like her.
You know, I think he's for real.
Those loony bin doctors
must have done a real number on him.
It's actually kind of sad.
Let him go.
What?
You heard me.
Look at him, he's a pathetic loser.
He doesn't pose a threat to anyone.
Are you serious?
No way! He has to die.
Who's the boss here?
I believe in an eye for an eye.
We've all lost something, including him.
We're square, you and me.
- Understand?
- Completely.
Mmm.
Fine. You know,
I didn't realize you were so sentimental.
He's not leaving
without some kind of punishment.
- He's not.
- Okay.
What'd you have in mind?
Your little private,
inside voice is screaming.
Want to tell me what that pow-wow
with Barnes was all about?
IA is re-opening the investigation
into the murder of Theo Galavan.
Anonymous person called in,
saying they saw me kill him.
That old chestnut, huh?
Is there something I can do?
You still friendly
with your gal over in IA?
Ginny?
Our paths have been known to cross.
Can they cross again soon?
I need to know what they have.
Sure.
Mr. Thatch?
Detective Gordon.
This is Detective Bullock.
What can you tell us
about the painting that was stolen?
Uh, the painting
is entitled Mad Grey Dawn,
and it depicted a railway explosion
at the turn of the century.
A minor work
compared to much of the collection.
Strangely, he simply defaced
two much more valuable paintings
in another section of the gallery.
A Marché and a Larue.
Follow me.
Priceless.
What kind of art thief would take time
to defile such masterpieces?
- An ignorant one?
- No.
This took a lot of time and effort.
He knows what he's doing.
He's not interested in profit.
He's trying to send a message.
Which is what?
No idea.
What about the painters themselves?
What about them?
Question marks are directly over
their signatures on the canvas.
There's entire books written
on each of them.
- I'm sorry, I--
- He would want to keep it simple.
What about their names?
"Marché" means "market"
and "Larue" is "the road," yes?
Yes.
Or "the street."
Market Street.
The painting he stole
depicted a railway explosion? Yes?
Yes. A bombing actually.
It was known as Bloody Monday.
Today is Monday.
And Union Railway Station
is on Market Street.
Attention, please evacuate
the train station in an orderly fashion.
Please find your nearest exit
and evacuate the train station.
Thank you.
- What are we looking for?
- I have no idea.
Get these people out of here. Go, go!
- Get outta here! Go!
- Move! Move!
Come on.
Bullock.
Listen up!
The device is inside the lockers.
Pinkney, get these people out of here.
Get them out of here.
Outside, now!
Get them out of here! Go!
How much time
till the bomb squad gets here?
Too long. Get back.
Okay, get back. Back, back, back.
Go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go.
- Hey, Ivy.
- Hey, Cat.
Hey, Billionaire Boy.
What is he doing here?
Shh. They're right upstairs.
He's staying with me for a while.
Don't touch anything.
What is this place?
Ivy works for a gang
that runs the magic mushroom trade.
What's a magic mushroom?
Some give you visions.
Some give you energy.
Some help you to sleep.
I've cultivated over a dozen kinds.
What are we doing here?
The gang is run
by Gilzean's nephew, Sonny,
and his merry band of losers.
So, these mushrooms are illegal?
Yes, very illegal.
Which means there's always
a ton of cash around.
You're going to rob them?
Uh...
Yeah.
Okay.
How do we do it?
We don't.
You have money, remember?
A lot of it.
Selina, I told you.
I want to survive on my own,
find out who I am without my money.
Without being Bruce Wayne.
Besides, I don't mind stealing
if it's from criminals.
What's the plan?
Meet Psilocybe Arkrescens.
Also known as the blue devil.
She slipped a few of them
in the gang's lunch today,
so all we have to do now is wait.
- What will they do?
- Instant death.
Kidding.
They'll be in a state of relaxed bliss.
Like a dream.
Trust me, it's great.
How long until they're out?
From art thief to mad bomber
in the same day?
What the hell is next?
I don't know. But he wanted us to find it.
I think that's what the heist was about.
He's playing a game.
Great.
That's exactly what this city needs.
Did you find any other brainteasers
that might indicate his next piece
of performance art?
No. Either he's decided to keep it
a surprise or he's taking a break.
I doubt we're that lucky.
I want every available resource
on this thing.
You got it.
Excuse me.
Officer Pinkney, can I get your signature
on this chain of custody form?
Sure.
- Thank you.
- Pinkney.
Detective Gordon.
We've been working together
for over a year, Ed.
You can call me Jim.
Jim. Heard you were able to save the day.
I got lucky.
I don't believe in luck.
You saw a problem
and you solved it. Bravo.
Hey, I want you
to oversee forensics on this one.
Maybe our luck will hold
and we'll get something
on the bomb signature or trace elements.
No other leads yet?
No. I have no idea
what this guy wants
or what he's after,
which makes him dangerous.
Oh, don't you worry. I'm on the case.
Right.
Shh.
Be quiet.
Someone might still be awake.
Who... Who are you?
Hey! Hey, hey.
We're no one.
You're dreaming. Pretty cool, right?
Totally.
Yeah.
Listen, if you give us the coffee can
and close your eyes,
you'll be able to fly.
Sweet.
Run.
Whoa! Where you going?
Hey, Cat.
Hey, Sonny.
You lose weight?
Keep cracking wise, Selina.
You ain't gonna be smiling
when my uncle gets to you.
Let's see how many lives
you really have left.
- Hi.
- Penguin?
- Hi. Hi.
- Hi.
Sorry to intrude.
Bit of a mess.
I was just passing by and...
May I...
Could I come in for a moment?
These feathers aren't as warm
as they look.
Of course. Where are my manners?
Uh, it's... It's so good to see you.
So, how have you been, old friend?
Well, I hope.
Yeah, well.
I have been. Been busy.
I've been really busy.
And what about you?
I hear that you've been released.
What... What just... What happened?
Oh, oh.
Well, just good old Butch
and Tabitha having fun.
They talked about killing me,
so this was actually pretty nice
of them, considering.
Pretty nice of them?
They did a pretty good job
on you in Arkham, huh?
I'm here to tell you, Ed, as a friend,
violence and anger are not the answer.
I am a changed man.
Better, and you can change, too.
Cool.
Tempting offer.
The thing is,
the me I am right now
is kind of hitting my stride.
Oh.
And I'm really grateful
for all that you've taught me,
and that bad stuff you told me
about Jim Gordon is really paying off.
- Is it?
- It is.
It's helped me to create
the perfect puzzle
to get rid of my Jim Gordon dilemma.
Normally, I would love to share,
but to be honest,
the new you is kind of freaking me out.
I'm just really busy right now.
Well, I'll be on my way.
Thanks for coming by.
So, I spoke with my gal in IA.
The snitch said
Penguin was beating Galavan to death
when you stepped in
and put a bullet in his chest.
Someone else was there that night.
Either that, or Penguin talked.
He did just get out of Arkham.
How the hell he did, I'll never know.
But lest we forget he was in there
for a murder you committed.
A grudge is not beyond
the realm of possibility.
He could have talked when he was arrested.
Used it to cut a deal, but he didn't.
Did your IA contact
give you anything else?
The witness has agreed
to swear out a statement.
IA has officially
reopened the investigation.
You are now the primary suspect
in the murder of Theo Galavan.
Well, tell my uncle to call me!
Look, I know you think
he's got a soft spot for you,
but I'm pretty sure that's gonna change
when he finds out you tried to rob him.
My guess is he's not gonna be
too happy with you, either,
when I tell him that I just waltzed
in here and grabbed the cash.
So, maybe you let us go,
and we call it even?
What kind of message would that send?
No. The Gilzeans
are all about consequences.
More like all about pizza.
You ever try our product, Selina?
Stop!
Aren't you being rather cowardly?
Assaulting a girl?
No, he's right. You know,
when you're right, you're right!
Knock it off, Sonny. You made your point.
Stay out of this, Selina.
Call me a coward again.
You're a coward.
An ignorant, brutish--
Stop!
While you're down there, kid,
lick my boot.
Strength costs wind.
Now, if you're gonna beat a big man,
all you have to do is outlast him.
Stop!
I actually think he wants a beating.
Is that your thing, kid?
You like pain?
An ignorant, brutish, cowardly clown.
Yep.
He likes it, all right.
Your mom and dad
must have been real freaks,
bringing up a weird kid like you.
Enough!
Let's go! Let's go!
Hello, Mother.
What a lovely spot.
I'm so sorry I couldn't be here
for the funeral,
but I think you'd be proud of me.
I'm a changed man.
Or,
at least I'm trying to be.
To be honest,
I don't know
if I'm gonna make it without you.
Hello?
I'm terribly sorry,
- I don't mean to interrupt.
- Not at all.
- Lilies.
- Her favorite, if memory serves.
Yes. They were.
Did you know her?
A long time ago.
I found her again only in death,
I'm afraid.
- I'm Elijah Van Dahl.
- Oh.
Oswald Cobblepot.
Cobblepot?
You're related to Gertrude?
My mother.
Mother?
You're Gertrude's son?
Yes.
I'm sorry. How did you know
my mother, exactly?
- How old are you?
- Excuse me?
How old are you?
- Gertrude left--
- Thirty-one.
Thirty-one years ago, yes.
That's right.
Oh, my God. She...
She never told me.
Told you what?
That I had a son.
Any word on the bomber?
Bullock's waiting on forensics.
I just wish I knew what his endgame was.
Feels like I'm missing something.
Is that why you're not eating?
Uh, yeah, I guess.
No.
IA is re-opening the investigation
into Galavan's murder.
- Why?
- An eye-witness came forward.
You... You told me it was over, Jim.
You swore to me.
I'm sorry.
I knew in my heart that it wasn't.
But I let you lie to me.
I didn't. I wasn't.
We should have left
when we had the chance.
Gone somewhere new, somewhere better,
somewhere fit to raise our child.
You knew I couldn't do that.
I can fix this.
How?
You did it. You killed Galavan.
I'll find a way. I have to.
What if you can't?
Hello, Officer Pinkney.
I'm so sorry to bother you at home.
Can I come in?
Uh, sure.
Make it quick. The ballgame's on.
What's this about?
Oh, Detective Gordon'll explain.
He's just behind me.
Oh, okay.
Hey, Pinkney,
what do you call a tavern of blackbirds?
A crowbar.
You get it? A crow bar.
I know it's kind of lame.
I just came up with it on the spot.
Ow.
Gertrude came to work
as a cook for my parents.
She was so young and beautiful.
So full of life.
So beautiful.
I was young then, too.
A boy, really.
A foolish, romantic boy.
When my parents found out,
they forbade us from being together.
I was the heir to a great fortune,
they said.
And she was just a cook.
I threatened to run away with her.
Turn my back on my family name
and my inheritance.
It was the first and only time
I ever stood up to them.
They must have known
my words were just that.
A spoiled child, making idle threats.
The next day, Gertrude was gone.
My parents told me only that
they had come to an arrangement.
She would be taken care of,
and I must never make
an attempt to find her.
And to my shame, I didn't.
I let them separate us.
I had no idea...
She never told me she was pregnant.
She didn't tell me about you...
If she did...
She told me that my father had died
when I was still a baby.
Easier than the truth, I suppose.
That your father was a coward
who wouldn't stand up to his parents.
She must have figured that the two of you
would be better off making your own way.
Which, in fact, is probably the truth.
Look at you.
A strong young man.
She did a good job, didn't she?
She tried.
We both miss her terribly.
My poor boy,
you've been all alone in the world.
Yes, I have.
No longer.
You have a home,
and a father,
and a family.
- A family?
- A big, happy family.
They're going to be
so thrilled to meet you.
Sir, please,
tell me truthfully,
is this a dream?
It's not a dream, my boy.
You're home.
- Yeah.
- Forensics just landed.
The timer on the bomb was activated
remotely by phone, which was smart.
Gave him time to plant it in advance
and set it off when he wanted.
We get a number?
Yeah. Call came from a payphone
inside 17, West Dewy Avenue.
Just a few blocks from Union Station.
Payphone, huh?
All right, I'll go over there
and check it out.
- See you tomorrow.
- He's probably long gone by now.
I can't sleep anyhow.
Yeah.
Hello?
Pinkney.
Gordon?
What the hell are you doing here?
Put your gun down. Now!
Place your gun on the floor.
I won't say it again.
Okay.
Listen to me.
I was just following up a lead
on the bomber investigation.
You were following up a lead
in Pinkney's apartment?
No.
I didn't know that
this was Pinkney's apartment building.
Why are you here?
Pinkney sent me a message.
Wanted to talk outside of work.
About what?
You.
I have to have to take you down
to the precinct.
There's been a mistake.
I hope so, son.
I hope so.
Almost done.
Okay.
Never seen someone
take a beating like that before.
I think Sonny's right.
You do like pain.
When it was happening,
it was like nothing else existed.
Everything I've been struggling with,
the emptiness
and confusion,
it just vanished,
and for the first time
in a long time,
I knew I was going to be okay.
I knew that whatever Sonny did to me,
I could take it.
That he couldn't break me.
That no one can.
Nobody's unbreakable, Bruce.
You want your rep here?
I didn't do this. Somebody set me up.
Cause of death,
blunt force trauma to the head.
Captain, listen to me. I--
Murder weapon was a crowbar.
We found it under the couch.
Your fingerprints were on it.
At Union Station,
I used a crowbar to open up the locker.
Somebody must have picked it up.
And that someone just happened to know
that you'd be paying
Officer Pinkney a visit tonight?
I told you.
I didn't know that he lived there.
Forensics traced the bomber's call
to a pay phone in the building.
Bullock will back me up.
He did.
But when I asked for the report,
it had nothing to do with a remote timer
or any traced call.
I know how this looks.
But Pinkney was one of us.
Why would I kill him?
Because he was the anonymous witness
that fingered you.
We found this Internal Affairs form
at Pinkney's place.
It's the exact same statement
that the anonymous witness made,
only Pinkney signed this
with his own name.
I guess he got cold feet
about putting himself on the line.
So he sent in the anonymous tip instead.
Must have figured you'd get nasty.
I don't know how you figured it out,
but you found out he was the witness.
No.
Maybe you went over to his place
to talk him out of it?
I told you,
I didn't know it was his place!
Or maybe you had no intention of talking,
and you just killed him.
You know me.
I know that something went down
between you and Galavan that night.
I saw it in your eyes
when IA was grilling you.
And now, the one person who was about
to shine light on this whole thing
is found beaten to death
with you standing over the body.
- What am I missing?
- I was set up!
Jim, how many lying,
son-of-a-bitch, low-life weasels
have you heard use that same line?
Somebody set you up?
That's what you're going with?
The least you can do
is admit what you did.
Be a man.
Pinkney was one of us.
He deserves that. I deserve that!
The least you could do
is look me in the eye
and remind me that
you were a good cop once.
That you still know right from wrong. Jim!
I want to talk to my rep.
You're a disgrace to the badge.
I trusted you!
But you broke my heart.
You, take him to county.
I don't want him here.
- Jim!
- Harvey.
The bomber, Harvey.
Everything that happened today
was set up to trap me!
The bomber, Harvey!
The four-week
murder trial of Detective Gordon
concluded just minutes ago,
with the jury returning
a unanimous verdict of "guilty."
The judge handed down
the maximum sentence of 40 years
to be served at Blackgate Penitentiary.
...jury was unanimous in its decision
after deliberating less than 24 hours.
District Attorney Harvey Dent
was not available for comment--
Wow.
You okay?
This isn't right.
This can't be right.
Tell me something that is.
Just hours ago, the murder
trial of Detective James Gordon concluded
with the jury returning
a unanimous verdict of "guilty."
The judge handed down
the maximum sentence of 40 years
to be served at Blackgate Penitentiary.
The jury was unanimous in its decision--
Oh, my. Awake at last.
Well, hello, dear.
Someone call Professor Strange!
We're gonna fight this.
- Lee.
- Did you hear me?
No matter what it takes,
we're gonna fight this.
The evidence isn't gonna change.
You're innocent.
I'm far from innocent. We both know that.
So, what? We just give up?
We move on.
Move on?
Move on to what?
You mean me.
You mean I move on.
I've thought long and hard about this.
- No.
- You have to listen to me.
I'm tired of listening.
This isn't fair!
How can you not be with us?
Birthdays,
and first steps,
and skinned knees,
and everything?
What, what? Visits through bars and...
And not knowing
when the phone is gonna ring
in the middle of the night
and tell me when you're--
I don't want that.
For either of you.
- You still have a chance at happiness.
- No.
You need to go somewhere.
Far away from here.
Somewhere fit to raise our child.
Start a new life.
Forget I exist.
It's the only way
either one of us survives this.
No, Jim.
Don't try to contact me again.
I won't reply.
No. Don't do this.
I'm sorry, Lee.
Jim, don't do this. I love you.
I'm so, so sorry.
Jim!
A toast.
I want to thank you all
for your generosity.
You have welcomed Oswald into our family
with open arms and open hearts,
and for that, I am truly blessed.
To family.
Uh, you guys have made me
the happiest man on the planet.
I am so grateful.
I love you all.
- Family.
- To family.
To family.
Oh...
- Brother.
- Yes, yes.
Yes.
Inmate Gordon,
prison transfer. Open the gate.
I'm gonna find who set you up.
This ain't over.
Yeah.
You were a good partner, Harvey.
Still am.
English - SDH