NARRATOR: Previously on Gotham...
ALFRED: Taking a life will lead you
down a darker path
that you could never imagine.
I know, I've been down it.
I'm not the hero Gotham needs.
ALFRED: Then it's gonna be
a long, bumpy journey back.
You've met Martin, Isee.
You and I, we're more than friends.
We 're conspirators.
Oh, no.
You are relieved of duty,
Harvey Bullock.
As of this moment, I am assuming the
captaincy of Gotham Central.
What did you have to do to get it?
NEWSREADER: Gotham finds itself in
the hands of a ritualistic cop killer
Being called Professor Pyg.
THE PYG: It doesn't stop until I've
butchered every single swine
on Penguin's payroll.
I'm gonna find you.
I hope you do, it's a Spectacle.
And you're my muse, Jimmy Gordon.
My poor lost lambs.
I come to you today with an offer
for this evening.
Fresh biscuits and
a hearty bowl of soup.
I have place settings for six.
Nobody wants some fresh pumpkin pie?
Smile.
My children.
There are two Gothams.
The haves.
And the have-nets.
I know what it is
to feel like a have-not.
But I say. "Enough."
Here's to giving the haves a taste
of what it is like to be
a have-not.
Let's begin.
Shall we?
I'Il be out of yourway
in just a second, Captain.
Harvey.
This isn't how I wanted
things to go down.
And yet. here we are.
You know what
I was thinking about today?
Our first case.
When I told you to walk Penguin
to the end of the pier,
put a bullet in his head
and dump him in the water,
and you wouldn't.
- You thought it was wrong.
- It was.
Well, maybe if you would have done it,
Falcone would still be running things
and a lot of people who are dead
would be alive today.
If I could go back,
I'd do the same thing.
'Cause you still don't understand
how the city works, Jim.
You want to be a hero.
And Gotham doesn't need heroes.
It needs people
who will do what is necessary.
You're wrong. If you show 'em the way,
the people will follow.
I guess we'II just have to
wait and see, huh?
When your leave is up,
there'II be a desk here waiting for you.
Sit around, watch you all day?
No, thanks.
Right there's perfect. Thank you.
Beautiful.
I predict this evening's fundraiser
will be a smashing success.
If I want Gotham's wealthiest families
to support the orphanage,
things have to be perfect.
I appreciate you taking part, Oswald.
Yes.
- Sadly, a situation has arisen.
- No.
That thing in The Narrows
with your former chief of staff?
No, no. This is far more serious.
It has to do with Mayor Burke
promoting James Gordon
to captain of the GCPD.
You're not really
worried about James Gordon.
Please.
The issue is the person
who ordered his appointment.
- I see.
- Do you?
Oswald, we both know
the mayor is a weasel.
Someone must've paid him off.
But I don't see why that means
you can't attend my dinner.
Because, my dear,
the mayor has vanished.
But I will find him.
I will learn the name of my enemy.
And there will be a reckoning.
And that is why I might
not be able to make it this evening.
Very well.
But a few of the children
are doing a song.
Martin is taking part.
It would mean the world to him
if you could come.
Of course.
Now, don't let me keep you.
If you think she's the one,
we could have Victor talk to her.
You do realize she is
literally my only friend.
I need the mayor.
I need proof.
But. sir, what if Ms. Falcone,
not to say it is her,
has seen to it that the mayor
is missing, well,
Permanently?
I could be Chasing a ghost
while she prepares her next move.
I wish I had a spy close to her.
Someone quiet.
Bring me Martin.
Who?
The boy with the pad around his neck.
The one who can't talk.
I thought I was clear. We're done.
Penguin suspects something.
What are you talking about?
He was just here saying
that he couldn't come to the party
I'm having tonight for the orphanage.
He knows someone paid the mayor
to make you captain.
I think he suspects me.
- Have you warned the mayor?
- I'm not a fool, Jim.
I had him leave town
after your appointment.
Sounds like you have
your bases covered as usual.
Thanks for the heads up about Penguin.
Don't call me again.
This is Harper.
Gordon, line one. Says it's private.
Sofia.
Wrong. Try again.
You son of a bitch.
Attaboy, Jim.
Or should I say "Captain"?
Congratulations, by the way.
So, do you remember when you said
the rot in Gotham went from high to low?
Y0u've hit the nail on the head.
Police were low,
and now it's time for Gotham's elite
to feel the pain.
Enter phase two.
I won't spoil the reveal.
Hurry outside for a little taste
of what's to come.
Ciao, mon ami.
He's outside. Let's go.
GCPD.
Make way. GCPD.
- Back up. Back up.
- Excuse me.
Are they dead?
Get forensics here.
And I want this whole area
closed off. No press.
That pig's eating that guy.
Now, Harper.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Where's breakfast?
Breakfast was produced and consumed
by yours truly at breakfast time.
It is now a fast approaching
Iuncheon, Master Bruce.
Whatever. Just give me a coffee.
Enjoying the benefits
of another night out on the tiles
with Tommy Elliot
and his band of miscreants, are we?
How absolutely delightful.
I know what you're going through,
you know, Master Bruce.
Yeah?
I went out with my friends.
I'm hungover.
It doesn't take a genius
to figure it out.
You're lost is what you are.
I've seen that countless times
in young men.
Going off to war with a clear purpose
only to return home to a normal life,
unable to assimilate,
confused, angry.
And they make a complete tosh of it.
I don't really care.
You killed Ra's al Ghul.
Vengeance for your parents' death
has been your driving force for so long.
You are completely lost without it.
I need to call Tommy.
Have you forgotten what day it is today?
- Give me my phone.
- You have, ain't you?
Today is the day
my father took me camping.
We put a rock on top of Mount Bristol.
We did it every year.
Now give me my phone.
You are Bruce Wayne,
son of Thomas Wayne.
And the sooner you start
remembering that, the better.
S0, you drink your coffee.
You go upstairs, you put your kit on
'cause you and I,
we're going for a walk.
According to the medical examiner,
both victims had been
living outdoors for some time,
most likely homeless.
Now, see these incisions.
He removed their organs.
- Any idea why?
- Not yet.
The Pyg all but announced
that his next victims
would be the rich and powerful.
The high in Gotham.
So why is he killing the homeless?
You are asking for logic
from a psychopath.
From him, yeah. Everything he's done
has been thought through carefully.
There was a card on the table in French.
It said. "Long live the revolution."
Maybe he's using them
to make a statement.
He wants the city's attention.
For what?
He said this is just a taste
of what's to come.
There's a piece that's still missing.
The homeless are densest in The Narrows
I'm gonna start there.
A hell of a first day to be captain.
Yeah.
Call me if you find anything else.
We checked all buildings
in the three-block radius, Captain.
Nothing.
AII right. Widen it out
a couple of blocks.
Focus on buildings
with protected loading docks.
Captain, that was Lucius Fox.
Final tox came back.
Both victims had sodium sulfide
and chlorine residue on their skin.
He says it's common
in paper manufacturing.
There's an old paper plant
a few blocks from here
that closed down a while back.
Let's check that out.
Backup still incoming. Should we wait?
No.
GORDON: Over here.
What is he doing to them?
Taking their organs.
HARPER: A smoker oven?
He's cooking them.
Harper.
Drop the gun, Captain.
Shoot this bastard.
Drop m
Thank you.
You found me too soon, James.
The table is not yet set
and no meal should be served
before its time.
You want a hostage? Take me.
No, no, no, no, no.
That won't do at all.
You must see my final act.
Along with all of Gotham!
Right. Well, it's a lovely day for it.
Best foot forward.
Very distinguished.
Sofia tells me you're taking part
in a performance this evening.
Well, she's quite a lady, isn't she?
She's been a friend to both of us.
Or has she?
Martin.
I worry Sofia is only
pretending to be my friend.
And worse,
I fear she may be using you.
Now.
I have been
running this over in my mind.
And there are two ways
this might have gone.
One, Sofia chose a specific orphan, you,
to place in my path. She groomed you,
she told you how to act.
Or,
Sofia simply
collected a group of children
hoping one would gain my trust,
and make me easier to manipulate.
In this version. you are innocent.
Martin.
This is the version
I very badly want to believe.
But I need proof
of our friendship.
I need to know
if my suspicions are correct.
And if so, what Sofia is planning.
And who she is planning it with.
I need you to be my eyes and my ears.
Do you think you could do that?
Don't let me down, Martin.
Please.
GORDON: I want a city-wide BOLO
on that van.
I want every cop in Gotham
on the streets looking for Harper.
She will not be the Pyg's next victim.
- Go.
- AII right.
- AII right. Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Captain Gordon.
- Captain Gordon!
Captain Gordon! Captain Gordon!
Is it true that the serial killer
known as the Pyg is back?
That he's responsible for the scene
outside the GCPD this morning?
We believe so, yes.
We've also heard
he's kidnapped a GCPD detective.
How can you
keep the people of Gotham safe
when you can't protect
your own officers?
We remain hopeful
for Detective Harper's safe return.
Let me be clear.
The GCPD will stop this monster.
- Thafs a promise.
- And if you fail.
Will you be pushed aside
like Harvey Bullock was?
We're done here. Thank you.
Captain Gordon!
What about the rumor that the Pyg
is now cooking his victims?
Who told you that?
Is it true?
As I said, the GCPD
will bring the Pyg to justice.
That's all.
Captain Gordon! Captain Gordon!
Someone leaked to the press
that the Pyg is cooking his victims.
Maybe it was the Pyg.
We know he wants attention.
Look, Jim.
Everyone in the department
is on your side.
Yeah.
There is something you need to see.
"I gran! this food
will be somewhat dear,
["and therefore
ven] proper for landlords who.
"As they have already devoured
most of the parents,
"seem to have the best title
to the children."
It's Jonathan Swift, A Modest Proposal.
He made an argument for cannibalism
about the rich eating the poor.
The poor are the homeless.
But who are the rich?
Swift didn't just talk about
the rich eating the poor.
He specifically mentioned the orphans.
I know where he's going.
He left this for me.
He's doing exactly what he did
with Harvey. It could be a trap.
And I won't lead more officers
to their deaths.
- You're going alone?
- I'm sorry, Lucius.
Where's Chef Louis?
Ici, mademoiselle.
It's such a pleasure
to meet you in person.
I was expecting you earlier.
Apologies. I was detained.
But I've made
a small change in the menu.
I've steered us away from haute cuisine
to something a bit more mundane.
Voila.
I'm calling them Gotham meat pies.
Your guests will die for them.
I've made us a delicious
brown English stew
with herb dumplings, Master Bruce.
Your father used to love it
when I made stew.
Did I ever tell you
howl met your old man?
In London.
He was doing postgrad work there.
He told me.
Yeah, but no details.
Well, I was just out of the army.
Two months.
I don't remember any of it.
Alla bit of blur, really.
Booze, drugs, brawling.
A sucking great black cloud.
One day I wake up
and I'm lying in this alley.
And I'm covered in blood.
Don't know how.
So, I picked myself up,
I took myself straight down
to the police station, turn myself in,
hoping that they would chuck me
into the big house
and throw away the key.
And they told me to shut up,
sit down and wait.
And there was this really annoying
Yank wandering about,
dressed like he's ready
for a game of tennis,
and it was your dad.
Anyway, he bowls up to me
and asks me what I'd done.
Asking me questions.
Eventually, you know,
I found myself telling him
stuff that I was too frightened
even to think about.
But I guess it'd just been building.
Anyway, at that point,
the desk sergeant called him over
and your dad turned around
at me, and he said,
"Alfred, last night, Iwas
being attacked in the alley.
"And you started fighting this geezer.
"I headed on my toes, and I ran away."
And I said, "Yeah, but that's not
what happened, is it, Thomas?"
And he says, "It is now."
Your father saved my life.
His friendship saved me.
You see, I know what
it's all like being lonely,
hoping that the world will punish you.
I can help you.
- Bruce, listen to me...
- Alfred, I hear you.
I just don't want
to talk about this right now.
AII right.
Well, this looks lovely.
The rocks are gone.
They musfve fell out in the car.
The keys are in the bag, just there.
(ENGINE STARTING)
- BeautifuL
- So nice to see you, dear.
- Thanks.
- Yes.
Oswald. you came!
Look at you two.
So handsome.
I know how important
tonighfs party is to you.
And I wouldn't have forgiven myself
if I had missed Martin's performance.
Why don't you go
find the other children?
Did you locate the mayor?
Unfortunately, no.
But I've not given up hope.
Well, I, for one, am happy.
This way you get to come to my dinner.
I need to go check on the chef.
He seems a bit odd.
Please. try and enjoy yourself.
Hello, Martin.
What are you writing?
Don't make a noise.
(SHUSHING)
I'm a cop. Who are you?
A waiter.
I'm looking for a man.
Caucasian, about five foot ten.
He would've brought the food.
Maybe the chef.
The chef's in the kitchen
Look, Ijust got hired tonight.
Whatever the dude's into,
I have no idea.
You're okay. You're okay.
Do me a favor.
Find Ms. Falcone, bring her to me.
- Can you do that for me?
- Yeah.
What's that in your jacket?
I don't...
Jim Gordon really is
an impressive policeman.
- Was he alone?
- It seems so.
But, man.
Whatever it is you're into.
My partner and I,
our rates just doubled.
(HARPER MOANING)
Harper.
Hi, friends. The Falcone orphanage
is the realization
of a long-cherished dream.
And one that
would have not been possible
without your support. So, thank you.
- Cheers.
Now. if you could please
take your seats in the next room.
A few of the children
have prepared a song.
Where's Martin?
I wanted to wish him luck.
Ah. Off getting ready, no doubt.
Oswald. I've been thinking.
Maybe things happened for a reason.
Licensing crime was a bold move,
but it would've destroyed you.
Whoever had Jim Gordon
appointed captain.
May actually have saved you.
By attempting to destroy
everything I ever created?
- Oswald...
- Enough!
If you're going to confess, confess.
And face the consequences.
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (SCREAMING)
S0 sorry to interrupt.
The servers are getting everyone seated.
We don't want the food to get cold.
Shall we go in to dinner?
Chop-chop.
AII right.
I stopped the bleeding, I think.
That's the best I can do
until I can get you out of here.
I gotta get that door open.
- Gordon.
- Maybe I can get the hinges off.
Gordon.
Idiots forgot to search me.
Is this another one of your plans?
No.
Ladies and gentlemen,
as you by now have surmised.
There's been a change in the program.
Tonight we are proud to present
the six merry Gothamites
of Squatter's Row
and Martin from
the Falcone home and school
for orphans, in our rendition of
the meat pie tango.
(TANGO MUSIC PLAYING)
Bob.
Fricks.
Trish.
Nunuh.
Cyrano.
Vincent.
You have it coming
You only have yourself to blame
If you would've been fair
If you would've been keen
I bet you these pies
wouldn't taste the same
Enough! Where are the other children?
If you hurt them, I swear...
(ALL SCREAMING)
Rude, I'm not finished.
Sit down.
Pull it out,
and the next one's in her eye.
Oswald, no.
Don't.
Now, to answer your question, my dear,
the other children and your staff
are safely locked in the kitchen.
Despite appearances, I am not an animal.
Martin, may we continue?
You have all fed upon the poor
of Gotham for years.
Now, you're going to know
what they taste like.
Please open your envelopes
and look at the photographs inside.
Come on.
Open them!
Who is Trish?
Well, I thought you should see
who you are eating.
Bob, Fricks, Trish,
Nunuh, Cyrano, and Vincent
all deserve our gratitude.
S0, these pies are...
People. Yup, they're people pies.
People.
And you're all going to eat them.
(ALL GROAN IN nnscusr)
Absolutely not.
Okay.
Let's try this again.
No!
Eat, orl kill the boy.
But he'sjust an orphan.
What did you say?
Well, these are made of people.
For God's sake.
You can't expect us, I mean...
S0 they kill some urchin.
What a waste of a good pie.
But I do applaud the sentiment.
Especially, as you, Mr. Cobblepot,
are the reason I'm here.
Me? Why?
I could've chosen any gathering
of wealthy Gothamites
who've gotten fat upon the poor,
but you,
with your Pax Penguina.
You are the biggest glutton of them all.
You have gorged yourself
on this city's heart.
Its lungs, its liver.
Why should today be any different?
Now, eat, little penguin. Eat.
Eat the pies or the boy dies.
(RETCHING)
If you don't all eat.
I will hunt you down and kill you all!
Now, that's what I like to see.
And as mother always used to say.
"Nobody leaves
until every plate is clean."
It's a compliment to the chef.
And I love compliments.
And Ms. Falcone...
Mangia, signorina.
Only if you don't hurt him.
Can you help me?
Yes.
(GROANS)
No!
He'II kill the kid!
Get off of me!
Martin!
Jim!
Get out of here!
G0!
Come on, Jim.
Don't give up.
You will ruin everything.
Should be better.
How is your hand?
I'II be fine.
How's Martin?
He's stronger than he looks.
You paid off the mayor
to make Jim Gordon captain.
Yes.
And you want me to believe
that you did this out of friendship.
To save me.
Itried to talk you
out of the license program,
you wouldn't listen.
There seemed no other way.
Of course, it's equally plausible
that you are my enemy
intent upon my destruction.
You could choose to see it that way.
The choice is yours, Oswald.
Well,
whatever your actual reasoning,
you went behind my back.
I would be justified in killing you.
But what you were
going to do for Martin.
That was real.
Don't ever betray me again.
Neveh
I will abandon the licenses.
But Jim Gordon cannot be captain.
Pick someone else then.
Garden's less than nothing to me.
Oh, my God, look!
- It's the Pyg!
It's really him.
CROWD: Bye, bye, piggy, bye, bye.
- REPORTER 1: Captain Gordon!
- REPORTER 2: Captain Gordon!
- Captain Gordon!
Is that the Pyg?
Did you really catch him?
The suspect known as the Pyg
is in custody.
Detective Vanessa Harper
is on her way to Gotham General
and is expected to make a full recovery.
The GCPD kept its promise.
Captain Gordon.
Yes?
Thank you.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Come on.
Hey, Alfred!
How was your walk?
Everybody out now.
Nobody move.
This is not your house.
If I want my friends to stay.
They're staying.
Like hell they are.
Dude, your butler
is a little out of line.
Have you been
hitting the sherry, Jeeves?
You have no idea what extreme danger
you are now in, son.
If I was you, I would walk away.
Yeah, whatever.
Meet us at the club.
Come on, driver will take us.
Well, you...
You certainly showed
a new side of yourself today
- haven't you, Master Bruce?
- Save it, Alfred.
You tell me a story
about you and my Dad,
and I'm supposed to get all weepy.
You don't know what I'm going through.
You and I are nothing alike.
Then talk to me.
Let me know how I can help you.
You can't!
Like you said. I did what I did.
I killed Ra's.
I avenged my parents' death,
and guess what?
Nothing changed.
It made no difference.
So then what did I do it for?
How can you help that?
I can help with the way
that you're feeling.
But you need to talk to me.
You have to face up
to who you really are.
Stop telling me who I am.
I know who I am.
And if you really want to help me,
you can stop trying to be my father,
and you can be my butler.
Clean this place up.
Tommy!
You're the hero of the day.
I was just doing myjob.
I know you hate me for what I did,
but you deserve to be captain.
I went to your father for help.
I knew what I was getting into.
It doesn't mean I have to like it.
But you accept it.
Because I do deserve it.
Just like Gotham deserves law and order.
And I'm gonna make sure it gets it.
You don't think I want that, too?
I'm not your enemy, Jim.
I never will be.
Did you find anything out?
"I saw Sofia
"kissing the policeman."
Is this true?
Martin, you are a good friend.
As for Sofia,
she will answer for what she's done.
I swear.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English Template