Previously onGotham...
It's a miracle.
- How do you feel?
- Different.
His name is Will Thomas.
Detective Gordon,
my friends, you'll save them.
Say hello to Butch.
No!
Gordon comes with me.
I'll take his head,
and you can have the rest of him.
This is what got you all hot
and bothered?
Crazy bitch!
Not all square yet, though.
You're going to help me do
what we all know needs doing.
- What's that?
- Kill Penguin.
- You made it?
- Show me what you got.
250 apartments.
Once the kids we liberated moved in,
word got out pretty fast
that there was a safe place
to live in the city.
You wanted to know
where the Street Demonz base was.
- Where is everybody!
- Holy crap.
What about that?
Penguin did this.
Penguin, our hero
He knows, no fear, oh.
He brings us joy and cheer, oh.
Oh Penguin, our king
Oh Penguin, our Penguin
He's brave and clever and kind
With a strong resourceful mind
He rules our land all day
In the most magnificent way
Oh Penguin, oh Penguin
Oh Penguin, our king
Oh Penguin, our king, oh Penguin
Production is steady, Mr. Cobblepot.
Our stores contain 512 loaves
of bread,
2,001l of filtered water,
400,232 bullets, and...
Penn.
- Why is my counter tenor out cold?
- I'm sorry, Mr. Cobblepot.
Everyone was working through
the night in the bullet factory.
We've been shorthanded,
since people started defecting.
Defecting?
You've been holding out on me, Penn.
A thousand apologies, I... I simply
couldn't stand seeing you upset
while you were recovering.
Tell me everything!
Rumor is they've fled to a place
called Haven,
in Jim Gordon's sector.
My subjects are fleeing
to Jim Gordon?
After he shot me?
What of my bounty on Gordon's head?
We've had trouble finding takers.
The gangs are too disorganized.
And ordinary people, well,
they love him, sir.
They should love me.
Without me, this entire island
would sink into chaos!
It's not just us.
People from every territory
are fleeing to Haven.
Finally, breakfast!
The Street Demonz.
To what do I owe this honor?
You hit our stronghold
and killed our men!
Not just us.
You hit the Lo Boyz
and the Undead too.
- Did I now?
- You tagged the scenes with graffiti
that said "Penguin was here!"
You dolt!
If I wanted to start a gang war,
you'd all be dead.
I wouldn't leave a few
and sign my name.
Someone wanted you to attack me.
That's a good point.
We didn't really think this through.
Well, there'll be plenty of time
for thinking
when my men are ripping out
your fingernails.
- Chain them up!
- Wait! Wait!
Tighten our borders.
No one in or out
or it's your head!
That's right, Edward.
It's Mr. Penn's head.
It's his head.
You're a good dog.
Word of this place is spreading
like a bad case of the clap.
We've got refugees coming in
from every territory in Gotham.
Can you blame them?
You saw what it was like out there.
People being starved and terrorized.
Used by the gangs as slave labor.
You think those same gangs
aren't gonna want them back?
Sooner or later, they're gonna come
looking for us.
Let them.
Hey, I get it.
But after our excursion
through Nightmare-town last week,
- we hardly have any ammo left.
- Sorry.
- And we barely have any food.
- Okay, all right.
This is the only safe place left
in Gotham.
I'm not turning people away.
I was afraid you were gonna say that.
- Hey, how you feeling? How are...
- I'm fine.
You getting any sleep?
You've been going full-tilt
for months.
Carrying the weight of everyone.
Share the load.
We can't have you fall apart.
Thanks.
I'm okay.
Please tell me some good news.
Water purification system repurposed
from Wayne Enterprises tech.
I know it's a drop in the bucket,
but every bit helps.
The last can of beans.
I ain't had my rations yet!
Hey. Break it up. Break it up.
Break it up.
For all the new people here.
Everyone is welcome in Haven.
But there are rules,
and one of them is we leave
the fighting outside.
The government already thinks
we don't deserve help.
We have to show otherwise.
Gangs want to tear themselves
apart outside, that's their business.
In here, in Haven...
we help each other survive.
Your speech worked.
For now.
What happens when they find out
the government abandoned them?
Sorry.
For what?
Jim, you're holding
this place together.
You're giving these people hope.
Hope can only go so far.
Not to put more on your plate,
but the kid whose friends
you saved from the slavers,
his bunkmates say
he's been having nightmares.
Last night he fell off his bed
half asleep and broke his arm.
Maybe you could talk to him.
Hey.
Don't feel like joining
the other kids?
We can't even begin to imagine
what you've been through.
But it's over, you're safe now.
I promise, I will never let anyone
hurt you ever again.
All right?
I got something for you.
My rations.
Pineapple.
Hang in there.
I'll come check on you later, okay?
Selina?
One second.
What are you doing out of bed?
The doctor said you need rest.
Does it look like I need rest?
No, but...
Look.
Whatever Ivy's root did to me,
I've never felt better.
So, now I have to find the freak
who shot me.
I've been looking for Jeremiah
since the bridges blew.
I haven't found a thing.
Right, but there have never been
refugees in the Green Zone before.
These people come from
all over Gotham, Bruce.
Someone has to know something.
I want to find Jeremiah
just as much as you do.
But even if we find him,
he's had months to fortify himself.
We can't go after him alone.
You scared, Bruce?
Of course I'm scared.
Jeremiah shot you to get to me.
He almost killed you.
I won't lose you.
I'm not yours to lose.
You can't stop me
from going after Jeremiah,
but I am asking you for help.
We take him down, we do it right.
We bring him back here,
and he's stands trial
for turning Gotham into a madhouse.
What?
I was hoping I could count on you.
I heard rumors about Jeremiah
in the Dark Zone.
But, who knows if they're true.
- The Dark Zone?
- On the other end of the island.
It's chaos.
Ruled by those who've lost their
minds since the bridges went down.
They said Jeremiah is there,
gathering followers.
Sounds like a lead.
No.
You can't go there. You'll die.
We've fought Jeremiah before.
You don't understand.
If you go to the Dark Zone, Jeremiah
is the least of your worries.
Everyone there is insane.
Look at what they did to my friend.
Penn! Where the...
Penguin, my hero
He having, no fear, oh.
-He brings us joy and cheer, oh.
-Stop.
Stop.
Where is my staff? Where is Mr. Penn?
They having to defected.
To Haven.
My guards didn't stop them?
My guards too?
Edward?
Edward, Edward!
They took my dog?
Rumors say pup went willingly.
Lie.
You're in luck, my friend.
Jim Gordon is luring people
from every territory in Gotham.
Including yours.
As our interests are now aligned,
I have decided that you may live.
He's been dead since yesterday.
Contact the Lo Boyz and the Undead.
You have men, vehicles, and gas.
I have the bullets.
It's time we paid a visit
to this Haven.
Right after I put on some clothes.
Jim!
Border guards just radioed.
Penguin broke through the barricades.
Street Demonz, other gangs,
rolling with him.
They're heading for Haven.
We can beat them there. Load up.
What the hell are we gonna do?
We don't have more than a dozen
bullets between us.
You're right.
If we get a firefight, we're dead.
Okay, I'm gonna need you to go
get some help.
I'm not sure we got any friends left.
I'm hoping we still have one.
So, this is the Dark Zone.
They should call it the Dull Zone.
Place is dead.
What?
You seem yourself again.
I'm glad.
Wait, I know this block.
Used to be the posh part of town.
Everyone with money got out.
You didn't.
I had a reason to stay.
Oh, God.
Help me, please.
- Come on!
- Wait! Wait! Wait!
- Oh, God.
- Get down!
Now we know who carved
"kill" into that guy's chest.
Do you think they know anything
about Jeremiah?
Let's find someone else to ask.
Let's go.
Before they see us.
Kill.
We're not here for you.
We're looking for Jeremiah Valeska.
Kill you.
Kill Jeremiah!
I don't think this guy's much
of a talker, Bruce.
What do you want to do?
Easy.
Find the schoolyard's biggest bully.
And kick his teeth in!
The chicky-chick is mine!
Selina.
Mine eyes have seen the glory
Of the coming of the Lord
He is trampling out the vintage
Where the grapes of wrath
are stored...
Everyone inside!
Inside.
Let's go, get inside.
What's going on, Captain Gordon?
Inside. Go.
Hold your fire.
Well, if it isn't my old friend,
Mr. Penn.
And the Gertrud Kapel
put Memorial Choir!
It is so nice to see
some familiar faces!
You shouldn't have come here,
Oswald.
Oh, well, perhaps you shouldn't have
stolen my people
or my dog.
Every refugee is here
of their own free will,
and under the protection of the GCPD.
Edward, Edward!
Come here.
Right now!
I will make this very simple, Jim.
You return our people, and Edward,
and an apology,
or we will destroy this little
commune of yours
and salt the earth
on which it stands.
The answer is no. Now turn around
unless you want a bloodbath.
Let me explain something, Jim.
I heard about your little excursion
through the territories.
So, whatever ammo you stole from me,
I'm betting you used it up,
which means you're bluffing.
You want to test us, Oswald?
I'm sure my men could use
the target practice.
Slice and dice, little chicky.
You look soft.
You look like 300lbs of ugly.
Kill and kill.
Where's Jeremiah?
- Where is Jeremiah?
- Jeremiah?
Tell me where Jeremiah is
or my face is going to be the last
thing you ever see.
Old Town North, okay?
We don't mess with him.
Old Town North?
You wouldn't lie to me, would you?
It's the truth.
Selina, he's had enough.
He's had enough
when I say he's had enough.
What the hell?
You won.
It's over.
Old Town North, see?
That was easy.
What are we waiting for?
You said they'll be out of bullets.
He's bluffing, you idiot.
How do you know?
I know Jim Gordon.
But if you require a demonstration,
three of you, march.
But, they have guns.
So, do I
and mine is most certainly loaded.
On my mark.
Make them count.
Well, Jim,
it seems you are out of ammo,
after all.
Now, if you don't want your men
to die in a hail of bullets,
you know what to do.
Fine. On the count of three.
- One, two...
- All right.
All right. Put them down.
Put them down.
Selina, what was that back there?
They had to know I was serious.
You didn't have to hurt him
like that.
He was trying to kill me, Bruce,
just like Jeremiah tried to kill me.
So, as far as I'm concerned...
he got off easy.
Whose side are you on, Bruce?
Yours.
Always.
Then let's do what we came here
to do.
Looks like we're close.
When I see him,
I'm gonna tear his throat out.
Selina.
Welcome, pilgrims,
to The Church of Jeremiah Valeska.
The only place
where you faithful pilgrims
can become your very best selves.
Who the hell is that?
I don't know.
I bet she knows
where Jeremiah is, though.
Stay here.
I'm gonna get a closer look.
No.
We do this together, Selina.
That was the deal.
Funny, I don't remember saying that.
Now, I know you've come from far
and wide to meet the man himself.
But first, he requires a show
of faith.
Don't be shy.
Jeremiah awaits.
Who is ready?
Lovely.
Jeremiah will be so happy.
But remember,
he wants only the most
faithful followers.
And you all have a chance
to prove yourself,
right up those stairs.
And the rest of you, get out!
Selina.
Wait.
I want to meet Jeremiah.
You don't look like
one of Jeremiah's worshipers.
I have witnessed his work firsthand.
I will never forget it.
Then right this way.
You're gonna regret this.
Strong words,
for someone who is out of options.
First, I'm gonna make you watch
while I destroy Haven.
Then, I'm gonna shoot you
and leave you for dead,
just like you did to me.
Sound fair?
If the government liberates
the city and finds out about this,
you'll be at the top of their list.
Wake up, Jim.
The government has abandoned us.
The only law in Gotham is power,
and that power belongs to me.
We have children here, families.
What happens when the gangs
take them?
They probably go back
to being slaves, I guess.
My people, on the other hand,
will go back to their regular lives,
with their bellies full of gruel
and their heads
full of wonderful thoughts
about their grand protector, me.
If this is about revenge against me,
do your worst.
But leave the refugees out of it.
So heroic.
Almost tempting.
But I think I'm gonna stick
to my original plan.
Jim's gonna die, isn't he, boy?
Oh, you're a good dog, yes, you are.
Mr. Cobblepot.
Stop. That one belongs to me.
No can do.
You sacrificed one of my guys
calling the cop's bluff.
So, what?
I said, he's mine.
Oh, thank you, Mr. Cobblepot.
Then, how about we take
your territory?
And your bullet factory.
Penn! Penn!
I'm sorry, Mr. Cobblepot.
You fool!
This never would have happened
if you stayed with me.
Why did you leave?
Everyone hated you.
You will pay for this!
Hey, Penguin,
you got something on your face.
Let me go! We had a deal!
Shut your mouth...
or the next thing that comes
out your mouth is a bullet.
Man, you are on fire!
I take it that didn't work out
the way you'd hoped.
Barbara?
Hey, you in here?
You've gotten good at that.
Haven't you heard, Harvey?
No men in the Sirens past midnight.
Sorry to bust up ladies' night,
but Jim Gordon needs your help.
Perhaps it's time Golden Boy
learned to save himself.
And aren't you tired
of playing sidekick?
See, I don't see it that way.
Me and Jim are friends.
We're fighting for the same thing.
It seemed like you got that.
You know, I remember
when you first partnered up.
He, the idealistic rookie.
You, the cynical veteran.
You were sane.
Now you carry his laundry.
Do you ever wonder what your life
might've been like
if you'd never met Jim Gordon?
I'd be dead, or wishing I was.
You're delusional, Harvey.
Just like all the sad saps
who think the government
is just gonna sail in and save them.
Maybe, and look, I know
you've had your differences with Jim,
but if you don't help him now,
- Penguin and the other gangs...
- Penguin?
You should've opened with that.
Let's move!
It's not working.
We need to find a way
to cut these bindings.
Well, I'm not helping you, Jim.
You are the reason
I'm in this predicament.
You have taken everything from me.
Keep your voice down.
I kept people safe.
I protected them from chaos.
They should have loved me.
Instead, they came here,
to this pigsty,
to be covered in fleas and filth.
Why? What makes this place
so special?
Well, for one thing,
it's far away from you.
Oh, that's rich, Jim.
You should be proud of yourself
for that one.
Quiet.
I think I saw someone place
a stash there.
- Who is that?
- A friend.
Just act normal.
I know it's a stretch.
Hey.
Bingo.
I'm gonna get out of here, Jim.
And I'm gonna watch these animals
tear this place to the ground.
So, you make your way back
to your territory, then what?
You don't think that eventually,
these gangs are gonna come after you?
We need to take them out.
Right here, right now.
Now, how do we pick it up?
I'll have to have a word
with the cleaning lady.
Mind your step, pilgrims.
But first,
the main attraction.
Six-shooters.
Bang, bang.
Each of you get one gun,
and one bullet.
What is this?
Like I said, a show of faith.
But if
you're ch...ch...ch...chicken...
Try me.
Oh, my little pilgrims.
This will make Jeremiah so happy.
Now,
on the count of three.
One.
Two.
Chicken poo.
Just seeing if y'all were listening.
Three!
Well, well, well.
You disappoint me, curls.
I had such high hopes for you.
What, with that
cocky little swagger and all.
I'm just not a mindless idiot
who's willing to get shot
in the head for nothing.
Hear that?
Curls is here to judge all of us,
to judge Jeremiah and his methods.
What a fitting reminder.
To outsiders,
Jeremiah's methods
may look like madness,
but we believers know,
his methods will be our salvation.
Now...
I need to have a word
with our friend.
The rest of you
get straight A's.
Please proceed
and be reborn.
What's the matter?
Don't you want to meet Jeremiah?
I do.
I'm just not willing
to play your little psychotic game.
But, baby, it's so fun.
If it's so fun, why don't you play?
Don't you get it?
I have.
The bullet's still inside.
Rattling around this old noggin
of mine.
Ping. Ping.
Ping.
Boy, do I feel it
when the nights get cold.
You're insane.
No.
I was willing to look death
in the face,
to allow the old me to die.
It's the gift Jeremiah's
brother Jerome gave him.
And the gift he wants
for all his followers.
Don't you want to experience
this gift for yourself?
I know I want you to.
Selina.
You know me.
There isn't a single part
of Bruce Wayne's life
that we don't know about.
His joys, his disappointments,
his desires.
But just like Bruce wasn't ready
to embrace his true self,
looks like you aren't either.
Maybe.
But one thing
Jeremiah did teach me is I...
hate having a gun pointed
at my face.
Oh, puddin', aren't you delicious.
Don't call me puddin'.
There you go, Selina.
I knew you had it in you.
All it took was a little kick
in the pants.
Where's Jeremiah?
Selina, drop the gun.
Oh... oh, your boyfriend's worried.
But I still don't think
you have what it takes.
Yeah?
Well, let's see what happens
when someone deserves
to get shot in the head.
Selina, stop!
Wait. You're bleeding.
If you know what's good for you,
you will let me go.
We need to get you patched up.
- What are you doing?
- I have been doing it your way.
I'm gonna do it my way.
Selina!
Look at those biceps.
I need him to build barricades.
Nah, homie. This guy's got cage match
written all over him.
I'll give you two of mine
in exchange.
How about this.
Drop your guns,
and I won't shoot you.
How the hell did he get free?
Don't matter. He's bluffing again.
I'm afraid he's not.
Neither am I.
Come on out, boys.
Yes, Edward, I killed the bad men.
- Penguin did.
- Penguin shot the gang leader.
We're safe now.
Penguin! Penguin! Penguin!
Penguin! Penguin!
You'd said we'd be safe here.
We were better off
where we came from.
Give it a rest, he saved us!
All right, listen up.
- Listen to me.
- For what?
Listen to me!
I know today was a hard day.
And I can't say
there won't be others.
But we won.
We got Penguin's guns,
his ammunition.
We survived.
And as long as we survive,
hope survives in Gotham.
I think that's worth fighting for.
So do I.
There's work to be done...
wounded to be cared for.
Food, water to be doled out.
Tomorrow's another day.
Go to.
Captain, we've got Penguin outside.
All right, give me a minute.
Hey.
That was a brave thing you did there.
We wouldn't have escaped without you.
You saved me and my friends.
I wanted to help.
I can't be everywhere at once.
I'm gonna need people
I can trust watching over this place.
Maybe...
you could be my deputy
here in Haven.
Thanks.
Because, honestly,
I'm allergic to pineapple.
Go get 'em, Deputy.
Jim, is this really necessary?
I did just save,
I don't know, hundreds of people.
After endangering them to begin with.
Forgive me
if I wanted to play it safe.
Still, I do hope that there are
no hard feelings.
You did the right thing today,
Oswald.
You're free to go,
just don't make me regret it.
Jim!
Harvey.
- Hi, Pengy.
- Jim!
- Hold your fire.
- Bye, Pengy.
- Barbara, no. No.
- Get out of the way! Now!
Outside of the Green Zone,
he's fair game, but not here.
Last chance.
Move now or you get my first bullet.
I'm not moving.