Previously onGotham...
You are cop in everything but name.
So even Gotham is not my job anymore.
The person who comes into contact
with my blood, it changes him.
It affects every person differently.
My God. They really want me as Mayor.
How would you know I would win?
I believe in you, Oswald,
even when you don't believe
in yourself.
- Miss Kringle.
- No, my name is Isabella.
You remind me of someone.
I'm Edward Nygma.
Past is the past.
I know that we can't change the past.
But there's difference between
moving on and letting go.
Who do you love?
Or I shoot both of them
which would be such a thrill.
Kill Lee.
I'm so sorry this happened.
Stop the press.
Tough guy Jim Gordon
sheds tear for Valerie Vale.
How're you feeling?
Like a bullet went
through my insides.
- You don't have any whisky, do you?
- Sorry.
You get a girl shot
and don't even bring her booze.
You got a lot of nerve.
I never meant for you to get hurt.
You did.
You wanted to save Lee.
I wanted to saved you both.
Yeah, but you could
only save one of us.
That's why you told Tetch to kill Lee
because you knew
he would do the opposite.
Oldest trick in the book.
At least tell me you caught him.
He's still in the wind. Listen.
- Vale, it's not what you think.
- It is.
You love Lee.
Which means we're done.
- If there's anything I can do...
- No.
No, Tetch was right.
You're nothing but trouble.
So let me get this straight,
you're about to be in possession
of some kind of virus.
Yes.
It's blood based and can be
a little unpredictable.
It can take weeks
for symptoms to manifest.
Oh.
This...
is an accelerant.
Mix it with the blood, wham bam.
That virus will hit them
like a semi going 90.
The Red Queen.
She's a blend of psychotropic plants.
Thought she'd be a big hit.
Turns out she's only good at
putting people in the looney bin.
- I'll take her.
- That stuff's no joke.
At first, it incapacitates you.
Then an hour into the trip
completely fries your brain.
Perfect.
I'm looking to side-line someone
before this evening's event.
That will do it.
Hey, what exactly are you planning?
This city tore my love from me
so I'm plunging it into insanity.
And that's where I discovered
my love of books?
I never thought a fractured
tibia would launch
my library career but it did.
Fun fact of the tibia is second
largest bone in the body.
Second only to the femur.
You have exquisite femurs.
- Morning paper.
- Yeah.
- What time is it?
- Oh, it's just past six.
Edward...
this past 12 hours have been
the best of my life.
When can we meet me again?
What can't you have for breakfast
or lunch?
Dinner.
- I'd love to.
- Delightful.
Meet me at the Mayor's
Mansion at eight.
I understand that one is expected
to wait 24 hours
before filing a missing
person's report,
- but sir, I'm the Mayor...
- Oswald.
I am so sorry.
When you didn't come home
I assumed the worst.
I'm so glad you're okay.
Better than okay.
I met someone.
I think I'm in love!
Hey! Hey, you can't be down here.
Oh, I disagree.
I don't understand
why we're doing all this, boss.
Wasn't plugging Gordon's
girlfriend enough?
Jim Gordon wasn't the only one
responsible for my sister's death.
Gotham ripped Alice from my loving
arms and turned her against me.
What better way to make this city pay
than by spreading my dear,
dead sister's legacy?
Oh, Alice.
Well, it's quite the operation
you've got going on here,
isn't it, Master Bruce?
- Do you need a hand?
- I got it.
Right.
- What time to expect Miss Kyle?
- 6.00, I think.
I see. All right.
She's coming, Alfred.
And Alfred...
Yes, yes, I know it.
I'll make myself scarce, so I'll give
you the privacy that you need.
Within earshot.
And the lights on.
Well, I got bad news and worse.
Skip the preamble.
It was definitely Tetch
and his two dum-dums.
And? What about Alice's body?
The eggheads here have had her
body on ice since it arrived.
Her blood's frozen but still viable.
- The second Tetch heats it up...
- He has himself the virus.
How the hell did he even get in here?
The old fashioned way,
somebody let him in.
I got an unconscious lab tech
and a missing guard.
My money's on the guard.
Shouldn't you be
at the hospital with Vale?
She's fine. Give me the rundown.
Oh, so I take it
you're re-joining the force?
I just wanna help.
There's no reason
I need to be a cop to do that.
As long as I'm captain of the GCPD,
you do.
I'm tired of giving you slack.
Get the hell off my crime scene
before I throw your ass in lock-up.
Biehls. Alban.
Escort Mr. Gordon off the premises.
If he resists,
book him for obstruction.
I'll go on my own.
Oh, hey, hey, hey. No.
I see that look in your eye.
Don't try to solve this by yourself.
Then help me.
If Tetch has Alice's blood,
we don't have much time.
No, I'm not gonna aid you
with your solo bull crap kamikaze
missions anymore.
Tetch murdered four people yesterday.
He shot Vale. I can't just
let him get away with it.
Nobody's asking you to.
But Barnes is right.
Either be a cop or don't.
What are you so afraid of?
Is that what you think?
That I'm afraid?
You know, you should go
to the hospital, be with Vale.
And let those of us who wanna
wear the badge do our damn jobs.
You are going to cut
quite the fine figure
at the Founders dinner tonight.
Yes.
Did you know that this dinner
has been thrown annually
for over 200 years?
It was started by
the first families of Gotham.
Only the most powerful
citizens are invited.
It's a shame I don't get a plus one.
I can't go anyway. I have a date.
With the woman
you claim to be in love with
after only knowing for a few hours?
The heart keeps its own time.
I'm partial to the purple.
The brocade brings out my eyes.
Are you sure you aren't mistaking
infatuation for love?
You did say she's the spitting
image of Kringle.
Isabella's beautiful and smart.
So she bears a passing
resemblance to Kristin?
It's just the universe telling me.
Telling me I have a second
chance of love.
Where did you say she works?
The Main Public Library.
You read about the brocade.
Do you mind if I skedaddle?
I just need to pick up
a few things for tonight.
Who am I to stand in the way of love?
The missing guard from the lab.
Called in sick.
My gut says he's lying.
Oh, he's certainly
no candidate for sainthood.
Gambling. Petty theft.
Might I have a word, Captain?
Bring him in.
What is it?
I just heard
from the head of Virology
at the Biomedical Facility.
This is about the tests they were
running on Alice's Tetch's blood?
- Yes, in the first trial...
- One of the rats went off
the rails and murdered the rest,
they know.
Doctor Thompkins told me.
But she thought,
there might have been an anomaly.
I'm afraid the second study
proves otherwise.
As in the first study,
the rats showed increased strength
and agility but, by week two.
The rats were exhibiting
manic tendencies.
Violent rage.
By the study's end,
every trace of their original
demeanour had vanished.
- I assume they're working on a cure?
- Yes, but it could take years.
And we all have hours...
Damn it.
If this virus gets set free...
- We have to find Tetch. Now.
- Yes.
Watch closely, Deever.
Isn't science marvellous?
Gravity, a few heaters and voila!
The last drops of coagulated blood
become cocktail mix.
Bravo, Alice.
Truly, your best work.
- You're kidding me.
- Please calm down.
He said, "Kill Lee."
- He knew Tetch wouldn't.
- How?
How could he possibly
have known that?
It, somehow,
he got inside Tetch's head.
And he knew that
he would do the opposite
- of what he told him to do.
- I see.
So why would Gordon
offer up the woman
he's dating in the place
of my fiancé?
Mario, stop it.
We have so much to be thankful for.
I just wanna move past this.
Fine.
But Jim Gordon is the reason
you were in danger to begin with.
- I want him out of our lives.
- Of course.
I came by to bring this to Vale.
I gotta get back to the ER.
He's angry.
I get that.
He has every reason to be.
I figured you'd be out
chasing down Tetch.
Barnes banned me.
No badge. No investigation.
It's never stopped you before.
They closed ranks. Even Bullock.
He says I'm refusing the badge
because I'm afraid.
Jim. I know what you did. Last night.
When you told Tetch to kill me,
you knew he would shoot Vale.
No. I'm sorry. That's not true.
At least have the decency
to be honest with me.
I am being honest.
I wanted to save Vale.
Bullock was right,
you are afraid.
- Hello, there.
- Mr. Mayor, what an honour.
How can I help you?
I am attending the Founders
dinner this evening
and I wanted to brush up
on the history
of Gotham's first families.
My chief of staff suggested
I come here.
I think you might know him.
Yes. I know Edward.
We just met but...
well, I feel I've known
him my whole life.
- How romantic.
- Oh. Listen to me. Blathering on.
You wanted a book.
I'm so glad you appreciate Ed.
Really, I should thank you
for brightening Ed's spirits.
He has been so down
since he got out of Arkham.
Edward was in Arkham?
You don't know?
It was front page news.
I stick to books.
Don't people typically go
to Arkham for murder?
I make it a policy not to gossip
about staff but yes.
Uncanny how much you look like her.
It's that swan-like neck.
Ed loves a neck.
Well, thank you for the book.
It was a pleasure meeting you.
Hey. Hey!
Hey!
The tea party was part one.
I wanna have a lot more fun.
I had my way with you.
Now, Gotham's up for round two.
What the hell are you talking about?
Why, I'm going to dismantle
your beloved city,
from the top on down.
And you can't stop me.
Enjoy the trip.
It's gonna be a bumpy ride.
Watch where you're going.
Of course, Mr. Mayor.
So sorry.
Cretin.
Jim.
Jim!
Finally, Sleeping Beauty stirs.
- Where am I?
- You got dosed, buttercup.
Welcome to your hallucination.
- What are you doing in it?
- Hell, if I know.
Now, we've got a lot
to be getting on with.
I don't have time for this.
See that's the thing
about hallucinations, Jimbo.
You gotta ride out the trip. Bummer?
What exactly does this trip entail?
Well, no one gave me an itinerary.
But knowing what goes on
inside of your head,
it'll be chock full of belly laughs.
Just kidding.
We all know fun isn't your forte.
This is where I face my inner demons?
That's up to you.
Well, go on.
Unless you wanna stay
in this tiny space with me.
I'll take my chances.
Jim.
Jim. Jim.
Bruce.
You don't have much time.
What are you talking about?
- You don't have much time.
- Bruce!
Bruce!
Where did Bruce go?
(Foreign Language)
What?
You never leave your unit behind.
I have to find him.
Bruce! Bruce!
I'm glad you came.
What did you mean when you said
I didn't have much time?
I just wanted you to follow me.
So I could show you that.
Down there.
It's because of you.
Congratulations, Jim. You did it.
You're the hero you always
dreamed of being.
Bruce. Don't.
Your name was on the schedule.
Yeah, I told you.
It was my shift at the Bio-Lab
but I came down with something.
The only thing you're coming down
with, pal, is ten years at Blackgate.
Hey, hey, hey.
That's no way to treat a sick man.
Listen, Sullivan.
Tetch got in using
an employee's key card.
Just show us your card
and you're free to go.
Screw you.
I want a lawyer.
You pigs think
you're such tough guys.
Honest citizens driven mad.
Tearing each other limb from limb
just because you decided
that this city's security
is not your concern!
Tell us what you know
about Jervis Tetch!
Stop! Please! Captain! Captain!
Captain! Captain!
Hey. I thought I was supposed
to be the bad cop here.
A bruiser in a wrestling mask paid me
to hand over my key card
and take the day off.
Promised I wouldn't get in trouble.
Said the cops will be too busy
taking back control of the city.
And? Tell us something
that might actually help.
He was driving a catering van.
Why would the Tweeds
need a catering van?
- Wait. What's the date?
- Friday.
- The date.
- The 27th.
The Founders dinner.
The Archbishop, the Comptroller,
the Mayor all in the same place.
Put together a unit.
And not a word to Gordon.
A drop of blood.
In each one glass.
Makes madmen of the ruling class.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Saving your life. Like you wanted.
The last thing I want
is your lips on my mouth.
Newsflash. Everything
that is happening is in your head.
Which means you made me give you
CPR.
Just like you put me in this really
cheesy nurse's uniform.
That's easily rectified.
Seriously?
One bad encounter with Bruce.
I don't wanna talk about it.
Fine, just don't fall into
a monosyllabic depression because...
we're at the next stop.
I have mixed feelings
about this floor.
I'm afraid to ask.
I'm so glad you're home.
Mum thought you were gonna be late.
Mum owes me a quarter. Mum!
We made a bet
that you were gonna be late.
Frankie had more faith than I did.
Now, go on.
Take those rolls to the table.
How was your trip?
Earth to Jim.
Sorry. You just look so beautiful.
You guys are gross.
Julie, one day
you're gonna love somebody
as much as I love your father.
- Never. Boys are dumb.
- Are not!
You feeling okay, honey?
I'm just glad to be here.
With you guys.
I love you so much.
Does that mean we can get a dog?
You two.
- Sure.
- Yes. You're the best, Dad!
The best!
Just the best, Jim.
No, no, no. No, no, come back!
You look like you need a drink.
Jim.
Open the damn gate, Barbara.
I need to get back to them. To her.
If you're so desperate to have
Thompkins and the two kids,
why're you in that crappy apartment
playing private dick?
Let go of me.
You don't know what the hell
you're talking about.
I know you're lost.
You wanna find your way home?
Play nice.
It's a long way to the basement.
So.
The little minx was a no show?
Well, it seems a frightful shame
to let this beautiful
meal go to waste.
What do you say we wrap it up
and have it for lunch tomorrow.
Hey.
You always bring your butler
along on dates?
All right.
I'll leave you to it.
Excuse me, miss.
You're late.
Stuff came up.
Geez. Chill.
Alfred really outdid himself.
I made all of it. For you.
What's with the attitude?
You stood me up.
I got busy.
Selina, if we're gonna do this,
whatever this is...
I need you to be honest with me.
This. Me and you.
It's weird for me.
Okay? It's weird for me.
It's weird for me too.
So are you gonna cut the cake,
or what?
Of course, I didn't wanna
stand in the way of love,
but this woman would
have been a disaster.
It sounds as if you did
your friend a favour.
I'm sorry,
I have been talking so much.
I never asked your name.
Kathryn.
Just Kathryn.
How did you end up
at the Founders dinner?
- If it's not rude for me to ask.
- Not at all.
I'm from one of Gotham's
oldest families.
And I'm part of a group
which oversees things.
What sort of things?
Everything that matters in Gotham.
We've had our eye on you
for some time, Mr. Cobblepot.
Who exactly are you?
We'll contact you
when the time is right.
Enjoy your evening.
Excuse me, did you notice the rather
severe-looking woman
I was speaking with?
- She said her name...
- Nobody move!
What is this? What is going on?
I'm afraid your evening
has been hijacked, Mr. Mayor.
I see the champagne
didn't leave a mark.
I'm so glad.
For those of you who don't know me,
my name is Jervis Tetch.
I promise not to take up
too much of your time.
But the fact is,
you are the heads of Gotham.
And tonight,
the heads of Gotham will roll.
But first...
a toast.
A drink.
- To your health.
- And if we don't?
Change, my friends, is nigh.
Drink the wine.
Or else you die.
Glasses down. Now! Glasses down!
Oh, my! Is that my dear sister I see?
She's in you, isn't she?
What fun!
Shut up! Shut up!
Last stop.
Don't be scared.
It's not easy to face
who you really are.
I should know.
Do you ever wish you were
the person you used to be?
Do you?
Use this.
Or don't.
It's up to you.
Good luck, Jim.
Sir.
You're looking for this?
- Dad?
- Hey!
It's good to see you, son.
I'm always losing that darn thing.
Get in. We don't wanna be late.
Doctor. Doctor. Some help.
Doctor, he's unconscious.
Doctor Calvi, he's in here.
Jim.
This was beside him.
Red Queen. I've heard of this.
- Give me 20 CC's of Haloperidol.
- Right away, Doctor.
Jim, can you hear me? Jim?
Jim!
Come on, Jimmy.
It's time to go.
- Something wrong?
- No.
I'm just glad to see you.
I missed you. A lot.
Sorry, I haven't been around more.
I heard you got into some
kind of trouble.
You wanna talk about it?
When I was a kid
people would tell me,
"Your dad's a hero."
All I knew was you went to court
every day and every night,
you came home and you played ball
with me while Mum made dinner.
Then I got older.
And I understood you were a hero.
Only for me, it wasn't just
that you'd been a great DA.
Since you got up, day after day...
you faced down the worst
the city had to offer,
but you never brought that home
to Mum and me.
You protected us.
I wanted to be just like you.
Turns out I'm the opposite.
I destroy everything
and everyone around me.
Don't. Come on, Jimmy.
I'm far from perfect.
I've got plenty of darkness
inside me.
I just don't dwell on it.
Focus on the good you can do.
That's what counts.
- That's what I'm trying to do.
- No.
You hide behind self-righteous lone
wolf nonsense because you're afraid.
Why is that?
Badge holds expectations.
People want a hero.
And I'm not.
You know what makes a hero, son?
A man who values protecting
others above protecting himself.
A man who knows his limits
but isn't afraid to fail.
A man who knows when to ask
for help when he needs it.
I wasn't always that man.
But damn it,
didn't stop me from trying.
- I don't know how to be that man.
- Sure you do.
You just have to follow the code.
What? You remember what that is?
No.
The code we Gordons
promise to live by?
No. Why can't I remember?
Because you're lost, son.
You wanna find your way back home?
The answer you're looking
for is in my ring.
Shoot. It's time for me to go.
- No. I wanna talk to you more.
- I can't.
- Someone's coming for me.
- No. Dad.
- No, Dad, please. Don't go. No, Dad.
- I'm proud of you, Jimmy.
Dad.
Jim!
- Jim, can you hear me? Jim.
- Yeah.
Yeah. I can hear you.
It's Haloperidol. Antipsychotic.
You were dosed with a pretty
powerful hallucinogen.
- It was Tetch.
- I know.
Someone saw him leaving the hospital.
You know, you're lucky.
Another minute
and we would've lost you.
Thank you.
- It's my job.
- Doctor Calvi.
We need your signature, please.
I'll get somebody to take the IV out.
Half-hour, a glass of orange juice.
You'll be good to go.
So what I did...
I killed my girlfriend...
who does look rather similar to you.
It was not out of malice or intent.
It was an accident
that I deeply regret.
And I was not gonna tell you this,
- but then...
- Edward.
I know what you did.
You do?
I spent the afternoon reading
every article about you.
You knew what I did and yet,
you still came on this date, anyway?
That's not logical.
Love isn't logical.
I've lived my whole life
inside the pages of books.
Any other men I've dated...
they didn't compare to the lovers
I spent my life with.
Anthony. Cleopatra.
Romeo and Juliet.
Othello and Desdemona.
All of whom died.
Edward.
You're the first to measure up.
You're the one I'm waiting for.
You're not scared of me?
Of course, I am.
Can't you feel how fast
my heart's beating?
Well, Ed, you would not
believe the night I've...
Oswald, good evening.
This is Isabella.
We have met.
Would you excuse me? I am very tired.
Dum spiramus tuebimur.
While we breathe...
we shall defend.
Come in.
Busy?
Just finishing up some
paperwork on Tetch.
He and the Tweeds are safe
and sound in Arkham.
Hopefully, that's the last
we hear from them.
Congratulations.
You did what I couldn't. I mean that.
A humble Jim Gordon.
What do you know?
I heard Tetch sent you on
quite the trip.
If it wasn't for Mario, I'd be dead.
Anyway, I'm not here about that.
I wanna re-join the GCPD.
Why the sudden change of heart?
I made a promise to someone
when I was younger.
I intend to keep that promise.
Good.
We need you here.
I need you here.
Welcome back, Detective.
It seems you left dinner
just in time.
Indeed.
And what did you think
of our new mayor?
My gut says once a criminal,
always a criminal.
Well, keep an eye on him.
Judgement is coming, Kathryn.
For all of us.