Previously on Gotham...
You paid off the mayor to
make Jim Gordon captain.
Don't ever betray me again. Never.
I need to know what Sofia's planning,
and who she is planning it with.
Plain, dumb Ed.
I would like you to go to the Narrows
and bundle him up, bring him back to me.
They're the ones that are the problem.
They work for Penguin.
I would like to announce
that we just quit working for Penguin.
This is your turf, now.
What is he doing to them?
He's cooking them.
They're people pies.
Eat the pies, or the boy dies.
No!
Jim!
The suspect known as
the Pyg is in custody.
The GCPD kept its promise.
I'm not your enemy, Jim.
I never will be.
Did you find anything out?
"I saw Sofia kissing the policeman."
She will answer for what she's done.
Thursday.
Thursday is my day. Thursday's my day.
You can't, you can't be here.
Thursday's my day.
Ooh, yeah.
I don't like that song.
My ma used to beat me to it.
It was playing when I killed her.
So, now, you turn it off.
Or I do the same to you.
Why did your mother beat you?
Were you a naughty boy?
Did you soil your trousers?
Was it...
a stutter?
Perhaps?
Open the gate, open the
gate, open the gate now.
Try it.
Everybody calm down.
Back off. Back off of the gate.
I really wish you hadn't done that.
I paid a fortune to look this good.
The gate is locked!
Everybody, just stay where you are.
All right, open the gate. That's enough.
Okay, it's over.
Just open the gate and let us in.
The doctors at Arkham took
these after the fight.
The Pyg had titanium
plates surgically grafted
onto the bones of his face.
The result of which radically
changed his appearance.
When we booked him, his
fingerprints were burnt off.
I've seen it before on criminals
that want to hide their identity.
But never anything like this.
And that's not all.
The doctors also noted scar tissue
behind his ears and along his neckline,
indicating he's had multiple surgeries.
That explains why we couldn't
I.D. him off his photo.
This doesn't make any sense.
The Pyg is a glory hound.
Everything he's done,
it's all been about
grabbing the spotlight.
Classic sociopath behavior.
So why doesn't he want us
to know who he really is?
Now is the time he should be
taking credit for his crimes.
Can you use this X-ray
to reconstruct his face?
See what he looked like
before he had any work done?
It's certainly possible,
but it will take some time.
Get started.
I want to know who the Pyg really is.
Morning, Cap.
Harper.
How's the shoulder?
This? Oh, just a scratch.
You got a visitor.
Thanks.
Sofia.
What are you doing here?
I haven't heard from you in a few days.
I didn't realize I was supposed to call.
I figured, after the other night,
we were gonna start
seeing each other again.
We're not.
I get it.
You're worried about Penguin
finding out about us,
that I made you captain.
You don't have to be.
I already told him.
I'm sorry, you did what?
I have it under control.
Is that what you think?
It's what I know.
I'm going to remove
Penguin from the picture,
and when I do, I want us to be together.
It's not gonna work, Sofia.
Even if Penguin is out of the picture,
I just don't see a way
forward for us. I'm sorry.
I run the dog races.
He runs the cock fights.
Now he's coming in,
muscling on my business.
I got mouths to feed.
You race those dogs again,
and I'll slit your damn throat.
All right. Enough.
If she stabs him, it solves the issue.
I started this court so we could
work out disputes peacefully.
This is how things are gonna be
done from now on, understood?
Now, you're both admitting
to having down months.
Seems the only solution
is for you to partner up.
Both of you work
together, you stay strong.
Okay. That's settled. Thank you.
Moving on. Next.
Wait.
How's your daughter?
Fever came down.
Thanks to you, Doc.
Good.
These bums are so lucky to have you.
You cure their children,
you solve their problems.
I haven't forgotten about you, Ed.
Yes, you say that and
yet, I remain a moron.
I said I would fix you.
And I will.
Make way.
Oh... out of my way!
Out of my way, I need to see the doc!
What happened?
Sampson sent his thugs to my
shop demanding protection money.
I told them no.
I said this is your neighborhood now.
I'm sorry, who's Sampson?
He controls the territory
just south of here.
All right, go to the clinic.
I'll stitch you up.
You know, this was bound to happen.
You're a new leader in the Narrows.
Sampson's just testing you.
But, you have to show
him and these people
that you can't be pushed around.
What, should I send Grundy
to rip his arms off?
Look at him.
It's what he lives for.
I'm asking these people
to settle things amicably.
I can't just be a hypocrite
and send Grundy every
time I have a problem.
Okay. What would you like to do?
Hello, Sofia.
Oswald, what a pleasant surprise.
Oh, I assure you,
dear,
there is nothing pleasant about it.
I have continually
been suspicious of you.
And yet,
at every turn,
you always had the perfect explanation
to put my mind at ease.
But now,
I finally have proof
that you are my enemy.
You lied to me.
You told me you hated Gordon.
You are his lover.
Martin saw you kissing
him after the party.
That's-that's ridiculous.
I'm not sure what Martin thought he saw,
but I can assure you, it was no kiss.
Enough of your lies.
Our entire friendship,
the intimacies we shared,
they were nothing more
than a pathetic charade.
Well, Oswald, I swear.
I swear, I care for you deeply.
Ha! Oh, I wish that were true.
Mm. But...
after Martin told me
about you and Gordon,
I did a little digging
into your boyfriend.
Interesting, he took a trip
down South shortly before
you arrived in Gotham.
Coincidence?
I think not.
So you see,
I know that the two of you have
been plotting to destroy me
from the very beginning.
Bravo, Oswald.
Do you know I was warned
you were a mastermind?
Turns out, you were an easy mark.
It is truly amazing
what you can accomplish
with goulash and a good foot rub.
Now I see the real you.
I was blind to your manipulations.
But today I'm going to
correct that mistake.
You will tell me the
full extent of your plan.
If your father was involved,
which of my captains you have turned,
and how you intend to
rid me from the city.
Bring him out.
Allow me to introduce
you to The Dentist.
And he is not the kind who gives out
lollipops after the visit.
Captain Gordon.
I wondered if my little
scuffle would bring you here.
I'm so glad it did.
I've missed our little chats.
Good. Then you can start by
telling me who you really are.
Don't you know?
Jim, I'm a reflection of you.
I don't see it.
James, you swine.
I want to know who's
hiding behind that mask.
What you see is what you get.
What I see
is someone who craves attention.
So why are you concealing
your true identity?
Don't you want to take the credit
for all your brilliant crimes?
Oh, I get all the credit.
The whole town has gone
hog wild for the Pyg.
Not since I caught you.
You're yesterday's news.
It's not true.
This is Gotham.
You're a second-class psychopath
compared to what we've got.
Jerome Valeska, Fish Mooney, Penguin...
they have staying power.
You don't. You're wrong.
I terrified this whole city for months.
People will remember that.
No, they won't.
In fact, they've already forgotten you.
But not you, Jim.
You're here. A final visit.
Now I'm gonna walk out that door
and never think about you again.
Mind games.
You really think that's
going to work on me?
Guard, we're done here.
James, we're not done here.
Have a nice life.
Don't you walk out on me.
You will never forget me.
I promise you that.
There you are.
So...
you're Doc.
I heard you had a giant.
I figured you might've
brought him along with you
rather than this, uh, has-been.
Excuse me.
Why would I bring Grundy along
for a friendly conversation?
Look, I understand you
had a deal with Cherry
where you left her people alone.
I expect you to honor the same with me.
Why would I do that?
You're not even from the Narrows.
You have no idea how
things work around here.
Maybe you're right, but I
do know that you love money.
I'm willing to offer you
ten percent of fight night.
You just don't get it, huh?
I'm not negotiating.
I'm taking.
I'm taking the clinic.
I'm taking the club.
I'm taking your whole damn neighborhood.
Okay, we tried this your way.
Let's use Grundy.
Well, that doesn't sound so good.
You cough up blood yet?
What's it to you?
Bad case of Narrows Lung going around.
What the hell is that?
It's a new virus.
I've seen it kill a few people already.
First you cough up blood
and within a few days you're dead,
unless you have treatment.
I'll sweeten the deal.
I will doctor your
people free of charge.
You're not gonna get a
better offer than that.
All right.
I'll be back in a few days
to negotiate with
whoever takes your place
after you drown in your own blood.
Tell you what, Doc.
Make it 30% of fight night,
you got yourself a deal.
That's too much. Don't take it.
Come by the clinic later.
We'll see about that cough.
Your teeth are quite lovely.
I look forward to putting
them in my trophy case.
You have no idea who I am, do you?
Of course I do.
You are Don Falcone's daughter.
He killed my brother.
I'm going to enjoy this.
It's true he killed your brother,
but not your wife, Elaine,
or your son, Joseph.
No, they're still alive,
probably having lunch
in your two bedroom on
Seventh Ave right now.
See?
I made it a point to learn every detail
of Penguin's organization.
For instance, I learned that
he only trusts one man
for this type of job.
You.
And in the event that
I am ever tortured,
my people have instructions
to kill your family.
Interesting threat.
But no one's going to know
that you were tortured
because no one is going
to find your body.
Oh, 'cause you don't think
I have spies inside
Penguin's organization.
He's right about me, though.
I have been conspiring
against him for months,
turning his captains
against him one by one
and today is the day that I
will finally take him down.
So, if my people don't
hear from me soon,
your family's dead.
But if you don't believe me...
drill away.
Excuse me, her restraints
need tightening.
Hmm, wise decision.
Now untie me.
Things are finally looking up.
Wakey-wakey.
Oh, hello.
I don't believe we've met.
I'm Barbara Kean.
This ferocious lady is
Tabitha Galavan, and that kitty-cat...
that's Selina Kyle.
I know who you are.
Penguin wants you dead for betraying him
down in the Narrows.
What do you want with me?
Well, we heard you and Ozzie are BFFs.
So you're going to try and leverage me
to get Penguin not to kill you.
We have some other demands,
but essentially, yeah.
That's a good plan.
Except for the fact that Penguin
just tried to kill me.
Why would he do that?
Because I am so close
to taking his underworld from him.
You're lying.
Am I?
I've been working Penguin for months.
Manipulating him into behaving
exactly how I want him to.
Every move he made
today, I orchestrated.
Now you three are screwing things up.
So... you want him out of your life,
let me go.
Maybe she's telling the truth.
She's a Falcone.
She learned to lie
before she could read.
But, whether you're friend or foe
makes no difference to me.
Because Penguin will
still make the deal.
Get him on the phone.
You'll grow into it.
Because of you,
I was able to vanquish my enemy.
And now that you've proven yourself...
I see a beautiful future ahead for you.
I have so much wisdom to impart.
And if you pay attention...
one day, all of this could be yours.
What's wrong?
What are you talking about?
You mean...
you did not see Sofia kissing Gordon?
"...they kissed."
Why would she do that?
Unless...
she knew exactly how I would respond.
She wanted me
to confront her.
Even torture her.
Boss.
We have a problem.
The Dentist is gone.
And what happened to Sofia?
To be honest, that's
still a little unclear.
Barbara Kean has her.
What?! How do you know this?!
She's on the phone.
Says she wants to make a deal.
Give me that.
Barbara.
Hello, Oswald.
I see you have crawled out from
whatever rock you were hiding under.
What are you doing with Sofia?
We scooped her up this morning.
And, of course, when we did,
we thought she was your
best friend. Turns out
she's your worst enemy.
I want her back.
Name your price.
We keep the gun shop,
we don't share profits,
and from this point forward, we
operate with complete autonomy.
Fine.
I will send Zsasz over to collect her.
She had better be there when he arrives.
She will be.
And as for you, young man,
our conversation is not over.
So this is what the Pyg used
to look like. That's him.
All right, send it out to police
stations across the country.
Start in the South. The South? Why?
When I pressed him,
he spoke in a Southern accent.
Could have done that
deliberately to throw you off? No.
He slipped up... I saw it in his eyes.
This is the best lead we've got.
Let's see where it goes.
I don't understand you.
If Sampson's cough will kill
him, why not let him die?
There's no such thing as Narrows Lung.
He probably just has bronchitis.
I give him some medicine, he
feels better, problem solved.
Okay, what about the 30%?
Once he has that, he's
just gonna want more.
Maybe.
Sampson, you son of a bitch.
Now do you see who you're dealing with?
I know you wanted to try this your way.
No more diplomacy, Lee.
Take Grundy and end this.
No.
I have a better idea.
That was easy.
Yeah. A little too easy.
Because he couldn't wait
to get you off the phone.
We need to get out of here.
And then what happens?
You take over
from Penguin?
We are not working
for anyone but ourselves.
I'm not asking you to.
I will give you everything you want
from Penguin.
You're not in a position
to offer us anything.
We're in charge here.
Uh, guys,
I think we should listen to her.
Why? Because Zsasz is
standing out front
holding a rocket launcher.
Ladies.
I'm gonna break his little beak in half.
Jim! Sorry, Cap, I tried to stop her.
I told her she had to wait.
It's okay, Detective.
I've got it.
Sofia, what happened to you?
I underestimated Oswald.
He found out we were
plotting against him,
and he-he just tried to kill me, Jim.
He can't hurt you here.
If he finds out I'm alive,
he will come after me,
and he won't stop until I'm dead.
You are the captain of the GCPD.
Your men would follow you anywhere.
Please, please, use the position
I gave you and end this.
What are you proposing I do?
You have an army... just
take the fight to Penguin.
So this was your plan.
To start a war.
You knew you didn't have the numbers
to fight Penguin on your
own, so you made me captain,
knowing it would come to this,
and I'd take him out for you.
Your job is to stop
criminals, Jim... here you go.
It is not that simple, and you know it.
We could bring law and order back
to Gotham.
This is exactly what you asked
for when you came down South,
and it is yours for the taking.
You know what has to be done, Jim.
Crush Penguin.
I trusted you, Martin...
and you betrayed me.
I think it's time for you
to go back to the orphanage.
Boss? Hold on!
Let the little spy step out
of the room.
So?
The place went up like
a great ball of fire.
Good. Alert the capos.
We are going to unleash
a crime wave on this city
like it has never seen.
That will teach Jim Gordon
to align himself with Sofia Falcone.
I wouldn't make that call if I were you.
I just spoke with Sofia.
She's alive, and she told
me you tried to kill her.
Hearsay, Jim.
Been here all day. I have witnesses.
I don't care.
I'm not here to arrest you.
I came to make a deal.
I think we've both put up
with Sofia long enough.
Victor, would you give us a moment?
Okay, Jim, you have my attention.
Since the moment she set foot in Gotham,
Sofia has put us on a path to war.
She's willing to let this
city burn to the ground
to prove herself to her father.
I can't allow that.
So what do you want from me?
I'm putting her on a train home tonight.
But I need assurances from
you you won't get involved.
Not good enough!
She needs to suffer
for what she has done.
That is not gonna happen.
And how do you think your girlfriend's
gonna react when she realizes
you betrayed her?
You think she's just
gonna run away quietly?
If she sets foot in Gotham again,
I'll put her behind bars.
And if I say no?
Then I'll have no choice
but to use the full force of the GCPD
to tear you apart, piece...
by... piece.
That does not sound very pleasant.
It won't be.
I guess I can put aside
my personal feelings
for the good of this city.
But I do have one question for you, Jim.
Once Sofia is gone...
where does that leave us?
No more licenses.
If you or any other
criminal in this city
break the law, my men will enforce it.
But at least you won't have
to worry about Sofia again.
So...
do we have a deal?
After all we have been
through together, Jim,
it is nice
that we can resolve this
matter with diplomacy.
Ah, Doc.
I heard about what
happened to your clinic.
What a shame.
I was looking forward to you
curing my, uh, Narrows Lung.
I want you cleared out of the Narrows
by the end of the day.
What did you say to me?
I think she was pretty clear.
Then allow me to be clear.
This is my turf, and
I'm not going anywhere.
And you two have dug your own graves.
Oh, well, then I guess
you don't want this?
What's that?
The antidote to the poison
I had slipped in your drink
about 30 minutes ago.
Ironic, isn't it?
It's the only thing from the clinic
that wasn't destroyed.
Some vials of medicine I had mixed
into a deadly combination.
Should be kicking in,
uh, right about now.
You're bluffing.
I feel absolutely f...
I'm sorry, what was that?
Get 'em!
Come any closer and I'll destroy this.
Like I said...
you leave by the end of the day,
and you'll live.
Deal?
Okay.
Oh.
Catch.
I know you're disappointed, but
I am doing this to protect you.
Disappointment doesn't quite
cover it, Jim. If you stay
in Gotham, Penguin will kill
you. Don't put this on Penguin.
If you have something to say,
I think you should say it.
We're the same, Jim.
I saw it the first moment we met.
We both want power.
You want to deny it, but it's true.
And it is just easier to send me away.
Detective Harper,
please take Ms. Falcone
to the train station and
escort her back home.
Please don't do this.
Better get going.
You'll miss your train.
Gordon put her on the train.
Talk about a turn of events.
Did not see that coming.
What about the kid?
You want me to take him
back to the orphanage?
That won't be necessary.
Martin, I have been thinking.
I was angry.
I did not mean what I...
Martin?
Martin.
Oh, he's cute.
He doesn't talk.
The kid gives me the creeps.
Let's get this over with.
Nervous about something?
Well, we have a long way to go.
So get comfy.
Tickets, please.
What...?
Hello, Victor.
Where's the boy? Alive, for now.
If Oswald wants to keep it that way,
he will meet me under the
Crown Point Bridge in one hour.
Next stop, Stevenstown.
That's my stop.
Do you mind?
Not at all.
Thank you.
Glad you could make it, Oswald.
Everything will be all
right, Martin, I promise.
Well, that depends on you.
Turn over control of
the underworld to me,
and I'll let little Martin
here... keep his head.
The name Falcone used to
mean something in this town.
Wait until your father hears of this...
threatening the life of a child!
He will be disgusted!
Wrong.
My father will be proud.
Must be hard to live your whole life
trying to get Daddy's approval.
I, myself, can't relate,
seeing as my parents loved
me without condition.
Say one more word and I will kill him,
and then I will execute you.
I am choosing compassion,
but I am willing to change my position.
Don't hurt the boy.
He's innocent.
I submit.
Go ahead.
Martin, I want you to know...
I'm sorry for what I said.
I do care about you.
You know that's true, don't you?
Good.
Now, go wait in the car.
You were wise to use the boy.
As you know, my heart
is my greatest weakness,
but...
I will not allow him to be used
as a pawn in your game anymore.
You wanted a war,
you've got one!
Ed.
Why so blue?
We had a great day.
You had a great day.
I did nothing to help.
That's not true.
I couldn't have done it without you.
I'm not meant to be a sidekick, Lee.
Sampson was right, I'm a has-been.
No, you're not.
Look, I asked you to trust
me with something today,
and you did.
So I'm gonna trust you with something.
I haven't been looking for
a cure for your brain, Ed,
because there's nothing wrong with you.
But you... Sure.
At first there was an
effect from the ice,
but I ran all the tests; it checks out.
There's nothing wrong
with you, physically.
Your condition is psychological.
Think about it.
You knew every move that
Sampson was gonna make
before he made it.
You lied to me.
Why?
Because I was afraid that
if I told you the truth,
you would go back to
being who you were before,
The Riddler.
And I like who you've become.
Who's that?
Ed Nygma.
The Ed that you were before.
My friend.
Well, that backfired.
Penguin's gonna be coming for us.
What are we gonna do?
We hit him before he hits us.
Lady, you lost.
Penguin just blew up that kid.
I admit I didn't see that coming.
But Oswald still has to align
his capos before he moves on us.
We use that window of
time to make our play.
You didn't get told "no" a lot as a kid,
did you?
You took your shot and you missed.
We're going it alone
from here. You leave now,
and you will never have
a piece of this city.
Now, that sounded like a threat.
Your club is destroyed.
You have nowhere else to turn.
You need me.
Penguin may have won the battle,
but tomorrow we win the war.
Boss.
My boy.
You did a splendid job of dying.
Victor will take you to a safe location.
You can never return to Gotham.
This is good-bye, my friend.
There, there.
This is what I have
to do to protect you.
One day, when you are
older, you will understand.
Sofia's on her heels, boss.
Let's finish her off.
Have someone else take the kid.
No.
I want my top man on this.
Besides,
I have something much better
planned for Sofia Falcone.
You were right about the Pyg.
A precinct down South
recognized the picture
you had me send out.
His real name is Lazlo Valentine.
What do we know about him?
He was being held for a string
of murders down there ten years ago.
But here's the thing:
his previous victims
weren't police officers,
and there was no Pyg persona.
Serial killers don't
usually change their M.O.
This guy did.
You said he was being held.
Did they say why their case fell apart?
It didn't. He escaped.
Call Arkham.
Have them put a guard on his cell.
I'm on my way.
Pyg?
Hello, Ed.
No.
No!
Miss me?
Open it, let's go.
Sound the alarm!