No. Oh, no, no.
The merchandise has gotta be mint
or you won't get a dime.
My God.
Jack.
Hi, Irwin.
Where's my stuff?
Aaron Danzig, 6'4", 225, mental age
of a young child.
We believe he's under the control
of this man.
Jack Gruber.
In Arkham off a rape-murder beef.
We can't find any records on Gruber
prior to his incarceration.
So we're guessing Gruber is an alias.
We're sending his prints nationwide,
see if we can find another name
for him.
Whoever he is, he's clever and angry
and a grave public menace.
The commissioner is deeply concerned
and he is on his way here
to talk to all of you right now.
You know what that means
and you know...
Jim?
- Captain.
- Hey, partner.
- Hi.
- You're out of your jurisdiction.
- Captain, this is my case.
- Jim.
- You need to get out of here.
- It's my case.
No, no, no. The captain is right.
You need to leave
before the commissioner gets here.
Why?
Because he holds you responsible
for all of this and... Oh, fudge.
He's here.
And you're there. Side step.
- Captain Essen.
- Good morning, Commissioner.
Officer Gordon, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
- Why are you here?
- I have a better question.
Why are you here, commissioner?
- Excuse me?
- This is the first I've seen
you down here with the rank and file.
You must be desperate.
Follow me.
Really nice knowing you.
Bring your friend, bullock.
I hate you.
It wasn't my idea,
it was your friend.
He came up with the double-cross,
made me go along.
You have a mind of your own,
don't you?
Hey, come on.
See?
I kept your gadgets safe.
I know what it means to you.
All of your experiments.
Oh, I appreciate that.
Please.
You don't have to kill me.
I don't...
...have to do anything.
I'm free.
You know the funny thing?
I think it was my time in Arkham
that freed me.
I mean, in here.
Now I see the world
for what it really is.
An abandoned factory full
of broken machines.
Some very few...
can be fixed.
Most...
just have to be scrapped.
Danzig, hold him, please.
Please.
Please. No, stop, please.
Two maniacs on the loose
makes the whole Arkham project
look kind of shady, huh?
The moneymen want results fast,
I bet.
You're strangely self-righteous,
given that it was you
that let these men escape.
Blame me all you want.
My name is already mud.
Those two will still be out there.
And that means you need me.
James.
Why did you become a policeman?
Your father
was the district attorney.
A proud station
for a man of substance
you would think that would inspire
a son to practice law.
I'm enforcing the law.
You wanna talk about my dad
or do you wanna catch
Gruber and Danzig?
Where do you get that rebellious fire
in your belly?
Can I take this opportunity to say
that I have no rebellious fire
here, nada.
Jack Gruber is out there.
Planning a catastrophe.
I know the man.
I know how he thinks.
I know what he'll do next.
Which is what?
That I'll keep to myself.
I guarantee I'll bring
in these two men.
But first I need you to reinstate me
as detective first grade in the GCPD.
Extortion, Officer Gordon.
- Twenty-four hours?
- What?
You've got 24 hours
to bring these men in.
You don't, you can both spend
the rest of your miserable careers
down at Arkham.
That will be all, detectives.
- What the hell just happened?
- It's okay. It's okay.
- Everything's gonna be fine, Harvey.
- Yeah?
Yeah, we just gotta catch
the bad guys.
- Where are we going?
- I don't know.
What? You just told him you knew
what Gruber was gonna do next.
I lied.
Please.
Don Falcone.
Have mercy. We're family.
I know, son.
I know it's hard.
A young man like you.
Doesn't seem fair.
Please.
Don Falcone, please!
This whole area used to be slums
when I was a boy.
You've come a long way.
Some of your people
are looking for you, you know.
But you're the one I wanted to see.
I've worked so long all my life
to get where I am.
So long I forget
why I wanted to be here.
Well, you wanted to be someone
and you are.
I mean, look at all the stuff
you have.
You're a good girl, Liza.
You need to find a young man
and get married, have babies.
It's not fair of me
keeping you cooped up here
doing my house work.
You'll never find
a good husband here.
Anyhow, if you'd like to get out
in the world, I was thinking
I could set you up with a bakery
or some type of business like that.
So you can be independent.
That's really nice, Mr. F. Thank you.
But I would rather be here with you.
- You would?
- I like it here.
You make me feel safe.
Well, good.
I like having you here.
Maybe I'll try to get a little
work done before dinner.
Making something special tonight.
What are you laughing at?
It's good to be back.
Only a man from a lunatic asylum
would say that.
You're like a human roller coaster
except you only go down.
Wouldn't that make him
more of an elevator?
You have anything useful, Ed?
I got a little less than 20 hours
before I lose my job.
I do have something useful.
- And it is?
- I cross-checked fingerprints.
The clinically insane Jack Gruber
of Arkham,
is a figment of the files.
The man himself
is really a career criminal
by the name of Jack Buchinsky.
How is that even possible?
Easy enough to bribe someone
to change the records.
Yep, apparently, he wanted
to be transferred to Arkham.
That's really good work, Ed.
What's this Buttinsky's deal?
It's... Buchinsky.
It's all in the files.
Just make sure you sign it out.
It's classified information,
so just be careful.
Miss Kringle?
I believe you left this on my desk.
It's a riddle.
It's a cupcake with a live bullet
sticking out of it.
It's a riddle.
It's menacing and weird and inedible.
Thank you for the files,
Miss Kringle.
This Buchinsky dude and his partners
pulled four successful
bank robberies,
killed six along the way before
the GCPD caught him by accident.
He never named his accomplices.
He's in prison, he hears Arkham
is opening its doors,
so he uses his connections,
and he gets himself a new identity
as the mental patient Gruber.
He must have some good connections.
Right, and when the rest of the nuts
get transferred to Arkham viola.
So he had partners, huh?
Yeah, GCPD never identified them.
They're still out there.
Yep, we find them, we'll find him.
Easy enough, huh?
Detective.
A hit.
What do we got?
Lead detectives dusted for prints,
two sets...
Gruber and Danzig,
just like we thought.
- Right. Thanks.
- All right.
Van checks out.
It was them.
Our man's an electronics freak,
right?
Yeah.
Think he went shopping?
He's dead.
Fried like a doughnut.
GCPD.
Turn around slowly,
let me see those hands.
Hey.
Hey, buddy.
Hey!
Help!
- Help, help! Please!
- Get back in the store.
Okay. Take it easy. Okay.
Please, there's been
a terrible mistake.
I am Don Falcone's housekeeper.
Fish? Thank God.
Why'd you have to pull me out
like that?
You scared the life out of me.
It's time, Liza.
I'm gonna make my move on Falcone.
And don't be scared, baby girl.
I got this.
Mr. Falcone, we have your girl, Liza.
Would you like to see her again?
Yes, I would.
She'll be glad to hear that.
For a fit young woman,
she has a low pain threshold.
Please! No! Stop!
An intermediary will be in contact
with you soon.
Don't hurt her.
She's a civilian.
Hello?
What now?
Now we let him sit
and think about his life for a while.
"The Electrocutioner."
Cute.
- No pressure.
- Don't worry, we'll get him.
Yeah, and we got 17 hours to do so.
I love the name.
It's catchy, has drama.
The Electro-cutioner.
Speaking of which,
given the general mode of attack,
may I suggest you both wear your
department-issue galoshes
while you're out in the field.
Galoshes?
In the event
of electrical misadventure,
your footwear should be insulated.
No, Mom! I'm not gonna wear
my rubbers on the case.
Nygma, give them here.
Seriously?
All right, so what do we know?
Gruber wasn't too happy with Irwin.
Maybe they were partners in crime,
Irwin turned on him,
Gruber took the fall.
Detective Gordon.
- Dr. Thompkins.
- My friends call me Lee.
Congratulations,
you got your job back.
Or not, depending.
- It's good to see you.
- Is it?
I, I know you're caught up
with the escape.
- That's why I'm here.
- Is everything okay?
Must be chaos down there.
We're getting by just fine.
Thanks for asking.
Oh, right, this is my partner,
Harvey Bullock.
Hola.
Detective Bullock.
Who's your little friend there?
Oh, this is why I'm here.
One of the women in my wing
is a pagan sorceress.
- Of course.
- She's very popular.
The inmates make dolls
to look like people
that they want to curse.
And then they give it
to the sorceress to curse them.
In exchange for extra soda and candy.
I curse you all the time.
You never give me candy.
I asked her if Gruber had ever given
her a doll to curse and she said yes.
This is the doll.
His name is Mr. M.
You owe me for a double six-pack
of root beer.
-Mr. M?
-Mr. M.
Mr. M.
Who does this look like to you?
I tell this guy, I said, Maurice
we've pulled out half
your freaking teeth.
What the hell are you waiting for?
- The tooth fairy?
- Right?
So, what he does
you know what Maurice does?
He smiles at me.
So I say, I'm gonna take out
another one, man.
I go to his molar.
I got to get Mario
and Gabe to help me pull it out.
Do excuse me.
Right. So we're, like, pulling it,
we're pulling it, right?
And finally, we get it out.
The thing is this big...
- Yes.
- Come see me.
I need you.
I'm on my way.
What's wrong?
Somebody took Liza.
Come, quickly.
You sly devil.
You took her.
You're mine now.
So I'm trying to tell this guy,
"Let him talk."
Because now he's trying to talk
but now I don't understand him
'cause he's got no teeth, right?
So I'm saying, "Let him talk.
Clean him out.
He's gonna tell us something."
Don Maroni, sir, forgive me.
Such fun we're having.
But I regret that I must run away.
If you'll let me.
My mother is sick.
Well, a sick mother's a sick mother.
Go.
Hey.
Penguin, you all right?
Hey, kid, what are you...
What's going on here?
Get down!
I don't know what happened.
It was like a silent bomb.
You know who did this, right?
Who?
A few years ago, Jack Buchinsky
and partners unknown
knocked over four banks.
Killed six people.
Buchinsky went down for life.
His partners were never caught.
You're one of those partners.
The one that took his share
and sold him up the river, I expect.
What guy was this?
Who?
While he's out there
looking to hurt you,
he doesn't care who else he hurts.
Women, kids.
Hey. That's not my fault.
Help me do the right thing here,
Don Maroni.
Let me place you
in protective custody.
- Protective custody?
- Yes.
Bait, you mean.
We catch our bad guy,
you get rid of a dangerous nuisance.
We both come out ahead.
Excuse me.
Hello?
I must be going.
Very urgent business.
With Falcone.
All right, make yourself at home.
Hey, sweetheart.
Get me a double espresso.
Extra sugar.
Nah.
I'm Barbara.
Barbara Kean.
My parents, they live here.
It's very nice to see you, Barbara.
Isn't it, Everett?
Yes, very nice.
It's nice to see you, too.
You've been well, I hope?
Yes.
- And you?
- Splendid.
Are you staying the night?
If that's all right.
In fact...
I... I thought maybe
I could stay a few days.
If that's...
Oh, I see.
Yes, of course.
I'm sure you're going
to be frightfully bored.
But stay until the weekend.
By all means.
Thank you.
How's that young man of yours?
James?
The policeman?
All well, I hope?
Yes.
He's well, thank you.
Good.
We're very happy.
Very happy.
You guys are, like, hungry for this.
What do you do here for excitement?
Remember that joke
about the what is it?
The two cops and the undertaker
that go on a fishing boat.
When you use a tethered goat as bait,
shouldn't the goat be out
in the jungle and not in the house?
This house is the best defended
spot in Gotham.
Buchinsky is crazy
and arrogant and resourceful.
Wherever Maroni is,
he'll come after him.
He'll enjoy the challenge.
I can show you.
- Hey, there.
- Hi, boss.
- How long have I been unconscious?
- Couple of hours.
Oh, my gosh.
I must go.
My, my poor mother is...
Your mother can wait.
It's her heart.
Poor thing. Valves.
She might be taken at any moment.
But... but by all means,
of course, she can wait.
When you woke up before,
you said you had urgent business...
with Falcone.
I did?
I said that, did I?
Carmine.
Some people have called me
about your girl Liza.
They want me to help make a deal.
I didn't think
it was going to be you.
I'm sorry.
I'm just an intermediary.
I just wanna help.
Please, my dear, stop.
I know this is you.
Be honest.
- It's me.
- Of course it is.
How long have I known you?
You're the smart one in the family,
didn't I always say so?
She won't be hurt.
Leave Gotham, that's all.
Leave Gotham, never come back.
You can take her with you.
Agreed.
That's the right decision.
I'll make the arrangements.
You were always my favorite.
Wait for my call.
He's leaving?
You did it?
Boss.
The genius, the vision.
You brought down the old man.
Finally.
Let's celebrate.
Butch, this is not the time
to celebrate.
He was a great man once.
You don't think somebody
would take him out if he stayed on.
I am doing him a favor
and giving him an easy way out.
I owe him...
at least that.
Of course. You're right.
It's best for everyone.
How did he sound?
Sad.
Look at me.
Is there something
you're not telling me?
No.
You're gonna have to leave town
with him.
String him along for a while.
Do you think you can do that?
- Sure.
But you like him though, don't you?
Well, I can like him, can't I?
He's been a perfect gentleman.
He could've done anything...
and he never laid a hand on me.
Liza, you can like him all you want.
But you can never tell him the truth.
I know that.
Sir.
Let me go to work.
No.
No?
If Fish and the others...
and there must be others.
If they all want me to step away
so badly, maybe it's time.
Why not?
Why am I still here fighting?
For what?
For respect.
You're Don Carmine Falcone.
Respect?
Who cares?
They all want me to go live
in the country with Liza.
I would like that.
That's what I want too.
So why not do it?
Please, don't talk that way, sir.
Just me on my own...
I can take out Fish's crew easy.
You're not listening, Victor.
Your job is to keep me and Liza safe
through the coming transaction.
That's all.
Yes, sir.
- Miss Kringle.
- What? What?
The cupcake is sweet,
the bullet is deadly.
A beautiful woman
is a dangerous thing.
Listen, I...
That is so...
I don't, I don't even know
what to say to that.
Nygma, you perv, back off.
Can't you see the lady
doesn't want you bugging her?
I...
Hey, there.
Hey, now. Who's bugging who?
I'm just, I'm just...
What's green and then red?
Frogs in a blender.
Walk away, Nygma.
Walk away.
I'm very sorry if I offended you,
Miss Kringle.
That was not my intention.
- Do you hear that?
- Go.
Thank you.
He is so weird.
I have no business with Falcone.
I swear on my mother's life.
May God strike her dead
with horrible torments if I'm lying.
Okay, then, my friend.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
Go see your mom.
- Give her a kiss from me.
- Thank you.
What the hell's going on here?
- Hey, hey!
- What's going on?
There's the one.
Under that funny-looking fella there.
Take him to the truck.
They didn't cook, just stunned.
I expected more oomph.
You want oomph, Jack?
Officer Gordon.
Nice shoes.
Detective Gordon.
Hands up, both of you.
You might wanna drop that.
Why fight me, Gordon?
Who here deserves your protection?
- Any of them?
- All of them.
Even Maroni? Please.
Just let me kill this false friend
and get on with my life.
All this fight, and for what?
I'm putting you back in Arkham, Jack.
That's closer to the mark now,
isn't it, Jim?
You need to win, don't you?
You pretend to care
about the law but in your heart,
it's all primitive ego
and your lust for blood and power.
You just hate to lose.
You know what? You're right.
I do hate to lose.
Congratulations, young man.
New day.
Next man that tries to take away
my shield, one way or another,
I'm gonna make him eat it.
Say again.
New day, commissioner.
I hope you have some nasty
pictures of him,
because I bet what you said
was very rude.
I'm done being careful.
You think you've been careful so far?
Men like Commissioner Loeb
are never gonna trust me.
You think you've been careful
so far?
So why play nice?
You think you've been careful
so far?
Don't worry, I know what I'm doing.
Let's go grab a beer.
Now you're messing with my mind.
I need something stronger than beer.
Hush, young man.
I can hear you sigh.
Sorry, sir.
Let him be.
It's good to see you, old friend.
I am so sorry
it took me so long to get here.
Such a day I've had.
I won't even tell you.
But I'm here.
You were right about Fish.
It's her that's taken Liza.
Sir, allow me.
I must tell you what I've discovered.
You're not gonna want to hear this.
Speak.
Liza was planted on you by Fish.
She belongs to Fish.
This was a setup from the start.
She found a girl
that looked just like your mother
and trained her to...
No.
I'm sorry.
- Prove that.
- How?
I can't.
I just know.
You're wrong.
When have I been wrong?
Hello, Fish.
Don Falcone.
We will meet at my place.
Acceptable?
Yes.
Is she there? Is Liza there now?
- Can I speak to her?
- No.
What time?
In an hour.
I'll be there.
Fish.
Don Falcone.
How's this work?
Liza is close by.
All I need for you to do
is sign papers.
Relinquish all control
of the family...
and then you're both free to leave.
Papers.
You think papers make a don?
I'm offering you a way out, Carmine.
I appreciate that, thank you.
But I need to see her first.
Before I sign anything,
I need to know she's all right.
She's fine.
I need to see her, or no deal.
- Are you all right?
- I'm okay.
How long have you known Fish Mooney?
I don't.
I just met her now.
No.
A little bird told me you and she
have been friends for a while.
No.
Told me that she told you stuff
about my mother so that I'd get
all caught up in you.
Because Fish knows,
you know, about my mother.
You know how much I love my mother.
Because we talked about her
all the time, you and me.
Remember, Fish, back in the day?
I do.
It seems as though a little bird
has been making a bit of mischief.
Yes...
that's what I had hoped.
But the truth is plain to see.
I'm very disappointed
at my own stupidity.
I'm sorry, Liza. Is that your name?
I'm sorry you had to get mixed up
in this.
Because I'm sure
you're a good, honest girl, really.
No.
I want these two alive for now.
Lock them up some place.
Don't bother yelling for help.
All of your people are dead.
Carmine, you have to under...
I can forgive all kinds of betrayal
and dishonesty.
But my mother...
How dare you use
my sainted mother against me?
That's wrong!
- You'll suffer for that.
- I need you...
Thank you, Fish.
For the first time in a long time,
I feel alive.
I remember who I am.
I remember why I'm here.
- Just listen...
- You can come out now.
Right as usual, my friend.
Say your goodbyes quickly.
Miss Mooney has places to go.
Hello, Fish.
Hi.
Dr. Thompkins.
Lee.
The desk sergeant said
it was okay to come back here.
- I didn't mean to disturb you.
- No, no. It's okay. Something wrong?
No. I was in the area.
And my sorceress wants her doll back.
Right. Yeah.
Is that why you're here?
Yes.
No.
She does want her doll back
but not entirely.
No.
You live here?
I'm sort of between places right now.
I don't know why I'm here.
Sorry.
A whim.
Wait.
Hey, Gordon, did you hear?
There's been a big shootout
at Fish Mooney's place.