Previously on gotham...
I need to siphon his strength
So when the time
is right,
Taking over
his organization will be
Like slipping on a glove.
The point wasn't
to steal that money, butch.
It was to hurt Falcone.
Bruce: What's her name?
Gordon: Selina kyle.
Bruce: So, she saw everything?
Gordon: Yes.
Her being here will put
master Bruce in great danger.
She's also
the best chance we have
Of finding who killed my parents.
You are gonna keep
working for fish.
You are gonna tell me
Every little thing
that she says.
Dent: Lovecraft, I have an eyewitness
who can tie you to the crime.
You and all the others involved.
So, tell me, dent,
who did I kill?
Thomas and martha wayne.
You lost, miss?
This is wayne manor?
Yeah, but not sure
you should be here.
Point you back to the road
if you're lost. No, thanks.
I am where I
need to be.
Shh...
Open him.
Keep it tight here.
Better?
Better.
If you want
to test yourself,
You should come with me
to the midtown bridge.
You've climbed it?
Yeah, to the top.
Kids go up there
to make out.
All the time.
I could take you, if you want.
Okay.
I'd like that.
Let me ask you a question.
What's up with all the weird
homework about your mom and dad?
I'm trying to understand
why it happened.
There's no why.
Bad stuff happens.
You-you got to get over it.
Maybe you're right.
Of course I'm right.
You want to kiss me?
No, thank you.
No?
I would like to,
But I can't help feeling
you have an ulterior motive.
I don't imagine
you consider me
A suitable romantic partner, so
why would you want to kiss me?
I don't know.
You think too much, kid.
I'm just trying to be nice.
No offense, you don't
strike me as a nice person.
What do you mean?
I'm nice.
I don't mean you're not a good
person, but you're not nice.
You don't care much
for other people.
Screw you, orphan.
Climb the damn bridge
on your own.
Yes, hello, miss.
How can I help?
Oh, dear.
My car, it went off the road.
Please...
Please come in.
Come in at once.
If you could call
an ambulance.
Alfred: Where exactly
are you hurt?
Alfred.
Is everything all right?
No, master Bruce.
This lady's been involved
in a car accident.
Run. Run!
This better be a way out.
The old servant's hallway,
it's through the closet.
But I need to help Alfred!
There's no time!
Bruce, come on!
Alfred might be hurt.
I can't leave him.
He told you to run.
Fine.
Stay, but I'm out.
Bruce!
Gordon: Local pd is
searching the woods,
But so far no sign
of Bruce or Selina.
What can you tell me
about this woman?
Well, she was, uh, early 30s.
A tasty fighter, actually.
Look, mate,
it's just a scratch.
Shove off, will you?
I've got stuff to do.
Look, we've got 50 police in the
woods, even more on the roads.
We need to focus on this woman
and her people.
What can you tell me about her?
They were trained killers.
And your bloody little girl
brought them here.
We don't know that yet.
Bullock: Jim.
You must be Alfred pennyworth.
Nice job out there.
Yeah, well,
not nice enough, eh?
This was taken off the dead guy.
Nothing else--
no keys, no I.D., nada.
Now, I know this girl.
She was grabbed
by the child snatchers.
And now she's getting
attacked by assassins
At wayne freaking manor?!
What the hell's
going on, compadre?
What, you haven't told him?
Told me what?
Selina kyle was in the alley the
night the waynes were murdered.
She saw the
killer's face.
Oh, for pete's sake,
don't do this to me.
Harvey dent in the d.A.'s office
is investigating dick lovecraft.
He thinks that lovecraft is
connected to the wayne killings.
So, he leaked
that we had a witness.
He thought he could
spook lovecraft.
Get him to
reveal himself.
Wow, that's
a hell of a plan.
How did it work out? Bravo!
We thought she was safe.
We thought no one knew
she was here.
Yeah, well, you were wrong,
weren't you, you plank?
How did they know?
Why didn't you tell me
about this foolishness?
Because you would have
tried to stop me.
Of course I would tried
to stop you, you putz!
What the hell are you thinking?
The wayne case is closed.
It is closed!
You know damn well
it's not closed!
Don't tell me what I know!
Will you shut up,
the pair of ya!
You can argue later!
Right now, we need
to find master Bruce.
All right.
If they don't come back soon,
They would have
headed to gotham.
Selina feels safe there.
Bullock: Good luck trying
to find her in the city.
A street kid like that?
But you will help us
find her, right?
Yeah, of course I will.
Because I have to be crazy.
Thank you.
All right,
I'll focus on lovecraft,
I'll find him, and if he is
Behind this, I'll get him
to call off the contract.
How you gonna do that? I don't know,
I'll think of something.
Run the streets, huh?
Focus on your contacts.
Go to work.
I'm coming with you.
All right.
You're pretty handy for a valet.
Butler, mate.
I'm the butler.
We need to call Alfred.
You see any phones?
No.
Perhaps we should go
back to my house.
If the police are there,
we'll know it's safe.
Yeah, right.
The police will
make it safe?
We have to contact
the police at some point.
Someone tried
to kill you.
Me?
Nobody knew
I was there.
It's your house; someone
wants to kill you.
Duh.
Why would anyone want
to kill me?
Must be all that lame
detective work you're doing.
Paid off good, huh?
Cheer up.
We're cool.
We lost them.
I'm worried about Alfred.
Relax.
Once I got you safely
hidden in the city,
I'll find you a phone.
Thank you.
I appreciate your help.
Hey...
Just trying to be nice.
How did Maroni know
where my money was?
Wha...
Well, that's
a very good question.
Not to criticize, but you
could have just called me.
I'm going to ask you once more.
How did Maroni know where
I kept my money? No one knew.
The robbery at the armory.
That wasn't Maroni.
I thought we were friends.
We had an understanding.
You tell me every move
Maroni makes.
What happened?
When did you turn on me?
Never, don Falcone.
I swear, never.
Maroni had nothing to do
with the armory job.
I would know.
I would have told you.
Who was it if not Maroni?
And how did they
know about my money?
Thank you, Liza.
Won't be long.
I'll come back.
I asked you a question.
Oh, you have a mole, obviously.
Which is not Maroni's forte,
is it?
No, this is someone else.
Someone artful.
Someone close to you.
I know who you're going to name.
But your hatred of fish
makes me doubt
Anything you say against her.
With respect...
I don't understand why you
still tolerate her existence.
She has proved her
disloyalty a hundred times.
She wants your head.
Like half the people
who work for me.
Fish makes me a lot of money.
I can handle fish Mooney,
Or whatever son of a bitch
did this to me.
Tell me how to find the mole.
You leave that to me,
don Falcone.
Dirty work.
I'll find your mole for you.
Trust me...
He'll belong to fish.
Bring me proof.
I don't get it.
You, gabe?
Not get it?
Quelle suprise.
What, pray, don't you get?
Why not just tell Falcone
the truth?
It was that Liza girl
that betrayed him.
Timing, gabriel.
Timing is everything.
And Liza is a time bomb.
Just...
Wait a while.
Then watch and learn.
Stay there in
case he shows.
Lovecraft isn't at home.
Housekeeper hasn't seen him
Since yesterday.
Allen says he didn't
Come into his office.
He and montoya are watching it.
How did the killers know
where to find my witness?
Let's keep calm here.
It's a win.
We've made
lovecraft panic.
This is a panic move.
A win?!
There's two children
out there with
Professional assassins
coming after them.
Bruce and Selina
could end up dead.
We're gonna get lovecraft
to call them off.
How did they know?
I never told you
her name,
Let alone
where she was hiding,
So you couldn't have...
I should say not.
And you never mentioned my name
To anyone, right?
No, we agreed.
I didn't mention
any names out loud.
No names "out loud"?
What about whispering?
Don't hold out on me.
I'll know.
For deep background,
I leaked your name
To a couple of
select sources.
I had to, for
credibility!
You're the wayne
murders cop.
Damn it!
That's how they got to her.
I'm surprised it took them
this long to find her.
This is on you, dent!
Whoa.
I'll stipulate mea culpa.
Kick my ass, be my guest.
But let's find
lovecraft first
And get him
to call off the killers.
He's not at home,
he's not at his office.
He could've left gotham.
Someone could be hiding him.
Lovecraft...
Has got a couple of condos
That he keeps under
his mistress's name.
One up in stevensburgh
and one, uh, uptown.
I'll take the one uptown.
If anything's happened
to these kids...
Bullock: We know
you ran with a girl
Called cat.
She's in serious danger.
Who isn't, right?
Crazy world.
How much?
There's $100.
All right, listen.
I don't know where
cat lives, all right?
She's... Private
About stuff
like that.
But... I heard that
she got a new fence,
'cause her old one got popped.
He'd know where
to find her.
Who's the fence?
I don't know.
But I know who would know.
Oh, yeah? Who's that?!
Damn it, Alfred,
save your cheese!
I can beat the truth
out of this kid
With a roll of quarters!
Yo, ask fish Mooney.
She runs
All the fences.
Forgive me for shocking you,
But let me give you
some context here.
I loved bannion.
We came up
together.
But he was supposed to guard
the armory, and he didn't.
And maybe, just maybe,
He looked the other way.
I don't know.
So what do I do?
Let it lie?
Boss, we understand...
Falcone:
Whoever else was involved
Will very soon wish
They could die quickly,
like bannion.
In the meantime,
All of us must do what's right
for the family.
Each of your tariffs
will increase 25%
Until we've built
the reserves again.
No disrespect, that's high.
A little bit.
What do you think, fish?
Am I being fair?
We're family.
We sink or swim together.
Falcone: You could
all learn from fish.
She trusts me.
Trust me, and I'll trust you.
It goes both ways.
Let's eat.
Bruce:
There's a phone!
Come on!
I don't...
I don't carry coins.
Do you have
any coins?
nope.
Not a dime.
Why does Alfred matter
so much to you anyway?
He's just your butler.
He's my family.
Good luck, kid.
See you around maybe.
What?
Wait!
Look...
Those bad guys
were there for me.
Not you.
You have nothing to worry about.
Go home.
But you said...
I was just trying
to freak you out.
I was playing with you.
You were playing with me?
That's kind of cruel, isn't it?
Yeah.
No, look,
You're right about me.
I'm not nice.
Not like you.
You got a nice way about you.
"a nice way"?
Yeah. That's why
I said that thing about
you being the target,
So, you know, we could hang out
a while longer.
I see.
It's very convoluted reasoning.
Whatever.
Anyhow, it's been cool.
I'm gonna disappear.
But you can't do that!
I wasn't asking.
You can't disappear!
You have to come
back home with me.
When detective Gordon
finds the man
Who killed my parents,
you have to testify.
You really think that
was ever going to happen?
Grow up, b.
No, don't!
You won't make it!
Help.
You're crazy.
Please don't run off again.
I'm out of breath.
Okay, kiddo.
You earned it.
You want to hang
with me, that's cool,
But my world, my rules.
You do what I say.
Yes, ma'am.
Why can't I call Alfred
Or detective Gordon
to let them know I'm okay?
Because we're disappearing.
You got to be like smoke.
Smoke doesn't
make phone calls.
What is this place?
The flea.
It's like the mall
for street kids,
Without the
crappy music.
We'll be safe
here till dark.
Falcone's making me nervous.
If he suspects it was us
who blew up his money,
Why hasn't he made a move?
'cause he can't be sure.
There are ten other people
who could have done this.
So what now?
You're going to stick
to the plan.
You're gonna reach out
to Saviano and Turski.
They are both very angry
That their taxes
have been raised,
And they're worried
about ending up like bannion.
They're ready.
The old man
Is herding his sheep toward me.
You got it, boss.
All right.
Hello, gentlemen.
Busy day, harvey.
Come back next year.
Bullock:
Hand to god, butch,
I'll be quicker than
a sailor on shore leave.
Thief we're tracking down.
Look familiar? Goes by "cat."
Nope.
Bullock:
Maybe fish knows her.
Gilzean:
Fish knows everyone.
Fish is busy.
She works with one of
Your fences, a new guy.
What's a fence?
Come on, butch. Be nice.
This is important.
Where's fish?
I told you, she's busy.
I once knew a fella
Called butch.
Yeah, he was a whitechapel lad.
Now, we called him butch,
you see, 'cause he wasn't.
It was a wind-up.
It was like
a joke name.
In fact, he was a horrible
little toe rag.
Gilzean: What?
I can't tell. Are-are you...
Are you threatening me?
Is he threatening me?
Yeah?
You can't...
Now...
Where is this fish?
Right here.
So... What's the fuss?
They're just fooling around.
We're looking
for this girl,
A street thief, goes by cat,
works with one of your fences.
Looks familiar.
What's the urgency?
Professional killers
are looking for her.
Professionals, huh?
This wouldn't be the lovecraft
witness, now would it?
How'd you know?
Streets talk.
Using her to scare lovecraft.
She saw the waynes' killer,
Supposedly.
Yeah.
Mm...
And you're here
because you want me
To help you find her,
don't you?
Yes.
Harvey...
Why in the world
Would I help you
find her,
Of all people?
She has Bruce Wayne
with her, miss.
Really?
Yes, miss.
I'm Alfred pennyworth.
I'm the boy's legal guardian.
Very pleased to meet you.
Likewise.
Miss Mooney, we need your help.
Well, you see, Alfred,
I would love to help you,
But it would infringe
upon my personal interests.
And why would I do that?
You have a very
eloquent... Gaze,
If I may say so, miss Mooney.
And I can see that you're
not a woman that would
Let petty self-interest
outweigh... Honor.
And compassion.
I'll make some calls.
But remember this kindness.
Much better.
Really?
I'm not sure.
You look badass.
No lie.
Ivy: Hey, cat.
Ivy...
What are you doing here?
What have you been up to?
I thought...
Yeah, juvie caught me.
I got adopted upstate.
Didn't take?
Good people--
they wanted me
To cut my hair, dress nice.
I know you.
You're mario pepper's daughter.
Yes. Who are you?
I'm Bruce wayne.
Ivy:
Yes, you are.
Billionaire Bruce wayne.
Stay cool now, Ivy.
I am cool. Why are
you telling me that?
Why are you telling me
what to do?
I'm not.
I'm just saying,
I don't want you
to get mad at him.
He's a friend.
Why would I get mad at him?
It's not his fault, is it?
Did you kill my father?
Do you make my mother
cut her wrists?
No.
Ivy: Somebody did--
somebody did,
But not him.
How you doing?
You doing okay?
I'm okay. And you?
I'm doing great.
How do I look?
You look good.
Have you seen
clyde the fence around?
Yeah, he's working
Out of the factory
on the narrows.
He's cute, isn't he?
Yes, he is.
Uh, thanks, Ivy.
Good to see you. Uh, we got
to go run and see Clyde.
Oh. Okay, fine.
Bye, then.
Keep moving.
She's just
a little girl.
Why are you
so scared of her?
Because she's scary.
Don't look back.
Gcpd!
Drop it.
Kick it over.
You're under arrest.
Conspiracy to commit murder.
Murder? Me, murder?
Look, what are you
talking about?
You put a hit out
on selina kyle.
No, not me.
The same people that came after
her came after me, too.
Th-they attacked me
on the street.
Why do you think
I'm hiding in here?
Why would they come after you?
Why do they ever come?
Because I know too much.
Cut the crap.
Who are you so scared of?
You have no idea, do you?
You think I'm
the big wheel.
When it comes
to the crunch, kid,
I'm nobody, just like you.
A-and the people
Who really, truly run this city,
They're watching you huff and
puff and run around crusading,
And they are laughing at you.
You're so deep in the maze,
You can't see
over the wall.
Tell me something I don't know.
My briefcase, under the bed.
Files.
Go.
Right before the waynes
got killed,
There was a run on wayne
enterprises stock.
Like somebody knew something
bad was gonna happen.
So I figured
I deserved a cut.
So I started digging.
I've come for that man.
You need not get hurt.
Mm... That was nice.
Let's do it again sometime.
Yeah?
Fish got a lead
on the kids,
At a place on the narrows
called the factory.
Word is, cat used
a fence named clyde.
He hangs there.
We're on our way now.
Alfred, let's go.
Fish, thank you.
You owe me.
Who don't I owe?
Mr. Lovecraft?
No, no, no, no, no.
This is detective Gordon.
Badge number 23-16-11.
Reporting body at 1257 antioch.
Cat! My baby!
Hey, clyde.
Well...
What have you got for me?
Hey!
Shh!
Wow.
Sweet swag.
Not your usual junk.
Selina:
Moving on up.
Where'd you get this?
You want a story or the swag?
How much?
Thousand bucks.
Please.
Give me a break.
That's rock-bottom,
you know it is.
Fifty bucks.
Fifty?
This pen is real gold,
And that's an antique
jade netsuke.
It's worth $2,000 on its own.
And who is this well-spoken
little... Dude?
Never mind
who he is.
Look, 500 is rock-bottom.
Why are you
wasting my time?
Relax.
I'm sure we can...
Make a deal.
No, thanks.
We'll go elsewhere.
Cool down, cat.
Or we'll poke your little
friend's eyes out.
That's it.
Relax.
I've got some friends
coming over
Who would just love
to meet you.
It's all there.
Don't look so anxious.
Yeah, well, um...
You guys are kind of sporty.
Where is she?
She's upstairs.
She better be.
Find me something heavy.
Am I the only one in this damn
town who waits for backup?!
Bruce!
Follow!
Where's Alfred?
He's in there.
Go!
Down!
Where's your girlfriend?
I have no idea.
Don't make me hurt you.
You're not on the contract.
She's gone.
Some advice, kid:
Don't ever mistake bravery
for good sense.
Alfred.
Fancy seeing you here.
You all right?
I'm fine.
How are you?
You really scared me,
master Bruce.
If you die...
Who employs butlers anymore?
Oh, thank god.
James: Lovecraft was a beloved
pillar of this community.
A dedicated servant
of gotham.
So, what do I tell
the media, huh?
Hmm?!
Any ideas?
He was a crook.
We nearly had him.
And he was killed by
whoever he would have implicated
If he had lived to testify.
Say that.
Forgive me if I can't get
behind your approach.
It was your gun.
I didn't kill him.
On balance, I believe you--
on balance.
But suicide is much cleaner...
It wasn't suicide,
it was murder!
It was suicide!
He went mad
Under your relentless
questioning,
Overpowered you
And killed himself
with your gun.
And don't tell me otherwise.
What do you say, counselor?
I'm at your disposal,
mayor james.
I'm sorry if we've
caused you any disquiet.
"disquiet."
You arrogant clowns.
You're hacking away at the very
foundations of this city.
Trying to take me down!
Should have the both of you
stuffed in a sack
And thrown in the river.
But I can't do that.
Two scapegoats would
look like panic.
But one of you is going down,
mark my words.
Sir, that's not right.
Hush.
It's not you, dent.
Obviously, it's
mr. Gordon.
Sir, I protest.
But not too much.
You see, counselor Dent
Knows how to walk the line.
He knows where the edge is.
You, mr. Gordon,
Do not know where the edge is.
Mayor James.
Kiss my ass.
Dick lovecraft's suicide is
a terrible, terrible tragedy.
Fighting the trumped-up charges
Of an overzealous police officer
was too much for him.
You have my word, dick.
This officer is
being dealt with.
Arkham Asylum?
A security guard for nut-jobs?
Criminal nut-jobs, yeah.
Are you taking the assignment?
It's that or quit.
So quit.
That's what they want me to do.
Damn, Jim.
Whoever your next partner is,
He or she will be
a lot easier than me.
Ed.
Detective Gordon, I hear you've
been thrown out in disgrace.
Is this true?
Yeah, it is.
I'm gonna write a letter
to the boss.
You do that.
Which boss should I write to?
Forget it, ed.
That's the breaks, huh?
You take care.
Maybe you should
take him with you.
You'd miss him if he was gone.
No, I wouldn't.
Let me buy you a drink sometime.
Soon.
Selina:
Your security still sucks.
No one's hunting for me.
I didn't expect
to see you again.
Never said good-bye.
No, we didn't.
Didn't want to be rude.
It-it's good to see you.
Here.
Thank you,
but you could keep this.
You need it
more than I do.
Nah, let's keep things
honest between us.
I'm keeping this one anyway.
Having a little chat,
master Bruce?
Thinking out loud.
Right.
Of course you were.
Shall I take that for you?
The old house
seems very quiet...
Without her, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
Sync: Xibirikinho