- Previously on "Gotham"...
- What's you record
for how many banks
you've robbed in one day?
You're playing a dangerous game, Lee.
My job is to make sure
that the people of the Narrows are safe.
I will do everything
in my power to ensure that.
I'm looking for Ed Nygma.
Five banks were robbed last night.
Why don't you try going
after the real criminals?
Making money off the backs of the poor.
Like Gotham Savings and Loan?
- You are a fool!
- Come out with your hands up!
- I expected you might come, Captain.
- There's two of them.
What if he's nuttier than the other one?
I'm nothing like Jerome.
I'm gonna drive you mad.
But don't worry, all of Gotham
will be joining you.
- Hands up!
- Bombs away!
I'm more than a man. I'm an idea.
And I will live on in the shadows
within Gotham's discontent.
Burn it down, brother.
Brothers and sisters,
let's raise a glass
to our fallen leader.
To Jerome!
This affair is invitation only.
Well, that's all right.
You're welcome to stay.
But you won't be leaving.
Ow!
Why so sad, bozos?
Did you think they could
get rid of me so easily?
Well, okay, so they did.
I'm dead. But let's not
dwell on negatives.
I have one last party to throw.
First on the to-do list:
Dig me up.
Dig me up!
Come on, clowns!
Dig him up!
Get Jerome!
We're gonna dig you up, Jerome!
You hear me?
Come on out of there!
Come on, dig, dig, dig!
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com
What are you gonna do?
What can I do?
The back door is just down
that hallway, right there.
I'm not letting her go, Harvey.
Why not? I'm the only one here,
and I'm really good at
looking the other way, partner.
Not this time.
She robbed a dirty bank.
People get away with a lot
worse in Gotham every day.
Doesn't make it right.
We got away with worse. Both of us.
Get out of here.
- What?
- I don't need that crap
thrown in my face right now.
Get out of here!
Well, you finally nabbed me, copper.
What the hell, Lee?
I don't suppose
this is where anyone expected
our story to end.
So it's ending?
Hard to imagine what's left.
I want to help you.
How?
Give up Nygma, return the money,
and ask the D.A.
for supervised probation.
I'm not betraying my friend.
They can call you The Doc.
You can rob banks, fight
gangsters, but I know you.
You're Lee Thompkins, and all this?
This is just a...
way of helping people.
I understand that.
Who doesn't want to be Robin Hood?
But you're still breaking the law.
Jim, you wish you could do
what I'm doing.
Helping people without the straitjacket
of the law... as if the law
means anything in Gotham.
If the law has lost its meaning,
it's because people like you
are turning your back on it.
I am fighting back.
I don't deny anything I've done.
You want to send me to Blackgate?
- Go ahead.
- I don't want to send you to Blackgate!
That's the last thing I want to do.
Don't you know I wish I could
let you walk out that door,
turn my head?
What's holding you back?
Maybe if you let me go,
you'd let yourself go, too.
So many things I wish I could change.
Things I've done.
Jim?
Sorry to stick my face in your business.
Something just came up.
I've already inspected it for
booby traps. It's clear.
- Well, that's a relief.
- I've taken the liberty
of setting up a monitor in your office.
You don't think he might
still be alive, do you?
What were the autopsy results, Lucius?
Dead when he came in.
More dead when he was eviscerated
and his brain was sliced up.
Hello, Jimmy!
If you're watching this,
things must not have gone well for me.
Hmm. Shucks.
I can only pray I gave as good as I got
and left ample carnage in my wake.
But I don't want to fixate
on disappointments.
Jimmy, I have one last
teensy request for you.
I want you to throw me a wake
at the GCPD.
Don't worry about the guest list.
I've already sent the invitations.
I don't like the sound of that.
Is everybody ready?
Lock down everything now.
Everybody, listen up! Lock it down!
Lock it down now!
The Doc's taken care of us.
It's time for us to take care of her!
Let's go down there
and bust her out of jail.
No one cares about
the fate of Lee Thompkins
more than me. Is that understood?
Which is exactly why I will not have you
bumbling into the GCPD en masse.
So we're gonna let her rot?
Leave her in the sweaty palms
of Jim Gordon?
I would sooner debate you all
on teleology versus deontology
than leave her
with that overgrown Boy Scout.
- Teleo... Huh? Geez.
- What?
My point exactly.
Look, if I had it my way,
Jim Gordon would be
off the field of play
once and for all, but Lee insists
that I employ only nonlethal means.
So, I and my brilliant crack team
will liberate Lee Thompkins
with surgical precision.
You stay here. Team, we have everything?
- Bicycle pump? Can opener?
- Right here.
Primer cord? Pickle jar?
Fishing rod?
Fabulous.
Okay, you four, you're with me.
You, go where Jim Gordon goes.
He comes under some harm, assist him.
I do not need Lee blaming me
if he's killed under friendly fire
while I go about my business. Okay?
All right, team. Follow my plan,
and we'll be back here
to finish counting this
in just a few hours.
Keep it up.
Breaking Lee out's
gonna be a piece of cake.
Hello? Wayne Manor.
Alfred, it's Gordon.
Where's Bruce?
Well, he's meeting with Jeremiah
about the energy project.
Something amiss?
He's meeting with Jeremiah Valeska?
Yes, that's right. Now you can tell me
why you sound so concerned.
Jerome's followers are rampaging
outside the station.
Oh, I see.
Are Master Bruce
and Jeremiah in any danger?
It's hard to say.
But right now, Jeremiah's maze
may actually be
the safest place for them.
Right. I shall head there nonetheless.
Thank you very much.
What's the plan?
Open up the armory.
Now you're talking. Guys!
Jim, hey! Hey, Jim!
You figure out where
we're gonna hit 'em yet?
- We're not.
- Say what?
You know how Jerome works.
Dead or alive, he uses distractions.
So what, we're gonna
just let 'em come in
through the front door and party?
This wake is just intended
to distract us
while his followers hit the real target.
Which is?
Well, we're never gonna figure that out
if we're inside fighting off
these maniacs, are we?
Look, they come in
the front door, right?
We fall back, get a few
shots off, make it look good.
Meanwhile, the entire
precinct sneaks out
this old service door
as quickly as possible.
I can't believe you're gonna
run away from these asses.
Once we're outside, we surround
the building, cordon it off.
- And then we trap 'em all inside.
- Correct.
They blow off some steam...
We hit 'em with tear gas
and knock a few heads.
Yeah. Course,
we still have to figure out
what the real target is.
Got a plan for that?
I do. It's a little sketchy
right now, but... Come on.
All right, listen up, people!
Here's the plan.
Jeremiah, I didn't think you could get
the generator program
working so quickly.
You ready for a demonstration?
Okay.
You hit that switch there,
and the facility
will be disconnected
from the power grid.
Ambient energy.
No cables or wires of any kind.
It's clean and stable.
Harvested from microtremors
and air density shifts. It's...
It's virtually without costs.
And with the prototypes at Wayne Labs,
we could power all of Gotham?
You've kept this project a secret, yes?
No one outside of Wayne
Industries knows it exists.
It's the ones who are closest to you
that you have to keep your eye on.
I know better than anyone.
Arkham Asylum sent me
Jerome's personal effects.
And amongst them,
I found his diary.
It's a catalog of his
fantasies and goals.
Every twisted vision he ever had.
Maybe you shouldn't spend
so much time reading it.
He was obsessed with
torturing and murdering
me, James Gordon, and you.
And if he had been just
the least bit sane,
he would have destroyed us all.
And Gotham would be in ruin.
Your brother is dead, Jeremiah.
It's time for you to come out of
this bunker and join the world.
Yes.
Yes, he's dead.
I still have trouble believing it.
Who is that?
It's just Alfred.
- Yeah?
- Oh, Master Bruce,
I've got some rather disturbing news.
Jerome Valeska's acolytes
are kicking off again.
Yes.
Thank you, Alfred.
I'm on my way.
Lunch plans.
That was a lie.
You're lying to me, Bruce?
You're right. I'm sorry.
It seems some of Jerome's
followers are causing trouble.
Oh, my God.
I was right.
No, Jeremiah...
I was right. He's not dead.
Bruce, he's not dead.
He's alive, and he's coming after me!
Jeremiah, easy.
Easy.
You're not thinking clearly.
Come on, this isn't like you.
Bruce.
Bruce, I need to tell you something.
After Jerome died,
he left one last final trap for me.
He sprayed me with his insanity gas.
"Special mixture,
just for you, brother," he said.
I can't stop seeing him...
clawing his way out
of his grave, coming for me.
And even though I know it's not real,
it... feels real.
And I can't control myself.
What if...
What if I could show you
he's dead and buried?
How?
We go there, to his grave.
- No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- Jeremiah, listen to me.
Your brother took away your
greatest strength, your mind,
and turned it into a trap.
But if you can see the reality,
you can be freed from that trap.
You really think that would work?
I do.
Then I'll try.
You're a good friend, Bruce.
We're getting you and
the other prisoners out of here.
What were you trying
to tell me before, Jim?
There's a van outside
waiting for transfer.
- Don't ignore me.
- I just want to get you safe first.
Come to the Narrows.
- What?
- Where you can make
a real difference in this city.
You can make up your own
rules about how to do it.
Alvarez, get them out of here.
Go.
Don't shoot.
Hold your fire.
There's too many of 'em! Fall back!
Fall back!
- Fall back!
- That's him!
He killed Jerome!
Gordon!
Stay together! Stay together!
Let's go! Let's go!
Well, look at us.
We caught ourselves
Captain James Gordon.
Assassin of Jerome Valeska.
Hi, guys.
Oh, don't try and get
chummy with us, Gordon.
We're gonna carve you up.
Yeah. No, I wasn't talking to you.
I was talking to them.
Hey, man, you like to dance?
Let's, you and me, talk outside.
What do you say?
- Still no answer.
- Then something's wrong.
We should go.
He was on his way to your office.
He'll wait for us there.
What was that?
We're almost there.
Just a quick look and we'll leave.
Bruce.
I don't know if I can do this.
Just a little further.
Oh, God, no.
His followers must have dug him up.
He's alive.
- I knew it. I knew it.
- We have to get out of here.
He's alive!
Jeremiah! Jeremiah!
How much longer are these petty
aggressions going to continue?!
There's nothing petty
about my aggression.
So, am I to starve
until I guess the source
of your resentment?
You said, if I joined you,
we'd be back on top.
Instead, we're grubbing for Jerome
and we got played by Nygma.
You said, if I joined you,
you'd find me a cure.
And yet...
I admit that...
through no fault of my own,
our advancement has not run apace.
"Not run apace"?!
We're squatting in Falcone's mansion!
We're knocking over liquor
stores to pay for groceries!
Meanwhile, everyone else
is carving up Sofia's territory.
We are lying in wait,
building a nest egg,
while less deliberate players
show us their cards.
If you don't find me Hugo
Strange and get me cured,
I am going to crush your windpipe
- like a beer can.
- Shh!
Did you just shush me?
Shush! I sense an opportunity here.
Live to Jennifer Luree.
In a twist that Jerome Valeska
himself could have thought of,
the GCPD are laying siege
to Central Precinct
while Valeska's followers
hold a wake for
their deceased role model.
- How is that an opportunity?
- Confusion is always
an opportunity for the clear-headed.
Someone is showing their cards, Butch.
Let's go take a peek.
You may recall what happened here
after the Arkham Asylum breakout...
One to the east, one to the west.
Let's go, let's go.
- Is he talking yet?
- I don't know.
- Let's check.
- Long live Jerome!
All right. One more time, sunshine.
Did Jerome leave any other instructions?
I'll never...
Harvey, Harvey.
Reporters, buddy.
All right, look,
this is how it's gonna go.
You're gonna start talking,
or I'm gonna stop caring whether
you can talk. You got it?
Ow! Ow! I'll talk!
I'll talk.
It's too late, anyways.
They're already dead.
Who? Who's dead?
Jeremiah and Bruce Wayne.
- You think he's telling the truth?
- I'm gonna find out.
They're at Jeremiah's bunker.
You hold down the fort here?
Long live Jerome!
Trouble, Mr. Riddler?
A complication, yes.
Hostiles take over the station.
Police will have removed the prisoners.
Where are they?
Oh, yes.
Oh, this might be
easier than I expected.
The Riddler! We're saved!
How did you get out?
Uh, through the old service door.
The old service door.
- What do we do now?
- Now we improvise.
They're gonna use tear gas in here soon.
I have to get in first.
We need a costume shop. Quick!
Penguin!
We're saved!
That one.
Jerome...
No. Not the...
You ever get tired of being wrong?
Jerome is in the house!
Jeremiah!
We need to leave! It's not safe!
You believe me now?
Jerome's alive.
No. His followers dug
him up. They're sick!
They're also dangerous
and they might be nearby.
How can I trust you if
you won't believe me?
You can trust me
because I'm your friend.
I want you to be my friend, Bruce.
You don't know what it was like...
living underground all those years.
And then you came along
and offered me everything
I could dream of.
Because I believe in you, Jeremiah.
We're gonna do great things for Gotham.
We could.
We really could.
I thought we would.
There's no reason to stop thinking that.
All we have to do is get out of here.
First, all we had to do
was come to the cemetery.
Now all we have to do is leave?
See, that's very confusing to me.
So, tell me again,
Bruce...
why'd you really bring me here?
I thought it would help.
I was wrong, but we need to leave.
What the hell are you doing?!
You think I didn't know
what was happening
from the moment
you suggested coming here?
Jeremiah, what are you talking about?
Stop pretending to be my friend!
I know what's really happening.
You can fool everyone else...
but I know you made a switch.
And you can't hide,
not even behind that new face of yours.
I know it's you.
I know it's you, Jerome.
Jeremiah, give me the gun.
Turn around, brother.
I said turn around!
You killed my friend Bruce.
Now it's time to put you
back in your grave.
Walk!
Come on, chug it.
Chug!
All the way! Yeah!
Wait.
Uh, oh.
Ed.
Bruce?
Jeremiah?
Just a little bit further, brother,
then you'll be back in your grave.
You're stronger than this, Jeremiah.
You know these ideas are just
the insanity gas talking.
I won't let your lies
fool me any longer!
Wh-What's happening?
Hi-ya, Jimbo.
Jerome.
Ah, don't bother talking to me.
This is a recorded message.
And, plus... I'm still dead.
Just more posthumous fun.
Look, I knew you'd see through
all those shenanigans at the station.
I'd given all my fans
a script for them to follow.
See?
I wanted to bring you here.
Oh.
Now do you believe I'm not your brother?
Jeremiah, listen to me!
Jerome's followers are doing this!
Nothing else makes sense.
He sent them instructions
to torment you.
A fake. Yes.
I can see quite clearly where
you cut off poor Bruce's face
and stitched on your own.
But...
I am a man of science.
So let's have some evidence, huh?
Hmm?
Oh, don't mind her.
She's just here to make sure there's
no talking during the movie.
And trust me, you're gonna
want to pay attention
so the twist makes sense at the end.
Hold still, brother.
Let's peel off that grotesque facade.
Come on.
Ecco.
I tell ya...
suicide really takes it out of a guy.
What is this?
Ah.
Jeremiah! Do not let
him turn you into him!
Do not let Jerome win this battle.
Jerome beat me?
That'll be the day.
No!
Long live Jerome!
Long live Jerome! Long live Jerome!
Jerome is victorious at last!
Jerome victorious?
Are you serious?
He's dead.
Haven't you been paying attention?
Thank God I'm done with that.
I am the one who's victorious.
Jerome is dead.
Is dead... is dead.
Long live... love live me.
Long live me.
Look, Bruce.
Like everything Jerome set his mind to,
his insanity gas failed.
Other than some...
mild cosmetic effects,
he might as well
have sprayed me with water.
You all need to see Jerome
for the utter dud that he was,
so I donned the mask of madness
to show you how feeble that is
compared to actual greatness.
Behold, the face of true sanity.
But... looks aren't everything.
I have a compendium
of Jerome's obsessions and goals, and...
I will outdo every one of them.
Jerome wanted to turn Gotham
into a madhouse.
But... to truly build something,
you must first tear down
what is already there.
I apologize for the deception, Jim.
I needed to ape Jerome
in order to persuade
his followers to throw
that macabre celebration
at your police station.
They are a pathetic lot,
but not without their uses.
Ah, sidebar.
That is a self-perpetuating generator.
It can store
a phenomenal amount of energy.
I would hate to be within a mile
of it if it were to...
overload.
Jeremiah, the gas worked.
Think about it: You want to carry out
Jerome's crazy plan sanely?
What could be madder than that?
Madder?
Let's see.
Ah. Here, for example.
Jerome wanted to slather you in honey
and have you eaten alive
by corpse beetles.
Now, that's mad.
Me, if I want to kill you,
I'll just do it.
I'll shoot you in the head.
Simply and sanely.
Jeremiah.
But I don't want to kill you.
Come on!
Are you gonna listen?
Or you gonna behave like children?
See, I don't want to kill you,
because I want to show you
how much I've changed things.
How much we've changed things.
'Cause I could not have done any of this
without your help.
My help?
That sound you are hearing...
that is a very bad sound.
One which I'm afraid makes you
something of a guinea pig, Jim.
I feel very indebted to you, Bruce.
See...
those generators
that we built with your money,
they work even better as bombs.
Killing you will help secure
the loyalty of Jerome's minions,
and, well, that is that.
Good-bye.
All right, everybody, listen up!
You know what to do!
Let's go get our house back!
That's one down.
Jim Gordon is dead.
No! No!
Yes, Bruce.
Sorry, but progress requires sacrifice.
I'm going to stop you.
I really hope you don't try.
I would hate to have to kill you.
In fact, I can honestly say...
you are my very best friend.
What I want to know...
with a minimum of fuss,
is what you and your cohort
were really up to today.
I'll never betray the memory of Jer...
Shh. Wouldn't dream of it.
I don't expect you to betray
the memory of that old corpse.
I want you to betray whomever it is
you are currently following.
Long live Jerome.
He's not talking.
Is that so?
You staring at me?
Yeah, I get it.
Sometimes I...
accidentally catch a glimpse
of myself in the mirror, and...
it scares me, too.
And then I get angry.
The longer I'm like this,
the angrier I get.
And right now, the way I see it,
you are preventing me
from finding a cure.
And that...
makes me very, very angry.
Is your plan
to gain his sympathy
by reciting your tale of woe?
Nah.
Just wanted to see if I could get him
to pee his pants a little in terror.
You want me to
shove some chicken bones
up his nose till he squawks?
Yes. That will do.
No.
Let's make this quick.
- No. No.
- Tilt your head back.
- Here comes the wishbone train!
- No. No, no, wait!
Smartest man in Gotham.
And you let your heart do the thinking.
Wake up, Ed.
Ow.
Were you awake the whole time?
Maybe.
Smartest man in Gotham, huh?
All right, get up. Up, up, up, up.
There are better things
to aspire to, you know.
I'm aspiring to them very much.
Just be yourself.
The guy who can let go
of the past and change.
I like that guy.
All right, now, how are we
gonna get past these psychos?
I'm assuming you brought
one of those for me?
Oh. Now, I would be into that,
but they only had one.
Instead...
the cavalry should be coming very soon.
Great.
Round 'em up!
Move, move, move! Let's go, let's go.
Okay.
Don't just wrap me
around your finger, Lee.
Come on. Let's run.
Where's my phone call?
That's for taking a leak on my desk.
What a mess.
You know, it's funny,
it kind of reminds me
of my first apartment in Crown Point.
How long ago was that?
I still live there.
Harvey.
I found the epicenter of that explosion.
It's Jeremiah's bunker.
That's where Jim was going
to look for Bruce.
Good evening, gentlemen.
Hey there, Mr. Valeska.
You alone, or you got
Mr. Wayne with you?
No Mr. Wayne.
But I'm not alone.
What the hell?!
Look at these.
The gifts of true friendship.
Let's load them on the trucks.
It's time to give Gotham City
its new face.
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com