Welcome to Wayne Enterprises.
I have some questions regarding
Wayne Enterprises' business affairs.
Where's Jim?
Don Falcone thinks
you don't know how to run a club.
- Hi.
- He'll help you out.
Those people out there
are using us as spare parts...
unless we do something about it.
- Alfred, can you teach me how to fight?
- Yes, I can.
BULLOCK:
Pretty handy for a valet.
Butler, mate. I'm a butler.
- What the hell is that?
- I made it.
MAN: You made it?
- Yeah.
- So, what is it?
- Well, it's a hood.
- Thought it would spice things up.
- When did we start wearing hoods?
- We didn't.
- Was I supposed to get one?
No.
MAN 1: Ladies...
MAN 2: And gentlemen.
We are not here for your money,
we're here for the bank's money.
So just stay cool and no one will get hurt.
Don't be brave.
Don't be frightened.
Do what you're told
and this will be over quicker...
than that time I hooked up
with a cheerleader on prom night.
- What are you doing up there?
- Getting them fired up.
- Ninety seconds.
MAN 2: Easy, ladies and gentlemen.
You know, banks like this one,
who are insured to death, by the way...
steal from us every single day.
About time a few of us returned the favor,
don't you think?
Sixty seconds.
You're doing great, folks, almost done.
Forty seconds.
MAN 2:
Nothing.
Not a scratch.
[LAUGHING]
- Thirty seconds.
- Let's get out of here!
You've been great, ladies and germs,
but we gotta go.
Did you see that?
That guy missed me with, like, six shots.
- He was old, nervous.
- No, no, no, it's the hood, I'm telling you.
[SIRENS WAILING]
- Damn it.
- We're cooked.
MAN:
Attention, citizens of Gotham.
- What the hell are you doing?
- There you go, everybody!
[PEOPLE SHOUTING]
Take back what's yours!
Follow me. Come on.
[WOMAN SOBBING]
BULLOCK: Well, we'll never know
how much cash was lost...
but I just saw a bum
eating oysters at Madeline's.
Another freak in a mask. Awesome.
Is that guard blind or wasted?
Clyde refused to wear his glasses,
said they made him look old.
Missing a man standing 20 feet in front
of you with six shots makes you look old.
- Who tripped the alarm?
- I did.
Why aren't you out there, detective?
This brazen audacity cannot be tolerated.
They didn't go for the vault.
Just the cash in the registers.
And the crew was in and out
in under two minutes.
The red-hooded man seemed nice.
Nice?
He wasn't stealing our money.
Just the bank's.
Then he gave a lot of it back
to people in the street...
like Robin Hood.
Great. This bank hires communists.
Robin Hood stole from the rich
and gave to the poor.
These armed thieves only threw cash away
to guarantee their escape.
It's very different, ma'am.
The thief in the back here.
- Was he always checking his watch?
- Yes, he was counting down.
- They knew what our response time was.
- Done their homework.
Has the alarm been triggered
for any reason recently?
- No.
- Well...
there was that time with the smoke bomb.
- Smoke bomb?
- A week or so ago...
a small flare or firework or something
was set off by the mortgages desk.
It tripped the alarm.
We thought it was just a kid's prank.
We're gonna need you to find the
surveillance footage from that incident.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Yes, sir. How can I help you?
Reggie?
I'm sorry for calling so late.
Forgive me.
Oh, my God, mate, how long has it been?
Twenty years.
I got picked up by the G.C.P.D. last night
for sleeping under the Westbury Bridge.
- Here, mate.
- Cheers, mate.
One of the officers was a Marine
back in the day.
I told him I was with Her Majesty's
Special Air Service back in the day.
So he took pity on me.
He says, "Why don't you look up
some of your old regiment?
You know,
see if one of the guys can help you out?"
Well, you know...
Pleased you looked me up, Reg.
If anyone would've told me this is where I'd
find you, I wouldn't have believed them.
I like it here, you know.
It's good for me.
I can see that.
I've missed you, mate.
Missed your ugly mug.
Cheers.
What happened, Reggie?
Vanessa died...
11 years ago now.
I just couldn't find the energy
to get back out there after that, you know?
Year later, I lost the house,
moved back to Gotham.
I've had a few jobs.
Nothing I'm proud of.
It was the drink, Alfie.
It was the drink.
BRUCE:
Alfred?
Um, Master Bruce.
This is, uh, Reginald Payne.
We served together, sir.
Very pleased to meet you, sir.
You were caught in the storm?
Reggie's had a run of bad luck,
Master Bruce.
I don't wish to be a nuisance, I just...
I hadn't seen Alfie in a very long time.
No, I'm glad you found us, Mr. Payne. Please
feel free to stay with us a few days.
- That's very kind of you, but...
- I insist.
Please.
Where are you taking me?
This way, Ms. Mooney.
Who chose these people?
Where did you get them from?
Sit, please.
Sit.
There you are, Mr. Red Hood.
Armed robbery perps dating back 10 years. I
took out dead ones and the ones in prison.
A who's who of scumbags.
They were casing the place
before they took it down...
set off the alarm and
timed the response.
He looks pretty young.
He might not be in here.
- You see that?
- No, because you took my glasses.
Right there underneath his coat.
He's wearing a work shirt.
"Kleg's Auto."
Idiot.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
"The Red Hood Gang."
It's got a ring to it.
- No, it doesn't.
- You see those people? They loved me.
- They loved the money you threw at them.
- Thanks for that.
- Shall we take it out of your share?
- You guys don't get it.
We're not just five mooks
with shotguns anymore.
We're the Red Hood Gang.
Taking from the rich
and giving back to the poor.
Mark my words, the people in this town,
they're gonna get me.
- Us.
MAN 1: Will you shut up?
That prancing could've gotten us killed.
You're wrong. That guard was 2O feet away
from me, not one shot got close.
- Luck!
- He looked real nervous.
It's the hood. It's good
luck, I'm telling you.
- I feel like a different person with
it on. MAN 2: Sit down, will you?
- We need to go over tomorrow's score.
- No, this sets us apart.
It's a piece of cloth,
two holes cut out of it.
It's a symbol.
Whoever wears the hood should lead.
[GUNSHOT]
He's right.
Any objections?
So you're the one causing all of the fuss?
The one with the knife now?
This is your facility?
I manage it, yes.
But do you own it?
The doctor owns it.
- Where are you going?
- Back to the basement.
- We're done here.
- Ms. Mooney.
Take a seat.
I will talk to the doctor
and the doctor only.
He's away on a consultation in Gotham.
Then call me when he returns.
He expressly asked me
to attend to your demands.
His name.
I'm sorry?
The doctor. His name.
Dulmacher.
You tell Dr. Dulmacher
that the basement is mine.
No one will leave unless I say so.
It will remain that way until he
sits with me and negotiates terms.
Perhaps you and I got off on
the wrong foot, Ms. Mooney.
When was the last time you had a shower?
New set of clothes? Hmm?
[INTERCOM BUZZES]
Take Ms. Mooney to my private bathroom...
and then pick up some fresh clothes
for her from storage.
Freshen up. Come back to me.
And then perhaps we'll talk some more.
So the mortician says to the waitress...
No, the waitress says to the mortician:
"He was always stiff."
MAN 1: That's it. Let's go.
- Wait, no.
Have a good night. See you next week, sir.
- Okay. That's fine, we got...
MAN 2: Check, please.
[ALL WHISPERING]
What's wrong?
Mr. Penguin. I mean, the Penguin. I mean...
What is it?
We're out of booze.
What? Hello?
Behind you, there's a wall of booze.
Just colored water, sir. Always has been.
We keep the real stuff down here,
but we're out.
- So, duh, order more.
- We did.
- It's just that...
BUTCH: It's Maroni's booze.
And he's a little grumpy
with you these days.
He was hardly a fan of Fish, either.
Why did he sell her booze?
Business is business.
But he hates you with a passion.
But he can't kill you, so...
This is ridiculous.
There's a thousand places to buy booze.
Well, that's where it gets complicated. See,
Maroni, he supplies this whole side of town.
No one would dare cross him to help you.
MAN 3: Boo!
- Thank you. Bye. Sorry.
MAN 4: You're not funny.
MAN 5: And you're not telling jokes.
You must take great pleasure
watching me fail.
On the contrary.
I was with Fish when we took this place
off a Chinese bookie nine years ago.
It was used for cockfighting.
Took forever to get the smell out.
My blood, sweat and tears are in this dive.
Well, if you'll excuse me...
it seems as though I need to procure
some alcohol for my dwindling clientele.
Be careful.
You've seen what happens
when you cross Maroni.
G.C.P.D.
Looks like they were here last night.
Hey. Your hot doctor friend, Thompkins.
- Leslie?
- Whatever.
Give me the double D. Dirty details.
Don't leave anything out.
Ha, ha. Gotta hand it to you, partner.
You don't sit around moping.
You got right back up on the hobbyhorse.
Let's just hope you can keep
your head straight whilst up there.
You had the purse,
now you got yourself the nurse.
Well, looks like I found our friend Floyd.
What? If I don't drink it, Forensics will.
All right. This was the guy with the hood.
He's wearing the same coat.
Wonder what he did
to piss off the rest of his crew.
Maybe they knew we'd catch up to him.
He was the leader, so it looks like we've
seen the last of the Red Hood crew now.
[ALL SCREAM]
Good morning, everyone.
Get off me. I got it.
We're not here for your money.
We're here for the insurance.
I mean, the bank's insured money.
Sixty seconds.
Hey, you gonna share
a little bit of that cash with us, Hood?
Thirty seconds.
Come on, a lot of us are hurting here.
Ten seconds. Let's go.
Ugh, fine.
[MAN LAUGHING AND CROWD SHOUTING]
So long, Gotham.
[SPEAKS IN JAPANESE]
And then there were four.
People are gonna hang out in banks
waiting for handouts from these idiots.
Can't catch a crew
no one wants us to catch.
Call me old-fashioned. When crooks are
more popular than cops, that's anarchy.
Think about it, as long as somebody's
willing to put that red hood on...
this gang can go on forever.
Hey, guys, got somebody
here you might wanna meet.
- This is Mr...?
- Chaing.
Chaing, right. He's an eyewitness.
From the bank?
I work at a restaurant a block away. The
gang parked their van there this morning.
I was throwing out the trash
when they ran back to it.
You see their faces?
Just one, the fat one with the hood.
He took it off to drive.
- I'll get the sketch artist.
- No, wait a minute.
We got the armed robbery files
already opened.
He can look through them,
see if he recognizes someone.
Maybe that someone is an associate
of Gus Floyd.
Problem is, records are old.
He might look different now.
We can pull a few
based off Chaing's description.
Get ourselves a good old-fashioned lineup.
Hey, wait a second. What's in it for me?
I got all these parking tickets
because my ex-wife is a crazy bitch.
We'll see what we can do.
[PANTING]
REGGIE:
You training for a fight?
- Just training.
- Who's helping you?
Alfred.
Good choice.
Show me your stance.
Good.
Hit me.
Again.
Whoa.
And don't hold back.
You have a go at me, son.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Come on. It should take more than that
to piss you off, son.
Come on.
Again.
[REGGIE LAUGHS]
Now, now. Never lose your cool.
It'll get you killed.
You wanna hit me, right?
Okay. Take a swing.
Take a swing. Go on, do it.
If somebody gives you a free shot,
you gotta make it count.
Now, you hit me as hard as you can.
Better. Put your shoulder behind it.
Put your body weight behind it.
Go on. Do it.
Harder. Again.
Again. Come on. Do it again.
Put me on my back, son.
Come on, you can do it. Come on, again.
- You're bigger than me.
- Use that to your advantage.
You hit me low.
Hit me in the knee, the ankle.
Forget about the gloves.
Use whatever's around you.
Here. Here.
Right.
That's enough of that.
Perhaps a shower's in order, Master Bruce.
Mr. Payne was just showing me
some alternative methods.
Yeah, I can see that, can't I?
Not methods that fit into our curriculum,
though, are they?
- No, they're not, but they're effective.
- Discipline, skill and hard work are effective.
Now, how about
I start that shower for you, sir?
No.
You ever raised a child before, Reg?
Me neither.
Hardest job I've ever had to do in my life.
Nothing prepares you for it.
Listen, I'm sorry if I overstepped
the mark. I was just...
- It's obvious how much you've helped him...
- No, he helped me.
I'm a better person for knowing him, Reg.
Let's keep our past where it belongs.
In the past.
That's it? Just two workers?
This'll be easy.
Make it quick, guys.
[SIRENS WAIL]
Well, this is inconvenient.
Whoa, officer. Nothing going on here.
Is that so?
Your liquor license is out of date.
- We're gonna be confiscating this
shipment. MAN: Does Don Maroni know?
Walk away before I run you downtown.
This town is truly going to the dogs.
Evening, fellas.
[MUTTERING]
Why the smile, Butch?
First, Maroni blocks our liquor,
and now, the cops.
Oh, who, them? They're with me.
I always keep a few uniforms in the closet.
A lot cleaner than going in guns blazing,
don't you think?
You're welcome, Oswald.
Nice work there.
- It's over here.
MAN: Nothing to worry about.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
OVER HEADPHONES]
Are you okay?
Of course.
Thank you for letting us stay here.
Sorry it got a little messy.
I was just about to go.
I like having you guys here.
[BARBARA COUGHS]
Selina.
Come here.
You know, you're turning
into quite a beautiful woman.
No, I'm not.
Remove the dirt...
that old hood, these ratty clothes.
How about we find a princess undernea...?
I have an idea.
Holy mOW-
BARBARA:
Take anything that fits you guys.
This is all stuff you've worn?
Most of it.
You sure must go out a lot.
I used to.
Come with me.
You're a true beauty.
Something you can use to your advantage.
Your appearance can be a weapon.
As powerful as any knife or gun.
Yeah?
What good's it done you?
BULLOCK: All right, backs to the wall.
Hold your numbers up. No talking.
- I thought they would be similar types.
- They are.
Look closely, Mr. Chaing.
I know how this works.
There, number four. The short fat one.
- You're sure?
- That's your Red Hood.
Threw all that money away
and I didn't get a cent.
Clyde Destro, 47. Conviction for assault
and robbery of a store three years ago.
- Let's book him.
- Wait a minute.
All we have is one witness
outside of the crime scene, that's it.
Now, Floyd was killed,
so we know they're turning on each other.
- Let Destro go?
- And tail him.
He takes us to the others,
we use them against each other.
- We catch the Red Hood Gang red-handed.
- That's right.
Can I get a ride home?
My girlfriend will freak out
if I turn up in a patrol car.
[DOOR OPENS]
MAN:
Well...
don't you look lovely?
There's still business to discuss.
Of course.
The basement.
How do I resume operations?
We do have a business to run.
Yes. You're stealing body parts.
For who?
We have clients all over the world
in need of such things.
Also, there's the doctor's...
personal experiments.
You have such a presence, Ms. Mooney.
Such a gaze.
Your eyes will fetch quite a penny.
You will take nothing from me.
Really? Because the way I see it,
you have two choices:
One, we kill you and your little friends
in the basement.
That's an inconvenience,
but an acceptable one.
Or two...
we take your eyes now...
and see how long a blind girl
can survive in the basement.
You forgot option three.
Stop her. No!
[SCREAMS]
No!
Oh, I know Eddie. Eddie...
I picked something out from the cellar.
I hope that's okay.
Well, that's really kind of you, Master
Bruce, but I think that we'll...
not be drinking this evening.
I'm sure it's perfectly fine
to have a glass of wine occasionally.
I picked an old one. Seems a shame
to let them gather dust down there.
"Domaine de la Romanée-Conti."
It's a rather nice Burgundy, actually.
It's a 1966.
Yeah. It's one of your father's favorites.
Why not, eh?
Take a pew.
- That's very kind of you.
ALFRED: There we go.
Cheers, mate.
Now, the idea, of course,
is to let it breathe for at least an hour.
Or not.
Delicious.
So he eventually opened his backpack
and he finds the bloody snake.
We've been waiting for it all night.
He didn't even flinch.
What did you do?
Oh, you know, I chopped its head off
and we ate the bloody thing.
We did.
- What did it taste like?
- Well, a bit like, um, fast food.
[ALL LAUGHING]
- It was horrible, wasn't it?
- It was horrible.
It was disgusting.
So, Mr. Payne, you were in the air force?
Special Air Service. SAS.
Best soldiers in the world.
If I'm being honest.
So that means covert missions?
That's right.
Before a conflict,
they dropped us behind enemy lines.
We were quiet, precise and deadly.
We never lost a man,
and we always completed our missions.
Except that once, I guess.
Yeah, well, that's enough
of the old war stories, eh, Reg?
What one time?
REGGIE:
There was a sandstorm.
We got separated.
Two of us were captured.
You?
REGGIE: He fought 12 of them off
before they cut him down.
Didn't you, Alf?
I'm here now, aren't I? It's what matters.
All right, gents, well,
I have to say this has been lovely...
but I'd like to tidy
up before I go to bed.
Heh. Tidy up?
Mr. Yes-Sir-No-Sir.
- Mr. Queensbury-Rules-and-Discipline.
- Thank you, that's enough.
Alfred's right.
It's time for bed.
- Good night, Master Bruce.
BRUCE: Good night, good night.
ALFRED:
Sleep well, son.
Why are you hiding from him
what you really are? Who you really are?
You're a war dog, Alfie.
You're a cold-blooded,
lethal war dog is what you are.
I've found some fresh clothes for you, Reg.
I folded them and I put them on your bed.
And I've taken the liberty of packing you
a lunch for your travels tomorrow.
It's been really nice to see you, Reggie.
I see them at night when I'm alone.
Their faces.
The faces of those we killed.
Do you?
I don't have to look for them, Reg.
They find me.
[GASPS]
DESTRO:
Holy crap.
You scared the snot out of me.
I had to see you. I couldn't wait.
- Where were you?
- Out.
What, just out?
What's it to you?
I need the hood.
What?
No.
My girlfriend, she wants to leave.
She called me a loser last night.
Her ex is back in town, he's a bouncer.
I figured she sees me in the hood,
she's gotta take me seriously.
Did you ransack my place looking for it?
I need it, Destro.
They're talking about it
on the streets and in the news.
- She sees me in it and I'm...
- No.
We have one last job
before we split up and skip town.
You have it on you, don't you?
You better use that thing
before I make you eat it.
[GUNSHOT]
[DESTRO GASPING]
He's alive.
Who shot you, Destro?
Give us the name of the guy.
- I need an ambulance.
- We'll get to that. The names of your crew.
- I'm bleeding out.
- Yeah, you're dying.
And unfortunately,
I'm not getting cell reception.
You know what might help?
The names of the guys in your crew!
GORDON:
I need an ambulance.
Java Heights and Homewood.
Apartment 466.
I might need some pressure on this wound.
Knock yourself out.
What do you got there, partner?
A stack of loan rejection letters
from the banks that were robbed.
"Dear Mr. Destro, we regret to inform you
your loan application has been denied."
"Mr. Destro, once again, we must deny your
application due to lack of collateral."
- What the hell would he need a loan for?
- Pastry shop.
Get out of here. You're a baker?
A damn good baker.
And they all turned you down?
So these are revenge robberies?
Banks don't care about people like me.
Or you, probably.
You have to force people to see you.
Otherwise, you're nothing.
There's a third letter here.
"International Savings Bank of Gotham."
This was the next target.
Where's my ambulance?
To new beginnings.
[SNIFFS]
I'm not trying to poison you, son.
Forgive me if I'm a little cautious.
If this club tanks, Falcone's not gonna
trust either of us again.
I don't know about you,
but I'm done playing the sidekick.
To no longer being a sidekick.
Do you miss her?
I do.
Even after everything she did to me.
Perhaps it's not our friends,
but our enemies that define us.
To Fish.
She got what she deserved.
[METAL CLANGING]
You're stealing from us?
You could have just asked me
for money, Reg.
You don't know how hard
that is, Alfie, do you?
We gave you somewhere to sleep.
We put food in your belly.
I'm in trouble.
Real trouble.
I don't need a lecture right now.
What kind of trouble?
You don't wanna know.
Right. Well, you put the bag down...
and you leave, now.
Did you bring a gun, Alfie?
No.
If there was any other way...
Oh, come on,
there's always another way, mate.
I'm sorry.
Sorry for...?
[ALFRED GROANS]
I'm so sorry.
This is Bruce Wayne. I need help at
Wayne Manor. My friend has been stabbed.
Alfred? Alfred, Alfred, look at me.
You're gonna be okay.
Alfred, stay with me.
Please.
Alfred.
There's only three of us.
- I'm worried if someone makes a move...
- Don't be.
I have this.
GORDON:
G.C.P.D.
We have you surrounded.
It doesn't have to end badly.
Put down your guns.
Suck it, coppers!
GORDON:
Hold your fire.
Drop it.
It's over.
MAN:
Yeah?
Don't be so sure.
I need a Danish.
Yeah?
Which hospital?
I can't lose him.
He's all I have.
REGGIE: He has nothing concrete.
Just faces, some dates.
Some newspaper articles.
There's no grounds for an investigation.
Just suspicions,
some cobbled-together theories.
Nothing.
WOMAN:
Has he had outside counsel?
I don't think so.
WOMAN:
And his caretaker, Mr. Pennyworth?
He's in the hospital.
WOMAN:
For how long?
If he lives, a few weeks, give or take.
Now is the time to make a move on the kid.
Thank you for your service, Mr. Payne.
I doubt we'll meet again.
He's just a kid.
A good kid.
Goodbye, Mr. Payne.