GORDON: Previously on Gotham...
- Oink. Oink.
- What the...
GORDON: A cop was murdered last night.
A bag man on your pay roll?
I think someone is trying
to send you a message.
Grenade!
- We have unfinished business.
- Listen, if you think you're gonna...
Don't talk about my mother!
BARBARA: An opportunity awaits you.
SELINA: With you and Barbara,
the three of us could give
all those creeps a run for their money.
PENGUIN: She's making alliances with
politicians, building a fortress,
She's been planning a war.
Oswald. I want you to know
I forgive you.
- PENGUIN: Just started an orphanage?
- I wanted to surprise you.
RA'S: If you don't kill me.
I will kill everyone you love.
(GROANING)
It doesn't stop till I've butchered
every single swine
on Penguin's payroll.
We both know, Captain Bullock,
you deserve this.
Hold on, buddy.
How long have you been
taking money from Penguin?
You gotta understand, Jim,
the debts I got...
Stops now.
Called dibs on my office?
- I ain't dead yet.
- Just measuring for when you are.
Shouldn't you be resting?
Lemme help you.
I'm fine.
Great.
S0 we can talk about you
taking Penguin's money.
- I'm not that fine.
- I meant what I said, Harvey.
- This stops today, you hear me?
- OFFICER: Hey, hey!
What the hell is that?
You're trying to change the subject.
Obviously.
But seriously, what the hell is that?
(GUNS cocxme)
OFFICER: Is that blood?
DELIVERY MAN:
Some fancy-ass guy on the phone.
How was I supposed to know
what we were carrying?
Stench of death, for starters.
I got a cold.
Forty-four boxes.
One for every cop in the precinct.
(INDISTINCT CHATFERING)
Pyg's escalating.
He's not just after dirty caps anymore,
it's the whole GCPD.
There are 45 cops here.
DELIVERY MAN:
Oh, yeah. The instructions said.
"Don't give nothing
to this one cop here, named..."
Uh...
Jim Gordon?
- (GUESTS CHATTERING)
- (MUSIC PLAYING)
Support are really pleased that you
enjoyed the finger food.
Helping the needy.
Very good for the soul, Master Bruce.
I have to say I really appreciate you
allowing us to do the fundraiser here.
The society meant
a great deal to your father.
As long as I don't
have to leave the house.
Well, you're Bruce Wayne, ain't you?
The world can come to you.
Hey. What the hell?
- Excuse me?
- You knocked into me.
Bruce...
- Sorry, I didn't notice...
- Well, you should've.
- Bruce...
- Honestly, I'm really sorry.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I haven't wanted to push, Master Bruce.
I mean, what happened with Ra's.
I know that you're hurting.
- Just please tell me what I can do...
- You can get off my back!
Sorry.
Ijust...
I can't stop thinking
about
what I...
I should feel bad,
9uilty, I...
- I'd just...
- You're just angry.
That anger is concealing
what's really going on.
Unless you face it full on,
it will consume you
and it'Il erupt.
I know what you're capable of.
And I don't want to see you
or anybody else get hurt.
I need some air.
GORDON: (SIGHS) AII right.
Next time you see red stuff
dripping from a package,
- consider calling the police.
- Where's COD?
Get the hell out of here.
Hey, Jim...
James, I am s0 happy
we are working hand in hand
to rid the city of this menace.
(CHUCKLES)
- Hejust showed up to offer his help.
- Did he?
Nice to meet you, Jim. I'm Headhunter.
I'm sure you've heard of me.
My new security consultant.
Recommended by Victor,
who is off visiting his bubby.
You wanna know why I carry two pistols?
Overcompensation?
See, I always shoot twice.
The first one does the job every time,
but the second one, well,
that's just my signature. Hmm.
He has a signature.
- C0lorful, isn't he? But effective.
- Mmm.
Mr. Headhunter and my men
will help the GCPD
until this Pyg situation is resolved.
We don't want your help
or that of your idiot hitman.
Pyg's actions threaten the both of us.
He's killing my cops, my employees.
Allegedly.
Get this through you head, Oswald.
We don't work for you,
and we don't work with you, ever.
(LAUGHS)
Well, your captain says otherwise.
Excited to work with you, Jim.
- Are you out of your freakin' mind?
- Jim, listen...
You are legitimizing him, Harvey.
He's been legitimized for years,
he was the freakin' mayor.
GORDON:
Is it about the money. is that it?
It's not about that.
How can I know that?
- How can you even know that?
- Take a look out there, okay?
Half the precinct skipped town
because they didn't want to wear
bacon flavored death masks.
We need the help.
You are dangerously overreacting.
I'm overreacting because every cop
in this precinct got a death threat.
Except, of course, for you.
S0 Penguin's guys are gonna
beat and torture their way
through the city,
- then execute Pyg if they find him?
- And?
And the people need to know
they don't need gangsters
to keep them safe.
I'II tell you what,
I'm gonna find Pyg, alive.
And I'II bring him tojustice.
Good for you.
Three cops just went missing.
Where?
It's gonna be tough. It's The Narrows.
So that's it. We're shutting up shop.
So long, farewell. Toodledoo.
- I can't believe this.
- I can.
AII this was so I could be
Ra's eyes and ears in Gotham.
He was bankrolling us,
and now, he's gone.
S0 I'm pulling the plug.
Help yourself to whatever.
So, all of this, being partners,
building something together... Lies.
A sales pitch. I couldn't do it alone.
We can still spy on thejerks
who come in here,
and get intel on jobs.
- We can make it work.
- What,
and the three of us stay together.
Like a plucky little family?
Well, how about a little
parting lesson from big sis?
In this life, you're on your own.
Always.
Ugh!
Bonus lesson:
Never make bellinis from a can.
I followed a buyer
from The Street Demonz.
They have a chop shop across town
and I saw exactly
where they hide their stash.
Let's hit it. Show her she's wrong.
We're not gonna rip off one of
Gotham's biggest motorcycle gangs.
Why not?
You and I will find something else.
(SIGHS HEAVILY)
(SIRENS WAILING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
Three missing officers.
Patel from our precinct.
Fazoli and Percoff from the 22.
Good Lord, there's blood all over.
He got 'em here.
Clear view from dozens of windows,
someone saw it.
They sure did.
AII right. bring it in everybody,
come on.
This is The Narrows.
The poorest of the poor.
The hardest of the hard.
Now I don't need to tell you that
they got a code of silence down here.
Which means we gotta make 'em
more scared of us
than they are of their own people.
We go floor by floor.
- AirmaiL
- (PANICKED SHOUTING)
(CHUCKLES)
Let's get 'em. Move on out!
This is gonna be fun.
- (0FFICERS SHOUTING)
- (MAN GROANING)
Get off of him! Ge! back!
Hey! Get off of 'em! Get off of 'em!
They're potential witness,
they're not perps.
This is The Narrows, Gordon.
You think there's a difference?
- Step away, Ruseckas.
- HARVEY: Hey, hey, hey!
Ruseckas, they need you upstairs.
You two, go, now.
(WOMAN soaamc)
Working out great.
If it gets me my cap-killer.
Yeah, it is.
Right.
(CLASSICAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Bruce.
Ijust wanted to say hi.
I'm Grace. We went to school together.
Grace Plumdoll.
Yeah. Sorry, I...
It's been years, I didn't recognize you.
- I heard you were homeschooling.
- Yeah.
Iam...
Why aren't you in school?
Because it's Saturday.
I don't mean to knock your fundraiser,
but is there any chance
that you're as bored as I am?
- You'd have to be pretty bored.
- (GRACE LAUGHS)
S0, do you wanna maybe go somewhere?
Yeah.
(INDISTINCT CLAMORING)
MALE TENANT: I don't know nothin'!
Come on, man, just leave me alone.
May l'_›
OFFICER: Hold it right there.
Ma'am, please.
I'm Detective Gordon.
We didn't see nothin'.
But you knew those missing cops
or knew of 'em, right?
Three officers, different precinct.
Same patrol car.
They were freelancing.
I know how it is down here.
Lot of bad stuff happens.
Half the time it's the cops doing it.
They were running some sort of
protection racket, am I right?
You sit over here.
Yeah? It gives you a pretty good view.
So what'd you see?
Please. I need you to leave.
No one's gonna know
you told me anything.
I give you my word.
- Can I help?
- Get out of here, now.
(OLD MAN COUGHING)
Will do, Jim.
Hey!
This is ridiculous,
we're on the same team.
(OLD MAN GASPING)
Get up. Get up, get up, come on.
Come on.
The old lady doesn't talk,
the old man gets it.
And after that,
I go apartment by apartment
until I get an answer.
Drop it.
- (GUNS COCKING)
- Back at you, Jim.
HARVEY: Whoa!
Whoa. Everybody stand down.
- I'm giving you three seconds.
- I'm giving you two.
No one is counting.
You drop your weapon.
I'II tell you what I saw.
He took them.
He was driving a hearse.
I didn't see the plate.
That's all right.
We don't need the plate.
Just tell me which direction
was he headed.
Down 7th.
Heading west.
Hey, thanks, Jim.
You know, I never really did
the whole good cop/bad cop thing.
It's quite effective.
West on 7th, that's Hoover Island.
It's tiny, there's only
a couple of abandoned buildings.
We can canvass the whole area
in 10 minutes.
- Yeah.
- HEADHUNTER: And the second shot,
well, thafsjust my Signature.
I know it doesn't look good.
But no one got hurt too bad.
And we got what we needed, right?
You just...
You gotta trust me on this one,
partner, okay?
People, we're moving out
to Hoover Island right now.
Let's move, go! Go.
Come on!
OFFICER:
This is the last building, let's go.
I got two in here!
(OFFICER WHIMPERING)
This man's alive, call an ambulance.
(PANTING)
- Help me.
- We will. We're here.
Jim. Pyg disappeared.
There's no sign
of the third cop anywhere.
AII right. Ge! some help!
Hddom
Oh, God. It's okay.
As you can see behind me,
we just had a major police operation.
A raid of some sort on this abandoned...
Sophia! Look! Those are my men.
And there's that Headhunter person
I was talking about.
Kind of a moron, but he is effective.
Found dead at scene.
Another is in stable condition
and on his way to Gotham General.
(LAUGHS) So, technically.
I saved that cop's life.
Such great PR. (LAUGHS)
GCPD.
A number of what I've been told are...
Excuse me, little person. Scoot.
Of former Mayor, Arkham inmate
and alleged crime lord,
Oswald Cobblepot.
It is unclear why Mr. Cobblepot
is aiding the police.
Is co-opting the police not the most
brilliant idea I've ever had?
It is Pax Penguina taken
to a whole other level.
Back to you, Matt.
Hello?
Isn't it?
Oh. You don't need to know what I think.
Well, now I definitely do.
(SIGHS)
Ears.
My father never w0uld've
publicly aligned with the GCPD.
They're incompetent and unreliable.
Eventually they will fail, and fail big.
And you will fail with them.
S0.
That's what I think.
- Thank you for your input.
- You're welcome, Oswald.
Because you have shown me,
very clearly, what not to do.
In fact, I'm gonna get more involved.
Personally.
Don't ask for my opinion
if you don't want to hear it.
Okay.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(CAR ALARM BLARING)
MAN: Yo!
The alarm's going off, what the hell?
Someone broke in?
I was... I was under the car.
The stash is gone.
Guy musta got out.
So, you musta messed up your onlyjob.
Guess it's time to burn rubber.
(GROANING)
Please. No!
- Get under.
- No!
Go on then, do what he says!
“°. no. no!
(MAN SCREAMING)
(SIREN WAILING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(SIGHS)
- Yeah?
- HARVEY: Hey.
We scanned the entire area.
Still no sign of Pyg or Officer Patel.
You get anything off Fazoli?
No, not a whole lot.
Wait a minute. He's coming to.
I'II call you back.
Officer Fazoli, it's okay.
It's all right.
You're on your way to Gotham General.
You're safe.
I'm Detective Gordon.
- Yeah, I know who you are.
- You were taken by The Pyg.
Did you happen to see his face?
No, he wore a mask.
The others?
Percoff didn't make it.
Patel's gone missing.
Do you remember anything?
I don't know, man.
He was torturing us for hours.
He was singing nursery rhymes
and talking crazy.
Oh, jeez.
I watched him bleed out Percoff.
Did he say anything about Patel?
I don't know, I don't remember.
Look at me, look what he did to me.
AII right. all right, all right.
Let's take a break.
Why is he doing this?
'Cause he's insane.
But it's more than that.
I guess he just reached
a breaking point.
There's so much rot in Gotham.
AII of it. High to low.
Sometimes, even Ifeel like breaking,
you know?
I was on Penguin's pay.
Started off with small stuff, and...
Deliveries, and payoffs, and then
it got bad.
I get it.
I've done bad stuff myself.
For Penguin. even.
But you and I can make it right.
Once I get Pyg,
I'm gonna take down The Pax Penguina.
And then I'm gonna go after
the dirty cops, one by one.
Now you have a chance
to make right what you've done wrong.
Help me.
Pyg is planning something.
Nearby... He was...
Maybe where he took Patel and he...
He kept saying something about.
"I'II bring justice to where there's
justice no more."
"Justice." The courthouse?
There ain't no courthouse
in The Narrows.
There's one they abandoned
a few years back.
Pull it over, I'm getting out.
DRIVER: Yes, sir.
- Thank you, Officer Fazoli.
- Hey...
You are one of the good ones, Jim.
Hey, Brant,
I ran into an old friend, Bruce Wayne.
Bruce, this Emma Hsueh and Tommy Elliot.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
- You two know each other?
- TOMMY: Oh, yeah.
Last time I saw this guy,
he punched me in the face.
- I should go.
- TOMMY: Hey, hold on, bro.
I totally deserved it.
If anything,
you Should've hit me harder.
S0 true. He was such a jerk back then.
- Okay.
- Little heads up
next time you just bring
some random kid to my place...
- Parents' place, Brant.
- He's so jealous.
Brant wanted Grace all to himself.
Whatever. You want a shot?
Maybe sample some party favorites?
I'm good.
I forgot about this guy, total animal.
So, what do you do for fun?
I used to walk on rooftops
and fight crime.
Now I'm not so sure.
Whoa! You're a bigger dork
than I remember. Just kidding.
Hey, whatever happened
to that creepy old guy, the butler,
is he still butling?
I'm kidding.
It's a joke.
But. seriously, does he butle with you?
- Bruce!
- Bruce, stop!
Stop! Bruce, get off him!
Bruce, get off of him!
- Stopl
- Bruce, get off him!
- Let go!
So, does he butle with you?
Brant, didn't you say
you had a hookup at that club?
Yeah. Yeah. this is lame. Let's go.
Branfs a tool, but this'II be fun.
Hello, there, partner.
- You followed me?
- Didn't have to.
Your Captain told me
where you were headed.
(SIRENS WAILING)
I guess he thought
maybe you needed some help.
Hi, Jim. Thanks for leading the way.
We'II take it from here.
Keep watching me like that
and I'II think you don't trust me.
Just give me my money,
so I can get out of here.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Where are you?
- SELINA: Okay, [don't wanna hear
how I'm an idiot.
I'm at the Demonz' place. It's...
- It's bad.
- What?
I'm hiding, but there are three of 'em.
Strapped. And they just called backup.
You idiot.
How about you yell at me
after you come get me?
TABITHA: Just wait right there.
Kinda have to.
Selena's at the Demonz'.
We gotta get her.
Isn't this what they call
a teachable moment?
Let her claw her way out.
- We owe her.
- That is what her salary was for.
Like, she only went there
to prove that we can make this work,
us running heists together.
Oh. Then she mighfve considered
not getting caught.
Shejust wants a purpose.
She wants a home.
Then it sucks for her.
You know, I thought y0u'd changed.
Like, maybe you could
think about somebody
- other than yourself for once.
- Then it sucks for you.
(CAMERAS CLICKING)
It was my idea
to offer my consulting services,
and I dare say
it has been a smashing success.
The Pax Penguina
taken to the tactical level.
And now we have reason to believe
that the notorious Pyg is trapped
in the courthouse behind us.
Look, I know it's a bit of a circus.
But there was no way in hell
I was gonna let you
go in there alone, all right?
The Pyg ain't gonna go down easy.
So I say we let
Penguin's thugs go in first,
let them be the cannon fodder
instead of our guys.
It's win-win. End of conversation.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Yeah.
- THE PYG: Did you know
Ispell my name with a "Y"?
I didn't. You want to meet me somewhere?
We can talk about it.
Please, Jim, I'm not that dumb.
Anyway, P-Y-G.
The "Y" is because
itk short for Pygmalion.
Like, I'm creating a new, better Gotham.
And I'm creating a new you, Jim.
- Really?
- Yes.
Except, there's a slight hirch.
I can't recreate you
if you are, you know,
dead.
Which you will be if you go in there.
- In where?
- Oh! Don't act dumb.
Only I get to do that.
Let them play cops and robbers,
it'II be fun.
But not you.
And why should I believe
anything you have to say?
Because you are
one of the good ones, Jim.
Harper! Call Gotham General.
Find out what the hell
happened to Fazoli.
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
Check again. Jones. Brant Jones.
I heard you the first time.
He said we could get in.
Nope.
Stupid bouncer's acting like
he doesn't know who I am.
He knows who you are.
He just doesn't care.
I don't care how much money you have.
You are a dark and a freak, Wayne.
- You always were.
- Brant, chill.
Gimme a second, guys.
(INAUDIBLE)
- It's your fault for inviting him.
- Shut up, Brant.
Wait, who is Bruce talking to?
(INAUDIBLE)
Let's go, QUYS-
Not him.
Lemme talk to the owner.
You're standing next to him.
I bought the place.
- You guys in or out?
- In.
Can't find either of them?
No, they're not.
They've no record of Fazoli.
They can't find the ambulance...
GORDON: Call it off!
Call off the raid.
Fazoli's dead.
The guy in the ambulance was The Pyg
in disguise.
- What the hell are you talking about?
- Pyg called me.
He warned me off.
He used the same phrase he used
in the ambulance.
He fed us the clue to get us here.
It has to be a trap.
So, the insane serial killer
who hates cops
warned you to save your life,
because why now?
Because I'm against dirty cops.
Except, all of the times you are one.
I'm telling you, Harvey, call it off.
Call it off.
I have another interpretation, Jim.
The Pyg is not trying to save you,
he's trying to save himself
by stopping the raid.
You are being played, and not
for the first time I might add.
We called Gotham General.
They can't locate Fazoli
or the ambulance.
Jim, it's Gotham General.
It's a madhouse down there.
If I'm correct, The Pyg
isn't even in the courthouse.
I came directly from the ambulance.
There is no way he beat me here.
You're wrong. Pyg is in there, Jim.
He's right.
We got a spotter across the street
that got a visual
on Pyg, in there,
standing next to Patel,
tied to a chair. I swear.
Look, I can't explain it.
AII I know is this is a trap.
Now you asked me to trust you,
I am asking you to trust me.
God, so tiresome. Start the operation.
Jim, I'm sorry.
I'm with Penguin on this one.
We gotta think about Patel.
Let's move out, people.
You better pray
I can clean up your mess
on this one, Harvey.
You are out of line, pal!
And you are gonna
get our guys slaughtered!
Jim Gordon!
I am ordering you to stand down!
Finally, a good idea, Harvey. Boys...
We've gone over the game plan, people.
You know what to do, let's go.
When's our guys coming?
How should I know? You called them.
(CRASHING)
(WHISTLES)
MAN: It's about time. Come on, this way.
I'II draw their fire.
If you see an opening, run.
Screw that.
Whatever we're doing,
we're doing together.
Well, I guess now we'II see
if I taught you how to use that whip.
WOMAN: Hello, excuse me?
- You guys order Thai?
- No.
Good, 'cause I don't have any.
(MAN GROANING)
- Nice shooting.
- Obviously.
Gimme my cut.
- Barbara...
- I'm sorry.
Did you want a hug?
Ijust killed five guys for you.
Actually, we did it together.
So that's it?
We're just over?
Over?
You think I came down here for kicks?
You're coming back to the nest.
We got a shipment coming in,
and a business to run.
Well, come on.
- (MUFFLED SCREAMING)
- Hey!
Got him! Come on.
Harvey.
Damn it!
Oh, no.
Patel.
Oh!
Oh, no.
- It's a setup!
- (MACHINE POWERING UP)
HARVEY: The exits are blocked.
That's not our guns.
They're pinned down.
- Get in there.
- Mmm-mmm.
Get in there!
(GROANING)
OFFICER: Headhuntefs hit!
Ruseckas!
Harper! Get Patel. Now!
Shoot the chain!
HARVEY: Look out!
Come on.
(GROANING)
I did not order the cops in there.
Ido not have that authority.
I made a suggestion,
it was Captain Bullock...
- FEMALE REPORTER: Gordon! Gordon!
- (REPORTERS CLAMORING)
How did you find the courage to
run in and save all of those people?
If The Pyg is watching,
the GCPD is gonna take you down.
And that was Detective James Gordon
with a very modest...
Nice one, Gordon.
Very good, James.
They think Patel's gonna make it.
Congratulations, Jim.
You're a hero.
And I'm just the cop who shot a cop.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
This is Gordon.
THE PYG: Wow. You were amazing.
Oh, I was right about you.
You are a get-things-done type,
Jim Gordon.
Ah, and those things
that you want to get done, well,
they're the same things I want.
Only if you want to go to prison
for the rest of your life.
Now that's just mean.
I'm gonna find you.
Oh...
I hope you do.
Because I want to thank you,
in the flesh, flesh,
flesh. (SNORTS)
Because what you said
about the rot in Gotham...
"High to low," so concisely phrased.
Well, it gave me an idea.
The next step in my plot, it's a saga.
It's an epic.
It's a Spectacle.
And you're my muse, Jimmy Gordon.
I'II see you soon.
(HEADHUNTER GROANING)
Man.
(SIGHS)
Well, I guess Gordon was right.
You know, we should've...
(GROANING)
Second 0ne's my Signature.
(conrmues GROANING)
(DANCE MUSIC PLAYING)
Dude, this is awesome.
I always knew there was
another side to you, Bruce Wayne.
I think I'm gonna try it out
for a while.
(LAUGHS)
(DANCE MUSIC CONTINUES PLAYING)
(DANCE MUSIC TURNS MELANCHOLY)
Thanks. That's from all of us.
Even if they're not saying it.
Thank you, Detective.
You'd have done the same.
Yeah, but not as well.
We got an unlicensed robbery.
I've got a license. But like I told you,
Ijust don't know where I put it.
Oh, wait. It's in my boot.
We ain't accepting these no more.
English-US-SDH