Previously onGotham...
How I ever let him lay a hand on me?
I'm glad he's out of your life.
Guard up, jab, jab.
Lead, jab, jab, right.
- What you doing?
- Alfred's teaching me to fight.
I need you to take me
to the Pike brothers.
The firebugs from the Narrows?
I just hang
with their sister, Bridget.
Hey, boys. We need the best,
and you guys are the best.
Bridget, you just got a promotion.
- G.C.P.D.
- Run.
- I got her. Drop it! Drop it!
- No.
One moment, Mr. Penguin.
Mother.
I don't know nothing.
You are going to go to Galavan.
Once you're inside his organization,
you will find my mother
and rescue her.
He'll buy it, if we sell it right.
That penguin just went crazy.
I mean, like, crazier
than I've ever seen him.
And you said it was me
who set up the count house raid.
Said I was traitor and a rat.
And he...
He came at me with a cleaver.
I tried to protect myself
and he did this.
Sick bastard.
How did you get away?
There's a lot of blood. A lot.
He tried to take another swing
he slipped and fell
and so I just run.
I run, and I run
and then next thing
I knew I woke up in the hospital.
Give me a shot, Mr. Galavan.
Let me show you what I can do.
Well, I'd like to help you out,
Butch.
But I already had several capable
two-handed thugs in my employ.
They don't know Gotham like I do.
I got brains. You ask anyone.
What do you think, ladies?
I think he's cute
like a sad bear.
I supposed he's telling the truth.
The little man was cracking up
the last time I saw him.
He was very mean to me once.
Held me hostage in my own apartment.
Said some nasty things.
- Isn't that right, stumpy?
- That's right, ma'am.
And I'm sorry for it.
Business is business, you know.
Please, let me work for you,
Mr. Galavan.
I got nobody else to turn to.
Oh, yes.
We can put cool things
on a stump
like knives and mallets and stuff.
How about a little, tiny chainsaw?
Yes.
Well, that settles it.
Welcome aboard, Butch.
Thank you, sir.
Bravo, congressman.
Well-saved.
You really are quite spry
for a big man.
Have you reconsidered your position?
Can I count on your support
this election?
Yes, yes, you have my full support.
Thank you so much.
Freeze.
Man, I do nothing.
Why are you chasing me?
Police officer died last night.
Killed by a firebug crew on a spree.
- You're a firebug, aren't you?
- No, man.
I've been out of the game
a long time.
- Don't lie to me, Nino.
- I swear.
Sir, that's a violation
of officer conduct regs.
Luke Garrett burned to death
in front of me 12 hours ago.
I'll conduct myself as I see fit.
These crews were working
with the kid, a girl,
wears a homemade fire suit.
If for real, never heard
of a female firebug before.
It's mad real like a unicorn
or something.
Sir.
Captain Barnes said
we must report any infractions.
- Even by superior officers.
- You do that.
What are you doing?
I can't sleep.
I don't know what to do with myself.
That's the point of being free.
You get to do
whatever the hell you want.
What am I gonna do?
I killed someone last night.
I can't go home.
- I can't go to the police.
- You gotta get out of town.
How? I've got no money.
No problem.
We'll get you some.
You mean like crime.
Man, you are square.
I guess I got no choice.
Why are you helping me?
Maybe you remind me of me.
If I was a doufus.
This crime,
what exactly you got in mind?
Ladies and gentlemen, or should
I say pimps, hoss, and thieves.
Do I have some product for you today?
Do you like what you see?
Come on, let me hear you.
All right.
Oh, check it out. Check it out.
Yes, nice and sturdy.
- I want her!
- Bidding will start at 800, a piece.
Oh, we got 800.
Can I get 850? Got 850.
Can I get 900? I got 900.
Can I get 950? 950? I got 950.
Those girls are for sale?
Told you this place was freaky.
We need to help them.
We're here to help you.
Because you killed a cop remember?
We get the money, we go.
- But...
- Listen.
Listen.
We go down the stairs.
A lock on the backdoor is busted.
I know, because I busted it.
Go in, wait for me to make my move.
How will I know when?
Pay attention.
Sold for 2500 to the gentlemen
with a burgundy hat.
Yes, indeed, come on ladies.
Found you a nice new home!
Oh, you'll be very satisfied.
Very, very satisfied.
Next up!
Check her out as she walks
down the place.
See how graceful she is.
Look at this one!
I'm going to start the bidding
here at 900!
Can I get 900?
Hey, pervs, this is a robbery.
Milo, kill that punk.
She's with me.
Now, each of you,
put all your cash in the bag.
Or what?
I ain't scared of you two.
Yeah, all right.
- Anybody else got a problem?
- No, no.
Yeah, I don't think so.
- Will you help me?
- Let me out.
And for the record, oh, y'all suck.
Come on, come on! Get me out of here!
Hey, stop!
- Oh, my God.
- I know, right?
Let's go.
Note in my file, are you serious?
Do I look like I'm joking?
We do not beat suspects.
Ever!
I get it.
- Luke was a good kid.
- We took him out of the academy.
You told him he was ready.
Now, he is dead.
You lose people in the war.
You know that.
Make no mistake. This is war.
But that doesn't give you or me
the license to break the law.
There's a line.
I learned that the hard way.
Respectfully, sir, this is Gotham.
There are gray areas.
I've learned that the hard way too.
And did you even get a lead
while you were out avenging Luke?
- No, sir.
Now, you got one now.
The day the owner called this in
a security camera caught it.
She's our firefly.
I don't know who the other one is.
I do.
Damn it.
Focus. Focus.
Head down. Head down.
Distractions will be
the death of you, Master Bruce.
Now, get in your toes.
In your toes, move.
Oh, don't dance around
like a bloody show girl.
Come on. That's better. Better.
Now, big left, big left.
Go on.
Now, your enemies
are gonna fight a lot dirtier
than that.
Bloody hell.
Very good, Master Bruce.
Have you spoken to Mr. Fox
- about the computer?
- Yes, I have, yeah.
How much longer till it's fixed?
I'll tell you when it's done,
won't I?
- Patience.
- I'm out of patience, Alfred.
I'm ready to begin.
I'll tell you when you're ready,
Master Bruce.
I'm ready now. I know I am.
Oh, by the way, by the way,
Ms. Silver called.
She wants you to go
have dinner this evening.
- Silver called?
- Yeah.
Told you. You're not ready.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
Well, he's just up
and moved out of town.
He was rude and inconsiderate
and perfectly in character
for Tom Dougherty.
Do you ever wonder where he went?
He could be dead in a ditch
for all I care.
- Kristen.
- And I mean it too.
He... he wasn't very nice to me.
- That's awful. I'm so sorry.
- Thank you.
But it all worked up for the best.
I know.
You and Ed seem to be getting along.
He is so gentle and kind.
Almost too gentle.
Look, I think a man
needs to have a little...
a little fire, a little danger
in him, don't you think?
Oh, I don't know about that.
And sometimes I feel like
he's holding something back
from me.
Like a secret?
I don't know.
I just, I guess I just wish
he would open up a little more.
Good morning.
Ms. Kringle. Ms. Thompkins.
Hi.
What do you call a three-legged cow?
- I am terrible with...
- Lean beef.
Or supper at my place?
Oh, Ed.
Ginger to ginger, we both know,
you know where Selina Kyle's at.
So why don't you tell me now
and save us the hassle.
Who's Selina Kyle?
- Cat.
- Cat?
Look, Ivy, you want me
to call the children's home
and have them come and get you now?
Or should I get a candy bar
and forget to have someone watch you.
Candy bar.
I struck out.
None of those three kids
I talked to have seen Selina.
Relax, your Uncle Harvey
has you covered.
She's in a squat off Jenkins,
condemned SRO.
I know it.
Hey, last time we saw this chick,
she had a shotgun pointed at us.
Maybe you should take
the fascist youth, huh?
No.
With Selina it's best to go quietly.
When you get to the bus station,
take the first bus south.
Stay on till the end of the line.
Well, what do I do then?
You got plenty of money,
you can do what you like.
Thank you for everything.
You've been a really good friend.
I got my cut.
No biggie.
Bridget, you need to run.
- Bridget, run. Run, run, run.
- No.
- Selina! Selina!
- Let her go.
No.
Selina!
Help me!
Hey!
Hands in the air.
- Drop the gun.
- Like hell I will.
- Where's your girlfriend?
- Who?
We've got both of you on tape.
Don't know what you're
talking about, Gordon.
She's burned down
half a dozen buildings,
killed a cop.
You're running
with a bad partner, kid.
You don't understand.
She was forced to do all of that.
Okay.
Let me help her.
Who is she?
Who's forcing her to do this?
Look, there's a lot of angry cops
out there.
She's gonna get shot on sight
unless I get to her first.
Her name is Bridget Pike.
Her brothers took her back.
Joe and Cale Pike.
They like kidnapped her.
They're the ones who made
her start burning stuff
in the first place.
It's their fault the cop died.
Pike brothers.
Why they burned down
Wayne Enterprises buildings?
- Who paid them?
- Why the hell should I know
why the Pikes do anything?
They're freaking nuts.
They treated Bridget like a slave,
chained her to the wall.
And you're angry about it.
Is that why you're armed?
You're gonna go after the Pikes?
- Rescue you friend?
- No.
That's a yes.
Look, you're gonna get
your friend and yourself killed.
Let me handle the Pikes.
No offense, Jim
but I like my chances
better than yours.
Why get involved?
Why risk you neck?
- Who is this girl to you?
- No one.
Just a girl in the neighborhood.
I give you my word,
I will do everything I can
to keep her safe.
But you have to stay out of it.
Tell me where she is.
Damn.
She's got six grand here.
Little Bridget put on
a big girl pants.
You can take all of it. I don't care.
Oh, I'm taking it.
That's not the issue.
The issue is you thinking
that it's cool
to just ditch your brothers.
Oh, snap.
Bridget's gonna get it.
Joe, please.
Did you even think about us, huh?
Did you even think how we would feel?
No, no!
Joe, I didn't mean anything by it.
I'm a sensitive guy
and you hurt my feelings.
You know, without family
what do you got?
You got nothing, right?
You wanna be part
of the family again?
I said...
do you feel like being part
of this family again?
Yes.
Damn.
Damn, that hurt.
Bridget's back.
If you try anything
like that again, I'll kill you.
And I'll skin that little cat
bitch too, you hear me?
You're never leaving.
- Yes.
- Good.
Go make our supper.
All right, let's pack it up.
Dear me.
A mallet.
That's useful?
Don't even start.
Tell me you bring good news.
I'm in. I'm in good.
And? And?
I'm asking questions.
But it's dangerous.
If I push too hard,
Galavan will be on to me.
I told you, he's a smart guy.
Look at me, Butch.
Are you my servant?
Yes.
Do you obey me in all things?
Then why do you bring me excuses?
Go find my mother
before I chop off the other hand.
Yes, boss.
Come on, harder.
Come on, Joe.
What are you gonna do?
- Kill us?
- Yup.
I'll check the other room.
Clear!
- She's not here.
- Damn.
I hate how it smells like good
barbeque.
Bitch!
Bullock, hey!
What? He scared the hell out of me!
And now he's dead.
Nice work, Bullock.
Well, yeah, my kicks did it.
Maybe it's because
he's fired like a taquito.
It's not on me.
Looks like Selina
was telling the truth.
Look, no one speak ill
of the dead
but these asshats had it coming.
These asshats
were professional arsonist.
Somebody hired them.
But why Wayne Enterprises?
Who cares?
Right, there's a freaky
firefly chick on the loose
with a flame thrower.
Let's start there.
Hallelujah.
Hello, Butch.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I just wanted to check in,
see how things were going.
Any complaints?
No, sir, I'm fine
like a bottle of wine.
Good.
You have a real future here.
You are a hard worker.
You're loyal to a fault.
Thank you, boss.
If only you were loyal to me.
I... I don't know
what you're talking about.
Come on, Butch, have some dignity.
I know what you're doing.
You're looking for Penguin's
mother, weren't you?
The hand was a nice touch.
Almost fooled me.
How on earth did penguin
gets you to do that?
I'm his servant.
I have to obey him in all things.
Penguin's done a number on you,
huh?
Tinkered with your wiring.
Perhaps we can help.
Tabi!
Tabi, could you come here please?
Penguin has brainwashed
this poor soul.
- Can we help?
- Be my pleasure.
All right, let's talk about this.
Can we talk about this?
Take it easy. What are you doing?
Relax. I just wanna help.
I'll leave you two to it.
Remember, dinner's in an hour.
We've set up a perimeter.
She can't have gotten far,
and we're sitting
on Selina Kyle's place.
Keep me posted.
Bridget Pike was abused
her whole life.
Forced to set those fires.
I promised my informant
I would keep her safe.
Weren't you the one saying
that Luke Garrett was just a kid?
That we owe him justice?
- I know, that's what I said.
- And you were right
and now she killed him.
Now she has two more dead bodies
on her.
So, I don't care about the hows
and the whys and the boohoos.
You don't make promises
you can't keep.
You find her, and you take her down.
- Clear?
- Yes, sir.
You must have spent years up here
watching these birds.
Remember when Mickey Slattery
called us orphaned bastards
and we try to throw him off the roof.
The cops are outside my place.
- You need to get out of town.
- I'm not scared of them.
Bridget, I know what you did
to your brothers.
Not that they didn't deserved it
but...
I was surprised.
Kyle flamed up good,
but it was Joe
who burned the brightest.
You don't sound like yourself.
I'm not myself anymore. I'm free!
Just like you told me I was.
So, what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna go after the rest of them.
- The rest of who?
- The pervs and the bullies!
The ones who hurt people like us.
No one's ever gone after me
or hurt me.
Yeah. Right.
Rule number one,
look after number one.
That's you!
Don't be crazy
or you'll get yourself killed.
Don't worry about me, Selina.
- This is what I was meant to do.
- Bridgit, please, don't do this.
It's nice to have someone
who cares about me.
Thank you.
I don't care.
I just think you're being dumb.
But, hey...
good luck.
I'll see you around.
A toast.
I'm so sorry.
Something came up last minute.
As I was saying...
To family.
In the end, that's all that matters.
Family.
I hope, in time, you'll come
to think of us as family, Bruce.
Thank you.
It's... it's been some time
since I had a meal like this.
You mean with girls?
You should come over more often.
We can, like, hang out or whatever.
I'd like to.
Look how cute they are.
Don't you just wanna eat them?
Tabitha,
leave the young people alone.
Well, they are cute and they know it.
These were the best mashed
potatoes I have ever had.
I swear, I'm gonna get plump.
I like that you have an appetite.
- Stop it, your spoiling me.
- I won't stop it.
I want nothing more
than to spoil you.
Ed, so forceful.
There's something else
I wanna tell you.
I just... I won't scare you away.
Please, tell me anything.
Do not hold back.
Kristen...
I like you very much.
I... I feel the same way about you.
And...
And?
Mr. Nygma...
is that your bedroom over there?
You like to see it?
Gordon, phone call for you.
- This is Gordon.
- Do you remember your promise?
Yes.
I think I know where she's going.
Go, go, go!
Go, go!
Come on. Go! Go!
All right...
All right. No one gets hurt tonight.
We follow protocols and stay safe.
Yes, sir.
Freeze!
- Hands in the air.
- Hold your fire.
Bridget Pike.
Stay away.
My name is Jim Gordon.
I know what your brothers did to you.
I know you didn't mean
for any of this to happen.
You don't know anything.
You put your weapon down
and come with me.
I can help you.
There are places you can go.
I'm not going to jail.
You're a juvenile.
We can work something out.
- Wait, wait!
- I said hold your fire.
Bridget!
Stop!
Take cover.
Bridget, wait!
I'm glad we have a moment alone.
There's something I need to discuss.
An executive at Wayne Enterprises
is been reported missing.
Sid Bunderslaw.
Do you know him?
Yes.
We've met several times.
- What happened?
- No one knows.
But it doesn't look good.
How did you hear?
Let's just say I have friends
in high places
and I've been following the goings-on
at Wayne Enterprises very closely.
What have you learned?
That your father was a good man.
A great man, even.
But in spite of that,
bad things happen at this company.
Unfortunately, I think you're right.
I can tell you're very mature
of your age.
Ready to tackle the problems
of your company head on.
But you'll need help.
Once I'm mayor, I would very much
like to be that person.
Thank you.
Mr. Galavan, I appreciate it.
Butch, what has happened?
I found your mother.
Where?
In a warehouse down by the port.
But they got me looking.
You halfwit!
If they kill my mother...
They don't know I'm here.
And the tiger lady,
she wanted to take her time with me
so she chained me up and I got out.
We gotta go now.
Yes. Yes, yes.
Good, Butch, you've done well.
Your loyalty will be rewarded
handsomely.
I swear it.
- Yes, boss.
- Rest here for a minute
and I'll go gather the troops.
How old are you?
Old enough to shoot you,
if that's what you are thinking.
No, that's not what I was thinking.
You don't have to point a gun
at me, I'm not gonna hurt you.
Damn right, you're not.
- My name is Lee.
- I know what your name is.
What's your name?
You're cute, for a doctor.
Thanks, you're cute, for a gangster.
Hi, Selina.
- Sorry about this, Lee.
- Oh, hey, no problem.
So is Bridget okay?
I'm sorry.
She's not gonna make it.
- You said that you'll help her.
- I tried, Selina. I tried.
But she didn't wanna go quietly.
I think she wanted it
to end this way.
Look, Selina...
Don't touch me. Don't touch me.
I know you were telling the truth
about Bridget.
And her brothers put her up to this.
I need to know who hired them.
I already told you I don't know.
And I still don't believe you.
What do you care?
You don't care about people like us.
It's not like you're really gonna
go after your little friend.
My friend?
Do you mean Penguin?
Why would he set those fires?
- That doesn't make any sense.
- Ask him yourself.
I'm done talking to you.
I should've never trusted a cop.
I tried to help her,
it just went a different way.
Is that what you call it
when someone dies?
Is that what you tell yourself?
I'm sorry.
Whatever.
You're so sweet.
Kristen, what's the matter?
I'm scared.
Of what?
Of Tom Dougherty.
He used to tell me...
if he ever saw me
with another man he would kill me.
I'm terrified of what will happen
when he comes back.
You don't need to worry about that.
You don't know him. He is a monster.
Listen to me.
You do not need to worry
about Tom Dougherty.
You are sweet, but...
you're not a fighter,
you couldn't possibly take him on.
Trust me, it's being taken care of.
What does that mean?
Some time ago,
he and I had an altercation.
I asked him to treat you
with more respect.
- Oh, my God.
- And he said he would treat you
anyway he liked and he assaulted me.
- Oh, my God.
- So anyhow, long story short.
I killed him.
Oh, man. That's...
You had me going for a minute there.
He was outside of your apartment
under the elevated train.
I stabbed him and he died.
- Ed, that's not funny.
- I'm not being funny.
T. Dougherty.
Do you believe me now?
Oh, my God.
What's wrong?
- Where are you going?
- How could you?
- No. Please, sit down.
- Don't touch me!
Would you please let me explain.
There's nothing to explain.
I don't even know who you are.
No, that's wrong. You are a murderer.
He was a monster, you said so.
He was abusing you.
I can't believe I even fell for you.
- You sicko!
- I'm not sick.
I love you. I did it for you.
Everything I ever thought
about you, I was right.
- I should have my head examined.
- Don't say that.
Wait, what were you doing
outside my house?
- I was worried for you.
- You were stalking me.
You are a psychopath!
That is not true.
That's not who I am.
Don't say that about me.
You are going to prison
where they will do horrible
things to you.
- Things that you deserve.
- Don't say that to me.
No. Don't touch me.
- Let go of me, freak!
- Please don't call me that.
Help!
Listen to me.
I am not the man you think I am.
I would never do anything
to hurt you.
I had to kill him because he hit you.
Do you understand that?
I did it for you.
I promise I would never do
anything to hurt you ever again.
I love you.
I've loved you since
the first moment that I saw you.
Kristen?
No, no, no.
Oh, don't.
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
Please.
Please, no.
No.
No!
Damn, this girl looks rough.
You tell people she's dead.
Well, that's a lie.
I heard the suit
she was wearing melted to her.
Say she's fireproof.
- Come on.
- Yeah man, fireproof.
That's why they send her down here
with the rest of the monsters.
For testing.