Previously, onGotham...
My name is Nathaniel Barnes.
I'm your new boss.
Sid Bunderslaw.
I'm the Director
of Physical Operations.
I've been expecting you.
Garrett, Pinkney, Josie, Martinez.
Congratulations.
You are now Unit Alpha
of the G.C.P.D Strike Force.
Time to take down the Penguin.
Mother.
You'll pay for this.
They die, your mother lives.
And I'm gonna need you
to take a crack on me also,
and miss, of course.
Get down!
If the bad guys
want to stop me running,
well then, I guess, I got no choice.
I will run for mayor.
Thank you for the trunk, old friend.
I'll call you when I need you.
I'm glad you call me a friend.
Figure of speech.
But do go on.
I can't help feeling...
when I'd be so much more
useful to you as a friend,
best of colleague and ally?
As opposed to the tool
you are at present?
Good question.
No.
I would be a much more
effective tool for you,
if I wasn't so worried
about my mother.
If you let her come home
I would still do your bidding.
Trust me.
I know who's boss now.
Lord have mercy.
No need to rub it in.
Yes, sir.
We all know who's boss.
What do you think, Tabitha?
I wasn't listening.
You know how I love
the big macho type.
- Leave him alone.
- Yeah, leave me alone.
The answer is no, old friend.
Off you go.
Stay by the phone.
I wish you wouldn't freak out
the help.
Got a mayoral campaign to run.
I need to know you're gonna
handle this part of the business.
- I get bored.
- I hate it when you say that,
you have plenty to do.
You have Mayor James
to play with it.
He's been here nearly a month,
he's getting old fast.
You have Barbara to hang out with.
Yeah, she's cool,
but she sleeps a lot.
- She's gone crazy.
- That's the best part about her.
Galavan, what the hell is going on?
Mr. Bunderslaw, welcome.
Well, what do you want with me?
You are the garbage man
for Wayne Enterprises, correct?
Every nasty little thing
the company has done,
you know all about it.
- No.
- Yes.
And you're gonna tell us
everything that you know.
And if I refuse?
Torture.
But that's for later.
Right now, there is something
of yours we need to borrow.
Sister, if you don't mind.
- Left or right?
- Either one.
Everybody who doesn't want to
get shot raise your hand.
Get down!
A damn rocket launcher?
Welcome to Gotham, Cap.
I can fit my yearly salary
in my hands.
Don't get any ideas
about that cash, son.
Just bag it up.
Don't worry, sir,
ideas aren't his strong suit.
Did some rough calculations, sir.
It's somewhere around
two million dollars here.
That's a strong body blow
to Penguin.
- He'll feel it.
- Sir.
They're asking for their pants.
Read them their rights.
Doesn't say squat about pants.
Wait.
Tell them whoever gives up where
they got the damn rocket launcher
gets to wear pants.
The rest can go naked for all I care.
Captain, a word.
There's a place called the Merc.
It sells most of the heavy
weapons in town.
They haven't been hit because
they pay off half the city council.
Merc, huh?
City council can suck my tailpipe.
We're gonna hit this Merc tomorrow.
Pinkney.
Belay that order.
No one gets pants.
We grab him up!
We grab him and we hurt him
till he tells us where she is
and then we hurt him more!
- Okay, is that a good idea?
- Do you have a better one?
- We can get the sister.
- And then what?
He's still out there!
And does he love his sister
as much as I love my mother?
I don't think so!
There's a pickle.
Mr. Penguin, sir.
The cops just hit the count house.
They took everything, every dollar.
Did you enjoy giving me that news?
Butch, I have an idea.
- Hey, you.
- Good morning.
How's your day look?
Strike Force is going out
on another raid.
Strike Force. I hate that name.
Yeah, I'm not wild about it myself,
but Barnes gets things done,
he can call us what he likes.
All right, so you go strike
with your force,
- and what are we doing tonight?
- Sleep.
- It's date night, mister.
- With who?
- Morning, Ed.
- Detective, Ms. Thompkins.
As you may have heard, I've recently
been seeing Ms. Kringle.
Kristen.
And she mentioned
that it might be nice
to go out with other people along.
So I thought perhaps
the two of you would enjoy
joining us for dinner tonight.
- We can't.
- We'd love to.
Sure.
Yeah. Yeah, I know. Great.
As a matter of fact, I just
bought some new fondue pots.
Why don't we do it at my house?
Excellent.
Excellent. I'll go tell Kristen.
I know. I know.
But it was the decent thing to do.
Fondue?
Have you ever tried it?
It's delicious.
It's at your place.
We can't leave, we're already home.
- Trapped.
- Don't be mean.
I'll make it fun.
Yes, ma'am.
Detective Gordon. Good morning.
I wonder if we could talk alone.
Of course.
Thank you for giving me
some of your valuable time.
Not a problem.
That night at the gala, I...
I just keep going through it.
Me too.
I never killed a man before.
Fear, blood...
I relive that moment over and over.
Do those thoughts ever go away?
No.
But over time they lose their power.
You did the right thing.
I guess I did.
I'm kind of amazed at myself.
But you doing the right thing
is what you do everyday.
It's why people speak
so highly of you.
You're a symbol
to the people of this city,
of hope, of honor.
That's why I'm here.
I would be honored
if you would consider
endorsing me for mayor.
Endorsement.
I'm flattered but I'm afraid
policeman and politics don't mix.
Maybe not for a cop on the street
but your president
of the policemen's union.
Where you lead, officers will follow.
That's more power than the kind
that comes out of a gun.
You seem like a good man.
But, I'm afraid
my answer has to be no.
I don't do endorsements.
I know better than to push.
But think about it.
We could really help each other.
Hi, Penguin.
- What do you want?
- Why so glum?
I just lost all my money.
Poor sad little brat head.
The money is immaterial.
Someone must have betrayed me.
Someone close.
You don't know that, boss.
Oh, don't I?
- Don't I?
- Whoa, chill, birdman.
- I got a job for you.
- What's that?
Addresses of places
you're gonna burn to the ground.
Starting tonight.
Arson now.
Sure. Fine. Whatever.
If I can find a trustworthy arsonist.
Paranoid, huh?
Get your head together,
little man, and get it done.
Oh, and whoever starts a fire
is gonna need this.
Nice place.
What's up?
I need you to take me
to the Pike brothers.
The firebugs from the Narrows?
I used to hang with their sister
Bridgit when I was a kid.
- Why do you need me to take you?
- To vouch for me.
The Pikes are the best arsonist
in town...
but they're also a Fish loyalists.
The idiots think
she's coming back someday.
She might come back.
- I was there, darling.
- She might.
Whatever.
The Pikes hate me and Penguin
for obvious reasons.
But everyone knows Fish loved you.
They do?
Your face will open doors, babe.
- Six hundred.
- Three-fifty.
Fine.
Just let me do the talking.
You just smile and make
it look like we're friends.
Friends?
That's a hundred extra.
Chisler.
So everybody knows she loved me?
That's what they say.
She loved me too once.
- I loved her.
- Then you shot her.
Well...
it was complicated.
Got that right.
Hi, Bridgit.
Hey, Selina.
It's been a while.
Me and my pet gorilla
are here on business.
Your brother's home?
Yeah.
Hey, boys.
What are you doing
with this rat, Selina?
He's okay. I vouch for him.
What do you mean "okay"?
The bastard shot Fish Mooney.
It was complicated.
He loves her just like you do.
- And if she ever comes back...
- When she comes back.
When she does
he will be right by her side.
If she comes back. Sure. But she...
But right now,
he got a nice job for you guys.
Business is business, right?
Hey, bygones, huh?
We need the best
and you guys are the best.
Easy.
- It's a lot of work.
- A lot of pay.
You up for it?
For sure.
We'll need more gear.
I'll hit the Merc and stock up.
Got enough gear
to burn down Gotham twice.
There's always room for more napalm.
Thanks.
Hey, sis.
What are you, a slop?
We have company.
What do we do
when we have company?
Get them a glass.
Ding, ding, ding. Go and do it.
Thank you, Bridgit.
You're gonna need this.
- Hey.
Looks like rain.
Yeah, it does.
I don't mind it.
Cleans the streets anyhow.
That's true.
Anyway.
Take care of yourself, Bridgit.
Be strong.
Yeah, can we get a price check
on brass knuckles in toxic green?
Three hundred gets it done.
And ten percent surcharge
for soiled bills.
Thank you kindly.
Try our Whiff-Away.
On sale now in Aisle Seven.
Welcome to Merc, your one-stop shop
for machetes, night-vision goggles,
and all of your personal
defense needs.
Robbery.
- G.C.P.D!
- Everybody on the ground.
This is a raid!
Spread!
I got him!
Stop! Stop right now!
What the hell are you packing?
When cheese melts
the protein matrix relaxes,
and the fats flow more like liquid.
It creates this low friction
mouthfeel
- which is why melted cheese is so...
- Ed.
Well, it's delicious.
Yes, it is.
Oh, no.
Lee, we should be eating
without Jim here.
- I'm so sorry.
- No, no, no, please.
Eat. It's fine.
- There he is.
- Hello there.
- Hey, Jim, nice to see you.
- Sorry, I'm late.
Really sorry. Long story.
I hope it hasn't been going too bad.
I know, it's the weirdest thing.
But Nygma's actually maintaining
this strange sort of cool.
- No.
- Seriously.
There's a lid for every pot.
Pardon me,
since Detective Gordon is here.
I'd like to propose a toast.
The less you have
the more they're worth.
To friends.
Hear hear.
I can't believe he's dead.
Biggest job of our lives
and this happens.
So, what do we do?
For sure we do the job.
How? We're screwed.
Who's our entry man now?
Crawling to rear vents,
climbing fire escapes.
We need a little skinny guy.
You think.
Hey, Bridgie.
You just got a promotion.
- No.
- Yes.
Please, you know I don't like fire.
You don't like fire?
Fire is our bread and butter.
It's our family business.
You don't wanna let down
your family, do you?
You're not my family.
What's that?
We're not your family?
- You got anybody else?
- My mother...
Your mother was a hoe.
And she's dead.
Who feeds you? Who puts a roof
above your head, huh?
We do. That's family.
I won't do it.
Fine, be like that.
But if you're not family,
well, that changes things
around here, though.
See, I'm a decent guy.
I would never put family
on the street.
But if you're not family...
well, why not make a buck.
Yo, that's a kick-ass idea.
So, what are you gonna do?
Do you wanna be turned out?
Or do you wanna be family?
Which?
Family.
He wanted me
to endorse him for mayor.
Wow. What did you say?
I said no.
- You don't like him?
- I do actually.
But I know better
than to let that matter.
Endorsing politicians, that's not me.
Still, he asked you,
that's very flattering.
You're a respected figure
in this town.
The way people look at you,
see you differently.
You treat it like it's a burden.
It could be a source of pride
or happiness even if you let it.
Thank you, Doctor.
Same time next week.
Don't tempt me.
I could psychoanalyse
a heck out of you.
But I'm gonna resist the urge.
Gee, thanks.
Be strong, Bridgit.
Okay.
- It's on.
- Now.
You gonna want to cut yourself
about a foot and a half of fuse.
Okay.
Push the wick
into the plastic explosive.
Okay.
Now get out the flame.
You got about a minute and a half
to get out of there
once that fuse is light.
Spark it up.
- It's lit.
- Okay, great. Look.
Sorry, there's one more thing to do.
- But it's lit.
- Well, you better hull ass.
Do you see a safe on your right?
- Yeah.
- Get to it.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Okay, now grab the box
at the bottom of the bag
and open it up.
Oh, my God.
Grody, right?
Okay, put it to the center
next to the door.
Welcome, Mr. Bunderslaw.
Okay. It's open. Now, what?
Joe?
Joe, where are you?
- Joe, what's wrong?
- I'm just messing with you.
Okay, so there should be
an old knife there. Grab it.
- Okay. Got it.
- Okay.
Now, scram.
Attagirl.
You did good, sis.
Get in the van. Chop-chop.
I burned my leg.
Well, you play with fire,
you get burn, all of that.
We got four more of this
to do tonight,
so get in the damn van.
Five locations,
all burned to the ground.
- Yeah, Garrett?
- Excuse me, sir.
Lab called in said the fires
were started with termite
and high-end accelerants.
So we're looking
for a professional arsonist.
Thanks.
And, Garrett, nice work yesterday.
Thank you, sir.
Strange.
Why would a pro do five jobs
in one night?
- What's the rush?
- And what if they're not done?
Find a pattern to these fires,
before they burn down
the whole city.
What are you doing?
Hi. Making a suit.
So I won't get burned again.
Why would you get burned again?
So they're making you
start the fires?
I guess.
Sit down.
You want a soda or something?
No. I, I can't. I'm suppose
to take that to Penguin.
Okay.
You know you're gonna get
yourself killed.
I'll be careful.
Well, careful ain't enough.
Look what happened already.
It was exciting, Selina.
I actually kind of enjoyed it.
Yup, you're gonna be bacon.
My brothers said I did a good job.
- It's the family business.
- They're not your family.
Your mom used to bang
their old man.
Is all.
You don't need them.
You don't need anybody.
Look at me. I'm free.
I remember when I was little
and you showed up at the Narrows.
You looked for your mom everyday.
Snot all down your face from crying.
So don't act like
you don't want a family.
- Don't talk about my mom.
- Who cares if you're free.
What good is freedom if you're alone?
What good is a family
if you're a slave?
Whatever.
I don't even know
why you think I care.
Doesn't make any sense.
This is the Wayne family crest.
So what?
Why does Galavan want an antique
knife that belong to the Waynes?
There's something here.
Something to understanding Galavan.
To beating him.
Well, if you wanna know
about old-time Gotham,
talk to Edwige.
Edwige?
Yeah. She runs the antique shop
in my old neighborhood.
Trust me. She knows things.
You can pick it up if you like.
That's okay.
Sorry.
I can't help you.
Edwige.
I can see that you know this knife.
You're scared of this knife.
Why?
- Why are you lying to me?
- I'm not.
Madame.
If there's one thing I know,
it's a liar.
Now, tell me about this knife.
Or I will use it.
This knife has a cursed history.
Almost 200 years ago,
it was used in a terrible crime.
Back then, five families
ruled Gotham High Society.
The Elliots, the Canes,
the Crowns, the Dumont,
and the most powerful
of them all, the Waynes.
They called Celestine Wayne,
the Crowned Jewel of Gotham.
A real beauty.
She was promised to the eldest son
of the Elliot family.
But there was another
who coveted her.
Caleb Dumont.
One night...
it was during an Easter party
at the Wayne Manor.
Celestine and Caleb went missing.
The Wayne men found them,
together, in an illicit embrace.
Caleb insisted
that they were in love and...
Celestine swore
on her mother's grave,
that Caleb had forced himself on her.
Justice, if that's what it was,
was swift.
Celestine's brother Jonathan Wayne,
delivered the punishment.
The Waynes, they were mad with rage.
They ceased the Dumont Holdings
and banished them socially.
Destroyed them.
Caleb Dumont went into exile overseas
to a penitentiary
of a religious sect,
founded by his family's patron saint.
Celestine died an old maid.
The Waynes forbade the press
from even mentioning the Dumont.
They renamed streets and buildings.
The remnants of the Dumont family
were forced to change their name.
The Waynes wiped the Dumont
out of our city's history.
Those remnants
of the Dumont family...
to what did they change their name?
Aren't you quick?
Galavan.
They changed their name to Galavan.
Just like that fellow
running for mayor.
And that's why I am scared
of this knife!
You're in deep waters, Mr. Penguin.
Thank you, Edwige.
That is where penguins thrive.
You hear anything about
any fires, you come see me,
earn yourself a "get out of jail"
free card, all right?
You got a look on your face.
It's well hidden behind
a bunch of corporate aliases.
But all the buildings
that burned down last night,
they have one landlord.
Wayne Enterprises.
The arsonist moved east to west.
They come out tonight,
and stick to pattern,
there's one obvious target.
An old building also owned
by Wayne Enterprises.
Gotham City Book Depository.
Yay! Stakeout. I'll buy the donuts.
Oh, just not chili dogs
this time, huh?
I'll let Barnes know the plan.
Sent the knife to Galavan.
Your favorite, isn't it?
Cross white 20 year.
That's the stuff, all right.
Have a taste.
No, I'm good right now. But thanks.
Have a drink, Butch.
Your conditioning
is still working nicely, hmm?
You can't refuse me.
You're the only man
I can truly trust right now.
You're starting to sound
a little paranoid, boss.
Am I?
Am I going mad?
How could I not? When that feign
has my mother in his clutches.
Have another drink, Butch.
Maybe I am going mad.
Or maybe I found Galavan's weakness.
You did?
The knife, Butch.
The knife that maimed his ancestor.
This is a blood feud for Galavan.
He wants revenge against the Waynes.
He's acting out of emotion.
And that can be manipulated.
Have another drink.
You are going to go to Galvan.
You're going to tell him I went nuts
and that I accuse you of setting
up the count shop raid.
You are in fear for your life
and you need a job. Got that?
Yes, boss.
Once you're inside his organization
you will find my mother
and rescue her.
Yes, boss.
But, Galavan's a smart guy.
Not to basic play.
No way is he gonna buy
a turned traitor.
No.
But he will buy that I think
you turned traitor.
He'll buy it if we sell it right.
Drink up.
- How do we sell it?
- I already sold him my paranoia.
But you're the closer.
How do we sell you?
How do we make him
trust and feel for you?
I wasn't sure.
But then Celestine and Caleb
told me how.
How?
It's the onions
that bring it together.
The sweetness and the acid,
am I right?
I hate stakeouts.
Half of good police work
is the ability to sit on one's ass
when it's called for.
If that were true,
you'd be commissioner.
Hardy har har.
Heads up.
All units standby.
We may have something.
Roger.
So, it's all old books in there,
so this one's easy.
Just spread the napalm around,
spark that thing up,
and go to town. Zero sweat.
This thing scares me.
Yeah, it's a flamethrower.
It's meant to be scary.
Get suited up. And get this done.
We got three more spots to hit.
All units converge
in our location now.
Moving in.
- G.C.P.D!
- Run.
Go, go, go!
Gray van leaving the alley.
Get back!
Please! Get back!
Drop it!
Put down the weapon.
Drop your weapon.
- I got her! Drop it!
- No!
No!
Drop it!
No! Let me go!
Garrett!
I got him. I got him.
I need an ambulance. Officer down!
Bridgit! Bridgit!
Come on. Hurry!
Quick! Follow me!
- Were are we going?
- Home.
Thanks.
- Any news?
- Not yet.
But he's a tough kid,
I bet you he makes it.
Your buddy's here.
Can't stop pressing the flesh.
A real publicity hound.
There's no cameras here.
Your attention, please.
Captain.
Luke Garrett passed away at 5:23.
- Damn it, man.
- It ain't right.
Burned to death in an alley
by some weirdo.
He was gonna be a great cop.
He was a great cop.
And we will mourn him.
But not now.
There's a cop killer on the loose.
I cannot abide that.
We will find the person
who killed our brother,
and we will put a stop to him.
Using any legal methods
at our disposal.
Excuse me.
Your fellow officer is dead,
I can see it in your face.
He is.
I'm sorry to hear that.
The bad guys in this town
are changing.
They're not playing by the old rules.
Or any rules.
We need every method
at our disposal.
And I'm not just talking about
more guns.
You need to go where you need to go.
Press who you need to press,
and have the city back your play.
Correct.
I don't know how bad it's gonna get.
But if you can give me your word,
then we won't have to face it alone.
You'll have my endorsement.
I promise you,
you will have whatever you need.
Father Creel.
Theo.
It's been a long time.
You look well.
As do you.
You've surrounded yourself
with luxury.
Well, I have to play the part,
Father, and...
as you'll see...
it's paying off.
Still sharp after all these years.
Do you have the Wayne boy?
Not yet.
There are some practical matters
I have to resolve first.
A few pieces to arrange
on the board before the checkmate.
But soon.
After almost 250 years
we can be patient.
The day of atonement is at hand.
Our brothers are crossing
the ocean even now.
Warriors like this city
has never known.
Gotham will be redeemed in blood.
And Bruce Wayne will die.