- Previously on Gotham...
- Hello.
- What's wrong with you?
- I let him out of his cage,
and he helped me get out of mine.
- You're him, the Riddler.
- Hi, Lee.
Butch?
You're alive.
Oh, Butch, I tried.
GILZEAN: Tabby, I'm gonna find a way
to get back to the old me. I promise.
GORDON: Tell me
about your mother, Jerome.
Did she have any enemies?
- No.
- Do you have any other family?
The circus is my family.
JEROME: Now, to free
the rest of our cronies
and blow this pop stand.
BRUCE: I could have killed
Jerome after he kidnapped me
and I didn't.
Any harm he does now,
I share a part of it.
I saw Jerome tonight.
He was looking for the name of
a school, St. Ignatius.
Stay the hell away from that madman.
I'll see you at St. Ignatius, Jim.
♪ ♪
Sir? Sir?
Can I help you?
My name is Bruce Wayne.
I'm looking for Jerome Valeska.
Has he been here?
I didn't have the pleasure
of meeting Mr. Valeska.
However, I did speak
with his friend,
the one with the top hat.
- Jervis Tetch.
- (clock ticking)
Yes, that's the fellow.
He was very polite.
What did he want?
The-the name of a, uh, student
who graduated St. Ignatius
ten years ago.
Xander Wilde.
Fine young boy, very bright.
Did Tetch tell you why Jerome
was looking for him?
No.
But he did have a message for you.
(tires screech)
Listen to me, you're being hypnotized
by Jervis Tetch. You don't want
to press that button.
But I have to.
He's depending on me.
GORDON: Bruce.
Step away from him.
BRUCE: Please.
Hand me the detonator.
I want to.
But I can't.
BRUCE: Captain Gordon, look.
He's under Jervis's spell.
(gasps)
(watch ticking)
Get down!
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com
♪ ♪
JEROME: Hear ye, hear ye.
I'd like to officially welcome you all
to our first ever
mandatory brunch meeting.
Now, I know what you're all thinking.
Why have I gathered
this legion of Horribles?
That has a nice ring to it.
- Write that down, will ya?
- Hmm.
Well, back when I was in Arkham,
I came up with a plan to turn
this city into a madhouse.
And now I am on the cusp
of making that happen.
But I need help from all of...
Put all questions on ice until the end.
Danke schoen.
Mr. Oswald.
Thank you for doing your
part in hosting us today.
Anything for an old friend.
Crane,
where are we at with the...
"you know what"?
It's coming along, dreadfully.
Oh, pun worthy.
Excellent. Freeze.
Ice Man, you're a science guy.
We're gonna need a lab, a big one.
- Easy enough.
- Hmm.
Now, all we need is Mr. Tetch to return
with some very important
information and...
Use the tongs, Carl!
You still haven't told us
how you're going to
take over the underworld.
Who says I want to do that?
I'm an artist.
I just want to paint the town crazy.
Once that happens, I could care less
how you Horribles rip the city apart.
I'm in.
- Let's do this.
- JEROME: Huh? No.
Not yet.
Nothing can happen until we have
our one last essential ingredient.
(door opens, closes)
The one thing that'll tie it
all together.
(sirens wail in distance)
Who is Xander Wilde?
I don't know.
Did Jerome say anything
at his uncle's diner?
Anything that can tell us
why he's going after him.
If I knew that, Captain,
I would tell you.
Would you?
How can I trust anything you say?
I told you not to come
here and you did anyway.
- Damn it, you could have been killed.
- ALFRED: Yeah, all right, Captain.
- I think you've made your point.
- And you?
Did you know he was going after Jerome?
Indeed, I did, yes.
GORDON: If he gets involved
in this case again,
I'll press charges. We clear?
Come on, sir.
BULLOCK: Yo.
I just talked to an administrator.
Xander Wilde was some
kind of child prodigy.
Now he's a hotshot structural
engineer at Meyer & Hayes.
What does Jerome want with an engineer?
Maybe he wants him
to build him something.
Let's go.
(Muzak playing)
(whistling)
(blowing)
- I used to be a great whistler.
- Mm-hmm.
(elevator bell dings)
Uh, yeah, hi.
I'm here to see Xander Wilde, and, no...
I don't have an appointment.
Don't bother going to security,
- they're all... headless.
- (woman screams)
Yeah.
(indistinct chatter)
HAYES: All right.
If you would all please
look at the rendering,
you'll notice that there are several
interesting engineering problems
that present themselves.
- Most...
- (people gasp)
Oh, don't get up.
I won't waste too much of your time.
I've got a business proposition.
Tell me what I want to know and
you don't get turned inside out.
Please, don't, don't hurt anyone.
Where is... (laughs)
Xander Wilde?
He's-he's not here.
Yeah. I'm not blind.
Maybe you are.
Hmm? You know?
Hmm? No one does.
- H-He's never stepped foot in this office.
- Oh, okay.
- (all gasping)
- (shouts)
(stammers): We've never met.
I-I've only ever communicated with him
through a proxy.
- A proxy.
- Yeah.
Hmm. (laughs)
That slippery little sucker
thinks he can get away from me.
- (groans)
- Where can I find this proxy, pray tell?
(whimpering, stammering)
I'll tell you. I'll tell you.
- (elevator bell dings)
- (people shouting)
- (gunshots)
- (screaming)
Jimbo! Ol' buddy, ol' pal.
It's great to see you.
Drop the gun.
- Oh, you are such a stick in the mud.
- Give it up, clown boy.
Hey.
Knock, knock.
You're supposed to say "Who's there?"
- BULLOCK: Thank you, Frances.
- GORDON: Yeah. All right.
Hey, Jim. Same story all around.
No one knows Xander;
no one even met him.
Apparently, he had a proxy
who handled his, uh,
dealings with the company.
Hayes was the only one
who knew their identity,
but, uh, obviously, he's not talking.
So we have to figure out
another way to find Xander.
I'm ahead of you. We looked into it.
No driver's license,
no known addresses... guy's a ghost.
Everything that's happened
in the last 24 hours...
the breakout, Tetch...
it's all been about
Jerome finding this guy.
I don't think it has anything to
do with him being an engineer.
- This seems personal.
- Makes sense.
I mean, Jerome went to his uncle
to look for him.
Yeah. So how are they connected?
What's up?
Is that Wayne Plaza?
GORDON: Take a look at
the initials of the engineer.
- X.W. Xander Wilde.
- Uh-huh.
Looks like we're gonna have
to go talk to the kid.
He's gonna be thrilled to see you.
(siren wailing in distance)
(indistinct chatter)
What time is it?
CROWD: Riddle time!
What time is it?!
CROWD: Riddle time! (cheering)
NYGMA: That's right!
It's riddle time at...
NYGMA/CROWD: The Riddle Factory!
(cheering)
Our first contestant is...
Lars,
(with German accent):
from the now defunct biker gang,
The Street Demonz.
It's been a rough go
of it lately, huh, Lars?
I've fallen on hard times.
But I'm damn happy to
be here with you, Riddler.
That's the Narrows spirit I love.
Now, you know the rules.
I ask a riddle.
You answer correctly, you ask me one.
You win them both,
and you're walking out of
here with cold hard cash.
(crowd cheers)
Lila.
Prepare the timer.
I am heavy forward,
but backward, I am not.
What am I?
LARS: Okay. I'm heavy forward.
Back-Backward, I'm not. Um...
- (sighs)
- MAN: You got this, Lars.
Okay, wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Wait a minute. No, no. I know this.
It's, uh...
No, no. I know this.
- WOMAN: Come on, Lars.
- Okay, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Um...
It's the hourglass.
(scattered laughter)
(buzzer sounds)
(crowd groans)
The answer is ton. T-O-N.
Backwards, I am "not."
Sorry, Lars.
Spin the wheel! Spin the wheel!
You hear 'em, Lars.
It's time to spin...
ALL: The Wheel of Misfortune.
ALL: Spin the wheel!
Spin the wheel! Spin the wheel!
- Lila, please.
- (chanting continues)
Spin the wheel! Spin the wheel!
(bell ringing)
(crowd cheering)
My personal favorite.
Rabid Sack of Rats!
(cheering)
- (laughing)
- (rats squeaking)
THOMPKINS: All right,
that's enough! Enough!
NYGMA: Doc Thompkins.
What brings Your Majesty down
to our rabble?
How you doing, Ed?
Haven't seen you
since we put Oswald on ice.
Well, I'm doing far better
than Sofia Falcone,
from what I understand.
Whatever the hell this is, it's over.
I don't think so. Ladies and gentlemen,
our queen has just informed me
she wants to shut us down.
How do you feel about that?
(crowd booing and shouting)
You hear that?
That's the sound of democracy.
The people have spoken.
And my name is the Riddler.
Okay.
You want to be entertained?
Hold this, will you?
- Then I'll beat him.
- MAN: Oh!
You can't be serious.
You realize what happens
- when you lose?
- I know.
I spin the wheel.
But if I win, you shut this place down.
(crowd shouting)
ALL (chanting):
Doc, Doc, Doc, Doc, Doc...
(man booing)
We have our next contestant!
(cheering)
JEROME: Got any ice cream in there?
I've always had a soft
spot for Chunky Monkey.
I was wondering when you would come.
Me? That's very flattering.
So tell me, Little Miss Proxy,
where is he?
I'll never tell you.
Hmm. I don't know.
See...
I can be very persuasive.
See that?
JEROME: Yeah.
I was wondering about that.
You got, like, a big dog or something?
No. That's how
I'm going to transport you.
Hmm?
(phone beeps)
I've got him.
(horn blows)
(glass clinking)
Butch?
I had heard you were different.
But I will be honest.
I like it.
What do you want?
I assume you've heard
about the Arkham breakout.
Well,
I just came from brunch
with Jerome Valeska,
and let's just say
that he has plans for Gotham.
What kind of plans?
That part wasn't entirely clear.
They seem to involve a great
deal of paint. (laughs)
No matter.
I have seen his kind come and go.
Jerome Valeska will flame out.
And in the rubble,
I will reclaim the underworld.
I could use a good man
like you by my side.
(chuckles)
You must be all out of allies
to come looking for me.
Don't be modest.
With your brute strength and my
brains, we will be unstoppable.
I did that job. I'm my own man now.
(laughs)
Really?
Because from where I am, you
look like a man who has nothing.
You'd be wise
to watch what you say to me.
- I'm not the same man you remember.
- And neither am I.
Look at the two of us.
We used to run this town together.
We were friends.
Look, you want your old
life back. So do I.
- We are the same.
- Wrong!
- (groaning)
- You can have your old life back.
I can't. Look at me.
Tabitha will never love me again.
Slaughter Swamp turned
me into a monster!
Now get out of here.
If I ever see you again,
I'll pop your head off like a flower.
(coughs)
(birds chirping)
Let me get this straight.
You tell us to stay out
of your investigation,
and now you want our help?
- Subtle.
- We have reason to believe
your father met with Xander Wilde.
Well, if he did, he certainly
would have made a note of it.
What was the name of the building again?
Wayne Plaza.
He was a meticulous notetaker, Thomas.
He organized everything by project.
Let's see. Wayne Gardens.
Wayne Hospital.
Aha. Here we go.
Wayne Plaza.
Right.
Oh, you're bang
on the money there, Captain.
Xander Wilde. Says he went to
meet him to finalize the plans.
No address, just the name of
the street... Annesley Drive.
That's out past Buxton
by the old rock quarry.
This man must have been
very important if my father
went out of his way to meet him alone.
I'm starting to think he
isn't just some recluse
hiding from the world.
He's hiding from Jerome.
(laughing)
How interesting.
(grunting)
(grunts)
Oh.
- Oh, you are incorrigible.
- (camera whirring)
And then again,
you always were.
(laughs)
Oh, wait. Or was that me?
Sometimes I get so confused,
I... I can't remember.
(laughing)
(sighs)
You didn't have
to run away like that, you see.
I would never hurt you... Xander.
I love you.
(laughing)
(cackling continues)
Can't wait to see ya!
Did you think about me?
I know that you did.
Oh, I'm gonna squeeze you until you pop!
BULLOCK: Where the hell's the house?
(buzzer sounds)
James Gordon,
here to see Xander Wilde.
(lock clicks)
So this whole joint's underground?
Mr. Wilde values his privacy.
How long has he lived here?
He finished construction six years ago.
(camera whirring)
- Ecco. 496.
- FEMALE VOICE: Welcome, Ms. Ecco.
He'll see you now.
Thank you for seeing us, Mr. Wilde.
I expected you might come, Captain.
BULLOCK: My God.
There's two of them.
May I put my hands down now, gentlemen?
Please?
Apologies, Mr. Wilde.
You took us by surprise.
That's understandable.
You can call me Jeremiah.
That's the name my mother gave me.
You solved her murder, Captain Gordon.
I owe you a debt of gratitude for that
and for putting Jerome
in Arkham, where he belongs.
He never mentioned you before.
No, I suppose he wouldn't have.
From the letters my mother sent me,
he never spoke of me after I left.
Left where?
The circus.
They hid me away to protect me from him.
See, we were always different,
Jerome and I.
From an early age,
I showed a proficiency
for maths and design,
and Jerome, mainly
the mutilation of alley cats.
On my tenth birthday, he held
a cake knife to my throat.
A few weeks later,
he lit my bed on fire.
It was like living in a nightmare.
My mother knew eventually
one day he would succeed,
so one night, my uncle came
to my room while Jerome slept,
and told me that he was taking me away.
I had no idea where,
but I kissed my mother good-bye,
told her I loved her,
and I never saw her again.
He took you to St. Ignatius.
Got a new name, a new life.
And I was finally able
to live without fear.
But in my heart,
I knew one day Jerome would come for me.
Well, that day is today, pops.
We have reason to believe
Jerome knows where you are.
We need to move you to a safe location
- until we can apprehend him.
- That won't be necessary, gentlemen.
I've spent the bulk of my life
preparing for this eventuality.
I am safest here in my home.
Not anymore.
Jerome knows the name of your proxy.
He got it from your boss
just before he executed him.
I heard about Jerome
visiting Allen Hayes.
It's tragic.
But the proxy's name
I gave to Allen was a fake.
You're lying.
I beg your pardon?
Yeah, there's something
about this guy that's fishy.
The security cameras outside.
They were turned on.
So why are the monitors in here off?
I don't see why
that's any of your concern.
Now, if you excuse me,
I'm a very busy man.
- Yeah. I'm sure that you are.
- Please don't touch that.
That's very sensitive equipment.
(Jerome grunting)
BULLOCK: Oh, yeah.
I'd say that's pretty damn sensitive.
Ladies and gentlemen,
a gauntlet has been laid
at the Riddler's feet.
Our leader, Doc Thompkins...
she thinks that she knows
what's good for you.
She thinks stapling a live barracuda
to someone's face isn't
damn good entertainment.
(crowd booing)
- Just get on with the show, Ed.
- Okay.
Enough! What time is it?
CROWD: Riddle time!
- What time is it?
- Riddle time!
- Lila.
- (crowd cheering)
Prepare the timer.
WOMAN: Let's go, Lee!
I can be broken...
without being held.
Given and then taken away.
Some people use me to deceive,
but when delivered,
I am the greatest gift of all.
What am I?
You stumped?
Of course I am.
You're the Riddler.
So you give up?
- No.
- MAN: Come on, Lee!
You're gonna give me the answer.
(laughs)
Really? How's that?
Because deep down, you want to.
Oh, so that's your plan?
To appeal to the inner Ed?
Well, you played the wrong hand, Doc.
Ed is gone,
and I will not be manipulated by you
the way that dope was.
I didn't manipulate him.
- I helped him.
- No.
No, you lied to him.
You promised to fix him,
and that pathetic dust mite
believed you,
causing me to be locked
inside of his feeble mind.
Okay, you have ten seconds left
to find your answer.
So prepare to lose.
But I know the answer now.
(chuckles)
You just gave it to me.
What are you talking about?
You're right. I told Ed
I would fix him, and I didn't.
I broke my promise.
And that, Riddler...
...is the answer.
A promise.
(crowd murmurs)
(crowd cheering)
Well played.
We're only halfway through.
And I assure you, you will not stump me.
Boo. (laughs)
You need to take us to your brother.
I can't do that.
What if he's nuttier than the other one?
I'm nothing like Jerome.
You want me to put you
in a cell next to his?
Because that is where this is heading.
And then what, Captain Gordon?
You couldn't hold him.
Arkham couldn't. I can.
And I will make sure
Jerome never escapes again.
No, no, no. Jerome comes with us.
And if you want to make
this easier on yourself,
I suggest you stay
the hell out of the way.
BULLOCK: Oh, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
The loonies are outside.
No. No.
No, no, no, no.
- How'd they find me?
- GORDON: They must have followed Jerome.
We need to move, now.
(alarm buzzing)
This is not good.
Is there another way out of here?
Yes, but I'm not leaving Ecco.
The loonies will use her against us.
She's devoted her life to me.
We get you out first,
then we can come back for her.
- Deal?
- (alarm continues buzzing)
As a child, I was
obsessed with labyrinths,
so I designed my house like one.
You mean this place is a maze?
Easy enough to get in; I'm the
only one who knows the way out.
Stay close to me.
The maze is built on a hundred acres.
There are 73 dead ends.
I once invited the top
maze designers in the country
to try to solve it... one did.
It took him three days.
GORDON: And how much further?
Not far. We just passed
the final switchback point.
If I knew this thing was 100 acres,
I would have stopped and got
a sandwich before we came.
Ecco.
Oh, thank God you're okay.
Hey, hey, hey, she's hypnotized.
(all grunting)
Ecco, it's me.
It's me. Ow!
Gordon! Help!
Gordon!
She's a pistol.
Come on.
Ecco, please. Where are you taking me?
- I'm taking you to Jerome.
- No.
He'll do horrible things to me.
Ecco...
- Stop!
- (gun cocks)
Ow.
Let him go.
(gasps)
(gun drops)
Thanks. He went that way.
All right.
GORDON: Jeremiah.
Let's try this way.
(sighs)
JEROME: Hello, brother.
(gasps)
So, how ya been?
Oh, you look great! (laughing)
To think I used to be
the handsome one, right?
How'd you find your way
through the maze?
Oh, bro,
we might not look the same anymore,
but we still think the same.
Plus, you used to draw
those stupid things
all the time as a kid.
I paid attention.
Hey, uh, hat-head. Take Crane.
Find Jimbo and his bearded sidekick.
Kill them.
(chuckling)
I've been waiting for this
moment for 15 years.
Ever since you ran away
in the middle of the night,
like a coward.
- You're insane.
- Yeah.
And I tried telling Mom,
but she didn't want to listen to me.
You blame me for everything
that's gone wrong in your life.
But the truth is, Jerome,
is you were born bad.
Born bad, huh?
So that's why you made her think
that I tried to kill you.
- Right?
- Yeah, we both...
What was it again? What was it?
I put a blade to your throat.
No, no, no, no, no. I tried to...
- light you on fire.
- We both know you wanted to!
Yeah, that was a funny story, wasn't it?
Okay.
Maybe it didn't happen
exactly like that, but...
but I didn't have a choice,
and I was right.
Hmm?
You killed our mother.
She did deserve it though.
(chuckles)
After that whore hid you away,
she gave up on me.
Poisoned by your stories.
You turned everyone
I ever loved against me.
My own flesh and blood!
Yeah, I guess it's like what they say.
We all could go insane
with just one bad day.
I guess with you,
it's more like one bad spray.
You'll see. (cackles)
Listen to what I have to say!
Oh, hell no! You are
not hypnotizing me again!
(shouting)
That's one way to do it.
Must go, must go, must go, must go!
(chuckles, exclaims)
What are you gonna do to me, Jerome?
Come on. I'm gonna kill you.
Of course.
But, first,
I'm gonna drive you mad.
But don't worry, you won't be alone.
All of Gotham will be joining you, too.
Must go! Must go! They're
after me and the Scarecrow.
These guys just don't give up, huh?
(Bullock yelling)
(gasps)
Get any closer and I splatter him.
I splatter bro-ski.
- (chuckling)
- GORDON: No, you won't.
If you wanted him dead, you
would have killed him already.
(chuckles) He's right.
- I'll see you soon. Mwah!
- (gasps)
(Jerome laughing)
(insects chirping)
Okay, Doc.
You've had enough time
to think of a riddle.
I hope you've come up with a good one.
I have.
Then ask away.
What three words are said too much...
meant by few, but wanted by all?
That's your riddle?
You're kidding. Right?
What's the answer?
Easy. "I love..." (clears throat)
The answer is, "I love..."
I love what, Ed?
- That's not my name.
- Then what's the answer?
You tricked me.
You're trying to awaken
a love that isn't there.
If it isn't there, then say the words.
WOMAN: Say it.
(crowd murmuring)
I won't say it.
(crowd booing)
- MAN: Come on.
- MAN 2: Say it.
MAN 3: Say it.
Time's up.
(crowd cheering)
ALL (chanting):
Doc, Doc, Doc, Doc, Doc...
(chanting continues)
(siren wailing in distance)
Thank you.
What did I say?!
(Oswald choking)
I can help you get Tabitha back.
I know how to reverse your condition.
(gasps)
- Talk.
- This barrel
is from Slaughter Swamp.
It turned you into what you are.
Talk.
Professor Hugo Strange
is the one man who can cure you.
Join me, and we will find him.
(gasping, coughing)
I thought I was gonna
be stuck like this forever.
You don't have to be, friend.
Okay,
I'll join you.
But you better deliver.
I'm not your friend.
I can live with those terms.
Why did you open
your club in the Narrows?
You could have set up shop
anywhere in Gotham.
You wanted my attention.
I came back here
because the people love me.
People didn't come here
because they love you, Ed.
They came for the money.
But I can give them what they want.
I just need your help.
Why would I help you?
(chuckles)
Because I know what you really want.
You love me.
You've loved me all along.
You're wrong.
That was Ed.
Okay.
So do it.
Kill me.
(gasps)
What's your record for how many banks
you've robbed in one day?
Three. Why?
I think you can do better.
You're playing a dangerous game, Lee.
I know.
♪ ♪
(indistinct chatter)
(chatter quiets)
It's all right, come on.
- Captain...
- It's okay.
This is Jeremiah Valeska,
Jerome's twin brother.
We need to put him into
protective custody.
Okay, follow me.
Thank you... Captain Gordon.
I, uh, wouldn't be alive
if it weren't for you.
Hell of a day.
What are you thinking?
Jerome told his brother
his plan was to turn Gotham mad.
How the hell is he
gonna do that, Harvey?
I don't know.
I thought it already was.
(gun clicks)
(gun cylinder spins, clicks)
- (clicks)
- Damn.
Doesn't even make me feel better at all.
CRANE: Jerome, the test subject
has arrived.
Ugh. Little large
for a test subject, don't you think?
He is not your test subject.
This is Grundy.
He will make a welcome
addition to the team.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
I like him.
He's scary. Good thinking, Mr. Oswald.
Nice to meet you, big fella.
Ow.
Ah. Test subject?
JERVIS: Here to test your plan,
an unwilling businessman.
BUSINESSMAN:
No, no, no. No, please, please.
Please don't hurt me.
CRANE: Oh, this... won't hurt a bit.
(groaning)
(coughing)
(businessman chuckling)
(cackling)
(cackling continues)
Oh, we're gonna need a lot more of this!
(cackling)
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com