Previously onGotham...
We got a warrant to search his office
and everything in it.
I'm just not sure there's much
more to see.
We're onto you. Dead people come here
and monsters come out.
Rule number one,
look after number one.
Don't be crazy
or you'll get yourself killed.
Nice to have someone
who cares about me. Thank you.
Why do they keep disappearing
down that hallway?
Oh, my...
Look at the man next to your father.
Hugo Strange. The Philosopher.
A friend. Someone he trusted.
That's not fair.
That's not right.
- Have you seen the news?
- Walking zombies in Gotham?
- What's new?
- Victor Fries and Theo Galavan
both went to Arkham as dead men.
- Both returned.
- I don't care.
So did your friend Bridgit.
Bridgit Pike!
Wait, they sent her to Arkham?
The only way we're gonna find out
what's really going on in there
is if we break in ourselves.
But I go alone.
- Holy cow!
- Forensic guy?
- Street trash girl?
- Where's Strange right now?
There's an elevator,
I'll tell you where it is.
Freeze!
- Bridgit?
- My name is Firefly.
The sooner you stop moving,
the sooner this will be over.
Thanks, no thanks.
You can't escape.
Enjoy yourself, Firefly.
You should feel honored.
You are a sacrifice
to the Goddess of Fire.
It's a blessing few receive.
Man, Bridgit,
someone sure scrambled your eggs.
You're late, Selina.
I was starting to get worried.
I'm not late.
I'm exactly where I'm supposed to be.
Have you seen Selina?
No.
So you're back
to being a rich kid, huh?
Why does your face look like that?
Selina.
She's in trouble and it's my fault.
Regarding last night's
nocturnal activities,
suspect calling himself Azrael
led a one-man assault
upon Wayne Manor,
whereupon an altercation ensued
in which said suspect was
blown up by a person or persons
unknown.
So he's dead.
Any questions?
Can you confirm that the man
known as Azrael
was in fact disgraced Mayor Galavan?
Well, seeing as how the suspect
is now meat dust,
a positive identification
would be difficult.
How long are you acting captain?
Until, literally, the second
someone else wants the job.
Who killed Galavan?
Which time?
Man, give me Azrael, Galavan,
whoever the hell he was,
over those jackals any day.
You need to bring in Hugo Strange.
Oh, yeah, on what charge?
Since when do you care?
Since I became acting captain,
the GCPD and the whole damn city's
got me under a microscope.
Besides which, we've been down
this road.
Strange is smart.
He'll have covered his tracks.
It's pointless going into Arkham
unless we know
what we're looking for.
We can't get that unless
we go in there.
I hear you, brother.
But my hands are tied.
Yeah? Well, mine aren't.
Well, enjoy it because
that's a luxury I don't have!
Detective Gordon.
I was hoping you'd be here.
Bruce, you gotta stop calling me
detective.
What is it?
Selina.
Hugo Strange has Selina.
Regarding last night's
nocturnal activities,
suspect calling himself Azrael
led a one-man assault
upon Wayne Manor,
whereupon an altercation ensued
in which said suspect was...
Yes.
Strange is losing control.
We need to gather the court.
Yes, ma'am.
We have a heartbeat.
He's waking up.
Look at me.
Good morning, son.
You're all right. I'm here.
Can you tell me who you are?
Can you tell me your name?
Who am I?
What is my name?
Yeah.
Amazing.
The Octopod DNA we introduced
provides exactly the effect
I was looking for.
Rest now, son.
I'll return momentarily
to tell you who you are.
What happened to me?
That's the seventh subject you've
woken up in the past 12 hours.
I assume he, like the others,
has no memory of his previous life.
Yes.
Perhaps the trauma of rebirth
is simply too much
for the human mind to process.
You're not worried.
Should I be?
Professor, our employers
are going to shut us down.
You must know this.
What I know
is what we've accomplished.
We've woken the dead.
And, yet, none have returned
with their memory intact.
A tedious point.
What's more preferable
than giving them personas
that we design and control?
An argument lost on our employers
who care about one thing
and one thing only.
You cannot order scientific
discoveries
the way you order a steak, Ethel.
Now let's try subject 13,
shall we?
How could you do this, Master Bruce?
I strictly forbid you from involving
that little girl, didn't I?
I know.
But Selina's always handled herself.
- I was sure.
- But, you were wrong, weren't you?
Well, it's different if you choose to
be involved in something like this
but you actively involved
Selina Kyle.
You put your own concerns
in front of that girl's safety.
You're bang out of order.
I am, I'm really disappointed
in you, Master Bruce.
You're sure she's still there?
Yes.
She wouldn't have missed
our meeting otherwise.
Strange must be holding her
prisoner in Arkham.
Only I doubt she's in Arkham.
I wager Strange has her in the secret
lab where he created Azrael.
But Strange runs Arkham.
He's seen there every day.
The lab must be accessed through
Arkham.
You're thinking it's underground.
It has to be.
There must be stairs,
an elevator, ventilation shafts.
I just don't know how to find them.
I may have a solution.
The technology Strange
is using to create these monsters
must be very advanced.
My guess is he's using plutonium
isotopes to mutate cell structure.
If so, there will be trace radiation.
At Wayne Enterprise, I developed
a miniature Geiger counter
for battlefield use.
Get me into Arkham and I'll find
the entrance to that lab.
Wayne Foundation gives the asylum
money every year.
I'll ask for a tour.
From the man that ordered
the assassination of your father?
He'll wanna find out what we know.
And he won't see me
and Lucius as a threat.
No.
Absolutely bloody not.
You're not to walk straight
into a lion's den.
I can't even go to back you up
with a leg like this, can I?
Alfred, you said yourself
that it's my fault
what happened to Selina Kyle.
That means it's my responsibility
to make it right.
And I may not be the man you choose
as second in a street fight
but anything I can do
to protect Bruce, I will.
Still, it's half a plan, isn't it?
I mean, just say that Lucius
can get you in there
and you find the entrance
to the laboratory, then what?
They tell me.
I call Bullock, he comes busting in
with a hundred cops,
keeps Strange busy, I find Selina.
I see.
And how exactly do you plan
on getting in?
I mean, these two, possibly, but you,
I mean, Strange won't let you
within a bloody mile of the place.
If I can get you inside the gate,
can you manage the rest of the way?
Yeah, I think I can.
The cuttlefish is a fascinating
creature.
Able to regenerate brain cells.
Secrete toxins from its skin, and its
DNA meshes so well with human.
I can't wait to see it in action.
Oh, I want to increase voltage
to her cortex.
Two-hundred-percent.
Are you certain, sir?
It will be like she's being struck
by a bolt of lightning.
Well, how much more damage
could we possibly do.
She's dead.
I'll see you when you wake, my dear.
I'm so pleased you two
are getting along.
I should warn you, Mr. Nygma, Mr.
Stirk has been known to eat people.
But he's promised to stop that,
haven't you, Mr. Stirk?
You have to get me out of here!
Are you asking for a favor?
You should have considered that
before you decided to escape.
How are you gonna stop Jim Gordon?
What?
Jim Gordon and the GCPD have
been here twice in the last week.
It's obvious that they know.
Obvious they know what?
Do I really have to say it?
You're making monsters
in the basement!
I'm hungry!
Quiet, Stirk.
"Monsters in the basement."
You are insane, Mr. Nygma.
Obviously.
Jim Gordon is coming.
And you're gonna need all the help
that you can get.
So why don't you go tell Strange
that if he wants to stop Gordon
and the GCPD
then he's gonna need my help.
Now!
We have a heartbeat.
She's awake.
Quickly, go get Professor Strange.
Mr. Fox is pulling up, upfront.
I told Gordon if I don't hear
from you within an hour,
I'm gonna go straight to Bullock.
I have to do this, Alfred.
- I don't have a choice.
- Of course, you got a choice.
In the same way, I can choose
to let you go with my blessing
and tell you to bring that
little girl home safe
or I can take you right now,
I can stick you on an airplane and
fly you somewhere very far away.
- You can't.
- Don't be such a blunk,
of course, I can.
I won't.
You see, for the past two years,
Master Bruce,
all I've tried to do is protect you
and keep you safe,
thinking that's what your father
wanted.
But you're not the same boy
he left behind, are you?
So I have to ask myself,
what would Thomas Wayne do
if he were here?
Your father took responsibility
for his actions.
He fought very hard
for what he believed in.
And I will not stop you
from doing the same thing.
So...
off you go.
Gordon and Mr. Fox
will be waiting for you.
Welcome back to the world, my dear.
I imagine you're feeling
rather confused.
Can you tell me who you are?
Do you remember your name?
Anything?
You are a war goddess.
Your name is Andrast...
No.
No?
My name is Fish Mooney.
I'm sorry.
Could you please repeat that?
I said my name is Fish Mooney, bitch.
And you better tell me
what the hell is going on.
You're making a mistake keeping me
locked in here.
Do you hear me?
What allowed her to come back
with her memories intact?
It's too soon to tell.
Perhaps it was the increased voltage.
Something unique about the cuttlefish
DNA we spliced with her own.
And then again, she was pulled
from that filthy river,
perhaps a contaminant
from the water altered the process.
Early readings have detected
abnormalities in her brain function.
Yes, she may reveal abilities.
The most important thing is
that she knows who she is.
Our masters will be pleased.
We've created the first,
true reanimant.
Have you made a decision
about Mr. Nygma's offer?
Oh, yes.
Let's let him have a go, shall we?
He was clever enough to find
his way to the basement.
And he does have a point,
he knows Jim Gordon.
I'll tell him.
Bruce Wayne is at the front gate
asking for you.
And he has someone
from Wayne Enterprises with him.
Bold move.
I'm more and more impressed
with this boy.
Shall I tell him you're not here?
On the contrary, I very much
want to speak with him.
Hugo Strange, at your service.
- Lucius Fox.
- Mr. Fox.
And of course you are...
Bruce Wayne.
I can't tell you what it means
to finally meet you.
Your father was very dear to me.
What happened to him and your mother
was indeed a great tragedy.
Please accept my condolences,
belated as they may be.
Thank you.
So how can I be of help?
It goes without saying that the work
we do here would not be possible
without the support
of the Wayne Foundation.
The asylum was a cause close
to my parents' hearts.
As such, I believe it is my duty to
see how their money is being spent.
So this is bit of an inspection.
Oh, nothing so formal.
We were just hoping
for a look around.
We don't normally give tours.
Even to someone who provides
a quarter of your operating budget?
Of course, we can make exceptions.
I'd be happy to be your guide.
Actually, I thought that you
and I could talk
while Mr. Fox looks around.
He's very discreet.
I see.
You've come armed with a plan.
I'm afraid we can't allow
civilians to wander about
but perhaps my assistant Miss Peabody
could accompany Mr. Fox.
That's fine. I'll just get my coat.
Mr. Wayne, if you will.
Bruce is going with Strange
to his office while I get the tour.
I see anything,
I'll mark it with this.
You're clear.
ARKHAM ASYLUM
- This is expired.
- Yeah, I lost my new one.
Keep meaning to have it replaced.
Do it today.
This is our rec room,
where our inmates work
on their socialization skills.
Who designed the uniforms?
Do you have much training
in mental health, Mr. Fox?
None, none at all.
- Shall we continue?
- Yes.
Bruce, as much as I value
the opportunity to finally meet you,
perhaps we could address
the real reason for your visit.
I'm not sure I know what you mean.
Well, you see, the other day,
James Gordon came to see me.
He asked about a project that your
father and I worked on a decade ago.
I was led to believe that
he was acting on your behalf.
Is that not why you're here?
After he left the GCPD,
I retained Mr. Gordon
to look into my parents' deaths.
He's been pursuing various leads
and he doesn't share
everything with me.
If he overstepped or caused some
offense, you have my apologies.
Thank you.
And I can understand
how you want answers.
How difficult it must be to accept
that something so horrific
as the murder of one's own parents
could be a random
and meaningless act.
So you want a reason.
Someone to blame.
In their case, I think
there was someone to blame.
Oh, so do I.
Sugar?
Arkham Asylum has been open
before the days of water
cures and trepanning.
That's boring a hole in the skull
to release bad humors.
We don't do that anymore.
What is that?
This measures air-quality.
Micro-particles.
Mr. Wayne is concerned
that the patients
are in a healthy environment.
Asthma and whatnot.
You're doing good so far.
I'm so relieved.
This way.
- Mr. Fox?
- Yep.
Coming.
You remind me of him.
Thomas.
You have that same look in your eyes.
What look is that?
Certainty.
As a scientist that's a luxury
that I cannot afford.
No, in science there must always be
some doubt but not with Thomas.
No. Thomas believed in things.
I think what you're referring
to is moral principles.
Yes.
Sadly, science and moral absolutes
do not make easy bedfellows.
Oh, the arguments we used to have.
I could never make him listen.
I'm glad to hear that.
Are you?
Haven't you ever imagined the life
that might have been
if your father hadn't been
so certain?
If he had listened?
Then he wouldn't have been
the man he was.
True.
But he wouldn't be dead either.
Along with your mother.
Are those ideals that your father
cherished so worth it?
Wouldn't you gladly trade everything
you believe
for one more day, one more hour
with your parents alive?
So you admit it then?
You admit what you did?
Here's what I admit, Bruce.
That I was your father's friend
and I pleaded with him
as I plead with you now.
Turn back.
Surely, you have those
that you care about.
For their sake, as well as your own.
Make the choice your father did not.
You have been searching
for the man who killed your parents
but the answer has always been
right in front of you.
Bruce, your father orphaned you.
His actions fired the bullet
that killed him and your mother.
He knew what he was doing
and he did it anyway.
I'm begging you
not to follow his path.
You want to know if I wish
my parents were alive?
Of course.
Would I give anything
to have them back?
Yes.
But my father fought and died
for what he believed was right.
And if necessary,
so will I.
Take them.
It seems you are your father's son.
I want you to know how greatly
I respect that.
Where's Selina Kyle?
What have you done with her?
They got you locked up good in here.
I'm gonna get us out of here,
Bridgit.
Bruce is gonna find us
and we'll get you help.
Lunchtime.
Where am I?
This isn't an island, is it?
Hey, lady, I just work here.
You want your lunch?
You wanna make yourself useful?
Make me a grilled cheese sandwich.
Someone will come looking
for the Wayne boy.
Yes.
You like him.
He reminds me of Thomas.
Whom I miss,
ironic as that might seem.
The boy is a threat.
You know what needs to be done.
You don't have much time.
You have less than you imagine.
Oh, no.
We need a word, Strange.
Of course, how might I be of service?
First, the father, now the son.
You have a habit of catching
the eye of the Wayne family.
Everything is under control.
So you say.
The fact is, you've lost sight
of your mission.
Sending men with swords into Gotham.
Freaks armed with freeze guns.
There have been missteps,
I grant you.
But look at all we've accomplished.
We do not care about your monsters.
What do they have to do
with restoring the dead to life?
Physical regeneration has always
been a necessary part
of bringing back the dead.
I had to resort to any means
necessary
to make humans stronger, faster...
Be that as it may, you have failed
at your core objective.
That is not true.
Immortality means returning to life
with one's mind
and memories intact
and you have not.
Oh, but I have.
When?
Today.
I brought someone back.
Memories, emotion, the soul itself.
Back from death.
If you're lying...
I am not.
Can you repeat the process?
If given time, I believe so.
Very well.
Find out what the Wayne boy
and his companions know.
Move everything you can
to the facility upstate.
Then destroy any evidence
of Indian Hill.
- By destroy, you mean...
- You have an explosive device.
Use it.
Destroy Indian Hill.
What's this?
It's a grilled cheese sandwich.
You made me a sandwich?
Yeah.
Why?
I don't know.
You told me to.
Wait.
I don't know what to do, Bridgit.
It's simple.
You can die.
Drop it!
Don't make me hurt you.
You think you can hurt me?
I am the Goddess of Fire.
You're not the goddess of anything.
You're Bridgit.
We grew up together.
We're friends!
When my mom left, you took me in.
- Goddesses don't have friends.
- Says who?
The professor.
He told me who I am.
Screw him.
Remember the pigeons?
How we used to feed them?
It's me, Selina.
You, you gotta remember.
I...
Cale flamed up good
but Joe burned the brightest.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah, you fried your brothers.
Not the memory I was hoping for,
but it's something.
You'll burn bright.
I know it.
No, no.
I am Firefly.
Fire cannot not touch me.
Oh, crap.
You're the Goddess of Fire, right?
Right?
Goddesses have servants and stuff.
Let me be your servant.
Why do I need a servant?
You can't be a goddess
without a servant.
Come on, it's totally part
of the story.
The professor just forgot
to tell you.
You gotta have a servant.
I guess that's true.
Hello.
Oh, man.
Double shifts until I say otherwise.
And I want everyone in a uniform
out on the streets.
Bullock!
Gordon, Master Bruce and Fox
are still in Arkham.
They should be out by now.
They're in trouble.
That son of a bitch!
Jim Gordon, I mean.
He's forcing my hand.
Are you listening to me?
Grab your gun, your badge, and
your bits and your bobs and let's go.
Hold on a second, okay?
You're talking about a place
that's built like a fortress,
chock-a-block with armed guards.
Now while we could send in
an assault force
of a middle-aged Irish detective
and a recently-stabbed Englishman.
I think the acting captain of the
GCPD could do a little better.
Right.
Go get our guys.
Bravo Team, on me.
Lucius.
Bruce, are you okay?
I'm fine. Where's Gordon?
I haven't seen him.
I'm sorry I got you into this,
Lucius.
It seems likely we're all going
to die in here.
Don't say that.
I don't mind dying.
I mind that I got you and Jim Gordon
and Selina Kyle involved.
Bruce, you are a remarkable
young man
but you didn't force any of us
to do anything.
We chose.
Hugo Strange said that all this time
I'd been searching for the man
who killed my parents
when really it was my own father.
That he knew what he was doing.
That I am my father's son.
Bruce, your father had the courage
to fight for what he believed in.
And as long as there is life,
there is hope.
Touching sentiment.
Who are you?
Where is Jim Gordon?
Yeah.
I would urge you to worry
about yourselves right now.
Jim Gordon has his own problems.
Strange, you son of a bitch!
Where's Bruce Wayne?
- If you've hurt him...
- Bruce Wayne is alive.
For now.
Try me and that may change.
You won't get away with this.
People know we're here.
They're already on their way
to stop you.
Yes. And I'm afraid I simply
can't allow that.
The work that I'm doing here
is too important
and at too critical a juncture.
But fortunately,
a solution has presented itself.
Gentlemen.
- What are you doing?
- Hold still.
The solution is very important.
You must not spill a drop.
So here's the situation.
Professor Strange has tasked me
with finding out
how much you two know
about what he's been up to.
And, more importantly, who you told.
Show us Jim Gordon and Selina Kyle.
Think you're not quite grasping
the power dynamic here, Turtleneck.
As I was saying.
We need to know what you know.
And you're gonna tell me
or poison gas will spew
from the nozzles above your head
and you will both die
very, very painfully.
I know this voice.
He worked for the GCPD.
He had a funny kind of name.
There's nothing funny about my name.
He was the one that framed
Jim Gordon.
You always were a smart cookie, Foxy.
Do you know why Strange gave me
this job?
It's because he knows that I would
kill you both and not bat an eye.
So, keeping that in mind,
five minutes on the clock.
Starting...
now.
Fun.
What the hell was that?
You'll see.
Allow me to introduce, Basil.
Basil just woke up this morning,
didn't you, son?
Yep.
He was confused, poor soul.
He had forgotten who he was, until
I reminded him of his great talent.
You see, Basil is a gifted performer.
A chameleon of sorts.
Would you like to see?
You belong in your own asylum,
Strange.
And you, James Gordon,
belong in the past.
The world has moved on.
While you and others like you
were living your sad, normal lives,
I was pushing the boundaries
of evolution.
The future belongs to my children
and that future is here.
Inbound to Arkham Asylum.
Strike force ready.
Tell me what you know.
Astonishing.
Oh, yes, oh, yes.
The finishing touch.
Introduce yourself, son.
Nice to meet you.
What the hell?
You son of a bitch!
Son of a bitch!
Nice to meet you.
I'm Jim Gordon.