GORDON: Previously on Gotham...
I wish something would happen
to old man Falcone.
Who would take over then?
Let me guess.
Maroni had nothing to do
with the armory job.
You have a mole, obviously.
Someone close to you.
BULLOCK:
Arkham Asylum?
Security guard for nut jobs?
Criminal nut jobs, yeah.
Metal needles were inserted
into the brain,
and electricity was applied
to his frontal lobes.
I want you to find out which one
of our inmates did this.
(bones snapping)
GRUBER:
Well done, Aaron.
Exactly like I told you.
Now, you are my
best work so far.
♪ ♪
(horn honking)
(buzzer blaring)
No. No, no.
The merchandise
has got to be mint,
or you won't get a dime.
(electrical crackling
and whooshing, screaming)
My God.
Jack.
Hi, Irwin.
Where's my stuff?
Aaron Danzig.
Six-four, 225.
Mental age of a young child.
We believe he's under
the control of this man,
Jack Gruber.
In Arkham
off a rape/murder beef.
We can't find
any records on Gruber
prior to his incarceration,
so we're guessing
Gruber is an alias.
We're sending
his prints nationwide,
see if we can find
another name for him.
Whoever he is,
he's clever and angry
and a grave public menace.
The commissioner
is deeply concerned,
and he's on his way here
to talk to all
of you right now.
You know what that means.
And you know...
Jim?
Captain.
Hey, partner.
Hi.
ESSEN: You're out of
your jurisdiction.
Captain, this is my case.
Jim, you need
to get out of here.
It's my case.
No, no, no.
The captain is right.
You need to leave before
the commissioner gets here.
Why?
Because he holds you responsible
for all of this,
and... oh, fudge.
He's here.
And you're there. Sidestep.
Captain Essen.
Good morning,
Commissioner.
Officer Gordon, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
Why are you here?
I have a better question.
Why are you here, Commissioner?
Excuse me?
This is the first
I've seen you down here
with the rank and file.
You must be desperate.
Follow me.
Really nice knowing you.
LOEB:
Bring you friend Bullock.
(whispering):
I hate you.
It wasn't my idea;
it was your friend.
He came up with
the double-cross,
made me go along.
You have a mind of your own,
don't you?
Hey, come on.
See? (chuckles)
I kept your gadgets safe.
I know what it means to you,
all your experiments.
Oh, I appreciate that.
Please.
You don't have to kill me.
I don't...
have to do anything.
I'm free.
You know the funny thing?
I think it was my time in Arkham
that freed me.
I mean,
in here.
Now I see
the world for what it really is.
An abandoned factory
full of broken machines.
Some...
very few...
Can be fixed.
Most...
just have to be scrapped.
Danzig, hold him, please.
(whimpering)
Please.
Please, no, stop. Please.
Please! Please!
Two maniacs on the loose
makes the whole Arkham Project
look kind of shady, huh?
The moneymen want
results fast, I bet.
You're strangely self-righteous,
given that it was you
that let
these men escape.
Blame me all you want.
My name's already mud.
Those two will still be
out there,
and that means you need me.
James, why did you
become a policeman?
Your father was
the district attorney.
A proud station
for a man of substance.
You would think
that would inspire a son
to practice law.
I'm enforcing the law.
You want to talk about my dad
or do you want to catch
Gruber and Danzig?
Where do you get the
rebellious fire in your belly?
BULLOCK:
Can I take this opportunity
to say that I have
no rebellious fire here, nada.
Jack Gruber is out there,
planning a catastrophe.
I know the man.
I know how he thinks.
I know what he'll do next.
Which is what?
That I'll keep to myself.
I guarantee I'll bring
in these two men,
but first, I need you
to reinstate me
as detective first grade
in the GCPD.
Extortion, Officer Gordon.
24 hours?
What?
You've got 24 hours
to bring these men in.
You don't,
you can both spend the rest
of your miserable careers
down at Arkham.
That will be all, Detectives.
What the hell just happened?
It's okay, it's okay.
Everything's gonna
be fine, Harvey.
Yeah?
Yeah, we just got
to catch the bad guys.
Okay, where are we going?
I don't know.
What? You just told him you knew
what Gruber was gonna do next.
I lied.
♪ ♪
(women crying)
MAN:
Please, Don Falcone,
have mercy.
We're family.
I know, son.
I know it's hard.
A young man like you,
it doesn't seem fair.
(gun clicks)
(whimpering):
Please.
Don Falcone, please!
(gunshots)
(thunder rumbling)
This whole area used to be slums
when I was a boy.
LIZA:
You've come a long way.
Some of your people are
looking for you, you know.
But you're the one
I wanted to see.
I've worked so long all my life
to get where I am.
So long, I forget why
I wanted to be here.
Well, you wanted
to be someone.
And you are.
Look at all the
stuff you have.
(thunder rumbles)
You're a good girl, Liza.
You need to find a young man
and get married,
have babies.
It's not fair of me,
keeping you cooped up here,
doing my housework.
You'll never find
a good husband here.
Anyhow, if you'd like
to get out in the world,
I was thinking
I could set you up
with a bakery or some type
of business like that.
So you can be independent.
That's really nice, Mr. F.
Thank you.
But I would rather
be here with you.
You would?
I like it here.
You make me feel safe.
Well, good.
I like having you here.
Yeah.
Maybe I'll try to get a little
work done before dinner.
I'm making something
special tonight.
(car door closing)
(screaming)
What are you laughing at?
Ah, it's good to be back.
Only a man from
a lunatic asylum
would say that.
You're like a human
roller coaster,
except you only go down.
Wouldn't that make him
more of an elevator?
You have anything useful, Ed?
I got a little less
than 20 hours
before I lose my job.
I do... have something useful.
And it is?
I cross-checked fingerprints.
The clinically insane
Jack Gruber
of Arkham is a figment
of the files.
The man himself is really
a career criminal
by the name Jack Buchinsky.
How is that even possible?
Easy enough to bribe someone
to change the records.
Yep, apparently, he wanted
to be transferred to Arkham.
That's really
good work, Ed.
What's this
Buttinsky's deal?
NYGMA:
Uh, it's, uh,
Buchinsky.
It's all in the files.
Just make sure you sign it out.
It's classified information,
so just be careful.
Miss Kringle?
(sighs)
I believe you left this
on my desk.
It's a riddle.
It's a cupcake
with a live bullet
sticking out of it.
It's a riddle.
It's menacing
and weird and inedible.
Thank you for the files,
Miss Kringle.
BULLOCK: This Buchinsky dude
and his partners
pulled four successful
bank robberies,
killed six along the way
before the GCPD caught him
by accident.
He never named his accomplices.
GORDON:
He's in prison,
he hears Arkham
is opening its doors,
so he uses his connections,
and he gets himself
a new identity
as the mental patient Gruber.
He must have some
good connections.
Right, and when the rest
of the nuts get transferred
to Arkham... voilà.
So, he had
partners, huh?
Yeah, GCPD never
identified them.
They're still
out there.
Yep, we find them,
we'll find him.
BULLOCK:
Easy enough, huh?
Detective.
A hit.
GORDON:
What do we got?
MAN:
Lead detectives dusted
for prints, two sets...
Gruber and Danzig,
just like we thought.
Right. Thanks.
All right.
Van checks out.
It was them.
Our man's an electronics
freak, right?
Yeah.
Think he went
shopping?
He's dead.
Fried like a doughnut.
(faint squeaking)
(faint squeaking continues)
GORDON:
GCPD.
Turn around slowly,
let me see those hands.
Hey.
(groans)
Hey, buddy.
Hey. Hey!
(screams)
Help, help! Please!
Get back in the store.
Okay. Take it easy. Okay.
(tires screech)
Please, there's been
a terrible mistake.
I am Don Falcone's housekeeper.
Fish?
Thank God.
Why'd you have to pull
me out like that?
You scared the
life out of me.
It's time, Liza.
I'm gonna make
my move on Falcone.
And don't be scared,
baby girl.
I got this.
(phone rings)
SCRAMBLED MALE VOICE:
Mr. Falcone,
we have your girl, Liza.
Would you like to see her again?
Yes, I would.
She'll be glad to hear that.
For a fit young woman,
she has a low pain threshold.
Please! No!
Stop!
An intermediary will be
in contact with you soon.
Don't hurt her.
She's a civilian.
(call disconnects)
Hello?
What now?
Now we let him sit and think
about his life for a while.
BULLOCK:
"The Electrocutioner."
Cute.
No pressure.
Don't worry, we'll get him.
Yeah, and we got 17 hours
to do so.
I love the name.
It's catchy, has drama.
The Electro-cutioner.
Speaking of which, given
the general mode of attack,
may I suggest you
both wear your...
department-issue galoshes
while you're out in the field.
Galoshes?
In the event of
electrical misadventure,
your footwear should
be insulated.
No, Mom!
I'm not gonna wear
my rubbers on the case.
Nygma, give 'em here.
Seriously?
BULLOCK: All right,
so what do we know?
Gruber wasn't too happy
with Irwin.
Maybe they were partners in
crime, Irwin turned on him,
Gruber took the fall.
Detective Gordon.
Dr. Thompkins.
My friends call me Lee.
Congratulations, you
got your job back.
Or not, depending.
It's good to see you.
Is it?
I-I know you're caught
up with the escape.
That's why I'm here.
Is everything okay?
Must be chaos down there.
We're getting by just fine.
Thanks for asking.
(clears throat)
Oh, right, this is my
partner, Harvey Bullock.
Hola.
Detective Bullock.
Who's your little
friend there?
Oh, this is
why I'm here.
One of the women in my
wing is a pagan sorceress.
Of course.
She's very popular.
The inmates make dolls
to look like people
that they want to curse.
And then they give it to
the sorceress to curse them.
In exchange for extra
soda and candy.
I curse you all the time.
You never give me candy.
I asked her if Gruber
had ever given her
a doll to curse,
and she said yes.
This is the doll.
His name is Mr. M.
You owe me for a double
six-pack of root beer.
Mr. M.?
Mr. M.
Who does this
look like to you?
MARONI: I tell this guy,
I said, "Maurice...
"we've pulled out half
your freaking teeth.
"What the hell are
you waiting for?
The tooth fairy?" Right?
(laughter)
(cell phone buzzes)
So, what he does...
you know what Maurice does?
He smiles at me.
So I say, "I'm
gonna take out
another one, man."
I go to his molar.
I got to get Mario and Gabe
to help me pull it out.
Do excuse me.
Right.
So, we're, like, pulling it,
we're pulling it, right?
And finally
we get it out.
The thing is this big...
Yes.
FALCONE:
Come see me.
I need you.
I'm on my way.
What's wrong?
Somebody took Liza.
Come, quickly.
You sly devil.
You took her.
You're mine now.
So I'm trying to tell
this guy, "Let him talk."
Because now he's trying to talk,
but now I don't understand him
'cause he's got no teeth, right?
(laughing)
So I'm saying,
"Let him talk. Clean him out.
He's gonna tell us something."
Don Maroni, sir, forgive me.
Such fun we're having.
But I regret
that I must run away.
If you'll let me.
My mother is sick.
Well, a sick mother's
a sick mother.
Go.
Hey...
Penguin, you all right?
Whoa.
Hey, kid, what
are you...?
What's going on here?
Get down!
(coughing)
MARONI:
I don't know what happened.
It was like a silent bomb.
You know who
did this, right?
Who?
A few years ago,
Jack Buchinsky
and partners unknown
knocked over four banks.
Killed six people.
Buchinsky went
down for life.
His partners were
never caught.
You're one of
those partners.
(chuckles)
The one that took his share and
sold him up the river, I expect.
What guy was this?
Bu... uh...
Who?
While he's out there
looking to hurt you,
he doesn't care
who else he hurts.
Women, kids.
Hey.
That's not my fault.
Help me do the right
thing here, Don Maroni.
Let me place you in
protective custody.
Protective custody?
Yes.
Bait, you mean.
We catch our bad guy,
you get rid of a
dangerous nuisance.
We both come
out ahead.
Excuse me.
Hello?
I... must be going.
Very urgent business.
W-W-With Falcone.
All right, make
yourself at home.
Hey, sweetheart.
Get me a double espresso.
Extra sugar.
Nah.
(rings doorbell)
I'm Barbara.
Barbara Kean.
My parents, they live here.
It's very nice to
see you, Barbara.
Isn't it, Everett?
(sighs)
Yes, very nice.
It's nice
to see you, too.
You've been well, I hope?
Yes.
And you?
Splendid.
Are you staying the night?
Uh, if that's
all right.
In fact, um...
I-I thought maybe
I could stay a few days.
If that's...
Oh, I see.
Yes, of course.
I'm sure you're going
to be frightfully bored.
But stay until
the weekend.
By all means.
Thank you.
How's that young
man of yours?
James?
The policeman?
All well, I hope?
Yes.
He's well, thank you.
Good.
We're very happy.
Very happy.
(men laughing)
You guys are, like,
hungry for this.
What do you guys do here
for excitement?
Remember that joke
about the, uh, what is it?
The two cops and the undertaker
that go on a fishing boat.
When you use
a tethered goat as bait,
shouldn't the goat be out in
the jungle and not in the house?
This house is the
best-defended spot in Gotham.
Buchinsky is crazy and
arrogant and resourceful.
Wherever Maroni is,
he'll come after him.
He'll enjoy the challenge.
(indistinct chatter)
(gasps)
Hey, there.
Hi... hi, boss.
How long have I
been unconscious?
Couple of hours.
Oh, my gosh.
I-I must go.
My-my poor mother...
Your mother can wait.
(quiet gasp)
It's her heart, poor thing.
Valves.
She-she might be
taken at any moment...
But... but,
by all means,
of course, she can wait.
When you woke up before,
you said you had
urgent business...
...with Falcone.
I did?
I said that?
Did I?
(phone ringing)
MOONEY:
Carmine?
Some people have called me
about your girl Liza.
They want me
to help make a deal.
I didn't think
it was going to be you.
I'm sorry.
I'm just an intermediary.
I just want to help.
Please, my dear.
Stop.
I know this is you.
Be honest.
It's me.
Of course it is.
How long have I known you?
You're the smart one
in the family.
Didn't I always say so?
She won't be hurt.
Leave Gotham.
That's all... leave Gotham,
never come back.
You can take her with you.
Agreed.
That's the right decision.
I'll make the arrangements.
You were always my favorite.
Wait for my call.
GILZEAN:
He's leaving?
You did it?
(laughing)
Boss?
The genius! The-the vision!
You brought down
the old man... finally.
Let's celebrate.
Butch, this is not
the time to celebrate.
He was a great man once.
You don't think somebody would
take him out if he stayed on?
I am doing him a favor
and giving him an easy way out.
I owe him at least that.
Of course.
You're right.
It's best for everyone.
LIZA:
How did he sound?
Sad.
Look at me.
Is there something
you're not telling me?
No.
You're going to have
to leave town with him,
string him along for a while.
Do you think
you can do that?
Sure.
But you like him, though,
don't you?
Well, I can like him, can't I?
He's been
a perfect gentleman.
He could've done anything,
and he never laid a hand on me.
Liza, you can like
him all you want.
But you can never
tell him the truth.
I know that.
Sir?
Let me go to work.
No.
"No"?
If Fish and the others...
and there must be others...
if they all want me
to step away so badly,
maybe it's time.
Why not?
Why am I still here fighting?
For what?
For respect.
You're Don Carmine Falcone.
"Respect"?
Who cares?
They all want me
to go live in the country
with Liza.
I would like that.
That's what I want, too.
So, why not do it?
Please...
don't talk that way, sir.
(laughs)
And just me on my own?
I can take out Fish's crew easy.
You're not
listening, Victor.
Your job is to keep
me and Liza safe
through the coming transaction.
That's all.
Yes, sir.
Miss Kringle?
(gasps)
What?! What?
The cupcake is sweet,
the bullet is deadly.
A beautiful woman's
a dangerous thing.
Um, uh, listen, I, uh...
That is so...
I don't...
I don't even know
what to say to that.
Nygma, you perv, back off.
Can't you see the lady
doesn't want you bugging her?
NYGMA:
I, um...
Hey, there. Hey, now.
Who's bugging who?
I'm just, I'm just...
What's green and then red?
Frogs in a blender.
(laughs)
Walk away, Nygma.
Walk away.
I'm very sorry if I've
offended you, Miss Kringle.
That was not my intention.
(rumbling nearby)
Do you hear that?
Go.
Thank you.
He is so weird.
OSWALD:
I have no business with Falcone!
I swear on my mother's life!
May God strike her dead
with horrible torment
if I'm lying!
Okay, then, my friend.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
Go see your mom.
Give her a kiss for me.
(shuddering):
Thank you.
(men and women clamoring)
(all yelling, clamoring)
Ah.
There's the one.
Under that funny-looking
fellow there.
(grunts)
Take him to the truck.
They didn't cook.
Just stunned.
I expected more...
oomph!
You want "oomph," Jack?
Ah.
Officer Gordon.
Nice shoes.
Detective Gordon.
Hands up, both of you.
Uh, you might want to drop that.
Aah!
(grunting)
Why fight me, Gordon?
Who here
deserves your protection?
Any of them?
All of them.
Even Maroni?! Please!
Just let me kill
this false friend
and get on with my life.
(both grunting)
All this fight.
And for what?
I'm putting you
back in Arkham, Jack.
That's closer to the mark,
now, isn't it, Jim?
You need to win.
Don't you? You pretend
to care about the law,
but in your heart,
it's all primitive ego.
And you lust
for blood and power.
You just hate to lose.
You know what?
You're right.
(sputters, whirrs)
I do hate to lose.
(cup clatters on ground)
Hmm.
(reporters clamoring)
Congratulations,
young man.
A new day.
New day.
Next man that tries to
take away my shield...
one way or another,
I'm gonna make him eat it.
Say again?
New day, Commissioner.
I hope you have some
nasty pictures of him,
because I bet
what you said was very,
very rude.
I'm done being careful.
You think you've
been careful so far?
Men like Commissioner Loeb
are never gonna trust me.
You think you've been careful
so far?
So why play nice?
You think...
you've been careful so far?
Don't worry.
I know what I'm doing.
Let's go grab
a beer.
Now you're messing with my mind.
I need something
stronger than a beer.
♪ ♪
(sighs)
Hush, young man.
I can hear you sigh.
Sorry, sir.
Let him be.
It's good to see you,
old friend.
I am so sorry it took me
so long to get here.
Such a day I've had...
I won't even tell you.
But I'm here.
You were right about Fish.
It's her that's taken Liza.
Sir, allow me...
I must tell you
what I've discovered.
You're not gonna
want to hear this.
Speak.
Liza was planted on you by Fish.
She belongs to Fish.
This was a setup from the start.
She found a girl that looked
just like your mother,
and trained her up...
(grunts)
No.
I'm sorry.
Prove that.
How?
I-I can't.
I just know.
You're wrong.
When have I been wrong?
(phone ringing)
FALCONE:
Hello, Fish.
Don Falcone.
We will meet at my place.
Acceptable?
Yes.
Is she there? Is Liza there now?
Can I speak to her?
No.
What time?
In an hour.
I'll be there.
(door opens)
Fish.
Don Falcone.
How's this work?
Liza is close by.
All I need for you to do
is sign papers...
relinquish all control
of the family...
and then you're both
free to leave.
Papers?
You think papers make a don?
I'm offering you a way out,
Carmine.
I appreciate that.
Thank you.
But I need to see her first.
Before I sign anything,
I need to know
she's all right.
She's fine.
I need to see her.
Or no deal.
(clicks tongue)
(door opens)
(footsteps approach)
Are you all right?
I'm okay.
How long have you known
Fish Mooney?
Huh?
I don't.
I just met her now.
No.
A little bird
told me you and she
have been friends for a while.
No.
Told me that she told you
stuff about my mother
so that I'd get
all caught up in you.
Because
Fish knows.
You know,
about my mother.
You know how much
I loved my mother,
because we talked about her
all the time,
you and me.
Remember, Fish?
Back in the day?
I do.
It seems as though a little bird
has been making
a bit of mischief.
Yes.
That's what I had hoped.
But the truth is plain to see.
I am very disappointed
at my own stupidity.
(door opens)
(whistles)
I'm sorry, Liza.
Is that your name?
I'm sorry
you had to get
mixed up in this,
because I'm sure you're a...
good, honest girl,
really.
(gasps)
(choking)
(crunching)
No.
♪ ♪
FALCONE:
I want these two
alive for now.
Lock them up someplace.
Don't bother
yelling for help.
All your people are dead.
Carmine...
you have
to under...
I can forgive
all kinds of betrayal
and dishonesty.
But my mother?
How dare you use
my sainted mother
against me?
That's wrong!
You'll suffer
for that.
I need you to...
Thank you, Fish.
For the first time
in a long time,
I feel alive.
I remember who I am.
I remember
why I'm here.
Just...
You can come out now.
(door opens)
Right, as usual,
my friend.
Say your good-byes quickly.
Ms. Mooney has
places to go.
Hello, Fish.
(laughing)
(shower running)
(shower shuts off)
Hi.
Dr. Thompkins.
Lee.
The desk sergeant said
it was okay to come back here.
I didn't mean to disturb you.
No, no.
It's okay.
Something wrong?
No.
Um, I was in the area,
and, um... my sorceress
wants her doll back.
Right, yeah.
Is that why you're here?
Yes.
No.
She does want her
doll back, but, um...
Not entirely.
No.
You live here?
Sort of between places
right now.
(laughs)
I don't know why I'm here.
Sorry.
A whim.
Wait.
OFFICER:
Hey, Gordon,
did you hear?
There's been a big shootout
at Fish Mooney's place.