Previously onGotham...
Uncle Frank, maybe you wanna tell me
where the hell you've been
- since I was a kid?
- The Court has a secret society.
If it's so secret,
how do you know about them?
Your father and I
were both members.
He was a drunk driver.
I watched him die.
My brother was making trouble
and they killed him.
One cannot deny a love.
I don't love you.
Look who's alive.
I just remembered there's someone
I need to kill.
The clone is in place.
- What about Bruce Wayne?
- He should be waking up
as we speak.
I've always done whatever
the court has asked of me.
- What are you telling me?
- The city is on the brink of chaos.
Seems like judgement came to Gotham
earlier than expected.
Members of the Ruling Council,
Gotham has fallen ill.
Violence and crime continue to spread
like an unstoppable disease.
Drastic action must be taken.
To that end,
a weapon is being built.
A weapon intended
to be unleashed on Gotham
so that the city may be cleansed
and rebuilt by us.
The Head of our Court asks
that we reach
a unanimous vote to proceed.
Judgement has been passed.
Gotham must fall.
I want to speak
with whoever's in charge.
That would be me.
Is the Court of Owls
behind my abduction?
The Court is a tool. Nothing more.
You can't get away with this.
People will know I'm gone.
We've taken precautions to ensure
your absence won't be noticed.
My clone.
He's in Gotham pretending
to be me, isn't he?
Alfred will figure it out.
Perhaps.
But by that time,
I'm hoping
we've accomplished our goals.
Which is what?
I need your help, Bruce.
Eat.
You're going to need your strength.
We'll begin soon.
Aubrey James about...
All right, come on people, come on.
Let's get back to work.
Joe, shut that off.
Can you believe this nonsense?
After all that's said and done,
who's back in charge?
Aubrey James.
The original crook himself.
How was the cabin?
- What?
- You and your uncle,
you must
have had a lot to catch up on.
Oh, yeah.
Any word on Nygma?
No, but after gassing the cadets
and dangling me over an empty
stairwell, he just disappeared.
No, riddles, puzzles
or singing telegrams yet.
Who's Michael Ness?
The drunk driver
who hit and killed my father
when I was nine.
I think what my uncle said
got me thinking.
- What do you got?
- Not much.
He was convicted of vehicular
manslaughter, got six years.
Then got his ticket punched
in a prison stabbing a few months in.
- Silver lining.
- Yeah.
But I pulled his medical file
from Blackgate
and found something that wasn't
in the original case file.
He had chronic persistent hepatitis.
I was gonna ask Lee what it was
when she got in.
Chronic persistent hepatitis
is a non-progressive form
of liver inflammation.
- How do you know that?
- You kidding?
It's known as the Irish Curse.
With chronic inflammation,
you cannot drink.
Nothing. Not a drop. Not even beer.
Well, this guy didn't get the memo.
His blood alcohol was off
the charts the night of the accident.
You're not hearing me, if this guy
had chronic liver inflammation,
if he blew a 0.1
on a blood-alcohol test,
he'd be dead
before he got behind the wheel.
If that's true, then someone
dummied up the report.
- Can you do some digging?
- Yeah.
- Find out who this guy was.
- Sure, but...
Hey, where you going?
Pretty cool?
I told you, the whole estate
was abandoned. Can you believe it?
As a matter of fact, I can.
You know,
the fresh air will do you good.
It smells like rotting death in here.
- I think someone's hungry, daisy.
- Stop it!
I told you I am fine.
I'm a grown man for crying out loud!
And you're hungry.
What's with you and all the plants?
They're my friends.
Your friends?
- Yeah.
- Wonderful.
You know, plants make better
friends than most people.
And some of them
helped save your life.
It's broth.
I even put in some White Willow
for your fever.
What is wrong with you?
For the millionth time,
I need to get back to Gotham.
What's the rush?
I was betrayed and shot.
I should be plotting my revenge.
Building an army.
Not drinking pinecone juice
with the crazy plant-lady.
So? Build an army.
No one's stopping you.
And I can even help
if you weren't being such a jerk.
Jerk.
Fine.
I need you to deliver a message
to Gabe.
Who's Gabe?
He's a moron.
But he's a loyal moron.
And every army starts
with one single loyal soldier.
"Please."
Please.
Okay. Fine.
Thank you for meeting me.
Why here?
It's public, open, easy to spot
if anyone was watching us.
The driver who hit my father's
car that night wasn't drunk.
I think he did it on purpose
and someone made it look
like an accident.
Easy enough for The Court.
So let's assume I believe you.
What do you want from me?
I've just learned something
I'm still having trouble believing.
A weapon is en route,
headed for Gotham.
A weapon the Court intends to use
to destroy the city.
What are you talking about?
You said The Court controls Gotham.
Why would they wanna destroy it?
This isn't The Court as a whole.
It's a limited to a number
of high-ranking members.
Fanatics who believe
the city needs to be cleansed.
And you really think
they're capable of this?
They've done it before.
Twice in the city's history
they've laid waste to Gotham.
It's no bluff.
So, how do we stop it?
I have no idea.
I don't even know
what the weapon is.
But that's exactly
what I'm going to find out.
- I can help.
- No.
The Court knows
I reached out to you but that's all.
We need to keep it that way.
In case I'm discovered.
Be careful, Uncle Frank.
Sorry, I didn't mean to intrude.
I saw you earlier.
Who was that man you were with?
My uncle Frank.
I thought you two were estranged?
We recently reconnected.
Good for you.
I've been coming here a lot.
The other day,
I saw this little old man,
must have been in his 90's.
All dressed up.
Standing in front of his wife's
grave, smiling.
I couldn't understand
what there was to smile about.
And then it occurred to me...
...they shared a whole life together.
I'm sorry.
How do you do that?
How do you just move on
leaving so much destruction
in your wake?
I wish I could do that.
- Yeah?
- Hey.
That driver that hit and killed
your father that night
was a career scumbag.
What'd you find out?
He did a stretch for Grand Theft Auto
among other things.
And get this, a high-priced
lawyer who got him his plea
was paid for by none other
than Carmine Falcone.
Okay. That's...
Easy. Okay, that's enough.
Boss, I can't believe it.
You know, that everyone
thinks you're dead?
- Yes.
- And that Barbara is running things?
Gabe. This might go faster
if you just listened.
I need to build an army
to exact my revenge
and to take back my throne,
will you help me?
Of course, I will.
When the guys hear
that you're still alive,
they'll come running.
I'll make sure of it.
What do you want me to do?
That!
I want you to do that, Gabe.
Right. I got it. No problem.
Hey, Saul.
There's something off about him.
No argument there.
I don't trust him.
Gabe?
He's a human Labrador.
You whistle, he comes running.
Trust me. He's loyal.
I have this perfume.
One whiff,
and a man will do anything I ask.
Including telling the truth.
Look, now that Gabe is here
I'm afraid this is
where we part ways.
I have an army to build,
a war to plan.
And we really do not know
each other that well.
You understand?
No.
Maybe you can ask one of your plants.
I do not trust you.
I saved your life.
My men are on the way.
You trust him?
But I...
I thought we were friends?
Friends?
You're being serious.
Look, don't take this the wrong way,
but you are a bit of a freak.
Did she tell you not to trust me?
Yeah.
Why?
Smart girl.
Shall we begin?
The temple is some sort of maze,
is that it?
Everything is a maze, Bruce.
The only difference is whether
we realize our place within it.
Given enough time,
I will find a way out.
How much time?
How long have you been
blindly running down the corridors
of your life only to end up
in the same place?
It's time to pick a direction.
You can speak in cryptic riddles
all you want.
I'm not scared of you.
But you are scared of something,
aren't you?
Sit.
Let me show you
what I have to offer.
You have some nerve
showing up here.
We need to talk. Alone.
No. We don't.
You took my son from me.
And you took my father
away from me.
I'd say that makes us even.
Your father was killed
by a drunk driver.
No, he wasn't, driver wasn't drunk.
He hit us on purpose.
But I think you know that
because you paid for his lawyer.
Still think we have nothing
to talk about?
If you have a question for me,
son...
...why not go ahead and ask it.
Did you order the hit on my father?
No.
I respected your father.
Much more than the son
he left behind.
But someone did.
It was a hit?
Yes.
The Court of Owls.
What do you know about them?
I know my uncle is a member.
- Are you?
- No.
But we've built a partnership
which has been mutually
beneficial over the years.
You mean, you do their bidding.
Everyone does
The Court's bidding.
Some of us just know it.
The person who came to you...
...a member of The Court?
- Yes.
- Who was it?
Who ordered dead on my father?
I want a name.
Frank Gordon.
Your uncle.
Hello, Jim.
I thought we could use a drink.
Is it true?
Did you order the hit on my father?
Carmine called
The Court after you left.
You shouldn't have gone there.
It will raise suspicions.
Is it true?
Yes.
Why?
I already told you.
Your father was determined
to expose The Court
and became a risk.
- Simple as that.
- And so you had him killed?
Your own brother?
You wanna shoot me, Jim?
You'd be doing me a favor.
But it won't change anything.
The only thing we can do now
is finish what Peter started
and bring down The Court.
It's what he would have wanted.
What my father would have wanted
is for justice to be done.
And so do I.
Frank Gordon, you're under arrest
for the murder of Peter Gordon.
Turn around.
- Turn around!
- Have you not been listening?
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say
can and will be used
- against you in court of law.
- Arrest me and it's over.
- You have the right to an attorney.
- Stopping,
them is the only thing that matters.
My father mattered.
Dock 9C.
It's where the weapon
will be arriving.
It's all I've been able to find out.
I need to speak with The Court.
Try to buy some time.
You need to find out
when the weapon will be arriving,
and you need to do it
without The Court
finding out you're involved.
Otherwise,
we're both dead.
Make a choice, Jim.
I didn't think you had it in you.
I know.
You never did.
Is that what this is about?
No one gave you a gold star
for thuggery?
If you're gonna kill me,
then get on with it already.
I ain't gonna kill you.
We're gonna auction off
that right to the highest bidder.
We?
That would be my sales force.
- Hey.
- Bless you, buddy.
If he had just listened
to me but no.
Nobody listens to Ivy.
- That's a lot to take in.
- Tell me about it.
A secret organization
that controls all of Gotham?
If that's true, somebody should tell
them they're doing
a pretty terrible job.
He told you all of this at the cabin?
Most of it.
The weapon intended
to destroy the city,
that's a new wrinkle
he threw at me today.
Quite the family reunion
you're having.
I didn't mean to involve you
in all of these.
I just don't know
who to trust anymore.
The way I see it, as hard as it was
to hear what Falcone had to say.
At least, he confirmed
the existence of The Court.
So, I take my uncle at his word?
You work the lead.
Check the docks, but that's just me.
I tend to give apocalyptic warnings
of mass destruction
the benefit of the doubt.
But it wasn't my father
who was killed.
So, if you wanna go after your uncle
for what he did,
I got your back.
He says The Court has destroyed
the city twice before in its history.
- We can't take that chance.
- I'll call Judge Bam Bam.
Get a warrant.
We'll hit the dock and start kicking
- the doors today.
- No. He was very clear.
The Court can't know
I'm looking into this.
G.C.P.D. cannot be involved.
So, who do we know
who can raid the docks,
won't raise questions
and isn't connected to the G.C.P.D.?
No, no, no.
Feels a little light.
And you know...
...mummy's gonna need
a new pair of stilettos.
Capeesh?
Who's next?
Barbara Queen.
Jim?
What an unpleasant surprise.
Let me guess.
Do I hear a favor coming on?
I've been waiting a long time
for you to begin your journey.
The only journey
I'm going to take is back home.
Back to Gotham.
Then we share the same destination.
What are those?
Acupuncture needles?
Of a sort.
Think of them as keys.
A way to open the mind
through that which it locks away
even from itself.
What are the symbols on the ends?
You said you wanted
to return to Gotham.
Here we are.
Come on, Tom! It wasn't that bad.
No? Childish drivel.
I thought the acting was fine.
The music was lovely.
What about you, Bruce?
It's a... sorry, Mum,
I agree with Dad.
It was kind of lame.
"Kind of lame?" There's no such
word as "kind of."
- It was totally lame.
- Yeah.
Dad.
- Mom?
- Give me your money.
How did... how did you do that?
How did you do that?
What was that place?
- A memory.
- No.
No, it was real.
The mind can do far more
than recall memories.
If one knows how,
you can experience them,
relive them as if they were
happening for the first time.
You're saying we were inside my mind?
One is always inside
their own mind.
Pretending we are separate from it,
that is the falsehood.
How could you show me that?
How could you take me back there?
You've never left that alley, Bruce.
Not really.
And for you to be able to accept
what it is I have to teach,
you need to...
rest.
We'll try again soon.
Torture is fun.
However, I need to know
what is coming into Dock 9C.
I told you there is no Dock 9C.
- I can't tell you what I don't...
- What you don't know?
Yes, I've heard that one.
Now, tell me something
I haven't heard.
You don't know
what they're capable of.
Even when Don Falcone
was running things,
he never asked questions
about what came into 9C.
In case you haven't heard,
Don Falcone ain't running things,
baby.
Now, what is coming into Dock 9C?
Something already came in last week,
but they picked it up, okay?
The crate is still over there.
I swear, that's all I know. I swear!
So...
You must have a phone number
to alert them when things arrive?
What do you say
we give them a little call?
Because I would love an introduction.
Get them!
I swear I didn't tell them nothing.
Make sure you get him from all sides.
Potential bidders need to know
that he's alive and well.
Once we get these delivered,
the auction can begin.
Forgot these in the car.
Cannolis from Alberto's, boss.
Thank God. I'm starved.
Alberto's are my favorite.
They always put the cream...
Looks like you've got yourself
into quite the pickle.
You're sitting right next to me.
I think our fates
are somewhat intertwined.
No. I'll be fine.
What? What are you talking about?
Totally fine.
If you have a plan, tell me.
Tell me.
What? You want me to beg?
Is that it?
I want you to be nice to me.
- Nice to you?
- Yes! Is that too much to ask?
No.
No, it's not.
Okay. I'll be nice. I promise.
Now, what is your plan?
Lay it on me.
Watch and learn.
Canolli guy. Hey, quick question?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, with that...
If I had information, like,
really good information
that would get you a ton
more money for Penguin...
Would you let me go?
I don't know. Maybe. What is it?
I can't tell you in front of...
Let me whisper it in your ear.
Do you like my perfume?
You'll do anything I ask?
Super. Kill them all.
- Wait!
- Stop!
- Get his gun.
- Grab the gun!
- And give it to me.
- Give it to him!
- Now, tell him to untie us.
- Untie us!
- You don't have to yell.
- I'm sorry!
I just got so caught up
in the moment.
You know,
I like the idea of an auction, Gabe.
I think I'll auction you
off to myself.
Piece by bloody piece.
Carmine told us Jim came
to him asking questions
about his father's death.
What exactly does he know?
Only what Carmine knew.
That I gave the order
to have Peter killed.
Nothing can lead back to The Court.
After all these years, why would
he start looking into this now?
I don't know.
Believe me,
this is the last thing I wanted.
Which is why I'm here.
I know my nephew.
Jim won't stop until
one of us is dead.
Unfortunate.
He would have made a powerful ally
in what lies ahead.
In that case,
you know what you have to do.
James Gordon must be killed.
Barbara called.
What'd she say?
Apparently, Dock 9C
is being guarded
by a blade-wielding, psychopath
who almost killed them.
Of course, it is, did she find
out if anything's coming in?
That's the thing.
- It already has.
- I thought,
your uncle said the weapon wasn't
in the city yet.
He did. Which means either he's lying
or he didn't know.
Either way,
we have to assume
the Court already has it.
We still don't even know what it is.
We know one thing,
Barbara said the crate that she saw
was stamped with Indian Hill.
So, something from the freak factory
is gonna wipe out the city?
Gordon.
We need to talk.
Did you know the weapon is here?
What? No.
What the hell is going on, Frank?
We're running out of time.
I'm at my house.
Go alone, come quickly.
I trusted you, Gabe.
How did you repay that loyalty?
Betrayal.
Not for nothing.
But I was there after your mother
was killed when no one else was.
And how did you repay me?
By passing me over.
A valid point.
Perhaps we forget
that loyalty must be extended
before it can be returned.
Yeah.
You were loyal to me once, Gabe.
I wonder could you be again?
Yes, boss.
I'd swear an oath on my dead
mother's grave right now.
God rest her soul.
No need for anything so dramatic.
Ivy? Would you mind ensuring
that Gabe's oath of loyalty
is noble and true?
If what is, what now?
Make him smell your perfume.
Right. Okay.
Raise your right hand.
Do you swear to be loyal and true
to Penguin?
No.
I don't understand. Why not?
Why can't he be loyal?
Go ahead. Answer.
I never was.
I only followed you out of fear.
We all did.
Actually, I can live with that.
Fear and respect. Management 101.
No one ever respected you.
We always saw you
for what you really are.
A tiny freak
who used to hold an umbrella.
Nothing more.
A freak?
A freak.
Yes, I'll think I'm freaking, freak!
Thanks for coming.
The weapon The Court is planning
to use on Gotham...
Came from Indian Hill.
Any idea what it might be?
No.
Like I said, I had no idea
that it had already arrived.
It's clear that The Court
no longer trusts me.
Then why call me down here?
I'm supposed to kill you.
Which leaves us where?
That's up to you.
I need someone to replace me
on The Court.
Someone who can find out
what the weapon is
and how to stop it.
Someone I can trust.
You need to join
the Court of Owls, Jim.
It's the only way.
You just said they want me dead.
They still want you on The Court.
They just don't see now
how it's possible.
But I do.
At some point,
a woman named Kathryn
is going to call...
...to ask if you're dead.
And when she does...
I suggest you pick up.
And tell her what?
That you blame me
for your father's death.
I gave the order to have him killed,
and I deserved what I got.
What are you talking about?
You have his strength, Jim.
You can finish what he started.
For both of us.
He would have been so proud of you.
No!
Please.
Please, I'm sorry.
I'll do whatever you want.
Just, please don't make me
go back to her.
Give me your money!
No!
I have so much to teach you, Bruce.
But your pain,
it blocks you from
who I need you to become.
Who Gotham needs you to become.
If one's feelings and emotions
are strong enough,
their consequences can follow you
back into the real world.
I don't know what you want
from me.
Over the centuries,
we've tried to end the cycle
of crime and violence
that plagues Gotham,
only for it to start up again.
And do you know why it does?
People are afraid.
And fear breeds hopelessness.
I'm supposed to believe you care
about the people of Gotham?
I do.
Very much.
Which is where you come in.
Gotham needs something
I believe only you can provide.
What?
A protector, Bruce.
I can't protect Gotham.
Not by myself. No one can.
Perhaps.
But if you were to become a symbol.
A symbol against fear.
Then, Gotham can be reborn.
Okay. I admit it.
I might have lost my temper
there a little bit.
Sorry about that.
It's okay.
I don't know why I let him get to me.
Sticks and stones, right?
Words always hurt me
way more than sticks or stones.
Yeah, me too.
So, does this mean you're giving up
your plans for revenge?
I can't take on Nygma and Barbara,
and the rest of them by myself.
Who said anything about taking them
on by yourself?
Selina told me some
pretty crazy stories
about people
she met down in Indian Hill.
You said you wanna
build an army, right?
Well...
What about an army of freaks?
What kind of freaks?
Kathryn, I presume.
Detective Gordon.
I can't say I'm entirely surprised.
I killed my uncle.
I make no apologies for it.
We understand.
Good.
Then maybe it's time we meet.
Agreed.