Previously on Gotham...
I'm assuming the captaincy
of Gotham Central.
You just better hope you can
pay up when your bill's due.
And it will come due.
Let me know how I can help you.
Stop trying to be my father.
Master Bruce, I'm so sorry.
Alfred, you're fired!
This is your turf now.
You're the new leader of the Narrows.
I am in control!
You're in love with Lee Thompkins,
you pathetic loser.
Shut up!
- Where are they?
- That's powerful stuff!
It can get into DNA.
You're gonna remember me, Butch.
I'm sorry, I tried.
What the hell happened to me?
That was you.
You sent this monster in my city.
Heard you got the Pyg.
Turned out well.
You didn't even need me.
They... they believe in you.
Don't let them down.
Listen...
How can I help you, Captain Gordon?
I assure you,
this is a respectable establishment.
Relax, I'm not here to shut you down.
I'm looking for someone.
We are trusted for our discretion.
Was he here?
Who did he spend the night with?
He specifically requested
Tallulah and the peep.
That's him. That's Bullock.
If he comes back, please.
Tell him to call me.
It was an old Chinese guy's place
filled with rare drugs and stuff.
He's split town,
the place is empty now.
Where are the drugs?
You said there'd be drugs.
Holy crap.
What the...?
Don't touch it, dude.
You just woke it up.
Hey, Tiffany.
- Who's that stiff at the counter?
- New customer. Nice guy, polite.
Leave him alone, okay?
Hey, new guy.
- Do I know you?
- No, mate.
Most definitely not.
Not from around here?
And what gave you that idea?
Here, miss. Thank you very much.
Keep the change.
That stiff's shoes are worth
more than my car.
I understand times are tough.
I understand you need
to make a living.
Yeah.
But it's time to stop
punishing each other
for the situation
the city has put you in.
Instead of stealing from those
hurting as much as you,
this community needs to start
protecting one another.
- We do what we do to survive!
- Yeah.
And is that all you want? All of you?
Just to survive everyday
one day at a time?
Listen, Doc, down here,
it's every man for himself!
That's the way it's always been.
- That's right.
- It's like shit.
How many of you have kids?
I've been running a clinic down here
for the last nine months.
And I have been treating your kids
for things like TB, hepatitis,
ketosis, pneumonia,
diseases that don't belong
in a modern city.
There are no functioning
hospitals down here.
And the doctors
are too afraid to visit.
You're not stealing from the rich,
you're stealing from each other.
You are fighting each other.
And you are living in a prison
of your own construction.
Well, hello, beautiful.
What's your name?
Ivy.
My name was Ivy.
Well, Ivy...
what's a nice girl like you doing
in a place like this?
That's a hell of a thing.
Let's go.
Extraordinary.
Hey, Little Lord Fuddy-duddy.
It's Fauntleroy.
What?
Little Lord Fauntleroy,
by Frances Hodgson Burnett.
- A tad saccharine for my taste.
- Shut up.
Wallet, watch, jewelry.
Absolutely not, I mean,
you're a big man,
but you're out of shape.
And what?
You're three beers in already?
That's enough!
Get out of here.
Not who I was expecting to see here.
Likewise.
Is Bruce with you?
No.
What are you doing here?
It's not too bad down here really.
I'll make you rent
a lovely space for who?
Next to nothing if you put her around
and you're patient.
You live here?
Nearby.
It's a long story.
Give me the chance to prove to you
that I can turn the Narrows
into a place
where you don't have to steal
from one another to live.
Yes.
- Yeah!
- Yes!
Let's go. Come on. Go. Come on.
Go. Go. Go.
Come. Come on, come on.
Everyone, move away
from the building.
- There's your mummy. There.
- Mummy!
That's the last one,
building's clear.
- Thank you, sir.
- Oxygen.
- Please.
- Over here, over here.
Listen up!
We need to set up a parameter
and start interviewing witnesses.
Let's go.
Place him on it.
Appears like you turned around
the GCPD, Captain Gordon.
Gordon?
Quite a mess.
Thought you might need help.
Thank you, we need to find
the source of the blast.
Alfred, I do wanna talk to you
but I have to deal with this first.
- Oh, you have my number, call me.
- All right. Let's go.
I'll ask you one more time.
Why were you here?
There was a wine and cheese mixer.
Laugh all you want,
they were trying to kill you.
This is the Narrows, bud.
That's everyday around here.
Yeah, just another beautiful day
in the Narrows, Captain.
Gordon.
Get him out of here.
What you got?
Well, it seems like a piece of a toy
plane and yet, if I'm not mistaken,
it's covered in plastic
explosive residue.
There's also the remnants
of what seem like trigger wire.
Whoever built it,
takes pride in their work
and has considerable talent,
historical knowledge,
even look at the detail.
Pretty elaborate.
I can think of easier ways
to kill a room full of criminals
than with a toy plane.
Perhaps, it was intended
to fly to someone specific
and not destroy the whole room.
Like an assassination attempt.
If so who is the target?
Whoever this was needs
to be made an example of.
I mean, can't they tell
you were trying to help?
- Maybe it wasn't one of them.
- Oh, of course, it was.
I just think that maybe the best
thing for The Narrows
is to burn it to the ground,
start over.
Well, that would certainly suit
everyone, wouldn't this?
I'm just saying,
someone tried to blow you to bits
and I bet they're gonna try it again.
So I'm gonna find them.
And when I do, Grundy's gonna
pull them apart, limb by limb.
Isn't that right, big fella?
Hey, Grundy.
You okay?
Yeah, okay.
My name is Butch.
Butch Gilzean.
- There he is.
- Nice
That was so brave, sir.
It's Alfred, please.
It's the good stuff.
My manager hides it in his drawer.
Thank you.
On the house.
What you did out there...
running into a burning building.
Well, I wouldn't have done it.
No hard feelings?
No.
Good man.
Thanks.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
- What happened there?
- I fell. No big deal.
There are a few places in this city
that collect and sell antique toys,
but only this one
also manufactures its own.
- Can I help you, gentlemen?
- Yes.
We were wondering
if you recognize this plane.
One of yours?
- Where did you find it?
- Yours or not?
It's a pine and lead 1944
Mustang replica.
We have these, yes.
But it's been altered.
To carry a bomb, yeah.
How many people work here?
There's me and my father.
And where is he?
Upstairs.
Go get him.
Got a hunch you'd like to share?
No, just a bad feeling.
Of course, I'd happily be wrong.
Who buys these things?
Not sure any of it's for sale,
I don't see price tags on anything.
- Any word from Harvey?
- Not yet.
Think he'll return to the GCPD?
To be honest, I'm not sure.
- Gordon?
- Get down!
Seek and destroy, seek and destroy,
seek and destroy.
Seek and destroy, seek and destroy.
Seek and destroy. Seek and destroy.
You've got to be kidding me.
Wait, wait, no, no, wait, wait!
Let him go, let him go, please!
He's my father.
I can't let you hurt him.
I swear to God, I had no idea
what my father was up to.
There's a machine gun built
into the wooden hand
of this nutcracker here.
Excuse me if I find that hard
to believe.
I didn't know, okay?
My father, he hates to be disturbed.
He also built a bomb that almost
blew up a building this morning.
We need to know why.
Who is the target?
I don't know.
Has anyone suspicious been here
recently asking for specialty toys?
No, no one comes in here.
This is just his workshop.
He mostly works at nights.
He boxes the things
he makes and ships them.
What?
Look, three days ago,
I thought I heard him talking
to someone behind his door.
His voice was low like
he didn't want me to hear him.
Did you hear a name?
I heard my father repeat something
like he was confirming a name.
He said, "The Doc."
"The Doc?" Who's that?
I have no idea.
All right, can you deal with this?
I'm gonna talk to somebody
who might know who The Doc is.
This place is killing you.
The taxi is here.
- Okay, what's the time though?
- Maybe like five minutes is good.
- Okay.
- Come on. Let's go, let's go.
On freeway, the truck overturned
spilling its load of gasoline
into Gotham's Nature Park.
The GCPD is warning all citizens
to remain clear of the...
Causing gas to leak into the water
supply which then ignited,
setting fire
to the resident's kitchen,
which set off a twenty-four
acre blaze.
Wayne Enterprises can't...
Now, there's no reason to ever
be alone in this city again.
The Sirens Club is back
with a passion.
Ladies drink for free
whilst men don't.
You'll like it, it's nice.
I know you.
All of you.
And I'm pretty sure I hated you.
You're funny, Alfred.
I honestly haven't laughed
this much in a very long time.
Oh, I'm glad I'm able to amuse you,
Miss Gale.
Your accent, I love it.
Where are you from?
A charming place called Whitechapel.
In East End, London.
Go back often?
No. Sadly, no.
Well, perhaps you should.
Why did you leave?
Well, I was in the military.
I was very proud
of serving my country,
not so proud of some of the things
we had to do though.
And when I left, I found myself...
lost.
You know, it's a tough transition.
Then I met this man.
He changed my life.
Brought me to America, gave me a job.
And where is that man now?
He's dead.
And I miss him.
I miss him very much.
Is that your boyfriend?
Hey, you didn't call me back.
I was heading to the diner
to pick you up.
Oh, that wasn't necessary.
Alfred was kind enough
to walk me home.
Thank you, sir.
I'd hate to think of Tiff alone
on these streets after dark.
Drop the accent, son! I see the face!
It was your idea, was it?
Wear her hair down,
to cover the bruisy.
Oh, my, what a little tattletales
you've been.
What am I to do with her?
Stop it! Don't make things worse.
- I can handle this!
- Listen to me! Listen! Listen to me.
You stay away from him.
He's dangerous.
- Let me walk you home.
- I'll be fine.
Oh, Tiffany, what did I tell you
about talking to strange men?
It's time to go.
We have so much to discuss.
You be careful.
There was a fatality
at the bomb site.
Young man found at the room
below the impact site
and well, perhaps
I should just show you.
- Of course.
- Yeah.
The cause of death
was ingested poison.
See that discoloration
around the mouth?
The poison entered directly
into the bloodstream.
Yeah, but see that's not
what's unusual.
There seems to be something emanating
from within the victim's body.
The time of death
was several hours ago.
But this foreign organic
material's not only alive,
but growing.
- Seems like moss.
- Toxicodendron radicans.
Poison ivy.
It's microscopic at first
but multiplying, growing.
Living off the victim's dead tissue.
Fascinating.
So the commercial worked.
We're back and busier than ever.
Good. Because that's the last time
you're getting me on camera.
Who is that?
Who's who?
Selina, will you tell those brats
over there to keep it down?
Why me?
Because you're a partner now,
and also the one paying,
is a friend of yours.
One, three. Coming up.
Bruce.
What's up?
- Champagne?
- No.
Why? They don't guard you here.
And even if they did...
this is Gotham.
By "they" you mean me.
This is my place too.
- Really?
- Yeah.
So you wanna tell
your little brat pack here
to reel it in a little
or should I call your keeper?
Go ahead, call Alfred.
He won't answer.
- Why?
- Because I fired him.
And it's time to move on,
you know what I'm saying?
You sure about that?
- I'm not buying it.
- Not buying what?
This.
You.
Firing Alfred?
What are you trying to prove?
- No, I saw her first.
- The lady was speaking to me.
Hey.
Hey, hey.
Silly boys.
I'm really not sure
what got into them.
You should leave.
Well, that's awfully rude.
But you always were.
Who is that woman?
She seems to know you.
Who cares?
Redheads.
They're all crazy, am I right?
Ivy.
I like what you've done
with the place.
Thank you.
Though, it's hardly a challenge
after what that crazy bird
passed for as taste?
What brings you here, my love?
Actually, you know,
I'm so proud to say that
I seem to maintain a very good
relationship with all my exes.
- You...
- Leave me off that list.
What can I do you for, Jimmy?
The Doc. You know him?
The Doc.
I believe he was the target
of an assassination attempt
in The Narrows this morning.
Do you now?
And you wanna protect the Doc?
I wanna know who wanted
to kill him and why.
You know him or not?
Oh, I know the Doc.
Dangerous character.
Someone like that,
you might wanna shoot first,
then ask questions later.
Something you're good at.
- Where is he?
- With Ed Nygma. They're partners.
- Where?
- The Narrows. Place called Cherry's.
Careful, Jim.
Sometimes, we search for things
we don't wish to find.
Harper, what's up?
I'm at a murder scene at The Narrows.
I'm busy. Can you handle it?
You're gonna want to check this out
in person.
I have the suspect in custody,
Alfred Pennyworth.
Beaten to death. Local girl.
Garbage collectors found her
about an hour ago.
She lived with her boyfriend
who was at work all night.
He told us that him and Pennyworth
got into it earlier.
Says that he was trying to keep
him separate from his girlfriend.
Says that he made advances
towards the victim.
According to him,
Pennyworth got rough.
Rough? That doesn't sound like him.
Come on, you and I both have seen
Alfred lose his temper.
There's more.
This was found next to the body.
It's an SAS signet ring.
Impressions of it
on the victim's face.
My God.
Thanks.
Give us a minute.
Is this yours?
Yes, but I...
- You hit this girl?
- No.
How can you even ask that?
It was the boyfriend.
I mean, he beat her before.
Now he's gone and finally killed her.
- He says you were fighting with him.
- Because he beat her!
I swear, he's a liar.
All right, calm down.
You're in enough trouble as it is.
The last thing you need to do
is lose your temper.
Who was this girl to you?
She is a friend.
Just a friend.
- What? You just met her?
- Well, no.
You might find this hard to believe,
Gordon but we connected.
She was a beautiful, kind soul.
Her murderer's name is Rooney, right?
Gil Rooney.
He has an alibi.
I swear to God,
I'm gonna kill that son of a bitch.
Calm down.
Take a breath.
Go with Harper to the precinct.
Make a statement.
I'll find you later, yeah?
And you're gonna arrest
Rooney as well, yeah?
He will make a statement. Yes.
Cap.
We got a witness who saw Pennyworth
and her boyfriend getting into it.
She saw the whole thing.
All right,
take Alfred back to the precinct.
Come by after my last stop.
Okay. Where is he?
Damn it.
Tabitha.
Butch?
Oh, my God. It worked.
It hurt, I'll tell you that.
What happened to you?
- And who turned you into this thing?
- I don't remember much.
I remember Barbara
shooting me in the head.
Something in that swamp
brought me back.
I'm a monster.
I came here...
Butch, tell me.
I came here because the one thing
that is still very clear
in this thick head of mine
is my feelings for you.
I still love you, Tabby.
Okay.
Goodbye, Tabby.
Thank you for waiting.
It's worth it, you'll see.
Believe in her passion
and your champion shall be.
Bombs can't stop her,
nor bullets too,
because she's here to speak out
and fight for you.
Ready to battle, ready to rock!
People of the Narrows,
here's the Doc!
Doc! Doc! Doc!
This morning,
someone tried to kill me.
Maybe it was someone
from the outside,
maybe it was one of you.
No. No way.
You know what, I don't know
and I don't care.
But what I do know...
is that someone did not like
what I was saying.
Now, why would the idea
of a united Narrows scare people?
I'll tell you why.
Because a united Narrows
is a strong Narrows.
Yeah.
- And guess what?
- What?
- They should be scared.
- Yeah!
Magnificent, isn't she?
- It's been forever, right?
- I should bust you right now.
Oh, come on, Jim. Don't be grumpy.
Your ex has my full support.
She's really gonna change
things around here.
Someone hired Griffin Krank
to kill her this morning.
You really think
they won't do it again?
- Krank?
- A toymaker but also an assassin.
That is so Gotham.
Because together, we have
the power to change our lives.
Yeah! Right!
Imagine a hospital,
imagine schools...
Yes!
imagine these slums torn down.
Yeah!
Your children deserve better.
Your children deserve life!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
- Yeah, all right.
- Thank you.
Jim.
Doc.
I'd like to think of that
as a sign of respect,
not just a lack of imagination.
How long you've been back?
A while.
I wish you would have contacted me.
I've been busy.
I could see that.
You look great.
You look the same.
Are you here to arrest someone? Me?
I'm here because someone
wants you dead.
The assassin is still on the loose.
As is the person who hired him.
You're not safe.
It's Gotham. Is anyone ever safe?
So you're partners with Ed?
Why?
- I'm right here.
- Why not?
Wouldn't have been my first choice
but the universe has many ways.
Still here.
I'll see you around, Jim.
I'm gonna take a look around.
That's...
Oh, boy.
I've been trying to get to you.
You shouldn't be here,
you're a wanted man.
Better stay cool,
I mean, I got friends.
That's for Tiffany!
- And that's for me!
- Help me!
This man killed my girlfriend.
He's a maniac!
Oh, you're making this too easy.
I'll just tell the cops
this was self-defense.
Sorry, it took me so long.
I was in the John.
I liked you better
when you were making tea.
Harvey, what the bloody hell
are you doing here?
I work here.
Don't say it like that,
this place has history.
I love bartending.
It involves two
of my favorite things.
Drinking and ignoring people.
Who are these jokers?
He's a bloody murderer.
Then call a cop, I'm a bartender.
No, he is the murderer.
I have an alibi.
Oh, yeah?
Let me guess,
one of these guys is your alibi.
- What do you say now, pal?
- Oh, I'm not an alibi.
I'll call it in.
Hi, Kitty Cat.
You suck at following people,
by the way.
Ivy?
In the flesh.
Just different flesh.
What happened to you?
Something wonderful.
Can you feel that
coursing through your veins?
It's my essence.
Is your head swimming?
Your mouth drying up...
it lives within me now.
It's power.
Drink.
It'll counteract the toxin.
It took me a few trials but...
it'll work.
See?
You have to trust me.
- You've gone crazy.
- No.
I haven't.
I have been reborn.
And I will never be underestimated
or ignored ever again.
You always looked after me, Selina.
Now let me help you.
Let's make Gotham my bitch.
Please, don't hurt me.
Why would I do that?
You tried to kill me.
Yeah, because you paid me to.
What?
You paid me good money
to kill the Doc, used your alias.
The Riddler?
You want me to finish the job or not?
I came to you?
Paid in cash.
Said the Doc was holding you back.
She has to die or you can't be free.
- Oh, God.
- I put myself at great risk for you.
Cops came to my workshop.
I can't go back there.
- My son...
- Let go of him!
Get down, Ed!
What the hell were you thinking
going after him alone?
Well, clearly I wasn't thinking.
Damn it.
Did he say anything
about who hired him?
It was him. All him.
He was a lone wolf.
That's what he said.
He was... he was afraid of what Lee
was gonna do to the Narrows.
Are you sure? His son said
he was talking to somebody
on the phone about the Doc.
He said that he was calling
around trying to get support
but no one helped him,
so he went in alone.
Crazy, crazy loon.
He told you all that?
I see I'm not much of a threat.
I'm so lucky that you came out here.
I don't know what I would've done...
This is Captain Gordon.
I have a suspect down outside
Cherry's Place on State
Street the Narrows.
Send all available units.
Nice job, Ed. I guess.
I'm back.
Move.
Of all the beer halls in the city?
Who was that, that jerk killed?
A lady.
Very beautiful,
kind, nice lady.
Then I drink to her.
I heard the call on the radio.
Don't worry, we'll get him to talk.
How you've been?
Awesome.
I missed you.
Is that so?
Well, I haven't missed you.
I haven't missed begging you
not to do something
just to watch you go ahead
and do it anyway.
Haven't missed watching you
bang Falcone's daughter
while she uses you
to get rid of Penguin.
Something's eating at you, Jim.
I don't know what it is
but you're no good
at keeping secrets.
And you're not gonna feel clean
until you get it off your chest.
You didn't come down here
because you missed me as a cop.
You came here to confess.
You want me to be your priest,
well, sorry pal.
I'm not interested.
So hit the bricks.
Take that with you.