JIM: Previously on
Gotham...
Listen to the watch.
Its ticking
synchronizes with your heartbeat.
Stand up on the back of the chair.
So you could get him to do
anything you wanted?
I want you to find my sister.
Her condition? Some poison in her blood.
- I announce my candidacy for mayor.
- (CROWD CHEERING)
ALFRED: Hugo Strange made another you.
- He's gone.
- BRUCE: He cut his hair.
To look more like you.
SELINA: Does Alfred know you have his car?
Would you like to go for a ride?
JERVIS: The ticking, it synchronizes
with your heartbeat.
Deep down, you want to die, Jim.
Step off the ledge.
- Stop!
- (JERVIS GROANS)
You don't understand.
My... My brother will find out I'm here,
and he'll come for me.
Nothing will stop him.
This is the brother that
took you to Strange to try and fix you?
ALICE: What? NO.
Jervis kept me a prisoner most of my life,
and when I finally managed to escape,
I ran as far away from him as I could.
Mmm-hmm. And landed in Gotham.
It seemed like a good place to hide.
Until Strange found me
and locked me in Indian Hill.
I'll admit, not the best luck for you
or your future landlord.
That was an accident...
The infecting part
or the lighting him on fire part?
I'm not a monster!
But if you want to see one,
just wait until my brother comes for me.
You don 't know what he's capable of.
This isn't over.
For either of us.
It's perfect! (CHUCKLES)
Oh, my sister used to love
amusement parks.
The rides, the food,
the tents with amazing acts.
That's why I became a performer.
Are you a family man?
Yes.
I am a family man.
The day I lost her
was the saddest of my life.
The only thing that got me through,
that kept me sane,
was the hope of
one day being together again.
Reunited.
And if all goes well, that day is today.
Of course, a reunion like this
needs to be a private affair.
You understand.
(DINGS)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
It's Election Day in Gotham,
with former mayor Aubrey James
and former criminal kingpin
Oswald Cobblepot running toe to toe...
BUTCH: You should take care of it.
- Appreciate it. Thank you.
- To you too.
MAN: Butch. Your phone call.
COBBLEPOT: I must say,
you are looking quite the dapper fellow.
(CHUCKLES) I had to guess
on the jacket size. I hope it fits.
Perfectly.
I cannot thank you enough.
- It's just a suit.
- No.
No, if it weren't for you,
I would still be falling asleep
to the screams of the insane.
It becomes almost a white noise
after a while, doesn't it?
It does.
I do believe, Oswald,
Arkham has made us both stronger.
I couldn't agree more.
Which is why
I had our release certificates framed.
A reminder of past struggles
and new beginnings.
If I didn't know better,
I'd accuse you of being a sentimentalist.
Guilty.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
You all set, boss? Busy day today.
Who were those people
you were speaking with?
Don't worry about it.
Come now, Butch. Play nice.
We're all on the same team here. Right?
My team. (CHUCKLES)
Yeah. Sure.
Whatever you say.
You keep your nose out of my business.
Yeah. Sure.
Whatever you say.
(SIGHS)
BARNES: Why is it that every time
something hits the fan around here,
I inevitably find you at the center of it?
I was just working a job.
Her brother asked me to find her.
Yeah. You're some sort of Pl now?
Is that it?
- I'm whatever pays the bills.
- Great.
What do we know about this girl's blood?
Not much. She claims
infecting the landlord was an accident.
Have Thompkins draw some samples,
see if she can find out
what we're dealing with here.
And pick up the brother for questioning.
Any idea where we might find him?
No. But when I do, I'll let you know.
- We have some unfinished business.
- Not anymore.
This is an active investigation.
You go anywhere near him,
I'll have you arrested.
For what?
No law against
two private citizens having a chat.
I'll come by later to pick up my check.
I bet I'd make a kick-ass Pl.
Get out.
Have you had this condition since birth?
Tell me about it.
If a person comes into contact
with my blood, it changes them.
It affects every person differently.
My brother believes
it brings out a person's true nature.
Is your brother infected?
Is that why you're so terrified of him?
Jervis isn't infected.
He believes we're connected.
Two sides of the same coin.
My way is the blood, and his, the mind.
Hypnosis.
It goes way beyond that.
He preys on fear, anger, regret.
And if he gets in your mind...
You're doomed.
MAN ON PA: Vote for Oswald Cobblepot,
your next mayor of Gotham!
Cobblepot for mayor.
MAN ON PA: And make Gotham safe again!
- Vote for Oswald Cobblepot...
- (TRAFFIC SIGNAL TICKING)
your next mayor of Gotham!
JERVIS: You are so very tired of life,
aren't you?
(WATCH TICKING)
Do you hear my watch ticking?
(TICKING CONTINUES)
Hard road for you, Jim Gordon.
Listen closer.
You are so very tired of life, aren't you?
Now you can rest, Jim.
(HORN HONKING)
Hey, pal!
You got a death wish or something?
ALFRED: Right, yes. Well, will do.
Thank you very much.
Good-bye.
Well, that was
the impound yard from downtown.
It appears the Rolls
was towed only this morning, Master Bruce.
This doesn't make any sense.
Why would he leave?
Well, he cut his hair
to look more like you,
if that's even possible.
You think
he went to the city to pretend to be me?
Yeah, absolutely. Bloody yes.
So, where would he go?
Take in a show, do a little bit
of shopping, have a facial?
I mean, where do pain-resistant clones
of multibillionaire teenagers normally go?
- Alfred.
- Well, I don't know.
But the car was found at 11th and Dillon,
wasn't it?
That's in the Narrows.
So I suppose we should be thankful
there's anything left to tow.
What in the dickens was he doing
down there in the first place?
Selina.
11th and Dillon is near her apartment.
Sorry, again, for the way I acted
when you came by yesterday.
- Any word on your friend Ivy?
- No. (SCOFFS)
I even braved a beat-down from Sonny
to see if she was
growing magic mushrooms for him again.
- Magic what?
- Mushrooms.
Sonny Gilzean.
Pounded you to
within an inch of your life.
Yeah. Sonny. Right.
Well, this is it. Time to earn a living.
- You work here?
- No.
I rob here.
What?
(SIGHS) The Bang Bang Room
is a betting parlor.
Should be flush today
with the mayor's race.
Meet me around back in five minutes.
Selina.
MAN: Yes! (LAUGHS)
Pay UP!
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
Hey, that guy at the end of the bar
said you're buying the place a round.
- (CHUCKLES) What?
- Mmm-hmm.
Oh, and your morn sucks.
Or something.
Really?
Hey, wise guy! Here's your drink!
- (BLOWS LANDING)
- (MEN SHOUTING)
MAN 1: Get him off me!
MAN 2: That's enough!
(MEN SHOUTING)
(DOOR OPENS)
Who the hell are you?
Sorry. My first day.
Uh, can you help me find the cherries?
No?
Probably behind the bar. Right.
Uh, I'll go check.
Hey, Squirrel, what's the odds of
a person getting out of here in one piece?
Not good, boss.
- My beloved mother always believed in me.
- (CAMERAS CLICKING)
Even when I doubted myself, she held firm.
Seeing all of your bright faces reminds me
that there is nothing you cannot do
if you put your mind to it.
And when I am mayor, I believe...
No.
I know that together,
we will make Gotham safe again!
(CROWD CHEERING)
Excuse me.
Are you on the election board?
Yeah.
I work for Mr. Cobblepot.
He just wanted me
to confirm what Butch gave you.
May I? Thank you.
It's all there.
Thank you.
Follow him for the rest of the day.
Don't let him leave your sight.
BARBARA: Well, look who's back.
I saw you last night.
You didn't even say hi. Rude.
I need to find Jervis Tetch.
Oh, you mean "The Great Jervis Tetch,
Hypnotist Extraordinaire"?
You believe it actually
says that on his business card?
Number's been disconnected. Where is he?
I don't know. Magic shop, bunny farm.
Someplace where everyone wears top hats
and drinks tea? (CHUCKLES)
Barbara.
You know, I'm not sure
I like this new thing of you
storming in here
every time you need something.
It's almost like we're married.
Scary thought.
I need a favor.
Oh.
Then you must be monumentally screwed.
What happened? Did he hypnotize you?
Make you bark like a dog?
He's dangerous, Barbara.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Okay.
He came in here earlier.
Said he wanted to hire some muscle.
- Muscle?
- Yeah.
For some performance he's planning.
Said he needed them to have flair.
What'd you tell him?
It's Gotham, baby.
We've all got flair.
Thanks.
- (BARBARA LAUGHS)
- Always a help.
(LAUGHS)
(BELL DINGING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(LAUGHS)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
JERVIS: Excellent!
Deever and Dumfree, I presume.
The Terrible Tweeds.
Your reputation precedes you.
And you are?
Jervis Tetch.
I have a job
that might suit your particular skills.
My sister's been taken by the GCPD.
I need to get her back.
You want to break someone out of the GCPD?
Not "someone."
My sister.
I assumed men like yourselves
understood the bond of family.
What's in it for us?
Does he ever speak?
Regardless, if you'll do the courtesy
of listening to me, I think you'll find
- I can be quite persuasive.
- (WATCH TICKING)
BOOKIE: Place is packed to the gills.
It's running 2-to-1, for Penguin.
Mmm. Sounds like you're busy.
- Maybe I should go, huh?
- No.
This won't take long.
I hate people with sticky fingers.
Okay, wait. What do you...
What do you need? Huh?
Money? Information?
- I could be useful.
- Oh, you will be.
You'll send a message.
But maybe, I don't got to do this.
I mean, maybe you learned your lesson.
Yeah, totally. I...
(SNICKERS)
- You're screwing with me, aren't you?
- Yeah.
Do it.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
(GROANS)
Bruce?
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
- (BONES CRACK)
- (YELLS IN PAIN)
(GROANING)
(TOOL CLATTERS)
SELINA: Let's go.
And although some have criticized
Mr. Cobblepot for running a campaign
based largely on name-calling
- and fear-mongering...
- (KNOCK ON DOOR)
...his simple message
- of "make Gotham safe again" has...
- (TURNS OFF TV)
Can you believe
Penguin might win this thing?
This city's going to hell in a handbasket.
(GROANS)
You Okay?
Fine.
I assume you didn't come here
to ask about my health.
I need to speak with Alice Tetch.
- No.
- Five minutes, that's all I'm asking.
She's scheduled to
be moved to a facility upstate.
- I'm sure she'll have plenty of time then.
- This can't wait.
What's going on?
You can talk to me, son.
Her brother.
I had a run-in with him last night.
Think he may have done something to me.
Like what?
I don't know.
I'm having thoughts.
(SIGHS) Look,
you've caught some bad breaks.
Blackgate. Lee.
I don't know what happened
when you went to see her,
but I can take a pretty good guess.
But at some point, you're gonna have to
make peace with the decisions you've made.
And what if I can't?
Take it from me,
you don't want to wake up one day
and realize that 20 years has gone by.
(SIGHS) We're keeping Alice
in interrogation.
Five minutes.
SELINA: What was that back there?
- FIVE: What?
- You.
Remind me to give props to Alfred
on his training.
I did not think you had that in you.
Me neither.
You Okay?
You?
A little lightheaded.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Bruce.
- Oh... You need a hospital.
- No.
No hospitals.
- Are those scars?
- Nothing, they're nothing.
You're not Bruce.
- Selina, just...
- You're not Bruce.
- Just... Just listen...
- What the hell are you?
I won't hurt you. Just let me...
Just let me explain.
I assume you know Butch is paying
campaign officials to buy the election?
You don't approve? (CHUCKLES)
My dear Ed, this is Gotham.
This is how things are done.
And in theory, I support that.
But, Oswald, do you see
how these people are cheering for you?
- Yes, they do seem very excited.
- You can win this on your own.
Why risk it? There is no upside.
I want this, Ed. I want this
like I've never wanted anything.
I know.
- Which is why you need to call off Butch.
- (CAMERAS CLICKING)
Mr. Penguin?
Hello, there.
I wanted to thank you
for getting rid of all the monsters.
(CHUCKLES)
Do you see?
People look at me differently now.
For the first time in my life,
I feel wanted.
Nice doing business with you.
And how do you feel now?
I feel like I've misjudged someone
who was supposed to be my friend.
I am your friend.
I can't be bought,
but I can be stolen with a glance.
I'm worthless to one,
but priceless to two.
- What am I?
- I don't care.
I do not need a stupid riddle right now.
I know what I want.
I want to be mayor.
Stay out of it, Ed. I'm warning you.
I need to find your brother.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
You turn me in, and now you want my help?
I was hoping we could help each other.
He's still in your head, isn't he?
JIM: How do I stop it?
ALICE: I don't know.
Most of the time,
once the trance is broken, that's it.
You should've been fine
the moment you stepped off the ledge.
Then why is it still happening?
Jervis has tapped into something
you're struggling with.
Something a part of you
would do anything not to face.
Then give me something to fight this
until I find him.
There's usually a trigger
that brings on the hypnotic state.
What's the last thing you remember?
He pulled out his watch.
- Asked if I could hear it ticking.
- That's it, then.
His watch.
Anything resembling the ticking
will trigger the impulse.
He's made you a prisoner in your own skin.
He did it to you.
When we were kids.
At first, he did it to control me.
Keep me with him.
But then he started
putting other thoughts in my head.
Thoughts, um...
Thoughts a brother should never have.
That's why I wanted to kill him.
I won't go back to him.
Not ever.
(CIRCUS MUSIC PLAYING)
(MAN WHISTLES)
Yeah! (LAUGHS)
Everybody! Come on!
JERVIS ON PA: Ladies and gentlemen!
It is with great excitement
- that we welcome you to our show.
- (GASPS)
That's him. He's come for me.
Getting you out of here.
...to wrestling's most notorious family,
here to entertain and amaze!
The Terrible Tweeds.
Let the show begin!
(MAN YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
(WOMAN SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
Harvey, look out behind you!
(GRUNTING)
Hello, sis.
We both know you can't kill me.
Not until I remove
that nagging little impulse I planted.
Turn around, hands in the air.
(WATCH TICKING)
JIM: Alice, go.
Now.
- (TICKING CONTINUES)
- Good-bye, Mr. Gordon.
No!
I doubt I'll be seeing you again.
ALICE: Get off me! Let go! (SCREAMS)
Mr. Gordon!
SELINA: Ugh!
It really doesn't hurt?
No.
Whatever they did to me at Indian Hill,
I don't feel pain.
So, Why'd they make
a Bruce Wayne look-alike anyhow?
I don't know.
I didn't even know I looked like him
until a few days ago.
I went to his house thinking he might
have some answers about who I am.
He didn't.
So you ran off and pretended to be him.
Why?
- You'll laugh.
- I doubt it.
Neither of you has a sense of humor.
When you came to see him the other night,
I was watching from the hall.
I saw the way you looked at him.
No one's ever looked at me like that.
I wanted to know how it felt.
You should have your eyes checked.
I didn't look at him like anything.
All I mean is that
I've never had a friend.
I've never had anyone.
You have no idea what it's like
to spend your whole life alone.
You're actually better off.
People are overrated.
You don't believe that.
My mom left before I could ride a bike.
Never knew my dad.
I had two friends.
One ended up barbecued, and the other's
at the bottom of the river.
What about Bruce Wayne?
Forget about him.
He's even more screwed-up than you.
You're more normal than you think.
Hey. You're up.
What's going on?
Barnes told me
what happened during the attack.
Nothing happened.
I heard the tape
from the interrogation room with Alice.
- Listen to me.
- Whatever Jervis is doing to you...
You need to uncuff me.
I can't do that.
I don't know what I would do
if something happened to you.
You'd be fine.
Do you really believe that?
You seemed to have moved on okay.
Yes, I moved on, Jim.
What choice did I have?
I went through
the most painful period of my life alone.
I cried myself to sleep every night.
And like an idiot,
I would wake up thinking,
hoping, that the next day,
you would show up at my door.
But you never did.
Mario was there for me
when I needed someone.
He was there
as I tried to put myself back together.
But I'm the one who doesn't care?
After everything that's happened,
you really have nothing to say to me?
The past is the past.
There's nothing I can do to change that.
Alice told me that
her brother preys on anger and regret.
I really don't want that
to be all that's left of us.
You mean all that's left of me.
Barnes asked me
to put you on a 48-hour suicide watch.
I've already signed off on it.
I know that we can't change the past,
but there's a difference
between moving on and letting go.
(DOOR OPENS)
Most of you guys
have been with me for a while.
You know me.
And I know Gotham
like the back of my hand.
(LAUGHS)
Penguin, when he's mayor, boys,
I promise you,
we are gonna run this city. Huh?
MAN: To Butch!
ALL: To Butch!
- I...
- What?
I lost track of the guy in the glasses.
Nygma?
That skinny loon gave you the slip?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Yeah?
No.
No, no, that's not possible.
Let's go! We got to go, guys! Come on!
(DOOR CLOSES)
Two of your brothers are dead.
The other two
escaped with Alice and Jervis.
And I need to know
where they're taking her.
(SNIFFLES)
Jervis gains a sister
and you lose two brothers?
That don't seem too fair.
Hmm?
I bet you were close growing up, huh?
Rassling around the house,
driving your mom crazy.
Five little kids all dreaming of stardom.
Yeah, I'm a fan.
My dad used to always take me down
to the rassling matches at the Garden.
I also happen to know most luchadores
request to be buried in their masks
- as a sign of honor...
- (LIGHTER CLICKS OPEN)
- ...and respect.
- (GASPS)
I really, really hope
that wasn't the case with your brothers.
This freak Jervis
did something to my friend,
and I need him to undo it.
Where are they taking her?
Okay, okay, I'll tell you!
(BLOWING)
JERVIS: Well?
You like it?
I know you were
surprised to see me last night.
And I want you to know that I forgive you.
For everything.
But...
I want you to understand the consequences
if you ever leave me again.
I need you to understand
how important you are to me.
Don't. Please.
Now, you might feel a little prick.
(SCREAMING)
(VEHICLE STOPS)
(VEHICLE DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
Your escorts agreed to take a long lunch.
You know where they took Alice?
Yeah. But it's only a matter of time
until Barnes finds out
- and sends in the cavalry.
- (UNLOCKS HANDCUFFS)
How'd you find me?
Lee.
- Lee?
- Yeah.
She also told me
if you check out on my watch,
it's my head.
I guess you're gonna have to trust me.
Remember to chisel that into my tombstone.
Let's go.
Thanks, Francisco.
(DOOR OPENS)
- Took you long enough.
- Where's Selina?
She's not at her squat.
If you did anything...
- She's fine.
- Where is she?
She left a little while ago.
I don't know where she went.
I take you in
and this is the thanks I get?
You run around with Selina,
pretending to be me?
Is that why you're angry?
Because I was pretending to be you,
or that I spent the day with Selina?
For someone who has everything,
you have no idea what you actually want.
Or maybe
you're just too scared to take it.
At least I know who I am.
Cool your boots, Master Bruce.
Let's all just take a breath, shall we?
Don't worry.
You won't be seeing me anymore.
Neither will she.
I don't know why I was created,
but I know I don't belong in Gotham.
Say good-bye to Selina for me.
And thank her for the kiss.
What are you going to use that for?
Oh. I imagine I'll
mix it into some public drinking fountain.
Create a few dozen monsters. (CHUCKLES)
Please, Jervis. Please.
- I'll do whatever you want.
- You will now.
Because you know the price
other people will pay if you don't.
I don't know
what I would ever do if I lost you.
That connection.
It keeps me sane.
It always has.
- (GUN COCKS)
- JIM: Tetch?
- Jervis?
- (CHUCKLES)
- Don't move!
- (GUNS COCKING)
Mr. Gordon.
I can't say I'm entirely surprised.
So stubborn.
- Let her go now.
- You know I can't do that.
But, if you let me leave
with my dear sister,
my dear Alice...
Then I'll free you
from that nasty little impulse.
Maybe you can live a long, happy...
Well, a long life.
Let her go and you live. That's the deal.
One question.
(TICKING)
Do you hear that?
Jim!
(GUNFIRE)
JERVIS: We both know what you really want.
I saw it in your eyes
the first time we met.
You want to be free.
Free from the pain.
And you can be.
Stop fighting and let go.
JIM: The past is the past.
There's nothing I can do to change that.
DR. THOMPKINS: There's a difference
between moving on and letting go.
No!
- Well, well, Mr. Gordon breaks my spell!
- (GUNFIRE)
(JERVIS LAUGHS)
I daresay it's time
we bid this foul city our good-bye.
- No!
- Alice!
- I'll never go with you!
- Why do you say such things?
We belong together. You know that.
I love you.
- You're insane!
- No, no!
(SCREAMING)
- No!
'(THUD)
(SOBBING)
JERVIS: You killed her!
(SIRENS BLARING)
(INDISTINCT POLICE CHATTER)
You want to explain yourself?
I was following a lead.
You were following
some misguided notion about friendship.
James Gordon is
gonna get you killed one day,
- you get that?
- Maybe.
But until that day,
I will never turn my back on him.
REPORTER 1 ON TV: The night that
all of Gotham has been waiting for.
The final results
should be coming in shortly.
This is it.
The moment I've been waiting for.
- Indeed.
- BUTCH: You!
You! You ruined everything!
Butch, release him this instant!
What is going on?
Well, I'll tell you what's going on.
He just cost you the election.
He went to every district official
and took the money back.
Said you wanted to run a clean election.
Tell me this is not true.
I'm afraid Butch is right. For once.
(ED GROANS)
Why?
After everything I've done for you.
Everything we could've done together.
You betrayed me.
Butch!
- (GUN COCKS)
- (CROWD EXCLAIMS IN FEAR)
Give me one reason why I shouldn't
let Butch kill you where you stand.
- Well, there are about 30 witnesses...
- I don't care!
- (APPLAUSE ON TV)
- And there's that.
REPORTER 2: In what can only be viewed as
a seismic shift even by Gotham standards,
former underworld kingpin Oswald Cobblepot
has won the mayor's office by a landslide.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(SHUSHING)
...momentum based largely
on his outspoken criticism...
I still won.
They really want me as mayor.
Yes.
I can't be bought,
but I can be stolen with one glance.
I'm worthless to one,
but priceless to two.
Love.
(CHEERING AND APPLAUSE ON TV)
CROWD: (CHANTING) Cobblepot! Cobblepot!
They love me.
If you would've bought the election,
you would've never known.
And now you do.
Feels good, doesn't it?
How did you know I would win?
I believe in you, Oswald.
Even when you don't believe in yourself.
You.
You never believed
I could win this election on my own.
I think maybe
you're not cut out for this after all.
What?
You got to be kidding me. This guy...
Don't worry.
I still need someone to crack skulls.
(CHUCKLES) Come, Ed.
We have plans to make. (CHUCKLES)
(LAUGHS) Hmm.
You think we'll ever see him again?
Well, that I very much doubt,
Master Bruce.
I reckon he's gonna try and get as
far away from Gotham as he possibly can.
I still wonder why Hugo Strange made him.
Long lonely nights in the laboratory,
probably wanted someone to talk to.
Or some other nefarious reason.
Perhaps.
There is one thing.
Yes, Master Bruce?
Do you think Selina really kissed him?
Bloody hell.
I mean, you've had training
in interrogation, right?
- You can tell when someone's lying?
- I’m not gonna have this conversation.
And if she did kiss him,
do you think she thought he was me?
Good night, Master Bruce.
I bet she thought it was me.
DR. THOMPKINS: Hey.
Hey.
You're here late.
Tweeds really did a number on this place.
Guess I'm medical examiner/medic.
Slash resident therapist.
I wanted to thank you
for telling Bullock where to find me.
I heard about what happened with Alice.
You okay?
- Yeah.
- No.
I mean, are you okay?
Whatever Jervis did to me, it's over now.
I'm glad.
Guess I should get going.
Lee.
There's something I need to tell you.
Something I should have told you
the moment I saw you back in Gotham.
- Everything you said today...
- I'm sorry about that.
Don't... You were right.
And after
everything that happened today...
This is harder than I thought.
What is it, Jim?
I'm happy for you.
You are?
Trying to be.
Maybe we can start there?
Yeah.
I think we can do that.
Bruce Wayne?
- No.
- But you could be.
In fact, you could be so much more.
Who are you?
You might think of us as your parents.
We've been
looking for you for a long time.
(DOOR CLOSES)
It is with a humble heart
that I accept the trust placed in me
by this great city to become your mayor.
The people have spoken,
and I have heard their call.
MAN: Yeah!
WOMAN: That's right!
And as my first act as mayor,
I would like to introduce you
to my chief of staff,
Mr. Edward Nygma!
(CROWD CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
(DRIPPING)
(GASPS)
No.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
English - SDH