Previously on Gotham...
Where is Xander Wilde?
My God.
- There's two of them.
- I'm gonna drive you mad, brother.
All of Gotham
will be joining you too.
You shall become the Demon's Head.
She's got the mark
of the Demon's Head.
No woman has ever been allowed
to lead the League of Shadows.
The sisters of the league
are yours to command.
Tell me what I need to know.
I could've killed Jerome,
and I didn't.
Don't take so much responsibility
that you get yourself killed.
I came up with a plan
to turn this city into a madhouse.
Oh, we're gonna need
a lot more of this.
Thank you all for
coming this evening.
As your interim mayor, I know my
recent appointment was sudden
and perhaps a bit of a shock to some.
Quite frankly, I was shocked.
What is important
now is the future of this great city.
That is why I'm meeting
with all of you.
Well, mayor, as chairperson
of Gotham's Moral Authority Society
our members have been, quite frankly
unnerved by the recent
going-ons in our great city.
We have seen criminals take office
gunfights in our streets,
- corruption on a massive scale.
- Mrs. Haverstock, the Commissioner
and I have worked tirelessly these
past few weeks
to improve the way
this city conducts itself.
- Wyatt? Everything all right?
- We're looking into it now, sir.
Did a window blow open?
It's gotten so cold.
- What's happened?
- Don't come any closer!
Good evening, everyone.
What do you want with us?
Sorry, no time for questions,
Mr. Mayor.
You see, your presence
is urgently needed elsewhere.
Whatever you expect as ransom,
I will double it.
I have access
to the police pension fund.
That can be a lot of money.
Tempting, but...
no, thanks.
Bridgit, isn't It?
I can get you safe passage
from the city, money, a new home.
It was people like you that locked
me up in Strange's lab
and thanks to that,
there is no Bridgit anymore.
I can get you a pardon, son. All will
be forgiven, just stop this lunatic.
Lunatic is a little harsh.
I prefer visionary.
Oswald, can't you do something?
Afraid not.
I am with Mr. Valeska, 100 percent.
Every cop this city will be looking
for us, and when they find you
expect no mercy,
just a hail of bullets.
So serious.
That's why your
approval ratings are so low.
Hey, tell you what
try threatening me again,
but this time, try it with a smile.
Oh, see, this is what's wrong, nobody
knows how to have fun anymore, right?
But see our friend down there,
bag head?
He's figured out a way to solve that.
Please stop.
It's time to give this city
the boost it needs.
Time to stop taking
ourselves so seriously.
I mean, come on, Gotham,
what do you have to lose?
Except your sanity.
You gonna tell me why we need to
come to the garage, Alfred?
Happy birthday, Master Wayne.
- You remembered.
- Of course, I remembered.
I bloody love your birthdays.
Your seventh was an absolute blinder.
I remember you had
about 50 kids come out,
but you were off outside on your own.
You were obsessed by this one gift
that your dad gave you,
this bright red wagon.
You were in the garden all-day
collecting these rocks.
When I asked what you were
gonna do with these rocks you said.
"I'm gonna build a home for my wagon
a secret place that only
I know about."
- What's this?
- It's the reason
I brought you to the garage.
Master Bruce.
Alfred, I don't know what to say.
V8, five-liter,
460 horsepower engine.
Painted matte black anti-reflective.
Very difficult to see at night.
Oh, and of course this.
One hundred percent bulletproof.
Best be prepared?
Oh, mate.
Jim, hey. What gives?
The mayor and the police commissioner
have been kidnapped by Jerome.
I got every cop in the city
out there searching all
the spots Jerome's been
seen the last week.
You got something for me?
I was gonna say I
won a hundred bucks
and a scratch
in the lotto at the liquor store
and we could go to the track with it,
but we can do your thing first.
- Gordon.
-We need to talk.
- Oswald?
- I'm out back, come alone.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, this is a first.
Are you doing anything about Jerome?
We're looking for him.
Do you know where he is?
And if I did, do you think
I'd just tell you?
Have you march in there, guns
blazing? He needs to be stopped.
He has everyone under his thumb,
Freeze, Firefly, Hatter.
They are all part of his plan.
A dark, terrible plan.
Which is?
Scarecrow has made a gas for him.
- Like the fear toxin?
- Worse, much worse.
I saw it turn someone into a
maniacal, cackling, violent animal.
And what does he plan to do with it?
He's smart, he hasn't shared his
plans with anyone.
Instead, we all have a separate
task to perform.
Such as?
He has yet to give me my role.
Why'd you come if
you're not gonna help?
He scares the living hell
out of me, okay?
I mean, I was willing
to play along with him for a while.
Perhaps he had a way
to make us all rich,
a return to the
good old days, you know?
But nothing good will come of this.
Or maybe you just don't
like the competition.
Jerome casts quite the shadow.
Oh, please, he's a
maniac, an anarchist.
He is not interested in
money or power.
- And I am a honest criminal, Jim.
- Where is he? Where is the gas?
He only tells you what he needs to,
when he needs to.
- I just know he has to be stopped.
- Jim, hey.
Are you down here?
- Jim.
- Yeah.
Hey, a uni just spotted
Jerome near Paisley Square.
All right, let's go.
Hey, what happened to my mic?
Hey, buddy, beat it,
will you? I'm trying to work here.
Where's everyone going?
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are the Arkham Asylum Lunatics.
We came here to blow some minds!
Sorry to interrupt your little show.
But you are gonna love this next one.
Introducing Mayor Pritchard,
Commissioner Reynolds
Archbishop McGregor
and this lady, whoever she is.
This is everybody.
Everybody, say hi.
Now, as you can see, we're still
waiting for two guests of honor.
But in the meantime,
let's go over the rules of tonight's
entertainment, shall we?
Dynamite.
Trigger. I don't get what I want?
Boom. Headless people.
And if any of you are thinking
of going anywhere, you'll die too.
Now, the one man
who can get me what I want.
Come over here. Calling Gordon.
Calling Captain James Gordon.
I speak on behalf of myself
and all other gang
leaders in this city
when I say your arrogance
and disrespect
will no longer be tolerated.
You beat and then dragged
my brother from here like a dog.
Your brother's an ass.
He abuses our staff and refuses
to pay his exorbitant tab.
He is my brother,
and he demands your respect.
And I suppose an apology
would be out of the question.
Your blood will be his apology.
Thought so.
I could've handled them.
That's the advantage of having
your own personal army,
Tabs. You don't have to.
Isn't that right?
What's wrong?
Ra's al Ghul chose you,
no one else, to pass on his spirit.
We will serve you,
protect you, of course.
But surely,
you intend to continue his legacy
and not just remain here
in this place?
What does that mean?
Continue his legacy?
I like the sound of that.
As I told you
we have much more to show you.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
The hell was that?
Gentlemen, ladies
your assistance is urgently required.
Be careful.
These are very dangerous materials.
Oh, we're counting on it.
More laughing gas. We need to make.
- What?
- There's no time to waste.
We need it in bulk, you see.
Well. Well, how much of it
do you need?
This much.
Ladies and gentlemen,
as I live and breathe,
James Gordon is in the house.
I'm not talking to you until
I can get up there
and check on the wellbeing
of your hostages.
First of all, Jim, you're late.
Secondly, I think I'm the one
who should be making demands.
Don't you?
What you're doing is an act
of terror, Valeska.
Yeah, you scumbag.
Ask our mayor what this city's policy
is on negotiating with terrorists.
Terrorists?
Frankly, I'm offended. No, no, no!
That's close enough, Gordon.
And none of you go anywhere either.
Deadman's trigger.
If this falls out of my hand
for any reason and, bang!
I got two empty chairs here.
You haven't even asked me
who they're for yet.
All right, I'll bite.
Who are they for?
Come on, James, you're a detective.
Do some detecting.
Jeremiah, your brother.
- Bingo. That's one.
- And the other?
Well, the only
other irksome do-gooder
who's ever spoiled
my fun in this town.
Bruce Wayne.
No.
No?
You can take me.
I'll sit up there with one of
those things around my neck,
but I won't let you have him.
Well, I don't want you, Jim.
I want my brother.
And I want Bruce. I want them now.
All right, let me get these people
out of here. I'll come up there and...
You are not listening to me!
And that is forcing my hand.
Jerome.
No.
Bring me my brother.
Bring me Wayne.
Bring them now.
Happy birthday, dear Master B
Happy birthday to you
I'll get some plates.
You know, for a billionaire,
your security system is lame.
Miss Kyle.
- Thank you, Alfred.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- For what?
Visiting me on my birthday.
I actually,
didn't know it was your birthday.
I just happened to be strolling
in the neighborhood.
Either way, it's good to see you.
I knew it was an act.
What?
The brat.
And the drinking, the... the friends.
It was an act.
I think you're more sure
about that than me.
Master Bruce. We have visitors.
Bruce, we need your help.
What happened?
Don't you know it's rude
to keep a guy waiting?
Bring me my hostages, James.
My trigger finger is getting itchy.
The hostages he wants
are his brother.
And you.
What? You're having a laugh.
No bloody way.
I don't like it any more than you do,
but Bruce you have to trust me.
Lucius and I have a plan.
Okay, you know what?
I don't think you're taking me
seriously enough. Well, all right.
Let's see, eenie, meenie, minie, mo.
One of these people have got to go.
It was that guy. Oh, well.
Did you see what just happened?
He's a raving lunatic.
He can't be trusted.
- For once, I agree with Alfred.
- Bruce, listen to me.
With your help,
we can prevent more deaths.
What's the plan?
Jerome is using a shortwave radio
trigger with a Deadman's switch.
If we can cut the signal,
he can't activate the explosives.
This emits a powerful signal that
disables all radio waves close to it.
Once within a few feet of Jerome's
device, his trigger will be useless.
That will give us time
for the snipers to get
a clean shot on Jerome,
Firefly and the others.
I wear this,
give you time to take them out.
- Correct.
- Are you sure it's gonna work?
I'm positive.
99 percent positive.
What are we waiting for?
They need our help.
Good man.
Ra's owned this house
for as long as this city has existed.
He said he kept his secrets in here.
Ancient secrets.
None of us have ever seen
what's behind this door.
It remains locked
and there is no key.
Tried dynamite?
No need.
Our master chose you for a reason.
All my life
I have known
that I was meant for more.
That there was something deep
inside of me that I couldn't explain.
I'm home.
Sir, we got the target in sight.
No way in from below the stage.
- Four my men have found positions.
- Good. Stay low, hang tight.
No hair-triggers.
One missed shot meansadios, mayor.
Copy that.
Standing by.
I watch the news.
I know why you're here, Mr. Gordon.
You must be out of your mind
if you think I'd be led
like a lamb to slaughter.
I understand your concern,
but your brother doesn't bluff.
If we ignore his demands,
there's no telling what he'd do.
We can block
his remote's signal with this.
If you and Bruce can get within
a few feet of him,
it'll disable his remote.
He'll be a sitting duck.
Our snipers can take it from there.
For God's sake, Gordon.
You have to know what he wants.
To murder us both on live television.
Mr. Valeska, I'm Bruce Wayne.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Likewise. I wish
the circumstances were better.
May I ask what it is
you've been working on?
Yeah, it's a compact electrical
engine. It generates power.
Fascinating. How much power?
Just two could light up
every building south
of the Westward Bridge.
You have a brilliant mind.
We all hope we can soon be
rid of your brother
so you can carry out your work
free from fear.
I understand if you choose
not to help us today, but
I trust that Captain Gordon
and Mr. Fox will see that
no harm comes to me.
But even if it does
maybe, by facing Jerome
I can show the people of Gotham
that standing up to terror
is the only way
to take its power away.
Well, said.
Harvey?
Hey. Just got word that
Freeze and Scarecrow
broke into Wayne Industries' chemical
lab. Jerome's playing the long game
but we're not sure what it is
unless we get ahead of him.
The gas. Penguin told me
about a new Scarecrow toxin.
Head over to the lab,
we're on our way to the square.
They've got a weapon. Poison gas.
Okay, let's go.
Thank you.
You two.
Hey. Hey, buddy.
What happened? What's so funny?
No, no, no.
Hello.
Ma'am. Let me help you.
- What happened?
- They made us make it.
- Tons of it.
- Where is it?
It's gone, they took it.
Why are we waiting
Ready, ready, ready
Someone's gonna die
Well, look who decided to show up.
We were starting to get nervous
especially the mayor here.
My guest of honor.
Please, take your seats on stage.
Come on.
Don't be shy.
It's all right.
We don't have all day.
It's activated,
just let them get a little closer.
On my command.
My men have all targets in view.
Standing by.
Hi, brother.
Now.
Fire. All targets fire.
I had my guys take up
the best vantage points last night.
So they've been watching
your little SWAT team all day.
Now, Bruce, brother dear.
Get up on stage.
It's time to get
this party really started.
What are you doing here?
This is a restricted area.
Our cargo is too precious to waste.
Let me give you something
I like to keep
up my sleeve for times
just like these.
Oh, my God!
You can pilot
this contraption alone, sir?
Yes.
Then look into my eyes.
The kidnappings,
the concert in the square?
All to draw the biggest crowds, so we
can drop the laughing gas on them.
This is madness.
I thought you'd appreciate
the beauty of it all.
But Jerome was right.
You know he anticipated
your betrayal?
That's right. You went to Gordon.
Judas.
Tie him up, put him on the blimp.
Jerome wants him
to have a bird's-eye view.
This book tracks Ra's legacy
dating back nine centuries.
Did you know he not
only overthrew governments
but infiltrated royal families?
Ra's influenced history.
He was a cult leader
and he still has
them brainwashed.
And what about me, am I brainwashed?
There are things written here
that could change
the way we view the past forever.
Perhaps I am the one
to bring that change to light.
Look.
This book was compiled
by shamans and mystics
from all over Eastern Asia
and the Middle East.
Shamans and mystics?
Give me a break.
It contains formulas for potions
and incantations said to raise demons
curse our enemies
and contact the dead.
This isn't you.
The Barbara I know would've already
sold this junk to the highest bidder.
Junk? This is my destiny.
And being with me and Selina
at the club? That isn't?
You begged me to partner with you.
Can't you see who that is up there?
That is me and Ra's 400 years ago.
Oh, please,
it doesn't even look like you.
It looks exactly like me. It is me.
I have finally found my true purpose.
I'm not gonna let
your jealousy distract me.
Ladies, escort Ms. Galavan
to the street.
I'll show myself out.
Actually, I think it's time my loyal
servants taught you some manners.
Why don't you do it?
Because I am the one true heir
of an immortal god's ancient dynasty
and I don't dirty my fingers
with the likes of you anymore.
No parent will admit it,
but everyone's got their favorites.
Right, brother?
The one who cleans their room,
does their homework.
Doesn't try to kill everybody.
Little Mister Perfect here
yeah, he was that guy.
He got adopted by rich folks.
Went to the top schools,
then a top college.
Meanwhile, I got dragged through
the circus by my depressed,
alcoholic mother.
Forced to clean up
elephant dung every day.
Who cares?
Do you know how big
those things are, folks?
But I know something
that Mommy and Daddy
they never knew.
You're as crazy as I am.
It's in your DNA.
See
we got the same blood
running through us.
We are practically identical.
You are a killer!
It's your nature.
Stop trying to fight it.
Take your best shot.
Hey, what the hell happened?
Snipers are dead. Get up on the roof,
take as many as you can.
All right. A bunch of chemicals
are heading this way.
Scarecrow had the Wayne chemists
mix it up.
That's why he's been stalling.
He wants a big crowd.
He's gonna release
the laughing gas right here.
We need to evacuate the area!
Get these people out of here!
Do whatever you have to,
get them out of here.
Time to kill this maniac
once and for all.
That was so good.
I love you.
Hey, hey, look up in the sky.
Holy crap.
Excuse me, sir, could you help me?
No can do, sport.
Gotta get this rig into position
for the boss.
And where is that?
Paisley Square.
Almost there.
Then I can drop the load.
With this lever.
You turn this thing around,
right now!
Can you not see that.
Like I said, pal, no can do.
Keep coming.
Get into position.
Holy moly.
- Jim, are you seeing this?
- Yeah, get everyone out of here.
I'm going after Jerome.
- I can take it down with a shot.
- And risk spilling the chemicals?
Oh, yeah, right.
- Oswald?
- Jim, Jim, help me.
They knocked me out and now, I am
in some blimp with that horrible gas
and the pilot.
He's been hypnotized and I.
You're on the blimp?
Yes. Yes, you have to help me.
No, you're gonna help us.
You're near the river,
I need you to steer it over there.
Steer a blimp?
Are you out of your mind, Jim?
I don't even drive my own car.
You don't,
thousands will die, maybe worse.
What's worse than that?
How can you run an empire
in a city full of lunatics?
Hands up.
Beautiful, isn't she?
Just give me a second.
Gotta call the pilot,
tell him he's in position.
Yes?
- Not cool.
- Jerome?
Jerome? I'm in position.
It doesn't matter.
Too late anyway. Bombs away!
Funny.
- Go!
- Let's go.
Up, up, up.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
River. River, yeah, yeah,
we gotta reach the river.
Quite the dilemma, Jim.
You gonna let me fall and die?
Or are you gonna pull me up
and arrest me?
What's it gonna be?
Lawman? Or murderer?
Good old Gordon.
Always playing by the rules.
That's why I'll outlive you.
That's why I'm loved, because I don't
give a damn about the rules.
It's a long way down.
You sure you'll outlive me?
Oh, I'm sure,
because I'm more than a man.
I am an idea
a philosophy
and I will live on in the shadows
within Gotham's discontent.
I'll be seeing you soon.
Au revoir!
- Never thought I'd see this.
- Sure he is dead.
- He can't be.
- Is he?
Yeah.
Get back.
G.C.P.D. everybody get back.
Mr. Valeska
I meant what I said about your work
being of importance to this city.
Let Wayne Enterprises
fund your work with a grant.
Thank you.
Captain.
Oswald?
Hello.
Still here. Will someone please
get me the hell off of this thing?
All right, we're on it.
How do we get a blimp
down safely from over a river?
You asking me? I say we let him
stew up there for a few more hours.
We'll get ahold of the standby pilot,
have advise. Sit tight. All right?
And Oswald Cobblepot
- Gotham thanks you.
- Wait, Jim. Jim?
Jim? Jim?
Jim?
Jim!
Never touch me again.
Miss Kean has a new path
to take now.
- It no longer involves you.
- Is that so?
We will accept you leaving this city
and never coming back.
The only thing I'll accept
is you kissing my ass.
We are trained
by the League of Shadows
in 90 different forms of combat
since we were five-years-old.
Oh, yeah? Which one of you bitches
wants to go first?
Next time, we kill you.
Let me help you.
Who the hell are you guys?
The ones that have been watching you
and Barbara Kean, the imposter,
for quite some time.
We serve the one and only
true master, Ra's al Ghul.
But he's dead.
Death is only an illusion.
Hello, brother.
Didn't think you could get
rid of me so easily, did you?
See, my days were numbered.
But you
oh, you can continue on for me.
Be my ultimate revenge.
So calm yourself.
Don't fight it.
Breathe it in.
This gas is a special mixture
I had made, just for you.
Something to finally set you free.
It's time to have some fun.
Burn it down, brother.
Burn it all down.