Raise your hands, Mr. Gordon.
I'm sorry, Steve, they made me do it.
All right, be quiet, you.
Miss Zant, we're sorry
to interrupt your breakfast,
but if you'll come with us.
Quickly!
You may lower your hands
now, Mr. Gordon.
[man] Thanks.
[Gordon] Turn around.
Is there a problem, Officer?
We know you sold the RPG
that took out Haven.
-So?
-So, I want to know who bought it.
Or what?
You gonna arrest me?
Who said anything
about arresting you?
I want a name.
-What do you say, boys?
-[guns cocking]
Should we show this lawman
how we feel about uninvited guests?
Now,
who told you I sold that RPG?
[grunting]
[gun fires]
Eduardo?
Nice shot, right? [snickers]
[female Delta Force soldier]
Lower your weapon now.
Delta Force, stand down.
-What are you doing here?
-Come on.
The last time I saw you,
you were running through sniper fire
plucking my sorry ass
from a burning truck.
The least I could do is pay you back.
I had that guy right where
I wanted him.
I'm glad you're here.
Yeah, me, too.
We hated each other in boot.
-Jim disapproved of my ops tempo.
-[chuckles] Yeah.
Because you only had one speed.
Too fast.
Took me a while to realize he wasn't
afraid to get his hands dirty.
-Just being careful.
-Yeah.
Well, Jim's taught me a thing or two
-about being careful.
-[Gordon exhales]
So, what's the mission plan?
Well, we are the help
Secretary Walker promised.
Our goal is to make
this hell-hole safe again.
So it took the murder
of hundreds of innocent civilians
-to get the government to act.
-We're here to eliminate
all criminal threats.
We're gonna blanket the city
with flash sweeps.
And what about the people
that are still trapped here?
-They need relief now.
-Hey, I'm with you.
But my mandate's clear.
First we restore order,
then we take the next steps.
[Delta Force soldier] Sir.
We got something, sir.
Captain Gordon, this is my second.
Sergeant Angel Vallelunga.
Captain.
Ledger.
Our arms dealer
kept track of his buyers.
"Edward Nygma.
Two RPG."
Nygma.
Yeah, the name's on my list.
You think he's our bomber?
Only one way to find out. All right.
You and I will get Nygma.
Harvey, I need you to set up
a command center
with the soldiers at GCPD.
-I'll grab some guys.
-Yeah.
Hey, look. Hey, Jim.
I'm not as fast as I used to be,
but I still got some fight in me.
I'm not a desk jockey,
I'm a street guy.
What you are
is the best cop that I know.
We're going after Nygma,
he's ten steps ahead.
If things goes sideways,
you're gonna have to take over.
I need your help, buddy.
I got it.
Alfred.
There you are, Master Bruce.
There's been a break
in the Haven bombing.
Seems that Gordon and Bullock have
got a rather strong lead, apparently.
-What's the matter with you?
-I can't find Selina.
I looked all over the Green Zone.
Somehow I think Miss Kyle
is perfectly capable
of looking after herself,
Master Bruce.
Except that she's not herself.
You saw what she did to Jeremiah.
Yes, I did.
Listen, come here.
Jeremiah Valeska deserved to die.
Jeremiah made Selina a murderer,
just like Ra's made me a murderer.
Ra's goaded you into stabbing him,
Master Bruce.
He used you as an instrument.
You're no murderer.
But Selina is.
You're not the same.
She did what she did with open eyes
and you got to learn
to respect that, son.
You're wrong about her, Alfred.
And I'm gonna go find her.
[scoffs]
[Nygma over recording]
It's Monday. 5:32 p.m.
I'm standing in a dumpster.
My head hurts.
[tape whirs]
It's happened again.
It's Saturday, 12:16 a.m.
My fingernails are full of dirt.
Have I been digging?
[tape whirs]
I think it's Sunday.
I can't find my watch,
but it's dark outside.
My feet are wet.
There's mud everywhere.
God, it doesn't make sense!
You're not a murderer, Ed!
Except Kristin Kringle.
And Officer Dougherty.
But all those people...
and children.
How could you do it?
Why?
[breathing heavily]
It doesn't matter why.
What matters
is that it was you
who killed them.
Not me!
[door slams]
[Gordon] Edward Nygma,
you're under arrest
for the attack at Haven,
and the murder
of hundreds of innocent people.
No.
No, Jim, I can explain.
Explain?
You son of a bitch.
You actually did it.
-On your knees, now!
-No, I didn't.
I can prove it. I just... I need...
I need a little bit of time.
-Say the word, Jim.
-[Gordon cocks gun]
You know me, Jim.
The people that I have hurt...
They hurt me first.
I didn't know a single person
in Haven.
I'm innocent.
It's your call, buddy.
He basically confessed.
We bring him in.
He stands trial.
Yeah, I don't think so.
[beeping]
Your friend is standing
on a pressure-plated IED.
One of several throughout the rooms.
Twitch...
and you'll repaint the room
with your organs.
Don't do it, Jim.
This little doohickey
monitors my heartbeat.
It increases by ten...
Boom. Decreases by ten... Boom.
[Gordon] You try to walk out of here
and a Special Forces sniper
will put a bullet in your head.
No, they won't.
This thing can detonate his bomb
from a mile away.
Or am I bluffing?
Once word gets out
that you're responsible for Haven,
you'll have a target on your back.
I'll take my chances.
-I think he's bluffing.
-No, no. He doesn't bluff.
I don't want anyone here
if this thing detonates.
You heard the man!
Tell Sergeant Vallelunga
-to stand down.
-Yes, sir.
Nygma walks.
A wristband that monitors
his heart rate.
Welcome to Gotham.
So what do we do?
Well, the way I see it,
now we're all tied up.
I just got to save
your life one more time
and I'm back in the lead.
Funny. Seriously,
what the hell we're gonna do?
Well, he pulled a book,
set the booby trap.
I think I can make it.
Assuming the vibrations
don't trigger the IED, what then?
Then we just got to figure out what
sort of puzzle he wants us to solve.
Puzzle?
There's always a puzzle with Nygma.
You ready?
[beeping continues]
[gasps]
[panting]
"Chess Strategy.
Knight Moves Nimbly in the Dark."
I'm gonna ring this nerd's neck.
In chess...
Knights move in an "L."
Two spaces straight
and one at a 90-degree angle.
"Butterfly Collecting
with Conviction."
Or...
"Chess Strategy.
The Knight's Gambit:
Escaping Checkmate."
[beep]
-You okay?
-You left the Army for this city?
It grows on you.
-[cell phone beeps]
-Harvey, come in.
[Harvey]Jim, you nab Nygma?
No. Put the word out.
Nygma's wanted for murder
and the attack on Haven.
[guns firing]
[Bruce] I'm looking for Selina.
[Barbara] Follow me.
Everybody, raise your glasses.
To the killer of Jeremiah Valeska.
[all cheering]
[all chanting] The freak is dead!
The freak is dead! The freak is dead!
[man on radio]Citizens of Gotham,
this is a special bulletin
from the police department.
We have identified the person
who fired a rocket-propelled grenade
that decimated Haven.
Be on the lookout for
a tall, skinny man
who goes by the name of Ed Nygma.
He was last seen wearing a green suit
and eyeglasses.
Ed Nygma.
-The monster of Haven.
-[booing]
Let's go get him.
-Yeah!
-Let's kill him!
-Kill him!
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
Excellent.
[snaps fingers]
Two hundred bullets, as promised.
Go have fun.
And there's more where that came from
if you keep up the good work.
Off you go.
[panting] Mr. Cobblepot, sir.
-It's--
-What? What?
"Edward Nygma is the monster resp...
responsible for killing
the innocents at Haven."
Ed, what have you done?
I saw him go that way.
-He's over there.
-[others] Get him. Come on.
Take him out!
[mob clamoring]
[Angel] Bane 01, this is Bird 02.
What's your status, Angel?
We cleared 13th to 36th Street,
west of Broadway.
Gonna keep pushing uptown.
It's progress.
But still no Nygma.
My boys will scoop him up
by nightfall.
Now, tell me about this Scarecrow.
Well, he has chemical weapons.
Your guys would need gas masks.
Taking him down would be a big win.
Well, that's why we're here.
[dog barking in distance]
Psst. Hey.
[exhales]
Time to wake up.
[gasping]
Who are you?
I'm the woman who's going
to carry out your execution.
[boys whoop]
[gasping]
[boys whooping]
-[boys whooping]
-[laughing]
[groaning]
That's just a taste.
It's only fair
you die slow and painful.
To pay for JoJo.
Who's JoJo?
JoJo was in Haven
when you blew it up.
[chortling]
This is a joke, right?
Three hundred people died in Haven.
[scoffs]
-We don't care about people.
-[man] Yeah.
[laughter]
[breathing heavily]
Look at how happy JoJo was.
[voice breaking]
He always had a smile on his face.
You anthropomorphizing nincompoop.
Dogs can't smile.
-[engine revving]
-[Nygma groaning]
[boys whooping] Yeah!
[laughs]
[groaning]
I'm going to fix you, Ed.
-[panting]
-[engine revving]
What the hell?
Floor it!
[screaming]
[both whooping]
Yeah!
[boys whooping]
I'm going to fix you, Ed.
[gasping]
[engine sputters]
Did I say stop?
-Sorry, Ma.
-Ma, can't we just beat him to death?
[pants]
[engine sputtering]
-[boy] It's not starting.
-Yes.
Anything but electrocution.
-Come on. Come on.
-Please don't let me die this way.
Oh, thank God, the fuel line's clogged.
[Nygma panting]
Unclog the line.
-[metal clatters]
-[boy laughs] Come on.
[breathing heavily]
-Please, shoot me.
-[whimpers]
Stab me. Anything but another jolt.
Hit it!
Oh, no!
[whimpering]
[woman screaming]
[woman] Help him! Put it out!
Oh, my Lord!
Help him! Help him!
[straining]
Who's gonna fix you, Oswald?
[henchman] The Army's invading the city.
Locking everyone up.
They're coming this way.
[Penguin] Please.
An invasion is tanks.
Infantry. These are scouts.
-What about Nygma?
-Nobody's seen him,
but we've got feelers out.
Well, you tell your feelers
that the first man to bring me Nygma
is the one who gets to live!
Now!
[Penguin sighs loudly]
I am surrounded by morons, Edward.
If I didn't have an empire to run,
I would go get Nygma myself.
[chuckles]
[gasping]
[gasps]
Hello, Oswald.
We have a great deal to talk about.
But first...
did you name your dog after me?
[Harvey] Jim.
Harper just radioed. She saw Nygma
going into City Hall.
He's going to Penguin.
Cobblepot's at the top
of my list from Walker.
Sounds like a two-fer.
Penguin's sitting on all the ammo
in Gotham.
He's better defended,
better manned than anyone else.
We need shock and awe.
Shock and awe is my default.
You ready?
You know what?
Take Harvey on this one.
I'll keep things locked down here.
Let's saddle up.
[music playing]
Man, you're killing my buzz.
[Bruce] Selina.
I know you, and this isn't you.
-You know me?
-Yes.
Maybe better than you know yourself.
Let me tell you something.
That night
that your parents were murdered,
I was in that alley
on the fire escape.
And I watched that guy
shoot your father
and shoot your mother.
And through it all,
I did...
nothing.
[chuckles]
I didn't call for help. I didn't...
[sobbing]
I didn't scream for the guy to stop.
It wasn't your fault.
You were just a scared kid.
No.
You were the scared kid.
We are not the same, Bruce.
I didn't do anything
because I wasn't willing
to risk my neck for someone else
because I didn't care.
That's who I was,
and that's who I am.
[rock music playing]
I love this song.
What did you do to me?
Oswald?
What are you talking about?
Oh, please.
You did something to me.
You...
You are the reason
I killed those people.
How could you?
You have made me into
some murderous puppet.
For weeks, I've been
waking up in strange places
not knowing how I got there
or what I did.
Driving myself mad,
thinking I had gone mad.
And now I know
that it was all your doing.
Of everything that you
have put me through...
this... this is the most cruel.
Ed...
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I did not make you do anything.
Then what is, "I'll fix you."
What did that mean?
You didn't fix me. You broke me.
Wait! No...
I said that to you
the night the bridges blew.
You think I wouldn't remember.
No, Ed, I saved your life. That's it.
[laughs nervously]
-What are you talking about?
-[sighs]
You had been stabbed, I paid
Hugo Strange to save your life.
[snaps fingers] I bet he did something
to you when he was patching you up.
You paid Hugo Strange to save me?
Why?
What was I supposed to do,
let you die?
After Butch, you were my only friend.
You shot Butch.
Which is why I needed you!
[frustrated grunt]
[exhales]
Edward Nygma,
if I wanted you to suffer,
I would never do it in
some backhanded way.
If you and I
are ever at odds again,
you will know without a doubt
that I am your enemy.
I promise you that.
As a friend.
[grunts]
[breathing heavily]
What a mess.
I might have killed you, Oswald.
And if that day comes...
I swear to you,
I will stare you in the eye
as I stab you in the heart.
[snickers]
Look on the bright side.
If Hugo Strange did do
something to you,
it means you are
not responsible for Haven.
-Where is he?
-[rumbling]
Sir, the GCPD and the Army
have blown the gates.
Stay here, you'll be safe.
Grab Nygma. They want him, not me.
He's gone.
Damn it!
[grunts]
[beeping]
[guns cocking]
[laughs]
Why, hello, Harvey. [chuckles]
Now, last time we were in a standoff,
you ran out of bullets.
[chortles]
I hope you're better prepared.
We don't want to take
your territory, Oswald.
But you have to put down your weapons
and hand over Ed Nygma.
Or...
If you and your friends aren't
out by the time I count to three,
I will mow you all down!
We good?
Yup.
Go ahead, count.
[chuckles]
Harvey, you're not thinking clearly.
Maybe call your boss.
See what he thinks.
[Harvey] I don't have to call anyone.
Go ahead, count.
-One...
-[silenced gunshots]
[Penguin gasps]
How's that for better prepared?
Where's Ed Nygma?
The whole of Gotham
is looking for you.
I need information. Your specialty.
I am going to cut your face
into a jigsaw puzzle
and watch you try
and put it back together again.
[stammers] Barbara!
Am I dumb?
In all the years of plotting
and the betrayals between us,
have you ever, ever known me
to do something as idiotically brutal
as shoot a rocket into
a building full of innocent people?
I did not kill those people in Haven.
Not exactly.
There's more going on here.
I'm waiting.
The night the bridges fell,
I was hurt.
Oswald took me to Hugo Strange.
And he did something to my brain.
And that's your excuse for
murdering hundreds of people?
I'm saying,
that Strange or somebody
can control me.
They killed those people.
Okay, let's say by some miracle
I believe you.
Why the hell should I help you?
Because who's working with Strange?
Who would force me
to kill all of those people?
Information is your lifeblood.
You help me,
and I will give you
the best intel you've ever had.
I don't know where Strange is.
But I can tell you
where you'll find his Igors.
[grunts]
[Eduardo] Where is Edward Nygma?
You're protecting a mass murderer.
Don't look to me for sympathy.
Fine.
But not with that meathead around.
[Penguin breathing heavily]
[Penguin laughing]
You know, they say you can
judge a man by his friends.
This from a man who has no friends?
[people clamoring in distance]
Talk.
Nygma's a patsy.
He is not a mass murderer.
Puzzles, games...
Perhaps the odd killing
here and there.
But hundreds of people? No.
That's not him, you know this.
So, who set him up?
[chuckles]
Jim, you want information,
I want to go home.
Eduardo is not gonna go for that.
Oh, I'm sorry,
I thought you were in charge.
Even if I were to let you go,
sooner or later
the Army's gonna come for you.
Things are changing in Gotham.
I'll take my chances.
Now, do you want Nygma or not?
I know where Nygma's going.
And I trust you know
what you're doing.
We do what we have to do, right?
Gentlemen. Come in, you're late.
The last body you procured for me
was gangrenous.
Completely unsuitable.
Oh, my.
Bye.
Hello, Professor.
[laughing] Mr. Nygma.
Let's skip the part where you deny
making me into a killing machine.
Tell me...
how you took control of my alter ego.
I don't follow.
You did something to access
the Ed Nygma side of my personality.
But you're Ed Nygma.
I'm also the Riddler!
Tell me what you did.
Why did you make me kill
all those people in Haven?
You did that?
How interesting.
I had no idea.
Do you really expect me
to believe that?
Mr. Nygma, I don't know
anything about your alter egos.
But I will confess that when I was
sewing up your knife wound,
I may have tinkered a little
with your brain matter.
-Would you just--
-I put a chip in your brain.
It allows you to be able
to be controlled remotely.
I knew it.
But I don't control you.
I gave control to others.
Who?
I will write it down.
That way, if I'm ever confronted,
I can honestly say
that I never told you.
[exhales]
Not to worry, you're experiencing
a simple neural cutout.
I am mystified as to how you've
become aware you're being controlled.
I suppose we're just going
to have to open you up
and take a look under the hood.
Won't we?
-Jim?
-I'm sorry, kid, it's just me.
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm just, uh... Just looking
for Jim. It's nothing.
I saw soldiers downstairs.
Yeah, the Army's finally
gotten off their asses
and decided to help.
Jim's out with them now.
Are you sure you're all right?
I don't know.
I see people losing
their will to do good.
People I love.
What if we don't make it out of this?
I'm not gonna lie, kid.
These past few months,
I've wondered the same thing.
And when I don't know
what to do, I come up here
and I dig into these case files.
Sit my ass down and I get to work.
I used to hate
this kind of paperwork.
Now, it's the only thing
that keeps me going.
-Why?
-Because the little things matter.
Act by act. Deed by deed.
It means something.
Even if no one notices or cares.
-Thanks, Harvey.
-You're welcome, kid.
If you really wanna do
an old man a favor,
you could scrounge me up
a cup of joe, because I, uh...
Kid's fast.
[device whirring]
I apologize for the discomfort.
The neural cutout
inhibits muscular function,
but not pain receptors.
A simple reboot of the chip
should be all that is required.
Although, the sound may be,
uh, somewhat unpleasant.
Not to mention the smell.
[Edward whining]
[panting]
[Edward growling]
Edward, I believe the time has come
for a change of scenery.
-[staple gun clicking]
-It seems a powerful electrical charge
overloaded your chip,
but I've gotten everything updated.
I will pass the good news
along to your handler.
[gun cocks]
[Gordon] Care to expand on that?
I was merely helping a man
who needed medical attention.
Yeah, I'm not buying it.
His eyes are open.
I gave him a bio-medical anesthesia.
Wake him up. Now.
-Do it.
-Oh, very well.
[screams]
I told you this wasn't me.
He put a chip in my brain.
And someone's been controlling it
this whole time.
And then he drilled in my head.
-[Gordon] Better talk now.
-I am a scientist.
A contract came along.
I developed a tool.
A tool? How dare you?
A contract from who?
[beeps]
Please escort the professor out.
Thank you.
Ta-ta.
What the hell is going on?
Sorry, pal, but this part of the op,
it's need-to-know.
Couldn't say anything until
we had the suspect in custody,
but Walker wants Ed Nygma
taken out now.
Walker was behind this?
She's been controlling Nygma
the whole time?
[Eduardo chuckles]
You know I hate this spook crap.
I don't ask questions,
I follow orders.
She's responsible for Haven?
-I don't understand, why--
-Jim, stop right there.
Trust me.
Walker wants you
to put a bullet in his brain.
No.
Call it proof of loyalty.
It's what she needs from you
before she can move forward
with the final relief plan.
Come on.
Look at him.
He's a loon, a cop killer.
Tell me the truth.
Did Walker destroy Haven?
Did you know? Tell me!
Jim, ours is not to reason why
and this is your chance
to be a part of this mission.
So, please.
You pull the trigger on him
or I pull the trigger on you.
After all this, you'd kill me
for some bureaucrat?
Mission comes first.
You taught me that.
What's your answer?
Looks like I saved your life
one too many times.
Maybe so.
[grunting]
[beeps]
You know Jim Gordon,
you know this city.
Find him and kill him.
[hammer thudding]
[gasps]
Boss, wake up.
-Wake up.
-Ouch.
Ooh! Stitches still sore, huh?
Never would have happened
if you wore that armor I'd prepared.
That bullet is
making you sentimental.
Give her a shake, huh?
Huh.
Better?
I told you I had to let Selina
thrust the knife into my flesh
at least once.
Verisimilitude trumps precaution,
you see.
I get it. Selina Kyle and Bruce Wayne
-needed to think you were dead, boss.
-Yeah.
-Wait!
-[gasps]
I take it you have news.
All systems go.
-Well, then lead the way.
-[gasps]
Doctor?
I'm hearing good things.
The bandages are ready to come off.
Your assistant thought
you'd like to see the results.
Indeed I would.
[laughs]
Oh, you two look beautiful.
Ah...
I love family reunions, don't you?