Previously onGotham...
Welcome home, Bruce.
The Court is readying a weapon
that can destroy the city.
You've done it.
You weaponized the virus.
We have to escape.
In what way that's gonna happen?
- We work together.
- So that we may be free
to murder each other outside.
How do you expect to win, Oswald?
I have an army of Hugo Strange's
monsters in my command.
- Selina, stop.
- He's not Bruce.
Where is Bruce?
Bruce is serving
a greater purpose.
We found another owl.
We take this map indicates
secret hideouts of the court.
James Gordon, you loved him,
and that love doomed Mario.
But guess who's really to blame.
I am.
We will destroy
the Court of Owls
and then you will do
whatever I say.
- Won't you?
- Yes.
The virus sample we got
from Hugo Strange, it's gone.
- Maybe Lucius took it?
- No. Lee has it too.
The day of judgment
has come to Gotham
and to the Court of Owls.
Three years ago,
a great crime was committed.
Thomas and Martha Wayne
were murdered.
Their blood is on the Court's
hands.
On your hands.
Thomas Wayne stood
against the court.
He threatened to expose us.
He paid the price.
And my mother?
She had to die as well.
Why is Bruce Wayne here?
He has come to pass judgment.
Enough of this.
You are the leader of the Court.
No, one disputes that.
But you absent yourself
from Gotham for years at a time.
Decisions had to be made.
The Ruling Council stands
by its actions.
They were your parents, Bruce.
You knelt in their blood
that night in the alley.
Let blood avenge blood.
Give the order.
You hesitated.
Next time, I won't.
I promise.
No.
I know you won't.
- Keep me informed.
- Bullock.
Any word from Bruce?
Alvarez said he wasn't
at the location.
But they're checking out the next
black site on the map.
All right.
Everybody else has the score.
Court of Owls is planning
an attack on the city.
They kidnapped Bruce Wayne
and now they know we're coming
for them.
So, be ready for anything.
Let's go.
This is the Ruling Council.
- Who could have done this?
- It's straight up execution.
Gordon, we got a breather.
Gordon. Traitor.
Yeah, I'm a traitor.
Where's Bruce Wayne?
Where's the bomb?
We were betrayed.
The leader, Bruce Wayne,
they killed us.
That guy is lying.
If Master Bruce wasn't in that room,
he's being held prisoner.
I mean, it's absurd
to think he had anything to do
with that carnage.
I still don't get why the leader
would whack his own
ruling council.
I mean, does this mean the virus
bomb plan thing is off?
Until we have the bomb
in our possession,
we have to assume
the plan is still on.
Maybe the leader was cleaning
house.
So, what's the next step?
Because we hit every spot
on that crystal owl
and all we got were dead people
wearing owl masks.
Run their identities,
we track their holdings,
we see where it leads us.
It worked for Katheryn.
Yeah? And how long
is that gonna take them mate?
We're all trying to find Bruce,
Alfred.
We're doing everything we can.
If only that were enough?
- He's worried about the kid.
- I don't blame him.
I have no idea how Bruce fits
into the Court's plans.
But what we saw today,
them executing their own.
They're zealots.
Capable of anything.
Gordon, those uni's you put
on Thompkins' brownstone?
They called. She's home.
I know what you're thinking,
brother.
Lee stealing the virus. That's weird.
But injecting herself?
This is Lee we're talking about.
You didn't hear what she said
to me last night, Harvey.
Okay, fine. Go.
I will be back as soon as I can.
Come again?
I said Oswald Cobblepot is alive.
- He's lying.
- I wish that were true.
He disappeared for days
and then he shows up
with some insane story
about him and Penguin
being trapped in bird cages
and escaping together?
- What'd you say you used? Pudding?
- Red Jell-O.
How stupid do you think we are?
You really want me
to answer that?
It's a setup.
Well, you would know,
being an expert in betrayal.
Keep pushing me.
- Calm down. Both of you.
- In the interest of cooperation,
your partner is backstabbing
actually led to the answer
you were seeking.
Who controls Gotham?
It's an organization calling
themselves the Court of Owls.
And?
Who are they? What do they want?
Well, unfortunately
my interaction was limited
to a woman named Kathryn
who had a stern up-do.
But I can tell you there is
no interest in the underworld.
So, at least for now, you shouldn't
worry about them.
You should worry about Penguin.
I'm sorry.
How is that our problem again?
You're the one that shot him
and dumped him in the river.
Oh, Butch.
I knew that your hand
was made out of lead,
but I forgot
your brain was as well.
- Cute.
- Thank you.
The three of you conspired
to help me murder him.
So in Penguin's eyes
we're all guilty.
He's right.
I'll get a team to hit Penguin's
house right away.
Don't bother.
He knows that's the first place
we'd show up.
He's probably stowed away
in some safe house.
Good thing, I know
where they all are.
Here we go, together again.
I should've told you...
Penguin has recruited an army
of Hugo Strange's monsters.
I'll take it from here.
Head back to the station.
Lee?
It's Jim.
Hello, Jim.
I knew you'd come.
Are you surprised?
You look surprised.
There's been a squad car
outside my house all morning.
That tells me you knew
I stole the virus.
Had you assumed
I inject myself?
- I'd hope I was wrong.
- That'll teach you.
Can I get you something?
I know how you like your whiskey.
- Why did you do this?
- You know, why, Jim.
You blame yourself
for what happened to Mario.
You didn't shoot him.
You didn't infect him.
It wasn't your fault.
I have to disagree with you
on that one.
But, honestly, the whole argument
is moot at this point.
No, it isn't.
Barnes was infected for weeks
before the virus fully took hold.
We can get you help.
I'm no virologist, but I'd say
we missed the boat on that one.
Come on, we can fight this.
Come with me.
Do you want to know
what the virus
has brought out of me, Jim?
What it shown me?
No.
My love for you.
It's pretty obvious
when you think about it.
Perfect Dr. Lee Thompkins.
Why would she be drawn to a man
with so much darkness
and such an appetite for violence?
Unless something inside her liked it.
Craved it.
Needed it.
It's not true.
The virus has shown me how
to give in to my deepest desires.
And I will no longer deny myself
what I really want.
There is problem, though, Jim,
isn't there?
You know, what the problem is,
don't you?
- Yeah. You need help.
- No. The problem...
Is that you are always denying
yourself who you really are.
But I can help you with that.
You see, Jim, I have a secret.
Harvey, I found something.
Right. This is a mocked up
of the map that Lucius made
of all the Court's black sites,
right?
One problem.
The place where Bruce
and I found the ritual crystal owl
should be here. Not.
But it's not.
Or maybe it's an old owl
that hasn't been updated.
No, mate. No.
You're missing the point. No.
Look, the Court has marked
all hideouts.
So, how'd you find the house
where you stole the owl?
Well, this is slippery.
Ukrainian smuggling firm
called the Whisper Gang.
And you're thinking that maybe
they know of other locations?
You know, where we can find
these clowns?
I do.
If there's any left alive.
What's he's so angry about?
We hunted down these freaks
to help him destroy Nygma
and Barbara.
We got this Freeze guy
and your pal Bridgit
- who does the fire...
- Wait. You found Bridgit?
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
Pengy disappeared the other day
and she and Freeze figured
he wasn't coming back,
so they split.
- Can you find her?
- Why?
There's a war coming between me
and Nygma and Barbara Kean.
- I need my army.
- What's in it for me?
My gratitude.
Fine.
Guys, we got company.
Not the good kind.
Ivy, let's go.
I can't leave Penguin.
Suit yourself.
You do have a way out, right?
Of course. This is a safe house.
Oswald!
Edward.
No, army of monsters? Such a shame.
- You want to kill him, or can I?
- Wait.
Something is wrong.
Oh, Ed.
So smart.
No!
- Damn it!
- Bravo, Oswald!
You're just delaying the inevitable.
Where's you far better half?
Where are you going, kitty cat?
Bruce.
What were you thinking about?
My parents.
I've wanted justice for them
for so long.
And now that I've achieved it...
What do you feel?
Failure.
I did not give the order.
You will get another chance
to prove yourself worthy.
Hello, Bruce.
It's good to see you again.
Hello, Professor.
Fascinating.
He's completely docile.
I'd like to hear your techniques,
Sensei.
One day, Professor.
Show me the weapon.
I told you, Bruce, that I did not
serve the Court.
I, we made use of the Court
for our own ends.
The one I serve believes
you have a great destiny.
My task has been
to prepare you for it.
But a final step remains
in your journey.
This detonator will trigger
the bomb.
Thousands will be affected
with a virus.
The city will be torn apart,
and out of the ashes...
A dark hero will rise.
You.
When the time comes,
you must press this button.
Are you ready to embrace
your destiny, Bruce?
Yes.
Gotham must fall.
Jim, me and Alfred got
a possible location on Bruce
from a bunch of Ukrainian yucks
wearing muzzles
if you can believe it.
Give me a call when you can.
Where the hell is Gordon, anyway?
He had to do something.
We're gonna have to give you
a badge or something
one of these days.
Please be very careful with this.
G.C.P.D. Nobody.
Go get Bruce.
Don't move a muscle.
Obviously I surrender.
You know, where to take it.
Bruce!
Oh, thank god.
I see that you're the top boy,
aren't you?
The leader.
Step away from Bruce
or I swear to God I will shoot
you straight in the face.
You had best put down the weapon,
Mr. Pennyworth.
No, bloody likely, mate.
Bruce?
Bruce, get out of the line.
No, Alfred.
I will not let you hurt him.
What's he done to you?
He has lifted the burden
of my past.
Revealed my true destiny.
Gotham must fall by my hand.
No.
Bruce!
- Dwayne. Hey.
- Yes, sir?
Steve, put this animal in a cage.
I'll be back to bust your head
in a minute.
Alfred, hey.
Are you okay?
Far from it.
I mean the leader of the Court
has turned Bruce
into some kind of weird
zombie zealot.
I mean, I wouldn't believe it if
I don't seen it with my own eyes.
I think he wants Bruce
to detonate the bomb.
- What?
- Bruce said something
about it being his destiny.
How Gotham must fall
by his hand.
This is bad.
How are we gonna find that
freaking bomb?
Let's go see "Baldy-locks"
and see what he can tell us.
Harvey, I heard from the unis
at Doc Thompkins'.
No, sign of her or Gordon
or his car.
Put a BOLO out on Jim Gordon.
And put one out
on Lee Thompkins too.
I'm right here, Harvey.
Lee?
Hey.
It's good to see you.
You wouldn't happen to know
where Jim is, would you?
As a matter of fact,
he's probably waking up.
Right about now.
Lee?
Lee!
Lee! Lee! Lee!
Take it easy, everybody.
Guns down, people.
It's all right.
Everybody, just step back.
You really did it?
You injected yourself
with the virus.
You're just like Jim. You seem
to think it's a bad thing.
Where is he?
He went to see you
at you brownstone
and now we can't get in touch
with him.
Well, look at you all worried
about your hero.
You put him up on this pedestal.
Forced him to deny his true self.
I am going to free Jim
and show everyone
who he really is.
Where the hell is he?
He's in a coffin.
Six feet underground.
Did you kill him?
Who said anything
about killing him?
Bloody hell.
I said he was in a coffin.
He's not dead. Not yet.
Jeez.
I forgot how jumpy everybody is
around here.
Jim, are you there?
Jim, you there?
Lee, what the hell are you doing?
Stay calm.
You gotta conserve your air.
Listen to me.
A little late for that.
Why don't say hi
to Harvey and the gang?
Harvey? You there?
We're here, buddy. Where are you?
Harvey, she's got the virus.
She's buried me alive.
I do the talking.
Now, if you're quiet,
I'll let you listen.
So here's the deal.
I buried Jim Gordon alive.
In a location that you might find
if you looked long enough.
But certainly not before
he runs out of air.
No, no. I'm the only one
who knows where he is.
But, here's the kicker.
I left him a way out.
You hear that, Jim?
I left you an escape hatch.
Have you found it yet?
You should have found it by now.
You left me the virus.
I told you I would help you
find your darkness.
Now, I can't do it for you.
You gotta do it yourself.
I won't. I won't do it, Lee.
You got two options.
You can take the virus
and find the strength,
then get out of there.
Or you can make that coffin
your permanent home.
Lee, please. Please.
In the name of all that is holy,
not insane.
Tell us where he is.
I swear to god, I'll let you
walk right out of here.
Tell us where you buried him.
Why would I wanna walk
out of here, Harvey?
I'm gonna miss the look
on all of your faces
when he takes that virus.
And seeing that he's got
roughly an hour left of oxygen,
I'm not gonna have long to wait.
Can I get a cup of coffee?
Get the lady a cup of coffee!
Put her in a cell.
Don't worry, I'm not gonna bite.
All right, everyone,
Bruce Wayne is still missing.
There's still a freaking
terrorist attack
that can go down in any minute,
so get back to your jobs,
do what you're supposed
to be doing,
let me worry about Jim Gordon.
What do we got?
- Jim, it's me. You there, buddy?
- Harvey.
These radios run
on a shortwave frequency.
I've gotta be close.
Get it over the Lucius.
He should be able to run down
a general fix.
- Hang tight. We're on it.
- Let's go.
All right.
Conserve your breath.
Stay calm.
I'm not working for Penguin.
So, you were just
holed up together for kicks?
No. Ivy just
asked me to come by.
- Why?
- None of your business, lunk.
So, now I gotta take lip
off a kid?
You're friends with that firebug,
aren't you?
Her name is Bridgit.
Penguin's army of monsters
deserted him.
And he needed your help
finding them.
You're gonna tell Penguin
that you know where this...
Bridgit is,
and that you'd like to meet.
And we'll take care of the rest.
Fine.
But I need cash
to get out of town.
- Fine.
- And nothing happens to Ivy.
She's stupid, but not a traitor.
Those things
aren't mutually exclusive.
Shoo. The grown-ups need to talk.
Oh, and forgive me if I don't
want you knowing the details.
That didn't work out so well
last time.
Bye now.
How much longer
are we gonna put up with this?
Jim!
Harvey, what did you find?
You were right about the walkie.
It's got a one-mile radius.
Lucius couldn't trace a signal,
but when looked at the map,
we figured there's only one place
she can take you.
Jackson Park.
I should have known.
That's nothing but dense forest.
It's a place to start.
We're gonna find you, brother.
I promise.
Harvey. Listen,
I know he's your mate.
But with everything else
that's going on,
with Bruce missing, the bomb...
Are you certain searching for Jim
is the best use of your time?
The situation were reversed,
he'd do the same for me.
- Besides, I got you.
- What do you mean?
I want you to squeeze Strange.
Find out everything he knows.
I saw how you dealt
with that Kathryn bird.
You like to get your hands dirty.
Why, are you sure about this,
mate?
I want you to get your hands
really dirty.
I want you to find out
where the leader's taking Bruce,
find the bomb.
And however much or little
is left of Strange after that,
even if it's just a pinky,
we will throw in jail.
Thanks.
Campos, call the K-nine unit,
have them meet us in Jackson Park
now.
You can't save him, Harvey.
He's gonna take the virus.
And we're gonna be together
the way we were meant to be!
It's gonna be beautiful.
Get off!
I find this sound and screaming
deeply upsetting.
It affects my concentration.
And my grip!
Please. Don't let me fall.
We can discuss this
in a civilized manner.
Well, that's rich
coming from the likes of you.
It's about to poison
thousands of people
and turn them
into raving lunatics!
Now, where is Bruce Wayne
and where is the bomb?
If I tell you, you'll drop me.
I end up dead...
Either way.
Self-preservation, is it?
That's your game.
All right, then, Humpty.
I've got a swap deal for you.
Dang it, pop.
Your freedom...
To Bruce Wayne.
You don't have the authority
to let me go.
I didn't have the authority
just hanging off the side
of a bloody building, did I?
Hey. See that fire escape
over there?
That leads directly to the street
and to your freedom.
Now, I won't stop you.
I just wanna know
where my boy is.
All right.
The leader has taken Bruce
to Wayne Enterprises.
They'll have a view
of the street below
as it fills with people
infected by the virus.
- But you're too late.
- Why.
What time is the bomb going off?
5.00 pm but that's not
what I mean.
The Bruce Wayne you know
is gone.
His mind is no longer his own.
Oh, you're so wrong.
You have got no idea
how strong that boy is.
Now, I'm a man of my word.
You can walk.
Just as soon as you wake up.
I don't know what you mean.
Slag.
You seem troubled.
I hope it was not the encounter
with your manservant.
No.
If this is my destiny...
I do not want to fail.
You won't, Bruce.
All this.
Everything the Court of Owls
set in motion,
everything I have done,
has been to prepare you
for this moment.
And afterward...
I will bring you to the one whose
vision has singled you out.
He is very eager to meet you.
Harvey. Anything?
Nothing yet. We've covered
about 30 acres.
How are you holding up?
Getting hard to breathe.
Stay off the walkie.
You gotta conserve your air.
That should be hard.
I'm running low on battery.
Then quit your yapping.
Harvey, there's too much
ground to cover.
You've done everything you could.
Okay.
Go to Plan B.
Take the virus.
- No.
- If you don't, you'll die.
Take the virus and we'll figure
something out.
I'm not gonna take the virus.
I won't become a monster.
Hold on.
- Alfred!
- Strange said
the bomb is due to detonate
at 5.00pm.
Five o'clock?
That's only in 20 minutes!
- Where?
- He never said, mate.
But he did say
that the leader and Bruce
heading directly
to Wayne Enterprises
to watch the fallout.
Now, the rooftop looks directly
onto Union Station.
The bomb's due to go off slap
bang in the middle of rush hour.
Wait! Stop!
I want every available unit
to Union Station.
I want it evacuated now. Go!
K-9, stay with me.
Harvey, at 5.00pm.
Union Station is gonna be packed.
Even with the evacuation,
thousands will be infected.
Not if we find the bomb first.
But I'm guessing it's not
gonna be sitting out in the open.
- No, it will be hidden.
- Where?
Yesterday, Kathryn said,
"Gotham will fall
when the clock stops."
What if she was talking
about a real clock?
The clock tower
in Union Station.
Harvey?
Harvey, do you hear me?
Harvey? Harvey, you copy?
Jim, I lost you! Jim?
Jim!
In the old days,
loyalty meant something.
Don Falcone. Maroni.
Even Fish.
They had their faults.
But they lived by codes.
Ed Nygma.
Barbara Kean.
They wouldn't even be allowed
to sit at the same table
as Don Falcone.
And yet, here I am
forced to demean myself
to do battle with them.
Yeah, people are dumb.
Plants are better.
You can trust them.
I have no more safe houses.
No, monsters.
I will not run from Ed Nygma.
Well, actually,
you have one monster.
- What?
- Selina called.
She found Bridgit.
She was gonna bring her by.
You're joking. That's...
Wait.
Why is Selina
suddenly helping me?
I don't know.
She was acting kind of weird.
Asking where we were,
did we have guns.
So I was like,
"We're all alone!"
You idiot!
- It was a set-up!
- No.
No, way.
Selina would never do that.
Unless they offered her money.
Hello again. Oswald.
Captain, over here.
I think we've found something.
We gotta get to Union Station.
That was Bullock.
Gordon's on his way
to Union Station.
He's infected with the virus.
Come on!
Hey!
You must be very proud
of yourself, Ed.
Thinking you outsmarted me.
Well, frankly,
it wasn't really a challenge.
Now, you're gonna do one thing
before you die.
Call me...
The Riddler.
No.
You have a choice, Oswald.
This can happen real quick,
or it can take hours.
Days.
- It will be...
- I'll take option B, Ed.
Since saying that ridiculous name
would be torture itself.
Very well.
Slow and painful it shall be.
Hello. Do I get no say
in all this?
- See how it feels?
- Guys.
You hear something?
This is a trap.
No, not exactly.
- Fish.
- Hello, Oswald.
Now, see that there.
That's a look of respect.
Or is it fear?
Hey, you, Fish.
- How have you been?
- Well, let's see.
I was alive...
And then I was dead.
And then I was alive.
Things are looking up.
My, my, my.
Now, this is quite the gathering.
You have to love Gotham.
People are always pointing guns
at each other.
- Why are you here?
- You shall...
See.
And as for you,
whoever you may be.
Please excuse us.
My little penguin and I...
Will be leaving.
Please. Carry on.
That woman always knew
how to make an entrance.
- Attention, all passengers.
- What?
This is an emergency.
Please proceed to the nearest...
Gordon! There you are.
This is an emergency.
Please proceed
to the nearest exit.
It's time.
Press the button.
Claim your destiny.
Let Gotham fall so you may rise.
No!
Whatever destiny he's sold you,
Bruce, he's lying.
- Press it, Bruce.
- Don't.
Bruce, don't.
I won't have him turn you
into a murderer.
This is an emergency.
Please proceed to the nearest exit.
Are you going to shoot me,
Alfred?
I wanna help you.
Reverse what he's done to you.
Bruce, if you press
that detonator,
there is no coming back.
He won't shoot you.
He's weak, Bruce.
But you are not.
Bruce. Please.
Give me the detonator, son.
No. You will press it!
Hello, lover.
I guess we're gonna have company.
Seek out the Yuyan building.
Find the demon's head.
Fulfill your destiny.
Bruce.
When you're ready
come and find me.
It's only a matter of time.
It's too late.
You all right?