Last season, onGotham...
It's in here. It's in this room.
My father's secret,
it's in this room.
Going after Loeb is suicide,
plain and simple.
As usual, wrong place, wrong time.
You're a disgrace, Loeb.
What's black and white
and red all over?
Stop talking like that.
Why did you kill your mother, Dru?
Barbara, Jason Lennon
killed your parents.
- You didn't kill them.
- Yes, I did.
Goodbye, Fish!
I'm the king of Gotham!
What is it, do you think?
Bloody hell.
No, wait, wait, wait!
There must be a million possible
combinations, Master Bruce.
- Drink it all.
- Thank you, Master.
Now go.
Come on, bro. Let's go. Let's go.
I am Zaardon, the soul reaper!
Forward, slaves!
You cannot escape me!
Sir, drop the guns!
- You! You!
- Please don't!
Your primitive weapons
cannot hurt me!
Prepare to die, insect!
Hey, listen. I don't wanna shoot you,
man, all right?
Too much paperwork.
So why don't you just
put the sword down?
Stay down. Relax.
Yo, Gordon. What's up? Busy shift?
- You're late.
- Jeez, relax, will you?
What's the matter with you, man?
Hey!
Bad idea.
How can this be?
Zaardon drank dragon's blood
from the master's chalice.
Zaardon? That's spelt how it sounds?
- Two A's.
- Close enough.
You dare send me to prison.
Oh, no, you're a cinch for Arkham.
Hear me, Gordon.
You might have won this battle
but the war has just begun.
The master will unleash hell
upon you.
Dark days are coming.
Thanks for the heads up.
Ed.
- Are you okay?
- Never better.
Officer Gordon, 236.1,
report to the captain's office
immediately.
I'm up. See you.
He's gone. Relax.
Holy moly. Look at you.
Everyone's gonna think
you're going nuts.
I get nervous when you talk to me
with other people around like that.
Stop doing that.
- What?
- That.
Copying me.
Dude, it's a mirror.
That's how they work.
You know what I think we need?
I think that we need
a little more fun.
Some romance.
Stop. I know where this is going.
I told you, leave Miss Kringle alone.
Imagine her in our arms.
Those big eyes looking up at us
and soft, trembling flesh.
Be quiet!
It's a simple question,
Officer Gordon.
Did you or did you not put your
hands on Officer Franks here?
Yes, I did.
From the first day on the job,
you have been an insubordinate
troublemaker.
I hope demotion to uniform duty
would suffice to make you quit.
It worked for your partner, Bullock.
However, you've now confessed
to violation of Section 12,
immediate dismissal is mandatory.
Commissioner, this is not just.
Officer Frank sustained no harm
and Officer Gordon showed
admirable restraint
in diffusing
a dangerous hostage situation.
Thank you so much for your input,
Captain.
The facts speak for themselves.
The facts say he deserves
commendation, not dismissal.
You're letting gutter politics...
That's enough, young lady.
Take Officer...
Mr. Gordon's badge and gun.
That's an order.
All good.
Let it go.
Thanks, Loeb.
It's been an honor working for you.
This is all for the best, you know.
Some men
are just not meant to be cops.
I told you I'd break you.
I will.
What did you say to him?
Did you get mad?
Well, I disagreed with his decision.
Come on. You know I need the details.
I said I'd break him.
Words to that effect.
Hey, you went out with a bang.
Maybe it's for the best.
That's what Loeb said.
I should have walked away.
I just hate to quit.
You didn't quit. You were fired.
What can you do?
There's things I can do.
I though you said you didn't have
any legal moves left.
I don't.
You wanna be a cop so bad
you're willing to break the law.
I'm willing to bend it a little,
yeah.
You're happy I got fired, huh?
You got me.
Well, only because I know
that you'll never quit.
And I love that about you.
But they have you
directing traffic, Jim.
Why keep beating your head
against the wall?
I'm a cop, Lee.
I'm a cop.
Hi, gorgeous. I'm Dru.
Keep moving, Ginger.
Just being polite.
- So, what are you in for?
- Killing my parents.
Me too. Well, Mum, anyhow.
Liberating, right?
What a rush!
Yeah, alrighty then.
I see the big handsome fellow
staring at you
like you're fried chicken.
Richard Sionis. He's a millionaire.
Daddy's on the airplane,
got a boat with a hot tub on it.
He killed 25 people. Just for fun.
So what?
So, he likes you.
He wants to be your friend.
Let me think.
No.
A girl needs a good friend in here.
See, the guards, they don't care.
They figure bad things happen
to bad people.
And they happen all of the time.
All the time.
Hey, you.
Hello.
Baldy. Here, here. Hello. Yes!
Hi. Come here.
- Hi.
My name is Barbara.
- Would you be my friend?
- Yes.
Hey, if someone here
tries to hurt me
- would you protect me?
- Yes.
Thank you so much.
You cutie.
Now, I have a friend.
You're bad.
Yes. So why don't you go
and make me a sandwich?
Your friend is a gorilla.
My friend runs the joint.
And he can get you things
that people other can't get you.
- Things like what?
- Anything you need.
I need a telephone.
Ogden Barker, in for 70 grand
plus two months vig
250 in change.
Says he owes Falcone.
Falcone's gone,
so his debt is forfeited.
Well, we can't have him saying that.
What if everybody started
saying that?
There'd be anarchy.
What is it?
Splendid.
Jim! Come on in.
My dear old friend.
We need to talk.
Leave us.
Hey, Selina. Moving on up, huh?
Trying.
Isn't she a darling?
It's like having a cat
around the house.
But no horrid dead mice.
I need a favor.
I figure you owe me one.
I do.
I'm always happy to help you, Jim.
But I, I don't recall...
The hospital.
I saved you from Maroni's men.
I was only there
because you arrested me.
For attempted murder.
Remind me again why I let you go.
Enlightened friendship.
I call us even but let's not quibble.
I'm so happy you came to me
for help, Jim.
The answer is yes.
Your wish is granted.
You don't know what it is yet.
You want Loeb fired
and your old job back, no?
Yes.
For a good friend like you,
it can be done.
If you're sure that's what you want.
I'm sure.
May I ask why?
Police work in Gotham
is such a thankless job.
Good pension.
What does Lee think?
Who?
Are you gonna help me or not?
Relax. I already said I would help.
He is so brusque, isn't he?
Oh, thank you.
While I think on it...
perhaps there's a small favor
you could do for me in return.
I know how you hate to owe favors.
I am having a small business
dispute with a friend of mine.
Ogden Barker.
You have a persuasive personality.
Perhaps you could talk to him.
You want me to collect a debt
for you?
I want you to prove to me
that our friendship is a real one
based on trust and equity.
That's fair.
No. Sorry. Can't help you.
Congratulations on all your success.
- Be good, Selina.
- Always.
Don't say no now, Jim. Sleep on it.
Screw, Penguin. Screw the GCPD.
And screw this city.
Amen. You're doing
the right thing, brother.
Walk away, Jim. Just walk away.
You would do the same thing,
right?
Me, I'm serving sandwich
to Beelzebub, but that's just me.
You are a moralist.
You could never work for Penguin.
Shame would eat away at your guts.
Yeah.
Slow down, slurp-man.
- You're not joining me?
- I've been sober 32 days.
- 32 days, huh?
- It's no biggie.
Once I quit the job,
quitting drinking was easy.
It's the job, Jim.
Makes us angry, makes us hard.
Yeah, it does.
It's hard to walk away
but it can be done.
I just couldn't carry
that badge anymore.
Look at me now.
I'm sober.
I have a woman
who does not dislike me.
I live in a house. I sleep at night.
I've never been happier in my life.
Here's to civilian life.
I'm proud of you, bro.
Gotta go.
Oh, really,
I'm most frightfully sorry
it took so long
to answer the door, sir.
Strange.
Normally, our buzzer sounds
when a car comes through the gates.
I walked.
You two are dirty.
What have you been doing?
I imagine you have something
important to say.
Yes.
I have been fired from the GCPD.
I won't be able to keep the promise
I made you.
I wanted to apologize.
Your apology is accepted,
of course.
But you didn't need to walk here.
A phone call would have been fine.
I needed the air.
No hope for reinstatement then, sir?
No.
Well, there is a way
but it's too ugly.
I would have to collect a debt
for Penguin
to prove our friendship.
But you can't do that
because he's a bad man.
The task could be demeaning.
Well, yes.
You were going to find
my parents' killers.
You were gonna fight for justice.
You were gonna clean up the GCPD,
change Gotham.
I had hoped to do that.
If you remain at the GCPD,
you might still be able to do
all of those good things.
But first, you must do
something ugly.
And your personal honor forbids that.
Yes.
Are you not sacrificing
the greater good
for the sake of your dignity
and self-esteem?
- For vanity?
- Steady on there, Master Bruce.
- Manners.
- He walked all the way here
to discuss the issue, Alfred.
I'm simply asking a question.
Surely sometimes the right way...
is also the ugly way.
Sometimes, a man can't tell you
the right way he is dealing with.
All kinds of business
you can't possibly understand yet
because you're still a child.
Yes, Alfred, there's still
a great deal I don't understand.
Please forgive me
if I've offended you, Jim.
No, no.
That's okay.
I'll show you out, sir.
Screw it.
Dru says you can get me
a telephone.
I try and help my friends.
What do your friends do for you?
Well, that depends on
how much you want the telephone.
Hold it right there.
Ogden Barker.
Penguin asked me to talk to you.
The hell, boy.
You got me worried there
for a minute.
I know you. You're Jim Gordon, cop.
Supposed to be a cold-stone hard-ass.
But you're Penguin's bitch, huh?
How many dickens
can you trust anymore?
He wants his money.
How many times
I gotta tell you, people, no.
To Don Falcone, I'll pay.
To that fruitcake leprechaun,
nish, not a penny.
Falcone's retired. Time's changed.
Penguin is boss now.
Like hell.
The freak won't last a year.
Don't underestimate him.
Advice now?
I'm trying to be nice here.
Let's work this out.
Yeah?
Let's not.
Walk away.
Walk away before I kick your ass,
you crooked punk bitch.
How much money you got there?
Looks like a lot.
- What is your problem?
- I don't have a problem.
Give me the money you owe.
How about I put a hole
in your face?
I'm gonna count to three.
You're crazy.
One...
Put the money in the bag. Do it!
Get him, man.
Stop! Thief!
Out of the way!
Hey, cop.
Fertilizer? What is your game?
I would have thought that's obvious
to a man of your perception.
It occurred to me
to follow my own advice.
Sometimes the ugly way
is also the right way.
I mean, a bomb, inside the house?
I mean, you're having a laugh,
ain't you, a bomb?
I was going to tell you.
I wanted to present it
as a fait accompli.
Don't start talking French to me.
You don't know the first thing
about bomb-making anyway, do you?
I read a book, Alfred.
It seems simple enough.
A book?
I mean, you're gonna blow
your bloody head off
before you put a dent in that thing.
You know, maybe that door
is trying to tell us something.
Maybe you're not ready
to find out what's behind it.
Maybe we should wait
until you're older.
I mean, who knows
what your dear old dad was up to
down there, anyway?
Like what?
Like things I wouldn't want
to describe to a child
which is exactly what you are.
I'm building a bomb
to blow down that door.
You may assist me or not.
As you wish.
But if not, some tea would be nice.
Right. Well, you're gonna need
ten more sacks of that.
Okay, for starters,
three more jerry cans, too,
extra timber,
and a heavy tarpaulin.
And I'll put the kettle on.
Excellent.
I'm so sorry things got messy.
What a foolish fellow.
Never mind. I will make sure
that there is no follow-up
from your colleagues.
Don't worry about a thing.
You knew.
You knew Ogden would go off.
What a devious mind do you have?
I have no idea.
We have a deal.
We do. We do.
Are you okay, Jim?
Yeah. Daydreaming.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- Hello.
- Hello. Jim?
- Hello. Are you still there?
- I'm here.
Hi. How are you?
How did you get to a phone?
Who cares?
We're talking at last,
that's the important thing.
What do you want?
Jim, there's been a terrible mistake.
I never told Lee
that I killed my mum and dad.
And I never attacked her.
She attacked me, Jim.
She's completely insane.
That's enough.
Don't call again.
Who's that?
Sales call.
- It can drive you crazy, huh?
- Sales call?
Don't.
- What?
- Don't answer it.
- Jim, you're scaring me.
- It's Barbara.
Go ahead, leave a message.
Hey, girlfriend.
Guess who?
Sorry I missed you. Bummer, eh?
I just wanted to say
that I hope you die screaming, bitch.
Bye.
Nice.
All right, look.
She's safely locked up in Arkham,
she can't hurt you.
I know. I know. She's just
a sick person spreading sadness.
Screw her. Let's be happy.
Let's go away some place.
We can't let a crazy woman
drive us out.
Why not?
Pride? Who cares?
We could go away and never come back.
What's keeping us here?
I can't leave.
Why not?
Jim?
I did a bad thing.
Hi.
Do you have any peanut butter?
What?
Peanut butter? Smooth.
Food preference.
Guard. Help! Help!
Hi, boss.
How about a bottle of beer?
Let me share a dilemma with you.
May I?
I need you to do something for me
that I know you won't wanna do.
What is it?
With most people,
there is no problem.
I find their weak spots
and use violence or blackmail
to persuade them.
But you...
you are a man of monkish virtue.
You have no vices to expose.
So, threats of personal violence
will only harden your resolve, huh?
No, that...
Come, sir, don't be modest.
You are a rare animal.
But that does lead us
to a sad pickle.
Since I can't persuade you
to do as I ask,
the only rational option is
to kill you
and negotiate with whoever
replaces you as a commissioner.
Now, Chief?
One moment, Victor.
The commissioner deserves time
to process all this.
Say a prayer or what have you.
What do you want me to do?
It's not worth talking about.
You wouldn't do it.
Tell me.
I need my friend Jimmy Gordon
reinstated as a detective.
See? You hate that idea.
No, I don't. I'll do it.
I can tell that you're not sincere.
Even if you do as I ask,
someday down the line,
you'll change your mind,
and you'll turn on him again.
- You want me to kill him now?
- No, make him a nice cheese toast.
- Yes, kill him now, please.
- I just want it to be clear.
No, wait! Let's talk about this.
Sorry, least worst option.
Unless of course...
No, you would never agree?
To what? Agree to what?
So long, farewell
Auf Wiedersehen, goodbye
Goodbye
Lovely, lovely. Bravo.
Mayor James regrets
he's unable to attend today.
But he sent a dear friend
in his stead.
Please welcome
distinguished businessman,
visionary, scientist,
acclaimed philanthropist,
and new chairman of the development
at the Gotham Chamber of Commerce,
Mr. Theo Galavan.
Thank you so much.
What an honor it is to be here today
to help bid farewell to a great man
and a faithful servant of this city.
What can I say about Gillian Loeb?
Someone tell me a funny story.
I have a good one.
So when I was in college,
I played for the varsity polo team,
and I had a, a string of ponies...
Greetings!
I am Zaardon, the soul reaper!
So, I have these ponies...
I'm an adopted son of this city.
I haven't lived in Gotham very long,
but I already love her like a native.
It just, it just kind of grabs
hold of you, doesn't it?
There's magic here.
Magic.
And that is down to everyday heroes
like Gillian Loeb.
Mr. Commissioner,
thank you for your service.
Thank you very much, everybody.
My best wishes to...
Commissioner Essen.
And the maitre d' says,
"You can't bring them in here."
Hear me, slaves!
My patience is wearing thin.
Surrender your souls to my mercy.
I swear by the master,
I shall feast on your pain.
I shall gorge on your torment.
I shall crush you like a bug.
Back up, Area Five! Area Five!
Welcome back, Jim.
I don't know how you pulled this off,
but I'm glad you did.
He's a resourceful man.
- Congratulations to both of you.
- Thank you.
And it is a new day, Jim.
We're going to do great things.
Yes, we are.
It is a new day.
Things are gonna be all right,
I promise.
- I hope it was worth it.
- I hope so, too.
Jim.
What's wrong?
There's been an incident
at Arkham Asylum.
Six inmates have escaped.
Barbara Kean was one of them.
Oh, my God.
- What the hell is this place?
- In Arkham, anyhow.
Things are looking up.
Welcome, everyone.
My name is Theo Galavan.
This is my sister, Tabitha.
- I gotta get my hands on that.
- Hey, come on.
I understand you're feeling
confused...
scared, a little groggy.
But please, relax.
Today is the first day
of a wonderful future for all of you.
If you want it.
Who are you?
Well, now the question is
who are you?
The world sees criminal lunatics.
I see brilliance.
I see charisma.
And power.
I see power.
Yes. Exactly, my man.
That is so spooky,
that is me to a tee.
These other bozos, I don't know,
but you're singing my song.
Quiet, Jerome.
Keep talking.
Imagine a group of brilliant outlaws
like yourselves,
each selected for a unique ability,
are working together as a team.
Imagine the synergy.
Imagine the impact.
Gotham will tremble before you.
Well, that sounds fabulous,
but I am not a brilliant outlaw.
I just have...
issues.
You have ferocity, and beauty,
and desire.
And that's enough.
Come with me, Barbara.
Whatever you want in the world,
it's yours.
Theo.
That's your name, right? Theo?
You're getting way ahead
of yourself here.
First of all,
keep your hands off her.
Second, this whole magic team,
I got to pass.
I don't take orders.
Good luck on everything, though.
It's an intriguing concept.
- This is very disappointing.
- Oh, fair play.
You want a reward
for busting us out of Arkham.
I am grateful.
How's a million bucks sound?
Pretty good, huh?
I can get it for you today
as soon as I hit the street.
Money is not the concern.
I had such high hopes for you.
And unanticipated sexual jealousy
that always poisons the well.
You have to go.
Tabitha will see you out.
Miss Kean is coming with me.
Oh, she doesn't wanna go
where you're going.
Anyone else who wanna leave?
Now, you're absolutely sure
about this, Master Bruce?
- I strongly advice...
- Alfred.
I need to know.
Let's do this.
Yeah. All right, sir.
- Yes!
- Yeah!
Dear Bruce
these last weeks,
I began to feel very mortal...
which prompts this note to you.
Perhaps, I'm being paranoid.
I hope so.
In any case, if you're reading
this, then I'm dead.
And you figured out
that the entry code is Bruce.
I'm sorry I had to hide
this part of my life from you
because this place only exists
because of you.
Becoming a father made me want
to be a better man.
And I started asking hard questions
about the family business.
So, here we are.
As I write this, you're 12
and a fine, good-hearted boy.
So I'm sure you'll be a fine,
good-hearted man.
But that's all I know.
I don't know what happened to me
or your mother...
or how life has turned out
for you...
I don't even know how old you are.
So, I'll resist giving you
much fatherly advice.
Only this.
You can't have both happiness
and the truth.
You have to choose.
I beg of you, my son,
please choose happiness.
Unless...
Unless you feel a calling.
A true calling.