Previously onGotham...
We will bust Penguin one day,
I promise you.
Harvey, we cannot let this slide.
You find someone with the license,
they walk.
Miss Falcone, I need know to that you
are not on some fool's errand
to rebuild your fathers empire.
An example needs to be made.
You may think you have everything
but there is one thing
you don't have.
- The Falcone name.
- Was that your plan?
Get close to Penguin,
gain his confidence, what then?
I used to be smart. Brilliant.
And now that's gone!
Never seen nothing like him before.
- Who are you?
- Solomon Grundy.
You know Grundy?
We're the very best of friends.
With your muscles, we can make money.
We'd like to put our hat in the ring.
Go get the doc!
Yeah! Come on!
Upper cut. Come on!
Finish him!
Good as new.
Doctor Lee Thompkins.
Oh, my.
Now, what is a girl like you doing
in a place like this?
I heard a rumor you were frozen.
Should've known it was too good
to be true.
Oh, you're not still mad at me,
are you?
Mad at you for what?
Killing Kristen Kringle?
Or framing Jim for murder,
so he would be in prison
when I lost our child?
I'm over all that.
Let's be friends.
I'm sensing sarcasm.
Just as sharp as ever.
Actually, funny that you mention
that...
- Goodbye, Ed.
- Wait!
Holy hell.
Butch Gilzean?
What have you done to him?
Nothing. Believe it, or not.
And he goes by Grundy now.
Hey, why don't you hang over there,
big fella?
Make sure that wall
doesn't wander off.
I have no idea what happened to him.
But he's freakishly strong,
can't remember anything about his
past life and seems to love me, so...
Big improvement.
But I, on the other hand,
I'm, I'm really hoping
to get back to who I was.
When I was on ice my head
got a little scrambled.
- Why should I care?
- Okay.
I came here with Grundy,
going to fight, make some money,
to get me smart again.
But you, Doctor Leslie Thompkins,
you can fix me.
You want me to fix you?
- Oh, you really are dumb.
- Okay, okay.
You're here for some reason.
I don't pretend to know what that is.
But if you help me, I will help you.
I know you're not really smart
right now,
so just try to understand this,
I will never help you.
I was raised to be a gentleman.
But you're also practical.
We were seen at dinner.
As we have been the past
three nights.
All of Gotham knows you have
the support of the Falcone family.
And I'm fairly certain
no one's watching us now.
I...
I just, I just like to know
where I stand.
This isn't easy for me.
To have someone I can trust.
A real friend.
You can trust me.
Let's have lunch tomorrow.
Just us.
Till then.
Have a nice dinner?
- How long have you been here?
- Long enough.
It's time that you tell me
what you're planning.
This again?
Ever since you've come to Gotham,
all you've done
is make Oswald stronger.
It's time I know your end game.
And if I refuse?
I'll put you on a train home.
I want to make you a promise.
In a matter of days I'll have
Cobblepot in the palm of my hand.
I fail, I'll stay, I'll go,
whatever you want...
Look, the count's good.
Well, now, go on, get outta here.
- I'll see you next month.
- Yeah.
Someone down there?
Freaking cat.
Oink. Oink.
What the...
If confirmed, bag
and seal immediately.
Hey.
It really one of ours?
Seems so. He was in the uniform.
But the killer took his badge.
No one recognizes him?
Well, that part
we have not figured out yet.
Let me show you.
Good God.
Freaky, huh?
Let's find out who this guys is.
Here we go.
Dave Metzger.
You know him?
Seen him around.
Not to speak ill of the dead
but he was a grade A bastard.
He have enemies on the force?
No, no cop would do this
to another cop.
But he was the candyman.
Penguin's bagman.
He was the one delivering payoffs
to cops in the precinct.
- I mean, that, that's the rumor.
- Yeah.
So someone killed him
to send a message...
- Where are you going?
- To see Penguin.
Maybe he knows why someone
wanted to kill his employee.
Don't go stirring the pot!
Enjoy your lunch Mr. Cobblepot.
I need to talk to you.
If it takes less than three minutes,
I'm all ears.
A cop was murdered last night.
Dave Metzger.
A bagman on your payroll.
Oh, and you think
I might know something?
Well, sadly, this is the first
I'm hearing his name.
A general does not need to know
every foot soldier.
You don't need to know him.
I think someone is trying
to send you a message.
What sort of message?
The killer placed a severed pig's
head over Metzger's own.
Not a very clear message.
Could have all sorts of meanings.
Metzger may have been dirty
but he was still a cop.
Someone killed him and is using
his death to make a point.
If that is in relation to you,
I need to know.
Jim, if someone had a problem
with me, I would know about it.
And I would deal with it.
I guess you're always one step ahead,
Oswald.
It's why I'm alive.
But I would like to help.
- Mr. Penn!
- Right here, Mr. Cobblepot.
Do we have anything that could assist
Detective Gordon in doing his job?
As a matter of fact, sir,
a few days ago,
Mr. Wally Clarke applied
for a burglary permit.
The Pork Barrel.
It's a butcher on Third Street.
They specialize in offering
the whole...
Thanks for the lead.
Enjoy your lunch, Oswald.
Don't thank me, Jim.
Thank the licensing system
you hate so much.
Now be sure to let me know
if I need to get more involved.
Until then, I'm rooting for you, Jim.
Have a seat, Wally.
You know how much trouble you're in,
huh?
You know what we do to cop killers?
I just told him, I didn't kill
nobody, specifically not no cop.
So you didn't lure Dave Metzger
into that alley,
split open his skull
and stick a pig's head on him?
What?
- Are you crazy?
- That's funny.
Because we searched the dumpster
behind your apartment.
Guess what we found?
Look at that!
Porky don't have no head.
What do you want to bet that head
was on the dead cop we found?
Screw it.
I have enough.
I don't need a confession.
I'm charging you with the murder
of Dave Metzger.
Wait! No!
It wasn't me.
It must've been the Prof.
- Who?
- The Professor.
That's what I called him,
because he, he, he talked all fancy.
He was the one got me
to rob the butchers.
We need a name. A description.
We did it all over the phone.
The whole deal.
I, I dropped the heads
under the Midtown Bridge.
The money was there. I never
met the guy, never got no name.
What do you mean, "heads?"
As in more than one?
How many did this guy want?
It was, it was four.
You think he could've told me
that he only needed the heads.
But no, I had to drag them up
to my house, chop heads...
Hey, shut up.
- Do you know what this means?
- Yeah.
It means there's three more victims
out there.
How many bagmen did Penguin
have on the G.C.P.D?
Wild guess, I'd say four.
The only one I knew was Metzger.
Yeah, well, the people who got paid
by those bad men?
They'll know who they are.
They're not going to talk.
We'll make them.
Hey, don't leave me back here
with this thing!
Hey!
She's not coming.
- What?
- Sofia.
- Your lunch date.
- It's not a date.
Whatever. She called.
She's not coming.
Did she say why?
Something came up?
I don't know. I wasn't listening.
It's just going to go to waste.
I want you to follow her.
Find out who she's with.
You think she's two-timing you?
She and I are not...
This lunch was her idea.
Now she cancels all of a sudden?
I want to know why.
That's all.
Now, Victor?
Today, we have ourselves a treat.
Our beloved Hammer
will take on a new challenger.
Just in from...
Grundy come from swamp.
Rules are simple.
Last man standing wins.
Besides that, anything goes!
Yeah! Just hit him!
Fight!
What are you doing? Fight!
- Grundy fight now?
- Yes! Now!
Grundy! Grundy! Grundy!
Grundy! Grundy! Grundy! Grundy!
Grundy! Grundy!
- Yes!
- Grundy! Grundy!
Yes!
Yes! Grundy has a best friend!
Grundy! Grundy! Grundy! Grundy!
Grundy! Grundy!
Looks like I got a new cash cow.
Take good care of him, Doc.
And clean up what's left of Hammer.
We're not looking to bust nobody.
We just want the name of the bagman.
Who delivers Penguin's money?
Don't know what you're talking about,
man.
- Wish I could help.
- Oh, yeah?
Hey! Hey!
Relax.
I know a couple of other guys
we can talk to,
who aren't such douche nozzles.
Seems like you should be looking
for whoever killed Dave Metzger.
Instead a shaking down other cops.
We're trying to save other cops.
More lives are on the line here.
Or you're using a cop getting killed
to go on a fishing expedition.
- Smells like IA to me.
- Hey!
Hold on! Hey! Hey! Just say
you're not helping we get it okay.
Get off me.
We're trying to stop cops
from getting killed!
How can none of you nitwits see that?
You're asking a cop
to snitch on another cop.
It ain't going to happen.
Fine.
- We'll do it your way.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, jeez!
Going to be a hot one today, huh?
Yeah.
It's got to be 90 out here.
Lot hotter in there.
- Probably a hundred.
- Let me out, you bastards!
You know what, Jim,
I think we forgot to get lunch.
Think we got time?
I could go for a burger.
All right, Culpepper, we're going
to be back in a couple of hours.
Bullock! Let me out!
I'm warning you!
Bullock!
Okay!
Chris Whitlock.
Makes deliveries for the West Side.
But don't say I told you.
Where can we find him?
He's supposed to be in court all day.
My contact on the South Side.
Said their bagman's Jenny Butler.
- Trying to reach her now.
- Good.
I just want to find this guy
Whitlock.
Hope he gives us the last name.
Should be getting out of court soon.
You ever think
you'd be running around
trying to save cops
on Penguin's payroll?
Bad cops.
They deserve to be prosecuted
and stripped of their badges.
Not butchered.
Call the police!
Hundred thousand people
in a square mile
and of course, nobody saw nothing.
Or is willing to admit it.
Butler got off duty last night.
Not seen since she clocked out.
Whitlock is doing court at 9,
never showed.
So, they were both were abducted,
taken somewhere, killed,
then brought to pose
in front of this building.
- Probably for us to find.
- That's a hell of a lot of work.
The killer believes his message
is important.
What? That he's got to rid
the city of dirty cops?
Specifically, the ones
who work for Penguin.
No wonder these guys look on edge.
Where are we on our fourth bagman?
We need an ID.
I'm working on it.
Good afternoon, sir, sir?
Detective James Gordon, G.C.P.D.
You've been playing here all morning?
On and off, you know?
Guy's got to a take a break
every now and then.
Yeah, sure.
You see anything?
Anything out of the usual?
Sorry, Detective,
I ain't seen nothing since the war.
- Right.
- All right, have a good one.
- Yeah.
Man. Man. Really?
Let's try this again.
You see anything?
An old van.
Filippelli Plumbing on the side.
Parked up the street
a good part of the morning.
Guy just sitting there.
Guy. What'd he look like?
White dude.
Didn't see his face.
I took a break.
I came back, the van was gone.
All right, thanks.
Keep the tip.
What happened to you, Butch?
Grundy.
Look at your hand, it grew back.
How is that even possible?
And look at this.
It's not even blood.
It's like swamp water.
Grundy from swamp.
Yeah. I heard.
You know, you don't have a heartbeat.
But you seem to be doing okay.
You know, Ed is not your friend.
He's just using you.
No.
Ed Grundy friend.
Ed Grundy best friend.
He just wants you to fight,
so he can make money
and make his brain better again.
Once he doesn't need you anymore
he's just going to discard you.
Or kill you, if that's even possible.
Do you understand?
Ed Grundy best friend.
That's right.
Best buddies.
A team.
Not to mention,
your boss's biggest new attraction.
Smells like we're sticking around
for a while.
Fabulous.
Unless, of course, you fix the broken
connections in this noodle
then we wouldn't have to stick
around.
We'd be...
- Gone?
- Yes, thank you.
- That's the word you're looking for?
- Yeah.
Of course, I'd pay you.
I'm patching up Grundy
as long as Cherry tells me to.
That's it.
Keep your money.
How's my best new fighter?
He going to be ready to go again
tonight, Doc?
Yeah, sure.
I got to step out for a while.
I'll be back.
Just make sure you're here.
We got a deal, you know?
Yeah. I know.
Hi, everyone,
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
I'll be right with you, okay?
All right. You can come on in.
Okay. Have a seat right there.
Help you up. One, two, three. Up.
All right.
Let's have a listen...
Sofia Falcone.
What are you doing?
Yeah. All right.
That was the Mayor's office.
Press has gotten wind.
Things are going to heat up fast.
Then we catch him fast.
All the cops who haven't called in.
Hahn. Peterson.
King. Nakajima. Massengale.
Yeah, so their precincts
are already looking for them
but I say we take this list
to Penguin.
- Have him point to a name.
- No need.
Nakajima is the bagman.
How do you know?
Peterson and Messengale
are both hard core Bible thumpers.
That leaves three.
And I've heard Nakajima's dirty.
Our units are already on their way
to his apartment, same as the others.
I say we retrace his beat.
- Concentrate our resources.
- Jim, hold on.
Doesn't something about this feel
weird to you?
Whoever set the trap for Metzger
knew where he'd be.
And the killer also knew Butler
and Whitlock's schedules.
Are you saying it's one of our own?
Someone who's fed up
with the corruption.
Decided to make a stand.
But to kill them?
Display their bodies that way...
I know, brother. But it's something
we at least have to consider.
Which means anything
that we say out there...
Got a lead on the plumbing van
your blind man saw.
Spotted near that abandoned dairy
on Commerce.
- Should we get the Strike Force?
- No, Gordon and I will cover it.
If, we need backup
I'll give you a call.
And till then, don't say a word.
And that's an order. You got it?
Let's go. Come on.
Oink, oink, little piggy.
Yeah!
Our new champion!
Grundy! Grundy! Grundy!
Grundy! Grundy!
So it turns out
Sofia broke her date with you...
It was not a date!
To have lunch with the Mayor.
They went to Angelo's.
She had the lobster ravioli.
He had the tagliatelle.
After they parted ways, Sofia went
to the old Gotham Heritage Hotel.
I don't understand.
That place has been vacant for years.
If I may, a couple months ago,
I'd gotten word a secret buyer
had purchased the hotel
at six percent over asking.
I think it's safe to assume
that buyer was Ms. Falcone.
But why?
When she got there,
she met with this clown.
The zoning commissioner.
She'd have to have had his approval
for the wall and gate she built.
She's making alliances
with politicians.
Building a fortress.
All the while she's pretending
to be my friend...
she's been planning a war.
Victor, we will be having a chat
with Ms. Falcone.
Just so we're clear,
is this a chat-chat?
Or a shovel-in-the-trunk
kind of chat?
Get the shovel.
Maybe I should rent an apartment
with all this money we're making?
Do you have any openings
in your building?
You know what, what you should be
doing with your winnings
is finding yourself a neurologist.
- Which I am not.
- It has to be you.
You know me, Lee, you know what
this coconut is truly capable of.
Which is why my answer is no.
I know about your clinic.
I'm guessing
that Cherry lets you keep that,
as long as you work these fights.
That's the deal that you have, right?
So?
So I'm guessing that, that means
something to you.
Which makes you vulnerable to...
to...
- Blackmail?
- Yes.
- Threats?
- Yes. Both of those.
All right, so, let's hear it.
- What's your brilliant scheme?
- What?
You said you wanted to force me
to help you, so, what is your threat?
Hit me.
If you don't help me,
I am going to...
do something to that clinic.
Oh, my God, you really aren't smart.
Jim?
Nakajima?
Sit tight, buddy, we're going
to get you out of here.
Grenade!
Run!
Harvey!
Detective James Gordon.
I hope you don't mind if I say,
I'm tickled pink to meet you.
I would shake your hand,
if it were possible.
I'm a big fan.
Big, big fan.
Great. My biggest fan is a pig.
Tell me where Harvey Bullock is.
Oh, that dirty pig?
Why do you waste your time with him?
He's holding you back.
Or can you not see that?
Never you fret.
He's still alive.
For the time being anyway.
But you, Detective, you,
you are as safe as safe can be.
You a cop?
What?
What makes you think that?
The things you knew.
The routes and schedules
of the cops you killed?
Oh. If I were a policeman,
you could what?
Reason with me?
Appeal to what we have in common?
Well, Jim, may I call you, Jim?
Jim, that's exactly
what I was going to do.
We have nothing in common.
Oh.
I beg to differ, mon frere.
You and I, both, see all too well
the corruption, the filth,
inside the G.C.P.D.
You and I know that Gotham cannot
survive unless the cancer is cut out!
We both share the same mission.
Only I do it
with a little bit more flare!
Killing Penguin's bagmen
won't change anything.
It will for them.
It will, quite a bit.
But in the larger scope,
you're right!
Which is why it doesn't stop there.
Not until I've butchered every single
swine on Penguin's payroll!
That could be half the department.
I never said it would be pretty.
Oh, it's the same old story.
No one wants to see
how the sausage is made
but once it is made,
isn't it delicious?
Bite?
You're delusional.
You're not doing this for Gotham.
You're doing it
for your own demented reasons.
My reasons are as real
as they come, Jim.
I have suffered profound loss
at the hands of greedy pigs in power.
Pro-found.
Then tell me.
Let me help make it right.
- Without all this...
- Jim!
Oops! Got to go.
Jim, where are you?
Never you fear, Detective,
you and I, we'll meet anon.
Don't you touch him!
Harvey!
Jim?
Backup's coming!
Harvey!
You heard Gordon, you freak!
Backup's on the way!
You got one chance to run.
Lies from a liar.
They would have been here by now.
Besides, we both know,
Captain Bullock, you deserve this.
Harvey!
I do hate to cut and run.
- Oopsie-daisy!
- Hold on, partner.
Hold on, buddy. Hold on.
You're going to be all right.
- Jim...
- You're going to be all right.
I promise you.
You're going to be all right.
Come on. Come on, buddy.
Come on, pal.
I can't miss any more work.
- They'll fire me.
- It's okay.
I'm going to put you on strong
antibiotics, okay?
Come on!
Oswald, I didn't know
you were coming over.
I thought I'd surprise you.
I'm sorry I had to cancel lunch
yesterday.
It was unavoidable.
You have to let me make it up to you.
How about now?
I was actually on my way out.
Oh?
Where to?
This is going to sound strange
but I can't tell you.
Not yet.
I, I want it to be a surprise.
The thing is...
cat's out of the bag.
- I don't understand?
- I know what you're doing!
The old Heritage Hotel?
The fortress from which you're going
to attack me!
What? No!
Oh, so you weren't pretending
to be my friend
while building your power base?
I should've known.
But your, your father's blood
definitely runs through your veins.
Luckily, not for long.
Oswald, you're making a mistake.
I'm your friend.
We'll see, won't we?
Now, let's go see
what you're building.
I can't wait.
Barkeep!
- Another grasshopper!
- Those won't help.
All right. Give me your money.
- What?
- The money you made.
Well, that he made. Give it to me.
I don't make any promises
but I'll see what I can do.
Lee, Lee... I just got to know.
Why did you change your mind?
- Is it my charisma?
- Close.
You asked what I was doing
in a place like this.
I didn't want to be here.
I didn't want to be anywhere
near Gotham.
I left. But I couldn't stay away.
Because the Tetch virus,
it hit the Narrows harder
than anywhere else.
- So?
It was my fault.
Jim tried to stop the virus
and I didn't let him.
I was infected but none the less,
I was there.
I don't have a choice.
- I have to be here.
- Wow.
If you wanted to blackmail me,
by the way, what you should have done
was taken advantage
of Grundy being popular.
Threatened to take him away
and then Cherry, afraid of losing her
star, would've forced me to help you.
Come by the clinic tomorrow.
We'll get started.
Bye, pretty lady.
Ed's going to be smart again.
Ed going to be smart?
Ed's going to be very smart.
It's okay, Charlie.
Oswald?
I want you to know, I forgive you.
Boss?
What is this?
What's happening?
Kids.
You started an orphanage?
I wanted to surprise you next week.
When everything was finished.
I... I...
Children, back inside please.
Oswald, I want you to know
I understand the pressure you face.
Your very survival depends on seeing
everyone as a potential threat.
And I watched my father bear
that weight for years.
I don't want you to end up like him.
Sofia, please, forgive me.
How can I?
When I've already forgiven you.
But you do owe me one thing.
Anything.
Lunch.
How do you feel about mac and cheese?
I love it.
Hey.
You gave me quite the scare back
there.
How you feeling?
I've had better days.
Doc says you're going to be okay.
No one shows but he knows.
Pyg?
Son of a bitch.
He could've killed me but he cut me
just deep enough to make you choose.
Go after him,
or save my worthless hide.
It wasn't a choice.
Either way, l owe you.
So pay it back now.
Tell me the truth.
How long you been taking money
from Penguin?
You knew Metzger was the bagman.
You knew Nakajima was dirty.
The Pyg says all this stuff
about you deserving to be killed.
I don't know
why I didn't see it before.
Maybe I didn't want to.
I just need to know how long...
are we talking years?
No.
Just since this license crap started.
The commissioner ordered us
to comply.
Then Metzger started showing up with
these envelopes stuffed full of cash.
I didn't do nothing
I wouldn't have done anyway.
You got to understand, Jim,
the bills I got, the debts I got...
It stops.
Stops now.
Gotham city on high alert.
Gotham finds itself gripped by terror
in the hands of a ritualistic cop
killer, being called Professor Pyg.
He is still at large
after evading the police.
The G.C.P.D are urging people
to remain calm
and to report any suspicious activity
to G.C.P.D Central Command.
"Two mother pigs lived in a pen.
They each had four piglets
and that made ten.
All the piglets loved to play.
And they rolled and they rolled,
in the mud all day.
At night, with their mothers,
curled up in a heap...
they squealed and they squealed
until they went...
to sleep."
And sleep well,
for tomorrow the axe shall fall.