Previously on Gotham...
We're onto you, Professor Strange.
Bad guys come in.
Monsters come out.
I am Firefly.
Selina.
Hugo Strange has Selina.
You remember your name?
My name is Fish Mooney.
Make me a grilled cheese sandwich.
You made me a sandwich.
- Why?
- I don't know.
And how exactly do you plan
on getting into Arkham?
- I'll ask for a tour.
- From the man
that ordered the assassination
of your father?
He'll want to find out what we know.
And we won't see me and
Lucius as a threat.
I call Bullock, he comes busting
in with a hundred cops.
Take them.
Move everything you can
to the facility upstate.
You have an explosive device, use it.
Destroy Indian Hill.
Basil is a chameleon of sorts.
Would you like to see?
You son of a bitch!
I'm Jim Gordon.
Right, go get our guys.
No sign of Gordon.
How long do you want us to wait?
Give him ten seconds.
If you don't see Jim, bust
that joint open and find him.
Ready, entry team. We go on one.
Go.
Cover me.
Go! Go!
Four, three,
two...
Stand down!
- Stand down, Officers.
- Hold!
Hold!
Stand down.
- All clear.
- Stand down! Stand down!
"All clear"?
Sorry to waste your time, hoss.
How about a ride to HQ?
Sure thing, Jim.
You okay?
You look kind of hinky.
Never better.
Strange! Strange!
Strange!
Strange, you son of a bitch!
Come back here!
So...
you're really doing this?
Not my call.
Prepare the patients for transport
to the upstate facility.
If even one of your patients
were to escape... They won't.
The police won't be delayed much longer.
Prepare the patients and move fast.
As soon as we're done
with Gordon and Wayne,
we will detonate the bomb.
Yes, sir.
DESTRUCTION PROTOCOL READY
www.TUSUBTITULO.com
-DIFUNDE LA CULTURA-
Okay...
quiz kids,
who's ready to play
Life or Death?
Sir, Mr. Nygma.
You are Nygma, aren't you?
This is absurd.
The police know we're here.
You can't kill us!
Are you ready to play?!
Yes.
Good.
You have one guess.
Five minutes to talk it over.
Who runs Indian Hill?
You have one guess.
Think carefully, fellas.
Answer correctly...
or die.
Strange!
Strange?
Hi.
What is that?
Honesty serum.
I need to know what you know.
Wait.
Wait!
So, how do you feel now?
Not good.
Can you be more specific?
I feel vulnerable.
Naked.
Your feelings are
entirely natural and normal.
There is nothing to be ashamed of.
You are in a helpless situation.
There is nothing
you can do.
Do you understand that?
Yes.
No.
No?
What can you do?
James, what can you do?
Made a plan.
Tell me your plan.
If I don't check in
with the GCPD by noon,
tell them I'm safe,
they'll come after you.
Yes.
Yes, I know.
You did check in with the GCPD.
Nobody's coming.
You can relax.
Jim?
Harv.
Strange is clean?
What the hell happened?
Dead end.
"Dead end"?
What are you talking about, "dead end"?
He's connected.
So is my mechanic. Who isn't?
Connected to people we can't cross.
What people?
You don't want to know.
Trust me.
You feeling all right?
You look like a sack of fish.
A little flu, maybe.
Well, then keep your distance.
I'm getting laid this
weekend, fingers crossed.
You have 60 seconds left.
Who runs Indian Hill?
I say Hugo Strange.
Wayne Enterprises.
Wayne Enterprises runs Indian Hill.
- That's surmise.
- Why would he ask that question
if the answer was obvious?
He wants to know what we know.
What we think we know.
Which is Wayne Enterprises.
Is that your answer?
Running out of time here.
Yes.
Correct!
Wayne Enterprises runs Indian Hill.
Bravo, Brucie.
You're almost safe.
Just one more question.
- You ready?
- Yes.
You have five minutes, quiz kids.
Answer correctly or die.
Wayne Enterprises runs
Indian Hill, but who runs
Wayne Enterprises?
Move 'em out in order
of security grades.
Lowest risk first.
Tranq 'em, immobilize them,
and put them on the bus.
And do it fast but very,
very carefully.
Security is our number one
priority.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, lady.
Busy day, busy day.
We'll get to you, Number 13.
Your mama may be Number 13,
but I'm a human being.
Fish Mooney, bitch.
Here you're Re-Animant
Test Case Number 13,
and I'm Ms. Peabody.
And you'd best not talk about my mama.
Ms. Peabody,
I apologize.
I'm a bit stressed.
I don't like being locked up.
It's against my nature.
I understand. I do.
But you are a priceless
scientific miracle.
You are history.
Seclusion is regrettable
but inevitable.
Look, I've been here before.
All you mad scientists say
the same kind of stuff.
I don't care.
Let me go.
Sorry, 13.
Let's go.
You're messing with the wrong woman!
You hear me?
The wrong woman!
Here?
A little too central, maybe.
You don't want one piece
to overpower the room.
Try over there.
You're absolutely right.
See? I told you she'd be useful.
Isn't that better?
Interior design ain't my thing.
News on the hour with WTGC.
Police sources say that
reports of an impending raid
on Arkham Insane Asylum and
its controversial chief,
Professor Hugo Strange, are inaccurate.
Despite the disclaimers, flurries
of police activity around
the troubled facility
- have fueled rumors that
arrests are imminent... - Hugo
Strange.
How interesting.
Answer quickly, please, Jim.
Without thinking. Who did
you love more, your
mother or your father?
Mother.
Why?
I resented my father's strength.
I see. Yes.
And when he died...
Yes.
...how did you feel?
Guilty.
For a car crash? Why?
It was not your fault.
I imagined he was gone. And then he was.
You lost a child recently.
Yes.
How does that make you feel?
Guilty.
Guilt again.
You blame yourself?
It was my fault.
Oh. Oh, I see. I didn't know that.
And what happened to the mother?
- Lee, was it?
- She's...
down south somewhere.
You still love her?
Yes.
You want to be with her?
Why aren't you with her?
I've put her through enough pain.
Jim, I need you to relax.
Close your eyes.
Imagine that I am God.
All-powerful.
I am God,
and I absolve you
of all of your guilt.
I put that guilt on you,
and now...
I take it away.
It's gone.
Your burdens are gone.
So how do you feel?
Good.
Better.
Good, good.
Jim...
now that we're relaxed
and speaking honestly, tell me:
what do you know about our
work here at Indian Hill?
You're building monsters
for military use.
Oh, we're doing much more
than that, but for who?
Who owns Indian Hill?
Wayne Enterprises.
And who controls Wayne Enterprises
behind the scenes?
Who controls
everything in Gotham...
behind the scenes?
I don't know.
The rich?
Oh, they are rich, I'm sure.
But can you be more specific?
Who controls Gotham, Jim?
You've never heard of a...
...secret council?
Secret council?
No.
Excellent.
Thank you.
That's what I needed to know.
Professor Strange?
Yes, Jim?
What you said about Lee.
I should have gone after her.
Oh, no doubt.
Guilt has compelled you
to sacrifice your heart
to your conscience.
But guilt
is useless.
Love, Jim.
Love is our guide.
Time's up, I'm afraid.
In the spirit of intimacy and honesty,
I have been speaking about your life
as if it had a future.
And...
that is not so.
You have a few hours.
You have
30 seconds left.
Who runs Wayne Enterprises?
Oh, the devil, maybe.
Is that the deal? Communists? Witches?
No. There's some truth
behind this question.
Some big secret.
I've worked for Wayne
Enterprises for ten years...
there is no big secret.
The board of directors
runs Wayne Enterprises.
15 seconds.
That can't be the answer, Lucius.
Ten seconds.
Give us more time!
Five seconds!
The board of directors.
Incorrect.
Oh, what a shame.
The correct answer is...
Sorry, fellas. You lose.
And what happens to losers?
Yowzah!
Death by poison gas!
Jim.
Hi.
Are we alive?
So far, so good.
Had to be sure... I
thought we were dead.
That was unpleasant.
How are things going for you?
We've had a hell of a time.
The same.
You okay?
I'm a little groggy.
He drugged me.
Made me talk.
About Wayne Enterprises, right?
About everything.
Bruce...
I never should have
made that oath to you.
- That's not really...
- I was arrogant and naive...
and I'm sorry.
I've tried to do the right thing, but...
what a fool I've been.
What kind of drugs did they give you?
Well done, Ed. I'm impressed.
You are a shaman of sorts.
- A witch doctor.
- So, just between us,
who does run Wayne Enterprises?
I could tell you, but then...
I would have to lobotomize you.
Gotcha.
So, moving forward, sir, I
would be more than happy
to help you with any
of your other cases.
You would be a wonderful
addition to my staff, Ed,
a wonderful addition,
if you were only sane.
- No, seriously...
- Yes, seriously.
You have been very useful,
and we arrogant physicians
have much to learn from a madman
like you.
But not that much.
No! No, no, no, no!
You will not treat me
like a crazy person!
No!
Madam, I bring good news.
Gordon and Wayne and Fox know
nothing but mundanities.
They have told no one the truth,
because they have none of the truth.
Our secret is safe.
Kill them all, then continue
with the evacuation of
your test subjects.
Yes, madam.
The destruction of Indian Hill
may proceed as scheduled.
Releasing Galavan was a
grave error on your part.
No more of your patients
will see the light of day
under any circumstances,
at any cost.
I understand, madam.
T*U*S*U*B*T*I*T*U*L*O*.*C*O*M*
These people to whom
Strange is connected,
they must be pretty heavy...
to make you back off.
Oh, they're heavy.
I don't want anything dangerous..
I just like being titillated.
Seriously, you don't wanna know.
Remember the time you called
me from the hospital
when you had Falcone on the gurney,
and the whole town and their uncle
were looking to kill you both?
- How could I forget?
- Remember what I said
to you on the phone?
Remember what I said?
I forget.
That's funny.
Gordon, you're back. What happened?
Where's Master Bruce? Where's Lucius?
Where are they?!
Have you seen them?
Hey, Alfred, take it easy.
- Where are they?
- Alfred...
Alfred...
relax.
Master Bruce and Lucius are...
headed back to Wayne Manor.
Yeah, well, that's a load of hot
tosh for starters, isn't it?
- I've just come back from there.
- What can I tell ya?
Maybe they... stopped to get a snack.
So, what about Strange?
It's complicated.
Well, go on, then! What?!
Complicated police business!
He's got a touch of the flu.
You.
How you doing?
Middling. What's your deal?
Chillin'.
They're gonna blow this dump sky-high
and the whole circus is moving upstate.
When?
Soon. Like, an hour.
- Can you escape?
- 'Course.
Firefly thinks I'm her sidekick,
so I got trusty status.
Then please do so. Get out
of here and call the police.
- I'll do what I like.
- I led you
into this mess... I was self-righteous
and arrogant and manipulative.
- I used you, and I'm sorry.
- Like you can use me.
I got you wrapped around my pinky.
Always have.
Be that as it may...
if you can escape, do it.
Manipulative.
As if.
What'd she say?
She'll do what she likes.
And there's a bomb.
Hello, number 13.
Stay calm.
No one's going to hurt you.
It's time to go on a trip.
Give me your right arm.
Say my name.
Fish Mooney.
That's right.
What's your name?
Ethel Peabody.
Ethel...
you seem sad
and anxious.
- You got that right.
- You let me out of here...
and I'll be your friend.
Oh, no, no,
no, no, no,
no, no, no.
Interesting. Ms. Peabody,
what are you doing?
What she says.
Why?
I don't know.
Miss Mooney,
you have special talents.
Some form of psychotropic
chemical agent on your skin, I imagine.
You're marvelous.
Yes, truly marvelous.
Always was.
Indeed.
Would love to chat about me,
but we have a bus to catch.
Ah, no, Miss Mooney,
if you and the others on that bus
were to appear in public,
it would cause a
revolution, an apocalypse.
I simply can't allow you
to just walk out of here.
Watch me.
Oh, please, don't go.
Please, you're breaking my heart.
I love you like my own daughter.
No one could love you more,
but I will have to kill
you before I let you go.
Please, choose
life.
You would have made a great pimp.
No, no, no, no.
No, no, no!
Bring him back.
Hugo...
I order you
to stop...
now.
Stop...
now!
You hear me?
DESTRUCTION PROTOCOL READY
ARMED
Security systems activated.
No!
Tried calling about a thousand times.
Still no answer.
Strange has him, I'm positive.
Holy crap,
are you still here? I told you
a thousand times
Strange is clean.
You in charge of that, are you?
It's strange, though, isn't it?
I mean,
strange they're MIA.
That's funny.
- Strange.
- Funny?
You know, maybe I should send
the strike force back into Arkham,
- have a little look see.
- No, no, no.
You don't want to do that.
Bad idea. Trust me.
That's a terrible idea.
How long you known me?
All right,
if you're good, I guess I'm good.
I don't know who's
got to you, Gordon,
but you're just, just...
...weird.
Hey, Alfred.
Miss Kean.
How's the butling business?
To what do we owe the...
Jimmy, my love,
I'm sure you're ever so busy,
but could we have a word in private?
You bet.
Well, you look terrible.
Gee, thanks, Barbara.
You look pretty good.
Shucks.
Question: what the hell is
going on down at Arkham?
Two questions back at you, gorgeous.
Why you asking, and...
what's in it for me?
I'm asking because a dear friend of mine
wants to know the answer,
and what would you like
to be in it for you?
Hey, spring is here, baby.
So, now you like me again?
What's not to like?
So, you've forgotten about Lee.
Lee?
Lee Thompkins.
Nah, screw that ho.
Water under the bridge.
You're not Jim.
Say what now?
You're not Jim!
Hold on there, woman.
Holy mother of saints.
Kill the captives. We have to go.
Where are we going?
What's the hurry?
Silence.
Freeze, get it done.
Jeez, relax.
What's with him?
Quiet!
Quiet yourself.
Why do you have to kill them?
Why are you so mean?
I knew I shouldn't have spared you.
Freeze, kill her.
Wait a minute!
I'm sorry, Firefly.
I told you she was an experiment.
But she's my friend. I need her.
We don't have time for this.
Please, don't let him hurt me.
Firefly...
...please, help me.
Don't you dare.
Out of the way, sparky.
Make me.
Firefly, no.
No!
What now?
Sounds like warfare.
What's going on?
Simple psychology.
Been waiting for the right moment.
You coming or what?
15 minutes to detonation.
Strange.
Strange!
Wake up.
Strange.
Strange!
Alpha and Charlie squads to Arkham.
Bravo and Delta to Indian Hill.
Move!
Hey, Penguin, so it turns out our Mr.
Strange is a very bad man.
The police are on to him now.
They figure he's planning
to run, but he won't.
Thanks to me.
Thank you, Barbara.
You have pleased me.
Saddle up, Butch,
we've got an old friend to catch.
Wake up, Strange.
I know you're in there.
Wake up!
Oh, Gordon.
I surmise my plan must have gone awry.
You could say. I'm gonna
stand you up now,
and you're gonna give us a
tour of your secret lab.
No.
You don't have a choice.
It's this way, right?
No, we can't go down there.
I set a bomb.
The lab is going to blow up.
We have to get out of here!
In ten minutes,
everything within a quarter
mile radius will be dust.
That's madness.
If you want to live...
which I do, frankly...
we had better leave.
We detected a radioactive
material down there.
You got it out first, right?
There wasn't enough time.
They forced my hand,
but I calculated the chances of
a radioactive cloud is fairly low.
If you're wrong, thousands
of people could die.
Yes, yes, yes,
but paying that price will be better
than releasing what's down there.
How do we shut it down?
The security walls
are up. The lab is sealed.
There must be some way in.
We have to go!
We have to leave now!
Tell me how to get that
bomb and shut it off
or I'll batter you to death right here!
In which case,
young man,
I suppose I will just have to die.
Wait, Nygma knows a way down there.
Could use some help.
Yeah.
You two,
you've got nine minutes.
Get as far away from here as you can.
No.
Go, go!
Lucius, this way.
Yes, of course, I know how,
but what is with all the hoo-ha?
What is the rush here?
Just do it.
What do I get if I do it?
You get to live.
Fair enough.
Security system is deactivated.
You any good at defusing bombs?
I don't know yet.
You?
Two minutes to detonation.
Oh, my.
Got any ideas?
You got a knife?
No.
ARMED
We're on a rush to Arkham
for patient evacuation.
We got bomb squad in set.
What now?
You're asking me?
How about if we just...
pull all this stuff off.
See what happens.
There's no cutoff program, maybe,
maybe there's no
tamper-proofing program.
Yeah.
No.
Water.
Need water.
What's going on? Hello?
45 seconds.
15 seconds.
Please.
I need water.
Water.
Hello!
Hello! Guys!
What's going on?
Hello!
Where are my people?
Y-you don't understand.
We have to find my people.
There will be...
There will be consequences.
You heroic son of a bitch.
A nuclear bomb?
You'll never guess what took us so long.
Problem.
Whatever was down there,
Whoever was down there at Indian Hill,
they're not there anymore.
Couple of squad cars are
in pursuit of a bus
that left the Indian Hills compound.
That's got to be them.
That bus cannot get away.
This is Unit 12.
In pursuit of Arkham bus
heading south along the D Line.
...Unit 12.
We'll pick 'em up at the next block.
Get ready.
Don't have much space here.
It's in civilian traffic ahead.
He's blocked in.
We'll do at the cross street.
Nothing. I'll check up ahead.
Car 32 to Captain Bullock.
Heading east toward Pettsburg.
Damn, damn, damn.
What's on that bus, Jim?
Tell me what's on the bus?
Monsters.
Come on. Monsters?
Hugo Strange would rather destroy
half the city than let them out.
And now they're out.
Code Red.
Code Red. All units Pettsburg Highway.
All units be on the lookout
for the Indian Hill bus
on Pettsburg Highway.
Captain Bullock, I've
got eyes on the bus.
Under the South Burnside Expressway.
Well, then stop the damn thing.
Don't let it get away.
Come to mama.
Professor Strange!
Professor Strange.
Come out.
Strange. We need to talk.
You did a very bad thing to me.
And now you're going to pay.
Impossible.
Nothing...
is impossible.
Holy...
No.
This city's in deep trouble
if we don't find that bus.
So let's find it.
Yes, sir.
I want squadrons of 20
in these quadrants here.
I want choppers in the air,
and I want tac units on all
the East Side bridges.
Bruce.
I have to go.
I might not see you for a while,
but I'll try to stay in touch.
Where are you going?
I have to find Lee.
Right move, mate.
Do me a favor.
Say good-bye to Bullock for me.
I don't really want the
whole Celtic farewell.
He's gonna have his hands full,
but I think he can handle it.
Will do.
Chocolates.
Girls like chocolates.
I'll keep that in mind.
Well, there's a man who's got
his priorities straight.
The love of a good woman and all that.
Well,
I hope you learned your
lesson, Master Bruce.
And that's the end of your
adventures with the police?
There's a secret council, Alfred.
A secret council that runs
everything in Gotham.
Oh, bloody hell.
It's them that wanted me dead.
We're so close, Alfred, we're so
close to the ultimate truth.
Oh, bloody hell.
Hey, don't look at me.
Right.
Jim! Hey.
Hey. Where you going?
Hey.
We got monsters to find.
And you'll find them. I have to go.
But this city's in danger.
You got this. I know you do.
And I have more important things to do.
- But...
- And Harvey,
Yeah?
You're the boss now.
Maybe get a haircut?
That's my car.
That's-that's my car!
Hey! Jim!
Help. Help.
Oh, those poor souls.
H-hello?
Hello?
Thank you.
www.TUSUBTITULO.com
-DIFUNDE LA CULTURA-