Previously on Gotham...
Alfred.
- The manor.
- It's my fault.
Mr. Cobblepot.
This never would have happened
if you stayed with me!
You're having a baby
with Barbara.
You don't think I'm fit
- to be a mother?
- What do you think?
- You're leaving Gotham.
- I believe the time
has come for a change
of scenery.
You found a way
out of Gotham?
It's a submarine.
Reunification with
the mainland hangs on
by a thread. Toxic chemicals
rain down onto the city,
and the government
cuts us adrift for good.
Gotham's Golden Rule.
No heroes.
Watch out for him.
He thinks he's a white knight.
He's a loose cannon.
You two here to pick up
your grandchildren?
Come on, Babs.
You got the only full bar
in Gotham.
And if you two dinosaurs want
to keep coming here,
you better up your intel.
We got a lead on
some black market heating oil.
♪ I've got a sickness... ♪
One drink.
To share.
Then you can go wheeze to death
somewhere else.
♪ I called a doctor ♪
♪ Said he can't do nothing
for me ♪
Would you look at that?
Dix! Look at you,
up and walking around,
you old son
of a bitch.
I've been looking for you two
for a while now.
Well, you found us.
You two ever think
about the past?
What we did?
What are you talking
about, Dix?
About her.
About what we did
to the girl.
Who is that? It is like
the living dead in here.
Enough of this.
Hey, Gramps!
Oh!
♪ Hot chills ♪
♪ Sweat rag ♪
♪ Sweat... hot. ♪
Can you please repeat
your story for Mr. Wayne, madam?
We live in the shelter
on West End.
There are so many of us
crammed in there.
Uh...
so much uncertainty,
fear.
And with the river poisoned,
it should've been awful,
but... people came together,
made it a home.
What happened?
Couple
of weeks ago, we...
heard rumors about something
underneath the building...
...where it connects
to the sewer.
Then people
started going missing.
Hank, my husband,
wanted to look for them.
Said we were a family.
So the two of you
went searching for them.
It was so dark.
I didn't see
what attacked us.
I hit my head.
And when I woke up,
Hank was gone.
Please, Mr. Wayne.
We have a daughter.
We'll do everything
we can.
Should we tell
Gordon?
He's stretched
thin as it is.
Alfred, we don't know who
or what is down there.
We know there's a man
down there, in danger,
and we know this
lady sent for us.
So go on, then. What do
you think we should do?
Let's go find him.
Under normal circumstances,
I wouldn't call you
for a couple of stiffs.
What do you normally do
when a couple of your patrons
- get stabbed?
- Bury the bodies.
Find out who did it and
then bury those bodies.
See, that's not something
you should be telling a cop.
We're living
in a different world, Harvey.
So why did you call us?
Take a look.
Boggs and Lewis.
You know them?
They were cops.
They were gone
before you joined.
- What happened?
- They came around,
peddling third-rate intel.
It was closing time,
so I let 'em in.
And then some other fossil
knifed them.
You saw him?
Yeah, he must've snuck in.
Looked like a cop, too.
These two knew him.
Bartender said
they called him
Micks... Hicks...
Dix?
Maybe.
No way.
Dix was Harvey's
old partner.
Well, there we go.
Case closed.
So you're telling me this guy
rolled in here in a wheelchair,
stabbed these two,
and rolled on out?
He wasn't in a wheelchair.
Then it couldn't be Dix.
He's been paralyzed
for the last 15 years.
Harvey, you're confusing me
with someone who cares.
I called you as a courtesy.
And now I'm wishing
I just dumped these two
corpses in an alley.
Do we even know
if Dix is still in Gotham
after the bridges blew?
I heard he moved into an
apartment about a year ago.
I meant to check up on him,
but... it can't be him.
I hear what you're saying,
but we should still talk to him.
Maybe he knows something.
Fine.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine. Thanks for asking.
Look,
I've been giving you space,
but we have to talk
about how this is gonna work.
I'm gonna be a part
of this kid's life.
Oh, you seem pretty confident
about that.
I am.
Reunification's gonna happen.
You should think
about what kind of person
you want to be when it does.
It's a chance
for you to start anew.
I like who I am.
Uh-huh.
You were due hours ago.
Yes, I was.
But I had to get us lunch.
- And I met Dale.
- I see that.
Do you see this?
Our secret plan
to get off this island.
Relax.
Dale is
completely trustworthy.
How do you know we can trust him
if you just met him?
Because he's mute
and dumb as a post.
Look, I know you're paranoid
about people watching us.
Someone is watching us!
Why do you think I installed
this alarm system?
And as safe as I feel
with your jingle bell
contraption in place,
I went out
and procured us some muscle.
You're welcome.
At least
you're doing something.
Ah.
How's my SS Gertrud
- coming along?
- Our submarine
is coming along
just fine, thank you.
I've been working
on the sonar,
which, turns out, is...
far more complex
than I anticipated.
Well, I am confident
you will figure it out.
Of course I will figure it out.
Because I figure
everything out.
The navigation system.
The oxygen exchange.
I will figure everything out,
because I'm the
only one working!
This was supposed
to be a partnership.
It is!
I already did my part
by stealing everything valuable
in Gotham,
of which you get half!
No!
Your goons stole it,
and then you killed 'em.
Are you expecting someone?
Who would I be
expecting, Oswald?
I told you
someone's watching us.
Dale, go do
what I pay you for.
Protect us!
Wait!
Penn?
Hello, Mr. Cobblepot.
Are you...
are you really... I...
I-I don't believe it.
Y-You're alive.
Indeed, sir.
I-I am.
But you-you were shot.
I-I was there.
This whole time,
I thought you were dead,
but you're alive!
You're only coming to me now?!
I-I'm so terribly sorry,
Mr. Cobblepot.
I wanted to come see you, but...
he wouldn't let me.
"He"?
"He" who?
Mr. Cobblepot...
...this...
is...
...Mr. Scarface.
Wonderful.
Look,
I'm sure Dix is in the clear,
but we do have
to ask.
That's not it.
I just...
I feel bad.
I should've been by before.
I'm all he's got.
Well, look,
what can you
do, right?
Dix!
What the hell?!
Bullock? That you?
Yeah!
Don't shoot!
Okay.
Come in.
Uh-huh.
Is that the way
you always answer a door?
Nowadays, you can't
be too careful.
Especially someone like me.
A kid comes in,
he'd cut my throat
for a cup of soup.
Uh-huh.
Anyway, I
wasn't expecting you.
Figured you forgot about me.
Look, partner,
when the bridges came down,
I got busy and...
Oh, sure, sure.
You forgot me.
Everybody forgets.
I didn't forget.
Planning on taking a trip?
Maybe.
I like to keep a bag
packed, just in case.
Yeah? Where were
you last night?
Where was I?
I was right here.
Anybody else
here with you?
Anybody that can
back up your story?
You're asking me
if I was out there killing
Boggs and Lewis?
Does it look like I was out
there killing Boggs and Lewis?
So you heard
about that?
Let me tell you something.
If it meant
that I can get out of
this son of a bitch wheelchair,
I would confess right here
and now to Boggs, to Lewis,
to anybody you want me
to confess to.
All right, fine.
But you were a detective.
What would you say
if you were us?
We come in here, you're
packing a suitcase.
I would say either I did it,
which I didn't,
or I'd be very worried
that I'd be next.
What do you mean,
you being next?
What's your connection
to Boggs and Lewis?
Come on. What?
Nothing. I just worked
with them. That's it.
We, uh... we worked
a case together.
The four of you?
Yeah.
Dix wasn't my partner then.
I was a rookie cop.
Wet behind the ears.
So what was the case?
Woman killed her husband.
As far as I can remember,
it was pretty open and shut.
But at least we can agree
that Dix didn't walk
into The Sirens
and stab those two guys.
So who did? Barbara said Boggs
and Lewis recognized the killer.
They called him "Dix."
We come in here, he's packing
a suitcase, he shoots at us.
This stinks, Harvey.
Hey.
You all right?
What the hell?
These basements run
along Gotham's sewers.
The river is right next to it.
You mean the river filled
with Jeremiah's toxins?
Who knows what kind of damage
these chemicals could do?
Yeah, you're right.
Just don't you touch anything.
Hold on.
Oh.
Bite marks.
Animal?
Well, it's no human
I've ever seen.
Whatever it was...
...it dragged him that way.
Seems like human skin.
Here's the file you asked for.
Victoria Cartwright.
- How'd you, uh...?
- I had Harper
run every case the
four of you worked,
cross-referenced with any woman
that killed her husband.
Do I need to read it, or are
you gonna tell me what's in it?
Victoria Cartwright
was a banker.
She led a very boring life.
Until she snapped and
put two.38 caliber slugs
into her husband.
End of story.
You guys
rehearse that?
Says there was no
physical evidence.
She was convicted
on the statement
of her seven-year-old
daughter, Jane.
This was 20 years ago.
Where's Jane now?
What's the point?
The killer's a man.
A man that can
imitate friggin' faces.
What was the name
of the guy that Strange
got to imitate you?
A Basil something?
That's who
we should be looking for.
That was different, and you
know it. Do we have an address
- for this Jane?
- No.
But the family's old home
is in the Green Zone,
- just east of the clinic.
- Jim, it's a dead end.
Is there anything else
you want to tell me?
You know what? Why
don't you hang back?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait.
You benching me?
Killer's still out there.
Keep an eye on your partner.
Penn. Arnold.
It's... Arthur.
You're holding a doll.
It's not a doll.
It's a dummy.
Oh, this is great.
I'm going
back to work.
- Excuse me.
- You're saying
he made you come here?
Mr. Scarface is very persuasive.
Persuasive?
He made me tell him
about your...
treasure.
Penn...
I think you need a rest.
And perhaps a psychiatrist.
Then we can discuss
you resuming your former duties.
Obviously, I won't pay you
for the time you were gone.
Shut your piehole!
This the one
you were telling me about?
Punk who thinks
he's in charge?
Yes, sir.
That's Mr. Cobblepot.
Oswald, if you don't
make him leave, I will.
- Yeah.
- No one's going anywheres.
Penn,
show these dewdroppers
we're serious.
Forgive me.
Now, let's
talk turkey...
turkeys.
- What a mess, huh?
- Yeah.
Boggs and Lewis were idiots,
complete idiots.
They should've known when
they see a guy walking,
that it ain't me.
You think the Cartwright girl
said something?
How would I know?
So, how you been
since the bridges came down?
You getting enough food?
Medicine?
What if I said "no"?
I'd feel like crap.
Then no.
The Cartwright girl is dead.
A buddy of mine,
who was a screw
over at Arkham, he said
she was an inmate there, and
she died a couple of years ago,
so this has nothing
to do with her.
GCPD!
Coming in.
Check upstairs.
Looks like
this place
has been abandoned since
before the bridges came down.
Yeah.
What the hell?
What the hell was that?
Someone's been living here.
What's that smell?
Everything all right?
All good. No one's here.
Hey!
No.
Don't look at me!
We found
your handiwork.
Nothing to say?
You're gonna have to
take that mask off.
The only way you're gonna keep
that mask on is if you talk.
Otherwise,
I'm gonna reach over this table,
and I'm gonna
rip it off of your face.
Who are you?
Nobody.
You're not Jane Cartwright?
Because you were
in her childhood home.
You're about the right age.
Talk to me, Jane.
I know after
your mother
was convicted, you ended up
a ward of the state.
In and out of institutions
until you ended up in Arkham.
Then you vanished.
Some say died.
What happened to you?
Me?
Nothing happened to me.
Okay.
What happened to Jane?
Oh.
Lots happened to Jane.
She was taken from Arkham.
Down, down...
down, the doctor
did things to her,
experiments on her and others.
You're talking
about Hugo Strange?
You were taken
to Indian Hill?
The professor was obsessed
with the power to change.
The way a chameleon
would change its skin.
He wanted humans
to have that power.
He made it so Jane
could change her skin...
her bones, her hair,
the color of her eyes.
All it takes is a single touch,
and her body becomes a mirror.
When it's done, she sheds
her skin and starts anew.
It remembers
everyone it touched.
It's touched you, Detective.
We can help you,
Ms. Cartwright.
Jane Cartwright is dead.
She died in Arkham.
That's when Jane Doe was born.
So why kill all these cops?
Do you want to know
why they died?
Ask your friend.
♪♪
What is that?
Aw.
We should head out.
My battery's dying.
Please.
He's coming. He's coming.
Who's coming?
What happened?
He's going to kill me.
I barely got away.
Are you Hank?
Yes.
Your wife sent us.
Is anyone else left alive
down here?
They're all dead.
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, God.
Hank!
Hank! Hold on, Hank!
Hand over the heaters!
If you don't mind.
Mr. Penn, can't we
just talk this through?
Get back!
I'm so sorry.
At least tell me what
happened after Haven.
Help me to
understand...
this.
Go on.
Sing your song.
After I was shot...
I woke up in
the GCPD morgue.
I was alone.
I patched my wounds
as best I could and crawled out.
I hid in a store.
An abandoned magic shop.
That's where
Mr. Scarface found me.
And he told me all about you.
How you used him.
Chewed him up
and spat him out.
Treated him like a palooka!
That's a lie!
Oh, please, Oswald.
It's what you do.
Arnold...
Arthur.
What do you want?
I don't want anything.
But Mr. Scarface, well...
...he wants your treasure.
And...
to be boss.
Really?
The-the dummy wants to be
the boss of Gotham?
Bingo!
Now, give me the key
- to your treasure room.
- Why would I do that?
You're obviously gonna
kill me anyway.
What am I doing?
I'm talking to a doll.
Dummy.
Seriously?
You know what,
Oswald?
Honestly, you
deserve this.
Nobody asked you.
You are
opportunistic,
your loyalty is...
shaky, at best,
and you will hurt anyone,
anyone to get what you want.
I hardly think you're
one to throw stones!
Listen, Penn...
Eyes down here, pal.
Sorry.
Mr. Scarface, I got
a question for you.
Shoot.
After you get your...
tiny wooden hands
on that treasure,
what are you gonna do?
Where are you
gonna go?
People are gonna come
after you eventually.
Then I'll, uh...
I'll take 'em all on!
Yeah.
Show 'em who's boss.
Ah.
You wouldn't
have to do that
if you could get off this
island, now, would you?
What are you doing?
Shut it!
Let the smart one talk.
How do you feel...
about submarines?
What are we doing here?
I just wanted
to take us, uh,
someplace quiet
where we could talk.
We did a bad thing.
Oh, come on, not that again.
We put a killer in jail,
all right?
What do you keep
moping about?
She was guilty.
She got what she deserved.
Drop it.
Did you get what
you deserved?
What?
You made that girl
into a murderer.
Oh, come on.
You...
your friends...
- the kid.
- Come on, you're...
I'm gonna make sure you
never do that again.
Harper, where's Dix?
I saw Bullock
take him in the back.
Barbara. What are
you doing here?
Seems my bartender overheard
the killer say something
before he ice-picked
Harvey's pals.
I thought I'd be a good citizen.
Okay.
"The kid's guilty, too."
The kid.
Listen... what you said before,
about me being a known criminal.
I was on some list your army buddy had.
When the government
rolls in,
am I gonna be arrested?
Honestly,
I don't know.
But that would work out
for you, right?
I go to jail.
You get the baby.
I don't want that.
Is that a promise?
I go straight,
I'm clear?
Stay right here.
Hey, Harvey,
where'd you take Dix?
I didn't take Dix anywhere.
Oh, God. Oh.
She got into your locker.
Must have taken your clothes.
We have to lock
down the GCPD.
Hey, Harvey.
We'll find her.
Come on.
Look at the size of it.
Living down here,
the toxins in the river
must have driven him mad.
Get out of here! Now!
Alfred!
I'm sorry!
Alfred! Stop!
Stop. Stop...
All right, everybody, listen up.
GCPD is now in lockdown.
Nobody goes in or out
unless I say so.
She could look like
anybody by now.
How are we supposed
to find her?
Jim!
Barbara?
What happened?
What do you mean,
what happened?
I've been attacked.
Where'd she go?
Wait a minute.
How do we know
it's really you?
Seriously?
This isn't proof enough?
What the hell?
That's her.
She's the imposter.
Shoot her!
It's me, you idiot.
That sounds like Barbara.
Barbara.
Tell me where we first met.
Don't shoot.
I'm leaving here.
Anyone tries to follow me,
she dies.
Shoot her.
We can't risk it.
Stay back!
Bullock, wait!
I'm fine.
All right,
take her to my office.
Don't let her out of your sight.
Okay.
I cannot believe that you
told him about the sub.
And that you're playing
along with his psychosis.
Obviously,
he was gonna kill you.
I bought us time.
I have an idea.
If you can just keep him busy
and wait for the signal.
Wait, what's the signal?
Quit your jawing.
So...
Mr. Scarface and I
have discussed our options.
And the submarine
sounds like a good plan.
And since we'll need
the smart one
to build this hayburner,
he can keep sucking air.
But Penguin ain't so lucky.
Do it, Penn.
Ventilate that mook.
I'm so sorry, Mr. Cobblepot.
- Oh.
- I wish things would've turned out differently.
Arthur, I want you to listen
to what I'm saying.
You accuse me
of manipulating you,
but what about him?
I never asked you
to kill anybody.
That is true.
Hey.
Think of everything
that we went through together.
Sofia Falcone.
Getting cut off
from the mainland. Starving.
You mean Penn was starving!
Fighting for scraps
while your dog ate steak.
I welcomed you into my home.
And yes,
I was not a good friend.
To you or to anyone.
It's why I'm alone.
But I saw you for what you are,
and I valued that.
That must be worth something.
Applesauce!
You're a liar and a thief.
All you do is take,
take...
Take.
And you never give anything.
You worked me to the bone.
Forced me to be your puppet.
Well, no more.
You hear me?
No more.
Take that. And that.
No.
Mr. Cobblepot.
You freed me.
How can I ever thank you?
Aah!
Why did you do that?
- He wasn't the threat. The dummy was the threat.
- Oswald.
I accept you for the
person that you are.
Just as you accept me for
the cold logician that I am.
That's why this friendship
is great.
And as friends,
I think we can both
agree that that lunatic
had to be stopped.
Perhaps, Edward...
we really are meant
for each other.
Jane.
I know you're up here.
Jane. I knew
you'd be here.
I'm sorry.
It was my job to protect you,
and I let you down.
You made Jane into a killer.
You and your friends. There
have to be consequences.
You killed three men already.
When is it enough?
When you're dead.
Put the gun down!
Shoot me.
You killed Jane years ago,
and you didn't even know it.
Just shoot me.
Let me see your face.
Your real face.
Why?
So you can see
what a monster she is?
Hugo Strange
only destroyed her face.
You destroyed her soul.
Let me see it.
You see?
You see what they did?
Jane...
we can work this out.
Just put the gun down.
The only way this ends is
with one of us dead.
Oh, Hank,
thank God you're alive.
The nurse thinks the man that
attacked us will never recover.
The toxins in the river
have done irreparable damage
to his brain.
I just think it's a
shame we couldn't save
the rest of the people who
went missing, Master Bruce.
We should've went to Gordon
from the start.
- We were reckless.
- Ah, that's nonsense.
We took decisive action.
We saved a man's life.
The people in this city
have suffered, Master Bruce.
They need someone that
will protect them.
I agree.
But there are better ways
to find absolution.
I, um, I don't follow.
What happened to Wayne Manor
wasn't your fault.
I know you've been
blaming yourself.
You didn't destroy our home,
Alfred.
But I feel like I did.
I feel like
I wasn't strong enough
to fight Tetch
or that bastard Valeska.
I feel like
because of my weakness,
you lost your last tie
to the past.
You lost your home,
Master Bruce.
I must never be that weak again.
Part of being a family
is that we can be strong
for each other.
And when did you get so smart?
I had a good teacher.
Victoria Cartwright
killed her husband.
After we arrested her,
she admitted it.
Later, she recanted.
But the physical evidence
wasn't there.
I was a new cop.
I wanted to make detective.
So you leaned on Jane.
Coerced a statement out of
her to put her mother away.
The woman was guilty.
Later I found out
the husband...
beat the mother and Jane.
I didn't know till after.
The bartender overheard Jane
say something about,
"the kid's guilty, too."
She meant the young cop.
She meant you.
I knew something was wrong.
I felt it.
I said something,
and they told me
to keep my trap shut,
just close the case,
put a bow on it.
After a while,
I stopped feeling it.
And I went down that path
for a long time
until I met you.
However much I've changed...
I can't change the past.
I made that girl a killer.
What do you want from me,
Harvey?
Forgiveness?
Can't give that to you.
I just needed you to know.