Previously onGotham...
Where are you at?
What's green and bad
and goes round and round?
Zebra, with a gaping whore.
You're brilliant mind is as damaged
as the rest of your body.
I guess she was right.
You're not smart.
We need an army to take on Penguin.
Makes me miss Falcone.
You came looking for a gangster,
that's exactly what you've found.
I'm a Falcone.
I need to know
what you're going to do.
You want the city back from Penguin?
I'll give that to you.
Did you really think
I wouldn't figure it out?
The two of you have been whispering
like teenagers for weeks.
You never deserved her
in the first...
Yes, I killed him. I am sorry.
There's a legend about this knife.
The man that killed my grandfather
can't have this. I promise.
That's Ra's al Ghul.
That knife is the key to everything.
Give me the knife
and I will release the boy.
- Bruce, hand me the knife.
- I can't.
- So who's the vegetable?
- Used to be a gangster.
Name's Gilzean, maybe Gold.
Hook a slug in the noodle,
then in a coma six months.
So hospital brass wants free up
some beds?
Yeah. Say take him upstate.
Rest in peace, Butch Gilzean.
Cyrus Gold.
Whoever the hell you are.
Hey, Harvey.
Does anyone contacted you
- about Ra's al Ghul?
- No.
I just heard from Judge Bam Bam's
clerk.
His trial got pushed off the docket.
And?
And I wanna make sure him being
minister of a foreign country
doesn't let him weasel out of this.
- He killed a boy.
- That's above my pay grid, pal.
I just bust the bad guys.
Do you?
These are release forms.
Of my collars. Let me guess,
each one of them has a license
from Penguin, right?
Jim, I am stuck between a rock
and a hard place.
Every move you bust with a license,
the commissioner orders me
to let them go.
- What am I supposed to do?
- Your job!
I am doing my job!
Gordon.
Got a call from the judge's clerk.
It's about Ra's al Ghul.
- Here.
- I am doing my job!
Master Bruce.
No sleep?
Again?
Once more about the boy's death...
Don't say it's not my fault.
It is my fault.
Alex is dead because of I hesitated.
Well, perhaps you did,
but that doesn't make you
his murderer, does it?
Ra's killed that innocent little boy
and he's gonna pay for it.
Do you really think walking out
in black cape will stop him?
He still wants this dagger.
Stop playing on the bloody dagger,
will you?
Just so we can just get
some breakfast, please.
I think I finally found something
at Dr. Winthrop's notes.
There's a description on the handle
that Dr. Winthrop
was able to decipher.
Says the knife is intended
for the one
who has bathe in the healing waters.
Well, assuming that's not me,
that must be our boy Ra's.
But that doesn't have to mean
it's for him to use.
Perhaps it's to be used against him.
- I see.
- No. You clearly don't.
What you're suggesting is
that knife, that knife alone
is the only thing capable
of doing him in.
If Ra's al Ghul believes
this knife will kill him,
that could explain
why he wants it so bad.
So he can destroy it?
Before someone fulfils the prophecy.
Master Bruce, I know that you feel
bad about Alex, we all do.
But at this point
you must remember your vow.
No killing.
Taking a life
never mind how justified
will lead you down a darker path
that you could ever
possibly imagine.
I know, I've been down it.
- Do you understand me, Master Bruce?
- I understand.
Good.
Let's get yourself ready.
Chop-chop.
Such a tragedy.
He was only a child
and was always so lovely.
A heinous crime.
Perpetrated against
such an innocent boy.
And his grandfather,
murdered just the day before.
I'll just be in a moment,
Master Bruce.
Diplomatic immunity?
You are joking, aren't you?
Not to par, abide Embassy file papers
to have him extradited.
Could happen this week.
That monster killed a child.
I know. I was there. Look...
I'm telling you this as a courtesy.
But the news will get out
and when it does,
I need you to watch Bruce.
I'm worried about him.
And you blame me.
You're his guardian, aren't you?
You're supposed to protect him,
instead you've been placing him
in harm's way.
Oh, I see.
So that's the right cause, is it?
Keeping you in the dark.
Well, if I was you
I'd focus on your job, Detective,
which is keeping Ra's al Ghul
behind bars. Tacks-up.
Just keep the news away
from Bruce as long as you can.
On that we agree, Detective.
The boy's been through enough.
Thank you for coming, Barbara.
Hell of a chicken coop.
So, what's the angle?
How about this?
Say the word, we'll be home
drinking Chianti by dinnertime.
I think I'll decline.
So why did you call me here?
To say goodbye.
When I brought you back to life,
I asked you to be my eyes
and ears in Gotham.
You became so much more.
Save it.
What about everything
you promised me?
"Do as I ask and I will give you
a gift beyond your imagining."
What the hell was that?
You'll see.
Goodbye, Barbara.
Born on a Monday
Christened on a Tuesday
Married on a Wednesday
Took ill on Thursday
Grew worse on Friday
Died on Saturday
Buried on Sunday...
Sweet mother of Mary.
Never seen nothing like him before.
He's white as a picket fence.
Easy. We ain't gonna hurt you.
What happened to your drawers,
big fella?
Easy.
No!
We're gonna get you, you freak!
Who are you?
Solomon Grundy
Born on a Monday
License compliance
amongst the G.C.P.D. remains high.
The program
is an unmitigated success.
Numbers, Mr. Penn.
According to my tabulations,
86 percent of crime
is accounted for under Pax Penguina.
Which means that 14 percent of crime
happens outside
of my licensing system!
The numbers are very good,
Mr. Cobblepot.
Get Firefly. I want examples made!
Yes, that might help.
But, then, if scorching
a few idiots was all it took,
anyone could rule Gotham.
Thank you for your insight,
Miss Falcone.
I don't recall summoning you.
I came to see if you had
lunch plans tomorrow.
An invitation?
After I killed your father's
last remaining loyalists?
Perhaps you overestimate
the pleasure of your company.
Oswald...
...you may think you have everything,
but there is one thing
you don't have.
The Falcone name.
A name that once accounted for
all criminal activity in Gotham,
as in 100 percent.
Now you're just rubbing it in.
I propose we have lunch
somewhere public.
By doing so, you'll show Gotham
that you have the support
of the Falcone family.
And that should be enough to send
those outlying criminal elements
scurrying back under your umbrella.
Mr. Penn, item number four
on my to-do list.
"Kill Sofia Falcone."
Add a question mark, will you?
Tomorrow it is.
Come on, you people have
pills for everything!
Insomnia, anxiety!
You have to have something for me!
I don't know,
a pill to reverse the effect
of having your brain frozen
and unfrozen?
That's kind of specific.
I will not be condescended to
by an idiot in a lab coat!
You're not even a doctor!
Okay, relax, man.
Just, tell me your symptoms.
Fogginess of the mind.
Decreased capacity
to think 10 steps ahead.
Inability to solve riddles!
God. I have got to improve
my brain function.
I could take a pill or a vitamin.
I'll even consider a natural remedy.
I don't want to get your hopes up,
but there is something.
What? Tell me.
A trial drug.
It claims to boost
your natural cognitive abilities.
- That's perfect. Where is this?
- The sample drawer.
What is it called?
Smartivia.
Blue pills, diamond-shaped.
Smartivia. Smartivia.
I don't see them.
Try towards the back.
I don't see it.
Oh, here it is.
Oh! God!
A fake gun?
Seriously?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I just need to know.
- Do these work?
- No, dummy.
They're sugar pills.
And I'm calling the police.
Go on, do it, do it...
Butch.
You know Grundy?
Butch...
I have never had an issue with you.
Barbara Kean, she is the problem.
You and Tabitha
are innocent bystanders.
Wow, you don't get much sun. No...
Man talk too much.
- Collins, deal with this, will you?
- Yep.
Gordon.
- Bruce is gone.
- What?
You've got to get me into Blackgate.
- What are you talking about?
- When we got back from the wake,
he said he was gonna go
straight to bed,
but he must've snuck out
between then and now.
My concern is
that he's taken the knife...
and he's gonna try and kill
Ra's al Ghul.
- You're serious?
- Yes, I'm bloody serious.
We've got to go to Blackgate now.
And then you can tell me
the many ways
I've failed the child, all right?
- Oh, I will.
- Listen to me.
The boy is on the verge
of doing something
that there's no coming back from.
He needs our help.
Right.
Let's go.
Yeah, it's about time.
Shift ended five minutes ago.
Come on.
You weak...
foolish boy.
You're still not ready.
My name is Bruce Wayne. Stop him.
Stop him.
Master al Ghul.
Take him below.
What? What are you doing?
We got your call, but...
I checked the logs,
Bruce Wayne hasn't been here.
With all due respect, I don't think
he'd come as a regular visitor.
He's a billionaire, after all.
I think what Mr. Pennyworth
is trying to say
is Bruce Wayne could have paid
someone to get him in here.
No offense.
We just want to look around.
Sure. Whatever you want.
But you came all the way here
for nothing.
And we're gonna need your weapons.
Standard procedure.
Of course.
- Finished?
- That's absolutely it.
Unless you want to check
my under crackers.
This way.
Under crackers?
They're here.
Sugar pills, my foot.
That dream was horrible.
Oh, God!
Oh, you're real.
You know...
Grundy?
What? No. No.
No, who's Grundy?
Solomon Grundy.
Born on Monday.
Your hand! How...
I'm sorry.
What happened to you?
Grundy not know.
Okay, let me get this straight.
You don't remember...
who you are or how you got here?
I'm sorry.
Grundy, I don't know you.
Best of luck, though. Hope you get
the skin thing figured out. Later.
You know Grundy.
You help Grundy.
Be Grundy...
friend.
I'm attempting to be civil...
but I can't help you.
Why?
I just can't, all right?
- Why?
- Because...
- Because I can't even help myself!
You don't know who you are.
Well, that makes two of us.
I used to be smart, brilliant...
and now that's gone.
I can't even rob a pharmacy!
So you want me to help you?
I can't.
Well, I am feeling a bit peckish.
We are closed.
Janos.
Last I saw you
was at my 10th birthday.
You bought me ruby earrings.
Said it would be a fitting gift
for the daughter
of the king of Gotham.
Sofia Falcone.
I heard you had returned to Gotham.
What can I do for you?
I was wondering how you were faring
under Penguin's rule.
The Szabo family is quite content
under Oswald Cobblepot's
licensing system.
But even if we were not,
we would be wise enough
not to say anything.
Good. Because I've invited him
to your restaurant for lunch,
and I want it to be a lunch
he'll never forget.
Bruce.
Where am I?
Beneath Blackgate Penitentiary.
Alfred Pennyworth and Jim Gordon
are upstairs...
in the company, unbeknownst to them,
of my men.
Let them go.
They have nothing to do with this.
Still playing
the white knight, Bruce.
You replaced the guards
before I got here.
I'm sure your friends
can fend for themselves.
You applied for diplomatic immunity,
knowing I'd hear about it
and come for you.
I wanted the knife,
but not for the reason you think.
It's been ages
since I first held this dagger.
It was given to me moments
after I was bathed
in the Lazarus Pit.
Submerged in the waters...
suspended between life and death,
I saw a vision of you...
my heir.
You're insane.
I'm not your heir. I don't even
understand what that means.
It means that you are the only one
who can end my suffering.
Please.
You want me to kill you?
Set me free.
Well, thanks for the snack, big guy.
It's been an emotional day.
I got to go.
No.
Not this again. Come on!
God, I've told you,
I'm better off on my own,
and you are, too.
So let go! Let go!
Hey, freak.
I knew we'd find you.
And it looks like you got a friend.
I assure you, we are not friends.
Get 'em. Both of 'em.
No! No!
Grundy!
Hot, hot!
Grundy friend, help!
Don't leave, no. Help. Help.
Hot.
Hot, hot.
Grundy friend not dumb.
Grundy friend, smart.
Well, I guess...
yeah, you're right.
Water beats fire.
That was smart.
Oh, boy.
I can't breathe.
Oswald.
They said this is their best table.
Interesting choice.
Are you sure it's not too intimate?
The point was to get the word out
that the Falcones support me.
Don't worry, people will talk.
I chose this place because I heard
your mother was Hungarian.
I thought you might
like a taste of home.
I can assure you, Oswald,
I'm not here to poison you.
Perhaps.
The chef likes to go heavy
on the paprika, doesn't he?
How is the food, otherwise?
Serviceable.
Well, I'm stuffed.
Thank you so much
for meeting me, Miss Falcone.
And thank you to your family
for their support.
You can't leave
until you've tried the goulash.
If it's anything
like the chicken paprika,
- I'll pass.
- It's the house specialty.
My mother made goulash.
Brought the recipe from Budapest.
Handed down through her family
for 300 years.
I doubt this will hold a candle.
- I'm leaving!
- Oswald?
Oswald?
It took me forever
to find his mother's recipe.
Did you follow it exactly?
I followed the recipe to a T.
The little man didn't like?
Honestly, I don't know.
How long have you worked here?
Two years, thereabouts.
I was in Blackgate for a time.
We must not have overlapped.
Here?
As a guard? As a prisoner.
Oh, yeah. Heard about that.
Is there a reason why you're not
taking us through maximum security?
Prisoners are in the yard
this time of day.
Been some changes
since you were here.
"McCloskey."
That's funny.
I know another J. McCloskey
who works here.
My cousin. Gets confusing sometimes.
All right, let's go.
Through this door.
I got to say, mate, I really love
what you've done with the old place.
However, I've got a question for you.
Yeah?
Where are the real guards?
Where is Bruce Wayne?
Ra's al Ghul has plans for the boy.
Where is he?
You'll never find him.
Oh, you underestimate my resolve,
pal.
Well, at least we know Bruce is here.
Well, we've walked the floor.
Where could he be?
There's the yard, the tower,
but they're too public.
There's a sub-basement,
accessible by the service elevator.
Which way?
Who did I tell you specifically
not to let in here?
Miss Falcone is here to see you, sir.
I'm sorry, Oswald.
I'm not sure what upset you, but I...
Enough!
Did you think I would really believe
this was all some coincidence?
That goulash tasted exactly
like my mother used to make!
You can't fault me
for the restaurant's authenticity.
You're buttering me up.
But for what?
Is it so hard to believe
that someone would want to do
something nice for you?
There was only one person
in my whole life
whoever did things for me
without wanting something in return.
And that was my mother.
Then I envy you.
My father never helped anyone
unless it benefited him.
And eventually it drove away
everyone who loved him.
Go.
I'll decide what to do with you
later.
Oswald, I only want to help you.
Oh, you want to help? Try leaving.
Your foot.
It's just the weather.
What are you doing?
- Don't.
- It's okay.
I won't judge.
When I was a child, I broke my ankle
while playing with my cousins.
I was desperate.
Crying in pain.
My father told me to put ice on it.
Toughen up, stop with the tears.
But my mother went with me
to the hospital.
And on the way, she told me that cold
actually increases the pain.
What's needed is warmth.
My mother.
She used to sing.
This may be hard for you
to understand.
But I have walked this earth
for centuries.
Waiting for you, Bruce.
Only you can kill me.
And only with that dagger.
That is my curse.
That is the meaning of my vision.
I don't believe you.
Believe me.
This is just another manipulation.
See.
Look.
My true form.
Every moment of my life is agony.
End my suffering.
Whatever your curse is...
you deserve it
for what you've done.
You're angry, Bruce. I understand.
But unless you strike me down
with that blade,
- you will never be free.
- No!
I won't.
Then allow me to tell you
what will happen...
if you don't kill me.
I will disappear...
and let you live your life.
You will follow the path of light.
Grow into a fine man.
Become a husband.
A father.
There may be a day
when you forget I ever existed.
But then I will return.
And I will kill everyone you love.
Just as you watched your parents die,
just as you watched me
slice your friend's throat,
I will slaughter your wife
and children
before your very eyes,
and there will be nothing
you can do about it.
Die.
Yes.
Attention, all inmates.
Prison in official lockdown.
Remain in your cell.
Are you going to arrest me?
For what?
For murder.
I don't know what I just saw
in there.
But as far as I'm concerned,
Ra's al Ghul's men broke
into Blackgate and he escaped.
I betrayed myself
and my parents' memory.
I took a life.
I did exactly what Ra's said I would.
Just because you know
you're capable of doing something
doesn't mean it has to happen again.
Bruce, you and I have known
each other a long time.
Since the night
your parents were murdered.
Now, you may not feel
like you're that kid anymore,
but I know that you are.
One who believes in doing good.
In fighting for what's right.
Who will do anything
to keep the people he loves safe.
Nothing that happened today
changes that.
What are you doing?
You said it yourself.
It's over.
No.
Can't let you do that, Master Bruce.
Alfred.
Listen, we started
this vigilante caper
to prepare for Ra's return,
didn't we?
But it's become
so much bigger than that.
I see that now. I mean,
I was wrong and you were right.
You can make a difference.
I'm not the hero Gotham needs.
I made that decision
the moment I killed Ra's al Ghul.
I took the dark path.
Yes, you did.
And it's gonna be a long,
bumpy journey back.
But I believe in you, Master Bruce.
I always have, and I,
I always will.
Now, I understand
that you don't feel worthy now.
But when you do, this...
this will be waiting for you.
As will I, sir.
Those guys that attacked us
didn't even have five bucks
between 'em.
We need a new plan.
What?
Truth.
Grundy friend know Grundy?
You deserve to know.
You and I...
were the very best of friends.
And then something happened to you.
And I just didn't recognize you.
But what is important
is that, with your muscles,
we can make money.
And with money,
we can make me smart again.
And then we'll figure out
what happened to you.
Just trust me. Okay?
Grundy, come on.
Beat him, yeah.
Yeah, come on!
Beat him. Come on, you big bull.
Get in there.
What is this, a knitting circle?
Let's see some blood!
Hey, I'm looking
for the person in charge here.
You're looking at her.
What do you want, squirt?
Well, if there's money to be had,
we'd like to put our hat in the ring.
And who are you?
I'm... Hey.
I'm this fine gentleman's manager.
Trust me, he's a monster.
Well, more grist for the mill.
We'll get you patched up.
Then we'll talk.
Hey.
Go get the doc.
All right, one, two, three.
Leave me, put it up.
Hey, Doc.
Cherry wants you to come
look at some new guy.
I'll be right there.