Previously onGotham...
I hope you know, Oswald,
you can always count on me.
Thank you.
Miss Kringle, dinner, Chei Moi.
Okay.
That's for Kristen.
Whatever happened with Tetch?
He broke his sister out of GCPD.
- I'll never go with you!
- I love you!
- You're insane!
- No!
No!
You killed her!
She died. He escaped.
Because I heard a rumor there's
something strange about her blood.
I'll tell you what you want to know.
You are gonna have
to buy me dinner though.
He killed you.
Those who hurt you will feel my pain.
- I love you, Daddy.
- I love you too, baby.
I'm so proud of you.
Bye!
Well, the good part is about
to happen.
I am so...
Look at that,
there's no greater symbol of love
than two people
who've made the choice
to spend the rest
of their lives together.
Hey, pal, we have
a reception to get to
- so what you say we get a move on?
- Yes.
About that I'm afraid
you won't be able to attend.
This some kind of a joke?
No.
It's quite serious, in fact.
You're needed elsewhere.
- Let's get out of here.
- Yeah.
- Hey, open the damn door!
- Sorry, we mustn't be late.
Please, just don't hurt us.
That's not my decision to make.
Your fate depends entirely
on James Gordon.
Hey! Hey!
- Don't forget to buckle up.
- Hey, open the door!
- Help!
- Help! Help!
What a beautiful morning.
Sun is shining, birds are singing.
And they say that fortune favors
the brave.
Do they have that saying
in your country, Olga?
Ya ne ponimayu.
I don't know what you're saying.
Vash zavtrak gotov.
It's not important.
What is important
is that I have found someone.
What good is love if it's one-sided?
I have no choice
but to confess my feelings to Ed.
Da.
Now that I understand.
It means yes.
My mother taught me that.
She used to tell me,
"Life only gives you one true love,
Oswald.
When you find it, run to it."
So that is what I'm going to do.
I'm also going to enroll you
in an ESL program.
You really should learn the language
if you're going to work here.
So I hear that Lee Thompkins
is running point on Alice Tetch's
blood at the GCPD.
That would make sense.
Can you get me a sit-down with her?
Oh, I see.
You're willing to help me,
just not when it comes to your ex.
It's complicated.
Actually, it's really simple.
You just pick up the phone,
you dial her number
and you let her know that
Valerie Vale would like a sit-down
to discuss Alice Tetch's blood.
See? It's pretty simple.
She won't give you anything.
You leave that part to me.
You know, I can get used to this,
you helping me with my stories.
We make a pretty good team.
Does that mean
you'll share your breakfast?
Absolutely not.
But really, when are you gonna
give up this P.I. act?
So far you've had two cases.
One girl died and the other one,
well, you never found her.
In baseball we call that an O-fer.
- I'm happy.
- Of course, you are.
You get to drink scotch all day
and have sex with me.
I got to go to work.
You know what?
This is nice.
Let me know when you hear
from Thompkins.
Can I help you?
James Gordon,
Jervis Tetch has a message for you.
Follow my friend where to go,
to learn the truth
you've hidden below.
Should you choose not to play,
precious people will die today.
- This is Gordon.
- Hello, James.
Jervis, never should've left
that hole you were hiding in.
Oh, I wasn't just hiding.
I put the time to good use.
Made a thorough study of you.
Quite the fascinating history.
Yet, so tragic.
A father lost.
Career gone by the wayside.
Failed relationships.
And here I didn't think about
you once.
Oh, James.
I've been inside that head of yours,
James.
I've seen the web of lies
you tell yourself.
Strung together to keep
that fragile psyche of yours intact.
Well, it's been nice catching up
with you.
I'm going to force you to confront
who you really are.
And I'm going to drive you mad
doing it.
Now, please direct your eyes
to the overpass.
Meet Dave and Amy Walters.
Married just this morning.
Lovely ceremony.
In 30 seconds, they're going to jump
to their deaths.
Take the stairs,
and you can save them.
However, down the street
there's a little boy.
His name is Shane.
And he's going to be hit by a truck,
driven by my highly
esteemed associate.
Choice is yours, James.
You can't save both.
So who's it going to be?
You can't save both of them.
You son of a bitch.
Good. Now I have your attention.
They were innocent, Jervis.
You didn't have to kill them.
It was your choice, James.
You practically pushed them off
the ledge.
Stay with me, James.
- James?
- What?
87, Fulton Street,
Apartment Four-C. Five minutes.
No police, or more people die.
Oh, boy, now it's official.
Why? You looking to back out?
You'd have to put a bullet in me.
Good thing I don't carry a gun.
My father called.
He wants to throw us
an engagement party.
- Told him we're not interested.
- Okay.
I know you had reservations about
moving back here.
And, you know my dad.
Half measures aren't his thing.
If we say yes, he's gonna put us
on display for the whole city.
I understand.
But we chose to build a life here.
And I'm glad.
An engagement party sounds wonderful.
These go directly
to the City Clerk's office.
And this...
leave this outside
Nicky The Nail's place.
Knock twice. Light it and then run.
Okay.
Good morning, Mayor Cobblepot.
Good morning to you,
my Chief of Staff.
Here are your schedules for the day.
This covers your duties as Mayor,
and this as Kingpin
of the underworld.
You really are settling into your
role here, aren't you, Ed?
And yet I still have so much
to learn from you.
I came up empty tracking down Butch.
Somehow that one-handed ape managed
to disappear.
I suspect he's hiding
with his old crew.
I'm sorry for letting you down.
You have done nothing of the sort.
I would be lost without you.
In fact, there is something
that I need to tell you.
Something very important.
What is it, Oswald?
You know what? I forget.
In and out of my head just like that.
Don't you hate that when
that happens?
That never happens to me.
You know what, I believe that.
So, where are we off to first?
P.S. 134. You're touring a school.
Press will be there,
so we better get a move on.
Great. I love children.
Okay, thank you very much. Okay?
Hey, Cap!
I just spoke to that kid over there.
You're not gonna believe this,
he said Jim Gordon saved his life.
Pulled him out of the way of a truck.
Get him on the phone, now.
I already tried him, no answer.
What happened? You forget your cane?
I don't need it anymore.
Put an all-points out on Gordon.
I want him found.
Hey, does that guy look strange
to you?
I mean, more so than
the usual wack job?
Hey, pal, you see what happened here?
A message for you.
James Gordon,
I have a message for you.
He's hypnotized.
James Gordon,
I have a message for you.
Tetch.
- Jervis.
- Cutting it close, James.
I like what you've done
with the place.
Everyone needs a hobby.
Take a peek through the lens.
Let's chat face to face.
I wonder, what is it that you have
against married couples?
Bad memories, perhaps?
Understandable.
Given the last time you saw a woman
in a wedding dress,
she had a shotgun pointed at you.
- Hey, Jervis.
- Yes, James?
Hello?
Don't you ever do that again!
Okay.
This is about your sister, isn't it?
In your addled brain, you blame me
for what happened to her.
Don't you talk about her!
I got to know her, Jervis.
She was a good person.
That's why she hated you.
Why she died trying
to get away from you.
You want revenge? Kill yourself.
Dismissive. Rude.
I don't like your attitude.
I'll tell you what. I'll come down.
We can talk about it in person.
Hang up again, she dies.
What're you talking about? Who?
Surprising, really.
Given that every relationship
you've been in ended in such misery.
And yet you made the choice
to date again.
Poor girl...
she had no idea
who she was getting into bed with.
She will soon.
See for yourself.
Great thing about reporters.
Tell them you have a story.
And they'll meet you anywhere.
Let me go!
I've got him in a safe house uptown.
You would not believe the amount
of steak that man eats.
Poor Butchie. Nothing but, Tabitha
and red meat all day.
You know, sooner or later,
Penguin is gonna figure out
who sprung him.
- You need a plan, sweetie.
- I'm working on it.
And in the meantime?
Has the flame rekindled
between you two?
Or you still holding out?
We'll see.
Speaking of old flames.
Well, you just can't seem
to stay away.
Tetch. Where is he?
How should I know?
And if you don't mind, Tabitha
and I are just in the middle...
unnecessary.
Jervis Tetch kidnapped Valerie Vale,
this morning.
He knew things that only
you could've told him.
I want to know where he is.
Oh, see that fire?
I mean, where was that
when we were together?
All I got was Captain Vanilla.
Seriously.
We have to open in a few hours.
Then talk.
Firstly, I don't know where Tetch is.
Secondly, he may have come in here
a few days ago, asking about you.
Asking what?
Oh, you know, everything.
Family stuff, GCPD.
The women in your life.
He seemed especially
interested in that.
He knew about Vale already,
but I told him about us.
About how you're still
in love with me.
Cry yourself to sleep at night.
And Lee? Did you tell him about her?
Oh, you mean Miss Rebound from me?
Of course.
We'll send you a bill for the damage!
Lee, listen to me.
I'm sorry, James. Lee can't come
to the phone right now.
Can I take a message?
No? Good.
Gotham Water and Power. Ten minutes.
I need to know she's okay.
Both Lee and Vale.
What you want means nothing to me.
Nine minutes.
James sends his regards.
Now where were we?
Oh, yes. Introductions.
Lee Thompkins meet Valerie Vale.
You both have one very important
thing in common.
You're two halves
of Jim Gordon's heart.
James Gordon,
I have a message for you.
Where is Jervis Tetch?
James Gordon,
I have a message for you.
Yeah, I know.
You said that the first hundred times
I asked you.
James Gordon,
I have a message for you.
Where is he? I know you can hear me!
Hey, Cap, a Uni just spotted Gordon
pulling up to Gotham Water and Power.
Tell him to hold his position
till we get there.
Glad you could make it, James.
Where's Lee and Vale?
Oh, you clearly have no sense
for stagecraft.
We must build to the climax.
This is merely the second act,
where we stoke the tension.
On the right is one of Gotham's
finest paediatricians.
On the left,
Channel Five's favorite anchor.
A doctor and a journalist.
- You get it?
- Yeah, I get it.
The choice is simple, you see.
It's kill one
and the other will go free.
But if your answer to me is no,
a thousand watts into them will go.
Sorry, Jervis,
I'm not killing anyone.
Yes, you will.
Now pick up the pistol and fire!
You want to show me who I really am?
Then show me.
Oh, I will.
I'm done playing your game.
Jim!
Hold! What the hell is going on here?
Captain Barnes,
you're just in time to see
James kill these two innocent men.
We need to find the main
power shutoff, now.
Go!
Even when you don't choose, James,
there are consequences.
No!
No.
- I'm gonna find you.
- Oh, I'm counting on it.
Just ask an old friend
how to get to the end.
This is our third grade class.
How many more grades
do we have to visit?
- This is a K through 12 building.
- Twelve?
But we don't have to see
every single class, do we?
Mayor James used to read
to the children.
Aubrey James is illiterate, ma'am.
It's well documented.
Perhaps, we should move on.
What's wrong with that boy there?
That's Luke.
He's new here.
Hello, Luke. I am Mayor Cobblepot.
Why aren't you playing
with the other children?
What if they don't like me?
Well, how would you ever know
if you don't give it a try?
And if they don't like you,
wait for them to turn their backs
and push them down the stairs.
Little guy needed a push, that's all.
I continue to be in awe of you,
Oswald.
Ed...
there is something I would like
to discuss in a more private setting.
Shall we say dinner at the mansion?
Eight o'clock?
I'll pick us up a nice bottle
of wine.
Tetch has Lee Thompkins
and Valerie Vale. You're sure?
I saw him take Vale and
I called Lee's cell and he answered.
So yeah, pretty sure.
Call the ME's office.
Call her fiancé. Find her.
What the hell is going on here?
Tetch blames me for what happened
to his sister.
He wants revenge.
So what?
He kills two innocent civilians?
How does that track?
He's obsessed with showing me
who I really am.
Driving me insane.
He killed them,
and I just stood there!
What were you supposed to do?
Shoot one of them?
You did what you could.
That's on him.
This is just to prepare me.
He's gonna make me choose.
He's gonna put me in front of Lee
and Vale,
and he's gonna make me choose.
And if I don't...
He'll kill both of them.
We're gonna find her.
I promise you that.
Listen to me, Tetch is a lunatic.
He's gonna get caught.
The most you can hope for is
a lifetime in prison. Don't do this.
Dumpree...
let's see what's in the kitchen.
Nice try.
So why'd they bring us back
to your place?
Like I know?
Well, any chance your boyfriend
might come home?
Not likely.
You do know what this is about,
don't you?
Yes. Tetch blames Jim for his sister,
and we're his means for revenge.
- I've been here before.
- That's too big.
It's never going to spring
the mechanism.
You know,
it is kind of ironic, though.
I was just asking Jim
to get me a sit-down with you and...
here we are.
See, I'm writing a story
on Alice Tetch's blood.
I know you're running point
for the GCPD.
You're not seriously trying
to interview me right now, are you?
Jim said you wouldn't talk to me.
And he was right.
I think he was just being
protective of you.
Anyway, about Alice Tetch.
I hear they're running experiments
on her blood at GCPD bio facility.
Care to comment?
Maybe you're just really scared
and this is your way of coping,
or maybe you're just insanely
committed to your job,
Either way, all I'm interested in
is getting out of here.
Try a cuticle pusher.
My dad was a cop.
Taught me how to pick locks.
I can walk you through it.
Thank you.
And in exchange,
you can talk to me about Alice Tetch.
You and Jim are made for each other.
Thanks.
It's not a compliment.
Thank you, Dr. Calvi.
I'll call you as soon
as we hear anything.
Mario's been in surgery all morning.
Says that he and Lee left
the house together this morning.
She was headed to the station.
He hasn't heard from her since.
Jervis must have grabbed her
before she got here.
What's his next move?
Tetch wants me to find him.
Well, if that's the case then why
didn't he just tell you where he is?
I don't know.
But the last thing he said
was something about an old friend
leading me to him.
Well, I'm not just gonna sit here
and wait for Tetch
to send you an invitation.
Listen up!
Jervis Tetch thinks that Gotham
is his personal playground.
He's taken innocent lives.
And now he has Lee Thompkins
and Valerie Vale.
And to whoever puts
the collar on Tetch,
my personal gratitude
and best bottle of brown.
Now, go to work.
Follow my friend where to go.
James Gordon,
I have a message for you.
Hey!
James Gordon.
I have a message for you.
How do I get to the end?
"The true test will be revealed.
A final decision you must yield.
Tea party begins once more,
when you walk through
Lee Thompkins' door."
- Jim.
- Not now.
What the hell's going on?
Where's Lee?
Look, you're just gonna have
to trust me.
Trust you?
According to Captain Barnes,
you're the reason
she's in trouble to begin with.
You know something.
You know where she is, don't you?
Keep your voice down.
- Does Barnes know? Where is he?
- No. He does not know.
Because if he showed up with 20 cops,
both Lee and Vale would be dead.
I see.
So you're going to go in all alone
and save them, is that it?
Actually, you might be the only
person who can help me.
Come on.
- Remember you have to feel...
- I got it.
Can I ask you something?
As long as it's not about
Alice Tetch's blood.
Why'd you move back to Gotham?
The way I hear it, you made a pretty
nice life for yourself down South.
- It's really none of your business.
- Maybe not.
But you could've moved to any city.
Gotten any job.
Yet, you chose Gotham and the GCPD.
You realize that we both might
die today, right?
Well?
I didn't come here for James Gordon
if that's what you're worried about.
Not bad.
- My turn.
- Okay.
- Okay, so what's our plan?
- You're gonna break free.
We're gonna lure in one
of these goons.
Hit him over the head with something.
Not good.
You can still get out of here.
I'm not leaving you here.
There's gotta be something else
we can use.
My... my.
You two have been busy.
Now if you'd kindly join me
in the dining room,
the guest of honor
will be here shortly.
Welcome to our tea party, James.
We've been expecting you.
Please...
have a seat.
I think I'll stand.
You'll do what I say
or things will get messy.
And by messy I mean, my two friends
will pull their triggers.
and then we'll have blood and
brains all over this beautiful table.
So...
place your gun on the platter
and have a seat.
Really?
After all we've been through today,
you have to think about it?
Not everyone here has to die.
It's going to be okay.
Don't lie to them, James.
Lee, would you mind passing
that down to James?
I must apologize
for the hideous China.
Frankly, I expected more
from Don Falcone's son.
Guess I know what I'm getting you
for your wedding.
To good health.
I think I'll pass.
Me, too.
You know what?
I'll have some.
Bravo, James.
Now I'd like to begin by telling
the story of a brother and a sister,
separated for years,
but whose love never waned.
Fair warning though,
it has a sad ending.
But I couldn't find my sister alone.
So I turned to this man,
James Gordon.
Whom everyone said was a good man,
an honorable man.
And what did this good man do?
Why? He found my sister
and he turned her against me!
Poisoning her mind!
And then he killed her!
Does that sound about right, James?
Sure. Why not?
Now, James, I get the sense
you're not being honest.
Though that's not surprising
considering you've run from your
true self every day of your life.
But you can't run from this choice.
The woman you love is going to die.
I just need to figure
out which one it is.
So, let's review our options,
shall we?
On the one hand,
we have Lee Thompkins.
Intelligent. Kind.
She thought she could save you
from your darkness.
Drag you into the light.
And what did she get for her efforts?
Pain and sadness.
Don't listen to him, Lee.
Look in her eyes...
she still has love for you, James.
And then there's Valerie Vale,
the intrepid reporter
from a blue-collar family.
She still has hope for you.
What will happen when she learns
who you really are?
So, those are the choices...
now it's up to you.
Which lady has your heart?
Who do you love?
You want me to choose?
Tell these idiots
to lower their guns.
I don't trust them not to shoot me
by accident.
You're right. They are stupid.
Down, boys.
Now you drop your gun.
And why would I do that?
Because I'll shoot you.
Well... well.
You okay?
This was your grand plan, James?
Play along until Dr. Calvi
could sneak in and shoot me dead?
But there's only one small problem.
Before you arrived,
I went down to the basement
and switched the magazine in that gun
with an empty one.
My apologies, Dr. Calvi.
I only set the table for four.
Dumfree, will you please escort
the doctor to the bathroom.
I believe there's still one chain
in working order.
Now, I'm out of patience!
Who do you love?
You want to talk about love? Fine.
Let's talk about who you love.
- Or loved.
- Don't.
Your sister knew you were crazy,
Jervis.
Stop it.
She was terrified of you.
She hated you.
- Enough.
- She told me...
what you did to her
when you were kids.
The thought of you disgusted her.
Lies! Deceit!
The story you tell is incomplete!
- She loved me!
- She loved you?
She killed herself rather
than be with you.
She didn't! No.
She impaled herself on a spike
and died in agony.
Because even that was better
than having you touch her.
No, no, no, no.
I saw her when she was dying.
Her face when she knew
she was finally safe from you...
she was smiling.
Because despite the pain,
she was happy.
Liar!
She was the only thing I ever loved,
and you... you sent her soul
to heaven above.
Yes. That's right. Me.
I'm the one you want.
So let Lee and Vale go.
Keep me. But let them go.
Oh, James.
You're trying to confuse me.
But I won't let you.
No, I'm determined
that you'll live on,
and suffer without your love
as I have.
Choose.
- No, I won't choose.
- You will!
You will!
You'll certainly spill.
I'll make it easy for you.
On the count of three,
instead of telling me who you love...
tell me who to kill.
Or I shoot both of them,
which would be such a thrill.
One.
Two.
Three.
Kill Lee.
Oh, finally.
The truth is revealed.
You chose Lee because you love Vale.
Very well.
I knew you had it in you, James.
All this time you made everyone
believe you were the hero.
But deep down
you always knew the truth,
you're a villain.
Vale.
This is Doctor Leslie Thompkins.
Please send an ambulance
to 25 Blackstone Drive.
Hurry.
Move.
You're going to be okay, Vale.
You hear me, you're going to be okay.
Hold on.
Victim's name is Valerie Vale.
Gunshot wound to the abdomen.
BP's 100 over 60.
Tachy's at 160.
O.R. one's prepped and ready to go.
Clear the way! Clear the way, please.
I got it from here.
Ed...
a man comes to a crossroads
in his life,
and he has to make a choice.
Does he choose safety and cowardice?
Or does he opt for courage
and risk everything?
I choose courage.
What I'm trying to say is...
The thing I've been wanting
to tell you all day long is...
I love you.
Impossible to pick
the perfect bottle, isn't it?
Well, it all depends on region
and vintage.
Of course, you have to consider
the wine pairing.
Miss Kringle?
No. Oh, no, my name's Isabella.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I don't usually talk to people.
There's just something about you.
No, no, please, there's...
there's no need to apologize.
You just...
You remind me of someone
that I used to know...
long time ago.
You struggle to regain me.
When I'm lost...
you struggle to obtain me.
What am I?
Time.
I'm Edward.
Edward Nygma.
Jim, how is she?
Still in surgery.
She seems like a tough cookie.
She'll be all right.
What about Tetch?
We got the whole department
canvassing the city. We'll find him.
Why didn't you come to me?
I couldn't.
And I thought I could save them both.
You did what you thought was right.
Maybe.
In the end,
I did exactly what he wanted.
He won.
We'll see.
Mario's a great doctor.
She'll pull through.
- Lee, about what I said...
- Jim.
Not now.