Previously onGotham...
Alfred! The manor...
It's my fault.
Mr. Cobblepot.
Penn!
This never would have happened
if you had stayed with me.
You're having a baby with Barbara.
- Don't think I'm fit to be a mother?
- What do you think?
You're leaving Gotham.
I believe the time has come
for a change of scenery.
- You found a way out of Gotham?
- It's a submarine.
Reunification with the mainland
hangs on by a thread.
Toxic chemicals
rain down onto the city,
and the government cuts us
adrift for good.
Gotham's golden rule.
- No heroes.
Watch out for him.
He thinks he's a white knight.
He's a loose cannon.
You two here to pick up
your grandchildren?
Come on, Babs.
You got the only full bar in Gotham.
And if you two dinosaurs
wanna keep coming here,
you better up your intel.
We got a lead on some black market
heating oil.
One drink. To share.
Then you go wheeze to death
somewhere else.
Would you look at that?
Dix!
Look at you, up and walking around,
you old son of a bitch.
I've been looking for you two
for a while now.
Well, you found us.
You two ever think about the past?
What we did?
What're you talking about, Dix?
About her?
About what we did to the girl?
Who is that?
It is like The Living Dead in here.
Enough of this.
Hey, Gramps.
Oh. What...
Can you please repeat your story
for Mr. Wayne, madam?
We live in the shelter on West End.
There're so many of us
crammed in there.
So much uncertainty. Fear.
And with the river poisoned,
it should've been awful,
but people came together.
Made it a home.
- What happened?
- Couple of weeks ago,
we heard rumors about something
underneath the building,
where it connects to the sewer.
And people started going missing.
Hank, my husband,...
wanted to look for them.
Said we were a family.
So the two of you went
searching for them?
It was so dark.
I didn't see what attacked us.
I hit my head, and when I woke up,
Hank was gone.
Please, Mr. Wayne.
We have a daughter.
We'll do everything we can.
Should we tell Gordon?
Well, he's stretched thin as it is.
Alfred, we don't know who,
or what, is down there.
We know there's a man down there,
in danger.
And we know this lady sent for us.
So go on then,
what do you think we should do?
Let's go find him.
Under normal circumstances,
I wouldn't call you
for a couple of stiffs.
What do you normally do when a couple
of your patrons get stabbed?
Bury the bodies.
Find out who did it,
and then bury those bodies.
See that's not something
you should be telling a cop.
We're living in a different world,
Harvey.
- So why did you call us?
- Take a look.
Boggs and Lewis.
You know them?
They were cops.
They were gone before you joined.
- What happened?
- They came around,
peddling third-rate intel.
It was closing time so I let them in.
And then some other fossil
knifed them.
- You saw him?
- Yeah, he must've snuck in.
Looked like a cop, too.
These two knew him.
Bartender said they called him
Micks? Hicks?
- Dix?
- Maybe.
No way.
- Dix was Harvey's old partner.
- Well, there we go. Case closed.
So you're telling me this guy
rolled in here in a wheelchair,
stabbed these two, and rolled on out?
- He wasn't in a wheelchair.
- Then, it couldn't be Dix.
He's been paralyzed
for the last 15 years.
Harvey, you're confusing me
with someone who cares.
I called you as a courtesy
and now I'm wishing
I just dumped these
two corpses in an alley.
Do we even know if Dix is still in
Gotham after the bridges blew?
Heard he moved into an apartment
about a year ago.
I meant to check up on him,
but it can't be him.
I hear what you're saying,
but we should still talk to him.
And maybe he knows something.
Fine.
- How are you feeling?
- I'm fine. Thanks for asking.
Look, I've been giving you space,
but we have to talk about
how this is gonna work.
I'm gonna be a part
of this kid's life.
Oh, you seem pretty confident
about that.
I am.
Reunification is gonna happen.
You should think about what kinda
person you wanna be when it does.
It's a chance for you to start anew.
I like who I am.
- You were due hours ago.
- Yes, I was.
But I had to get us lunch.
- And I met Dale.
- I see that.
Do you see this?
Our secret plan
to get off this island?
Relax.
Dale is completely trustworthy.
How do you know we can trust him
if you just met him?
Because he's mute and dumb as a post.
Look, I know you're paranoid
about people watching us.
Someone is watching us!
Why do you think
I installed this alarm system?
And as safe as I feel with your
jingle bell contraption in place,
I went out and procured us
some muscle.
You're welcome.
At least you're doing something.
How's my SS Gertrude coming along?
Our submarine is coming along
just fine, thank you.
I've been working on the sonar,
which turns out is
far more complex than I anticipated.
Well, I am confident
you will figure it out.
Of course, I will figure it out,
because I figure everything out.
The navigation system.
The oxygen exchange.
I will figure everything out
because I'm the only one working!
This was supposed to be
a partnership!
It is!
I already did my part by stealing
everything valuable in Gotham,
all of which you get half.
No!
Your goons stole it,
and then you kill 'em.
Are you expecting someone?
Who would I be expecting, Oswald?
I told you someone's watching us.
Dale, go do what I pay you for.
Protect us.
Wait.
Penn?
Hello, Mr. Cobblepot.
Are you, are you really,
I... I don't believe it.
- You're alive.
- Indeed, sir. I... I am.
But, you were shot. I... I was there.
This whole time, I thought you were
dead but you're alive!
And you're only coming to me now?
I... I'm so terribly sorry,
Mr. Cobblepot.
I wanted to come see you, but...
he wouldn't let me.
"He?" "He" who?
Mr. Cobblepot...
this is...
Mr. Scarface.
Wonderful.
Look, I'm sure Dix is in the clear,
but we do have to ask.
That's not it.
I just, I feel bad.
I should've been by before.
I'm all he's got.
Well, look, we came to him, right?
Dix!
- What the hell?
- Bullock?
- That you?
- Yeah.
Don't shoot.
Okay.
Come in.
Is that the way
you always answer a door?
Nowadays, you can't be too careful,
specially someone like me.
A kid comes in, he'd cut my throat
for a cup of soup.
Anyway, I wasn't expecting you.
Figured you forgot about me.
Look, Martin,
when the bridges came down,
- I got busy, and...
- Oh, sure, sure. You forgot me.
Everybody forgets.
I didn't forget.
Planning on taking a trip?
Maybe. I like to keep a bag
packed just in case.
Yeah? Where were you last night?
Where was I?
I was right here.
Anybody else here with you?
Anybody that can back up your story?
You're asking me if was I out there
killing Boggs and Lewis?
Does I look like I was out there
So, you heard about that.
I'm gonna tell you something.
If it meant that I can get out of
this son of a bitch wheelchair,
I would confess right here and now.
To Boggs. To Lewis.
To anybody you want me to confess to.
All right, fine.
But you were a detective.
What would you say if you were us?
We come in here
and you're packing a suitcase.
I would say either I did it,
which I didn't,
or I'd be very worried
that I'd be next.
What do you mean you being be next?
What's your connection
to Boggs and Lewis?
Come on. What?
Nothing.
I just worked with them. That's it.
We, we worked a case together.
- Four of you?
- Yeah.
Dix wasn't my partner then.
I was a rookie cop.
Wet behind the ears.
- So what was the case?
- Woman killed her husband.
As far as I can remember,
it was pretty open and shut.
But at least we can agree
that Dix didn't walk into The Sirens
and stabbed those two guys.
So who did?
Barbara said Boggs and Lewis
recognized the killer.
They called him Dix.
We come in here,
he's packing a suitcase.
He shoots at us. This stinks, Harvey.
Hey.
You all right?
What the hell?
These basements run along
Gotham's sewers.
The river is right next to it.
You mean the river
filled with Jeremiah's toxins?
Who knows what kind of damage
these chemicals could do?
Yeah, you're right.
Just don't you touch anything.
Hold on.
Bite marks.
Animal?
Well, it's no human I've ever seen.
Whatever it was...
he dragged it that way.
Seems like human skin.
Here's the file you asked for.
Victoria Cartwright.
- How'd you...
- I had Harper run
every case the four of you worked,
cross-referenced with any woman
that killed her husband.
Do I need to read it
or you're gonna tell me what's in it?
Victoria Cartwright was a banker.
She led a very boring life...
Until she snapped
and put 238 caliber
slugs into her husband.
End of story.
You guys rehearse that?
Says there was no physical evidence.
She was convicted on the statement
of her seven-year-old daughter, Jane.
This was 20 years ago.
- Where's Jane now?
- What's the point?
The killer is a man, a man that can,
imitate friggin' faces.
What was the name of the guy
that Strange got to imitate you,
Basil something?
That's who we should be looking for.
That was different, and you know it.
- We have an address for this Jane?
- No.
But the family's old home
is in the Green Zone.
- Just east of the clinic.
- Jim, it's a dead end.
Is there anything else
you wanna tell me?
You know what?
Why don't you hang back?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey.
- Are you benching me?
- Killer's still out there.
Keep an eye on your partner.
- Penn, Arnold...
- It's Arthur.
- You're holding a doll.
- It's not a doll.
It's a dummy.
Oh, this is great.
I'm going back to work. Excuse me.
You're saying he made you come here?
Mr. Scarface is very persuasive.
Persuasive?
He made me tell him about your...
treasure.
Penn...
I think you need a rest.
And, perhaps, a psychiatrist.
Then, we can discuss you
resuming your former duties.
Obviously, I won't pay you
for the time you were gone...
Shut your pie hole!
This the one you were tellin' me
about?
- Punk who thinks he's in charge?
- Yes, sir.
That's Mr. Cobblepot.
Oswald, if you don't make him leave,
I will.
- Yeah.
- No one's going anywheres.
Penn, show these dewdroppers
we're serious.
Forgive me.
Now, let's talk turkey, turkeys.
What a mess, huh?
Boggs and Lewis were idiots.
Complete idiots.
They should've known when they see
a guy walking that it ain't me.
You think the Cartwright girl
said something?
How would I know?
So, how've you been
since the bridges came down?
You getting enough food? Medicine?
What if I said no?
I'd feel like crap.
Then no.
The Cartwright girl is dead.
A buddy of mine was a screw over
at Arkham.
He said she was an inmate there
and she died a couple of years ago.
So this has nothing to do with her.
GCPD. Coming in.
Check upstairs.
Looks like this place has been
abandoned
since before the bridges came down.
Yeah.
What the hell?
The hell was that?
Someone's been living here.
What's that smell?
Everything all right?
All good. No one's here.
Hey.
Don't look at me.
Don't you look at me!
We found your handiwork.
Nothing to say?
You're gonna have to take
that mask off.
The only way you're gonna get
that mask on is if you talk.
Otherwise, I'm gonna reach over
this table
and I'm gonna rip it off your face.
- Who are you?
- Nobody.
You're not Jane Cartwright?
Because you were in her
childhood home.
You're about the right age.
Talk to me, Jane.
I know after your mother
was convicted,
you ended up a ward of the state.
In and out of institutions
until you ended up in Arkham.
Then you vanished.
Some say died.
- What happened to you?
- Me?
Nothing happened to me.
Okay.
What happened to Jane?
Oh.
Lots happened to Jane.
She was taken from Arkham.
Down, down, down.
The doctor did things to her,
experiments on her and others.
You're talking about Hugo Strange?
You were taken to Indian Hill?
Professor was obsessed
with the power to change.
The way a chameleon
would change its skin.
He wanted humans to have that power.
He made it so Jane
could change her skin,
her bones, her hair,
the color of her eyes.
All it takes is a single touch
and her body becomes a mirror.
And when it's done,
she sheds her skin and starts anew.
It remembers everyone it touched.
It's touched you, Detective.
We can help you, Ms. Cartwright.
Jane Cartwright is dead.
She died in Arkham.
That's when Jane Doe was born.
So why kill all these cops?
You wanna know why they died?
Ask your friend.
What is that?
We should head out.
My battery's dying.
He's coming! He's coming!
- Who's coming? What happened?
- He's going to kill me.
I barely got away.
- Are you Hank?
- Yes.
Your wife sent us.
Is anyone else left alone down here?
They're all dead.
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Hank! Hank!
Hold on, Hank!
Hand over the heaters.
If you don't mind.
Mr. Penn, can't we just talk this
through.
Get back!
I'm so sorry.
At least, tell me what happened
after Haven.
Help me to understand this.
Go on.
Sing your song.
After I was shot...
I woke up in the GCPD morgue.
I was alone.
I patched my wounds
as best I could and crawled out.
I hid in a store,
an abandoned magic shop.
That's where Mr. Scarface found me.
And he told me all about you.
How you used him.
Chewed him up and spat him out.
- Treated him like a palooka!
- That's a lie!
Oh, please, Oswald. It's what you do.
Arnold...
- Arthur, what do you want?
- I don't want anything.
But Mr. Scarface, well...
he wants your treasure,
and to be boss.
Really?
The dummy wants to be
boss of Gotham.
Bingo!
Now, give me the key
to your treasure room.
Why would I do that? You're obviously
gonna kill me anyway.
What am I doing?
- I'm talking to a doll.
- Dummy.
- Seriously?
- You know what, Oswald?
Honestly, you deserve this.
- Nobody asked you.
- You are opportunistic.
Your loyalty is shaky at best.
And you will hurt anyone,
anyone to get what you want.
I hardly think
you're one to throw stones.
- Listen, Penn.
- Eyes down here, pal.
Sorry. Mr. Scarface.
I got a question for you.
Shoot.
After you get your
tiny wooden hands on that treasure,
what are you gonna do?
Where are you gonna go?
People are gonna come after you
eventually.
Then I'll... I'll take 'em all on.
Yeah. Show 'em who's boss.
You wouldn't have to do that
if you could get off this island now,
would you?
- What are you doing?
- Shut it.
Let the smart one talk.
How do you feel about submarines?
What we're doing here?
Just wanted to takes us,
some place quiet.
Where we could talk.
- We did a bad thing.
- Oh, come on. Not that again.
We put a killer in jail. All right?
What do you keep moping about?
She was guilty.
She got what she deserved. Drop it.
Did you get what you deserved?
What?
You made that girl into a murderer.
Oh, come on.
You.
Your friends.
- The kid.
- Come on. You...
I'm gonna make sure
you never do that again.
- Harper, where's Dix?
- I saw Bullock take him in the back.
Barbara, what're you doing here?
Seems my bartender overheard
the killer say something
before he icepicked Harvey's pals.
I thought I'd be a good citizen.
Okay.
"The kid's guilty, too."
"The kid."
Listen.
What you said before,
about me being a known criminal.
I was on some list
your army buddy had.
When the government rolls
in am I gonna be arrested?
Honestly, I don't know.
But that would work out for you,
right?
I go to jail, you get the baby.
I don't want that.
Is that a promise?
I go straight, I'm clear?
Stay right here. Hey, Harvey.
Where'd you take Dix?
I didn't take Dix anywhere.
Oh, God. Oh...
She got into your locker.
Must've taken your clothes.
We have to lock down the GCPD.
Hey, Harvey.
We'll find her.
Come on.
Hey, look at the size of him.
Living down here, the toxins
in the river must've driven him mad.
Get outta here, now!
Alfred!
- Alfred! Stop.
- Stop.
Stop.
All right, everybody listen up.
GCPD is now in lockdown.
Nobody goes in or out
unless I say so.
She could look like anybody by now.
How are we supposed to find her?
Jim.
Barbara?
What happened?
What do you mean what happened?
I've been attacked.
- Where'd she go?
- Wait a minute.
- How do we know it's really you?
- Seriously?
This isn't proof enough?
- What the hell?
- That's her.
She's the imposter. Shoot her!
It's me, you idiot.
That sounds like Barbara.
Barbara.
Tell me where we first met.
Don't shoot.
I'm leaving here.
Anyone tries to follow me, she dies.
- Shoot her!
- Can't risk it.
Stay back!
Bullock, wait!
- I'm fine.
- All right. Take her to my office.
- Don't let her out of your sight.
- Okay.
I cannot believe that you told him
about the sub.
And that you're playing along
with his psychosis.
Obviously he was gonna kill you.
I bought us time.
I have an idea.
If you can just keep him busy
and wait for the signal.
- Wait, what's the signal?
- Quit your jawing.
So, Mr. Scarface and I,
have discussed our options
and the submarine
sounds like a good plan.
And since we'll need the smart one
to build this hayburner,
he can keep sucking air.
But Penguin ain't so lucky.
Do it, Penn, ventilate that mook!
I'm so sorry, Mr. Cobblepot.
I wish things would have turned out
differently.
Arthur, I want you to listen to
what I'm saying.
You accuse me of manipulating you,
but what about him?
I never asked you to kill anybody.
- That is true.
- Hey...
Think of everything
that we went through together.
Sofia Falcone.
Getting cut off from the mainland.
Starving.
You mean Penn was starving!
Fighting for scraps
while your dog ate steak!
I welcomed you into my home.
And, yes, I was not a good friend,
to you or to anyone.
It's why I'm alone.
But I saw you for what you are
and I valued that.
That must be worth something!
Applesauce!
You're a liar and a thief!
All you do is take, take...
Take!
And you never give anything.
You worked me to the bone!
Forced me to be your puppet.
Well, no more.
You hear me?
No more.
Take that! And that!
No!
Mr . Cobblepot.
You freed me.
- Yeah.
- How can I ever thank you?
Why did you do that?
He wasn't the threat.
The dummy was the threat...
Oswald.
I accept you for the person
that you are.
Just as you accept me
for the cold logician that I am.
That's why this friendship's great.
And as friends,
I think we can both agree
that that lunatic had to be stopped.
Perhaps, Edward,
we really are meant for each other.
Jane?
I know you're up here.
Jane. I knew you'd be here.
I'm sorry.
It was my job to protect you,
and I let you down.
You made Jane into a killer.
You and your friends.
There have to be consequences.
You killed three men already.
When is it enough?
When you're dead.
Put the gun down.
Shoot me.
You killed Jane years ago
and didn't even know it.
Just shoot me.
Let me see your face.
Your real face.
Why? So you can see
what a monster she is?
Hugo Strange only destroyed her face.
You destroyed her soul.
Let me see it.
Do you see?
Do you see what they did?
Jane.
We can work this out,
just put the gun down.
The only way this ends is
with one of us dead.
Oh, my God. You're alive!
The nurse thinks the man
that attacked us will never recover.
The toxins, the river have done
irreparable damage to his brain.
I just think it's a shame we couldn't
save the rest of the people
that went missing, Master Bruce.
We should've went to Gordon
from the start.
- We were reckless.
- Nah, that's nonsense.
We took decisive action,
we saved a man's life.
The people in this city
have suffered, Master Bruce.
They need someone to protect them.
I agree.
But there are better ways
to find absolution.
I... I don't follow.
What happened to Wayne Manor
wasn't your fault.
I know you've been blaming yourself.
You didn't destroy our home, Alfred.
I feel like I did.
It feels like I wasn't strong enough
to fight Tetch
or that bastard, Valeska.
I feel like, because of my weakness,
you lost your last tie to the past.
You lost your home, Master Bruce.
I must never be that weak again.
Part of being a family is that
we can be strong for each other.
And when did you get so smart?
I had a good teacher.
Victoria Cartwright
killed her husband.
After we arrested her,
she admitted it.
Later she recanted.
But the physical evidence
wasn't there.
I was a new cop.
- I wanted to make detective...
- So you leaned on Jane.
Coerced a statement out of her
to put her mother away.
The woman was guilty.
Later I found out the husband...
beat the mother and Jane.
I didn't know till after.
Bartender overheard Jane
say something about
"the kid's guilty, too."
She meant the young cop.
She meant you.
I knew something was wrong.
I felt it.
I said something and they told me
to keep my trap shut.
Just close the case, put a bow on it.
And after a while,
I stopped feeling it.
And I went down that path for a long
time until I met you.
However much I've changed...
I can't change the past.
I made that girl a killer.
What do you want from me, Harvey?
Forgiveness?
I can't give that to you.
I just needed you to know.