Previously onGotham...
My best wishes
to Commissioner Essen.
Welcome back, Jim.
I don't know how you pulled this off,
but I'm glad you did.
Sometimes the right way
is also the ugly way.
There's been an incident
at Arkham Asylum,
six inmates have escaped.
Barbara Kean was one of them.
Oh, my God.
The world sees criminal lunatics.
I see brilliance.
Gotham will tremble before you.
"I beg of you, my son,
please, choose happiness.
Unless you feel a calling,
a true calling."
Mr. Mayor, you wanna know
what I really am?
Yes, sir.
- Shall I tell you?
- Please, please.
At heart, I'm an ardent student
of human nature.
Fascinating paradox we are.
So wise, yet so foolish,
so brave, and yet so fearful.
For instance, this is a glass jar
inside of it, is a hairy spider,
a tarantula, I guess
but I'm no expert.
In a minute,
I'm gonna open that little hatch
in the front of your box,
I'm gonna drop the spider inside,
and I'm gonna close it.
That's choice A.
Choice B, I open the hatch
you speak to your lovely secretary,
Maggie, on the telephone
you tell her you've run away
with some woman
and you'll be sending
written instructions shortly.
So which is it, Choice A or Choice B?
Choice B, please. Please, Choice B.
The Telephone.
Of course...
it's human nature.
See? There is no spider.
But if you don't do what I ask,
you'll wish there was one.
Why are you doing this to me?
Don't fret so.
You're part of a great endeavor.
A great cleansing.
Monsters are coming, Mr. Mayor.
Monsters.
Cleanse the city, implied and fire.
What the hell is this?
"Where is Mayor James?
Who is his mystery lover?"
No one cares
who the mayor is banging!
You can do better than this,
people.
Now, go out and get me
some headlines, damn it!
What the heck?
Yes, all right, all right.
Oh, my God.
Perfect. Next.
Mister X.
A little to the right.
Okay, that's the spot.
Perfect.
What shall we do with the spare?
I know.
Aaron, would you kindly...
Maniax!
Now that's a headline.
You all know what we're facing here.
48 hours ago,
six criminally insane inmates
were busted out of Arkham Asylum.
Yesterday, four of those inmates
broke in to Yellen Shipyard,
kidnapped seven workers,
then dropped them off the roof
of the Gotham Gazette.
As of now, we still have no leads
on the person or persons
behind the breakout.
Jim Gordon's lead. Jim.
These are our targets.
Jerome Valeska,
18 years old, matricide.
Arnold Dobkins, schizophrenic,
poisoner, rapist.
Aaron Helzinger...
killed his entire family
with his bare hands.
Robert Greenwood,
killed and then ate a dozen women.
Barbara Kean...
killed her parents.
We'll gonna work this
in groups of four.
I'll hand out assignments
throughout the day.
Alvarez is my coordinating officer.
Any questions?
Let's get to work.
Fine job yesterday, gentlemen.
We opened big.
The whole city knows your name now.
So bravo. Let's give ourselves
a round of applause.
Now that we have Gotham's attention,
it's time for The Maniax
to make a grand entrance.
Wasn't that it?
That was the overture.
Now, the audience is hushed,
expectant.
The curtain rises.
Then what happens?
Oh, then, we confront Gothamites
with their most primal fears.
Take from them
all they hold dear and sacred.
And then what happens?
Right then, we offer them salvation.
And then they are ours.
Let's get busy, man.
Patience.
First, you gentlemen need to learn
a little stagecraft.
- Stagecraft?
- You're going to be on TV.
You have to present yourselves
with style and vigor.
Dobkins, say "Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen."
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Again, with a smile.
Now you.
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Not bad. Sinister and authoritative.
Never mind.
Jerome.
Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
Very good.
Boyishly charming.
The laugh is fabulous. Use that.
Now, me.
I am so glad that you two
are getting along.
We're a little busy here.
So if you could leave
the poor mayor alone.
- We're bored.
- Yeah.
Why do the boys
get to have all the fun?
Your time is coming, I told you.
You haven't killed him, have you?
No, I don't think so.
Nope, hanging in there.
When?
When is my time coming?
Soon.
Very soon.
Would you tell me
about James Gordon?
What do you wanna know?
It's hard to believe.
My father has been sneaking down
here for years
and I never even knew about it.
That makes two of us, isn't it?
Wait, let's just think about this.
Are you certain you wanna turn
that bloody thing on?
Of course, I'm certain.
Have you thought it through,
Master Bruce?
This computer could contain
all my father's research
into Wayne Enterprises.
All this time, I've been looking
for a smoking gun
and here it is.
Exactly, a smoking gun.
Now, guns are for grown-ups,
aren't they?
That's a metaphor, Alfred,
not an argument.
Here it is.
It's working!
What are you... what are you doing?
Alfred, stop, what are you doing?
What are you doing, Alfred?
Please, stop it!
It's ruined. It's ruined.
What's wrong with you?
Why did you do that? Answer me!
Had to be done, Master Bruce.
This was the key
to exposing Wayne Enterprises.
Everything that I've worked for.
Everything my... everything my dad
worked for is now gone.
Because of you!
If I'd known what was down here,
I'll never helped get you in.
Well, look around you,
look, look. Liters of blood.
A bulletproof vest
with two slugs in it!
Guns, weapons.
I mean, whatever is on that computer
probably killed your father.
And I'll be damned
if I see you suffer
with the same fate, Master Bruce.
I'm trying to protect you.
I'm trying to keep you safe.
I want you to go.
- No, I know that you're...
- No.
- That you're upset...
- Alfred...
I want you to go and never come back.
Do you understand me?
You're fired.
Very well, Master Bruce.
As you wish.
Oh, shiny.
Give that back.
I saw it first.
No, you didn't. I said give it back.
Make me, you little brat.
Your samurai skills
are excellent, Greenwood San.
But they are nothing compared to me.
Prepare to die!
That's enough!
That's good.
I tried to stop them.
Boys, we're a team.
We can't fight amongst ourselves.
Yeah, we're a team, boys.
And I'm the captain.
Captain of my foot.
I've murdered a dozen women.
Terrorized the city.
What have you done?
Chopped up your mummy.
Everybody has to start somewhere.
See, I have vision,
and ambition, and brains.
You're just a nutty old cannibal.
How many people can you eat
before that shtick gets old?
I could eat one more.
I can see we're gonna have
to resolve this one
once and for all.
You all know this game, right?
Over it.
Who wants to be the boss?
Ladies first.
Hey, Greenwood,
what's the secret to good comedy?
Timing.
And what's courage?
Grace under pressure and...
Who's the boss?
I'm the boss.
I believe you are, Jerome.
I believe you are.
Arigato, sensei.
Five lunatics and Barbara?
Brother, you got no luck.
I told you civilian life
was better, didn't I?
Yeah, you did. Actually,
that's kind of why I'm here.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
What are you doing here?
Jim, you remember Scotty,
my girlfriend.
- Fiancée.
- Right.
My fiancée.
Yeah, Scotty. Good to see you.
Relax, honey, we'll just talk.
Oh, like hell, you are.
He's gonna ask you
to come back to work.
He didn't asked me anything.
We're just having a chat.
Is that right?
Is that why you're here, detective?
Just to have a chat?
No, no, she's right.
Harvey, I need your help, okay?
She said it better.
I'm short-handed
and I was thinking maybe you...
He has a life, the answer is no.
He is not coming back.
Hon. I'm telling him no.
And it's like what she said...
I have a life.
I get it.
Okay. I'm happy for you.
Just a thought.
- Wish me luck.
- Good luck.
Jim, one last thing,
one last thought
from your Uncle Harvey.
These Maniax killed a bunch of people
from the shipyard, right?
Yellen shipyard, yeah.
Why there?
They could have gone anywhere
and killed anyone.
But these lunatics specifically
chose that shipyard, eh?
Wonder why?
Good to see you. Scotty.
Yeah, I'll call you back.
- Commissioner!
- Tell me something good, please.
- Harvey isn't coming back.
- That's not good.
But he did suggest a lead
that panned out nicely.
Turns out, the Maniax
stole a refueling truck
from the shipyard yesterday.
Why wasn't it reported?
It was one of over
a hundred service vehicles.
It took a while to track down
the entire fleet.
But when we did,
we found that one was missing,
fully-loaded with gasoline.
You get a license plate?
And a description of the vehicle.
Put out an APB.
- God, I'm so glad you're back, Jim.
- Me too.
Wish I could say
the same for Bullock.
I can't believe he's really gone.
I mean, he's a cop.
He was born to be a cop.
Not anymore. He's a happy man.
I didn't have it in me to push him.
You ever think about that?
Walking away, I mean.
No, you?
I did for a long time.
But not anymore?
I've sat back and watched old,
corrupt, lazy men
buy their way into this job
and waste it.
Not me, Jim. Not me.
- A new day.
- You're damn right.
I just want to say it's been
an honor and a privilege
to serve you and your family, sir.
Thank you.
If you need any references,
I'll be happy to provide them.
Is that all you're taking with you?
That's what I have, sir.
All right, well then.
Oh, dear, yes, I'll best be off,
I've got a train to catch.
Goodbye, sir.
Goodbye, Alfred.
I beg your pardon, sir?
I said, goodbye.
Yes.
Goodbye, sir.
I spy with my little eye,
something that is...
Yellow.
Score, Gotham, score! We want more!
Hit them where it hurts
and knock them to the floor!
Yay, Gotham!
Oh, hello, Ms. Kringle.
Hello, Mr. Nygma.
How is your day going?
Fine.
Question for you.
Yes?
Did you know that house flies
hum in the key of F?
No.
No, I did not know that.
Okay then.
Well...
- Bye.
Dammit! We agreed
you were gonna ask her out!
We didn't agree to ask her.
We agreed to think about asking her.
But there's no point.
She doesn't like you.
Maybe she'll like me.
You ever consider that?
I got confidence, ladies love that.
No, she won't like you.
She won't. Go away.
Please, just go away!
Hey!
What's going on?
Is that a gun?
What's he doing?
We got a sighting
of the stolen truck.
Yeavely Park.
I want you all to know this was
a very difficult decision for us.
It was between you
and a senior citizen bingo party.
In the end, we decided
to skew a little younger.
Youth one today, sorry.
Give me an O!
- I said give me an O!
- O!
- Give me an N!
- N!
- Give me another O!
- O!
What does that spell?
Oh, no!
Do it. Do it. Do it.
Ready? Okay.
This is so embarrassing.
Anyone got a light?
I do. I got.
Stand your ground, boys.
They can't shoot at the bus.
Hold your fire, hold your fire.
Aaron, Greenwood,
get the truck started.
We're gonna blow this barbecue.
Light them up.
Everybody, okay?
Who broke you out, Dobkins?
You're gonna have to talk sooner
or later, tell me now.
I am a victim here, sir.
I was coerced.
- Abducted and coerced.
- By who?
If I tell you that, I got to get
some kind of guarantee...
I understand that you were
just trying to protect me.
But there's nothing, nothing,
that you can do to stop me
from carrying out my father's work.
I know that now.
I don't want you to go, Alfred.
But you're either with me
or you're against me.
And if you're against me,
I don't have a choice.
I'm with you, Master Bruce.
I've always been with you.
But what you're doing
is tantamount to suicide.
This is big boy's stuff.
You're too young
and you're not ready.
Then make me ready.
You, you've lived a dangerous life
and you survived.
So teach me.
Teach me how to do the same.
I'll do whatever it takes,
I'll train every day.
Yeah, but you said that before,
hadn't you?
That was before.
Now I know the truth.
And I know what I have to do.
I'll even go back to school,
if you want.
School even?
If I agree to help you
to make you ready...
You must do exactly as I say
and when I say it,
with no exceptions,
is that understood?
Understood.
But in return,
you must fix that computer.
Fix it?
How on Earth am I gonna do that?
That's not my problem.
I'm not the one who broke it.
High caliber, high velocity.
Charged by the size of the wounds,
he was definitely shot
from some distance,
someone knew how to shoot.
Who, dammit. And why cheerleaders?
Where's the motive?
They didn't even ask for a ransom.
They want headlines.
They want mass panic.
- They got it.
- Yeah.
Let's see if you can ID that bullet.
You never know your luck.
- You holding up?
- Holding up.
I love you.
Likewise.
Gin and tonic, please, sir, governor.
Ice and slice.
Nice place.
It is.
- Been here before, then, have you?
- It's my regular spot.
Oh, well, you're a local. Nice.
Don't I know you?
Do you?
Yeah.
You're that Mr. Fox,
that scientific chap
from Wayne Enterprises, ain't you?
That is me.
Alfred Pennyworth.
Young Master Bruce Wayne's guardian.
Oh, yes?
It's funny how it came, knowing him.
Coincidence, I mean, me bumping
into you like this, I mean...
I was just thinking about you.
Okay, Mr. Pennyworth, I'll bite.
What were you thinking about me?
Oh, no, Alfred, please.
Please, Lucius.
Lucius.
You know...
I once knew this guy,
he's called Onslow
in the Isle of Dogs
in East End of London.
Larry little scallywag he was,
you see, too smiley by half.
I never trusted him.
Okay, when one day, Lucius,
he comes bowling up to me
and he asked me to do him
this right iffy favor.
No, it doesn't matter what it was.
The point being against
my better judgment...
I agreed to do it.
But, Lucius, I told him,
I told him straight, I said,
"If you let me down Onslow,
I will tuck you up sunshine
like a kipper."
He swears blind,
swears on his mother grave
he never do such a thing,
but of course, he did,
Couldn't help himself
if he'd let me down.
So I tucked him up.
Like a kipper.
What is a kipper?
It's a type of smoked fish.
Very nice with eggs
and brown toast for breakfast.
But what I learnt
from Onslow is this.
There are two types of people
on this planet, you see.
Them you can trust...
And them you can't.
I cannot disagree.
Which kind are you?
Both kinds of people would give you
the same answer, wouldn't they?
Exactly.
Exactly right.
There lies the problem, Lucius.
You see, I need to confide in you.
But I need to know
that you are trustworthy.
Perhaps I should decline
your confidence.
I don't like the sound
of these kippers.
Yeah, well, it's just a little
bit late for that unfortunately.
I mean, it's you after all, Lucius,
that created this mess
when you told Young Master Bruce
that his dear old dead dad
was a stoic.
Oh, exactly.
You see, that's the problem.
I got no one else to turn to.
I have to confide in you.
- I see.
- Do you?
I mean, just to be crystal clear
about on this.
If it turns out...
that I can't trust you...
I swear on my mother's grave,
you, my old sausage...
are a dead man.
I have only the best intentions
for Bruce Wayne.
Well, another gin and tonic,
please, sir, governor,
and whatever this young man
is drinking, one for himself.
How are you at fixing computers?
Hey, Alvarez. You.
Let ballistics know we got
a red ball for him, will you?
On it.
Gordon.
Hello, Jim. It's Barbara.
Hi, Barbara. How are you?
Oh, me? I am fabulous. How are you?
I'm good. What's new?
Mr. cool guy, huh?
You must be mad at me.
Listen to me, if you turn
yourself in, I can help you.
How, Jim?
By taking me back to Arkham?
I don't think so.
You're sick.
Of course.
Everything is always my fault.
So typical.
Listen to me.
I know you Barbara, I know you.
You're a good, kind woman.
This isn't you.
You could always make me laugh.
How do I look?
I need to talk to
Commissioner Essen right away.
- It's an emergency.
- Yeah, go ahead.
She's right upstairs.
Yo, Commish.
Yeah.
I heard you were looking for us.
What...
Barbara...
Don't move.
You're wrong about me, Jim.
I tried telling you,
but you never listen.
I'm listening now.
Yeah, sure you are. Now.
Come on.
Let's go talk this through, huh?
Oh, it's too late for that.
Aaron...
That's enough.
I'm not sick, I'm free.
You don't get that.
I could explain it,
but you should probably
get back to work.
Who knows what went wrong
while you're gone.
Hell of a first week
you're having, Commissioner.
I wish I could tell you that things
were gonna get better for you.
But they're not.
Here, bring that up here,
you'll get a better good angle
of the room.
Why are you doing this?
To rule the world, blah, blah, blah.
But we'll settle for some dead cops
and some good PR.
- Kidding!
- Yeah, whatever, I get it.
You're just crazy.
Crazy?
Look at me.
You can see I'm not crazy.
Very soon, little man,
you will be dead.
And the world will go on without you,
you'll be nothing.
No one will even remember your name.
No, that is where you're wrong,
old lady.
We will leave a mark on the city.
We will spread across like a virus.
And do you know why?
There's nothing more contagious
than laughter!
My line.
There's nothing more contagious
than laughter.
That was strangely pleasant.
Do it again.
That's gonna leave a mark.
You got me.
My turn.
Lee!
Jim!
- Are you hurt?
- No. I...
I was in my office
and I heard gunfire and I hid.
Where were you?
Barbara was here. She lured me away.
Essen!
Hang on, Cap. Hang on.
Boss, boss, stay with me.
Breathe.
It's a new day, Jim.
This is indeed broken.
I have a lot of questions for you.
Oh, I imagine so.
- Did my father tell you everything?
- Heavens no.
Your father,
he was a very private man.
He had to be.
I simply helped with technical
resources, like this computer.
Do you know what's on it?
No, I didn't want to know,
to be honest.
- But you could fix it?
- I should think so.
But it is going to take some time.
Well, thank you for your help.
I loved your father.
I regret that I never told him so.
I regret that I didn't help him more.
Hand me the soldering iron, will you?
Yeah.
Master Bruce.
What is it, Alfred?
How are you doing, Mr. Nygma.
Here's your aspirin.
Thank you.
Detective Gordon!
Bruce.
I heard the news.
I was worried
something happened to you.
I'm very relieved.
Me too.
The last time that we met,
I was very hard on you.
I wanted to apologize.
You've been a really good friend.
She was a good woman.
Good cop.
It's good to see you
but you don't have to do this.
Let's not talk about it.
We are who we are, right?
No use fighting it.
What does Scotty say?
She'll understand or she won't.
Guys, you need to see this.
I'm reporting live from the
scene of the GCPD massacre.
We have just obtained
video footage of the attack
recorded by one of the assailants.
I wanna warn those of you watching,
what you're about to see
is very graphic.
Hello, Gotham City.
We are the Maniax.
And I'm Jerome, the shot-caller
of our little gang.
We're here to spread
a message of wisdom and hope.
Some people have no manners.
You're all prisoners.
What you call sanity
is just a prison in your minds,
that stops you from seeing
that you're just little tiny cogs
in a giant absurd machine. Wake up!
Why be a cog? Be free like us.
Just remember, smile.
Oh, time to go.
But don't worry,
we'll be back very soon.
Hang on to your hats, folks.
Because you ain't seen nothing yet!