Previously onGotham...
What's your record for how many banks
you've robbed in one day?
You can't take ownership
of everyone's problems.
We all have our flaws.
But you're still breaking the law.
I want you to throw me a wake.
Dig me up.
I would liberate Lee Thompkins
with surgical precision.
Dead or alive,
Jerome uses distractions.
Got a plan for that?
Bruce?
Jeremiah.
Oh, God, no.
He's still alive.
Jerome is dead.
Long live me.
I could not have done any of this
without your help.
Those generators that we built...
...work even better as bombs.
Sources tell us Captain James Gordon
was at the scene
and is missing and feared dead.
Investigators are certainly
looking into
what could have caused
the sudden explosion.
Harvey.
I just got off the phone
with Search and Rescue.
Whatever blew Jeremiah's bunker
was catastrophic.
There are no signs of life.
Tell 'em to keep looking.
- Harvey, I think...
- Listen.
Jim found his way out.
- Understand?
- Gotham's Police Department
has dispatched an investigative unit,
which is currently canvassing
the area,
looking for any traces
of Captain Gordon.
Screw that, and screw her.
Listen. In two minutes, Jim Gordon's
gonna come walking through that door
and chew all your asses out
for standing around
and not doing your job.
Now, first responders
are on the scene.
I want CSIs out there pronto,
and I want everyone looking for
Jeremiah Valeska and Bruce Wayne.
That's who Jim was looking for
when this whole thing went blooey.
You ain't the captain.
The captain ain't here.
I'm ranking detective.
Last time we followed you,
the Pyg slaughtered us.
All right, look, enough.
Jim trusts him, okay?
So, everybody, get back to work.
Harvey.
Jeremiah Valeska wasn't
inside the bunker when it blew.
- How do you know?
- 'Cause he's outside,
and he's not alone.
What the hell?
You might not recognize
Jerome's followers,
as I've given them
something of a makeover.
But I assure you,
they're as loyal to me
as they ever were to him.
More so.
'Cause I accomplished something
my brother never could...
...killing James Gordon.
Jeremiah! Jeremiah!
You're a liar!
Not so fast.
I have bombs planted around the city,
just like the one that killed
Jim Gordon.
Jeremiah! Jeremiah!
All you need to know is,
if I hit this detonator,
Gotham is blown back
to the Stone Age.
If I pull this trigger,
your brains are blown
through the back of your skull.
Dead man's switch. You're familiar.
It's another little something
I took from my brother,
except mine's a bit more advanced.
You shoot me, my thumb loosens,
and then boom, boom,
boom, boom.
No, you will do what I say.
You're more sick than your brother.
Don't compare me
to that short-sighted psychopath.
He just wanted to destroy things.
Me, I'm a builder.
I'm gonna create a new Gotham
in my image.
But every artist
needs a blank canvas, so...
...all of this has to go.
I detonate the explosives
in six hours.
I want the city empty when I do.
You need us to evacuate
Gotham in six hours?
That's impossible!
Then, everyone who dies screaming,
who watches their loved ones
crushed before them,
will have you to thank,
Detective Bullock.
Look...
...nobody has to die.
Well...
...except for these people.
I know seeing is believing, and I do
want you to believe me, so...
Oh, my God!
Get officers on the scene now! Go!
Six hours, Detective.
The clock is ticking.
Shame. I liked the clock tower.
Jim took me there on a date once.
Now they're both up in smoke.
Good riddance.
He always did want to die a hero.
And that was Jim's problem.
Me? I'd rather live.
- And live well.
- Hmm.
If it isn't little Penguin.
Oh, and Butch's corpse.
Hey, Tabby.
Butch.
The man responsible
for the recent fireworks
is Jeremiah Valeska.
Twin brother of our old associate.
He has plans for Gotham.
Plans we learned about
courtesy of this gentleman.
They ripped out my fingernails.
I believe that this is a golden
opportunity for cash and glory.
Normally, I would keep
both of them for myself.
But I find myself a bit short
of the necessary manpower.
- Or womanpower, if you will.
- Mm.
I'll go 50-50 on the take.
An alliance with you?
I'll pass.
Pity. With the money
we were gonna make,
I'd hoped to finally be able
to cure Butch of his condition.
Wait, what do you mean?
Hugo Strange ran Indian Hill.
Indian Hill's toxic sludge
turned Butch into this.
Hugo Strange can fix Butch.
But it won't be cheap.
Strange might be my only hope, Tabby.
Don't look at me like that.
I almost got killed fighting
your ex-boyfriend's rotting corpse.
I think it's time to return
the favor.
Fine. But Swamp Boy keeps his funk
ten feet from me at all times.
What did you have in mind?
Evacuate the city in six hours?
Five and a half hours.
And it will happen,
because this maniac
has bombs hidden all over Gotham.
Think of how many lives are at stake.
And every minute you hesitate
means fewer people get to safety.
- We'll need police.
- We are police! We're here to help.
Harper, please,
will you help the mayor?
You got it.
Holy mother of God.
Bruce Wayne.
Hey.
Bruce.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
I heard about Jim.
- Is it true?
- As far as I'm concerned,
Jim Gordon is alive, kicking,
and waiting for us to find him.
Detective.
Don't lie to me.
It's not looking good, kid.
I was hoping you could help me.
Did you see Jim?
How did you get out of the bunker?
Jeremiah and I had already
left the bunker.
Jerome, Jerome sprayed him
with a gas that drove him insane.
I'm so sick of that freaking family.
Did you hear about
Gotham Clock Tower? Huh?
This guy's got these massive
explosives...
- It's my fault.
- What?
Jeremiah had plans
to create next-generation generators.
I funded him.
Wayne Enterprises built those bombs?
Listen, the schematics
for the batteries
should be in the Wayne Enterprises
R&D lab.
Lucius could take a look at them,
figure out how to disarm the bombs.
- I'm, I'm gonna go get them now.
- No, no, no, no, no.
- You're going home.
- No, I have to do...
Look, I know you feel guilty,
but Jim Gordon was,
is important to all of us.
And it's my job, so go home.
Be with Alfred. Be safe.
It's what Jim would want.
Lucius!
Alfred, where have you been?
No, not Alfred.
I hope you didn't catch a cold
in my brother's grave.
I know those things aren't
exactly designed for the living.
What have you done?
Where's Alfred?
Such anger.
Some people, not me, of course,
might consider that ingratitude
considering all I've done for you,
all I'm still doing for you.
You mean lying to me?
Using my company to build bombs?
Trying to kill me?
Bruce, let's get something straight.
If I wanted you dead, you'd be dead.
I'd have put a bullet
through your brain
and left you to rot in that grave.
But I meant what I said.
You're my best friend,
and today I'm gonna prove it to you.
You are insane.
You killed Jim Gordon.
And if you don't want your manservant
to die, too,
you will follow my instructions
to the letter.
71 Welling Avenue.
Be there in an hour.
Tell the police and I'll know.
Just like I know
that's where you are right now.
Well, well.
Jim Gordon, back from the dead.
Where am I?
The Narrows.
I was in Jeremiah's bunker.
There was a bomb.
Ed had you followed.
His people found you after the blast.
I'll have to thank him
when I arrest him.
I'm surprised he didn't kill me.
I am, too, actually.
What do you plan to do with me?
I don't really know.
Lee, I have to get back to the GCPD.
Jerome's brother Jeremiah...
Blew up the Gotham Clock Tower
about an hour ago.
The city's being evacuated.
I have to...
It's just a painkiller.
It does make you easier to handle.
You're not going anywhere.
My jacket. In my jacket...
I got those from Jeremiah's office.
They may give us some clue
as to what he's planning.
Please, let me take them to Harvey.
Oh, Jim, you still think that you're
the only one who can save the city.
- Wait.
- Get some rest.
Doctor's orders.
Jeremiah's followers
must have taken Alfred
while I was at the cemetery.
I bet he put up a fight.
Thanks again for meeting me, Selina.
- Sure.
- I didn't have anyone else to call.
I know it's asking a lot,
so I just really appreciate...
Bruce, I'm gonna be here
whenever you need me.
Okay, that's the address.
I don't see anyone, though.
- That could be a trap, right?
- I don't know.
Jeremiah could've killed me
at the cemetery.
He wants something out of me.
Like what, to be your best friend?
Trap or not, if Alfred's in there,
I need to find out.
Alfred?
Alfred!
Alfred.
You want to help Jim Gordon?
Have you lost your mind?
You brought him here
because you thought
it would give us leverage
with the GCPD.
Yes. By holding him hostage.
This drawing is the key
to Valeska's plan.
We solve it and we trade
the information for clemency.
Perhaps.
Or, perhaps,
there's something more going on.
What happened between Jim and I
is over.
I'm trying to protect
what we've built.
I still like my plan better.
Ed, if this maniac levels
half the city,
it's gonna disrupt food distribution,
water supply, power.
The people of the Narrows
will suffer the most.
We can prevent that,
while, at the same time,
helping us out of this mess we're in.
Please.
Fine.
If this is what you want,
I will do it.
For you.
Do it for us.
After the mayor's evacuation orders,
the New Trigate Bridge is absolute...
Where are we at with the evac?
Bridges and tunnels
are bumper-to-bumper.
National Guard is bringing
in the choppers.
But we're talking
about evacuating hospitals,
nursing homes, jails.
Some people just don't want to leave.
We're seeing the same level of panic
on every bridge and tunnel...
God, what a mess.
Just make it happen.
- Okay.
- Excuse me.
All right.
Let's go over this building...
I got the schematics
from Wayne Enterprises R&D.
The Wayne kid
said the bombs were batteries.
A series of networked
self-perpetuating generators.
But when supercharged,
they contain enough energy
to level a city block.
Got it. Battery bombs from hell.
Just tell me this will help us
find and disable them.
Disable, yes. Find, no. But...
...look, look here.
Because they were created
to be networked together,
Jeremiah would have to send the
signal a centrally located core relay
in order to blow all the bombs
from a single detonator.
Lucius, just English, please.
Sorry. The bombs are connected
by a nervous system.
The core relay is the brain.
We find that, we destroy that...
We can stop the bombs from going off.
- Yes.
- But how do we find it?
How do we find this brain?
Oh, Bruce.
You are about to have
a very transformative experience.
I envy you.
Call our friend.
Tell him to kill the butler.
He's no longer necessary.
Oswald Cobblepot.
Barbara Kean.
In my stronghold.
Not one step closer, Mr. Valeska.
And is that my dear Jongleur
with my core relay in his hand
and a grenade taped to his mouth?
Indeed, it is.
Huh. Well...
...it seems you have the upper hand.
Undoubtedly.
And now...
...we have our own demands.
50 million dollars.
That's what you want.
It's a nice round number.
I don't quite have that
on me right now.
You gave the mayor six hours
to evacuate Gotham.
An impossible task.
Let him buy another hour.
He will save thousands of lives.
50 million dollars
will seem cheap.
I see.
I play the villain,
you get away scot-free and rich.
I get you the money,
you give me back my core relay.
That is usually
how a handoff works. Yeah.
You drive a hard bargain,
but I'll see what I can do.
Just like that?
After knowing your brother,
I expected something more...
Insane?
I'm nothing if not sane
and reasonable.
Two things my brother never valued.
Which is why I'll be successful
where he failed.
Well, that and being
vastly more intelligent.
Now, to see about your money.
This is Jeremiah Valeska.
I'd like to speak to the mayor.
I have additional demands.
Yes, really.
50 million, unmarked bills.
I'll tell you the location.
We're not just
gonna hand this thing over
and let him destroy Gotham, are we?
Of course not.
Once we get the money,
we kill Jeremiah and his people,
give the core relay to the police,
split the 50 million,
and are hailed
as the heroes of Gotham.
And we cure Butch.
And that. Certainly.
Would you believe it?
They put me on hold.
Well...
...there's always plan number two.
- Get down!
- Wait!
Are you out of your mind?
Why do you keep insisting I'm insane?
What's insane about
having a backup plan?
Something Jongleur never knew about.
And, so you know, this building
is within the blast radius.
And because of your interference,
I'm gonna detonate the bombs
as soon as I'm far enough away
to observe the destruction in peace.
No! You promised the city six hours!
And whose fault is it
that I changed my mind?
Tell our men to rewire the bombs
to work in direct sequence.
And, the rest of you...
...kill these idiots.
Alfred!
Hello, Bruce.
Jeremiah!
I imagine, you're wondering
why is Jeremiah doing this?
My brother once said,
"All it takes is one bad day
to reduce the sanest man alive
to lunacy."
Jerome gave me what I thought
was the worst day of my life.
But only by losing everything
was I able to face
what was inside me.
And I believe I've seen
something very special
- inside of you as well.
- Alfred.
But to free it, you'll have to lose
everything and everyone
you hold dear.
I instructed Scarecrow to mix up
something exceptional.
No!
Your butler is going to show you
the path ahead.
Now watch closely.
No. No!
Alfred!
Hello, sleepyhead.
You do realize the city
is about to be blown up?
It's an odd time for a nap.
You know that she drugged me.
Yeah. Don't really care.
Thank you, gentlemen.
I want to make one thing very clear.
If Gotham becomes a rock pile,
I mind zero percent.
I'm only helping you
because I'm with Lee now.
Fine. Whatever.
Feign nonchalance. It's very cute.
It's almost convincing.
Ed, Jeremiah Valeska is threatening
to destroy half the city.
You really think I care
if you've deluded yourself
into thinking you and Lee
are a couple?
You see...
...that is my point.
You don't believe that Lee
could actually love me, do you?
Honestly? No.
You're a psychopath and a murderer.
And the fact that you need me
to validate your crazy fantasy
means that you don't believe it
either.
That doesn't matter.
What matters is stopping Jeremiah
from killing thousands of people,
so can we...
- Yeah. We're gonna settle this.
- Ed.
No, Jim.
This isn't the GCPD.
Here, I make the rules.
So, we're not gonna do this
until we talk about
what I want to talk about.
Lee's changed. I accept that.
Maybe she will never be
the person that I knew.
Fine. But she is not
who you think she is.
The fact that she's with you
in whatever way she's with you...
Oh, Jim.
She's with me in every way.
Means she wants something from you.
So when it's done,
she'll get rid of you.
So, you're saying
that she wouldn't be with a killer?
And yet, she was with you.
And you, Jim, are 10 times the killer
that I ever was.
You have a point.
Maybe that's why she's not
with me now.
Can we do this?
Why not?
Just try to keep up.
I'll speak slowly.
So, most labyrinths
are constructed as contiguous lines
along concentric circles.
- One way in, one way out.
- But this one's different.
Undoubtedly.
Those red rectangles...
...they're unbound on one side.
And they overlap black lines
which would lead out
of the labyrinth.
So, maybe we're not looking
at plans...
...but the end result.
Voilá.
Look familiar?
So, this...
...is Wayne Enterprises.
This would be Gotham Central Bank.
These are the buildings Jeremiah's
planning to demolish with his bombs.
Once those buildings are blown,
they collapse and create the
labyrinth from the finished drawing.
Jeremiah lived his entire life
in a maze.
Now, he's trying to remake the city
into the place he feels most safe.
It's actually rather elegant.
I need to get to the GCPD.
Yeah, no, sorry.
You're not going anywhere until
we get this information to the mayor.
Lee and I have some legal knots
we need untangled.
Yeah. Before we spend
the rest of our lives together.
So, you're gonna use this
to hold the city hostage?
Time is running out.
Well, then the mayor would be wise
to forgive Lee and I
our indiscretions.
Ed, wait.
There's one thing I can't figure out.
One?
You're being a little kind
to yourself.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
I think you made a mistake.
Where?
Get the core relay, he says.
Have the upper hand, he says.
Finally.
Let's get the hell out of here before
Jeremiah blows us all to smithereens.
This is all your fault, Oswald.
- You'd better...
- Fix it. I know.
- What?
- Harvey.
Is this Oswald?
I'm, kind of busy.
I have information regarding
Jeremiah Valeska's plan.
What information?
- Wait a second. Is that gunfire?
- Just listen.
Jeremiah is not honoring
the six hours.
He will blow the bombs as soon as
he can watch the catastrophe
from a safe distance.
Jeremiah said something
about rewiring the bombs
to communicate with each other.
He called it a direct sequence.
Communicate with each other.
Harvey.
Harvey!
It's a backup system from
when they operated as batteries.
That means we can disrupt them
by disarming the first bomb
in the sequence.
It's like removing one light
from a string of Christmas lights.
If only we knew where the bombs were.
He's back.
- Hey.
Gordon is alive.
Jim! Oh!
Oh, buddy.
All right, easy there, big fella.
Remember, I just got blown up.
- How'd you get out of the bunker?
- It's a long story.
But what matters is,
I have the locations of every bomb
Jeremiah planted.
Alfred.
Jeremiah said Bruce Wayne
might try to bring his friends.
I suppose you're one of them.
What? No. I just wandered in here.
I think our little experiment
is about to get
much more interesting.
Jeremiah wasn't bluffing.
There's at least a dozen bombs
on this map.
But you're saying if we disarm
one of them in the sequence,
we'll stop all of them
from going off.
And according to this,
the closest one is just a mile away.
I need to look at the schematics
to determine the best way
to neutralize them.
Alert the bomb squad.
Tell 'em to meet me there.
Wait. Harvey.
Let the bomb squad handle this.
You don't have to go.
Yes, I do. I need this, Jim.
Yeah.
It doesn't matter.
The experiment is nearing
its conclusion.
Your friend will soon be driven mad.
Stop!
No!
Alfred.
Alfred, please.
Please stop.
Alfred.
Alfred. Alfred, stop!
Alfred!
Just stop. Alfred. Please.
No!
- No!
- Brucy.
Give me a smile.
Smile.
Alfred, listen to me.
You can beat this.
You can fight this.
Alfred, you're stronger than him.
Do not let him win!
No! No! Alfred!
- Bruce. Bruce. Bruce. Bruce.
- Alfred! Alfred!
Breathe. Look at me.
Scarecrow was just pumping
his fear gas in here.
You were only seeing
what he wanted you to.
- No, no, no, no, no.
No, Bruce, Bruce, Bruce.
Bruce, Bruce!
Listen. Listen to me. Listen.
Look at me, look.
Just look at me.
Look, I'm fine.
It's me.
It's Alfred.
Alfred.
Hey.
I'm at the site.
Where the hell's the bomb squad?
The evacuation's jamming the streets.
They're still en route.
I can't wait. I got to go in.
Do you see the bomb?
I don't know what it's supposed
to look like,
but I think it is exactly
what I'm staring at.
Lucius, we got to do this thing.
- Harvey...
- Listen. We can't wait.
We don't know when Jeremiah's
gonna set this thing off.
Then you're gonna have to unscrew
the antenna
- to activate the kill switch.
- Okay.
Lucius.
It's making some kind of weird noise.
What kind of a noise?
A bad one, and... and it's,
it's, getting all glowy.
Then, you are going to have
to work quickly.
Okay.
Jeremiah! Jeremiah!
All my life, I spent by myself.
Hidden away.
I am so glad to be sharing
this happy moment with all of you.
Today marks the dawning
of a new Gotham City.
One where we will all be free.
Now...
...shall I do the honors?
Once you unscrew the antenna,
a kill switch breaker should pop out.
Destroying it should stop the signal
from the detonator to all the bombs.
Which breaker is it?
What?
- What do you mean, which breaker?
- There are two of 'em.
Jeremiah must've changed them
since making these schematics.
- Okay. I'll break both of 'em.
- No, wait, Harvey,
one of the breakers could be
the supercharge fail-safe.
Whatever you do,
do not touch that one.
- Or?
- Or all the bombs will blow.
Lucius, they're identical.
Then, Harvey, I don't know.
- We interrupt this program...
- That's Jim Gordon!
He's not dead.
This is a message
to the followers of Jeremiah Valeska.
Jeremiah claims to have killed me.
Well, bad news, I'm alive.
No. No, no, it's a trick.
I killed him.
So, just know you're worshipping
a fraud.
A pale imitation of Jerome.
You did your worst, Jeremiah,
and I'm still here.
- You lied to us.
- Gordon's alive.
What does it matter
whether he's alive?
When I hit this switch,
we will hear the sounds
of a new world being born.
Oh, for the love of God.
Our world.
Eeny, meeny, miny, moe.
Which of you will make it blow?
Now, listen.
- He's a liar!
- He's a fake!
Liar!
Stop!
I want you all to know...
...I find your fickleness
quite hurtful.
And more so...
...very predictable.
Well, that is disappointing.
If you'd ask me this morning how many
people I was gonna kill today,
I would've been way off.
Perhaps the outcome
was not what we had hoped,
but it was worth the risk.
Ozzie, if I were you, I would
limp out of here while you still can.
Fine.
- Let's go, Butch.
- Nope.
I'm done.
Ever since we teamed up,
everything's gone to crap.
Hell, we don't even know
where Strange is.
Except I do know where Strange is.
You mean to tell me you've known
where he is the whole time
- and haven't told me?
- I just got word.
No more excuses!
He fixes me now!
And how exactly do we pay him?
I can be very persuasive.
Think. Think.
Think, think, think,
think, think, think.
How did they beat you, huh?
How did they figure you out?
Gordon must've stolen
the blueprints to the maze,
found one of the bombs,
and sabotaged the sequence.
I'll have to start again.
You're tenacious.
I like that.
Who are you?
What do you want?
I had a vision
of Gotham in flames.
Together, we can make that happen.
Well, I appreciate the offer,
but recent events have convinced me
of the benefits of working alone.
Don't be so rash.
Your dream of a new Gotham
will come to be.
With my help.
You're behind me, aren't you?
I can conquer Gotham on my own.
What makes you think
I need your help, whoever you are?
Because, my boy,
all this is not just about Gotham.
This is about Bruce Wayne.
You here to arrest me?
To thank you
and to present you with an offer.
Leave Gotham.
Start a new life somewhere else.
Alone.
And if I don't?
I know we can't change the past.
What we've done
or done to each other.
I can't pretend to recognize
the person I see before me.
But whatever happens,
after I walk out that door,
I care about you.
And I always will.
Lucius!
Call the mayor. Tell him
not to lift the evacuation order
until all the bombs
are under lock and key.
And I want every cop out there
to keep looking for Jeremiah Valeska!
What?
Give it up for Harvey Bullock!
Oh, dude! Come on!
Thank you.
Come on.
Right. Well, I'm gonna take
a very long and a very hot shower.
And then I'm gonna make us
a legendary fry-up.
Will you be joining us, Ms. Kyle?
I got no plans.
Excellent.
You all right, mate?
Good, lad.
Thank you again.
I don't know what would have
happened if you weren't there.
You're welcome.
Why do you think
he's so obsessed with you?
Jeremiah said all it takes
is one bad day
to drive a person insane.
I wonder if my parents dying
made me a little insane.
Maybe he sensed that.
Maybe he wanted to bring it out.
Well, you proved him wrong.
To be fair...
...the day's not over yet.