[1930s music playing]
[gun firing]
[record skipping]
[music stops]
[cocks gun]
[indistinct chatter]
Fire on my command.
For Gotham.
[man on radio] Mr. Gordon, your people
decided to ignore evacuation orders.
No, no, no.
It is clear you don't understand.
What's to understand, Mr. Gordon?
I'm afraid
you are not making yourself--
For the last time.
After the bridges blew
and the government
declared Gotham off-limits,
the city was up for grabs.
Given over
to criminals and murderers.
Now, territory is controlled by
whoever has enough power to hold it.
We have Penguin in City Hall,
for God sakes.
He raided the armory
and stockpiled weapons,
then re-purposed a factory
to manufacture ammunition.
[cocks gun] [gunshot]
[Gordon] It's made him unassailable.
Barbara and The Sirens
control an area around their club.
It's the only place in Gotham
not suffering for food, or booze.
Barbara trades mainly in information.
Just be gone by midnight.
It's women only.
Men can buy windows of time.
It's two minutes
past pumpkin time, sweetheart.
Word is, she enforces her rule
with an iron hand.
The west is Jonathan Crane,
the Scarecrow.
[whimpering]
[growls]
[man] I won't do it again.
[all cheering]
[screaming]
Victor Fries is further north
and warring with Firefly.
And to date, there have been
no confirmed sightings
of Jeremiah Valeska.
And then there's us.
GCPD controls a 10-block area
around the precinct,
where we feed and protect
150 civilians.
That number could grow,
as who knows how many others
are trapped around the city.
These are people who couldn't get out
when the city was abandoned.
The poor, the sick, whole families.
The government has a duty.
You have a duty to help them.
-[man] Mr. Gordon.
-Captain Gordon.
We've been over this
time and time again.
No one is allowed in
or out of Gotham.
The people we are protecting
are not criminals.
And anyone who stayed
after the evacuation order
is no longer
the government's responsibility. We are surrounded by hostile forces.
We are running out
of food, ammunition.
There are children here.
You have to evacuate them.
A committee is being formed
regarding the situation in Gotham.
Committee?
At least let us re-supply ourselves.
[sighs] We understand the situation.
You don't understand. If you did,
you would do something.
Just say we're on our own.
[static]
[doctor] Paralysis aside,
we need to operate
before her spine collapses on itself.
In truth,
she should have been evacuated.
[Alfred] Yeah, well, we tried to get her
out the night everything went to hell.
And then
they blew the bloody bridges. [Bruce] Can you operate here?
I don't think we have a choice.
[Bruce] Selina.
[crying]
-The doctor wants to operate.
-Fine.
Whatever.
I'm going to be here the whole time.
[continues crying]
[all shouting]
Enough!
The cops are getting fat
while the rest of us are starving.
Damn right!
While the rest of us are starving!
You hungry, yeah?
[indistinct shouting]
Harvey, lay off, lay off. Everyone.
Sir, everyone gets the same share.
Police and civilians alike.
If we start handing out more,
the supplies will not last.
You're lying. He's lying!
The cops get more!
That's enough!
You don't like the rules, leave.
I'm just saying--
Say it walking, putz.
-[crowd grumbling]
-[man 1] Come on! You look well-fed.
[man 2] Let's go.
Hey, come on, that's enough.
Move it out of here.
[Gordon] So, how are we doing?
[Lucius]
Well, we got a month of food left.
Less if refugees keep coming.
What did
the department of douchbag-ery say?
Same as always. Not sending any help.
Not letting anyone leave.
I had to try.
Swear to God,
I am never paying taxes again.
And if people ask?
Well, sooner or later, the government
will do the right thing.
Rebuild the bridges,
take back the city.
Just have to be patient.
And the truth?
We're on our own.
Truth is, we have no idea
what might happen.
And our job is to keep ourselves,
and everyone else, alive.
[Harvey] We're down
to our last rounds of ammo.
What if Penguin or someone else
decides to make a move?
We're sitting ducks here, man.
-[snoring]
-[pigeons cooing]
[gasps]
[siren wailing]
[exhales]
-[growling]
-[gasps]
[barking]
[Nygma] Okay. Where was I?
Happened again.
This time, woke up on a rooftop.
Same thing. No idea how I got there
or what happened
during the preceding hours.
Show yourself.
I know it's you inside there, Ed.
Idiot Ed still won't appear.
Coward.
But I know it's him controlling me
when I'm sleeping.
Why?
What is he doing?
You know, you could get someone else
to turn on the spotlight.
I like doing it.
I guess it reminds people
that even in darkness there is light.
And it reminds me.
We're low on supplies.
Government won't evac,
won't send in help.
It doesn't make sense.
I imagine from where they sit,
it's pretty easy
to ignore people's suffering.
I gave Lucius permission to raid
the Wayne Enterprise's R&amp;D lab
for whatever he could scavenge.
He's working on night-vision goggles
for your men. It's not much.
Everything helps.
Bruce, we stayed because people here
still need protection.
That hasn't changed.
I should go.
The doctor is worried
Selina's condition is getting worse.
They're going to operate.
Let me know how it goes.
Are you sorry you stayed?
No. You?
Hell, no.
Mr. Cobblepot offers 1,000 rounds
of freshly-minted 9mm stock
for 1,000 pounds of grade-A steak.
Hmm.
So, what we're hearing is true.
Cupboard's a bit bare in Penguinland.
Absolutely not.
Mr. Cobblepot just had
a hankering for red meat.
[scoffs] Please! Ozzie wants to get fat
on rib-eye
while his minions starve.
-Shocker.
-[Tabitha] I have a question.
Why hasn't your boss left his citadel
since the bridges blew?
He's scared I'm going to
stick him in the throat?
Tabby's still raw from when Penguin
murdered Butch right in front of her,
so it will have to be 2,000 rounds.
Barbara, we're not giving
that bastard anything.
Exactly.
We're trading for something we need.
No.
Honey,
no one is asking you
to forget what happened.
But how do we protect the women
who come in here every day
looking for safety?
We need this.
Penguin's time will come.
I promise.
[scoffs]
He's going to regret giving me this.
Better make it 3,000 rounds.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[officer 1] Something's out there.
There.
See? The shadow moved.
[laughing]
It's just a shadow, man.
No. Something's out there.
There, see?
[screaming]
Hey, you okay?
-[whimpering]
-[Crane growls]
[officer 2] You okay?
Don't you want me to make it stop?
Yes!
Open this door.
[whimpering]
No, no, no! Don't open the gate!
[groans]
[Crane] Split up. Take what we came for.
Kill whoever stands in your way.
Show these fools the face of fear.
[thugs shouting]
These here are the weak points.
Reinforce all barriers
that front Penguin's territory.
I want to be ready.
[generator powers down]
[people groaning]
[Harper] What the hell?
Find Lucius.
Tell him to meet me at the generator.
[heart monitor beeping]
[respirator hissing]
[Bruce] Lights are out everywhere.
[Alfred] Don't you worry, Master Bruce.
The clinic has got
its own backup generator.
[generator powers up]
You see? Everything's ship-shape
and Bristol fashion.
[Bruce] No.
Something's wrong.
Men in the basement.
They're stealing all the medicine.
Alfred, stay with Selina.
Of course,
but you can't go down there.
It's going to be pitch black.
Gonna need a torch or something.
Lucius gave me something better.
Careful.
I know
what you're thinking, Captain.
"I have so few bullets,
"do I spend one on him?
"Is it worth it?"
I already know it's not.
Now the question is,
why are you here?
It's not to steal the generator.
Why would I want light?
Fear lives in darkness.
So what then? Came for our supplies?
Exactly so.
But since I'm here,
I'll also take your life.
[both grunting]
It's been a while
since you tasted my toxin, Captain.
What are you scared of now?
Not you.
[both grunting]
[Crane screaming]
[Harvey] Hey! Hey!
They got the beans.
[man] Go, the lights are back up.
Go, go, go.
[stammers] Did you hear that?
[screams]
[body thuds]
[both grunting]
Hello?
Scared?
Hey, guys?
Look, guys, this isn't funny.
-[Bruce grunting]
-[gasping]
[Bruce groaning]
[man] Go back!
[indistinct shouting]
[crowd clamoring]
First their government abandons them,
and then some freak
dressed like a scarecrow
steals their grub.
I'd be pissed, too.
So, where are we?
[Lucius] At current consumption,
we've got a week of food.
-Go to half rations.
-We're already at half rations.
Cut them again.
The people won't be happy.
I haven't been happy in 10 years.
At least they'll be alive.
All right, that buys us two weeks.
Then what?
[Harvey] Jim, at this point,
the bastards across the river
are going to have to
step up and help.
Why start now? They haven't before.
[Harvey] For the love of God!
Because we stayed
to do the job they wouldn't. Huh?
And now they're just going to
sit back and watch while we starve,
or tear ourselves apart,
because that's what's
going to happen.
[Gordon] I know, Harv,
but right now, we have to
tell these people something.
[Bruce] Tell them help is coming.
I'll fly in supplies.
We tried that.
We couldn't even get permission
to take off.
Zero tolerance. Nothing in or out.
Well, I'm not asking for permission.
It's ready.
Alfred has already radioed
to have it delivered
from our East Bay hangar.
We can have a supply truck here
within hours.
Man, it is nice to have
a billionaire around.
[Gordon] Even if it succeeds,
the government's going to find out.
It's a one-time solution.
[Bruce] Scarecrow's men
didn't just take food.
They stole medicine from the clinic.
There are people in pain.
Harvey, tell the people
help is on the way.
[Harvey] You got it.
How's Selina?
She's strong. She'll pull through.
[Selina]
Doc says the surgery was a success.
My spine
is not going to turn to jelly.
I'll still
never be able to walk again,
so, that's a bummer.
There's limited resources here.
But there's hope
once we join the mainland.
Gee...
For a second there, I was worried.
Selina, I know you're in pain.
Some medicine is on its way.
You know what's funny?
Jeremiah shot me to get to you.
[scoffs] After all the things I've done,
what did me in was being your friend.
I just wish Jeremiah had killed me.
Doctors can't help her.
She needs the witch.
[indistinct chattering]
How's the mood?
They're hanging in there.
They love their Jim Gordon.
But if that chopper doesn't come,
it'll be bad.
It'll come.
[operatic music playing]
[Penguin grunts]
Feels good.
Missing something, no?
Put a knife on it.
-[door opens]
-[chuckling]
Another shutdown at the factory.
A worker fell into a hydraulic press.
It appears he passed out from hunger.
Sir, I worry, if we don't increase
the food allowance--
Mr. Penn, I feel
for all of our workers.
But I cannot give what I do not have.
Overcooked!
[dog whines]
[Penguin] Edward.
[chuckles]
Such a good boy! [chuckles]
Quality at the factory
is also suffering.
-More misfires.
-Nonsense!
[Edward whines]
[Penguin] Our rounds are fine.
And now you've upset Edward.
Ow!
As you see, more misfires.
Sir, if we don't
give better quality...
-Stop.
-Sir?
-Shut up!
Shut up.
Do you hear that?
[chuckles]
You said yourself, Penguin has
locked himself in City Hall
with a small army.
-I know that.
-And I know you miss Butch.
Do you? Because he only did it
to hurt me.
That's why I have to make it right.
And how are you going to do that
and not get killed?
I need you, too.
[helicopter approaching]
Tabby, you hear me?
Is that a chopper?
There it is.
This is Bruce Wayne. I'm at the GCPD.
We can see you.
[pilot] Copy that, Mr. Wayne.
Moving toward the rendezvous point.
Mayday. Mayday.
We've been hit.
We're going down hard.
Harvey, chopper went down.
Get a team together now.
Oh, my God.
Chopper went down
in Low Boyz territory.
I expect we'll have to
fight our way in and out.
I know it's a lot to ask,
but without those supplies,
we're done.
[Harper] Can we get some more ammo?
We're running dry down here.
Be happy you got what you got
and get in.
Alfred, I expected to see Bruce here,
wanting to come along.
[Alfred] Well, you'd think, wouldn't you?
It's his chopper, his pilots.
Maybe thought you wouldn't allow it.
[car engine starts] Just keep an eye on things
while I'm gone.
[sirens wailing]
[indistinct chattering]
[tires screeching]
Hello.
The Low Boyz, is it? [chuckles]
I suspect you know who I am.
This ain't your turf, bird man.
Be that as it may,
I'm here to claim that.
[guns cocking]
Like hell.
[sighs]
Get it in the truck.
-[tires squealing]
-[siren wails]
[Gordon] Oswald!
[Penguin] Jim!
I thought you might show up.
It is so good to see you, old friend.
How are you faring
in these troubled times?
Tell your men to step away
from the chopper.
Sorry. Mouths to feed.
And you know all about that,
don't you?
I hear you are
up to your ears in refugees.
We're protecting children,
families. We need those supplies. You shouldn't have
shot it down, Oswald.
You think I did this?
[laughs] No, no, no.
That would mean that I knew
a chopper was coming,
which I did not.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
We're still taking everything,
but I did not fire the shot.
It was an RPG. Who else has
that kind of firepower?
Fair point.
But if it was me,
wouldn't I just admit it?
I mean, it's not like
I'm going to be arrested. [chuckling]
Then who was it?
[Penguin] No idea.
Now, nice as it was catching up,
it's time you skedaddle
while you can.
We are kind of
outgunned here, partner.
[Penguin] Listen to Harvey.
After all we have been through,
do not make me kill you.
Not like this.
[groaning]
You should have stayed home.
Listen to me.
I know you're upset about Butch.
-He thought you were his friend.
-I was his friend!
Liar!
You put a knife in my mother's back.
His blood is on your hands!
You really think that
I expected to come here
and walk away?
Jim, are you just going to
let her kill me like this
in cold blood?
Jim, listen to me.
You are not the only one
keeping Gotham from the abyss.
I am, I provide stability.
I may have pulled the trigger,
but you killed Butch.
Shut up and die.
[misfired gunshot]
[clicking]
[laughing]
[Tabitha grunting]
If that was one of my bullets,
I will certainly be having a word
with my foreman.
Unacceptable!
Say hello to Butch.
[Barbara screaming]
[whispers] Barbara.
Don't.
[yelling]
-I'm out.
-Me, too.
Oh, Jim, sounding a little quiet
over there.
What the hell do we do now?
[grunting]
[yelling]
[groans]
I know I shouldn't be here.
But look,
Penguin had a truck out back.
I took these, and there's more.
I could kiss you, kid.
For the record, this is not
how I wanted things to go.
[Barbara] You son of a bitch.
I will rip out your heart!
Quiet! Now that is exactly
the kind of talk
that's going to force my hand.
But for old times' sake,
I will give you a chance.
Can we move past this?
Say the whole Tabitha-Butch chapter
is over.
I am going to feed your guts
to the rats,
you beaky-nosed freak!
So, no.
[scoffs]
[gun cocks]
What's the plan, boss? Cover me.
Oswald!
I want to make a deal.
A deal, Jim?
We split
whatever's in the chopper 50-50,
and you let Barbara go.
No.
He does not get to
limp out of here alive!
[groans]
I got a deal for you, Jim.
She dies, I take everything,
and you go home
and reflect long and hard
on my generosity!
[Gordon] And if I say no?
What happens
when the government finds out
you murdered the only cops
left in Gotham?
Nothing.
Jim, as far as I can tell,
you have nothing to offer,
and you're out of ammo.
[groans]
[screaming]
Not anymore.
Truth is, I was never going to
make that deal.
I need all those supplies. Load up!
[groans loudly]
[officer] We got it. Here we go, people.
Heads up!
[Harvey] You think Penguin
is going to pull through? [Gordon]
Cockroaches are hard to kill.
At least he'll be
out of commission for a while.
You had him dead to rights.
You could have put him down for good.
Yeah, shot a man without warning.
Three months ago, I would have
lost my badge for that.
Three months ago, we weren't
fighting for our survival.
You think it didn't cross my mind? I know what we're up against, Harvey.
No one is coming to help.
Why didn't you do us all a favor
and put that murdering son of a bitch
in a hole?
You want rules for this game?
I'll tell you.
I'll make it simple, okay?
You win, or you die.
The next time, shoot to kill.
-Are you all right?
-No.
But we're alive, so that's something.
What's up?
The medicine
has just been taken to the clinic.
I need to check on Selina.
Yeah, sure. I'll get you a ride.
Hey! Let me know how she is.
And, Bruce...
Next time you want to help, just ask.
You've earned a place here.
[radio static]
[woman on radio] Captain Gordon? Hello?
Captain Gordon, come in.
Captain Gordon, do you read me?
Hello?
Come in.
This is James Gordon.
Who am I speaking to?
A friend.
We want you to know
you have allies across the river.
We will find a way to help you.
And who are you?
[gasps]
Get out of here!
Really?
A dumpster?
[breathing heavily]
[yells]
What are you doing to me?
Show yourself!
What is happening to me?
I promise.
If it's the last thing I do,
I will kill him!
[Penguin screaming]
My leg!
He shot my leg!
I just fixed this.
Mr. Cobblepot,
if you could hold still.
Put out the word.
One hundred thousand rounds
of ammunition
to whoever kills Jim Gordon.
I want his head!
[screaming]
[door closes]
[gasps and whimpers]
[Selina screaming]
Selina!
[Selina] Let me go!
Let me go!
[sobbing] I can't use my legs.
I have no reason to... I can't...
You should have just let me do it.
Let her do what? What happened?
She was trying to kill herself.
I've got restraints
for when she wakes.
I told you.
You want to cure her?
You have to go to the witch.
And where do I find this witch?
-[woman] Thank you so much.
-No problem.
-Thank you very much.
-[Harvey] Saint Jim of Gotham. All right.
Hey. Every new refugee who comes in,
I want questioned.
We need information
on Jeremiah Valeska.
I haven't heard that clown's name
in three months.
Why now?
Just call it a hunch.
Well, rather than a week of food,
we've got six weeks.
-It's not a lot.
-Yeah, but it's better than we were.
Don't give up hope.
Captain Gordon! Captain Gordon!
What's going on?
I was on duty
at the Thompson Street barricade.
He just appeared.
He said he needed to see you.
What happened, son?
Where did you come from?
Past the train station. [Harvey]
That's on the other side of town.
This kid must have made it through
half a dozen sectors to get here.
[Will] My brothers and sisters...
They're killing us.
[Gordon] Who is?
[Will] You have to help us.
[Gordon] Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Get him to the clinic.
[Will coughs]
I know you're all asking,
"Why are we still here
"when our own government
won't help us?"
It's simple.
We're supposed to be
giving these people hope.
Hope that if they're in danger,
someone will come.
We will come.