Previously on Gotham...
Where is Xander Wilde?
My God.
There's two of them.
I'm gonna drive you mad, brother.
All of Gotham
will be joining you, too.
You shall become the Demon's Head.
She's got the mark
of the Demon's Head.
No woman has ever been allowed
to lead the League of Shadows.
The sisters of the League
are yours to command.
Tell me what I need to know.
I could have killed Jerome,
and I didn't.
Don't take so much responsibility
that you get yourself killed.
I came up with a plan
to turn this city into a madhouse.
Oh, we're gonna need
a lot more of this!
Thank you all
for coming this evening.
As your interim mayor,
I know my recent appointment
was sudden,
and perhaps a bit
of a shock to some.
Quite frankly, I was shocked.
What is important now
is the future of this great city.
That is why I'm meeting
with all of you.
Well, Mayor, as chairperson of
Gotham's Moral Authority Society,
our members have been,
quite frankly, unnerved
by the recent going-ons
in our great city.
We have seen criminals take office,
gunfights in our streets,
corruption...
Mrs. Haverstock.
The Commissioner and I have worked
tirelessly these past few weeks
to improve the way this city
conducts itself.
Wyatt, everything all right?
We're looking into it now, sir.
Did a window blow open?
It's gotten so cold.
- What's happened?
- Don't come any closer.
No!
Good evening, everyone.
What do you want with us?
Sorry, no time for questions,
Mr. Mayor.
You see, your presence
is urgently needed elsewhere.
Whatever you expect as ransom,
I will double it.
I have access
to the police pension fund.
Wow, that could be a lot of money.
Tempting, but no thanks.
Bridgit, isn't it?
I can get you safe passage
from the city,
money, a new home...
It was people like you that
locked me up in Strange's lab,
and thanks to that,
there is no Bridgit anymore.
I can get you a pardon, son.
All will be forgiven.
Just stop this lunatic.
Lunatic's a little harsh.
I prefer "visionary."
Oswald, can't you do something?
Afraid not.
I am with Mr. Valeska 100%.
Every cop in this city
will be looking for us,
and when they find you,
expect no mercy,
just a hail of bullets.
So serious.
That's why your approval ratings
are so low.
Hey, tell you what.
Try threatening me again,
but this time, try it with a smile.
Oh! See, this is what's wrong.
Nobody knows how
to have fun anymore, right?
But see our friend down there,
bag head?
He's figured out a way to solve that.
It's time to give this city
the boost it needs.
Time to stop taking ourselves
so seriously.
I mean, come on, Gotham,
what do you have to lose?
Except your sanity.
You gonna tell me why we needed
to come to the garage, Alfred?
Happy birthday, Master Wayne.
You remembered.
Of course I remembered.
I bloody love your birthdays.
Your seventh was an absolute blinder.
Yeah, I remember you had about 50 kids
come up here,
but you were off outside on your own.
You were obsessed by this one gift
that your dad gave you,
this bright red wagon.
You were in the garden all day,
collecting all these rocks.
When I asked you, "What are you
gonna do with these rocks?"
You said, "I'm gonna build a home
for my wagon.
"A secret place
that only I know about."
What's this?
Well, it's the reason why I brought you
down to the garage, Master Bruce.
Alfred, I don't know what to say.
V8, five-liter,
460-horsepower engine.
Painted matte black,
anti-reflective,
very difficult to see at night.
Oh, and of course this...
100% bulletproof.
Best be prepared, eh?
Oh, mate.
Jim, hey, what gives?
The mayor and the police commissioner
have been kidnapped by Jerome.
Got every cop in the city out there
searching all the spots
Jerome has been seen the last week.
You got something for me?
I was gonna say I just won 100 bucks
in the scratch-off lotto
at the liquor store,
and we could go to the track with it,
but you can do your thing first.
- Gordon.
- We need to talk.
- Oswald?
- I'm out back. Come alone.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
All right.
Well, this is a first.
Are you doing anything about Jerome?
We're looking for him.
Do you know where he is?
And if I did, do you really think
I would just tell you?
Have you march in there,
guns blazing?
He needs to be stopped.
He has everyone under his thumb.
Freeze, Firefly, Hatter.
They are all part of his plan.
A dark, terrible plan.
Which is?
Scarecrow has made a gas for him.
- Like the fear toxin?
- Worse.
Much worse.
I saw it turn someone into
a maniacal, cackling, violent animal.
What does he plan to do with it?
He's smart. He hasn't shared
the details of his plans with anyone.
Instead, we all have a separate task
to perform.
Such as?
He has yet to give me my role.
Why did you come here
if you're not gonna help me?
He scares the living hell
out of me, okay?
I mean, I was willing to play along
with him for a while.
Perhaps he had a way
to make us all rich,
or return to the good old days,
you know.
But nothing good will come of this.
Or maybe you just don't like
the competition.
Jerome casts quite the shadow.
Oh, please.
He's a maniac. An anarchist.
He is not interested
in money or power.
And I am an honest criminal, Jim.
Where is he? Where is the gas?
He only tells you what he needs to,
when he needs to.
I just know he has to be stopped.
Jim, hey!
You down here?
- Jim?
- Yup.
Hey, a uni just spotted Jerome
near Paisley Square.
All right, let's go.
Hey, what's happening to my mic?
Hey, buddy, beat it, will you?
I'm trying to work here.
Whoo!
Where's everyone going?
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are the Arkham Asylum Lunatics,
and we came here to blow some minds!
Sorry to interrupt your little show.
But you are gonna love this next one.
Introducing Mayor Pritchard,
Commissioner Reynolds,
Archbishop McGregor,
and this lady.
Whoever she is.
This is everybody.
Everybody, say hi.
Now, as you can see,
we're still waiting
for two guests of honor.
But in the meantime,
let's go over the rules
of tonight's entertainment, shall we?
Dynamite.
Trigger.
I don't get what I want,
boom.
Headless people.
And if any of you are thinking
of going anywhere,
you'll die, too.
Now, the one man
who can get me what I want.
Calling Gordon.
Calling Captain James Gordon.
I speak on behalf of myself
and all other gang leaders
in this city
when I say your arrogance
and disrespect
will no longer be tolerated.
You beat and then dragged
my brother from here
like a dog.
Your brother's an ass.
He abuses our staff and refuses
to pay his exorbitant tab.
He is my brother,
and he demands your respect.
And I suppose an apology
would be out of the question.
Your blood will be his apology.
Thought so.
I could have handled them.
That's the advantage of having
your own personal army, Tabs.
You don't have to.
Isn't that right?
What's wrong?
Ra's al Ghul chose you,
no one else, to pass on his spirit.
We will serve you, protect you,
of course,
but surely you intend to
continue his legacy,
and not just remain here
in this place.
What does that mean?
"Continue his legacy."
I like the sound of that.
As I told you,
we have much more to show you.
Are you ready?
Yes.
What the hell was that?
Gentlemen, ladies,
your assistance is urgently required.
Be careful,
these are very dangerous materials.
We're counting on it.
More laughing gas,
we need to make.
There's no time to waste.
We need it in bulk, you see.
Well...
Well, how much of it do you need?
Oh!
This much.
Ladies and gentlemen,
as I live and breathe,
James Gordon is in the house.
I'm not talking to you
until I can get up there
and check on the well-being
of your hostages.
First of all, Jim, you're late.
Secondly, I think I'm the one
who should be making demands.
Don't you?
What you're doing is an act
of terror, Valeska.
Ask our mayor
what this city's policy is
on negotiating with terrorists.
"Terrorists"?
Frankly, I'm offended.
No, no, no.
That's close enough, Gordon.
And none of you go anywhere, either.
Dead man's trigger.
This falls out of my hand
for any reason, and... Bang!
I got two empty chairs here.
You haven't even asked me
who they're for yet.
All right. I'll bite.
Who are they for?
Come on, James.
You're a detective.
Do some detecting.
Jeremiah, your brother.
Bingo. That's one.
And the other?
Well, the only other
irksome do-gooder
who's ever spoiled
my fun in this town.
Bruce Wayne.
No.
No?
You can take me.
I'll sit up there with one
of those things around my neck,
but I won't let you have him.
Oh, I don't want you, Jim.
I want my brother,
and I want Bruce.
I want them now.
All right, let me get these people
out of here, I'll come up there...
You are not listening to me.
And that is forcing my hand.
Jerome.
No!
Bring me my brother.
Bring me Wayne.
Bring them now.
I'll get some plates.
You know, for a billionaire,
your security system is lame.
Miss Kyle.
Thank you, Alfred.
Enjoy.
Thank you.
For what?
Visiting me on my birthday.
Oh!
I actually didn't know
it was your birthday,
I just happened to be strolling
in the neighborhood.
Either way, it's good to see you.
I knew it was an act.
What?
The brat,
and the drinking, the friends.
It was an act.
I think you're more sure
about that than me.
Master Bruce,
we have visitors.
Bruce, we need your help.
What happened?
Don't you know it's rude
to keep a guy waiting?
Bring me my hostages, James.
My trigger finger is getting itchy.
The hostages he wants
are his brother and you.
What, you're having a laugh.
No bloody way.
I don't like it any more
than you do,
but, Bruce, you have to trust me.
Lucius and I have a plan.
You know what?
I don't think
you're taking me seriously enough.
Well, all right.
Let's see.
Eenie, meeny, miny, mo.
One of these people got to... Go.
Oh, it's that guy.
Oh, well.
Did you see what just happened?
That man's a raving bloody lunatic.
He can't be trusted.
For once, I agree with Alfred.
Bruce, listen to me.
With your help,
we can prevent more deaths.
What's the plan?
Jerome is using
a short-wave radio trigger
with a dead man's switch.
If we can cut the signal,
he won't be able to activate
the explosives.
This emits a powerful signal
that disables all radio waves
close to it.
Once within a few feet
of Jerome's device,
his trigger will be useless.
It will give us the time
for the snipers
to get a clean shot on Jerome,
Firefly, and the others.
If I wear this, then that gives you
time to take them out?
Correct.
Are you sure it's gonna work?
I'm positive.
99% positive.
What are we waiting for?
Those people need our help.
Good man.
Ra's owned this house
for as long as the city has existed.
He said he kept his secrets in here.
Ancient secrets.
None of us have ever seen
what's behind this door.
It remains locked.
And there is no key.
Tried dynamite?
No need.
Our master chose you for a reason.
All my life,
I have known
that I was meant for more,
that there was something deep
inside of me that I couldn't explain.
I'm home.
Sir, we got target in sight.
No way in from below the stage.
Four of my men have found positions.
Good. Stay low, hang tight.
No hair triggers.
One missed shot means adio's Mayor.
Copy that.
Standing by.
I watched the news.
I know why you're here, Mr. Gordon.
And you must be out of your mind
if you think I'm gonna be led
like a lamb to slaughter.
I understand your concern,
but your brother doesn't bluff.
If we ignore his demands,
there's no telling what he might do.
We can block his remote signal
with this.
If you and Bruce can get
within a few feet of him,
it will disable his remote.
He'll be a siting duck.
Our snipers can take it from there.
For God's sake, Gordon.
You have to know what he wants.
To murder us both on live television.
Mr. Valeska.
I'm Bruce Wayne.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Likewise.
I wish the circumstances were better.
May I ask what it is
you've been working on?
Yeah, it's a compact electrical
engine. It generates power.
Fascinating.
How much power?
Just two could light up every
building south of Westford Bridge.
You have a brilliant mind.
And we all hope we can soon
be rid of your brother,
so that you can carry out your work
free from fear.
I understand if you choose
not to help us today,
but I trust that Captain Gordon
and Mr. Fox
will see that no harm comes to me.
But, even if it does,
maybe by facing Jerome
I can show the people of Gotham
that standing up to terror
is the only way
to take its power away.
Well said.
- Harvey.
- Hey.
Just got word
that Freeze and Scarecrow
broke into Wayne Industries'
chemical lab.
Jerome's playing the long game here,
but we're not gonna be sure what
it is unless we get ahead of him.
The gas.
Penguin told me about
a new Scarecrow toxin.
Head over to the lab.
We're on our way to the square.
They've got a weapon.
Poison gas.
Okay, let's go.
Thank you.
You two.
Hey. Hey, buddy.
What happened?
What's so funny?
No, no, no, don't.
Ma'am, let me help you.
What happened?
They made us make it. Tons of it.
Where is it?
It's gone. They took it.
Well, look who decided to show up.
We were starting to get nervous,
especially the mayor here.
My guest of honor.
Please, take your seats on stage.
Come on.
Don't be shy.
It's all right.
We don't have all day.
It's activated.
Just let them get a little closer.
On my command.
My men have all targets in view.
Standing by.
Hi, brother.
Now.
Fire. All targets, fire.
I had my guys take up the best
vantage points last night.
So they've been watching
your little SWAT team all day.
Now, Bruce, brother dear.
Get up on stage.
Time to get this party
really started, huh?
What are you doing here?
This is a restricted area.
Our cargo is too precious to waste.
Let me give you something
I like to keep up my sleeves
for times just like these.
Oh, my God!
You can pilot
this contraption alone, sir?
Yes.
Then look into my eyes.
The kidnappings.
The concert in the square.
All to draw the biggest crowd,
so we can drop the laughing gas
on them.
This is madness.
I thought you'd appreciate
the beauty of it all.
But Jerome was right.
You know he anticipated
your betrayal?
That's right.
You went to Gordon.
Judas.
Tie him up.
Put him on the blimp.
Jerome wants him
to have a bird's-eye view.
This book tracks Ra's' legacy
dating back nine centuries.
Did you know he not only
overthrew governments,
but infiltrated royal families?
Ra's influenced history.
He was a cult leader.
And he still has them brainwashed.
And what about me, am I brainwashed?
There are things written here
that could change the way
we view the past forever.
Perhaps I'm the one
to bring that change to light.
Look.
This book was compiled
by shamans and mystics
from all over Eastern Asia
and the Middle East.
"Shamans and mystics."
Give me a break.
It contains formulas
for potions and incantations
set to raise demons.
To curse our enemies
and contact the dead.
This isn't you.
The Barbara I know would have
already sold all of this junk
- to the highest bidder.
- "Junk"?
This is my destiny.
And being with me and Selina
at the club, that isn't?
You begged me to partner with you.
Can't you see who that is up there?
That is me and Ra's 400 years ago.
Oh, please.
- That doesn't even look like you.
- It looks exactly like me.
It is me.
I have finally found my true purpose.
I'm not gonna let your jealousy
distract me.
Ladies, escort Ms. Galavan
to the street.
I'll show myself out.
Actually, I think it's time
my loyal servants
taught you some manners.
Why don't you do it?
Because I am the one true heir
of an immortal god's ancient dynasty.
And I don't dirty my fingers
with the likes of you anymore.
No parent will admit it.
But everyone's got their favorites.
Right, brother?
The one who cleans their room,
does their homework,
doesn't try to kill everybody.
Little Mr. Perfect here.
Yeah, he was that guy.
He got adopted by rich folks.
He went to the top schools,
then a top college.
Meanwhile, I got dragged
to the circus
by my depressed, alcoholic mother.
Forced to clean up
elephant dung every day.
Who cares?
Do you know how big
those things are, folks?
But I know something
that Mommy and Daddy,
they never knew.
You're as crazy as I am.
No.
It's in your DNA.
See,
we got the same blood
running through us.
We are practically identical.
You are a killer.
It's your nature.
Stop trying to fight it.
Take your best shot.
Hey, what the hell happened?
Snipers are dead.
Get up on the roof,
take as many as you can.
All right, just know a bunch
of chemicals are heading this way.
Scarecrow had the Wayne chemists
mix it up.
That's why he's been stalling.
He wants a big crowd.
He's gonna release the laughing gas
right here.
We need to evacuate the area.
Get these people out of here.
Do whatever you have to.
Get them out of here.
Time to kill this maniac
once and for all.
That was so good! I love you.
Hey, hey! Look! Up in the sky!
Holy crap.
Excuse me, sir. Could you help me?
No can do, sport.
Gotta get this rig into position
for the boss.
And where is that?
Paisley Square.
Almost there.
Then I can drop the load
with this lever.
You turn this thing around right now!
Can you not see that...
Like I said, pal,
no can do.
It's coming.
Get into position.
Holy moly.
Jim, are you seeing this?
Yeah, get everyone out of here.
I'm going after Jerome.
I can take it down with a shot.
And risk spilling the chemicals?
Oh, yeah, right.
Oswald?
Jim! Jim, help me.
They knocked me out,
and now I am in some blimp
with that horrible gas.
And the pilot,
he's been hypnotized.
You're on the blimp?
Yes. Yes, you have to help me.
No, you're gonna help us.
You're near the river.
I need you to steer it over there.
Steer a blimp?
Are you out of your mind, Jim?
I don't even drive my own car.
If you don't, thousands will die.
Maybe worse.
What's worse than that?
How can you run an empire
in a city full of lunatics?
Hands up.
Beautiful, isn't she?
Just give me a second.
Gotta call Tyler,
tell him he's in position.
Yes?
- Not cool.
- Jerome?
Jerome?
I'm in position...
Doesn't matter.
Too late anyway.
Bombs away!
Funny.
No!
Come on.
Now, come on.
Up! Up! Up!
Oh, okay. All right.
Okay, okay. Okay...
River. River... Where is the river?
Quite the dilemma, Jim.
Are you gonna let me fall and die...
Or are you gonna pull me up
and arrest me?
What's it gonna be?
A lawman or a murderer?
Good old Gordon.
Always playing by the rules.
That's why I'll outlive you.
That's why I'm loved,
'cause I don't give a damn
about the rules.
It's a long way down.
You sure you'll outlive me?
Oh, I'm sure.
'Cause I'm more than a man.
I'm an idea, a philosophy.
And I will live on in the shadows,
within Gotham's discontent.
You'll be seeing me soon.
Au revoir.
Never thought I'd see this.
Sure he's dead. I can't believe.
Is he?
Yeah.
Get back.
GCPD. Everybody get back.
Mr. Valeska.
I meant what I said about your work
being of importance to the city.
Let Wayne Enterprises fund your work
with a grant.
Thank you.
Captain.
Oswald.
Um...
Hello.
Still here.
Will someone please get me
the hell off this thing?
We're on it.
How do we get a blimp down safely
from over a river?
You asking me?
I say we let him stew up there
for a few more hours.
We'll get a hold of
the standby pilot.
Have him advise.
Sit tight, all right?
Oh!
And Oswald Cobblepot,
Gotham thanks you.
Wait, Jim. Jim?
Jim? Jim.
Jim!
Never touch me again.
Ms. Kean has a new path to take now.
- It no longer involves you.
- Is that so?
We will accept you leaving this city
and never coming back.
The only thing I'll accept
is you kissing my ass.
We have been trained
by the League of Shadows
in 90 different forms of combat
since we were five years old.
Oh, yeah? Which one of you bitches
wants to go first?
Next time, we kill you.
Let me help you.
Who the hell are you guys?
The ones that have been watching you
and Barbara Kean,
the impostor, for quite some time.
We serve
the one and only true master,
Ra's al Ghul.
But he's dead.
Death is only an illusion.
Hello, brother.
Didn't think you can get rid of me
so easily, did you?
See, my days were numbered,
but you...
Oh, you can continue on for me.
Be my ultimate revenge.
So, calm yourself. Don't fight it.
Breathe it in.
This gas was a special mixture
I had made
just for you.
Something to finally set you free.
It's time to have some fun.
Burn it down, brother.
Burn it all down.