Previously on Gotham...
I have walked this earth
for centuries.
Only you can kill me,
and only with that dagger.
- What did I say?
- I can help you get Tabitha back.
Professor Hugo Strange
is the one man who can cure you.
Join me, and we will find him.
Okay, but you'd better deliver.
Why would I help you?
You love me.
You've loved me all along.
What's your record for how many banks
you've robbed in one day?
You're playing a dangerous game, Lee.
Ra's al Ghul chose you
to pass on his spirit.
We have much more to show you.
All my life, I have known
that I was meant for more.
This isn't you.
I'm not gonna
let your jealousy distract me.
Ladies, escort Miss Galavan
to the street.
We serve the one
and only true master, Ra's al Ghul.
- But he's dead.
- Death is only an illusion.
- What the hell?
- You didn't sense our approach?
No, you're ninjas.
The Demon's Head gives
its bearer power
to see past, present, future as one.
You should have anticipated
our attack.
So, this was a test?
I'm the Demon's Head.
My hand is a fricking lightbulb.
That is only its mark.
You have yet to access
its real powers.
So, you're questioning
whether I'm worthy?
I am sick of this.
The men from the League,
Tabitha, and now you.
You misunderstand.
How do you think Ra's al Ghul became
the world's most fearsome warrior
and ruled empires?
He saw the future.
So, attacking me was what?
A way to jump-start it?
Like, "Hey, Demon's Head,
snap to it"?
The powers of the Demon's Head
are triggered by intense emotions.
All right. So next time,
don't go so easy on me.
And take that knife out of my face.
You don't have
a covert mode on this thing?
Show-off.
So, you gonna tell me
what Tabitha needs us for?
All I know is, it's about Barbara
and it's important.
- So, what's the emergency?
- Inside.
You coming?
Tabitha, what am I doing here?
- What the hell?
- Wait.
What the hell? What is this?
I don't know.
She didn't tell me this part.
Barbara needs our help.
She's gonna get herself killed.
She has this thing called
the Demon's Head.
- This is about Ra's al Ghul?
- He is the one who gave it to her.
These guys are gonna help us
take it back.
Okay, so, why do you need Bruce?
You're gonna bring him back.
You can't do this.
Ra's wanted to die.
He wanted me to kill him.
And now we need him alive.
No. No. No!
No! No!
Bone, flesh, breath.
Come back to us, our leader.
Now, we close the circle.
We give you the blood of the one
who slew you.
No!
You have no idea what you've don...
Five banks in one night?
You're joking.
I wish these guys were slick.
Banks didn't even know
they were hit till they opened.
One of the banks,
the thieves came in on boats
through the sewer.
Tunneled into one of the vaults.
All branches
of Gotham Savings and Loan.
Why the same banks?
Maybe a leak in security?
Maybe a grudge.
Five banks in one night.
It's like someone was trying
to make a point.
Prove how smart he is.
- Ed Nygma?
- If the bowler fits.
Should I put out a BOLO on him?
Sure. In the meantime,
there's someone else I can talk to.
Say hey to Lee for me, won't you?
Tell her nice shooting with Sofia.
- What, I can't make a joke?
- That's what that was?
Why don't you put that BOLO out?
Let's see your hand.
- This is for you. Enjoy it.
- Good.
- Hey.
Thanks.
Look at them.
We did good.
Oh, yeah. My brilliance allowed us
to rob five banks in one night.
Now, the fine folks of The Narrows
will be drowning in booze
and smokes for years to come.
So inspiring.
They're also gonna use the money
to buy food,
and clothing, and medicine.
What's wrong?
What am I to you?
A friend. A partner.
Are you always this amorous
with your friends?
- I know it only happened once...
- Ed...
- Don't call me Ed.
- Hey.
I care about you. I depend on you.
You know, what we've got planned.
Other things are just gonna have
to wait.
You're not stringing me along,
are you, Lee?
Don't you wanna find out?
The answer to the riddle?
Maybe I do.
Are we good for tomorrow night?
Yeah, we just have
a few last details.
And trust me, this is going
to be a work of art.
That sounds promising.
Oh, what the hell? Count us in.
- You could've told me.
- You wouldn't have brought him.
- Yeah, because he's my friend.
- What is Barbara? What am I?
Pick a side and stick to it.
Do you know what you've done?
The years, I spent planning my death.
- Now, you've ruined it!
- Master,
the woman you gave
the Demon's Head to,
- she started a war.
- I started that war!
The League of Shadows was rotten.
Only through violence
could it be reborn!
Master, our lives are yours to take.
But this woman does not serve
the League.
Her goals are limited, selfish.
That's Barbara, all right.
Whatever faith you had
in her was misplaced.
If she keeps the Demon's Head,
the League shall die.
Wait, what do you mean
if she keeps the Demon's Head?
I thought you were supposed to get it
the second you
- came back.
- No.
Barbara must give it to me.
She'll never do that.
Then, I'll kill her
and rip it from her corpse.
You owe us.
I... I'm sorry. We owe you how?
Because we made you. Both of you.
Without me,
you would still be trapped inside Ed.
And you would still be stitching up
busted lips ringside.
I need money
to buy back Sofia's capos.
Butch is saving
for future medical expenses.
What'd you make last night?
Three, four million?
Say we go halvsies.
I've heard your offer.
And here's my counter, bite me.
I don't like people coming
into my club,
telling me what to do.
And I don't like threats,
implicit or otherwise.
And I really don't like people
telling me they made me.
Well, said, Lee.
Oh, god. Are you kidding me?
- What?
- Okay, we're done.
I... I... I thought you got past
all that
- when you became the Riddler.
- Past what?
Ed's pathetic adoration of her.
But no.
Clearly, he passed it along you.
Like a virus.
She knows it and she's using you.
Shame on you,
stringing along this troubled man.
- Get out.
- I don't think so.
We did not come here for violence.
We came here hoping
our friends would honor their debts.
Let us hope they come to our senses.
A little advice.
Be sure to skim some off the top
when she tosses you aside.
Kind of defeats the purpose
if I can hear you.
Hello, Barbara.
Ra's.
Don't be afraid.
What happened?
- How are you even...
- It's a long story.
But tell me,
what have you done with my gift?
Well, you might have left a how-to.
Plus a heads-up
to your League of Shadows cronies.
Turns out the old boys club don't
appreciate a woman calling the shots.
But you have plans?
On rebuilding the League of Shadows?
You're read...
the histories that I left for you?
I've read them,
but I need to do my own thing.
Your own thing?
With the power you gave me,
I can rule Gotham
like no one ever has before.
The people will worship me
like a queen.
How disappointing.
You're right.
They should worship me like a god.
Enough.
Give me your hand
so that I can take it back.
No, it is mine. You promised me!
I was mistaken in you, Barbara.
Mistaken? Tell that to her.
You think that is you?
She was just a whore.
I killed her out of pity.
You're lying.
The Demon's Head is my destiny.
Then why have you not
unlocked its secrets?
You sad, deluded woman.
You thought you were
a reincarnated queen.
But in truth,
you're just
an unstable nightclub owner,
whose greatest accomplishment
was the murder of her own parents.
You are nothing.
Now, give me your hand.
Or I will kill you
and take the Demon's Head by force.
Try it, zombie-boy.
Get her out of here. Go!
I'm fine.
Get in!
All right. You know, the rules.
Hands only. No, drinking water.
I want a good clean eat.
Ready? Ready?
- All right. Yeah, go.
- Yeah, come on.
- Come on, eat it, eat it.
- Come, come, come on.
I'm looking for Lee Thompkins.
- Come on, eat.
- The Doc?
Lee?
- The winner!
- Jim.
You don't look like a guy
who got shot four times.
Because you were able
to keep me alive.
- Thanks.
- I'd just shot Sofia Falcone
in the head.
I was in a good mood.
I'm looking for Ed Nygma.
Five banks were robbed last night.
Has all the hallmarks
of an Nygma special.
Haven't seen Ed in weeks.
I know you feel loyalty towards him,
but you, of all people,
should know he's sick.
- He's a psychopath.
- We all have our flaws.
Lee.
I can understand why you're here.
But there are other ways
of finding absolution.
You can't take ownership
of everyone's problems.
This is The Narrows.
Nobody owns anything down here
but the slumlords.
Try going after the real criminals.
The people making money
off the backs of the poor.
You mean like
Gotham Savings and Loan?
None of the guards were killed.
The more I think about it,
it doesn't exactly feel
like Ed Nygma.
- Or not just him.
- If we're done here...
Whatever's happened.
You can always call me.
I can help.
You really don't get it, do you, Jim?
It was good to see you.
Ra's just tried to kill me
because of you.
You could've just given him
the Demon's Paw.
Head!
It's the Demon's Head,
and it is mine!
You betrayed me.
I was trying to save you from myself.
Also, the other day,
you actually told your thugs
- to kill me.
- It was a spanking.
If I wanted you dead, I would've
- done it...
- Oh, shut up, both of you!
We're wasting time.
Ra's could be on his way right now.
Which wouldn't be a problem
if she'd give him what he wants.
- Never gonna happen.
- So, what should we do, Barbara?
We just gonna walk around
with targets on our back?
No, we're gonna kill
the son of a bitch.
The kid did it before, right?
Yeah, but that was different.
We had a special knife.
That one you got from auction.
- Where is it?
- We gave it back
- to the Nanda Parbat embassy.
- Great.
So, we'll do a little smash and grab
and then I'll filet the zombie.
I have to be the one holding
the knife.
It's part of the ritual.
Like the blood.
I have to kill him again.
Even if that's the case,
Master Bruce.
I can't allow you to do it.
- Not again.
- We might not get
another chance, Alfred.
This is the only way.
Says you, the mystical knife expert.
I've got the Demon's Head.
I bet if I'm holding it in my hand.
What if killing Ra's
unlocks my powers?
Yeah, and what if you fail
and Ra's gets the knife back?
We'll worry
about who kills him later.
Right now, we have to get
the knife before Ra's does.
Embassies are heavily guarded,
and we can't wait till night.
We're gonna need guns,
smoke grenades to cause a diversion.
If I may,
there may be another option.
But you gotta guarantee, you're
not gonna stab us in the back...
again.
So, in short,
we'd like to thank you very much.
Both of us would like to thank you
for taking such good,
such good care of her.
But now, we'd like
to take the knife home, please.
Well, it, it was never yours
to begin with, Mr. Pennyworth.
It belongs to my people.
When Mr. Bruce Wayne
purchased it at auction,
he was rescuing
a looted historical treasure.
That's why you returned it to us.
Yeah, but it was a loan,
wasn't it, mate?
It was never meant as a keepsie.
This knife is worth millions,
and you just gave it away?
- You idiot.
- Easy, muffin.
Look, you look like you got
a stable head on your shoulders.
Why don't I make a little donation,
and you give us the knife
and we walk away?
Does Bruce Wayne
even know about this?
Whatever your agenda is
I believe that you
and your chippie should leave.
A chippie?
Did you just call my missus
a chippie?
What is that, like...
What... a chippie? Is that a
new term or someth... Something?
-Sir?
- What?
- What? What's happening?
- What, what?
- I can't breathe.
-Oh, my god.
- I think he's having a heart attack.
- I can't breathe. I can't breathe.
He's having a heart attack!
Look at what you did.
Tell security it's a false alarm.
- I can't breathe.
- A false alarm.
- I can't breathe. I can't breathe.
- Give me your jacket.
- Put your jacket under his head.
- I can't breathe. I can't breathe.
Put your jacket.
It really hurts.
It really, it really hurts.
Put your head back.
- Are you breathing? Deep breaths.
- All right?
- Just breathe.
- It really hurts.
- Stay with me.
- I feel much better now.
Sorry about the fuss, fellas.
Chippie.
I think she's using you.
Shame on you.
Stringing along this troubled man.
"This troubled man."
Who can't argue with that.
Oh, no.
Sorry, just because you're in charge
doesn't mean I disappear.
That's because you're too stupid
to know when you've lost.
Have I?
"Lee, what am I to you?"
Does that sound like you to you?
Because to me,
that sounds like me.
I'm not proud of that phrasing.
I'm inside you, buddy. Like a virus.
- Infecting your thoughts.
- Oh, please.
You couldn't even begin
to comprehend my thoughts,
much less influence them.
What about your feelings?
How else would you explain those
desperate attempts
to gain her approval?
No. No.
If anything, she's the one who...
You gave money away to the poor.
- That was part of a larger plan.
- Yeah, her plan.
What did you ever care about
- The Narrows?
- I don't.
Every person here could drown
in a stew of their own filth
and I wouldn't lose a wink of sleep.
Oh, I know.
Because all you care about is her.
Just like I did.
So, keep that up, buddy.
Because soon, there'll be no telling
where you end and I begin.
That's not gonna happen.
Well done. Now, knife, please.
Selina, it has to be me.
Selina.
Give me the knife.
And you'd better scram
while you still can.
I'm taking the knife.
You do not wanna make me angry, kid.
Sorry, muffin.
I need you to step back.
Don't you even go there, love.
- Selina, don't give her the knife.
- Let's screw this.
Your arrogance is gonna get
someone killed.
- Don't you know?
- Or just you.
- What?
- Stop.
Thank you.
Now, get in!
Selina, let's go.
Nice doing business with you, boys.
You were right.
She's using me.
Finally.
- So much for you being smart now.
- No.
The most brilliant minds are often
blind to the most obvious truths.
Fine.
- And you came to me.
- Because that love-struck moron, Ed,
is floating down a river of dopamine
deep within the primitive
reward circuit of my brain.
And I need you to help me drown him
for good.
Did you bring the half share
of profits we asked for?
That money's gone.
Distributed among the riff-raff
of The Narrows, but...
those five banks
were merely the first stage
of a very sophisticated plan.
And the coup de grâce is tonight.
I knew you were scheming something.
That's why we were gonna
rob you afterward.
But I prefer this way.
There better be enough in there
to get me fixed.
- Don't forget our deal.
- I won't.
Thank you so much.
And how big is the score?
About 100 million...
A piece.
And you help me deal
with Lee Thompkins.
Thank you for coming back.
We serve the Demon's Head, Barbara.
- So, what's the play?
- Simple.
I do the flashlight hand thingy,
summon Ra's.
Little stabby-stab with the knife.
Send him back to hell.
Think I can remember that.
You can't be serious.
That's your plan?
How do you expect
to get the drop on someone
who's studied Kung Fu for 2000 years
and is a zombie?
I'm not feeling a lot of faith here,
kitty cat.
Maybe I'd have more,
if you knew
how to use your Demon Head
for something other
than a flashlight.
- You're gonna get us killed.
- Got any useful suggestions?
- Maybe call backup.
- I did. Here they are.
What if Bruce is right?
Let him use the knife.
At least we know
that it worked before.
You just took the knife from him.
Because you told me to pick a side.
I thought you had a plan other than,
"Let's stab the immortal undead guy
and hope for the best."
Listen, Selina,
we're strongest when we're together.
- Now, are you in, or are you out?
- If it's suicide by Ra's, I'm out.
Fine then. Go!
What if she's right?
I can't control the Demon's Head.
Maybe it's like Ra's said.
Maybe I am just a nightclub owner.
I should have never trusted
those men.
I didn't want you to have
the Demon's Head.
I'm not even sure I want it now.
Three years we've been together,
on and off.
And I've never seen
you doubt yourself.
So, however you wanna play this,
I'm in.
But if you're saying
you're not worthy,
that's where I jump ship.
Let's do this.
I suppose on the bright side,
you won't have to kill him.
Again.
- Except I'm the only one who can.
- So said, Ra's.
I mean, no disrespect to your
magical daggers in order to that,
but I'd love to see what would happen
if I pulled his head off
his bloody shoulders.
I can't believe Selina gave
Barbara the knife.
Yeah, well,
at least we know where she stands.
That's what you think.
Oh, you got
a bloody cheek turning up here.
I gave Barbara the knife
because if there was a chance
she could use it,
I wanted her to.
- So Bruce didn't have to kill him.
- I would've done what I had to.
And gone back to being the douchebag
you've been the last few months.
So, no, thank you.
She's got a point there,
Master Bruce.
Thanks for the explanation.
You can leave now.
- Bruce.
- You sided with them.
Why does it have to be about sides?
There is somebody, something,
out there that needs to be stopped.
So, why can't we focus on that?
Another good point.
Barbara and Tabitha are gonna
get themselves killed.
And I don't want that to happen.
There were easier banks to hit.
- Why yours?
- I keep telling you, I have no idea.
I'm a victim.
You're treating me like a criminal.
Yeah, I wonder
where we get that from.
- Excuse me?
- We did some digging.
You bank has been investigated
for redlining,
- usury, illegal foreclosures.
- And cleared on all counts.
- You have good lawyers.
- So, we deserve to be robbed?
- I'm done here.
- Ma'am,
can you give us a second, please?
- What the hell are you doing?
- She's a crook.
A bigger crook than
whoever ripped her off.
You mean Lee?
Look, brother,
I know what this is about.
You went down to The Narrows
and came back all fired up, okay.
But alienating her
is not gonna help us.
If Lee's involved with Nygma,
we gotta stop it before it goes bad.
Which of your branches
are the most vulnerable?
As of this afternoon, none of them.
We have a security protocol
after the Arkham breakout
and the robberies.
You moved your assets
to a secure location.
Yes, of course. All 45 branches.
This morning.
It's totally safe.
Fortified and heavily guarded.
Where is it?
- Pistol would've been more fun.
- You indulge me.
Breaking open the vault
is the last detail.
- Big detail. How did you solve it?
- Little help from some friends.
I'm the revealer of masks.
When I appear, friend becomes foe.
And the one that you love
becomes the one that you hate.
- What am I?
- Betrayal.
Hello, Lee.
Yeah, it's not a dart gun. Let's go.
- Nice entrance.
- I do hope you've reconsidered
and are planning
to give me what I want.
I've thought about it,
a lot and about us.
We had something, didn't we?
Back when you were less dug-uppy.
I do not have time for this.
I will give you what you want, Ra's.
But I want you to admit
we had a connection,
and that those things you said to me
were just mind games
to make me lose my nerve.
You want me to tell you
that you're special.
- Would that be so hard?
- No.
And moreover, it's true.
You are special.
I'm just sorry it had
to come to this, Barbara.
Me too.
But thank you for saying that.
She must do this by herself.
Barbara, fight.
This is Barbara's fight.
- Well, now, look at you.
- Yeah, look at me.
You wanna give it another shot?
She's mastered the Demon's Head.
I can see why he likes this thing.
That's enough.
Give me what I want,
or your friend dies.
- I thought this was between us.
- Choose, now.
Tabby, I...
I can't give this up.
No!
That's enough. Choose. Now.
You win.
Just don't hurt her.
Barbara Kean,
you surprise me yet again.
Maybe I wasn't mistaken
in you after all.
No.
Give me the knife, Ra's.
Let me kill you.
Today is not the day that I die.
This is the price
for taking advantage of me, Lee.
You're wrong, Ed. I wasn't using you.
Again, don't call me Ed.
And I'm not wrong about you.
Truck is almost full.
- We should go.
- Tell the Ogre.
Have him leave the property deeds.
They all belong to The Narrows.
Worthless.
And so ends the tale
of the queen of The Narrows.
Goodbye, Lee.
- What are you doing?
- How did that go again?
"I'm the revealer of masks.
When I appear, friend becomes foe."
- Betrayal.
- Exactly.
What the hell are you doing?
Just burning The Narrows
property deeds.
Not that!
He's proving his love
by betraying us.
These bars can't hold me.
- When I get out...
- We'll be gone.
I just wanted you to hear something.
Oswald, we've been through
thick and thin,
and I hold no grudge on you.
But you come against Lee,
and you come against me.
I'm gonna dismember you, you twerp.
Yes, not even gonna try with you.
- Let's go, Lee.
- It won't make any difference.
She's still using you.
You are not The Riddler,
you are a fool!
Why do that?
Why bring Penguin and Grundy
if you're just gonna
lock them inside?
I needed Grundy to open the vault.
And Oswald was gonna rob us anyway,
so I just kept an eye on him.
He'll get over it. Or he won't.
So, you don't think I'm using you?
No, I know you are.
Then why would you betray
your friends for me?
Is this,
- are you Ed?
- No, I'm me.
- How can you be sure?
- Because Ed didn't understand you.
He didn't see how deeply
you had changed. I do.
I know that, that virus
woke up something deep inside you.
And you let that something loose
when you shot Sofia.
And you love it.
And I love it too.
And I know you that don't feel
the same way about me,
but you will.
And when you do, I will be here.
Ed Nygma, you are a riddle.
That's the nicest thing
someone's said to me.
- That's Jim.
- This alarm just went off.
- He was onto us.
- We can just go out the back.
No, they'll see the truck.
One of us needs to distract them.
- Done.
- No.
I can handle Jim Gordon.
You take the money to The Narrows.
You trust me?
I do.
Go.
G.C.P.D. Nygma,
we know you're in there.
Come out with your hands up.
Sweet, merciful mother.
You know, your rights.
You'd have done the same for me.
Ladies.
I hope this isn't one of those
kill-the-old-queen situations.
We discussed things.
Demon's Head or not, you fought.
Not for yourself,
but those alongside you.
You are worthy, Barbara Kean.
We follow you
to our deaths and beyond.
You can find from Barbara
where the League hides,
temples, safe houses.
He'll be in one of them.
Meanwhile, I'll try to fix the knife.
Yeah, we just take it
to the magic-knife shop.
No, problem.
- Selina, be serious.
- I am.
If Ra's wanted you dead,
you would be.
He obviously likes you.
- It's not about me.
- I know it's not about you.
Gotham has managed
a long time without you.
It can manage a little longer
if you have one night off.
You did good today.
So did you.
Poor timing. Apologies.
I only want to talk.
Alone, please.
I'm staying.
Very well.
She's right, you know, Bruce?
I do like you. Respect you.
Respect you for what you'll become.
- You have no idea what I'll become.
- Of course, I do.
At least, who you could become.
Why are you here?
I felt I owed you an explanation
as to why I chose to live.
When I took back the Demon's Head,
I saw a vision...
of a cataclysmic event soon
to befall this city.
- What event?
- A cleansing fire.
It will destroy,
purify,
create.
Create you, Bruce.
Because I will use it
as a mighty forge
molding you into a Dark Knight
of Gotham.
If it doesn't kill you, that is.