I love this city.
And I see it going to hell.
Sometimes,
I think this place is cursed.
I won't let it fall apart
without a fight.
THIS FALL
Citizens of Gotham,
we will not,
we cannot let these killers
and these robbers and these rapers
and these thugs win.
Not on my watch.
WITNESS
THE ORIGINS
There's a war coming.
A terrible war.
OF THE
INFAMOUS CITY
There will be chaos, rivers of blood
in the streets, I know it.
ONE
DETECTIVE
That's my new partner, Jim Gordon.
You have a little danger
in your eye.
I wonder
what you plan to do with that.
ONE MISSION
You've killed people before?
- That was war!
- This is war! We're at war!
ONE CRIME
What's your name?
My name is Bruce Wayne.
THAT WILL CHANGE
EVERYTHING
I promise you,
I will find the man who did this.
IN ONE CITY
I'm learning to conquer fear.
Fear doesn't need conquering.
Fear tells you where the edge is.
If somebody has to take over,
it might as well be me.
Gotham is on a knife edge.
THE SAGA BEGINS
This is not a city for nice guys.
Stop or I'll shoot!
However dark and scary
the world might be right now,
there will be light.
There will be light for us.
BEFORE
PENGUIN
CATWOMAN
BEFORE
RIDDLER
POISON IVY
BEFORE
BATMAN
THERE
WAS
GOTHAM
THIS FALL
FOX