Oh! Hey.
What? I think she got my wallet. Yeah.
Hey!
Thief, stop! Stop her!
Pss-pss.
MARTHA:
Oh, come on, Tom, it wasn't that bad.
THOMAS:
Oh, no? Childish drivel.
MARTHA: Well, the acting was fine
and the music was lovely.
What about you, Bruce?
Sorry, Morn, I agree with Dad.
It was kind of lame.
THOMAS:
There's no such word as kind of.
- It was totally lame.
- You two are so judgmental.
- What's up, folks?
THOMAS: Stay calm, Bruce.
MUGGER:
Give me your money.
No problem.
We're cooperating.
MUGGER:
The necklace.
THOMAS:
It's okay.
Easy.
BRUCE:
Mom? Mom?
Dad? Dad!
Dad.
No!
Sit down.
- Don't move.
- Don't touch my face.
MAN 1: Ease up!
MAN 2: Shut up.
MAN 3:
I need my pills.
- I need my pills.
OFFICER 1: You wish.
MAN 3:
Come on, where are my pills?
OFFICER 1:
Back, back. Come on.
Where are my pills?
[CLAMORING]
[GUNS COCKING]
- Give me my pills, bitch.
- Hold your fire!
Hold your fire! I got this!
Hold your fire.
Easy, easy.
Sir, look at me.
Not at them, look at me.
[GRUNTING]
My name's Jim, Jim Gordon.
What's yours?
I need my pills.
Everything's gonna be all right.
Look at me.
I got your pills right here.
Huh? You want some pills?
Want some pills? All right.
Here you go, here you go.
Here are some pills for you, all right?
These aren't my pills.
[PRISONERS JEERING]
Sorry, guys, didn't mean
to bark at you like that.
- I got a little bit carried away.
OFFICER 2: Get up here.
Hey, come on. Take it easy.
- Come on, hey, guys.
- Hey.
What the hell are you doing?
- We had the drop on him.
- Well, he's dropped, isn't he?
You could have gotten hurt.
Rookie mistake.
Next time, shoot the son-of-a-bitch.
If I shoot, that sets everybody off.
Gunfire every which way.
Somebody takes a cop's gun,
you shoot him.
- That's basic.
SERGEANT: Bullock, Gordon, you're up.
Double homicide, Theater District.
Give me a break. Shift's nearly over.
Yeah, nearly.
[SIRENS WAILING]
Oh, the legendary Harvey Bullock.
No rest for the wicked, eh?
Tannenbaum, looking crisp.
This is my new partner, James Gordon.
What we got?
Just got here myself.
Male, female, gunshot.
Their kid saw the whole thing.
Poor bastard hasn't spoke a word yet.
GORDON:
My name's James Gordon.
I'm a detective.
What's your name?
It's okay. You don't have to talk.
Listen, T, do me a favor.
You didn't see me, okay?
I see you right in front of me.
What's your problem?
That's Thomas and Martha Wayne.
I don't need that hassle.
Call Major Crimes, they'd love to have this.
Yeah, but they're not here.
And your partner's talking to the witness.
So that makes it your case.
BRUCE:
Bruce.
My name is Bruce Wayne.
Can you tell me what happened, Bruce?
[SOBBING]
When I was about your age,
a drunk driver hit our car.
Killed my dad. I was right next to him.
I know how you feel right now.
And I promise you, however dark and scary
the world might be right now...
...there will be light.
There will be light, Bruce.
We just got out of the movies.
We were walking through the alley
to catch an uptown cab...
...and a man came out of the shadows.
He was tall with a black mask.
He had a hat and gloves...
...and shiny shoes.
He took my dad's wallet
and my mom's necklace.
And then he shot them for no reason.
I should have done something.
But I was too scared.
There was nothing you could have done
to stop what happened.
But there is something you can do now.
You can be strong.
Be strong.
I promise you,
I will find the man who did this.
Hey, who the hell is that?
James Gordon.
Alfred Pennyworth.
We're gonna get the guy that did this, sir.
New boy, are you?
You could say.
Good luck, mate. Come.
Don't look, head up, eyes front.
Don't let them see you cry.
Shouldn't we be there
when they move the victims?
Why?
Listen, hotshot, do me a favor.
Don't start talking to witnesses
until I say so.
- What's your problem?
- My problem, soldier boy...
...you just caught us
a gigantic flaming ball of crap.
Oh, yeah? How's that?
You never heard of Thomas
and Martha Wayne?
Yeah, sure. The Wayne Foundation.
Yeah, two of the richest
and most powerful people in Gotham.
You can't even imagine the pressure
if we don't close this quick.
- So let's close it quick.
- Yeah, right.
This is a random street robbery, Holmes.
Perp could be any one
of 10,000 mopes out there.
Oh, crap.
COOK:
Order up.
Well, well, well,
if it isn't Montoya and Allen.
Major Crimes Unit.
- This is my new partner, Jim Gordon.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hi, Harvey.
- You're on the Waynes, huh?
- It's a terrible thing.
- Yeah.
- Any leads?
- Just getting started.
I'll be straight.
You want us to take it off your hands?
- No, no, no.
- Hold on, rook.
Why you want it?
You got a lead?
No, we just need the press action.
I don't know.
Come on.
You know you're scared of this case.
- I'm scared.
- So do the right thing for once.
For once? Where the hell do you get
the nerve to say that to me?
- You can kiss my ass.
- Okay, you be that way, brother.
We're just trying to be collegial.
You know, I almost gave it to you.
But you couldn't help yourselves.
You had to go and be disrespectful.
Okay, Harvey.
Stay frosty.
Good luck.
Self-righteous do-gooding skell huggers.
Always badmouthing us
like they're such freaking angels. Please.
JAMES [ON TV]: As mayor of this great city...
...I swear to you, the perpetrators
of this heinous crime will be captured...
...and will be punished
to the fullest extent. I swear that to you.
Poor bastard.
First a crime wave, and now this.
Take all the people and resources you need.
Just close this case.
Yes, captain.
Jim, will you give us a minute?
Captain.
The answer is no.
[BULLOCK & ESSEN ARGUING]
ESSEN: Teach him the ropes.
BULLOCK: On a weak case?
ESSEN: Yes.
- Do you want me to change his diapers?
[INDISTINCT ARGUING CONTINUES]
He'll get me killed.
I don't care, I can't go out there with him.
She said you had to keep me, huh?
Yeah. She did.
She said you're a war hero.
And your daddy was a big-shot DA
back in the olden days.
So I have to keep my trap shut
and do as I'm told.
Ouch.
Listen, kid. You got juice, do me a favor,
ask for a transfer.
Yeah, no.
Sorry, this is where the action is.
You'll get used to me.
Jim, you seem like a nice guy.
But this is not a city or a job
for nice guys.
You understand?
- No.
- And that's your problem.
You're a cynic.
A slovenly, lackadaisical cynic.
[CHUCKLES]
You're probably right.
Okay, soldier boy...
...let's go roust some muggers.
Lackadaisical. Hmm.
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
Hey.
How you doing?
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
Guess what this is.
Just tell me, Ed.
I want riddles, I'll read the funny pages.
It's a .45 caliber
300 grain cupronickel wadcutter.
Came out of Thomas Wayne's chest.
- That's a six dollar bullet.
- Uh-huh.
- What kind of gun--?
- Ah-ah-ah. Don't ask, just tell.
It's from a pistol not known
by our database. No prints either.
BULLOCK:
What else you got?
What's nowhere but everywhere
except where something is?
Nothing?
You need professional help, Nygma.
Seriously.
Let's go.
So I'm thinking,
our man wears shiny shoes...
...uses high-end ammo,
and nobody on the street knows who he is?
Maybe he's not from the street.
Like, a debonair playboy robber
does it for kicks?
Who would pretend
to be a street robber, huh?
A professional killer, or somebody
with a personal grudge against the Waynes.
How'd this professional know the Waynes
would come down that alley?
Good question.
Essen said we don't catch a break
in the first 48, go see Fish Mooney.
- Fish Mooney? Works for Carmine Falcone?
- Her. Theater district's her turf.
Anything happens there, she hears about it.
GORDON:
Why didn't we come to her first?
BULLOCK:
She's kind of a last resort.
Tell Fish I'm here.
[MAN GRUNTS NEARBY]
BULLOCK:
Hmm.
RAOUL: Unh!
FISH: I still care for you deeply.
But I don't believe that you care
for me anymore.
[STUTTERING]
I care for you.
Then where's my money?
RAOUL:
I'll get it, I'll get it.
[GRUNTS]
Boy.
- Sorry.
- If you let this hair go frizzy, you will be.
Ma'am, Detective Bullock is here.
- Keep him warm.
- Yes, ma'am
Hey, Oswald, you want a turn?
- May I?
- Knock yourself out, kid.
Thank you, Mr. Gilzean.
[RAOUL GRUNTS
THEN OSWALD CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHING]
- Harvey. Ha, ha.
- Fish.
Where have you been?
Where haven't I been?
[FISH CHUCKLES]
- Who's the friend?
- Detective James Gordon, ma'am.
Hmm.
Well, aren't you a cool glass of milk.
Ma'am, was that screaming
we heard back there?
Yes. My boys are watching a scary movie.
- Really.
- No.
Actually, one of my staff
has been stealing money from me.
So we're beating his punk ass.
BULLOCK:
Relax, junior. Fish gets some leeway.
Her staff are rough characters,
need firm handling.
So this isn't a social visit, then.
Unfortunately not. Brass sent me by
to talk to you about the Wayne murders.
Terrible thing.
[RAOUL GRUNTING NEARBY]
Junior, if you're worried, go back there
and see if anyone wants to press charges.
- If that's okay with you, Fish.
- Oh, I don't mind at all, Harvey.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
[GRUNTING AND YELLING]
- Oswald, whoa.
- Yeah, take it easy, Penguin.
You know I don't like to be called that.
Ooh. Scary.
How's everybody doing?
Who are you?
James Gordon, G.C.P.D.
BUTCH:
Oh, you came with Harvey, huh?
Glad to know you, James.
I'm Butch Gilzean.
Drop the bat.
Oh, come on, now.
Oswald and Raul here were just
having a little fun, weren't you, boys?
- All in fun.
- No problem. Fun.
BUTCH:
You're a new guy, huh?
How do you like Gotham so far?
Well enough.
See you around.
[FISH & BULLOCK LAUGHING]
Oh, hey.
Everything all right back there?
It's always good to see you, Harvey.
And look at you and your excellent suit.
You know, I'm so happy you don't have
to wear that silly uniform anymore.
- You told me it looked good.
- I lied.
[BARBARA CHUCKLES]
- You ready to rock and roll?
- Uh...
Barbara, I'm beat.
Do we really have to go to this thing?
No, of course not.
- Thank you.
- You owe me.
[GORDON SIGHS]
So talk to me.
We're getting nowhere on the Wayne case.
I made a promise to Bruce Wayne,
and I can't deliver.
But you will.
I don't know.
Maybe I'm out of my depth.
Hey, I very much doubt
you are out of your depth.
But even if you are,
you know how to swim, don't you?
Yes, I do.
So swim.
I'll swim. You're right.
Are you hungry?
I'm all right. I had a few dogs.
When I'm Mrs. Gordon
and you're living here all the time...
...I'm gonna put you
on a proper healthy diet.
Mm-hm.
[BUZZING]
I've got a lead.
Meet me at Fourth and Grundy in an hour.
On my way.
Hey.
You all right?
Couple drinks. I'll be fine.
GORDON:
Bullock...
Fish Mooney heard from one of her fences
a guy tried to sell him an antique.
Four strand pearl necklace
with gold settings, one strand broken.
- Like Martha Wayne was wearing.
- Mm.
Guy's name is Mario Pepper.
Career street thug. Long sheet for robbery,
assault, rape, extortion, drug dealing.
GORDON:
Nice guy.
Hi.
- What's your name?
- Ivy.
Ivy, is daddy home?
You don't wanna talk to daddy.
Why's that, Ivy?
He's mean.
PEPPER:
Hey, who is it?
Mario Pepper, we need to talk.
I've done nothing.
So it'll be a pleasant talk.
Where were you last Saturday around 9:30?
I was here at home with my family.
That's right. He was here.
A pearl necklace sound familiar?
No.
Then I guess you don't mind
we, uh, take a look around the place.
You need a warrant.
You're a felon on parole.
All we need is reasonable cause.
Stop! Stop or I'll shoot!
[WOMAN SHRIEKS]
Out of the way!
[METAL CLATTERS NEARBY
THEN PEPPER YELLS]
[GRUNTING]
Thanks.
[CHATTERING]
BULLOCK:
What kind of guy are we dealing with?
Probable? I had to.
We got him.
[CHUCKLES]
[CHEERING]
[SIREN WAILS]
Mario Pepper was framed
by Fish Mooney and the cops.
I saw Ms. Mooney
with Martha Wayne's necklace.
She was discussing how to get it
into Pepper's home, inside a bag of drugs.
This was shortly after she met
with Detectives Bullock and Gordon...
...from the homicide squad.
Mooney works with Carmine Falcone's mob.
You saying Falcone had the Waynes killed?
- I'm just telling you what I saw.
- Why snitch on your own boss?
I confess, that poor orphan boy
pricked my conscience.
No.
You wanna push Fish out, huh?
That's beside the point.
I've done my civic duty.
Good day to you both.
You kept your promise.
Thank you.
I'm sorry you didn't see a trial.
That's okay.
Renee, long time.
Yeah.
[SIGHS]
Sorry to drop by unexpected like this.
How have you been?
I'm good.
- You?
- All good.
You're running an art gallery now, right?
- Yeah.
- That's so cool.
And I'm engaged.
Yeah.
James Gordon, huh?
- That's why I'm here.
- Oh?
The G.C.P.D. framed Mario Pepper
for the murder of the Waynes.
- What?
- They framed and killed an innocent man.
And you're here to tell me
that James was in on this?
- Yes.
- And what's your proof?
I can't tell you, but it's the truth.
James Gordon is not a good guy.
You deserve better.
James Gordon is the most honest man
I've ever met.
He's not capable of doing that.
- You sure you know what he's capable of?
- Yes, I know him.
Does he know you?
Don't.
Like I know you?
Here you are.
Barbara, what's wrong?
Did you frame Mario Pepper?
- No.
- I knew it.
- Who told you?
- Doesn't matter, as long as it's not true.
- It's not. Who told you it was?
- Nobody.
Bee, I know when you're lying.
GORDON:
Montoya.
What's your evidence
that Pepper was framed?
I was wrong to reveal
that information to Barbara.
- We're old friends.
- I asked what evidence you have.
You'll see the evidence when we get you
and your crooked friends into a courtroom.
We're working on it.
Save your energy.
If Pepper was framed, I'll find out.
Hey, you got a problem here, Gordon?
And then you and you
just need to stay out of my way.
GORDON: Mrs. Pepper
- Go away.
Ma'am, if your husband was innocent,
you need to talk to me.
If your husband didn't kill the Waynes,
how'd he come to have the necklace?
You bastards planted it on him?
IVY:
Bastards.
Alice, how would the police
have the necklace?
- We didn't kill the Waynes.
ALICE: So you say.
God knows my husband had his demons,
but he never killed nobody.
Can I see his shoes?
Shoes?
- This is all of them?
- Uh-huh.
Damn.
Framed? How you figure? You were there.
We framed him?
Somebody could've planted
the necklace on Pepper.
- Mooney could've set the whole thing up.
- Why?
To cover up for the real killer.
Mooney works for Falcone.
Maybe Falcone wanted the Waynes killed.
Wait, wait, wait.
Why would such a nutty idea
even enter your head?
Montoya from MCU.
That pill-head looney-bird?
What's her proof?
- Wouldn't tell me. Didn't trust me.
- She doesn't have any.
If they did, they'd have used it.
Pepper didn't wear shiny shoes.
He didn't own any shiny shoes.
Shiny shoes. Mother of God.
Shiny shoes. Just suppose for a moment,
just suppose Pepper was innocent.
I killed him.
- We killed him.
We'd lose our jobs at the very least.
The case is closed. Forget about it.
- Even if the real killers are still out there?
- Yes.
This is very perilous stuff
you're messing with.
Listen to me for once, Jim.
Forget about it.
[DOOR OPENS]
Detective Gordon.
Tell Mooney I'm here.
- Regarding what, shall I say?
- Mario Pepper.
Mario--
- May I ask why?
- No.
No. Yes. Heh.
None of my business.
James Gordon. How nice.
The day I met you,
when I was out back there with your boys...
...what did you and Harvey talk about?
Shouldn't you ask Harvey?
He's your partner.
- I'm afraid he might lie.
- Hmm.
He might.
And you think I'll tell you the truth?
You just did.
James, wait.
You have a little danger in your eye.
I wonder what you plan to do with that.
You'll have to wait and see.
I hate surprises.
[GRUNTING]
BARBARA:
Detective Bullock?
Miss Kean.
Um, James went for a walk last night,
and he never came back.
Have you heard from him?
I'm really worried about him.
He's on a stake-out.
Yeah, his phone
probably ran out of juice, is all.
Oh.
Right, well, that's a relief.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
Wait, wait, wait.
Shut up.
BUTCH:
Hey, what are you doing?
- Over here, you'll get a better angle.
SERGIO: What?
- You're a director now?
- Don't get fresh. I'm just saying.
Hey, Butch.
[CHUCKLES]
Harvey.
Who told you we'd be here?
Everybody knows
this is where you take your problems.
- That's my partner you got there.
- Ex-partner.
Oh.
Let me talk to Fish.
I'm not afraid of death
so much as I am of dying.
I, um, wanna die how my father died,
peacefully, in his sleep.
Not like his screaming,
terrified, passengers.
[LAUGHS]
[PHONE RINGING]
- Yeah?
BUTCH: Bullock showed up at the plant.
- Wants to talk to you.
- Put him on. Give me a moment, kid.
You're doing good.
BULLOCK: Fish?
- Speaking.
Don't be like that.
Listen, you gotta let my boy go.
- How long we been friends?
- For a long time. Until today.
I did a big favor for you and your pals...
...and now it's gonna blow up in my face
on account of your stupidity.
The kid's not your problem.
He was hipped to the frame by
Major Crimes, they'll be coming after you.
- How did they get onto me?
- The usual way, I guess.
Somebody talked.
FISH:
Huh. Not one of my people.
That's what everybody says.
- True.
- Listen, you gotta let my boy go. Hmm?
You kill my partner, I gotta come after you.
[CHUCKLES]
I don't wanna do it,
but how am I gonna look...
...you kill my partner, I don't make a move?
All right.
But promise me
that you'll keep him under control.
- I promise.
- Cool.
Put Butch on, please.
Yeah, boss.
That son-of-a-bitch just threatened me.
You hang him up with his partner.
BUTCH:
You got it.
Hey, how you doing?
I'm good. We're going home.
- Yeah?
- I'm just glad everything could work out--
[GRUNTS]
Cops.
Bless your heart.
Would you be a sweet boy and rub my feet?
Give me a moment, darling.
I haven't forgotten you.
I like you. You're funny.
[FISH CHUCKLES]
Now, this amateur nonsense is a good sign.
There used to be some discipline.
Falcone is getting old and soft.
It's time.
Somebody has to take over,
it might as well be me.
Yes, it might as well.
And you? You're like a son to me.
You know that, Oswald?
I feel that way also.
Which is what I don't understand.
After all I've done for you...
...and right when I'm on the verge
of great things, you betray me?
Why would you betray your mother?
I don't know what you mean.
It was you.
You snitched to the MCU.
You wanna know how I know?
Because only you
saw me with the pearls, no one else.
It was Gilzean.
He's the snitch.
[FISH CHUCKLES]
No.
- Gilzean is loyal.
- So am I.
I would open a vein right here and now
if you asked me to.
Go on, then.
Open one.
I, uh-- I was speaking poetically.
FISH:
Prove it.
Prove your loyalty, my little Penguin.
Please, Miss Mooney. Please, don't.
[GRUNTS]
You broke my heart!
[OSWALD YELLING]
BUTCH [NEARBY]:
Are we rolling?
How you doing?
Been better.
Thanks for trying to help.
Wish I hadn't.
- Did you just slap my hand?
- Hey, Butch!
BUTCH:
Save your breath.
If it was up to me, you'd get a bullet
in the head and a decent funeral.
But Fish has her ways.
Yo, Franky! Showtime.
[ALARM BUZZING]
[BULLOCK GROANS]
Don Falcone.
Forgive me, young man,
I forget what your name is.
Or perhaps I never knew it.
Gilzean, sir.
FALCONE:
Gilzean.
Tell Miss Mooney she's too impetuous.
If she wants to kill policemen,
she has to ask permission.
Yes, sir.
[BULLOCK GROANS]
There are rules.
Cut them down.
That's right, there are rules.
It's good to meet you at last, James.
I knew your father very well.
The best DA this city ever had.
He and I understood each other.
There was respect. Friendship, even.
Friendship?
Trust me, that's the only reason
you're alive now.
Blood doesn't lie. I know that when you
leave here, you'll do the right thing.
I will.
I'll tell what I know.
Which is what?
I know that you own the police department,
probably the mayor too.
And I was sure
that you had the Waynes killed.
But if you did, you wouldn't risk
letting me live, would you?
Then again, how did Fish Mooney
come to have Martha Wayne's necklace?
- A replica?
- Yes.
But if you didn't have them killed,
why frame Mario Pepper?
Or are you covering up for somebody else?
Who knows who killed the Waynes.
Some lowlife.
We needed a culprit before the funeral.
Pepper was sacrificed so that the people
of Gotham would see swift justice done.
So they can feel safe and secure.
- And that matters so much to you.
- Of course.
I'm a businessman.
You can't have organized crime
without law and order.
I love this city, and I see it going to hell.
But I won't let it fall apart without a fight.
You make a life of crime sound very noble.
You have a hard head, James,
just like your father.
Don't be self-righteous. Don't be arrogant.
You want me to keep quiet about all this.
Gotham is on a knife edge.
What do you suppose bringing down
city hall and the police force will do?
Even if you could.
Would it make things better?
[SPEAKS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[THUNDER RUMBLES]
- Lookit, Jim.
- I'm listening.
I wasn't being honest with you.
But you weren't ready for the truth.
You didn't tell me
because you were ashamed.
Why are we stopping here?
No, please. Please, I beg of you.
Shut up!
This is the fool that snitched
to Montoya and Allen.
Falcone wants you to walk him to the end
of that pier and put a bullet in his head.
Then everybody knows
you're with the program.
And if I don't?
Then I'm supposed to take you out
and him too.
Here's the thing, Jim, I like you.
I might not have the stomach to do it,
but I'll try.
Because if I don't,
someone will get to you quick enough.
Then they're gonna get to me,
probably Barbara as well.
Who knows what you told her.
- I told her nothing.
- You think Falcone cares?
- Come on, you've killed people before.
- That was war!
This is war!
We're at war with scumbags like him.
Sometimes in a war, you gotta do
a bad thing to do good, right?
So, do you do this bad thing, or do you die
and maybe your girl dies?
I might be lackadaisical, hmm?
But that's not a tough call.
[WHIMPERING]
GORDON:
Walk.
Please, Mr. Gordon, just let me live.
I'll do whatever you say,
I'll be your slave for life.
Listen to me, there's a war coming,
a terrible war.
Falcone is losing his grip,
and his rivals are hungry.
There will be chaos,
rivers of blood in the streets, I know it.
I can see it coming.
I'm clever that way.
And I can help you.
- I can be a spy--
- Shut up!
Turn around.
For God's sake, have mercy.
Don't ever come back to Gotham.
Attaboy.
Oh, my God, James.
I've been so worried.
What happened to you?
Hey! Master Bruce!
Get your bloody ass down off there!
How many times have I told you?
Why were you up on the roof?
I'm learning to conquer fear.
Fear doesn't need conquering.
Fear tells you where the edge is.
Fear is a good thing.
And you think I haven't told him that,
do you?
- You came here for a reason, I imagine.
GORDON: Yes.
Mario Pepper didn't kill your parents.
He was framed by the police department
and the mob working together.
We killed an innocent man.
ALFRED:
Right.
So who did it, then?
- I don't know.
ALFRED: I see.
Well, sterling work there, then, mate.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Don't be.
I'm glad he's still alive.
I wanna see him again.
Bruce, I'm asking you
to give me a second chance.
I'm going to find out
who killed your parents and why.
And I'm gonna clean up
the damn police department if I can.
But I can only do that from the inside.
So I'm asking you to stay silent
about what I've told you.
Your call.
Right, well,
that's sort of convenient, isn't it?
Alfred!
Thank you.