Previously on Gotham...
Monsters are coming, Mr. Mayor.
(man screaming)
ESSEN:
Six criminally insane inmates
busted out of Arkham Asylum.
(cheerleaders screaming)
GORDON:
They want mass panic.
(cheerleaders screaming)
BARBARA: Hello, Jim.
How do I look?
GORDON:
Barbara!
Yo, Commish.
Yeah.
(laughs)
GORDON: Don't move!
(Aaron yells)
BARBARA: You should probably
get back to work.
Who knows what went wrong
while you were gone? (gasps)
(weakly):
It's a new day, Jim.
(screaming)
(groans)
(coughs)
Jerome Valeska.
The attack on the GCPD.
Someone on the streets
is talking.
Somebody knows something.
Valeska has red hair,
crazy laugh.
Might be rolling
with a blonde number.
I-I don't know anything.
Honest!
You believe him?
Nope.
Me neither.
It's the truth!
But, hey,
I-I can help you guys, you know,
spread the word and stuff.
Valeska killed a friend of ours.
Anybody hides him,
anybody protects him,
they go down, too, you got it?
Now spread the word.
No! No!
BARBARA:
Sneaking out?
Just like a guy.
There are loose ends
that need tying.
Need this?
Bring back bagels.
THEO:
No need for that.
I thought Ms. Kean and I
could have a little chat.
Good morning.
Jerome is waiting outside.
Try and keep
him focused.
(chuckles softly)
You be nice.
You two seem to be
getting along.
I'm so glad.
She needs a friend.
My sister is a very
special person.
She seems so strong,
but yet she's quite fragile.
Sugar?
Sure.
You acquitted
yourself very well
at the adventure
at the GCPD.
Jim Gordon escaped
the carnage unscathed.
Top marks.
Thank you.
Did you know
my family built this city?
We carved the bedrock
upon which it stands,
yet there is not a bridge,
an alley,
a ditch that carries our name.
My forefathers were betrayed,
their legacy erased,
and I am here to punish those
who wronged us
and reclaim what is ours.
Strawberry?
I didn't ask.
So you're gonna
take over Gotham by unleashing
a bunch of loonies.
Awesome plan.
That's only part one.
So what's
the second part?
Oh, you're gonna love it.
There's a starring
role for you.
You'll be famous
and powerful,
and your fondest dream
will come true.
You know my dreams, do you?
When Jim Gordon has outlived
his usefulness,
I'm gonna help you destroy him.
Not kill him.
Destroy him.
Body and soul.
(gunfire, people screaming)
Bang.
(cackling)
Shocking images. Gotham is
on high alert today after...
BULLOCK: Look, I'm just saying,
I'll chuck mopes out of windows
until the cows come home,
but at some point,
we got to go see Penguin.
Why would he break
Jerome out of Arkham
or attack the GCPD?
He wouldn't, but that weasel's
running things now.
If there's chatter,
he'd know it.
I'll think about it.
Jim...
I'll think about it!
Alvarez, where are you
with Jerome's circus contacts?
Circus is upstate.
I'm just waiting...
Follow up.
His father's probably with him.
He covered for him once before.
He might have
some information.
Do it. Yo, Detective!
Which escapee
are you tracking?
Helzinger.
No one's seen him.
He's six-seven, 275,
with the mind
of a five-year-old.
Somebody's seen him.
Hey!
What are you doing?
That stays up until we have
her killer in custody.
You understand?
Yes, sir.
Sarah Essen
and nine of your brothers
were killed in this house.
In our house!
Their murderer stood right
there, and he laughed at us.
Never forget that.
What?!
THOMPKINS:
So how are you?
GORDON:
I'm fine.
Really?
Look, I know Essen
was your friend.
Lee, whatever
you're about to say,
I know it's coming
from a good place,
but I can't hear it right now.
So, the Gotham Children's
Hospital gala is tonight,
which I helped
organize.
I can't.
You can't go?
No.
Even though a few hours
away from all of this
might actually help?
Lee.
Okay. I just have
to tell you something,
because if I don't
and you find out,
you're gonna be pissed.
There's gonna be a magician.
(chuckling)
Yeah. Right.
Stop beating yourself up.
I'm trying.
I know you are.
I should have been here.
I wasn't.
Stop it.
Kiss me.
(sighs)
Better?
(clears throat)
Not to interrupt your
weirdly timed make-out session,
but Alvarez got in touch
with the circus manager.
The blind fortune teller,
Jerome's dad,
bailed on him, stayed in town.
Got an address.
I'll call you.
Okay.
Who's there?
I know someone's there.
(grunting softly)
Hi-ya, Pops.
Long time... no see.
(laughing)
JEROME:
So, how you doing?
Ah, the silent
treatment, eh?
Here, I'll tell
you a story.
Hmm. Oh.
You remember
Kansas City, Dad?
The circus went through
town every spring
right around my birthday.
There was this guy.
Him and my mom used to
drink and fornicate
and beat the crap
out of me.
They'd make a whole
night out of it.
And I remember
one time--
it was my ninth
birthday--
him and my mom
had just finished
round one of boozing, boning,
beating up Jerome,
and were deciding
to take a little break.
Anyway...
Mm.
I was outside the trailer,
and you were there.
And you said,
"Why are you crying,
Jerome?"
"It's my birthday. (sobs softly)
And my mom and the snake guy
are beating me."
And then you said,
"This world doesn't care
about you
"or anyone else, Jerome.
Better to realize that now."
And that was it.
You see, there's this guy, Dad.
He believes in me.
He thinks I'm
gonna be a star.
And, tonight, all of Gotham
will see that, too.
Except for you.
'Cause you'll be,
you know, dead.
Jerome...
Is this the part
where you say
how sorry you are? Hmm?
How you should have
believed in me,
how it's not too late
to start again?
News flash, Dad:
it's too late.
You don't have to do this.
No.
I'm pretty sure I do.
I was a bad father,
but I did love you.
To kill me for that...
(cackling)
That's not why
I'm gonna kill you.
Plans to Arkham Asylum.
Look at these.
Ah.
Letters between you
and your troubled son.
Innocent at first glance,
but Detective Gordon--
you remember him, right?--
he'll feel little bumps.
A secret message
written in Braille
between you and your son,
discussing my escape.
Finally, the knockout gas
used to disable the orderlies.
'Cause, you see, Dad,
this guy I was
telling you about,
he's the one who
broke me out of Arkham.
He doesn't want anyone
to know about that.
Obviously. So...
the police will find
these letters, mmm,
and they'll think,
"The blind old fool
really loved his son.
What a wonderful
father." Oh.
There won't be a dry eye
in the house.
They'll never believe it.
Ah, sure, they will.
Cops are dumb.
There's nothing to eat
in this dump.
Finish up and let's go.
JEROME:
Sorry you're gonna miss
my big night, Dad.
But, hey,
you're psychic.
So, tell me,
do I kill?
You...
will be a curse upon Gotham.
Children will wake
from sleeps screaming
at the thought of you.
Your legacy
will be death and madness.
Ha, ha, ha.
Well...
say hi to Mom for me.
(knocking)
GORDON:
GCPD!
Mr. Cicero,
it's Detective Gordon.
We need to speak with you
about your son.
Mr. Cicero?
(muffled scream)
Mr. Cicero?!
Harvey, window!
(gas hissing)
Harvey?
(coughing)
(ears ringing, heart beating)
(whistling a tune)
JEROME:
Detective Gordon.
Old pal.
That gas sure packs
a wallop, huh?
(grunts)
That's cute.
(choking)
I'm sensing anger.
You killed Sarah Essen.
Now I'm gonna kill you.
(chuckling)
Don't shoot him.
How about a little
flesh wound?
No, no.
My dibs.
("Dirty Boogie" by the
Brian Setzer Orchestra playing)
(lively chatter)
This is a waste
of time.
We had a deal,
didn't we, Master Bruce?
Part of which was you resume
your normal lifestyle.
Your parents were both patrons
to the Children's Hospital.
Therefore,
it makes you a patron.
Besides...
there's gonna
be a magician.
And you like
magicians, don't you?
No, I don't.
I hate magicians.
You know what I said
about being normal?
Excuse me.
I'm Lee Thompkins.
I work with
James Gordon.
He's mentioned you,
and I saw you and thought...
Of course. It's very
nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
This is my guardian,
Alfred Pennyworth.
It's an absolute pleasure.
Thank you.
How is Detective
Gordon doing
since the attack
on the precinct?
I was thinking
I should call him.
He'd appreciate that.
♪ A girl like you
I could never bring home ♪
♪ Dirty boogie... ♪
Can I get you
something to drink?
Uh, just water.
Thank you.
♪ It's the dirty boogie
for me... ♪
So...
♪ Dirty boogie... ♪
I hear there's gonna be
a magician.
♪ Hey, you all ♪
♪ Dirty boogie ♪
♪ How's it go? ♪
♪ Not too slow ♪
♪ When I get low-down,
it's the dirty boogie for me ♪
♪ Let it go, let it go,
all right... ♪
Hello, Selina.
Hey.
I-I didn't expect
to see you here.
Well, you want to steal stuff,
it helps to go
where the rich people are.
You do know this is a benefit
for Children's Hospital?
So?
So these people
are here for a good cause.
Me eating is a good cause.
Besides, didn't I steal
something for you, once?
Selina, that was different.
Right.
♪ Scream and shout... ♪
How'd that go?
You get into that guy's safe?
Yes.
Though things didn't turn out
quite like I planned.
A lot's happened since then.
Alfred says
there's gonna be a magician.
I'm working.
And I hate magicians.
See you around, Bruce.
So you want
to share your plan?
Remember I told you
I could divine
the thing a person
truly wants?
What Gotham wants is a hero.
And tonight...
I'm going to give them one.
Shall we?
Jerome and Tabby
went on ahead.
Great cape.
Thank you for filling in
on such short notice.
But how did you hear
our magician dropped out, Mr...?
Rodolfo.
Well, you know, magic.
(both chuckle)
Oh, I won't be needing that.
(muffled grunting)
MAN: Come on.
I'm sorry, but really,
there is no mystery.
Tabitha, have you met
Deputy Mayor Kane?
Harrison,
this is my Tabitha.
Ah, nice to meet you.
Uh, and could you please
tell your brother
that when a handsome billionaire
appears out of nowhere,
people get curious.
Where'd he come from?
How'd he make his money?
Who's he dating?
My wife would kill me if
I don't get something--
a-a tidbit.
He's a monster in the sack.
Do you have any news
of Mayor James?
No.
No, it's a real mystery.
We don't know where he is.
How intriguing.
Harrison, would you mind?
A little family business.
Of course.
Ms. Galavant.
Everything's ready.
See you at home.
So, uh, how do you go from
being in the Royal Marines
to a butler?
Well, it's a bit tedious,
really, after a while.
You know, parachuting into one
global hot spot after another.
Warlords putting ridiculous
bounties on your head.
Gets a bit boring, really.
You have amazing stories.
Yeah, well, you know,
one or two.
You know, I don't really
get nights off,
but if ever you'd like
to pop by Wayne Manor
for dinner one evening, I...
Oh, that's very kind of you,
Mr. Pennyworth, but...
No.
Alfred. Please. Alfred.
Alfred.
That's very kind of you, but...
Now, having said that,
I don't see why I can't
take a night off, and
I... I happen to know
the head chef at Chez Parnes.
Well, I-I'm afraid I...
Did you say Chez Parnes?
I've been trying to eat there
for quite some time.
You have the most
beautiful eyes.
Oh, wow.
Okay, well, thank you,
but, uh...
Alfred, I'd
like to leave.
Yeah, um...
What about Dr. Thompkins' water?
And, of course, you're gonna
miss the magician.
Sorry, I must have
forgotten your water.
Alfred, I still
want to leave.
Are you not
feeling well?
Oh, n-no, he's-he's
absolutely fine. He's fine.
Why don't you just
pop off to the bar,
Master Bruce, and...
(quietly):
Show's about to start.
Is it time?
I roped myself into
emcee duties for the night.
I hope you'll stay
for the show.
I wouldn't miss it
for the world.
What?
(music ends, applause)
Good evening.
I'm Dr. Lee Thompkins.
For the past five years,
I've had the honor of being
part of the Children's Hospital.
Thank you for your support.
And thank you so much
for coming out tonight.
Over the years,
we've had magicians
come and entertain
our children.
And so tonight, we have one of
the magicians here for you.
Without further ado,
please allow me
to present to you
the Great Rodolfo.
(music playing, applause)
(gasps)
(yawns)
(laughter)
Ha!
Greetings, ladies and germs!
I am indeed the Great Rodolfo.
Please ogle my
lovely assistant.
Ooh!
(laughs)
(drumroll)
For my first act,
I'll require a volunteer.
Let me see.
Duck, duck,
duck, duck, duck, duck, duck...
goose!
Go on, Master Bruce.
Be a sport.
Don't keep the
lady waiting.
Fine.
(applause)
Hello, young man.
Does this
handsome gentleman have a name?
Bruce.
Bruce!
Well, Bruce, this
won't hurt a bit.
Is there a doctor in the house?
(laughter)
No, just... Excuse...
Just wait! Wait!
Wait one second!
Go home.
I'm fine.
You've been running this
since last night,
and you got a face
full of that gas. Go home.
You going home?
(sighs)
I didn't think so.
(groans):
Oh.
Maybe I will go
get some sleep.
Yeah? Good idea.
But we got somewhere, right?
At least now we know
who broke Jerome out of Arkham.
Yeah. Crazy old blind man
that lived alone.
The clever crazy
old blind man.
If his father broke him out,
why'd Jerome kill him, huh?
He was probably
playing this maniac shtick
since you sent him away.
He was just a kid.
Every evil bastard in the world
was just a kid once.
Yeah.
But I don't think it was
his father that broke him out.
(chuckles):
Well, cool.
Back to square one.
All right, I will go
and get some sleep.
For the record,
I knew Essen
a hell of a lot longer than you.
She saved my ass
hundreds of times.
You really should go home.
First thing tomorrow,
we'll go see Penguin.
You're right.
He's got his ears on the street.
Jim.
Never mind.
I'll see you tomorrow.
(fanfare plays,
laughter, applause)
Give 'em a wave.
(laughs)
(rim shot)
(applause)
Some people say
Bruce has a split personality.
(laughter)
Very good, Master Bruce.
(blows kiss)
(microphone feedback hums)
For my next illusion,
I'd like to call to the stage
esteemed Deputy Mayor
Harrison Kane.
Is there something familiar
to you about those two?
Oh, my God.
(phone ringing)
Lee, I was just...
Jim, it's Barbara.
She's here.
And-and I think maybe Jerome...
(muffled groan)
By the way, nobody here...
is getting out alive.
(laughter)
(crowd gasps)
(groans)
(crowd murmuring, screaming)
(Jerome cackling)
Right, Master Bruce,
time to leave.
Ta-da!
(screaming continues)
(laughing)
Selina!
Bruce!
(Jerome cackling)
(panicked chatter, screaming)
(Jerome continues cackling)
(tires screeching)
(sirens wailing)
You! What's going on?
Hostage situation.
The magician just killed
the deputy mayor.
It's Jerome Valeska,
the same man that killed
Commissioner Essen.
Who's in charge here?
I guess you are.
(phone ringing)
Lee.
Thank God.
I've been trying to...
JEROME: Sorry, Jimbo.
It's just little old me.
Jerome.
Are you outside?
(gasps)
You are, aren't you?
(laughs):
Oh, goody!
I swear to God,
if you've hurt her...
Breathe, James.
I haven't touched a hair on
your girlfriend's pretty head.
See for yourself.
(over speakers): This is
live television after all.
(Jerome laughs)
(Jerome laughing)
The feed just came back.
(Jerome imitates explosion,
laughs)
You son of a bitch.
True, but not the point.
Hey, let's talk
about what I want.
Excuse me.
(clears throat)
$47 million,
a helicopter, obviously,
the dry cleaning
I left at Mr. Chang's--
be careful, the man is a crook--
and, mm, I don't know, a pony.
(laughs) Uh...
You got ten minutes,
or I start killing people.
Remember,
this is being broadcast
to every home in Gotham,
so, you know,
don't let people die. Bye.
(cackling)
(cackling continues)
I think that went well.
THEO:
Enough!
You need to pack up
your pathetic little sideshow
and leave.
Is that right?
It may be presumptuous to speak
for all the citizens of Gotham.
But we are sick of you!
You're a small,
vicious man with a pathetic
need for attention.
Enough, man.
For God's sakes, enough.
I'm curious what your
leverage is here, Mr...?
Theo Galavan.
Well, Mr. Theo Galavan,
if you don't sit down,
uh, I'm going
to shoot you.
In the face.
I know there is some
human decency left in you.
If you need to take
a hostage, take me.
But let these people go
home to their families,
to their children.
(crowd gasps)
BARBARA:
Boring.
JEROME:
Right?
Get your men.
We're going in.
I used this
to sneak into the party.
We're lucky those dummies
didn't know about it.
Wait.
We're almost outside.
Wait. I have to go back.
Are you crazy?
That guy was killing people!
Yes, and Alfred's back there.
I'm not going back.
I don't expect you to.
Selina...
I miss you.
I just wanted
to say that.
(sirens wailing,
helicopter whirring)
You're refusing a direct order?
I could have your stripes.
That maniac killed
the commissioner.
Not my men.
We're not equipped for this.
Fine. I'll go it alone.
(sighs)
Oh.
Hold very still.
(breathes slowly)
Oh.
I can't look.
Someone tell me
how it turns out.
(toy gun squeaks, crowd gasps)
(laughs)
Damn!
Turn around.
(crowd gasps, Barbara whoops)
Well, clap!
(applause)
(laughs) Ooh!
So, Lee, how's Jim doing?
I hope he's not
blaming himself
for this whole
Essen being killed thing.
You are one crazy bitch.
So rude.
You know, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna make a prediction.
(grunts):
Ow!
Within a year, Jim and I
will be back together.
(giggles)
Want to know why?
Because we're both the same.
We both have a dark side.
And one day, we will tell
our grandchildren
about how this man-eating harpy
almost tore us apart!
But in the end,
love conquered all. (giggles)
You...
I'm sorry. What's that?
(grunts)
Hasn't been ten minutes.
I need to buy you a watch.
(crowd gasps)
Well...
I think it's time for tonight's
first official victim,
you all know and love,
poor rich boy,
parents murdered in an alley,
and my favorite volunteer.
Where is... Bruce Wayne?!
You know I'm an orphan, too,
Bruce?
I killed my
parents though.
Where are you hiding?
Bruce!
Where are you, buddy?
Kill his butler.
MAN:
Come on, move it, butler.
(gun clicks)
JEROME:
All right.
Last chance, Bruce,
but it's about to get
very butler brainy out here.
D-Detective Gordon.
He's going to kill Alfred.
I have to help him.
(singsongy):
Brucey!
No. It's you he wants.
Bruce, just wants you.
I will not let him hurt Alfred.
JEROME:
I'm bored.
Shoot the butler.
Stop!
(crowd gasps)
(laughs)
What the bloody hell
are you doing, Bruce?
There's a gun
in my jacket.
Detective Gordon's
behind the curtain.
(crowd gasps, gun clicks)
Let's get this
started, huh?
You, check behind the curtain;
make sure no one's
playing silly buggers. (laughs)
(crowd screaming)
Drop the knife!
(cackling)
I don't have a clean shot!
Stay calm, Bruce.
(laughs)
Seems like we got ourselves
a pickle.
What do you say, Brucey boy?
Want to boost
our ratings, huh?
(laughing)
Smile.
THEO:
I said, enough!
(crowd screaming)
I know, I know.
(gasping weakly)
This is not what
we rehearsed.
I'm so sorry, Jerome.
You have real talent.
But now, you see,
the plot thickens.
Enter the hero.
(straining):
You said...
I was
gonna be...
(sighs)
Jim!
Stop her!
(crowd gasps)
...a pony. (laughs) Uh...
See, someone like that has
no interest in building things.
He's not part of a tradition.
Hmm?
It's chaos for
chaos sake.
(Jerome cackling over TV)
Perhaps I could use a new laugh.
(door opens, closes)
BULLOCK (chuckles):
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
Huh?
Wow.
Dude!
Color me impressed.
You know,
if I close my eyes,
I can still see you holding
Fish's umbrella.
"Yes, Ms. Mooney.
"No, Ms. Mooney.
Whatever you say, Ms. Mooney.
That wig looks great on you,
Ms. Mooney."
Seriously, the worm
has turned.
Detective Bullock.
I heard you rejoined the force.
I am so happy.
But aren't you missing
all of the excitement?
Yeah, I got the word
too late.
Besides, I want
to talk to you.
Of course.
Always happy to help.
See, there's talk
on the street
that Jim Gordon
did a favor for you,
collected a debt,
and the guy ended up dead.
(laughs)
Rumors.
(scoffs)
(laughs):
Rumors.
Huh.
Well, then again,
where there's smoke...
Jim shouldn't
worry about that.
He and I are
good friends.
Well, see, that's the problem,
Oswald; I think he is worried.
Because something
happened today,
and you were the obvious person
to come to.
And I sensed
Jim was a little reluctant
to come down here.
Like I said, he shouldn't worry.
As long as you two
remain friends.
Exactly.
Yeah.
I got half a mind to take you
outside and beat you senseless
with a garbage can.
(guns clicking)
Maybe some other time.
Call yourself
whatever you want, man!
The King of Gotham.
But, to me, you'll always be
that little umbrella boy.
And if you come after
Jim Gordon,
you got to come after me.
And I still owe you for Fish.
But, seriously,
this place is amazing.
(kisses)
(door opens, closes)
Get me another drink!
You were very brave.
You helped save the lives
of everyone in here.
Your parents,
they would've been proud.
ALFRED:
That they would've been.
They also would've
given me the sack
if I let you do
something so idiotic.
It was all of us.
We were a team.
Yeah. I guess we were.
Is he okay?
Fine. Though
I'd still like him
to get checked out
at the hospital.
Barbara gave him quite a knock.
Any word on her?
No, she went through a trapdoor
in the stage.
They must have
always been planning to use that
as their exit.
Don't worry. We'll find her.
Uh, Mr. Galavan, sir.
Alfred Pennyworth.
I'd just like to thank you
for saving
young Master Wayne's life.
Oh.
If there's anything
I can ever do for you, sir...
Or I.
I really just did
what any citizen of Gotham
would have done.
I wish that were true.
Jim Gordon.
Theo.
Well, if you ever
need anything,
please, call.
We're all in this
together, right?
Thank you, sir.
Right, well, I suppose I better
be getting this young man home.
It's been much more
of an exciting evening
than originally planned.
I never did like magicians.
(chuckles)
Good night.
It was very nice meeting you,
Dr. Thompkins.
And you, Bruce.
Good night's sleep,
you'll be right as roses.
I do hope we get to see you
again soon.
Thank you.
Alfred.
Sure you're okay?
I'm fine.
Kiss me?
Jim...
Kiss me.
Oh, bugger.
Alfred.
You knew, didn't you?
I didn't know, Alfred.
You did. You let me make
a right mug of me-self.
BRUCE:
Alfred, I had no idea.
ALFRED: You did.
I didn't know.
ALFRED:
Well, I didn't know.
REPORTER:
Despite the presence
of the GCPD, it was
billionaire Theo Galavan--
newly arrived in Gotham
but already
making his name--
who stood up
to the escaped lunatic.
Am I a hero?
Hmm. Apparently.
(chuckles)
THEO: I think tonight,
the people of Gotham have said,
"Enough."
The reign of tyranny is over.
Now the real fun begins.
Poor Jerome.
THEO:
Yes, very sad.
Such a compelling character.
But limited, you know?
He was never
gonna last long.
Hmm. I don't know
about that.
The kid had a
way about him.
Oh, poor baby,
did you get a bump?
REPORTER: ...the killer,
Jerome Valeska, is dead,
his murderous escapades
left a deep impression
on Gotham.
JEROME: Nobody here
is getting out alive.
(cackling)
(parents arguing)
Coming through.
(sighs)
Bang. (cackling)
(cackling)
(cackling continues)
(knife slices, man gasps)
CICERO: You will be
a curse upon Gotham.
Children will wake
from sleep screaming
at the thought of you.
Your legacy will be
death and madness.
(cackling echoes)