Previously on Gotham...
Jim, meet my daughter, Sofia.
Do you ever think about
walking away from it all?
Sometimes.
This drawing depicts a man
being healed by water.
That's Ra's al Ghul.
He wants the knife.
The opening bid
will begin at $50,000.
A hundred thousand dollars.
Two million dollars.
Sold to Mr. Bruce Wayne.
I guess you could say
I'm your number one fan?
What's black and white
and red all over?
Zebra, with a gaping hole.
I think something is wrong
with your brain, Ed.
Gordon, you've got a visitor.
- You shouldn't have come back here.
- I'm a Falcone.
You came looking for a gangster.
That's exactly what you found.
That knife is the key
to everything.
Well, not everything.
Hmm.
Beautiful.
And you bought this at auction?
Supposedly, it was
the embalming knife
of the first-century
Mesopotamian king.
Balahsi.
And what is it that you want
of me, Mr. Wayne?
Anything you can tell me, Dr. Winthrop.
I wanna know exactly
what it is I bought.
Perhaps you should've considered that
before you dropped two million
dollars on it, shouldn't you?
Leave it with me overnight.
I'm back.
Man, you really need
to clean that room.
My delightful grandson.
I have access to the very clean
historical records room
at Gotham Central Library
and he uses it for his homework.
Oh, Alex, let me introduce you
to Mr. Bruce Wayne and his guardian
- Alfred Pennyworth.
- What's up?
Whoa.
Where did that come from?
That cuneiform's definitely
pre-Phoenician.
Alex is an avid student of history
and sometimes assists me.
A word, Master Bruce.
Now it's all very well involving
an old geezer, but a young man?
Just you remember
who's after that knife.
What so important about it
that Ra's al Ghul
wants it so badly? We need to know.
Dr. Winthrop.
Alex.
I have to ask you
to keep this matter between us.
- Of course.
- Yeah, cool.
I mean...
Yes, Mr. Wayne.
I'll check back tomorrow.
Until then.
No.
Come on, Ed. Come on.
You can do this.
This has to be the perfect riddle.
No!
Yes.
Yes!
Is that you?
Tomorrow night, Oswald,
is the night you die.
Alex.
Bring me the Palmerian Codex.
Ah!
What is it?
"He, who rises from the waters,
"whom death shall not touch.
"With this sacred blade,
"his final savage destiny
"shall be fulfilled.
"The earth will quake.
"Blood will flow.
"All tremble
"before the Demon's Head."
What's the Demon's Head?
Not what, my boy.
Who.
There is a legend
in the time of this knife,
of a man who could not die.
Or who died, but was reborn.
Have you ever, in your reading,
come across the name Ra's al Ghul?
He was a warlord.
But those guys always had stories
invented about them.
They're just stories.
My boy, people believe
in these stories.
They kill for them.
I think Bruce Wayne has stumbled
across something
much more complex than he imagined.
And infinitely more dangerous.
No one should be here.
Here, take this into my office.
Stay quiet. Quickly.
Dr. Niles Winthrop.
- What a pleasure.
- Who are you?
The museum is closed.
How did you get past the guard?
My apologies.
But my business is pressing.
"Greek, Vase - second Century."
Oh.
This was made by a forger
in Marrakech in the 15th century.
He had some talent,
but told the most obscene jokes.
Tell me who you are,
or I shall call the police.
I am looking for a knife
Bruce Wayne brought you earlier today.
I don't know what you mean.
The best liar I ever met
ran a brothel in Shanghai.
Her quite considerable gift was that
you knew she was lying,
but didn't care.
You so badly wanted to believe her.
You, Dr. Winthrop,
are a terrible liar.
Where's the knife?
The police, they're coming.
I imagine they are.
End of crime, my ass.
Harper?
- Where's Bullock?
- He asked me to fill in.
He took a sabbatical for a few days.
You baby-sitting me?
Do you need baby-sitting?
- What have we got?
- Dr. Niles Winthrop.
Curator of antiquities.
Looks like somebody snapped his neck.
No witnesses, of course.
Fire alarm triggered security.
Maybe the dead guy pulled it
right before the...
Yeah, thanks. Anything else?
Yes, actually.
According to
Professor Von Dead's log book,
the last person to visit him,
I'm talking
just yesterday afternoon...
Bruce Wayne.
It's all right, let him in.
Detective Gordon.
What...
- What happened?
- We were thinking
we would ask you the same thing.
You met with Dr. Winthrop
just yesterday, correct?
I...
I bought an old knife at auction.
Dr. Winthrop agreed
to examine it for me.
I was coming by
to check on his progress.
When was he killed?
According to the fire alarm,
just past midnight.
Whoever did it
must have snuck past security.
His grandson. Alex.
He's my age, a little bit younger.
- Have you talked to him?
- No one's seen any kid.
I'll get on it.
Where's the knife?
Alfred was right.
I shouldn't have left it.
Bruce, slow down.
What's this knife?
You think someone
would actually kill for it?
Detective Gordon, I'll tell you
what you want to know.
But all I ask is
that you let me come along.
If this is because of the knife,
then I'm responsible.
Bruce, a man is dead,
a child is potentially missing.
This is not time to play detective.
What do you know?
What's so special about this knife?
As far as I know,
it's just an old knife.
But I paid a great deal for it.
And there was another bidder.
A very aggressive one.
Barbara Kean.
Right.
Well, Harper will track down
the grandson.
I'll deal with Barbara. You go home.
I'll call you when I need you.
You're here. Finally.
I've kept you waiting. Apologies.
I see my guests have arrived.
Oh, yeah.
Gotta say, they don't do much
for the vibe of the place.
If you had acquired the knife
when I first requested it,
they wouldn't be necessary.
What's so special
about this knife anyway?
Sentimental value?
Only a destiny
born of blood and magic
two thousand years in the making.
Uh-huh.
Now Dog-Boy here is gonna fetch...
His name is Anubis.
And yes.
Bring me the knife.
And you can kill the boy.
Boss.
Knocking, Victor. We discussed this.
Uh-huh?
She's here.
Show her in.
Ms. Falcone, welcome to Gotham.
Mr. Cobblepot,
it's a pleasure to meet you.
Call me Oswald.
Please, have a seat.
Thank you for coming to see me.
I learned from my father
when the king of Gotham
summons you, you come.
And how is Carmine?
Can we hope to see him sometime soon?
Shall we just address
the elephant in the room?
By all means.
My father's illegal businesses
hold no interest for me.
I'm here because the Falcone family
has a number of charities
that need my attention.
And you can only provide
that attention
by being here personally. In my city.
- I understand your concern...
- Oh, do you?
But I assure you,
it's unfounded.
You know, your father
taught me many things.
Among them was to nurture
a healthy paranoia.
For example, when I took over,
some of his old capos
went underground.
Now, perhaps
they've vanished for good.
Or perhaps they're waiting
for a Falcone
to return to lead a rebellion.
Who knows?
But, I hear your father's voice
whispering in my ear,
"Be careful."
Now...
I need to know that you are not
on some fool's errand
to rebuild your father's empire.
Otherwise...
I will stab you.
I was 13 when my father
first sent me away.
He said that
Gotham was too dangerous.
But this is my home.
I wanted to come home.
That's why I'm here.
Is that enough?
Gotham, Mother to us all.
I think we have nothing
to worry about.
Give your father my best, will you?
Jim.
What a lovely surprise.
Barbara.
Heard you popped up.
Seems like you landed
on your feet, as usual.
Hmm.
A woman has to stay busy.
You seem different.
You like this me better?
You recently bid on a knife
at auction.
So much for catching up.
That knife is now missing
and the person who had it is dead.
What were you doing last night
around midnight?
I was here
with witnesses.
We done?
No.
This place.
The money you used
to bid on the knife.
- Who's bankrolling you?
- A client.
And, no, though tempting,
I can't give you the name.
Is it Ra's al Ghul?
If it is Ra's al Ghul, you don't know
who you're dealing with.
I don't know who or what
you're talking about.
Now, should I call my lawyer?
We'll be in touch.
Come here.
You followed me?
After I told you to stay away?
What the hell were you thinking?
I told you I'm responsible.
You should have let me come with you.
It's clear she's lying.
I can help you find the killer,
find Alex.
That's my job!
You wanna help?
Who is Ra's al Ghul?
And why didn't you
mention him before?
I wasn't certain he was involved.
- The way she talked, I...
- You're lying, again.
Ra's al Ghul is the real leader
of The Court of Owls.
He's the one responsible
for the virus
and having me kidnapped.
And you didn't think to mention
any of this before?
Why would he want the knife, huh?
What's so important about it?
I have no clue. That's what
I've been trying to find out.
- Yeah?
- Gordon, the kid's not at home.
Apparently,
Grandad was looking after him
while the parents were traveling.
He's not at school,
no one's seen him.
Great.
Listen, I need all the info
you can get
on a man named Ra's al Ghul.
He could be connected.
Sure. But how do you spell...
No one's seen the boy.
He's either hiding
or the man
who killed his grandfather has him.
The police were triggered
by a fire alarm at the museum.
Alex could've pulled it,
taken the knife.
If so, he'd be hiding, scared.
Where could he be? Think.
I only met him for a second.
You want to play detective?
Now is your chance.
What was he wearing? What did he say?
Give me anything.
He had on his school uniform.
He just came from studying at...
Gotham Central Library.
His grandfather had a room there.
Alex has a key.
If he's hiding,
he's made a choice
not to trust the cops.
If I show up, he might run.
He needs to see a face he knows.
Come on.
Ed Nygma sent you?
The Edward Nygma?
Do it again.
My once friend Oswald, now my foe
It's me, Ed, just so you know
It's time we meet,
I think you'll agree
You'll find me where
the Earth meets the sky
Where water flows and birds fly by
At dusk we'll meet,
I'll see you there
We'll settle things
unless you're scared
What the hell was that?
We should torture 'em.
Just get them to tell us
where Nygma is.
No, he just found us on the street.
Well that's exactly
what you would say.
Leave!
That barmaid who kidnapped Ed
said he lost his step.
Clearly she was mistaken.
He's up to all of his old tricks.
So I'll meet him.
You and your men will hide nearby.
Attack when I say.
Do not kill Ed though.
I want Victor to freeze him again.
- Huh?
- Not you, the other Victor.
Oh.
"Earth meets sky,
"water flows, birds fly."
Obviously, he means the pier.
Gather your men.
I want Ed Nygma.
Historical Records room?
In the back.
Alex?
It's me, Bruce Wayne.
You can come out, it's safe.
Alex, please, I just wanna help you.
Alex.
This is Detective Gordon.
You can trust him.
Okay. Okay, all right.
I'm so sorry.
That man, he killed him.
He killed my grandfather.
It was a man? You saw his face?
I only saw him from behind.
It was the knife.
Did you know it was dangerous?
No. I had no idea.
Alex, we need to get you down
to the station.
I can't. That man,
he'll think I saw him.
- He'll come after me.
- I will protect you, I promise.
He'll keep coming
till he gets the knife.
Alex, do you have the knife with you?
No, I hid it.
Take Alex and meet me
at the station. Go.
Who sent you?
Thanks for clearing that up.
Bruce?
Run!
- Bruce Wayne call in?
- No.
We released a city-wide BOLO.
What about that name I gave you?
Zip. I tried Richard Gull,
Ralph Ghoul...
Detective Gordon?
Ra's al Ghul.
Minister of Antiquities attached
to the consulate of Nanda Parbat.
Thanks for coming in.
Nanda Parbat.
That's in the Himalayas, right?
Well done, Detective.
Few in your country have even heard
of our tiny nation.
Why don't we speak
in my captain's office.
A bit more private.
Of course.
- I'll be with you in a minute.
- Thank you.
I don't get it.
This is the guy
that you're looking at for murder?
Why does he just walk in?
Barbara must've told him
we were looking for him.
- Yeah, but...
- The two thugs at the library.
If they're working for him,
they would've told him
that we've contacted Alex.
He could think
that Alex gave us the knife.
I can use that.
Call Alfred Pennyworth.
See if he's heard from Bruce Wayne.
That thing bit me.
- I need to get you to a hospital.
- No. No.
Then the police.
- Detective Gordon...
- No, I can't. I can't, they'll find me.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared.
I don't know how you do it.
You fought those men, and I...
I just froze.
Same as when that man
killed my grandfather.
Fear is normal.
In the alley,
when my parents were killed
I was terrified.
I just stood there.
There's nothing wrong
with being afraid.
Once you realize it's normal
then you can put it in its place.
Then, you can act.
Fight back.
I felt bad for you.
When that happened to your parents.
You were all the kids at school
talked about.
What did they say?
That you live alone
in a mansion,
don't go to school,
fly around in jets.
They make you sound weird.
- Maybe I am.
- No.
You're cool.
I'm weird.
And you're a little weird too,
I guess.
But...
You're weirdly cool.
I'll take you to the knife.
Can I get you anything? Coffee?
That won't be necessary.
I think you know why I'm here.
- Enlighten me, Minister.
- Barbara Kean,
with whom you spoke,
was acting on behalf of my government
to procure a certain property.
Said property is
the cultural patrimony of my people.
Why not bid on the knife yourself?
There were competing claims.
And if we bid officially,
alarms may have sound
and so it seemed better
to do it quietly.
But Miss Kean
failed.
And now,
regrettably, I understand
there's been a murder?
Dr. Niles Winthrop.
Curator at the Gotham
Natural History Museum.
That's awful.
But the reason I'm here, Detective,
is to press my claim
on behalf of my government
and entreat you
to return the knife to me.
You say this knife
is important to your country.
Please explain.
There is an ancient story
amongst my people
of a man who could not die.
In his time,
he committed terrible acts.
Raised a great kingdom.
And then vanished.
What happened to him?
If the legend is to be believed,
he walked away from his throne,
vowing that one day he would return
and complete his destiny,
but that would require
a particular knife.
This knife.
A story.
As I said.
But to my people,
very meaningful.
I hope that satisfies your curiosity.
Some.
But you see, Minister,
my chief concern
is there's a boy,
the grandson of the curator.
He's being hunted.
Now, perhaps
that's because of the knife.
Or perhaps,
the killer thinks he saw something.
Did he?
No.
- Then he's safe.
- Yes, but you see,
I would have to know that
for certain
before I would do anything
that might affect the case.
Such as release the knife.
May I see the knife, Detective?
It would so set my mind at ease.
Where the bloody hell is Gordon?
Gordon, incoming!
Gordon, where the hell is Bruce?
You!
- Alfred, back off!
- Wait, wait! Get your hands off me.
You don't know
what you've got in there.
I'm starting to,
but you are not helping.
I need you to calm down.
- Let me finish talking to him.
- Gordon.
- Not now!
- Gordon!
He's bloody vanished.
He knows we don't have the knife.
We have to find Bruce.
- Donna Falcone.
- Do not call me that.
- You gotta hear us out.
- No, I don't.
I didn't invite you here.
We're not having this meeting.
Now I'm gonna ask you,
please, politely, to leave.
We served your father for years.
When Penguin took over,
we had to go underground.
Then we heard a Falcone
was back in Gotham,
we knew it was time.
Did you ignore my father
like you're ignoring me?
I just told you to leave.
Just tell us
when your father's coming back
to put that Penguin in his place.
Please understand me,
my father is not coming back.
This is Penguin's city.
And I want you to leave
- before he finds out you're here...
- Too late, I'm afraid.
Victor, how many graves did you dig?
Two.
But they're roomy.
And there we are.
My paranoia is put to rest.
Phew!
You used me.
You had me come to your club.
You knew word would get out.
That my father's loyalists
would find me.
I was a worm on your hook.
With one difference, my dear.
The worm is usually eaten.
So you trust me now?
You're alive, aren't you?
I would plant roses.
They cover up the smell.
My father wouldn't have
killed those men.
He would've invited me to his club,
as you did, but then gone further.
He would've invited me to dinners,
had us seen in public,
sent the message
that the old order supports me.
And those men you killed
would've pledged you loyalty.
Now they're fertilizer.
See, my father, he knew how to build
on the strength of others.
But it's your city.
New times, new methods.
There was an ancient Sumerian
jewelry box here.
I just replaced it.
Hiding in plain sight.
Good thinking.
Bruce, there's a legend
about this knife.
That terrible things happen
because of it.
But what if it's not just a legend?
My grandfather is dead.
The man that killed him,
he can't have this.
I won't let him.
I promise.
We have to get out of here. Run, run!
The Nanda Parbat consulate
is giving us the run around
and we can't get in there
without a warrant.
- Bruce still hasn't called you?
- No.
What the bloody hell were you doing
letting him tag along
with some murder investigation
in the first place, eh?
No, you do not get to lecture me
about a lack of honesty and openness.
You and Bruce have been
up to something for weeks.
What have you two
gotten yourselves into?
Damn it, Alfred. I'm on your side.
Well, that may be, mate.
But whatever Master Bruce decides
to tell you is his decision.
Isn't it?
You are his guardian.
You are allowed
to violate his privacy
if it is gonna keep him
out of danger.
Stick to the point.
What are you doing to find my boy?
What can I do, huh?
I have every cop in this city
on alert.
But as long as Ra's al Ghul
thinks he has that knife,
his life is in danger.
Yeah, right,
and what about the other boy?
Did he tell you
where he put the knife?
No. But I have to assume
Bruce is taking him to get it.
All right.
There's gotta be a clue or something
inside here.
- What?
- You stay here.
What?
The access I gave you
depended on trust.
If you can't be honest with me,
there's nothing I can do.
Harper.
If Mr. Pennyworth tries to leave,
arrest him.
On what charge?
She'll think of something.
I went to the pier.
I waited. Ed didn't show.
He...
- God, just get on with it!
- Right.
One, two...
I waited and waited but you never came
You must be a coward or worse,
a lamebrain
I'll give you one chance
to make it right
Meet me again, this time at midnight
I'll make this one easy
This place makes some people lie
Some people speak
and some people cry
Honestly, that could be anything.
Can we please just torture them, now?
Why not?
Wait a minute.
Run.
Bruce.
Down!
Let's go. Let's go.
Take him, take him, go.
Get off of me.
It's time you tell me
what's going on.
What is so important
about this knife?
Why are people dying for it?
Excellent question, Detective.
And you shall have your answer soon.
Just give me the knife
and I will release the boy.
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
Of course.
Bruce, hand me the knife.
Bruce. Hand me the knife.
You don't understand.
He killed Alfred.
And then brought him back to life.
And Alex's grandfather
was afraid of this knife.
I can't give it to him.
If we don't hand it over now,
Alex is dead.
- That is all that matters.
- No.
You don't know who he is.
I can't.
Well done, Bruce.
You're finally beginning
to see things clearly.
The question is...
Are you strong enough?
- No.
- Drop the weapon.
Hands in the air, on your knees.
Arrest me.
Ra's al Ghul
is on his way to Blackgate.
And we made contact
with Alex's parents.
It's gonna take them
a couple days to get home.
Bruce.
Ra's is a psychopath.
You're not responsible
for his actions.
I wanna help.
But everything you've said so far,
Alfred dying and coming back to life,
magical waters.
Give me something I can believe.
Perhaps now you understand
why we held back.
It doesn't matter
what you say, Detective.
This is all my fault.
Alex is dead because of me.
I killed him.
Oswald!
I waited for you.
Again.
And you didn't show. Again.
You coward.
Where are you?
Here.
And I may be many things,
but I'm not a coward.
Your riddles suck.
"This place may make some people lie,
"some people speak,
and some people cry."
That could mean anything.
Lying, speaking, crying.
You're just describing
a range of human behavior.
No!
I meant, lying, as in "lying dead..."
Laying down. Lying down.
As in dead.
Oh.
The answer was Stoker Cemetery.
Clearly.
Only an idiot wouldn't see that.
Face it, Ed. You can't make riddles
to save your ass anymore.
I guess she was right.
- What? Who was right?
- Your number one fan.
She said that there
was something wrong with you.
Took me a while to believe it, but...
You're not smart.
I am too smart.
- I'm the Riddler.
- Oh, God, that name again?
Tell me, how long did it take you
to come up with those riddles?
- I don't know.
- A minute? Two minutes?
A few hours.
Six hours.
- Six hours?
- Yes!
For two bad riddles?
Does that sound
anything like the old you?
Well, perhaps I'm still recovering
from being frozen in a block of ice!
But revenge
will certainly make me feel better.
You will never have revenge on me.
Ah! Yeah, I will.
- No, you won't.
- Oswald.
I'm gonna shoot you.
Yes. You might shoot me, kill me,
but only he can get revenge on me.
The man I froze on that pier.
The man who would've killed himself
before writing those idiotic riddles.
The man whose name
I still will not speak.
But he's gone.
You're just Ed Nygma.
And, not even Ed Nygma,
because Ed Nygma
would've noticed something.
What?
Doesn't it feel kind of chilly
in here?
You remember him?
My other Victor?
I'm going to put you on ice, again.
You want the same pose
or something else?
No, wait, please.
- Got it, same pose.
- No!
Okay, Oswald.
I'm not the Riddler.
Do it.
Stop.
I've changed my mind.
I'm not gonna freeze you.
I would only be freezing Ed Nygma.
Who cares about that?
No. A better revenge
is having you live,
knowing that you're not him
and you never will be again.
Goodbye, Ed.
Who am I?
I must have been seven or eight.
It was late.
I snuck downstairs to find my father
with a man before him on his knees.
Begging for forgiveness.
My father stabbed him in the neck.
The next morning,
there wasn't a trace of blood.
And we had breakfast at that table.
Now you'd think I'd want to stay
far away from Gotham
but this house, this city,
is in my veins.
I'm home, Jim.
Word on the street is three
Falcone capos have gone missing.
They were in hiding.
Penguin used me as bait
to draw them out.
And killed them.
And you let him?
Don't act the innocent, Jim.
You came to Carmine Falcone for help.
It was never going to be bloodless.
So is that your plan?
Get close to Penguin,
gain his confidence, what then?
I need to know
what you're going to do.
No, you don't.
You want this city back from Penguin.
I'll give that to you.
But you have to trust me.