MAN: Previously on Gotham...
Where are you, Ed?
What's green and red
and goes round and round?
Zebra with a gaping hole.
Your brilliant mind is as damaged
as the rest of your body.
I guess she was right.
You're not smart.
We'd need an army to take on Penguin.
Makes me miss Falcone.
SOFIA: You came looking for a gangster.
That's exactly what you found.
I'm a Falcone.
I need to know
what you're going to do.
You want the city back from Penguin.
I'II give tha! to you.
Did you really think
I wouldn't figure it out?
The two of you have been
whispering like teenagers for weeks.
You never deserved her
in the first place.
Yes, I killed him.
I am sorry.
(Bruce) There's a legend
about this knife.
The man that killed
my grandfather can't have this.
I promise.
That's Ra's al Ghul.
That knife is the key to everything.
Give me the knife
and I will release the boy.
- Bruce, hand me the knife.
- I can't.
(KNIFE sucmc)
(SCREAMS)
DRIVER: So who's the vegetable?
ORDERLY: Ah, he used to be a gangster.
Name's Gilzean. Maybe Gold?
He took a slug in the noodle.
Been in a coma six months.
So, hospital brass
wants to free up beds?
Yeah. Say take him upstate.
(BOTH LAUGHING RAUCOUSLY)
Rest in Peace, Butch Gilzean,
Cyrus Gold,
(CHUCKLES) whoever the hell you are.
(BOTH LAUGHING RAUCOUSLY)
Hey, Harvey, has anyone contacted you
about Ra's al Ghul?
No.
Ijust heard from
Judge Bam Bam's clerk.
- His trial got pushed off the docket.
- And?
And I want to make sure, him being
minister of a foreign country,
doesn't let him weasel out of this.
- He killed the boy.
- That's above my pay grade, pal.
Ijust bust the bad guys.
D0 you?
These are release forms.
Of my collars.
Let me guess, each one of them
has a license from Penguin, right?
Jim, I am stuck between
a rock and a hard place.
Every moop you bust with a license.
The Commissioner orders me
to let him go.
What am I supposed to do?
- Your job.
- I am doing myjob.
Gordon, got a call
from the judge's clerk.
It's about Ra's al Ghul.
- Here.
- I'm doing myjob.
Master Bruce.
No sleep?
Again?
Once more about that boy's death.
Don't say it's not my fault.
It is my fault.
- Alexis dead because I hesitated.
- Well, perhaps you did,
but that doesn't make you
his murderer, does it?
Ra's killed that innocent little boy
and he's going to pay for it.
You really think locking him up
in Blackgate will stop him?
He still wants his dagger.
Stop going on about
the bloody dagger, will you?
Just so we can just
get some breakfast. Please.
I think I finally found something
in Dr. Winthrop's notes.
There's a description on the handle
that Dr. Winthrop
was able to decipher.
Says the knife is intended
for the one
who was bathed in the healing waters.
Right. Well, assuming that's not me,
that would be our boy Ra's.
But that doesn't have to mean
it's for him to use.
Perhaps to be used against him.
- I see.
- No.
You clearly don't.
What you're suggesting is
that knife and that knife alone
is the only thing
capable of doing him in.
If Ra's al Ghul believes
this knife will kill him,
that could explain
why he wants it so bad.
S0 he can destroy it.
Before someone fulfills the prophecy.
Master Bruce, I know that
you feel bad about Alex, we all do.
But at this point,
you must remember your vow.
No killing.
Taking a life,
never mind how justified.
Will lead you down a darker path
than you could ever possibly imagine.
I know. I've been down it.
- Do you understand me, Master Bruce?
- I understand.
Good.
Just get yourself ready.
Chop-chop.
WOMAN: Such a tragedy.
He was only a child,
and always so lovely.
A heinous crime,
perpetrated against
such an innocent boy.
WOMAN: And his grandfather, murdered,
just the day before.
I'II just be a moment, Master Bruce.
Diplomatic immunity.
You are joking, ain't you?
The Nanda Parbat embassy filed papers
to have him extradited.
- Could happen this week.
- The monster killed a child.
I know. I was there. Look,
I'm telling this you as a courtesy.
- Oh!
- But the news will get out.
When it does,
I need you to watch Bruce.
I'm worried about him.
And you blame me?
(SIGHS)
You're his guardian. aren't you?
You're supposed to protect him,
and instead you've been placing him
in harm's way.
ALFRED:
Oh, I see. So that's rankles, is it?
Keeping you in the dark?
Well, if I was you,
I'd focus on your own job, Detective,
which is keeping Ra's al Ghul
behind bars, tucked up.
Just keep the news away from Bruce
as long as you can.
On that, we agree, Detective.
The boy's been through enough.
(RACY INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(LOCKER DOOR OPENING)
(GATE BUZZING)
Thanks for coming, Barbara.
Hell of a chicken coop.
S0 what's the angle?
How about this?
Say the word, we'II be home,
drinking Chianti by dinnertime.
I think I'II decline.
S0 why did you call me here?
To say goodbye.
When I brought you back to life,
I asked you to be
my eyes and ears in Gotham.
- You became so much more.
- Save it.
What about everything
you promised me?
Do as I ask, and I will give you
a gift beyond your imagining.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
What the hell was that?
You will see.
Goodbye. Barbara.
(noon SHUTS)
(OMINOUS INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
(GRUNTING)
(SINGING)
Born on a Monday
Christened on Tuesday
Married on a Wednesday
Took ill on Thursday
Grew worse on Friday
Died on Saturday
Buried on...
Sweet mother of Mary.
Never seen nothing like him before.
He's white as a picket fence.
Easy. We ain't gonna hurt you.
What happened to
your drawers, big fella?
(SQUEALS)
Easy.
No!
(GRUNTING)
We're gonna get you, you freak.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GASPING) Who are you?
("SOLOMON GRUNDY" PLAYING)
"Solomon Grundy.
"Born...
on Monday."
License compliance amongst the GCPD
remains high.
The program is an
unmitigated success.
Numbers, Mr. Penn.
According to my tabulations.
86 percent of crime is accounted for
under Pax Penguina.
Which means that
14 percent of crime happens
outside of my licensing system.
The numbers are
very good, Mr. Cobblepot.
Get Firefly. I want examples made.
Yes, that might help.
But then, if scorching a few idiots
was all it took,
anyone could rule Gotham.
Thank you for your insight,
Miss Falcone.
I don't recall summoning you.
I came to see
if you had lunch plans tomorrow.
An invitation?
(SCOFFS)
After I killed your father's
last remaining loyalists?
(CHUCKLES)
Perhaps you overestimate
the pleasure of your company.
Oswald.
You may think you have everything
but there is
one thing you don't have.
The Falcone name.
A name that once accounted for
all criminal activity in Gotham.
As in, one hundred percent.
Now you'rejust rubbing it in.
I propose we have lunch
somewhere public.
By doing so, you'll show Gotham
that you have the support
of the Falcone family.
And that should be enough
to send those outlying
criminal elements
scurrying back under your umbrella.
Mr. Penn, item number four
on my to-do list.
Kill Sofia Falcone.
Add a question mark, will you?
Tomorrow it is.
God! Your people have pills
for everything!
Insomnia. Anxiety.
You have to have something for me.
I don't know.
A pill to reverse the effect
of having your brain frozen
and unfrozen?
That's kind of specific.
I will not be condescended to
by an idiot in a lab coat!
You're not even a doctor!
Okay, relax, man.
Just tell me your symptoms.
Fogginess of the mind,
decreased capacity to think
ten steps ahead,
inability to solve riddles.
I have got to improve
my brain function.
I could take a pill or a vitamin.
I'II even consider a natural remedy.
I don't want to get your hopes up,
but there is something.
What? Tell me.
Atrial drug.
It claims to boost
your natural cognitive abilities.
- That's perfect! Where is this?
- The sample drawer.
- What is it called?
- Smartivia.
Blue pills. Diamond shaped.
Smartivia. Smartivia.
I don't see them.
Try towards the back.
Ah! I don't see it.
Here it is.
(GROANING)
Afake gun? seriously?
Wait, wait, wait.
I just need to know.
Do these work?
No, dummy. They're sugar pills.
And I'm calling the police.
(ALARM RINGING IN DISTANCE)
Go on, gently.
(GASPING)
(SIRENS BLARING)
(GROWLS)
Ow! (PANTING)
(YELLS)
Butch!
You know Grundy?
Butch.
I have never had an issue with you.
Barbara Kean, she's the problem.
You and Tabitha were
innocent bystanders.
Wow. You don't get much sun. Look...
Man talk too much.
- COllins. Deal with this, will you?
- Yep.
Gordon. Gordon!
- Bruce is gone.
- What?
- You've got to get me into Blackgate.
- What are you talking about?
When we got back from the wake,
he said he was gonna go
straight to bed,
but he must have snuck out
between then and now.
My concern is that
he's taken the knife...
and he's gonna try and kill
Ra's al Ghul.
- Y0u're serious?
- He's being bloody serious.
We gotta go to Blackgate now.
And then you can tell me
the many ways
I failed the child, all right?
- Oh, Iwill.
- Listen to me.
The boy is on the verge
of doing something that
there's no coming back from.
He needs our help.
AII right.
Let's go.
(DOGS BARKING)
(TENSE INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
It's about time.
Shift ended five minutes ago.
Come on.
(ENTHRALLING INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
You weak,
foolish boy.
(GRUNTS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GASPING)
You're still not ready.
My name is Bruce Wayne. Stop him!
Stop him!
Master al Ghul.
Take him below.
What... what are you doing?
(DOOR BUZZING)
We got your call.
But I checked the logs.
Bruce Wayne hasn't been here.
With all due respect, I don't think
he'd come as a regular visitor.
He's a billionaire, after all.
I think what Mr. Pennyworth
is trying to say
is Bruce Wayne could have
paid someone to get him in here.
No offense.
We just want to look around.
Sure. Whatever you want.
But you came all the way here
for nothing.
And we're gonna need your weapons.
Standard procedure.
Of course.
(CLEARS THROAT)
- Finished?
- That's absolutely it.
Unless you wanna
check my undercrackers.
This way.
Undercrackers?
They're here.
(GROANING)
Sugar pills, my foot.
That dream was horrible.
Oh, my God! Oh, you're real.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
You know Grundy?
What? No. No.
No, who's Grundy?
Solomon Grundy.
Bom on Monday.
Your hand. How...
I'm sorry, what happened to you?
Grundy not know.
Okay. Iet me get this straight.
You don't remember...
who you are or how you got here?
I'm sorry.
Grundy, I don't know you.
Best of luck, though.
Hope you get the skin thing
figured out. Later.
(SCREAMING)
You know Grundy.
You help Grundy.
Be Grundy friend.
I'm attempting to be civil.
But I can't help you.
Why?
Ijust can't. AII right?
- Why?
Because...
- Because I can't even help myself.
Ow!
You don't know who you are.
Well, that makes two of us.
I used to be smart.
Brilliant.
And now that's gone.
I can't even rob a pharmacy.
S0 you want me to help you?
I can't.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Well, I am feeling a bit peckish.
We are closed.
Janos.
Last I saw you was
at my tenth birthday.
You bought me ruby earrings.
Said it would be a fitting gift
for the daughter
of the king of Gotham.
Sofia Falcone.
I heard you had returned to Gotham.
What can I do for you?
I was wondering how you were faring
under Penguin's rule.
The Szabo family is quite content
under Oswald Cobblepofs
Iicensing system.
But even if we were not,
we would be wise enough
to not say anything.
Good.
Because I've invited him
to your restaurant for lunch.
And I want it to be a lunch
he'll never forget.
(FUNKY INSTRUMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
RA'S: Bruce...
Where am I?
Beneath Blackgate Penitentiary.
Alfred Pennyworth
and Jim Gordon are upstairs.
In the company, unbeknownst to them,
of my men.
Let them go.
They have nothing to do with this.
Still playing
the white knight, Bruce?
You replaced the guards
before I got here.
I'm sure your friends
can fend for themselves.
You applied for diplomatic immunity,
knowing I'd hear about it.
And come for you.
I wanted the knife.
But not for the reason you think.
It's been ages
since I first held this dagger.
It was given to me
moments after I was bathed
in the Lazarus Pit.
Submerged in the waters.
(GASPING)
Suspended between life and death.
I saw a vision of you,
myhüh
You're insane.
I'm not your heir.
I don't even understand
what that means.
It means that you are the only one
who can end my suffering.
Please.
You want me to kill you?
Set me free.
Well, thanks for the snack, big guy.
But it's been an emotional day.
Gotta go.
(EXCLAIMS)
Not this again, come on!
I've told you,
I'm better off on my own
and you are, too.
So let go!
Let go!
Hey, freak.
I knew we'd find you.
And it looks like you got a friend.
I assure you, we are not friends.
Get 'em. Both of 'em.
No, no!
(GRUNTING AND GROANING)
Grundy!
(SCREAMING)
Hot! Hot!
Grundy friend, help!
Don't leave. No. Help!
Help. Hot. Hot!
Hot!
(GROANING)
Grundy friend not dumb.
Grundy friend...
smart.
Oh, yes.
Yeah. you're right.
Water beats fire. (LAUGHS)
That was smart.
Oh, boy.
(GASPING) I can't breathe.
Oswald.
- They said this is their best table.
- Interesting choice.
Are you sure it's not too intimate?
The point was to get the word out
that the Falcones support me.
Don't worry. People will talk.
I chose this place because
I heard your mother is Hungarian.
I thought you might like
a taste of home.
(SCOFFS)
I can assure you, Oswald.
I'm not here to poison you.
Perhaps.
(COUGHS)
Well, the chef likes to go heavy
on the paprika, doesn't he?
How is the food otherwise?
Serviceable.
Well, I'm stuffed. Thank you so much
for meeting me, Miss Falcone.
And thank you to your family
for their support.
You can't leave
until you've tried the goulash.
If it's anything like
the chicken paprika, I'II pass.
It's a house specialty.
My mother made goulash.
Brought the recipe from Budapest.
Handed down through her family
for 300 years.
I doubt this will hold a candle.
(GRUNTS)
- I'm leaving.
- Oswald.
Oswald!
It took me forever
to find his mother's recipe.
Did you follow it exactly?
I followed the recipe to a T.
The little man didn't like?
Honestly, I don't know.
How long have you worked here?
Two years, thereabouts.
I was in Blackgate for a time.
- We must not have overlapped.
- Yeah?
- As a guard?
- As a prisoner.
Oh, yeah.
Heard about that.
Is there a reason why you're not
taking us through maximum security?
Prisoners are in the yard
this time of day.
Been some changes
since you were here.
McCloskey? That's funny.
I know another J. Mccloskey
who works here.
My cousin. Gets confusing sometimes.
AII right. Let's go,
through this door.
I've got to say, mate, I really love
what you've done with the old place.
However, I've got a question for you.
Yeah?
Where are the real guards?
(ALL GRUNTING AND GROANING)
Where is Bruce Wayne?
- Ra's al Ghul has plans for the boy.
- Where is he?
(CHUCKLES) You'll never find him.
Oh, you underestimate
my resolve, pal.
Well, at least we know Bruce is here.
Well, we've walked the floor.
Where could he be?
There's the yard.
The tower, but they're too public.
There's a sub-basement.
Accessible by the service elevator.
Which way?
(DOOR opens)
God.
Who did I tell you, specifically.
Not to let in here?
Miss Falcone is here to see you, sir.
I'm sorry, Oswald.
I'm not sure what upset you, but...
Enough!
Did you think I would really believe
this was all some coincidence?
That goulash tasted exactly
like my mother used to make.
You can't fault me
for the restauranfs authenticity.
You're buttering me up.
But for what?
Is it so hard to believe that
someone would want to do
something nice for you?
There was only one person
in my whole life
who ever did things for me
without wanting something in return.
And that was my mother.
Then I envy you.
My father never helped anyone
unless it benefited him.
And eventually, it drove away
everyone who loved him.
Go. l'll decide
what to do with you later.
- Oswald, I only want to help you.
- Oh, you wanna help?
Try leaving.
(SCOFFS)
Your foot.
It's just the weather.
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
What are you doing?
- Don't.
- (SOFTLY) It's okay.
And I won't judge.
When I was a child, I broke my ankle
while playing with my cousins.
I was desperate. Crying in pain.
My father told me to put ice on it.
Toughen up, stop with the tears.
But my mother went with me
to the hospital.
And on the way, she told me
that cold
actually increases the pain.
What's needed is warmth.
My mother.
She used to sing.
(HUMMING)
RA'S: This maybe hard
for you to understand.
But I have walked this earth
for centuries...
waiting for you, Bruce.
Only you can kill me,
and only with that dagger.
That is my curse.
That is the meaning of my vision.
I don't believe you.
- Believe me.
- This is just another manipulation.
See.
Look.
My true form.
Every moment of my life is agony.
End my suffering.
Whatever your curse is,
you deserve it for what you've done.
You're angry, Bruce. I understand.
But unless you strike me down
with that blade,
you will never be free.
No!
I won't.
Then allow me. to tell you
what will happen...
if you don't kill me.
I will disappear.
And let you live your life.
You will follow the path of light.
Grow into a fine man.
Become a husband.
A father.
There may be a day when you forget
I ever existed.
But then, I will return.
And I will kill everyone you love.
Just as you watched your parents die.
Just as you watched me
slice your friend's throat,
I will slaughter your wife
and children before your very eyes
and there will be nothing
you can do about it.
(GRUNTING AND GASPING)
Die.
(SCREAMING)
Yes. (BREATHING HEAVILY)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENTS)
Are you going to arrest me?
For what?
For murder.
I don't know what
I just saw in there.
But as far as I'm concerned,
Ra's al Ghul's men
broke into Blackgate and he escaped.
I betrayed myself,
and my parents' memory.
I took a life.
I did exactly what Ra's said I would.
Just because you know
you're capable of doing something
doesn't mean it has to happen again.
Bruce, you and I have known
each other a long time.
Since the night your parents
were murdered.
Now you may not feel like
you're that kid anymore,
but I knowthat you are.
One who believes in doing good.
And fighting for what's right.
Who will do anything
to keep the people he loves safe.
Nothing that happened today
changes that.
What are you doing?
You said it yourself.
It's over.
No.
- Can't let you do that, Master Bruce.
- Alfred.
Listen, we started
this vigilante caper
to prepare for Ra's return,
didn't we?
It's become so much bigger than that.
I see that now, I mean,
I was wrong and you were right.
You can make a difference.
I'm not the hero Gotham needs.
I made that decision
the moment I killed Ra's al Ghul.
I took the dark path.
Yes, you did.
And it's gonna be a long,
bumpyjourney back.
But I believe in you, Master Bruce.
I always have and I... I always will.
And I understand
that you don't feel worthy now.
But when you do, this...
this will be waiting for you.
As will I, sir.
These guys that attacked us.
They didn't even have five bucks
between them.
We need a new plan.
What?
Truth.
Grundy friend know...
Grundy?
You deserve to know...
you and I,
(SIGHS)
were the very best of friends.
And then something happened to you
and Ijust didn't recognize you.
But what is important
is that with your muscles,
we can make money.
And with money,
we can make me smart again.
And then we'II figure out
what happened to you.
Just trust me, okay?
Grundy, come on.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING AND CHEERING)
(PUNCHES THUMPING)
(GRUNTING)
Yeah, come on!
What is this? A knitting circle?
Let's see some blood!
Hey, I'm looking for the person
in charge here.
You're looking at her.
What do you want, squirt?
Well, if there's money to be had,
we'd like to put our hat in the ring.
(LAUGHS SARCASTICALLY)
And who are you?
L'm... Hey!
Come back.
I'm this fine gentleman's manager.
Trust me, he's a monster.
Well, more grist for the mill.
We'II get you patched up.
Then We'II talk.
Hey!
G0 get the doc.
AII right. One, two, three.
Hey, doc! Cherry wants you
to come look at some new guy.
WOMAN: I'II be right there.
English - SDH