Previously onGotham...
Went to see a sergeant I know
and we did some digging on any M.
And Malones that fit our particulars.
Patrick Malone,
goes by the nickname "Matches."
So, you found him.
What do you need me for?
I need you to get me a gun.
So, you're gonna kill him.
I love you.
- Kristen.
- No!
If we can cure a man
like Oswald Cobblepot,
we can cure anyone.
Nobody yet has failed
to regret vexing the Penguin.
And you are vexing me!
You don't eat.
What's the matter, Liebchen?
You are sick?
So, pale you look.
Tell Mama what's wrong.
You don't have to tell.
I know.
Life is hard when you are special.
And you are so special.
So, clever. So, handsome.
When you are older, with a stick
you'll beat away the women.
But only if you eat your goulash,
so, you can grow big...
and strong.
Matching the Crane formula
to our own enforced REM
stimulation seems to be providing
the desired results.
How's his behavior day-to-day?
Docile, friendly.
Appetite?
Low, but I'm not concerned.
I'm curious to see how he responds
to adverse stimuli.
Let's move on to the...
ice cream test.
Ice cream.
Why do you have ice cream?
I'm sure I don't know.
It's unusual, isn't it?
My name's Oswald. What's yours?
I don't have ice cream.
Why do you have ice cream?
Please, by all means, you...
I don't have ice cream!
Why do you have ice cream?
I apologize, sir.
I don't know what...
Excellent.
No violent reaction.
The treatment is working perfectly.
Guards.
Where's my ice cream?
How come you have ice cream?
I want mine!
Where is it? Where is it?
I want my ice cream!
What flavor is it? What flavor is it?
- Hey.
- Hey yourself.
What? You asked me for it.
I know.
- If you don't want it...
- I want it.
You look scared.
I'm not.
Is it loaded?
Ain't no point in an unloaded gun.
Guns aren't for show, Bruce.
And they're not for protection.
They're only for one thing.
Of course.
Lee.
- Good morning.
- Hey.
Look, what we talked
about after Arkham...
That's not why I'm here.
I wanted you to take a look at these.
It's Kristen Kringle's
final paychecks.
Her paychecks? How'd you get these?
I went to Human Resources
to get her new address
and they gave them to me.
She never picked them up.
They don't know where she is.
She never cashed them,
never left a forwarding address.
That's odd.
Well, Dougherty has money.
Maybe they're traveling.
I don't like it.
She said that Dougherty
hurt her before.
Really?
Have you talked to Ed about it?
- No.
- Maybe he's heard from her.
I didn't feel like it was
right to worry him.
I just want to know
that she's all right.
I can take it to Missing Persons.
No, no, that's all right.
I'll look into it.
I'll let you know what I find.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Oh, Master Bruce.
- You ready?
- Yes.
I'm gonna need more than that.
We're on the hunt
of an extremely dangerous man.
This is life-and-death stuff.
I need you to tell me
that you are sure.
Now, are you sure?
Yes, Alfred, I'm sure.
Right.
And when we're on the street,
you follow my every lead.
No faffing about, is that understood?
- Yes.
- Good lad.
Our quarry is an East Side boy.
His misspent youth, Patrick "Matches"
Malone was arrested several times
with a geezer called Cupcake.
I suspect there's irony
at play there.
They were partners in crime
until Matches' testimony put
Mr. Cupcake in a Blackgate
pen for ten.
Says here that Cupcake's out now
and he runs this strong-arm little
firm called the Mutants.
So, I guess we'll have to start
there then.
- Solomon!
- Grundy!
Remember, let me do the talking.
I know how to handle this type,
all right?
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen!
Hope we find you well.
We're hoping to have a little chat
with a gentleman called Cupcake.
You found me, sweetheart.
What's up?
Mr. Cupcake,
pleasure to meet you.
My name's Alfred Pennyworth.
Now, we're on the hunt
for a guy called Matches Malone.
Now, we know he snitched you up
a few years ago.
So, I'm sure you wouldn't
mind returning the favor,
if you know what I mean.
- Who's your friend?
- Never mind who he is.
I'm Bruce Wayne.
Boy billionaire Bruce Wayne?
That one.
I'm willing to pay you a lot of money
if you can tell us where
to find Malone.
Oh, really? Why?
- Master Bruce, please let me...
- I think he killed my parents.
That's a good answer.
How much money?
How much will make you talk?
Million dollars.
- That's too much.
- The boy's cheap.
Mr. Cupcake, if I may be
so bold as to just...
You, I'm talking to the shot caller.
Tell you what, son,
I'll make you a deal.
Give me $50,000,
you won't get Matches,
but you get to leave here
with your fingers and toes.
Steady on, pal.
I'm just messing with you.
I wouldn't hurt the little boy.
I like little boys.
You, on the other hand,
I'm not sure about you.
Tell you what, I'll give you
that rat Matches for 50 grand.
But first...
you must fight me.
I beg your pardon, excuse me?
Fight me, baby.
No, you see, I'm not really a...
I'm not really a fighter.
I saw you step up just now.
"Steady on, pal."
Mr. Cupcake, I really can't
foresee anything positive
coming out of this altercation.
You're in my house!
- Fight is what we do here!
- Yeah!
- That's right.
I'll pay you 100,000 dollars
for the name and no fighting.
I'm not about money, little boy.
I'm about respect.
No fight, no deal,
no Matches, no exit.
All right, well, I suppose, you know,
Mr. Cupcake, if you put it like that.
If you wouldn't mind, sir.
Will you be all right?
We'll have to wait and see, won't we?
Are you acting like this is my fault?
- It's not for me to say, is it, sir?
- How is it my fault?
I told you to let me do the talking,
did I not?
And did you do the talking? Yes.
I think you'll find, yes,
you did do the talking.
To be fair, I think the result
would have been similar in any case.
If, Master Bruce, we are lucky enough
to walk away from this alive,
let this be a lesson to you.
And another thing.
Pick your battles.
Don't let them pick you.
Right!
On your honor, I win...
we walk.
Sure thing, mister.
On my honor.
They'll understand.
But the fight doesn't stop
till somebody says uncle
or goes to sleep.
Now get it on.
The other thing,
of course, Master Bruce,
to remember is that timing
is everything.
See, there's other factors
at play there, Master Bruce.
- There's footwork and leverage.
- Stop talking!
What? What, you want some?
Alfred!
- Uncle! Uncle!
- No!
He's slowing!
See, Master Bruce,
big muscles require lots of blood.
Strength costs wind.
Now, if you're gonna beat a big man,
all you have to do...
Is outlast him.
- Go!
- No...
Uncle, uncle.
Uncle! And the butler wins.
Are you okay?
I'm absolutely flipping peachy, mate.
You're a tough old cat.
Not too shabby yourself, Mr. Cupcake.
- Matches.
- 50 grand.
Will... will a check be all right?
Yeah, yeah, sure,
a check will be fine.
Make it out to cash.
Go see Jeri down at Celestial
Gardens on the East Side.
She'll know where to find Matches.
Pleasure doing business with you,
Mr. Cupcake.
How do you feel?
A couple of hours skip
and I'll come up lovely.
Good. You stay here.
You ain't going nowhere...
Till I'm up and about.
Yes, I hear you.
Promise me, Master B.
Say again?
Prom...
Sorry.
- Blood.
- Life.
- Throat.
- Song.
- Cat.
- Kitten.
- Mother.
- Hug.
Crime.
- Punishment.
- Revenge.
Remorse.
Remorse. Let's talk about that.
I feel it. A lot.
Remorse is progress. Remorse is huge.
Is it?
I feel terrible about stuff.
I... I was so mean to people.
Remorse is a healthy and natural
response of the human condition.
It is a good sign.
It is a normal sign.
I want to be normal.
I want to be good.
You must think I'm lying to you.
Oh, no.
I can tell when someone's
lying to me.
Oswald, you are making
a magnificent transformation.
Your real self is emerging.
A kind, decent young man.
Just a few more therapy sessions
and you'll be right as rain.
More therapy?
Oh, just a little.
I know there's a discomfort factor,
but after all,
it is making you better.
Yes?
Oh, you do want to get better...
Don't you?
Yes, Professor Strange.
Oswald, please. Call me Hugo.
Yes, Hugo.
Hey, Ed, you busy?
I'm studying decomp rate
of various colors of ink to see
if we can use tattoos to help
determine time of death.
Is that a yes or a no?
Please come in.
How can I help you?
I was wondering if you'd heard
from Kristen Kringle lately.
I'm strong as a rock,
but a word can destroy me.
What am I?
Silence. I've heard nothing.
Well, I don't want to alarm you,
but we can't seem to locate her.
She hasn't cashed her
last few paychecks.
Oh, my Lord. Do you...
do you think that something
bad has happened?
No. No, no,
we're not there yet, anyway.
"We"? Who is "we"?
Oh, just me and my curiosity.
I don't know Tom Dougherty well.
What is he like?
What is Tom Dougherty like? Rotten.
That's what I'd heard.
And Kringle told you herself that
she was moving south with Dougherty?
Not in person. She left a note.
Could I take a look at it?
I didn't really think of it
as a keepsake.
Right.
Excuse me.
Yeah.
Again?
Yeah, okay. I'm on my way.
So, that's the game, is it, Jimbo?
Gonna try to outsmart me?
Play me for a fool?
I don't think so.
Well, that took you long enough.
For a butler, you sure
do get beat up a lot.
- What happened?
- We got his name, Jim.
The name of the man
that killed Bruce's parents.
Matches Malone.
Dude, we're the cops.
Thank you for sharing this with us.
- When were you gonna tell us?
- I haven't got time to explain none.
We got a good, solid lead
from the same place
that I got seven bells knocked
out of me.
Now Bruce, he won't answer his phone,
so, my guess is he's gone
after this Malone...
- solo.
- "Gone after"?
To do what, exactly?
What can he do? He's a kid.
Only reason to go alone,
he's gonna kill the man.
I mean, I... I told him not to.
I said, "You're too young
for killing."
- Said I'd do it for him.
- Again, we're the cops.
Do not tell us stuff like this.
You've got to understand,
both of you...
this is not a game.
I understand.
Tell me where he is.
Hey, cowboy.
Yes, sir.
Have fun.
I got a feeling inside of me
It's kind of strange,
like a stormy sea
I don't know why, I don't know why
I guess these things have got to be
I got a new rose, I got her good
Guess I knew that I always would
I can't stop to mess around
I got a brand-new rose in town
Hello, Bruce.
What took you so long?
I'm looking for Jeri.
Yeah, you are.
Follow me.
Come.
Take a pew.
Iced tea? Soda?
No, thank you.
You like the show?
I liked it.
Are you Jeri?
Some people call me that.
What? What can I do for you?
Sorry. You know my name,
so Cupcake called you.
I assumed you already know
why I'm here.
I just want you to say it.
I'm looking for Matches Malone.
Why?
He killed my parents.
What you gonna do if you find him?
Ask him some questions...
Kill him.
Okay, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Killing people isn't,
you know, that easy.
Hey, maybe you've killed
people before.
- You killed people before, blood?
- No.
But no one's killed
my parents before.
Well, Matches has killed
dozens of people.
Men, women... Children...
He's a professional.
And what, exactly, are you?
Do you know where he is?
Course I know where he is,
he's a friend of mine.
You gonna give me a good reason
to tell you where he is?
Justice.
Please.
- Money.
- Nope.
I don't care about money.
Try something else.
I have a gun.
That's a good reason.
Please.
Tell me where he is.
Come on, kid...
you ain't even pointing it at me!
What is your problem?
I've been told it's unwise
to point a gun at someone
if you're not ready to shoot them.
And I'm not.
Very wise young man.
Thank you, Jeri.
It's been... Interesting...
talking to you.
Matches lives in that big building
on Grand Street between 9th and 10th.
Apartment 9B.
Why did you tell me that?
I thought he was your friend.
He is. Well, he was.
Matches is gonna be happy to see you.
You, my boy, are the childish
hand of fate.
Well, that makes me God in a way,
doesn't it?
And who doesn't like to play God?
Bruce!
- Bruce!
- Hey!
Please let me go.
Bruce, listen to me.
I know what you're doing.
Alfred told me everything.
He shouldn't have done that.
- I understand how you feel.
- No, you don't.
No, you're right. I don't.
And it doesn't matter.
This is as far as you go.
You're gonna take over from here,
are you?
Yes, I am.
I'm sorry, Detective Gordon.
That doesn't reassure me.
Bruce, I can't let you do this.
G.C.P.D! One, two, three, four!
Hey!
I got a new rose, I got her good
Guess I knew that I always would
I can't stop to mess around
I got a brand-new rose in town
See the sun, see the sun,
it shines...
Matches Malone?
I want to hire you.
Kids now.
So, you want to hire me?
I want someone to die.
- Wait a while. They will.
- I don't want to wait.
You're kind of young to be putting
out a contract.
I'm old enough.
Are you a proficient killer?
I thought you wanted to hire me.
You didn't say nothing about
a job interview.
I have to be sure
I'm getting the right man.
Don't you know a killer
when you see one?
Actually, you look very ordinary.
Have you killed a lot of people?
I kill all kind of folks.
Just about every way you can.
Rich, poor, guilty, innocent.
By hand, by blade, by gun.
Burn just one guy to death,
they call you Matches
the rest of your days.
Life's funny, isn't it?
Cat got your tongue?
What's the matter, kid, you sick?
Sorry.
I'm fine. Nervous is all.
You seem to be the right man.
Damn right I am.
- Where is Bruce Wayne?
- You are so angry.
I'm sensing a personal relationship.
Maybe like a surrogate
father type of thing.
- Where is he?
- He is...
he's a really good kid.
He's got steel in him.
He's gonna grow up
and be a strong man one day.
Well, if he lives long enough.
This is gonna go a lot better for you
if you don't make me angry.
Angry is your natural state,
isn't it?
You are the infamous Jim Gordon?
- Everybody knows about your temper.
- This isn't about me.
There's a kid out there in danger.
Oh, there's lots of kids
out there in danger!
Why is this poor little rich boy got
your special attention?
You're trying to make me angry.
Do you want me to hurt you?
Could you?
- I got nowhere else to be.
- No.
Tell me where you sent
Bruce Wayne, now.
You are a lot less fun
than advertised.
What time is it?
Yes, he should be there by now.
So, you could get there just in time
for the cleanup.
Price starts at ten grand
or so for a simple hit
on an adult male vic.
Then there's a sliding scale,
depending on how hard the job is.
Charge double for women.
Triple for kids.
No babies. I won't kill babies.
"Ten grand"?
That's cheap.
Low overhead.
Who do you want dead, son?
You really don't remember me, do you?
Remember you?
No.
- We've met before?
- Yes.
We've met before.
You killed my parents.
Keep your hands where I can see them.
Relax, kid. I won't jump you.
I could if I wanted to, but...
I'm too tired.
Who are you, now?
My name is Bruce Wayne.
And when was this we met before?
Two years ago.
An alley in the theater district.
You killed my mother and father,
Thomas and Martha Wayne.
I was there.
Rings a bell.
You looked right at me.
I was busy that year.
My parents were important people.
It was a big deal
in all the newspapers.
I don't read the papers much.
Don't watch TV.
Always the same bad news.
- You really don't remember?
- Oh, hey...
some of them stick with you.
There was this mustached fella.
He was a big fat crybaby.
Comes back to me in my dreams
all the time.
Like he's important.
I can't even recall his name.
Did I stab him? Toss him off a roof?
I don't know.
My parents were in evening clothes.
It was cold and wet.
You... you grabbed my mother's
pearl necklace, it broke.
Oh, yeah.
And the beads went everywhere.
Coming back to me now.
It was a nice-looking blonde lady...
silver-fox-type dude and a kid.
That was you?
That was me.
Who hired you?
Maybe nobody did.
Maybe I just saw some rich suckers.
Somebody like that walks
into a dark alley,
they deserved it,
because they let it happen.
It's the way of the world,
isn't it, son?
- Don't call me son.
- Why?
If I did what you think I did,
then I made you what you are.
Just like Gotham made me.
Just like the rich folks like
your parents made Gotham.
I might as well call you son.
I can make you tell me who hired you.
- You think so?
- I can hurt you.
I can shoot you in the knee.
Or the stomach.
But you can't make me
tell you a damn thing.
Killer's code ain't much,
but it's what I've got.
If I did what you say I did
and someone hired me to do it,
you'll never know their name.
Not if you take me apart piece
by piece.
You better believe that.
Well, then I guess there's
nothing left to say.
Here's to you, son.
You've been a long time coming.
You want me to kill you.
Why?
Little rich kid like
you wouldn't understand.
Try me.
A man gets tired...
doing wrong and going unpunished.
Nothing happens.
You start to wonder if...
there is a God.
Tighten your left-hand grip.
Aim right here.
A little low. She'll kick.
Come on, pull the damn trigger.
No.
Don't lose your nerve now! Do it!
Look at me!
I'm a monster.
You need to kill me.
I wish you were a monster.
But you're just a man.
Bruce! He's in there.
- Good luck, buddy.
- Hey, hey!
Hey!
I think there's been a mistake!
- Hey.
- Who's there?
Remember me?
I'm the man with the ice cream?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, you knocked me
around pretty good.
Guess that ice cream must
be delicious.
It was pretty good.
You look kind of uncomfortable.
I have a sharp knife here.
What say I help you out?
Help me out?
You have to promise to be nice, okay?
There's no ice cream in here,
so there's no reason
to get mad, okay?
- Promise?
- Okay.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
Bravo, Cobblepot.
Sir?
This is an official certificate
from the Gotham Board
of Health and Hygiene.
It states that Oswald Cobblepot
has passed all mandated tests
and by the laws of Gotham City
is hereby declared...
sane.
I'm sane?
You are as sane and normal
as any other citizen.
Ms. Peabody, even.
Do you know what that means?
No more therapy?
Oswald, you are a free man.
I don't follow you.
You are sane, ergo,
there is no reason for you to be
in a mental health institution.
You are free to go.
I'm fine right here.
Oswald, Oswald, Oswald,
you are just feeling
anxious about change.
That is totally normal to feel
that way upon release from care.
Okay.
I guess if it's normal.
You are a sane, gentle, good man.
And good things happen
to good people.
They do?
I... I've never heard that before.
A true thing. Trust me.
Well, you've been right so far.
Thank you, Professor... Hugo...
For being such a kind mentor
and friend.
That's very touching, Oswald.
Thank you so much.
And now, why don't you
go back to your room
and get your belongings together?
Okay.
Are you sure about that,
- letting him go?
- Not really.
- He's an experiment.
- He's a notorious criminal.
- There'll be an outcry.
- The outcry will pass.
People are afraid of progress,
Ms. Peabody and yet, somehow,
we keep progressing.
I hope you'll at least alert
the police he's been released.
Enough input, Ms. Peabody.
I have other reasons,
deeper plans for Cobblepot,
that you can't know about now.
For your own safety.
Deeper plans?
Deeper than building semi-human
creatures in the basement?
I'm sure I don't want to know,
thank you very much.
On your head be it.
There's a reason why we might
have missed Malone.
Okay? His record goes back
to nursery school on up,
assault, robbery, battery,
a couple of hits for the mob.
But this is way, way back.
Last few years, nothing.
That's why his name never came up
as a potential suspect.
Flying under the radar, I guess.
It happens.
Guess we'll never know
if he really did it.
The boy says he confessed.
That's good enough for me.
Malone killed the Waynes.
The question is, who paid him
to kill the Waynes?
That's a question
I no longer care to ponder.
Hey, Ed. How you doing?
Oh, getting along just fine.
Keeping busy.
Any news on the Kringle front?
No. Damn.
Sorry. I've been a little busy.
I'll get into it.
- Don't worry.
- Me, worry?
I'll let you know as soon
as I know anything.
Detective Gordon,
do you have a second?
Yeah.
You'll let me know.
I bet you will.
Acting like you forgot
all about Kristen Kringle.
- Sure you forgot.
- You're ready.
- Thanks, Detective.
- You suspect me somehow,
that must be it.
You're trying to lull me into a false
sense of security
while the claws of your investigation
close around me.
Is that it, my little man?
You take me to be a fool?
We'll see about your clever
little plan, Jim Gordon. We'll see.
I can make plans of my own.
Master Bruce!
"Alfred,
I have left home for a while
to live on the streets with Selina.
Please, wait and listen
before you react.
You need not worry that I'm in danger
or that I've lost my mind.
I've thought long
and hard about this decision
and I know it's the right one.
Malone's death made me realize
a couple of things.
You can't kill murder.
You can't get revenge on evil.
You can only begin to fight such
things by not doing them.
And you can only fight them
where they live,
not just at Wayne Enterprises.
In the streets, in the slums,
in the bad parts of town.
So, that's where I'm going."
He's lost his mind.
"I'm not going to start
battling muggers or anything.
But one day,
I am going to do something
to help the people of Gotham.
I don't know what yet, but I will.
Meantime, I need to learn stuff.
Number one: I need to learn
how to live in the same world
other people have to live in.
Selina's giving me a place to sleep
and will show me the ropes,
so, like I say,
there's no need to worry.
I'll be in touch soon
and I'll come home eventually.
Please, Alfred,
trust me and honor my wishes.
Don't try to bring me back.
I need to do this.
Sincerely,
your good friend
Bruce."