FISH: Killing Falcone would only
create chaos. I need to siphon his strength.
So when the time is right, taking over his
organization will be like slipping on a glove.
I'm so angry all the time.
Will it ever go away?
Alfred, can you teach me how to fight?
GORDON: You've been through a lot.
BARBARA: I'm scared, Jim.
Everywhere I go,
I can feel that monster Zsasz.
ALVAREZ: Gordon, some unis
brought in a perp. Claims to know you.
Hey, detective.
Miss me?
Barbara?
SELINA:
Whoa.
Sweet crib.
You must be one rich cop.
- It's my girlfriend's place.
- Where is she?
I don't know. Barbara?
So, what? I get to stay here alone?
I'm hungry.
BARBARA: Dear Jim, I thought I could
be strong and brave for you, but I can't.
Every place I go, I see Falcone and Zsasz.
I'm nervous and needy and screwed up.
I know that's not what you need or want.
So I'm going away
for a while to get myself together.
This is Gordon.
Oh. Uh, right, yeah. We're in the penthouse.
Come on up.
Sounds like your girlfriend's
not coming back, huh?
Why is she worried about Falcone?
None of your business.
What happens now?
You gonna get the charges dropped?
I will, but you're my only witness
to the Wayne murders.
You gonna cuff me to a drainpipe again?
I'm not gonna hold you against your will.
G.C.P.D., juvie, you'd break out.
So I do get to stay here.
No. I have someplace else in mind.
That's the sketch artist. I need you
to describe the man who shot the Waynes.
Wait, where am I going to stay?
Wayne Manor.
Don't speak to the inmate. Don't touch
the inmate unless in service of your job.
Don't accept anything from the inmate
under any circumstances.
Who is this guy, anyway?
OFFICER 1:
Ian Hargrove. Some genius bomb maker.
Took out over a dozen buildings
in Gotham.
OFFICER 2:
The one that blew up the commissary?
Yeah. He did it with match shavings
and apple cider vinegar.
So no mistakes today, got it?
GUARD:
Raise your hands up.
GORDON: She said this is the man
who killed your parents.
She said she saw his face.
Do you recognize him, Bruce?
No.
What's her name?
Selina Kyle.
- Do you believe her?
- Yes, I do.
So she saw everything?
And you want her to live here with us,
do you?
Common street criminal.
She's hardly older than Bruce.
She's just a kid who's seen too much.
This is for her safety.
G.C.P.D. is full of moles.
How long would you have us
put her up, then?
I don't know.
No, the answer is no. Her being
here will put Master Bruce in great danger.
Alfred.
She is the witness to a murder, Master
Bruce. You do understand that, don't you?
She's also the best chance we have
at finding who killed my parents. Isn't she?
Yes, she is.
Then she can stay.
As long as it takes.
I've made my decision.
Yes, Master Bruce.
Look, I know this is a lot,
but I'm doing everything I can.
Montoya, Allen and I are meeting
with an ADA they trust this afternoon.
Oh, a trustworthy lawyer. In Gotham.
Look, if we find this guy, we'll need her.
She'll have to testify before a judge.
Won't be easy.
Witnesses back out all the time.
The ones that stick it out
do so because they care about the victims.
We'll do our best to be nice to her, then,
won't we?
That's from the Chinese Ming Dynasty.
Five.
Five hundred years old.
You can get one just like it
for 5 bucks in Chinatown.
I'm Bruce Wayne.
Selina Kyle.
People call me Cat.
Nice to meet you, Cat.
What are you doing?
- Nothing.
- What's in your hand?
I said, what's in--?
What the hell?
[GROANS]
Hargrove!
Ian Hargrove, time to go.
MAN:
Kid, you screwed up, bigtime.
But you're still young. You deserve
a second chance. I have a bet for you.
You call heads or tails.
You lose, you go to jail.
You win, we let you go.
- Bet.
- Hold on, there's a catch.
You have to make a promise to God.
If you win, you're gonna take this as a sign...
...that you need to go back to school
and get your life straight. Can you promise?
- Do you promise that?
- Yes, sir.
Okay, then.
- Call.
- Heads.
Walk away, kid.
Somebody up there loves you.
Hey, Harvey.
Go. Remember your promise.
Jim Gordon, G.C.P.D.
I hear good things about you, counselor.
Harvey Dent. Likewise about you, detective.
Was some trick with the coin. What if he
guesses wrong? Gonna send him to jail?
Teenagers, they nearly always call heads.
Don't know why.
Two-headed coin.
Whatever works, right?
So who is he, Jim?
Who really killed the Waynes?
Well, this is what we have.
No ID.
But this is from an eyewitness
that you have in custody.
It's not enough to go to the law with.
Even if we had ID...
...it's the people who hired him we want.
I agree.
Your eyewitness is useless in a courtroom.
But the idea of your witness
could be immensely valuable.
Ever hear the name Dick Lovecraft?
Sure. Billionaire.
Property. Construction. Chemicals.
As corrupt as they come.
Falcone, Maroni, even Wayne Enterprises.
Lovecraft has dealings with all of them.
Since the Waynes' deaths, he's doubled his
fortune, including a piece of the Arkham deal.
DENT: Lovecraft had a long feud
with Thomas Wayne over deals and politics.
They couldn't have had
a more different vision for Gotham.
I'd bet my career
on his involvement in the Wayne murders.
That's a big bet.
I want to use your witness
to go after Lovecraft.
How? My witness can't connect
Lovecraft to the perp.
Lovecraft doesn't know that.
I'll let it leak out...
...that we have a secret eyewitness
who's going to blow the case wide open...
...and connect Lovecraft
to the Wayne killings.
Lovecraft will get very nervous.
The people around him will get nervous.
And that's when people start talking.
Unless Lovecraft wasn't involved.
If so, which I doubt, we still win.
Whoever was involved
will get their cage rattled, won't they?
- Bet he makes a move.
- You like to bet a lot.
What have we got to lose?
- My witness becomes a target.
- No.
That's the beauty of it. We never file papers.
We never name names.
It's just a powerful story.
Your witness is perfectly safe.
You're on board with this?
We've been on board, Jim.
Harvey's one of us.
I want what you want, Jim.
I want to make this city a better place.
No names. Not mine.
Not my witness. Nothing. Just a story.
Just a story.
All right. Let's try something.
BULLOCK: Thought I was gonna have to
work this without you. Where you been?
You know what? On second thought,
never mind, I don't want to know.
- What we got?
- A biggie.
Blackgate prisoner escaped
while in transit for psychiatric care.
Name's Ian Hargrove. Clinically insane,
with a compulsion for blowing things up.
Exploded a bunch of old buildings around
Gotham. Last one, two janitors were killed.
Says here
he was busted out by four gunmen.
Yeah, which is odd.
Hargrove never used accomplices.
All right. Who did he spend time with at
Blackgate? Who did he communicate with?
His entire stretch
he was isolated from gen pop.
Never made or received calls.
Only one visitor in two years,
his brother, John.
- Got an address?
- We do.
Unis are bringing him now for questioning.
We're lucky you deigned to show up.
- Yeah, sorry.
- No problem.
Girl trouble?
Yeah.
I told you, those high-society dames
get you all twisted.
Get your guard up. I'll knock lumps
out of you. Watch your feet.
Right. Jab, jab, right.
Jab, jab, right.
Keep that guard up.
Yes.
- Oy!
- Sorry, Alfred.
- Hello.
- Bruce.
- That hurt.
- Yeah, it was supposed to.
Taking a punch is just as important
as throwing one, Master Bruce.
- What you doing?
- Alfred's teaching me to fight.
- Why?
- I'll be prepared if something bad happens.
Yeah, because you live
in a pretty rough neighborhood.
Not here. In Gotham.
In Gotham,
people don't fight with gloves.
How's your room? Good?
It'll do. I'm hungry, though.
Right. Well, breakfast was served at 8,
which you slept through.
- Lunch will be served at 12.
- There's plenty in the kitchen.
Alfred would be happy to fix--
No, he won't be, will he?
He's not a bloody hotel.
Relax, old man. I'll figure it out.
You can mind your manners as well,
you cheeky little minx.
Be nice to her, Alfred. She's our guest.
I'm terribly sorry, Master Bruce.
Didn't realize you fancied her.
What do you mean? No.
It's nothing to be embarrassed about.
It's only natural, isn't it? But you watch her.
She's a lairy one.
All right. Left, left, right.
Keep your guard up, son.
You know about girls, do you, Alfred?
A sight more than you.
And she, mate, is trouble.
Oy. Oy, oy!
PENGUIN:
Liza, Liza. What are you up to?
[SNIFFS]
[SNIFFING]
Mm.
Lilacs.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
I don't know anything about his escape.
I haven't talked to him.
Your baby brother busts out of prison
and doesn't call you?
The only person he's talked to in two years.
What happened?
- You two have a falling-out?
- No.
Ian and I are close. Always have been.
Even after he bombed those janitors?
That was an accident.
BULLOCK: That's what they all say.
JOHN:  It's the truth.
[DINGS]
My brother's not a killer. He never was.
He blew up 12 buildings in Gotham.
Yes. Munitions factories and their offices.
Places that made guns
and bullets and missiles.
I know he was wrong. But Ian thought
that what he was doing was good.
He didn't hurt a soul
until the last bombing.
He felt terrible about it.
Practically handed himself in to the cops.
And pleaded guilty. Ian has had
mental problems since he was a kid.
My parents didn't have money to get him
help. He sure wasn't getting it at Blackgate.
Look, my brother's not a bad man.
Then what is he?
He's sick.
There's a difference.
GORDON:
Okay. So who would want to bust him out?
I don't know.
But my brother needs help.
You have to find him.
[DOOR OPENS]
It's done.
I have a delivery for you.
I'll take that.
- Whoa. Who sent this, anyway?
- Who cares?
Mm.
[TIMER TICKING]
Wait a second. You hear that?
Sounds like ticking.
[TIMER DINGS]
[EXPLOSION & MEN YELLING]
[DOOR OPENS]
- Good morning.
- Uh-huh.
- How'd you sleep?
- Your house makes noise.
It's old.
You didn't come here with much. If you
want, Alfred can buy you some clothes.
Pass.
Detective Gordon told me
you live on the streets.
Yeah. So?
- What's it like?
- Not as nice as here.
- Do you live alone?
- You gonna ask me questions all morning?
- Aren't you supposed to be in school?
- I'm developing my own curriculum.
It lets me move at my own speed
and focus on areas that interest me.
- Why? You're a billionaire. What's to learn?
- That's a strange attitude.
So where are your parents?
They alive?
Um...
Sure. They're around.
- Where?
- What's that to you?
- Nothing. I just thought--
- Well, you thought wrong.
I'm not an orphan. I got family all over.
This was bad enough
when it was a prison escape.
Now we got five dead security guards,
and the press is calling Hargrove a terrorist.
Get anything from the bombing site?
BULLOCK: Forensics is looking into it,
but the entire office was destroyed.
- Including all security footage.
- Yeah.
We do know that Hargrove and his guys
made off with a compound called HMX.
It's military grade.
Ten times more powerful than C4.
- Nasty stuff.
- Using explosives...
...to steal explosives. What's that about?
- Trading up?
- Must be another target that's hard to crack.
- You know what I'm gonna say.
So go. Do it.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
This is Gordon.
ALFRED [OVER PHONE]:
Yes, detective. It's Alfred.
Alfred. ls everything all right?
Selina okay?
Well, she's safe.
- But?
- But I'm afraid this isn't going to work out.
She's a tough nut, this one.
Well, look, we need her help if we have
any chance at catching the Waynes' killer.
Hold on to her for now.
I'll be out to check on her as soon as I can.
We shall patiently await your arrival...
...detective.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- Everything good?
- Right as rain.
- Sure you want to go through with this?
- Butch, don't go getting scared on me now.
Never, boss.
[DOOR OPENS]
- Oswald, you're back.
- Ha, ha.
I'm starting to think you enjoy being hurt.
[LAUGHS]
I was passing by. Thought I'd say hello.
Well, you've said it.
Now, why are you here?
Honestly, I'm just trying to be friendly.
[PENGUIN SNIFFS]
Mm.
Lilacs. Mm.
You smell good.
You don't.
[LAUGHING]
Snappy as ever. Oh. Ha, ha.
Well, goodbye, then.
Sorry you're still grumpy with me.
But you know,
reaching out in friendship is never wrong.
Man, that dude's creepy.
Forget him. He's nothing.
Hargrove's contacts and phone records
from before Blackgate.
Oh.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Barbara left.
- "Left" left?
- Yeah.
- Where'd she go?
- I don't know.
It's a ploy. She wants you to set a date.
It's a standard move. She'll be back.
- Do you play video games?
- Ed.
Don't ever do that again.
My apologies.
Do either of you play video games?
I do. I-- Ha, ha. I love video games.
Each one presents a new challenge.
A puzzle. A lot like detective work.
- Ed.
- Oh. Sorry. I had a chance to analyze...
...the shrapnel from the securities office.
I found something.
It's a name plate. It was damaged,
but you can still read the information.
It's from an abandoned metal factory
here in Gotham.
That's really good work, Ed. Thanks.
- Thank you, detective.
- Let's go check this out.
GORDON:
G.C.P.D. Freeze!
Don't shoot.
- You found the name plate. Thank God.
BULLOCK: ls anyone else here?
No, but they'll be back soon.
Please help me.
They broke me out. They kidnapped me.
Said they'd kill my brother if I didn't help.
- Who's they?
- Russians. One of their names is Kasyanov.
- Planning something against Falcone.
- Falcone?
Yeah, it's a big job. A vault. That's why
they needed me to build explosives.
What's this?
Behind you. Get down! Get down!
[GUNFIRE]
KASYANOV:
Keep them pinned down!
- Get out of here.
- Help me!
Move, move.
Come on.
If you want to go somewhere,
we can call you a taxi.
- You move quiet.
- So do you.
Are you leaving?
Thinking about it.
I'm sorry if talking about your family
upset you.
I wasn't upset.
You seemed kind of upset.
That's your mom, huh?
She looks nice.
She was.
You saw her.
The night she was killed.
Uh-huh.
And you saw me?
What I did. What I didn't do.
What are you talking about?
What could you have done?
I don't know. Something.
You're dreaming, kid.
A gun's a gun.
My mom's in show business.
Oh?
Yeah. She sings and dances
and does magic tricks.
Gets paid like millions.
But that's just a cover. Really,
she's a secret agent for the government.
Wow.
Yeah. She's on a secret mission.
But when she's done,
she's coming back to get me.
That's good.
Yeah.
Did you ever kiss a girl?
No.
Do you want to?
Why do you ask?
Just curious.
Time for your studies, Master Bruce.
BRUCE:
Thank you, Alfred.
You're more than welcome to join,
Ms. Kyle.
Right.
I'll see you later.
Do you have any idea how many angry
phone calls we've been getting this week?
- Got a terrorist out there.
- That's our fault?
Jim.
No. Please.
You tell me, detective.
How is this my fault?
For starters, you have the mentally ill
housed at Blackgate.
A prison with no facilities for them.
You send them out for treatment.
Which was exactly where Hargrove was
headed when he was broken out.
- I want him found.
- Yes, sir.
- Today.
What is wrong with you?
Hargrove's brother, John? I put him
and his family in protective custody.
That'll help.
Only problem is,
Hargrove doesn't know that.
All right, Dent. You drag me down here.
Now what?
I got the last piece of the puzzle in place.
I'm bringing charges against you.
Oh, that old song again.
You will never prove fraud.
You know that, and I know that.
Fraud charges are only part of it.
Oh, really? What, then, jaywalking?
Conspiracy to commit
first-degree murder.
Murder? So tell me, Dent. Who did I kill?
Thomas and Martha Wayne.
Oh, my God.
I have an eyewitness who can tie you to
the crime. You and all the others involved.
It's absurd.
DENT:
Help yourself out here, Dick.
Think about your options.
This is going to get ugly.
[SCOFFS]
You're a fool.
And you have no idea who or what
you're even dealing with.
Don't threaten me! I will rip you open.
It's good to see you, Dick.
- Jim. Got it.
- Yeah.
Meet Gregory Kasyanov. Long rap sheet.
Worked for Nikolai before he died.
GORDON: Who's he work for now?
BULLOCK: Beats me.
All right. Hargrove said it was a big job,
a vault. Somebody's gotta be bankrolling it.
Someone with cash and pull
and beef with Falcone.
Problem is, in Gotham, anyone with
cash and pull has beef with Falcone.
GORDON:
Hmm. So who is it?
You kept me waiting.
Ran into a little trouble.
Nothing to worry about.
Good. I've got a lot riding on this job.
You've said.
FISH: Your boss, Nikolai,
is dead because of Falcone.
You want to get back at him,
you hit him where it hurts, his money.
- Ain't that right, Butch?
BUTCH: Yup.
The root of all evil.
We'll take his money. No problem.
As long as it's there, like you said.
Oh, it's there. I'm positive.
The truck you needed.
And Gregor?
Break a leg.
[HEART BEATING]
You're the weirdest kid I've ever met.
- Why are you doing that?
- Training.
SELINA:
Oh.
Like the boxing.
So if anyone mugs you with a diving board,
you'll be ready? Huh?
Yes. I mean no.
- I'm developing self-discipline and willpower.
- Why?
So I can be strong.
I get you. But it won't work.
- Not on the streets. Not in Gotham.
- Why's that?
Out there on the streets,
it's not enough to be strong.
You gotta be mean.
You gotta be ruthless.
Know what ruthless means?
- Of course I do.
- Yeah?
Well, you ain't. You're a nice kid.
Five minutes on the street,
you'll be mincemeat.
And holding your breath
won't do a damn thing.
MAN [ON RADIO]: The subject
for today's category is numbers. Here we go.
How many bones in the human arm?
Thirty-two.
BOY [ON RADIO]: Thirty-two.
MAN: Correct.
Next, how many
elements in the periodic table?
One hundred eighteen.
BOY: Uh, 118.
MAN: Yes, again.
Now for a tough one.
How many eyes are there on cards in a deck?
Forty-two.
BOY:
Twenty-one.
[BUZZER BUZZES ON RADIO]
MAN: No, sorry.
The number you were looking for is 42.
You forgot to double it for two eyes.
Whoo! Ha, ha.
MAN: That concludes our show for today.
We'd like to thank all our contestants...
...and those of you playing along at home.
We'll be right back after this.
Okay, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What about the explosives?
NYGMA:
It's a very specific type.
It's highly volatile,
and it's very difficult to manufacture.
It's for one use, and one use only.
- To penetrate iron.
- Like a vault in a bank.
Mm-mm. No, they're steel.
No one makes anything out of iron anymore.
Not for a hundred years.
The Gotham Armory.
Yeah. They have those iron vaults
they used to keep the gunpowder in.
A few years ago,
a private investment group bought it.
Ten to one Falcone's behind it.
Mm-hm. Do you--?
How much longer?
It's ready.
It didn't work.
[MAN LAUGHS]
Hey, hey. Promise me
nobody else is going to get hurt.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Sure.
No problem. Cross my heart.
BULLOCK:
You're surrounded.
[SIRENS WAILING]
BULLOCK:
There's no way out.
Drop your weapons!
KASYANOV:
Don't do it. Get back.
Hargrove!
Ian Hargrove,
your brother and his family are safe.
We have them in protective custody.
KASYANOV: If he runs, shoot him.
- Don't shoot!
MAN: You shoot him, they shoot us.
- Drop your weapons.
["THE FINAL COUNTDOWN"
PLAYING ON CELL PHONE]
Get away from the truck!
Everybody down!
[ALL YELL]
Mm.
- Why'd you do that?
- Bet you can't hit me.
I could. Why would I want to?
- Try.
- What for?
Hit me, and...
...hmm, I'll let you kiss me.
Ha!
- You didn't get me.
- Oh, no.
- Oh!
- Ha-ha-ha.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
BRUCE:
Stop it! No, hey--!
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
GORDON [OVER PHONE]: Morning, Alfred.
- Detective.
I've been trying to get out there.
Sorry. Everything okay?
- Is she behaving herself?
- Well, not really, no.
- It's all right.
- It is?
Yes, well,
she's a breath of fresh air, I might say.
Glad to hear it.
I'll be out there as soon as I can.
Very good, sir.
[GASPS]
Oh.
Forgive me for the intrusion,
but it's urgent I speak with you.
You know who I am.
Yeah.
Falcone would kill you
if he knew you were here.
Perhaps.
But what would he do if I told him
you were spying on him for Fish Mooney?
You don't have any proof.
No.
But suspicion, it's a funny thing. Heh.
Falcone might not choose to believe me
at first, but every time he looked at you...
...he'd ask himself, "Is she?
Could she? Would she?"
You're wrong. He cares about me.
Let's call him and find out, shall we?
Stop!
Your secret is safe with me.
I won't tell...
...because you are going
to keep working for Fish.
And you are not gonna tell anyone,
or you'll die.
[CHUCKLES]
GORDON:
Messages for Gordon? Thanks.
- Jim, you have a minute?
- Uh, yeah.
- I met with Lovecraft.
- How'd it go?
He was scared. He's involved, all right.
- Scared isn't proof.
- You didn't see him.
Told the same story in a few other spots.
All the players know. Someone will talk.
If and when they do, no one makes a move
without talking first. Move together on this.
Absolutely.
Nice work on the Hargrove case.
You saved his life. You're a regular saint.
- Thanks. We'll talk again soon, I hope?
- You bet.
Thanks, counselor.
- Finish up with Hargrove?
- Yeah.
- He's on his way to Arkham.
- Arkham?
Mayor's directive. He's taking
all the criminally insane inmates...
...and sending them to Arkham
for appropriate treatment.
That's nuts. The building's 200 years old.
Welcome to Gotham.
Oh. Hargrove said the bomb
that blew up the money wasn't his.
- Whose was it?
- He didn't know.
How did it go?
Cops were everywhere.
My guys had no way out.
- Had to make the call.
- Is everybody dead? Gregor? All his men?
Every last one.
Good. I can't stand loose strings.
You're not mad?
That's a hell of a lot of money we lost.
Mad? I couldn't be happier.
The point wasn't to steal that money.
It was to hurt Falcone.
Well, that you did, Fish. That you did.
Good afternoon.
Thank you all for coming.
As you know, the people of Gotham have
been shaken by tragedy in recent days.
Tragedy no citizen should have to endure.
What has happened these past few days
is a result of Gotham's criminally insane...
...not getting the appropriate treatment
and help that we owe them.
That is why I am moving forward with plans
to turn the renovated Arkham Asylum...
...into a remedial facility
for the criminally insane.
Barbara, it's me.
I got your letter, and I, um...
...know you said you needed
some time away from Gotham.
From me.
But I want you to come back.
I need you to come back.
I don't have anything without you.
And I love you.