GORDON:
Previously on Gotham...
My name is Nathaniel Barnes.
I'm your new boss.
Sid Bunderslaw.
I'm the director
of physical operations.
I've been expecting you.
BARNES: Garrett, Pinkney,
Josie, Martinez,
congratulations.
You are now Unit Alpha
of the GCPD Strike Force.
Time to take down the Penguin.
OSWALD: Mother...
You'll pay for this!
THEO: They die,
your mother lives.
I'm gonna need you
to take a crack
at me also--
and miss, of course.
Get down!
(crowd screaming)
If the bad guys want
to stop me running,
well, then I guess
I got no choice.
I will run for mayor.
(thunder rumbling,
sirens wailing, horns honking)
Thank you for the trunk,
old friend.
I'll call you when I need you.
I'm glad you call me a friend.
(scoffs)
Figure of speech.
But do go on.
I can't help feeling...
wouldn't I be so much more
useful to you as a friend?
As a colleague, an ally?
As opposed to the tool
you are at present.
Good question.
No.
I would be a much more
effective tool for you
if I wasn't so worried
about my mother.
If you let her come home,
I would still do your bidding.
Trust me, I know who's boss now.
(chuckles)
Lord have mercy.
No need to rub it in.
(snaps fingers)
Yes, sir, we all
know who's boss.
What do you think, Tabitha?
I wasn't listening.
You know how
I love the big macho type.
THEO:
Leave him alone.
Yeah, leave me alone.
Shh!
The answer is no,
old friend.
Off you go.
(grunts)
THEO:
Stay by the phone.
(sighs, shudders)
I wish you wouldn't
freak out the help.
I've got a mayoral campaign
to run.
I need to know your gonna handle
this part of the business.
I get bored.
I hate it when you say that.
You have plenty to do.
You still have
Mayor James to play with.
He's been here
nearly a month.
He's getting old fast.
You got Barbara
to hang out with.
Yeah, she's cool,
but she sleeps a lot.
And she's kind of crazy.
THEO: That's the
best part about her.
Galavan?
What the hell is going on?
Mr. Bunderslaw, welcome.
What... what do you
want with me?
You are the garbage man
for Wayne Enterprises,
correct?
Every nasty little thing
the company has done,
you know all about it.
No.
Yes, and you are gonna tell us
everything that you know.
And if I refuse?
(thunder rumbling)
Torture.
But that's for later.
Right now, there is something
of yours we need to borrow.
Sister, if you don't mind.
Left or right?
THEO:
Either one.
No...
(Bunderslaw screaming)
(squishing)
MAN: 25 and 25 boxes.
(snoring)
Hm?
(grumbling)
God...!
Anybody who doesn't want
to get shot,
raise your hand!
Whoa!
Get down!
(shouting)
A damn rocket launcher?
Welcome to Gotham, Cap.
I can fit my yearly salary
in my hands.
BARNES:
Don't get any ideas
about that cash, son.
Just bag it up.
Don't worry, sir.
Ideas aren't his strong suit.
Did some
rough calculations, sir.
Somewhere around
two million dollars here.
It's a strong body blow
to Penguin.
He'll feel it.
Sir?
They're asking for their pants.
Read 'em their rights.
Doesn't say squat about pants.
Wait.
Tell 'em the whoever gives up
where they got
the damn rocket launcher
gets to wear pants.
The rest can go naked,
for all I care.
GORDON:
Captain.
A word?
There's a place
called the Merc.
Sells most of the
heavy weapons in town.
They haven't been hit,
'cause they pay off
half the city council.
The Merc, uh?
The city council
can suck my tailpipe.
We're gonna hit
this Merc tomorrow.
Pinkney, belay that order.
No one gets pants.
We grab him up.
We grab him, and we hurt him
until he tells us where she is,
and then we hurt him more.
Okay, is that a good idea?
Do you have a better one?
We could get the sister.
And then what?
He's still out there,
and does he love his sister
as much as I love my mother?
I don't think so!
GILZEAN:
Hmm, it is a pickle.
Mr. Penguin, sir,
the cops just hit
the count house.
They took everything,
every dollar.
Ooh!
(gasping, grunting)
Did you enjoy giving me
that news?!
(grunting)
Ah!
Butch!
(wheezing)
I have an idea.
Hey, you.
Good morning.
How's your day look?
The strike force is going out
on another raid.
Strike force.
I hate that name.
Yeah, I'm not wild
about it myself,
but Barnes gets things done.
He can call us
what he likes.
All right, so you go
strike with your force,
then what are we doing tonight?
Sleep.
Uh-uh, it's date night, mister.
With who?
Morning, Ed.
Detective, Ms. Tompkins.
As you may have heard,
I've recently been seeing
Miss Kringle.
Kristen.
And she mentioned
that it might be nice to go out
with other people along,
so I thought, perhaps,
the two of you would enjoy
joining us
for dinner tonight.
We can't.
We'd love to.
Sure.
Yeah, yeah, no.
Great.
As a matter of fact,
I just bought some
new fondue pots.
Why don't we do
it at my house?
Excellent, excellent.
I'll go tell Kristen.
I know, I know, but it was
the decent thing to do.
Fondue?
Have you ever tried it?
It's delicious.
It's at your place.
We can't leave.
We're already home.
Trapped.
Don't be mean.
We'll make it fun.
Yes, ma'am.
Detective Gordon?
Good morning.
I wonder if we could, uh,
talk alone?
Of course.
Thank you for, uh, giving me
some of your valuable time.
Oh, not a problem.
(sighs)
That night at the gala, I...
I just keep going through it.
Me, too.
I've never killed a man before.
Fear... blood...
I relive that moment
over and over.
Do those thoughts ever go away?
No.
But over time,
they lose their power.
You did the right thing.
I guess I did.
I'm kind of amazed at myself.
You, doing the right thing,
it's what you do
every day.
That's why people speak
so highly of you.
You're a symbol
to the people of this city--
of hope, of honor.
That's why I'm here.
I would be honored...
if you would consider...
endorsing me for mayor.
Ah, endorsement.
I'm flattered, but, uh,
I'm afraid policemen
and politics don't mix.
Maybe not for the cop
on the street,
but you're the president
of the Policeman's Union.
Where you lead,
officers will follow.
That's more power
than the kind
that comes out of a gun.
(quiet laugh)
You seem like a good man,
but...
I'm afraid my answer
has to be no.
I don't do endorsements.
I know better than to push.
But think about it.
We could really
help each other.
Hi, Penguin.
What do you want?
Why so glum?
I just lost a lot of money.
Aww.
Poor sad little bread head.
The money is immaterial.
Someone must have betrayed me.
Someone close.
You don't know that, boss.
Oh, don't I?
Don't I?!
Whoa, chill, birdman.
I got a job for you.
What's that?
Addresses of places
you're gonna burn to the ground.
Starting tonight.
Arson now?
(chuckles)
Sure, fine.
Whatever.
If I can find
a trustworthy arsonist.
Paranoid, huh?
Get your head together,
little man, and get it done.
Oh, and whoever starts the fires
is gonna need this.
(pounding on door)
(cats meowing in distance)
(breaks bottle)
(door closes)
Nice place.
Whassup?
I need you to take me
to the Pike Brothers.
The firebugs from the Narrows?
I used to hang
with their sister, Bridgit,
when I was a kid.
Why do you need me to take you?
To vouch for me.
The Pikes are
the best arsonists in town,
but they're also Fish loyalists.
(scoffs)
The idiots think she's
coming back someday.
She might come back.
I was there, darlin'.
She might.
Whatever.
The Pikes hate me and Penguin,
for obvious reasons, but...
everyone knows
Fish loved you.
They do?
Your face will open doors, babe.
Six hundred.
Three-fifty.
(sighs)
Fine.
(sirens wailing in distance)
Just let me
do the talkin'.
You just smile
and make like we're friends.
Friends?
That's a hundred extra.
Chiseler.
So, everybody knows
she loved me?
That's what they say.
She loved me, too, once.
And I loved her.
Then you shot her.
(grunts)
It was complicated.
(scoffs) Got that right.
(knocking on door)
SELINA:
Hi, Bridgit.
Hey, Selina.
It's been a while.
Me and my pet gorilla
are here on business.
Your brothers home?
Yeah.
(rock music playing,
muffled, from distance)
Hey, boys.
What are you doing
with this rat, Selina?
He's okay.
I vouch for him.
MAN:
What do you mean, okay?
The bastard shot Fish.
It was complicated.
He loves her just like you do.
And if she ever comes back...
When she comes back.
When she does,
he will be right by her side.
If she comes back?
Sure.
(chuckles): But she...
But right now,
he got a nice job
for you guys.
Business is business, right?
GILZEAN:
Hey, bygones, huh?
We need the best,
and you guys are the best.
(guns clicking)
Whoa.
Easy.
(whistles)
That's a lot of work.
GILZEAN:
A lot of pay.
You up for it?
For sure.
We'll need more gear.
I'll hit the Merc and stock up.
MAN 2: We've got enough gear
to burn down Gotham twice.
There's always room
for more napalm.
Thanks.
(groans)
Hey, sis...
what are you, a slob?
We have company.
What do we do
when we have company?
We get them a glass.
Ding, ding, ding.
Go and do it.
Thank you, Bridgit.
(door opens, closes)
(scoffs)
You're gonna need this.
(crying softly)
Hey.
Looks like rain.
Yeah, it does.
I don't mind it.
Cleans the streets anyhow.
That's true.
(thunder rumbling)
Anyway, um,
take care of yourself, Bridgit.
Be strong.
WOMAN (over P.A.):
Yeah, can we get a price check
on brass knuckles
in toxic green?
300 gets it done.
Uh, 10% surcharge
for soiled bills.
Thank you kindly.
WOMAN (over P.A.):
Try our Whiff-Away.
On sale now in Aisle Seven.
Welcome to Merc,
your one-stop shop
for machetes,
night-vision goggles,
and all of your personal
defense needs.
Huh.
Robbery.
WOMAN (over P.A.):
...mouthpiece and muzzle guard.
GORDON:
GCPD!
BARNES:
Everybody on the ground!
This is a raid!
Runner!
I got him!
Stop!
Stop right now!
(gunshots)
What the hell are you packing?
NYGMA: When cheese melts,
the protein matrix relaxes
and the fats flow
more like liquid.
It creates this
low-friction mouth feel,
which is why melted
cheese is so...
Ed.
Uh, it's delicious.
Mm-hmm. Yes, it is.
Oh... ha...
(laughter)
Oh, no! (giggles)
Oh, Lee, we shouldn't be eating
without Jim here.
I'm so sorry.
No, no, no, please, eat.
It's fine.
Oh.
There he is.
Hello, there.
Hey, Jim.
Nice to see you.
Sorry I'm late.
(sighs)
really sorry.
Long story.
I hope it hasn't
been going too bad.
You know,
it's the weirdest thing,
but Nygma's actually maintaining
this strange sort of cool.
No.
Seriously.
(laughter)
There's a lid for every pot.
Pardon me.
Since Detective Gordon is here,
I'd like to propose a toast.
Mmm!
The less you have,
the more they're worth.
To friends.
Oh.
Hear, hear.
I can't believe he's dead.
Biggest job of our lives,
and this happens.
So what do we do?
For sure, we do the job.
How? We're screwed.
Who's our entry man now?
Crawling through air vents?
Climbing fire escapes?
We need a little skinny guy.
You think?
Hey, Bridgy...
you just got a promotion.
No.
Yes.
Please, you know
I don't like fire.
You don't like fire?
Fire is our bread and butter.
It's our family business.
You're don't want to let down
your family, do you?
You're not my family.
What's that?
We're not your family?
You got anybody else?
My mother...
Your mother was a ho,
and she's dead.
Who feeds you?
Who puts a roof above your head?
Huh? We do.
That's family.
I won't do it.
Oh.
Fine, be like that.
But if you're not family,
well, that changes things
around here, though.
See, I'm a decent guy.
I would never put family
on the street.
But if you're not family...
hell...
why not make a buck?
Yo, that's a kick-ass idea.
So what are you gonna do? Hm?
Do you want to be turned out?
Or do you want
to be family?
Which?
Family.
He wanted me
to endorse him for mayor.
Wow.
What did you say?
I said no.
You don't like him?
I do, actually.
But I know better
than to let that matter.
Endorsing politicians--
that's not me.
Still, he asked you.
That's very flattering.
You're a respected figure
in this town.
(sighs)
The way people look at you,
see you differently,
you treat it like it's a burden.
It could be a source of pride,
or happiness even,
if you let it.
Thank you, Doctor.
Same time next week?
(laughs gently):
Oh...
Don't tempt me.
I could psychoanalyze
the heck out of you.
But I'm gonna resist the urge.
Gee, thanks.
(siren wails in distance,
horns honk)
BRIDGIT:
Be strong, Bridgit.
Okay.
It's on.
JOE: Now...
you're gonna want
to cut yourself
about a foot and
a half of fuse.
Okay.
Push the wick
into the plastic explosive.
Okay.
Now get out the flame.
You got about a minute and
a half to get out of there
once that fuse is lit.
Spark it up.
(gasps)
It's lit.
Okay, great.
Sorry, there's one more
thing to do.
But it's lit!
Well, you'd
better haul ass.
Do you see a safe on your right?
Yeah.
Get to it.
Okay.
Okay, now grab the box
at the bottom of the bag
and open it up.
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Grody, right?
Okay, put it to the sensor
next to the door.
MALE VOICE:
Welcome, Mr. Bunderslaw.
Okay.
It's open.
Now what?
Joe?
Joe, where are you?
(snickers)
Joe, what's wrong?
I'm just messing
with you.
Okay, so there should be
an old knife there. Grab it.
Okay.
Got it.
Okay, now...
scram.
(screams)
(fire alarm ringing)
JOE: Attagirl.
(siren wails in the distance)
You did good, sis.
Get in the van,
chop chop.
I burned my leg.
Well, "you play with fire,
you get burned," all of that.
We got four more
of these to do tonight,
so get in the damn van.
(sirens approaching,
horn honking)
Five locations,
all burned to the ground.
Yeah, Garrett?
Excuse me, sir.
Lab called in, said
the fires were started
with thermite and
high-end accelerants.
So we're looking for
professional arsonists.
Thanks.
And, Garrett,
nice work yesterday.
Thank you, sir.
Strange.
Why would a pro do
five jobs in one night?
What's the rush?
And what if they're not done?
Find a pattern to these fires.
Before they burn down
the whole city.
♪ ♪
What are you doing?
Hi.
Making a suit,
so I won't get burned again.
Why would you
get burned again?
So they're making
you start the fires?
I guess.
Sit down.
You want a soda
or something?
No, I-I can't, I'm supposed
to take that to Penguin.
Oh.
Okay.
You know, you're gonna
get yourself killed.
(scoffs)
I'll be careful.
Well, careful ain't enough.
Look what
happened already.
It was exciting, Selina.
I actually kind of enjoyed it.
(scoffs)
Yep, you're
gonna be bacon.
My brother said
I did a good job.
It's the family business.
They're not your family.
Your mom used to
bang their old man
is all.
You don't need them.
You don't need anybody.
Look at me-- I'm free.
(scoffs)
I remember when I was little and
you showed up at the Narrows.
You looked for
your mom every day.
Snot all down
your face from crying.
So don't act like
you don't want a family.
Don't talk about my mom.
Who cares if you're free?
What good's freedom
if you're alone?
What good's family
if you're a slave?
Huh?
Whatever.
I don't even know
why you think I care.
(door closes)
Doesn't make any sense.
This is the Wayne
family crest.
So what?
Why does Galavan want
an antique knife
that belonged to the Waynes?
There's something here,
something to understanding
Galavan, to beating him.
Well, if you want to know about
old-time Gotham, talk to Edwige.
Edwige?
Yeah.
She runs the antique shop
in my old neighborhood.
Trust me.
She knows things.
OSWALD: You can pick
it up if you like.
That's okay.
Sorry.
I can't help you.
Edwige, I can see
that you know this knife.
You're scared
of this knife.
Why?
Why are you lying to me?
I'm not.
Madam, if there's one thing
I know, it's a liar.
Now, tell me
about this knife,
or I will use it.
(clears throat)
This knife has a cursed history.
Almost 200 years ago,
it was used in a terrible crime.
Back then...
five families ruled
Gotham high society.
The Elliots, the Kanes,
the Crownes, the Dumas...
and the most powerful
of them all-- the Waynes.
They called Celestine Wayne
the crown jewel of Gotham.
A real beauty.
She was promised
to the eldest son
of the Elliot family.
But there was another
who coveted her.
Caleb Dumas.
One night...
it was during an Easter party
at the Wayne Manor...
Celestine and Caleb
went missing.
Wayne men found them together
in an illicit embrace.
(Caleb and Celestine
shout in protest)
We're in love!
Caleb insisted that
they were in love and...
Celestine swore
on her mother's grave
that Caleb had forced
himself on her.
I'm innocent. Celestine!
I'm telling the truth!
Justice, if that's
what it was, was swift.
Celestine!
Celestine's brother Jonathan
Wayne delivered the punishment.
(screaming)
The Waynes...
they were mad with rage.
They seized the Dumas' holdings
and banished them socially,
destroyed them.
Caleb Dumas
went into exile overseas,
to a penitential religious sect
founded by his family's
patron saint.
Celestine died an old maid.
The Waynes forbade the press
from even mentioning the Dumas.
They renamed streets
and buildings.
The remnants
of the Dumas family
were forced to change
their name.
The Waynes wiped the Dumas
out of our city's history.
Those remnants
of the Dumas family...
to what did they change
their name?
Aren't you quick?
Galavan.
They changed their name
to Galavan.
Just like that fella
runnin' for mayor.
And that's why I'm scared
of this knife.
You're in deep waters,
Mr. Penguin.
Thank you, Edwige.
That is where penguins thrive.
You hear anything
about any fires,
you come see me,
earn yourself
a "get out of jail free"
card, all right?
You got a look
on your face.
It's well hidden behind
a bunch of corporate aliases,
but all the buildings that
burned down last night,
they have one landlord:
Wayne Enterprises.
Uh-huh.
The arsonists moved
east to west.
If they come out tonight
and stick to pattern,
there's one
obvious target,
an old building also owned
by Wayne Enterprises--
Gotham City Book Depository.
Yay.
Stakeout.
I'll buy the doughnuts.
Just no chili dogs
this time, huh?
I'll let Barnes
know the plan.
(door creaks shut)
(thunder rumbling)
Sent the knife to Galavan.
Your favorite, isn't it?
Crosswhite, 20 year.
(chuckles)
That's the stuff,
all right.
Have a taste.
Nah, I'm-I'm good right now.
But thanks.
Have a drink, Butch.
(chuckles)
Your conditioning is still
working nicely, hmm?
(snickers)
(mocking tone):
You can't refuse me.
(snickers)
You're the only man
I can truly trust right now.
Starting to sound
a little paranoid, boss.
(laughs)
Am I?
Am I going mad?
Mm, how could I not
when that fiend has
my mother in his clutches?
Have another drink, Butch.
Maybe I am going mad.
Or maybe I found
Galavan's weakness.
You did?
The knife, Butch.
The knife that
maimed his ancestor.
This is a blood
feud for Galavan.
He wants revenge
against the Waynes.
He's acting out of emotion.
And that can be manipulated.
Have another drink.
You are going to go to Galavan
and you're going
to tell him I went nuts
and that I accused you of
setting up the count shop raid.
You are in fear for your life,
and you need a job, got that?
Yes, boss.
Once you're inside
his organization,
you will find my mother
and rescue her.
Yes, boss.
But...
Galavan's a smart guy,
and that's a basic play.
No way is he gonna buy
I turned traitor.
No.
But he will buy that I think
you turned traitor.
He'll buy it...
if we sell it right.
Drink up.
How do we sell it?
I already sold him my paranoia.
But you're the closer.
How do we sell you?
How do we make him trust
and feel for you?
I wasn't sure.
(chuckles)
But then Celestine
and Caleb told me how.
How?
(screams)
It's the onions that
bring it together.
The sweetness and the
acid, am I right?
I hate stakeouts.
Mmm, half of good police
work is the ability
to sit on one's ass
when it's called for.
If that were true,
you'd be commissioner.
(laughing):
Har-dee, har-har.
Heads up.
All units stand by.
We may have something.
MAN:
Roger.
So it's all old books in
there, so this one's easy.
Just spread the napalm
around, spark that thing up
and go to town.
Zero sweat.
This thing scares me.
Yeah, it's a flamethrower,
it's meant to be scary.
Get suited up and
get this done.
We got three more
spots to hit.
All units converge
on our location. Now.
OFFICER:
Moving in.
GCPD!
Run!
Go, go, go!
Gray van leaving the alley.
Get back!
Please!
Drop it!
Put down the weapon!
(flamethrower clicks)
Drop the weapon!
I got her!
Drop it.
No!
Garrett, no!
Let me go!
Let go of it!
No!
Let go of me!
(screaming)
Garrett!
I got him, I got him.
(screaming)
I need an ambulance!
Officer down!
Bridgit! Bridgit!
Come on, hurry!
Quick, follow me!
Where are we going?
Home.
(sirens approaching)
Thanks.
Any news?
Not yet.
But he's a tough kid,
I bet you he makes it.
Your buddy's here.
Can't stop pressing
the flesh.
Real publicity hound.
There's no cameras here.
BARNES:
Your attention, please.
GORDON:
Captain?
Luke Garrett...
passed away at 5:23 a.m.
Damn it.
MARTINEZ:
It ain't right.
(voice breaking):
Burned to death in an alley
by some weirdo.
He was gonna be
a great cop.
He was a great cop.
And we will mourn him.
But not now.
There is a cop killer
on the loose.
I cannot abide that.
We will find the person
who killed our brother, and
we will put a stop to them
using every legal method
at our disposal.
Excuse me.
Your fellow officer is dead,
I can see it in your face.
He is.
I'm sorry to hear it.
The bad guys in this
town are changing.
They're not playing
by the old rules.
Or any rules.
We need every method
at our disposal.
And I'm not just talking
about more guns.
You need to go
where you need to go,
press who you need the press and
have the city back your play.
Correct.
I don't know how bad
it's gonna get.
But if you can
give me your word...
we won't have
to face it alone...
...you'll have my endorsement.
I promise you, you'll have
whatever you need.
(siren wailing in distance)
♪ ♪
Father Creel.
Theo.
It's been a long time.
(sighs deeply)
You look well.
As do you.
You've surrounded
yourself with luxury.
Well, I have to play
the part, Father, and...
as you'll see...
...it's paying off.
Still sharp
after all these years.
You have the Wayne boy?
Not yet.
There are some practical matters
that have to be resolved first.
A few pieces to arrange on
the board before the checkmate.
But soon.
After almost 200 years,
we can be patient.
The day of redemption
is at hand.
Our brothers are crossing
the ocean even now.
Warriors like this
city has never known.
Gotham will be
redeemed in blood.
And Bruce Wayne will die.