There's a war coming...
a terrible war.
There will be chaos.
Rivers of blood
In the streets.
I know it.
I can see it coming.
It's time.
Somebody has to take over.
It might as well be me.
My name's james gordon.
I'm a detective.
My name is bruce wayne.
I promise i will
Find the man who did this.
Stop or i'll shoot!
He was framed... to cover up
For the real killer.
I know that you own
the police department.
Probably the mayor.
You can't have organized crime
without law and order.
You snitched,
My little penguin.
Please!
Falcone wants you to put
a bullet in his head.
Then everybody knows
you're with the program.
Don't ever come back
to gotham.
Ah, there you are.
Been all over
the bloody house
Looking for you.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
You, my old son,
are a terrible liar.
What have you got there?
Come on. Show me.
Oh, my god,
you stupid little boy!
Oh.
It's all right. I'm sorry.
It's gonna be all right.
Hi! I'm patti.
This is doug.
We're with
the mayor's
Homeless outreach project.
We have some sandwiches
and some soup.
We got cookies,
got candy.
Who here likes chocolate?
Ain't you hungry, cat?
Yeah, dig in.
Take a sandwich.
This is what i need.
Sure, go ahead.
Plenty for everyone.
Yeah, sure. Take two.
Hey!
Hey, lady.
Oh, fudge!
Don't worry. I'll go.
Slow down there,
buckaroo.
I got you one,
but i dropped it.
Yeah, thanks.
Where is everybody?
I don't know.
What do you think?
I think it's been a long shift.
We give this bum three hours,
Then we knock off.
He was a vet.
I salute his service.
Now he's a dead bum.
People are shooting bums
All the time. We might as well
be looking for the tooth fairy.
Hey, guys.
Hey, bo.
How come you weren't here?
Whoa, whoa.
Good morning to you, too.
Where were you?
I was at a restaurant
down the street here,
Chez vous. They had
some homeless junkie kid,
Fell through their
front window last night.
I been taking care of that.
This is a potential murder.
You're first responder.
You're supposed to preserve the
integrity of the crime scene.
He's got a point.
Well,
The restaurant that pays me $50
a month to look out for them.
So i'm gonna babysit
a dead wino? I got a family.
He's got a point.
Why'd the kid
jump through the window?
Who knows? He was high.
Did you ask him?
Why am i the bad guy here?
I'm asking about the
kid because maybe he's
related to the victim.
And you're not a bad guy...
you're just a bad cop.
Whoa. Who you talking to?
You know, i already had...
Hold on.
Come on. Come on!
You want it? Any day!
Hey! Whoa!
And then zeb and smoke
went right down,
And that's when that wacky
dude just shot soldier.
That's when i realized
i needed to get out of there.
So i ran and i ran,
and that's how
I ended up on the floor
of that restaurant.
She used a pin.
I swear.
A big pin.
But, listen, this is
not the first time.
Street kids have been
disappearing for weeks now.
By the dozen.
No one knows why.
First we heard about it.
Why-why would you?
Nobody gives a crap about us.
I mean, look! That is proof!
That's not proof. That's a scab.
Now, listen, macky,
We're grown-ups.
We're smarter than you.
Man, whatever.
So you're gonna...
You're gonna tell me the truth!
It was you, wasn't it?
It was you that killed
that poor old man.
It was you. Now, you're gonna
tell me the truth, or i swear
To god, i'm gonna beat it
out of you!
That old man was a war veteran!
Listen,
Cat was there. Cat saw
the whole thing. Ask cat.
Ask cat!
Relax, macky, relax.
No one's gonna beat you.
Who's cat?
What do you mean,
no one's gonna beat him?
Isn't that what i
just said i was gonna do
Right now, just now?
I was gonna beat him?
Come here! Come here. Come here.
He is 16.
Yeah, and six-foot, 220.
He can take a punch.
Look, i wasn't gonna beat him.
I just wanted to scare him.
But if i did want to beat him,
i could.
It would be my prerogative.
It's illegal.
Ill...
How now so righteous?
Hmm? Not long since you
put a man in the river.
You want to say that
a little louder?
Not everybody heard.
Ever since then, you've been
a royal pain in the ass.
You think i or anybody
Around here gives a crap
about a dead snitch
Or your guilty
conscience?
We got our own problems.
Guilty conscience,
Call it what you want.
I'm gonna do what's right.
You're beginning to irritate me.
Get your hands off me.
Hey!
Watch the shoes, clown.
Shift's over.
Come on.
Seriously.
Thank you so much,
guys, truly.
I'm very grateful.
I've been waiting for hours.
No kidding. Look like you
crawled out of a cemetery.
Smells like it, too.
Open a window back there.
There you go.
Yeah.
Yes, thank you.
Forgive me,
i am somewhat disheveled.
A temporary setback,
i assure you.
Thank you so much.
What the hell happened
to you anyhow?
It was my own fault.
Foolish arrogance
led me astray.
But i learned my lessons.
I'll be back,
stronger and smarter than ever.
Good luck with that, bro.
Here i am riding around
in a lovely truck,
Sharing an ice-cold beer
with my new friends.
My luck's already
turned, right?
Dude, anyone ever tell you,
when you walk,
You look just like a penguin?
No.
Nobody's ever told me that.
He's saying he has a right to
stop me from beating on a mope.
Damn right i do.
How am i supposed
to work with this?
Look it, jim, it's not
like i can order you
To break the law,
but this is gotham.
You don't bend,
you'll get broke.
I understand.
I thought
You were with the program.
He is.
Well, let's get back
to work.
Where are you at?
Well, if the boy we have
is telling the truth,
There's a couple of kidnappers
out there
Abducting homeless children
in numbers.
They lured them close
with a food truck
From the mayor's homeless
outreach project.
And they drugged them
with a jab from a big pin.
Wh-why would anyone want
to abduct
Scaggly-ass
orphans in bulk?
I mean, where's the market?
They're out on the street
Because no one
wants them anyway.
If they said
they were snatching
Cute girls, i'd believe 'em.
But what would anyone want
with a lard-ass like macky?
What is it, ed?
Guess what i found.
I did a blood test
on him, and he had
High levels of atp.
What's atp?
It's a fast-acting
knockout drug.
They used to use it
at the old arkham asylum
To bring down
troublesome patients.
It's hard to get.
No recreational use.
Okay. That's interesting.
Anything else?
Thank you, ed.
Get to work.
And keep this quiet.
No press. Not a word.
Shouldn't we tell the
public what's going on?
Warn them?
Department policy.
We don't advertise this kind
of stuff. Causes panic.
The headlines will read
"gotham's kids snatched."
Which would be true.
No press.
That's an order.
Follow up on the drug,
the atp
And the arkham connection.
Arkham's been closed
for, like, ten years.
Yeah, 15.
Drug suppliers might
still be in business.
Oh, uh,
This happened on
fish mooney's turf.
Do you want to see if it's safe
for us to go back there,
Or is, uh, she still mad at us?
That's a good question.
Bravo!
Don falcone.
What a wonderful surprise.
Welcome.
Thank you, my dear.
Can we... Talk?
Of course. Give me a moment
to clear the place.
No, no.
No need to
spoil the fun.
Men who are about to die
are very honest.
It pays to listen to them.
That's some toast.
I spoke with your man cobblepot
before he died.
Odd little fellow.
Perceptive.
He told me the death
of the waynes
Would bring troubled times
for our family and gotham.
What did he know?
Business is good as ever.
No, he was right.
The waynes and the falcones were
the pillars of the same house.
We understood each other.
Now that they're gone,
everything is out of balance,
And the wayne empire is in flux.
Who knows
who will end up in control?
The maroni family
senses weakness.
They'll start making moves,
And every criminal in the city
will start making moves.
Please don't lose any sleep
over maroni.
He's number two for a reason.
I never lose sleep
over my enemies.
It's my friends
that keep me awake.
Huh.
Cobblepot told me
You say i'm old and soft
And ready to be taken out,
and you're the one to take me.
Don falcone, i would never,
Ever say that.
I only have deep love
and respect for you.
You have been
like a father to me.
I'm so... Happy to hear that.
Let's forget all
about it, then.
The babbling of a condemned man.
Enough business.
How have you
been, my dear?
Thriving, i hope.
Yes. Good. I'm good.
Which of these is your lover?
Please. My heart has been broken
Far too many times
for that nonsense.
Hmm.
I heard you had a lover.
Well, if you're referring
To the boy that i keep around
for exercise...
My lover he is not.
What's your name?
Lazlo, sir.
Lazlo, be good
to this woman.
She's very precious to me.
If you break her heart,
You break my heart.
Yes, sir.
Mmm.
Give me your hand.
Thank you for being honest.
It means a lot to me.
It shows wisdom
And humility.
Out!
Everyone out!
Never, never in his life
My son is away this long.
Nightclubs is his business.
Such hours.
But always, he comes home
to his mother.
His clothes are here.
My son would never
Leave his clothes.
Oh, so elegant, he is.
Yes, i-i show you.
Damn. Mooney and the cops
must have had him killed.
Looks like
the snitches get bumped.
That's life.
They're not going to
get away with it,
Not as easy as they think.
You take things too personally,
you know what?
Yeah, i do. That
was a good snitch.
- What are we...?
- Nothing.
Uh, mrs. Cobblepot...
Kapelput.
Mrs. Kapelput,
do you know anyone
Who might want
to do your son harm?
Harm?
No. I-i would feel it.
A mother feels
these things.
It's a woman.
Some painted slut
has him in her clutch.
A woman... You think?
I am sure.
So handsome he is.
And so naive.
Who are you again?
Uh, detectives
with major crimes unit, ma'am.
Oh, gcpd.
Like that.
But honest.
Hmm.
Boss, don't get mad at me,
But i know that look.
Now is too early to
make a move on falcone.
I know.
Not yet.
I need more money, more men,
more territory, i know.
I'll play this thing loyal
and bide my time.
But i swear, butch,
On my sainted mother's grave,
Some day soon,
I am going to kill that old man
With my bare hands
and my teeth.
I'll be holding
your shoes.
I just wish
that penguin was still alive.
I didn't make that little punk
Suffer near badly enough.
Excuse me, sir?
Uh...
I couldn't help but notice
the sign on your trailer.
Is it still for rent?
100 bucks a week.
It ain't much, but...
I'll take it.
You don't want to
look at it first?
No, i'm not fussy.
It's all yours.
The key?
Hey, sweet truck. You got
that big hemi in there?
Yes. Yup.
That big hemi's in there.
Somewhere.
Uh, sir, the key?
It's in the door.
Okay.
What's up, players?
You got any smokes?
No.
Where are we?
Damn if i know.
I think we're dead.
Harvey.
Jim. How marvelous.
You still mad at us?
No. Please.
I'm quite fond
of you, and...
You intrigue me.
I knew i'd regret killing you
as soon as i gave the word.
But you know me.
I'm feisty.
What do you know about
A man and a woman abducting
street kids on your turf?
No foreplay with you, hmm?
Figures, but you got
with the program.
Killed penguin
your own bad self.
I was surprised.
Straight arrow like you.
I guess you misjudged me.
I guess i did.
You're just a little sinner
like the rest of us.
I'm almost
Kind of sad about that.
We're looking for a man
and a woman,
Middle-aged,
White,
Targeting children under 16.
They use a poisoned pin,
if you can believe it.
Oh. Used to be there was only a
market for nice-looking girls.
That's what i said.
But now there's a
new buyer overseas
That will take anyone
young and healthy.
Overseas where? Who's "they"?
Nobody knows.
What do they want 'em for?
And no one cares to know.
Ta-da! Moo shu.
Sorry. Go on.
They drug them
with a big pin?
That is so creepy.
No, you don't want to hear
this stuff. It's depressing.
What do they use them
for? The children?
Nobody seems to know.
And we can't say a damn thing
to the press. Bad pr.
I can't believe the
system is so corrupt.
You have no idea.
What do you mean?
No. You know,
figure of speech, i guess.
Did something happen that
you're not telling me about?
These last couple of weeks...
You've been different, troubled.
Hmm.
No.
Been having trouble sleeping,
i guess.
The newspapers must get
anonymous tips all the time.
Oh, sure, yeah.
You mean, call it in myself?
No, i can't do that.
Gotham gazette.
The newsroom.
Wait. No.
Hi. Listen,
i can't talk long.
Somebody is abducting homeless
children off the streets,
And the cops are trying
to keep it quiet.
Go talk to captain sarah essen
of the gcpd. She has got a kid
In custody who can tell you
the whole story.
End the call.
I got to go.
Listen to me, barbara.
When i tell you stuff,
that's just between us.
You can't do that,
what you just did.
But it was the right thing
to do.
That's not the point.
Well, what is the point?
You're right.
It was the right
thing to do.
Don't do it again, okay?
Yes, boss.
"gotham spirals ever downward."
"mayor james under attack."
"vows swift action."
"points finger
At police department's
sluggish response." et cetera.
It's just ink.
Did you give them this?
Me?
You've done it before.
On my own case? Never.
Be a very stupid thing to do.
Jim?
I didn't call it in.
I swear.
Another mystery.
We have a thin
lead on the case,
If you'd like to hear it, ma'am.
There's only
three companies
In gotham that stock
this atp stuff,
And you need a special
license to buy it.
Chances are, one of
the three's crooked.
We're looking to lean hard
on all three,
Like they are crooked,
See which one pops.
That was sneaky good.
Almost couldn't tell
you were lying.
I wasn't lying.
Good morning, judge baker.
Thank you, sir.
Yes, all three.
Welzyne,
Dracotech and
quillan pharma.
You guys have screwed me.
Against my better judgment,
I sell you the juice,
I let you guys
use my storage space
Because, "no problem," you said.
And now look.
Heat.
White-hot heat.
No problems, my friend.
We're here
to take the merch away.
You'll be clean as a whistle.
Merch?
They're children, damn it.
They're
human beings.
Didn't i tell you to check
on them ten minutes ago?
I want another five large.
But we had a
deal already.
I got to stand up
for what is right here.
Be fair, sir. We don't have
that kind of cash on hand.
That's your problem. I can wait.
I thought you was
worried about the heat.
Well, if heat arrives
in the meantime,
I can get rid of the
evidence very quickly.
We have an obligation
to deliver.
The dollmaker doesn't
tolerate failure.
We need those children.
Well, that's also your problem.
No. Hey, hey, this
is totally inappropriate.
I mean, we were having
a business discussion here.
You weren't being fair.
Oh, gosh. Cops.
You didn't call the
gazette, but did your girl
Call the gazette?
Yeah.
I knew it.
I didn't know
she was gonna call 'em.
Seriously, you got to learn
to control your woman.
I kind of like her
the way she is.
No, these high-class
temperamental broads...
They need firm handling.
Trust me.
Trust you? On women?
Damn right.
All varieties.
From hausfraus to movie stars.
I love 'em all.
Now, you? Let me guess.
High school sweetheart.
Then a bunch of hos overseas
Only made you sad,
And then there's barbara.
Pretty much.
You, my friend, are a monkey
Riding a racehorse.
Good evening.
May i help you?
Detectives gordon and bullock.
We need to speak
To whoever's
in charge here, ma'am.
Of course.
Mr. Quillan, detectives
are here to see you.
Oh?
Oh, wow.
Detectives.
Hey, what's up?
Nothing serious,
i hope.
Cut the crap. We have a warrant
to search the premises.
We know what you're doing.
Well, then, you know
some boring stuff, then.
I mean, what are you
talking about?
You're peddling atp
to those kid snatchers.
Oh, my gosh, no.
I-i mean,
We used to stock atp,
but not since
The arkham asylum closed.
Uh, uh... I heard that
the wayne foundation
Is planning on reopening
The old place again.
But now that
the waynes are dead,
I guess everything's
up in the air.
Uh...
What a world, eh?
Nobody's safe.
Jim!
Go, go!
Where the hell were you?
Get rid of 'em now.
And hose down the room.
Zeb.
Freeze.
On behalf of all
the citizens of gotham,
I want to thank
you brave gentlemen
From the bottom of my heart,
and i want to promise you kids...
We will take
care of you
As if you were
our own children.
But here's the thing.
The people who victimized
these kids are still out there.
And hundreds
of vulnerable youngsters
Are still living rough
on our streets.
Alone, unprotected,
And let's face it,
That's the real crime here.
So what are we
Going to do to help these kids?
Yesterday i made a phone call
To juvenile services
and the gcpd
To initiate a humane
but tough-love program
To get these kids
off the streets
And into the loving arms
Of juvenile services.
I think that went very well.
I think so.
A small toast,
your honor?
You read my mind.
Mr. Mayor.
Uh, where are you sending
All the children
that get rounded up?
Foster homes for the cute,
undamaged ones.
Upstate for the rest.
Upstate?
The alpena youth
corrections facility.
A fine institute.
Prison, in other words.
Forgive me,
Your honor.
Detective gordon's
our house firebrand.
No, no, no,
th-that's okay.
Jim... May i call you jim?
Half the petty crime
in the city
Is homeless kids.
They need structure.
People who care
for them.
For the greater good of gotham
and for the children. You see?
I see you're using
the child snatchers
As a pretext
to lock up children
Without a trial.
Thank you, my friend.
Valuable input.
Most refreshing.
L'chaim.
Yo, gordon.
Man's been waiting
for you upstairs.
Mr. Pennyworth.
Alfred, please.
It's bedlam, isn't it?
Rough job you got.
Best job in the world.
I wonder if it
might be convenient
For you to visit us tomorrow.
Of course.
Why? Is something wrong?
I don't know.
Never had a child before.
Nor me.
The boy respects you.
Teatime, shall we say?
Teatime.
Name.
Ma'am, there's
been a mistake.
I'm not meant to go upstate.
I need to talk
To james gordon.
He's a cop.
You'll be allowed a phone
call when you get upstate.
Name.
I need to talk to him now.
He'll thank you for it.
Not happening. Name.
Bite me, pigarina.
Jane doe.
Hey.
Relax, kid.
Juvie's not so bad.
First week,
Whatever you do,
Don't make friends
with anyone that's friendly.
When you get into a fight,
go for their eyes.
Hiya, kids. How you doing?
Are you ready
to go on
A big adventure?
Sit down, young lady.
I said sit down.
Like now.
Okay.
Next naughty child to stand up
Gets a black mark right here.
One or two or three...
i could explain that.
But a busload...
A whole busload
of the little bastards...
What am i supposed to say?
Oops? Just tell me
it wasn't them, i'm begging you.
Just tell me it wasn't
the snatchers.
Bus driver was a man,
guard was a woman.
It could be them.
You're killing me.
We're working it, your honor.
Look, i told you everything
i know. I told you.
Now, you see that man there?
He doesn't like it when
i beat people, but for you,
He's got no objection.
Why is that?
Math. The lives of 30 children
versus one scumbag.
So i can beat you
like a bongo drum
And saint jim here
won't intervene.
Give us something.
Okay, okay, look...
The truck.
You know, when they came to
Pick up the last
bunch of kids.
On the side of it,
there was a-a picture.
Like a logo.
I-i didn't want to say before
Because it would give
a bad impression.
See, it doesn't reflect,
really, what, you know...
What was it?
It has a...
A blue plate
and a silver fork.
A plate and a fork?
Yeah, you know,
like, with the...
Like a catering company?
Like food?
Well, yeah, like that,
I mean, you know,
but, i mean, that
Doesn't mean... You know.
Doesn't mean what?
Look, i don't know
what they do to them. Aah!
Hey. Hey.
All right, draw the logo.
Uncuff him.
There you go, kids.
Let's go, let's go.
Keep moving.
Come on, come on.
Don't worry.
Everything's gonna be all right.
That's right. That's right.
Come on.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Come on!
Go.
Funny thing.
By my count,
According to the sheet they
gave us, we're one short.
Me, too. Maybe there's
one on the bus. Hmm.
Shh!
Nope. Weird.
Must be a miscount someplace.
Never mind. We got
more than enough.
We did good.
Indeed we did.
The dollmaker
will be so pleased with us.
All right, thanks.
Nothing. You?
Apparently, there are
no companies
In gotham with trucks with a
plate and a fork as their logo.
Selling children for food?
Is such a thing even possible?
We've got officers
searching all the trucks
On every bridge and tunnel.
But they had a
three-hour window.
We can only pray they
stayed in the city.
If not, they could be any
place on earth by nightfall.
Scum-sucking toads.
- Where are they?!
It's not a blue plate.
It's not a fork, either.
It's a trident.
When you stow this
on the ship,
Make sure there's plenty of room
for the doors to open.
The ship's crew has...
Let me out!
Quiet in there!
Hush.
My eyes!
She scratched me!
Oh!
Come on, follow me.
Mmm. Let me look.
Hmm. Yeah.
It's nothing. It's a scratch.
We'll get you to the doctor,
You'll be right
as rain in no time.
You sure?
What was that?
Hang on.
Well...
You are a very naughty
little girl.
Hi. What's your name?
Why is that your business?
Jim!
Where are the kids?
Where are they?!
He's not been sleeping.
And when he does, he
has these nightmares.
Now he's hurting himself.
Burning himself.
He's cutting.
Is he getting professional help?
Oh, you mean a
psychiatrist?
No, no, he won't have 'em.
No psychiatrists.
That's a rule.
You make the rules, don't you?
You're his guardian.
Bruce's father gave me
very firm orders was him
And his missus to die.
Now, i will raise
The boy the way
his father told me to raise him.
Which is how?
Trust him
to choose his own course.
He's, after all, a wayne.
Sounds like a recipe
for disaster.
What do you want me to do?
He wants you
to talk some sense into me.
Haven't i told you
to stop creeping up
On people like that before?
It's bloody rude!
All right, then, bruce.
Talk to me.
I'm perfectly fine.
Alfred's a worrywart.
What did you do to your hand?
I burned it.
Listen to me, bruce.
You've been through
a terrible experience.
Talking to someone
can be very helpful.
You must have seen
terrible things in the war.
Does it... Does it help you
to talk about what you saw?
Yes. A little.
You're not a very good liar.
Bruce, you're hurting yourself.
I'm testing myself.
Different, but i
appreciate your concern.
I've been following your
adventures in the newspapers.
I feel very sorry for
all those poor children.
Me, too.
I'll give you some money
to give to them.
I'm afraid
it doesn't work that way, bruce.
What way does it work?
Those children need someone
who cares for them,
Like you have right here.
Money won't buy that.
There must be something
i can do.
What about clothes?
They all looked awfully ragged.
They did, didn't they?
After all this?
You're sending
us upstate?
Selina...
Cat.
Cat, even if you didn't have
outstanding warrants, you're 13.
No parents or guardians.
That's not true.
I have a mom.
Says here she's deceased.
That's not true.
She's alive... Someplace.
Be that as it may,
We're not allowed
to put you back on the street.
It's for your own
well-being.
Have you been there? Upstate?
Yes.
Then you know.
You know.
Go get detective james gordon.
He works here.
Cat...
The police are very busy people.
Go get him...
Or...
I'll say you touched me.
Excuse me?
James gordon.
I'm gonna scream in
about three seconds.
Hello.
Yes, this is he.
Well... I'm looking at your son
Right now, and...
He doesn't look good.
Madam, i assure you, your son
is not trying to trick you.
Oh, he will die
A horrible death unless he...
No, no. No, really truly,
he isn't joking.
I'm not joking.
I will poke his eyeballs
Out, and...
How can you say that?
You saw the video i sent.
I'm not lying.
Madam, madam,
C-calm yourself.
If $10,000 is too much,
i'm sure we can...
Hello? Hello?
Well, that's disappointing.
She didn't believe me.
You must be quite the scamp.
I got it.
Hello again,
young lady.
How can i help you?
We need to talk.
So, now you want to talk, huh?
Okay. It's all right.
Thanks.
Selina is it?
Cat.
You macky's friend?
Yeah, i know macky.
Those bastards nearly
got you twice, huh?
You're quite a survivor.
You have no idea.
Suppose i had something
You really, really wanted.
If i gave it to you,
Could you get me out of here?
What do you got?
I've been watching you.
You're a friend of the boy.
You're not like the rest
of these crooks.
The boy? Bruce?
What do you mean,
you've been watching me?
That mario pepper guy
was a patsy, huh?
What makes you say that?
Could you? Could
you get me out?
It's possible.
I saw who really
killed the waynes.
Saw him clear as day.