Previously on Gotham...
You know, you can't commit
a crime in Gotham
without a license from Penguin.
Tell your family's Oswald Cobblepot
keeps them safe.
Not the GCPD.
We'd need an army to take on Penguin.
I am not giving this city over
to Penguin.
I don't care
what the Commissioner says.
Makes me miss Falcone.
I'm done with this business. I'm out.
I've got a place down south
I can go to.
We need an army.
He's got one.
You show your face to Falcone,
he will kill you.
An opportunity awaits you.
Why do you want this so bad?
I'm sick of not being
taken seriously.
With you and Barbara,
the three of us could give all those
creeps a run for their money.
You were the one time
I let love weaken me.
- No!
- And I want you around
as a constant reminder,
never make that mistake again.
I'm the one you seek.
I am Ra's al Ghul.
I have to be ready
for when Ra's al Ghul returns.
You need to find your true north.
Let that guide you.
It is you...
At last.
I was no more.
Now you live.
- How can this be?
- The power is in the water.
It has given you life and a destiny.
You must find your heir,
as I found you.
Find him.
Be free.
Alfred, you read?
Loud and clear, Master Bruce.
Looks like the rumors
around town are true.
Penguin's bringing in a big shipment.
Whatever it is must be valuable.
He's got four armed men
loading it onto a truck.
I'm gonna go down
for a closer look.
How did I know
you were gonna say that then?
I'm wearing bulletproof armor,
remember?
Yes. Lucius Fox's armor
was bulletproof.
My mask is not.
Don't get shot in the face. Got it?
Do I detect a note of sarcasm,
Master Bruce?
Hold on.
I just picked up a thief
heading toward the truck.
Thieves stealing from thieves
is a victimless crime, Master Bruce.
You just walk away now.
- They're walking into a trap.
- Master Bruce.
I'm all for you protecting
the innocent.
But I won't have you risking
your life over a thief.
Now, walk away.
Master Bruce?
The hell are you supposed to be?
Must be real stupid trying
to steal from Penguin.
Bad idea.
Hold it!
Let's get out of here!
Come on.
In the truck.
Damn it!
Hola, Señor.
Can I help you?
James Gordon.
I'm here to see Carmine Falcone.
He's not expecting me.
Come with me, please.
Carmine.
Jim.
You're a long way from home.
Came down to see you, Carmine.
Heard you retired down here.
Sorry for not calling ahead.
No, you're not.
It's quite the spread you have here.
I think we're past
the point of small talk, Jim.
Just tell me why you're here.
Morning, Daddy.
How was Artemus?
Feisty, as usual.
But I whipped him into shape.
Who's this?
James Gordon.
Jim, meet my only daughter, Sofia.
What are you doing here, James?
Go ahead, Jim.
I have no secrets from my children.
Penguin has taken over the city.
GCPD has turned its back on Gotham.
There are families
that are still loyal to you.
I need your help to knock him
off his perch.
Sure this isn't about you, Jim?
Your loss of power in Gotham?
This is bigger than me.
You have fight, kid.
I've always admired that in you.
But I can't do what you ask.
Why?
Because I'm dying.
Doctors don't know why.
Maybe old age. Karma.
They seem to think the air is
better down here for me.
Give me more time.
I'm not one to argue with doctors.
Or time.
So you see, I can't go back with you.
I'll go back.
Hush.
You're not ready for Gotham.
There was a time in my life when I
would've done anything for the city.
Those days are gone.
I'm sorry, Jim.
You're on your own.
You sure you know what you're doing?
You're mad because
I didn't listen to you, Alfred.
You're damn bloody right I am, yeah.
You're right. I let my guard down.
It won't happen again.
All right, there we go.
Might leave a little bit of a scar.
Thanks, Alfred.
All right.
Oh, no, where do you think
you're going?
To the docks.
I'm sure there's a manifest
on the freighter.
Whatever's in that crate
must be important
if the thief was willing
to steal it from the Penguin.
I want to know what it is.
Right, so being shot
wasn't enough, was it?
You got to let this slide, Master B.
There's more to this, Alfred.
I can feel it.
This is my chance
to investigate a real crime.
Stop it before it becomes
something bigger.
Fine. But just don't go charging
around in broad daylight
with that bloody mask on.
It'll be like having a socking great
bulls-eye on your back, all right?
So how do you suggest
I get on to the ship?
There are other kinds of masks
you can wear, Master Bruce.
As you can see, the scatter pattern
is tighter than most.
You won't find a superior
weapon anywhere in Gotham.
I'll take two dozen.
Excellent.
You can pay out front.
Right this way, sir.
Thank you, everyone for coming.
Tabitha planning on coming to work?
I am paying her half the profits.
Don't you mean a third?
That depends.
Where's my crate?
I ran into some trouble.
- Did Penguin's men see you?
- No.
I wore a mask like you said.
I know you're pissed.
I'm not mad. I misjudged you.
I was wrong to cut you in
on my new business.
You're clearly not ready.
You're serious?
I can get the damn thing!
I'll do it myself.
But if you do want to redeem
yourself, you can do the floors.
Mop's in the closet.
You can mop your own damn floors.
Another excellent night of business,
Victor.
Except for the part
where a couple of thieves tried
to rob your shipment.
- What?
- Relax, boss.
My men stopped them before they
could get their hands on anything.
You see what I'm dealing with, Ed?
That shipment is full
of black market items
I'm auctioning off tonight
to Gotham's elite.
I stand to make a killing.
I cannot do that without the items.
Where are they?
- At the warehouse.
- Take me.
I want to be sure
it's all accounted for.
And once I do, bring everything
back here for safe keeping.
Okay.
No.
No!
- This cannot be happening!
- I don't know.
Kind of opens up the room.
Whoever did this, I want them found.
I want them dead.
And I want Ed back here today!
Where are you, Ed?
- Oh! He's up! He's up! He's up!
- Where am I?
Whose... how did I get here?
I brought you here.
You're in my home.
What do you think?
I'm sorry. Who, who are you?
You don't remember?
Hilltop Elementary?
Mrs. Macher's class?
I was third row,
closest to the window?
Eddie, it's me. Myrtle Jenkins.
I followed your rise
to becoming the Riddler.
I've read every article.
All the police reports.
I guess you could say,
I'm your number one fan.
Okay.
Oh, I should get going.
Whoop! That's gonna be tough.
- Why am I tied up?
- You're not.
Your muscles have
atrophied from being on ice.
Okay? But don't worry, these warming
lamps should help thaw you out.
- Ice?
- Yeah.
The last thing I remember...
- Yeah?
- ...was being frozen by the river.
How long was I on ice?
Five months.
I know. Since then Penguin opened
a club called the Iceberg Lounge.
You were its centerpiece.
That little freak.
He put me on display
like some caged animal?
Yes.
And I will nurse you back to health
so you can reclaim your throne
as Gotham's greatest villain!
Oh! Oh, caveat.
With me as your sidekick, of course.
Doesn't that sound wonderful,
my love?
You lost, kid?
My uncle Al works on your ship.
My aunt hasn't heard from him
in a few days, and she's worried.
There are a few men below deck.
I'm pretty damn sure none of their
old ladies are looking for them.
Listen, I told my aunt I'd find him.
Can I just take a quick look?
I'll be in and out in a few minutes,
I promise.
Sure. Go ahead.
Thank you.
Bet you think you're real smart
giving us the slip?
I don't know what you're talking
about.
Save it. Somebody tried to steal
from this ship last night.
Did this to my face.
Tell me who you are working for.
I assure you,
I'm just here looking for my uncle.
I took a wrong turn.
Assure?
Here's a little advice.
If you're gonna play the part
of a street kid,
learn how to talk like one.
Hey, Andy! Get over here.
What'd I tell you
about bothering me at work?
Sorry, fellas.
You're right, though.
The boy's acting
does need some work, doesn't it?
You see, improvisation, Master Bruce
is a very important weapon
in any actor's toolkit.
Should we go?
There's a knife being sold
at your auction tonight.
I was thinking you might be
kind enough
to sell it to me ahead of time.
And why is this knife
so important to you?
It's not.
I have a client who's interested.
Gave me a ton of cash,
so I was hoping to get it for a
lower price and make a profit.
That start with the attempted
five-finger discount last night?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Of course, you don't.
I'll triple the opening price.
It'll probably go
for less at auction.
My dear, wherever you disappeared
to these last few months
has not made you a better liar.
It's clear
that this isn't about a profit
but about your mysterious benefactor.
He is your client, is, is he not?
Reveal his identity to me
and you have a deal.
Wow.
He's really got his hooks into you.
See you tonight, I guess.
Don't forget to bring your checkbook.
Always a pleasure, Oswald.
The knife was used to embalm
King Balahsi.
According to this,
he ruled Ancient Mesopotamia
for the first century.
And what thief in Gotham
would want a knife like that?
That's a good question.
According to the manifest
the shipment was full
of jewels and expensive art.
Yet, our thief went for the item
with the least intrinsic value.
Well, that tells me she
was a gun for hire.
But who hired her?
I think I just found the answer.
Alfred, look.
This drawing depicts a man
being healed by water.
Look at his eyes...
his face.
Who does that remind you of?
That's impossible.
I mean, this, this drawing
is 2,000 years old.
I know.
That's him.
That's Ra's Al Ghul.
He wants the knife.
I struck out with Falcone.
That right?
Try not to sound too happy about it.
Look, if you brought back Falcone,
that would mean gang wars
and blood in the streets.
And I don't like it
when the streets are bloody, Jim.
Yeah. I'll see how you like it
with Penguin.
See you tomorrow, Harvey.
Mind if I join you?
What are you doing here?
I figured you didn't know
anyone in town.
I thought I'd keep you company.
Or maybe I just didn't want to drink
alone.
To my dad.
I am sorry about your father.
We may have had our differences
over the years.
But I always respected him.
When I was a little girl,
if I wanted to spend time
with my father,
he'd have me schedule an appointment.
Save the respect.
I know who my father is.
Took him getting sick for us
to finally have a real relationship.
How long have you lived down here?
Since I was 13.
My father thought sending me away
from Gotham would keep me safe.
There are worse places to grow up.
People are happy here.
You can see the sun every day.
And I wasn't alone. I had Mario.
We took care of each other.
I know there's nothing I can say.
I am sorry for what happened to him.
You're right.
There is nothing you can say.
He was infected with the virus.
You did what you had to.
There's no sign of Nygma
anywhere in Gotham.
Word on the street is
it was an inside job.
Find whoever's in charge of hiring.
Kill them.
I want everyone here interrogated.
There's a traitor amongst us.
Those needles should help
stimulate your muscles.
You'll have feeling back in no time.
Just call me the Riddlette.
I know. What do you think?
I think that rehashing someone
else's idea isn't very original.
Wow. It's an homage
and I thought you'd like it.
It's very nice.
This is so much fun.
If only I were the criminal
mastermind you are,
we would've been together sooner.
I'm sorry.
I don't really follow that.
Well, it took me months
to plan your escape.
I had to learn Penguin's schedule.
When he came and went.
Devise an exit strategy.
I'm sure it would've taken you
two seconds to think something up.
It is slightly impressive
you were able to outwit Oswald.
Though, as you say, my plan
would've taken much less time.
Oh, wait. That is a great idea.
You should tell me what
your plan would've been.
Because a window into your master
villainy would mean so much to me.
I...
Here I am, bombarding you
with silly questions
after everything you've been through.
You must be exhausted.
Yes.
Yes, I must be exhausted.
Ooh! Soup's ready.
Do you like tomato?
I put little question marks
in it, too.
Last one.
One, two, three.
Anything, my love?
No!
Acupuncture is therapeutic snake oil.
I've been focused on repairing
the wrong muscle.
What?
Your brain.
It fires synapses that carry neurons
to the rest of your body.
And if we can stimulate it, perhaps
your other muscles will follow.
- Logical.
- Yeah.
- What do you suggest?
- Well, in anticipation
of our partnership,
I have been working on a few riddles.
- Yes. Riddles.
- Yeah.
That's exactly what I need.
That's gonna make me feel
like myself again.
- Fire away.
- Okay. Here goes.
What's black and white
and red all over?
Easy. Zebra with a gaping hole. Next.
- No. It's actually a newspaper.
- That's ridiculous.
There's nothing red in a newspaper.
Next.
- Well, it makes sense. And if you...
- Next!
Oh, I have a face and two hands,
but no arms or legs.
What am I?
Deformed baby. Come on.
Surely, you can do better than this.
Oh, the answer is a clock. Hands.
Oh, my.
I think something is wrong
with your brain, Ed.
There is nothing wrong with my brain.
The problem is your riddles.
Bring me a riddle
that is worthy of my name!
Well, next time
I'll know to pack a swim suit.
You actually own one?
Yeah. I got a nice two piece.
He comes with a sense of humor.
Do you ever think about walking
away from it all?
Gotham?
Sometimes.
But I can't.
Why not?
It's in my blood.
Father spent his entire life
fighting for the city.
Never took the easy way out,
neither can I.
What?
Give them to me.
Don't really think they're your size.
Come on.
That too?
- What are you doing?
- Come on.
You can't be serious.
Just a little water, Jim.
Can't remember the last time
I just stood still.
Right, Master Bruce.
Let's go over the plan again.
It's simple.
I show up at the auction
and buy the knife.
Should be easy enough.
I am a billionaire.
And a very public one at that.
Turning up at the Penguin's
black market auction's
certainly gonna raise
a few eyebrows, isn't it?
You're the one that said that bidding
on it was the smarter play.
That I did. But I didn't mean
as going as yourself, did I?
Oh, what do you think the idea was?
Going down to the docks pretending
to be someone else?
I was trying to teach you a lesson.
Now if you're gonna continue down
this vigilante path, Master Bruce...
you've got to learn
how to assume other roles.
Play the role
that you were born to play.
That of a privileged,
somewhat pedantic teenager
with deeper pockets
than anybody else in this city.
You mean behave like a spoiled brat.
It goes against everything
that your beautiful parents
tried to ingrain in you...
but yes, sir.
Bruce Wayne.
Billionaire brat.
Two hundred and fifty thousand!
Two hundred
and fifty thousand dollars.
Going once. Twice.
Sold to Mr. Bruce Wayne.
That's what I'm talking about!
I love art.
I love it! Yeah!
I'm gonna put it in my
in my bathroom.
Steady on, Master Bruce.
Let's not overplay your hand,
shall we?
I must admit, this is fun.
And try to exercise a modicum
of financial restraint.
Technically, you are the richest man
in the room,
but let's not try and buy absolutely
everything, shall we?
True. But if I only bid on the knife
everyone's been trying to steal
from Penguin,
it might draw his suspicion.
If I go on a spending spree,
recklessly throwing my money around,
he won't think twice.
Nice. When'd you think of that?
Improvisation, Alfred.
It's a weapon in any actor's toolkit.
All right, sir. Here we go.
Oswald! My friend!
Bruce Wayne. What a lovely surprise.
You certainly are getting out quite
a lot these days, aren't you?
The way I see it, everyone else
in this town is having fun,
- why shouldn't I?
- I agree.
You and your insanely
large bank account
are more than welcome here.
Barbara Kean.
I thought she died.
Unfortunately, nobody stays dead
in this town.
Excuse me.
You do realize, don't you,
Master Bruce
that if you actually win,
Ra's Al Ghul
will come after the knife.
Let him.
The next item up for auction
is an embalming knife
from the tomb
of King Balahsi of Sumeria.
Opening bid will begin
at 50,000 dollars.
A hundred thousand dollars.
What does she want with it?
I have no idea. Stay focused.
One hundred thousand dollars
to Miss Kean.
Do I hear...
One hundred thousand and one dollar.
Actually, Mr. Wayne, the bidding
amounts are in fifty thousand...
- Two hundred thousand.
- Fine.
We have two hundred thousand dollars.
Two hundred thousand and one dollar.
Mr. Wayne.
How about you let someone else
have some fun?
Oh. Sure. No problem.
I'm sorry about that.
Three hundred thousand.
Very well. Three hundred...
Three hundred thousand dollars
and one cent.
Five hundred thousand.
Now back off, you little brat.
Wow, Miss Kean.
That's a lot of money...
For someone like you.
Two million dollars!
Two...
Sold to Mr. Bruce Wayne.
Congratulations, Bruce.
Thank you.
I do love seeing that woman lose.
But a little piece
of friendly advice.
Barbara Kean does not give up easily.
She'll be coming for that knife.
I would just keep a close eye on it
if I were you.
There's a new wrinkle, isn't it?
What's green and red and goes
'round and 'round?
Someone's obsessed
with the color red.
The answer obviously
isn't newspaper.
You're stalling.
No.
You don't know the answer.
Of course, I do.
No, you don't, Ed.
Your brilliant mind is as damaged
as the rest of your body.
Actually, my body is feeling fine.
Frog in a blender!
Selina?
Why are you sitting in the dark
by yourself?
I was expecting someone else.
Like who?
Doesn't matter.
What are you doing here?
Heard about Penguin's auction.
So Barbara sent you for the knife.
Figured, what? Because we're
friends I'd just hand it over?
Something like that.
Why is it so important to her?
How should I know?
She was supposed to get it
for some client.
Said he was a pretty dangerous guy.
And that if you were smart,
you'd hand it over
and save yourself the trouble.
So you're here to protect me,
is that it?
The knife can't possibly mean
that much to you, Bruce.
I don't know, like you said,
I spent 2 million dollars on it.
I think I'll keep it.
- Why are you acting like this?
- Me?
What about you? Are you really
Barbara Kean's errand girl now?
I'm her partner.
But if I don't give her
this knife back,
she won't ever see me as an equal.
I'm asking you to do me a solid.
I'm sorry, Selina.
You should go.
Morning, Harv.
Jim, hey.
This is Detective Harper.
She just transferred over
from the three-five.
- Jim Gordon.
- Nice to meet you, Detective.
Heard a lot of good things.
From who?
It's good to have you in the fold,
Harper.
Thanks.
Gordon.
You got a visitor.
Hot damn!
Fox in the henhouse.
No offense, Harper.
None taken.
But you got the wrong idiom, Captain.
No, I don't.
Be right back.
Sofia, what are you doing here?
I came to help you.
Oh, yeah? How's that?
Penguin.
Oh, I know you
didn't directly ask me.
But I find men tend to have
trouble seeing the simple solution
even when it's presented to them.
You shouldn't have come back here.
Oh, Jim.
I don't need your permission.
Or my father's.
I'm a Falcone.
This city is my birthright.
My father might not think
I'm ready, but I am.
Is that so?
What do you think I've been doing
down South the past 10 years?
You knew you were coming back
from the moment
I left your father's house.
Everything that's happened,
was what?
- You sizing me up?
- No.
Not everything.
But I had to get to know you
if we're gonna work together.
We're not.
Don't be sore, Jim.
You came looking for a gangster.
That's exactly what you found.
We can do great things
together, you and I.
I'll be in touch.
You?
You were the one who stole from me?
Some good it did.
The ice broke his brain.
What are you talking about?
What's green and red and goes
'round and 'round?
- Frog in a blender.
- Exactly.
Ed couldn't even get that.
Does seem unlike Ed
to keep this rube alive.
Sound the word.
I want him found.
And her?
A lot of people have been trying
to steal from me lately.
An example needs to be made.
Have fun, Victor.
- Love your dress.
- Thank you. I made it.
Excellent technique, Barbara.
I'm impressed.
I had a good teacher.
I wish you'd've called ahead.
Does that mean you don't have
the knife?
No. Bruce Wayne has it.
Bruce.
Really.
How interesting.
- You're not angry?
- No. Not at all.
You see, Barbara,
when I bathed you in the Lazurus Pit
I did it in the knowledge
that you would become
a competent ally of mine.
And so far, you've done
an admirable job.
I'm glad you feel that way.
And I wouldn't worry
about that knife.
Didn't seem all that special to me.
Oh, but you couldn't be more wrong.
You see,
that knife is the key to everything.
Well, not everything.