Previously, on Gotham...
That's for Reggie.
Now, I don't know
what you want with
Master Bruce, but I'm certain
that his life's gonna be a damn
sight better without you in it.
I would be honored
if you would consider
endorsing me for mayor.
If you can give me
your word that
we won't have to face it alone,
you'll have my endorsement.
It's been some time
since I've had a meal like this.
You should come over more often.
We can, like, hang out
or whatever.
I'd like that.
Let go of me, you freak!
Listen to me.
I did it for you.
Kristen?
I've been following the
goings-on at Wayne Enterprises.
What have you learned?
That your father
was a good man.
But in spite of that, bad things
happened at his company.
(screams)
Looking for Penguin's mother,
weren't you?
I have to obey him
in all things.
Penguin has brainwashed
this poor soul. Can we help?
(grunting)
I'll leave you two
to it.
Father Creel.
You have the Wayne boy?
Not yet, but soon.
I found your mother.
Where?
In a warehouse
down by the port.
You sure this is it?
GILZEAN:
I'm sure, boss.
Once my mother is safe,
we go after Galavan
and his sister.
They're gonna pay
for what they've done.
Mother!
Mother.
(laughs)
(gasps)
You're okay.
Thank God.
Oswald?
Is that really you?
Your sweet face.
Like a vision.
I'm taking you home, okay?
Oh!
THEO:
And there I was,
thinking you understood the
meaning of consequences.
Consequences, yes.
I assure you
that my understanding
of consequences
will be made quite clear
once my mother
is outside.
But we've had
so much fun together.
My sister gets attached
to her playthings,
so I must insist
she stay.
And those bolt
cutters are useless.
The only way
out of there
is with this.
Very well.
Butch?
Shoot them both in the
head and grab the key.
Oswald?
Mother, I'm sorry,
but what they've
done to you will not stand!
I gave you an order!
Shoot them both in the head.
No.
No, no, no,
that's not possible.
You have to obey me.
You have to!
That time has passed.
They fixed me.
Tabby is well-versed
in the protocols
of conditioning.
There's always a trigger word
implanted during the process.
All I had to do
was get Butch remember
what it is.
I'll admit,
it took a few tries.
And now here we are.
(gasps)
Please.
I can still be valuable.
You'll see.
I so wish
that were true.
Then kill me if you must,
but let her go.
I'm begging you.
Doesn't look like begging to me.
Indeed, half-hearted
at best.
Please.
I'll do anything.
(sighs)
Perhaps she has
served her purpose.
Don't pout.
You still have the
former mayor.
He's so dull.
He just moans all the time.
(whimpering)
(laughing)
I told you everything
would be okay.
Didn't I?
(laughs)
And it will be.
(knife slashes)
No!
(sobbing)
Oswald?
What is wrong?
You look so sad.
(sniffles)
Nothing's wrong, Mother.
Nothing at all.
We're together now.
That's all that matters.
That's all
that ever mattered, right?
Ever since...
you were a little baby.
My little Cobblepot.
I'm sorry.
This is my fault.
Please forgive me.
I'm so sorry.
For what?
You were always such a good boy.
No, no.
THEO:
Kill him.
Dump the bodies...
...anywhere.
You don't have the stomach
to kill me yourself?
No wonder your family was
run out of town.
You come from a long line
of cowards!
(sighs)
Fine, fine.
Any last words?
Yes.
I'm going to kill you.
(screams)
(breath trembling)
KRINGLE:
You are a psychopath!
I am not the man
you think I am!
I would never do
anything to hurt you.
(gasps)
(sighs)
DARK NYGMA:
Rise and shine.
(laughs)
What are you doing here?
I banished you for good.
Almost. Love of a good woman
and all of that.
Though, we both know
how that turned out. Yikes.
That was an accident.
I'm not that man.
I'm gonna make this right.
See, I knew you'd wake up
all boo-hooey.
You probably have half a mind
to turn yourself in.
Luckily, I have the other half.
Do you like magic tricks?
What?
Of course you like magic tricks.
After all, I do.
Well, guess what?
I can make a body disappear.
(gasps)
Where is she?
Where is Ms. Kringle's body?
Open the envelope.
"I hid her body while
you were catching some Zs,
"you'll need a helping hand,
so look for her initials
down at the GCPD."
You went to my work last night?
Well, technically, you did.
I was just in the driver's seat,
so to speak.
How?
You're a figment
of my imagination.
A projection of impulse.
Nothing more.
That is uncalled for.
Uncalled for?
You hijacked my body
while I was asleep
and you stole
my dead girlfriend.
(laughs):
Okay.
Yeah, that's true.
But I'm doing this
for your own good.
If I was you-- which, again,
I sort of am--
I'd get cracking.
You do want to find
the body first, right?
REPORTER: Reporting live from
city hall, as we celebrate
the latest mayoral election.
Early exit polling confirmed
that Gotham City's new mayor
will be Theo Galavan,
who is projected to win
in a landslide,
helped by the endorsement
of many prominent citizens,
including police union president
James Gordon,
city controller Edwin...
(TV clicks off)
I can't believe
you're gonna be mayor
of this sinkhole.
Can I go
to the victory party tonight?
You promised me fun.
When are we gonna
unleash a little hell?
There'll be plenty of time
for unleashing hell and parties
once Bruce Wayne
has signed over his company
and met his unfortunate destiny.
Until then,
I need focus.
Young Bruce
has become fond of you.
His trust will be crucial
when the time comes.
I need you
to ensure that no one else
is whispering in his ear
until I make my offer.
See this finger?
I've got little Bruce
wrapped tight around it.
What a vixen you've become.
You make me very proud.
And we have Penguin
to deal with.
I'm on it.
No.
I'm about to become mayor.
I'm gonna have
an army at my disposal.
Time to use it.
BULLOCK: Looks like you backed
the right horse.
You trust him?
A Gotham politician?
About as far as
I can throw him.
But if he gives the
GCPD what it needs,
he's all right by me.
You know, Selina said
Penguin was behind
the Wayne Enterprise fires.
So?
First he's going
after mayoral candidates,
next thing you know,
he's burning down buildings.
Doesn't make any sense.
Guy is an abacus
of crazy.
Nothing he does
surprises me.
What the hell happened?
Penguin.
He tried to kill our next mayor.
Mr. Cobblepot knew
that I was poised
to win the election today,
and he came to me
seeking an alliance.
And you refused.
(scoffs)
I politely declined, yes.
So he stabbed you
in the neck?
GORDON:
That seems like
a pretty extreme reaction,
even for Penguin.
We've been trying
to build a case
against Penguin
since I got here.
We assume that he's
behind the earlier attacks
on the other candidates as well.
And this is the second time
he's tried to kill me.
The man is a menace.
And one that I fully intend
to put behind bars.
I assume you have
something for me?
Arrest warrant
for Oswald Cobblepot
as well as search
and seizures
on all his properties
and known associates.
Quite a list.
We'll get right on it.
Anything else?
Yes. In lieu
of recent events,
Judge Turnball has declared
a state of emergency
and granted the
mayor's office
additional powers.
Meaning what, exactly?
The moment I'm sworn in,
I'm implementing a curfew
and I'm ordering
your Strike Force
to begin door-to-door searches
until Mr. Cobblepot
is apprehended.
You're talking
about martial law?
We're talking
about bringing
a dangerous fugitive
to justice.
We'll be acting within
our legal rights.
Am I right, Mr. Dent?
Absolutely.
You'll have our
full support, sir.
Thank you, Captain.
Detective Gordon?
You seem...
hesitant.
Cautious.
(sighs)
You told me we needed to use
every method at our disposal
to go after men like Penguin.
Men who don't play
by the rules.
Desperate times call
for a strong measure.
I have no problem going
after Penguin
with everything we've got,
but if we start kicking down
the doors of average citizens
and policing through fear,
we're no better than he is.
People still need to trust us.
And they will.
Because at the end of the day,
all people want is to feel safe.
Just remember, Detective.
You came to me.
REPORTER:
...Theo Galavan will be
the mayor of Gotham.
A crowd has gathered outside,
and the excitement is brimming,
and in just a moment,
we'll also be talking
to many of the supporters
that gave up their time
and effort to support...
(TV clicks off)
What do you have
against the front door?
Nothing.
It's the ape who opens it
who I could live without.
I haven't seen you in a month.
Selina, what are you doing here?
You wouldn't believe
the week I've had.
This friend of mine, Bridgit,
decided to build this fire suit.
Selina...
Some people just don't...
Whose is that?
Sorry. I got lost
on the way back from...
Hello.
Hi.
Silver St. Cloud,
this is my friend Selina.
Selina, this is Silver.
Nice to meet you.
You, too.
Are you staying for lunch?
No.
Please say you are.
I just moved here
and don't know many people.
Bruce, go tell Alfred to set
another place for lunch.
Come on, it'll be fun!
Go. Shoo.
While it's just us girls,
let me give you a little advice.
You come around here again...
Well, that would be bad.
For you.
(chuckles)
Who the hell are you?
I'm Bruce's friend.
His only friend.
(sniffs)
(chuckles)
And you're a piece
of gutter trash.
Now, tell me something,
would anyone miss you
if one day you were just...
gone?
(chuckles)
I didn't think so.
BRUCE:
I told Alfred.
What are you guys talking about?
Nothing.
Just girl stuff.
NYGMA: "...you'll need
a helping hand.
Look for her initials
down at the GCPD."
"Look for her initials
down at the GCPD"?
down at the GCPD."
Kristen Kringle. K.K.
K.K.
K.K., K.K., K.K.
♪ Closest to the bone ♪
♪ Sweeter is the meat ♪
♪ Last slice of Virginia ham ♪
♪ Is the best that you can eat ♪
♪ Don't talk about my baby ♪
♪ She's slender
but she's sweet ♪
♪ Closest to the bone ♪
♪ And sweeter is the meat ♪
♪ Everybody thinks I'm insane ♪
♪ To overlook her faults ♪
♪ But here's the reason
I like 'em skinny ♪
♪ Instead of full of schmaltz ♪
♪ Don't talk about my baby ♪
♪ She's slender
but she's sweet ♪
♪ And closest to the bone ♪
♪ And sweeter is the meat. ♪
(gasps)
No.
Come on.
OFFICER: Hey, Mike, can you
give me a hand with this?
Putting Penguin
in the crosshairs of the GCPD
will drive him underground.
We can't kill him
if we can't find him.
We won't have to find him.
He's going to deliver
himself to us.
And why would he do that?
Penguin's rage will consume
his better judgment,
leaving him with an insatiable
craving for revenge.
All we need to do
is keep him hungry
and invite him to dinner.
And then I get to kill him?
Yes, kitten.
Then you get to kill him.
First, I would like
to thank this city
for the immense trust
it has placed in me.
I'm eager to get to work.
I'd also like to address
the recent attempt on my life
by the man known as Penguin.
It is true that he attacked me,
and as of now,
he is still at large.
Men such as Penguin
will no longer be tolerated.
These are men who scurry
from the light of decency
like cockroaches.
Men who...
not even a mother could love.
(reporters shouting)
(clattering)
He dies.
Tonight.
BULLOCK:
Yeah. Got it.
Gilzean's holed up in
a booze joint downtown.
Penguin?
Hmm-mm.
And get this. Word on the street
is Gilzean's started
his own crew.
Sounds like they had
a falling out.
Maybe he's ready to talk.
Yeah.
Hey.
I heard about what happened
to our new mayor.
Never a dull moment, huh?
No kidding.
You left your keys again
this morning.
Oh.
(softly):
Thank you.
What's this one?
A key to my apartment.
Oh?
I'll be in the car.
What? It's just a key.
Yeah, no, uh...
Do you want a key to my place?
Not even a little bit.
Wait. Do you have a place?
I think so.
Sorry. Caught me off guard.
I guess I do spend
most nights there.
Which I love.
What I don't love is hauling ass
out of bed at 2:00 a.m.
when you come home
from a stakeout
smelling of chili dogs.
I love to watch you squirm.
I was not squirming.
Little squirm.
(sighs)
I had no idea
we were entertaining today,
Master Bruce.
Anyone else popping by?
BRUCE:
No. Thank you, Alfred.
SILVER:
This is marvelous, Alfred.
I fell in love
with Lapsang souchong
when I lived in Fujian.
Driving through
the Wuyi region,
all you could smell
is the burning cedar
they use to smoke leaves.
Right, well, technically
it's, uh, pinewood, miss,
but I appreciate
the enthusiasm.
(sniffs)
That smell
really does slap you
in the face, doesn't it, Alfred?
(chuckles)
So, Selina?
Tell me about yourself.
Any family?
You really buying her act?
I beg your pardon?
Let me ask you
a question.
How long have you been
a two-faced slut?
Selina!
No, seriously,
what're you after?
It's the money, right?
I mean it's not
his wacky sense of humor.
I think I should go.
No, wait.
Is that a tear?
You're good.
I'm sorry.
Good-bye, Bruce.
Silver.
What did you just do?!
I know you're not the best judge
of, like, you know, people,
but that girl is bad news.
I just did you a favor.
I want you to leave.
(scoffs)
Fine.
Whatever.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe I'm not
the best judge of people.
Because all this time,
I thought you were my friend.
But clearly,
you have no idea
what that means.
"I'm tired of hiding
and want to be free.
"To locate her body,
find the two things missing
from me."
DARK NYGMA: The back of our head
kind of looks funny.
It's like the top of a pencil.
Why are you doing this?
Because... it's fun!
And it's good for you.
How is it good for
me to be tortured?
To be driven insane!
I'm trying to show you
who you are.
How have you not
realized that yet?
Though, to be honest,
I'm surprised you haven't
figured out this riddle yet.
Should I have
made it easier?
You could start by
using proper grammar.
A period at the end
of a sentence is...
"Find the two things
missing from ME..."
M, period, E, period.
Oh, God.
M.E.-- medical examiner.
You didn't!
I did.
I say we wait and see if
someone can walk us inside.
Try and keep things civil.
Did I tell you I was
thinking about getting a cat?
What?
Hey! How are you?
Why don't you get your
head in the game here?
I'm sorry.
It's just...
Do you believe
Galavan's story?
Questions like that
are above my pay grade
and below my
sense of wonder.
Penguin's a pragmatist.
Hitting Galavan
for refusing an alliance?
That doesn't get him
anything but heat.
So, what really
happened do you think?
A few months ago, nobody knew
who Galavan was, right?
Now, all of a sudden,
he's mayor?
Doesn't happen by accident.
It takes planning.
And it takes help.
Guys like Galavan
are born on third base.
Stealing home's
practically a birthright.
Think about the timing.
He shows up just after
Mayor James disappears.
The massacre
at the gala
turns him into a hero.
Penguin's assassination attempts
on mayoral candidates
launched his campaign.
Everything that's
gone down up to this point,
you could argue
was orchestrated.
Look, what you're talking about
is Machiavellian-level crazy,
even by Gotham standards.
Yeah.
There's our door pass.
MAN:
Yeah, so your mother tells you.
Yeah, his mama stopped
talking to me ages ago.
(laughter)
Oh, finally.
Whoa, whoa!
Hey, hey!
BULLOCK:
I wouldn't!
Aw, come on.
(laughs):
I really wouldn't.
That's a lot of firepower
there, Butch.
You expecting company?
Neighborhood ain't what
it used to be, Jim.
Where's Penguin?
How should I know?
You're the boss' lapdog and you
don't know where your owner is?
I ain't nobody's lapdog.
Not anymore.
Prove it.
Tell us why the hell
Penguin went after Galavan.
I ain't telling you anything.
And unless you have a warrant,
I'm gonna have to ask
you boys to leave.
Yeah, see the thing is
our newly elected mayor
kind of
wants results on this.
So we drag you in, chances are
that's where you're gonna stay.
ZSASZ:
I'm here for Gilzean!
Anyone who leaves now
leaves alive.
Anyone who stays
dies!
You have 60 seconds
to do the math.
Sorry, Butch.
Seriously?
No honor among scumbags, huh?
Hey, don't shoot!
I'm out of here!
(grunting)
What are you doing?
You tell us what the hell's
going on with Penguin
or we leave you with Zsasz.
You can't do that.
Bullock?
We can totally do that.
Galavan was telling
Penguin what to do.
Knocking off the candidates,
torching the buildings--
it all came down
from Galavan.
The hell was Penguin
taking orders?
Kidnapped Penguin's mother.
He was keeping her
for leverage.
"Kidnapped"?
Jim?
I think we need to go.
I didn't think Galavan
actually go through with it.
Go through with what?
Go through
with what?!
GCPD!
Put down your weapons!
(gunfire)
We're outmanned here
big time, partner.
Yeah.
But not out-gunned.
Oh, hell yeah.
(siren wailing in distance)
ZSASZ:
I'll take that as a no!
See you later, Butch!
(door slams)
(tires squealing)
That's a new one.
You think he was
telling the truth?
Nobody's
telling the truth.
This is Gotham.
Bruce.
What a lovely surprise.
Hello, sir.
I was looking for Silver.
She's here.
Seemed a bit upset
when she came in.
Yes, a friend of mine
stopped by the house
when Silver was there.
They--
Say no more.
I was your age once.
(chuckles)
Your feelings
do you credit.
I never met your father,
but it's clear
that he instilled in you
a sound moral compass.
He did.
You know, we're both...
very alike.
Born into wealth
and privilege,
yet forced to walk
our lives alone.
Haunted by loss.
Driven to prove
ourselves worthy
to those who came before.
Be careful, Bruce.
That way of thinking--
the need to fill a void--
it can consume you.
Does it every go away?
No.
But you can find closure;
a way to move on
without letting go.
How?
Well...
(chuckles)
I don't want to make
any promises,
but when the time is right,
we'll talk again.
(footsteps approaching)
I, uh, need to get
ready for the party.
Excuse me.
I knew you'd come.
No one's to kill Galavan but me.
Understand?
Boss, I get what you're feeling.
Mother's love--
it's the most beautiful,
most simple--
Gabe!
Cops aren't gonna let you within
a hundred feet of Galavan.
Let us whack him for you,
please?
No.
He's mine.
(sniffles)
Now, let's get dressed.
We've got a party to attend.
Listen up, people!
(indistinct chatter)
Our newly elected mayor
is going ahead
with his victory
celebration tonight.
He will be exposed.
He will be vulnerable.
And he will be protected.
By you.
The brave men and women
of this police force.
You all have your assignments.
Detective Gordon here
will be running point.
Detective?
Penguin has already
made one attempt
on Galavan's life today.
We should be ready for anything.
Let's show this city
what it means to carry a badge.
As you were.
GORDON:
I want check-ins from perimeter
teams every five minutes.
Martinez,
how's the avenue looking?
All clear.
Sniper Teams Alpha and Bravo
report all clear as well.
Copy that.
What you find out?
Spoke to the super at
Gertrude Cobblepot's building.
Turns out, no one's
seen her for two weeks.
Timeline matches
Gilzean's story.
Maybe or maybe the old broad's
on a sunset cruise, hmm?
You know, there's something
that Gilzean said
that I can't shake.
He said he never thought Galavan
would go through with it.
Go through with what?
I don't think
Gertrude Cobblepot
is on a cruise.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let me be the first
to officially
introduce you to the honorable
Theo Galavan,
the new mayor of Gotham!
(crowd cheering)
♪ ♪
Ed?
(gasps)
Oh...
What are you doing?
Dr. Thompkins, hello.
Uh, I'm just...
double-checking notes
for a Jane Doe case I'm working.
Do you need help?
No! No, no, no.
She's all gone.
Or she's--
I'm sorry, I'm--
I'm all done
with checking my notes.
Uh, what notes?
It's all up here.
(quiet laugh)
Do you realize that
by assigning simple
mnemonic devices to case files,
you can produce recall capacity
equal to that
of photographic
or even eidetic memory?
Ed, what's going on?
Okay.
(chuckles nervously)
Um, truth be told,
uh...
I was hoping
to run into you here.
Alone.
It's Miss Kringle.
Uh...
We had a fight.
I'm sorry.
(chuckles) Every relationship
hits a rough patch now and then.
And you've been so supportive.
And I was hoping that maybe
we-we could go grab a coffee
and you could give me
some advice.
Uh, do you want to finish up
what you were doing first?
No, no, no, no.
I... I can come back
another time.
It's not like they're
gonna go anywhere, right?
(laughs)
You'd think so.
(chuckling):
Yeah, okay.
THEO:
Detective Gordon.
WOMAN:
Hey. That's it, sir.
Perfect.
Thank you so much.
I, uh, heard about
your shoot-out today.
Something about one
of Penguin's former Lieutenants,
a Butch Gilzean?
Some men ambushed us
as we were questioning him.
He escaped.
Did you get anything out of him?
Before the attack?
No.
That's a pity.
Well...
MARTINEZ: Detective,
I have a large group of men
approaching from off
the main road.
I have eyes on the target.
Appears to be Cobblepot, sir.
Hold your fire.
Perimeter units,
prepare to engage.
(gun fires)
The target is down.
Martinez, I said hold your fire.
It wasn't us.
We have an unknown
shooter on the roof.
I repeat: we have an unknown
GORDON:
Martinez.
Is Penguin dead?
No, it wasn't him.
GORDON: Find the other shooter
and find Penguin--
we need him alive.
MARTINEZ: Detective, all the
targets are dressed as Penguin,
and all are heavily armed.
Positive I.D. is impossible.
Martinez,
you're clear to engage.
All perimeter units,
crash our location now.
Drop it.
Turn around.
Hands above
your head, now.
So forceful.
I like a strong
confident man.
(coughs)
(gun fire continues)
GORDON: We got
to get you out of here.
Radio his driver,
have him pull the car around
to the back service entrance.
Got it?
Yes.
Cover us?
No problem.
(speaks indistinctly)
MAN: Remaining officers stay
inside and clear the lobby.
MAN 2: Confirmed.
Primary is on the move.
Initiating exit plan
using the south entrance.
MAN 3: Roger that,
Detective Gordon is en route
to the rear entrance
with the mayor.
Need that limo at the back
service entrance, stat.
MAN 4:
Copy that.
Get him out of here!
(gun fires)
Go!
Hello, Jim.
Please step aside.
You know I can't do that.
You would if you knew what kind
of man you were protecting.
Shoot him,
Detective.
Oswald, listen to me.
You have to put
the gun down.
He killed my mother, Jim.
I know.
Detective Gordon,
I am ordering you
to put that man
down now.
He had her murdered
in front of me.
I held her.
Watched her die.
Do you know what
that's like?
It changes a person.
(footsteps approach)
BULLOCK: Sorry about
your mother, Penguin,
(gun cocks)
but I'm gonna need you to put
the shotgun down on the ground,
slowly, now.
One of us is gonna die tonight.
I have made my
peace with that.
I suggest the new mayor
does as well.
Don't make us shoot you.
Shoot me and you have no idea
what his endgame is, Jim.
And you should.
Because it concerns
someone you know,
someone you care about.
(whispering):
Shoot him.
(gun fires)
GORDON: Down!
BULLOCK:
Jim, Oswald!
Penguin smashed the mayor's ride
through the main checkpoint.
The good news is--
with the gunshot wound
to the shoulder and the APB,
I doubt he'll make it
out of the city.
He won't be trying
to make it out.
We lost more
people tonight.
Good people,
including Martinez.
Sometimes the good guys
have a bad night.
This ain't your fault.
I know.
It's his.
(reporters clamor)
My ancestors were swordsmiths.
They knew that to good steel,
it had first to be forged.
I look at tonight...
I look at tonight
as a baptism of fire.
A fire from which
we will emerge stronger.
Our resolve forged
to bring about
a new day in Gotham.
(listeners applaud, clamor)
(TV clicks off)
I've felt pretty alone
since moving here.
Until I met you.
But I-I don't want to come
between you and a friend.
You won't.
Selina is never going
to like me.
I don't care.
I like you.
THEO:
Detective Gordon.
Mr. Mayor.
You catch my speech?
I think I've heard
enough speeches.
I had high hopes for you.
I thought you were prepared
to make the hard choices,
to do whatever it takes
to rid Gotham of its monsters.
I am.
I've just decided...
I'm gonna start with you.
Dangerous words...
when addressing the man
who now controls this city.
Desperate times.
They are, indeed.
♪ ♪
I want to know why you did this.
When Dr. Thompkins walked
in the room, how did it feel?
I was terrified.
She could have
discovered the body.
But she didn't.
You got away with it.
That's not the point.
(echoing):
That is absolutely the point!
You can still feel
the rush, can't you?
Coming so close
to getting caught.
Knowing what you would
have been forced to do
if she had discovered
the body,
discovered what
you had done.
Standing... standing at
the edge of uncertainty
and peering
into the void.
Now tell me,
how did it feel?
Beautiful.
♪ Closest to the bone ♪
♪ Sweeter is the meat ♪
♪ Last slice of Virginia ham ♪
♪ Is the best that you can eat ♪
♪ Don't talk about my baby ♪
♪ She's slender,
but she's sweet ♪
♪ Closest to the bone,
and sweeter is the meat. ♪