Previously onGotham...
I'm arresting you for the murder
of the boy you blew up
under the Crown Point Bridge.
You blew that kid sky-high.
You are a lying!
You are a lying traitor!
I need you as the head of the GCPD.
Let them think you're a hero.
I screwed up, Harv.
Sofia hired the Pyg
and I covered it up.
- We all have to make sacrifices.
- No!
It was all about family.
Never said it was a happy family.
My friend thinks
we're here to rob you.
But I know you torture plants
in the name of science,
Roland Charles.
Lee Thompkins may have made Ed
strong but I see the other you.
The Riddler.
I'm back.
What's that smell?
Uncle Penguin sent me to get you.
Come on, let's get ice cream.
The Narrows is under new management.
The Narrows is Sampson's turf.
And Sampson well...
collects protection.
But people need to find out
what happens...
when you don't pay.
Please, my family.
Do I look like an animal to you?
I wouldn't hurt your family.
Unless they don't pay me.
Before Don Falcone died,
he warned me,
I had no idea
what I brought to the city.
I now know
he was talking about the Pyg.
Somebody must have told him.
My guess, that person has evidence
that links Sofia
to the Pyg's murders.
Why not come forward
with what you know?
It has to be more than
just my words against hers.
Or are you afraid the truth
is gonna drag you down too?
Harvey, we've been over this.
- When did you know?
- I swear,
I had no idea
until after it was too late.
Now you can be pissed,
but this is bigger than both of us.
I need to know I can count on you.
Yeah, Jim.
I'll help you take
you take down Sofia.
But then you're gonna have to pay
for what you've done.
I personally guarantee it.
I know an ex-Falcone assassin,
might have beans to spill.
Went by the name of
Scandinavian Skinner.
Sit tight.
I have history with The Skinner.
You know, you have like
no food in here, right?
Selina?
What are you doing here?
What's... what's wrong?
Why does something have to be wrong
for me to come by?
Seriously?
I need help.
You mean money?
I stole something, fenced it
and now I wanna get it back
and I'd steal it
but the fence is difficult.
So I need money.
Why don't you just ask
Barbara Kean for the money?
Because I don't wanna
get her involved.
Look, I'll... I'll pay you back.
I just... I don't have time because
if the fence sells what I...
But you still haven't told me
why you wanna give it back.
Because it's what I stole
from Roland Charles.
- The Wayne scientist...
- That Ivy killed.
I didn't know
she was gonna do that, Bruce.
And I... I just...
You feel bad.
Look, if you don't wanna help me
then I'll just find another way.
Let me get some cash.
There is oatmeal raisin cookies
in the blue tin.
Why are you dragging me here?
Cobblepot.
Guy called.
Want me to give you a message.
Finally.
"I could lend you a hand,
but you won't find me helpful.
My name may sound tasty
but the flavor is dreadful."
Is it knuckle sandwich?
Yeah.
Hello, Agnes.
Or should I say The Skinner?
Detective Bullock.
I don't go by that name anymore.
I'm retired.
- You kids, don't spoil your dinner.
- Okay, Grandma.
I'm looking for someone
who might have been
Don Falcone's eyes and ears
when he was down south.
Why would I tell you that?
Because we have history.
That history got me
four years in the gulag.
Either you help me...
or I tell your beautiful
grandchildren
how heir Meemaw
used to skin people alive.
Hey kids, you want to hear
really funny story?
Alright. Alright.
Never mind.
Falcone...
only really trusted the bookkeeper.
The one who always smelled of fish.
- Mr. Penn?
- Yeah.
Penn.
But good luck finding him.
I heard he's vanished.
Poof.
How is Martin gone?
Never mind.
Penguin is coming.
Go to Arkham and kill him, now.
Okey-dokey.
Oh, by the way, a buddy of mine
just got out of the hospital,
and he was looking for work.
You mind if he tags along?
Hiya.
Just make sure Penguin dies,
choking on his own blood.
- Why is Cobblepot in the infirmary?
- Heard he mouthed off to a guard.
Then slipped and hit his head.
Like I said...
Bullock. This is a surprise.
Yeah, Oswald. Good to see you too.
Just have a few questions
about a former employee of yours.
They got guns!
Open that door!
Get out of the way. Clear out!
Move, move, move!
Hey!
You two! Don't come any closer!
Bullock!
Dude, I thought you stopped
being a cop?
- Guess it didn't take, huh?
- Not so much.
- You remember Wendell, don't you?
- Howdy.
I don't know why you two are here,
and I don't care.
- Walk away!
- See.
I'm afraid we can't do that.
We're not leaving here
without the Penguin.
Harvey, do yourself a favor.
Give us Penguin...
and leave to get drunk another day.
As tempting as that sounds, no.
Come on, let's go! Let's go!
It's okay.
We'll come back.
He's escaped.
Oswald Cobble pot has escaped!
Nygma.
- What?
- You're just different.
Different how?
You're a complete douchebag to me
at the club.
And now you're not.
Listen Selina, about that night...
Oh, no. You're not gonna try
to apologize to me, are you?
- No, I just wanted to say...
- Save it.
Because you're probably gonna be
douchebag to me later anyway.
Missed you too.
Kitty cat.
Back so soon?
What's up, Floyd?
I'm gonna need that stuff,
I brought to you the other day.
You mean this stuff?
This stuff you try to break-in
and steal last night?
You think,
I wouldn't check the camera?
Go ahead.
Remember what I said
about being a douchebag?
I'll pay double what you gave me.
This your bank?
How about I take the money...
and I keep your stuff?
Next time...
take the deal.
Got it.
I knew that as soon as I rescued
Martin that she send her hitman.
How is Martin?
Snug as a bug in a rug.
Here, will you hold this?
So, do you want to know
how I found him?
So turns out, Zsasz...
huge fan of the disco.
So, I dressed up as an old polis...
Perhaps another time.
Now that Martin is saved,
we need to focus on killing Sofia.
- We need a power base.
- I know.
That's why we're here.
Hello.
Ed. You're back.
How are you doing?
Worlds better.
Honestly thank you. I...
Oh no, what happened to your hand?
Sofia Falcone...
smashed it with a hammer
and then threw me out on the street.
And put Sampson
in charge of the Narrows.
- I see.
- But together,
we can get that bitch back.
Can show her she can't just take
everything we've built.
Yeah Oswald, she can't help.
What is this?
What is going on?
What's wrong with you?
I let him out of his cage and he,
in turn, helped me get out of mine.
Your him. The Riddler.
Hi, Lee.
You know, it's really helping that
you were still running the Narrows,
maybe could help us, but...
- I guess not.
- Yeah, so what's your next
brilliant idea?
Sofia will have turned Falcone
mansion into a stronghold
It would impossible to get at her.
Oswald. You think I don't have
a backup plan?
Gonna have Victor Freeze
put you in a block of ice.
I'm going to take you to Sofia
like a chilly Trojan horse,
pretend to hand you over.
Are you kidding me?
It's a fantastic plan.
- Try again!
- Alright, let me help.
Look, all of your old capos have
pledged their loyalty to Sofia...
Do you think I can't handle it?
- I know you can't.
- Look what she did to me.
I will pull the trigger
on that bitch myself.
That's some tough talk.
But we both know that's just talk.
Enough! Both of you!
If we wanna fight Sofia,
we need muscle.
I agree.
I can tell you where to look.
Don't you think he misses you?
Who's she talking about?
Grundy!
You down here, big fella?
Your best friend and pal.
Edward Nygma.
Hey, guess what? I'm smart again.
There he is.
Pale skin, nobody upstairs,
who's my buddy?
Correct, you.
Oh, boy. So we're corralling allies.
Penguin and I are gonna kill
Sofia Falcone,
and we need a big galoot like you for
cannon fodder. How's that sound?
What's your problem?
Why you looking at me like that?
Oh, dear.
You're not the only one
who got smart.
Okay, Butch. I helped you.
You remember? Hot? Hot hand?
Yeah? Ed put out fire.
But you're not Ed anymore.
And I'm not Grundy.
- Where the hell is Ed?
- He'll be here.
No.
No, he betrayed me too. I know it.
I should never
should have trusted him.
Calm down.
No! Do not tell me to calm down.
You have no idea
what I've been through.
Calm down. Ed will be here.
He will bring Grundy
and we will make Sofia pay.
I can't wait any longer.
How did Nygma get in touch
with Penguin anyway?
I don't know.
Nothing's ever easy with you, is it?
It's always like find Lee
and then she'll point us to Ed
and then we'll find Penguin.
And he'll tell us where to find Penn.
Or we could just talk to Oswald
right now.
Hey, you son of a...
What are you doing here?
We're looking for an Arkham escapee
about yea tall, walks with limp.
Mommy complex.
Those trumped-up charges
you use to put me away,
have lost their teeth.
Martin is still alive.
- So, produce him.
- Nope.
He is not safe
until Sofia Falcone
has been dealt with.
Permanently.
I think you and I want
the same thing, Oswald.
We both want Sofia to go away.
Then turn around and walk away.
Let me do what I do.
No. I want her in jail
and for that I need evidence.
I want you bookkeeper, Mr. Penn.
Where he know about...
That little weasel was working
for her!
Yeah, he was working for her.
For Don Falcone. Everybody.
You might wanna check
your management style, pal.
I will kill him. I will kill him.
Oswald, Oswald.
Calm down you show us...
where we can find Mr. Penn...
and I'll let you walk away.
I don't believe you.
Sofia sent Zsazs to Arkham
to kill you.
Her goons' run the Narrows.
How long do you think it's gonna
take until she finds you?
I overheard Mr. Penn talk about
a place just out of town.
Near the Tricorner.
The spa Bosh Sumka.
Offers special therapy.
If he's hiding, he's probably there.
Oswald.
Thank you.
That's really nice, now put
your hand behind your back.
No. No. We had a deal!
Harvey, what are you doing?
If you wanna look the other way,
Jim, fine.
I didn't agree this squad. Come on!
No!
- I will not forget this!
- Relax.
The information on Penn is good
at least you'll be free
of Sofia Falcone.
Well, well, well.
Sofia is gonna be very curious
to know why you're looking for Penn.
Hey, Penguin. Remember me?
Oh, God. No.
Wait, is Penn important or something?
That's a yes. You see that?
That's his "yes" face.
Get him in the car.
Guess I'll have to go dig him up
myself.
Now, you boys wanna come quietly...
or do you wanna do it the fun way?
The fun way. Nice.
- Lee?
- Shut up and get down.
Lee!
Come on. Let's get out of here.
We need to get to Penn
before Zsasz does.
We need a car.
Migraines still?
It's like I've being hit in the head
with a brick.
What is that stink?
Should've known.
Grundy smells like old dentures.
It's him.
I know, I can smell him.
Hello, Barbara.
Scary.
Nygma tried to recruit me
against Sofia.
He's working for Penguin.
I figured after all Ed did to you,
you should be the one who kill him.
Wait, Butch.
Don't just walk away again.
Tabby, I wanna find a way to get
back to the old me.
I promise.
Any ideas?
You okay?
I'm fine.
We send Nygma back to Sofia.
She would torture him
to get to Penguin.
Lee has no more allies.
Boom, rebellion quells, we're heroes.
Then, what about Nygma?
He just gets to walk away?
When Sofia doesn't need him anymore,
she'll kill him.
Same end result, none of headache.
Well, we did find Penguin,
but then he got away
So why aren't you looking for him
instead of wasting my time?
Because I also found out that Gordon
is looking for Mr. Penn.
Find Penn before Gordon does.
Yeah, so Penn, Penguin
I mean, where are we, priorities-wise
Do both.
Thank you for coming to my rescue.
Don't bother.
Without you, I can't get to Sofia.
Touching.
I cannot believe I'm doing this.
Believe it.
No Ed, no Grundy.
We're running out of time.
You know this cockamamie scheme
will probably get me killed.
If it puts Sofia in the ground,
I'm okay with that.
Last time you came to me
with one of your schemes
to regain the city.
You promised every resources
I needed to reverse my condition.
So that didn't happened.
An omission. I regret
and will rectify if given the chance.
God!
You cannot honestly tell me
you were happy here.
Tinkering away on whatever...
Don't touch that.
You need money for your research.
Sofia wants Penguin.
So, you deliver him to her,
you can name your price.
I may have something.
Keep this on you. It's on a timer.
Best I can do on short notice.
Being frozen affects my brain
the way it did Nygma.
- I cannot afford...
- Ready?
- Not yet...
- Don't care.
So now, you're gonna return it?
- Selina, you said...
- Can you do it?
That's really why you came to me.
It wasn't about the money.
You did not kill Roland Charles.
I was there though.
What am I supposed to say? I...
I stole your jewelry.
Sorry.
Sometimes that's enough.
His strength of mind is impressive.
You are going to tell me
where to find Penguin.
Or I will make all of this look like
a pleasant dream.
Okay.
I can be done with the teeth
the eyes or the mind.
What am I?
I can be humorous
but I'm never funny!
What am I?
Tell me where he is.
I am telling you!
You're too stupid to figure that out.
Miss Falcone, you got a visitor.
Kinda in the middle of something.
Guy's got Penguin.
Bring him in.
Well, this is unexpected.
I heard you were looking for Penguin?
He never was a great boss.
Well, well, Oswald.
Is he alive in there?
Maybe.
I want 100,000.
Pay him.
I'm not even gonna ask.
Oh, by the way,
I found out where Penn is.
Take him to the docks, shoot him,
and throw him in the river.
Watch Penguin.
Let's go get Mr. Penn.
Lovely Ms. Gonzalez. Well done.
Pull it little harder.
That... that's it, Mr. King, come on.
What fresh level hell is this?
Who's hungry?
GCPD!
We're looking for Arthur Penn.
What are you doing?
Anonymity is a strict edict here
at the resort.
- I bet.
- What is going on?
- That's him.
- Penn! Penn!
Oh, no.
Let's take a walk.
As you were.
Mr. Cobblepot.
You're working for her too.
- I assure you...
- Of course, you are!
- Where is she?
- You don't understand.
Where is she?
Is it done?
Sofia left before I could kill her,
she's on her way to stop Gordon.
Meet me at the Spa Bosh Sumka,
and we will kill her together.
Nygma was here.
Miss Falcone
tried to get him to turn on you.
What?
He endured the tremendous
amount paid.
He wouldn't give you up.
Where is he now?
Her thugs took him to the docks...
to kill him.
I worked for Don Falcone
for years...
before Mr. Cobblepot.
When Sofia came to Gotham,
Don Falcone asked me
to keep an eye on his daughter.
She found out.
So you made another deal with her.
You weaselly triple agent you
It's how you stay alive
in this business.
And she let me live...
as long as I informed to her
about Mr. Cobblepot.
That's how she was able to stay
one step ahead of Penguin,
with inside information.
- Then what?
- She asked me to put her in touch
with Lazlo Valentine.
The Pyg.
So, I did.
But I told Don Falcone right away.
Alright. You're coming with us.
We need your statement
for the record.
Get down!
Get Penn out of here,
he's all that matters.
We gotta get you to the hospital.
Gunshot will draw attention.
Cops will be here soon,
I can make it 'til they arrive.
James Gordon.
We could've had a good thing,
you and I.
You just had to go and ruin it.
Go.
That's an order.
Get Penn. Get Gordon.
Get out!
Lee!
- Where's Sofia?
- In there, with Jim.
Take the car.
He's hurt, bad.
Get in.
Can't catch a break today.
Let's go get milkshake.
Jim, you really are
such a disappointment.
Would it have been so bad?
Being in the palm of my hands?
Having me chip away at your soul
little by little?
Was it so important to rob me
of my revenge?
It wasn't about me.
I wasn't gonna give you the GCPD.
Of course, it was about you.
Your pride, your arrogance.
Do you think that what I was
asking for was any different
that what my father had for 30 years?
You mean your father who you killed?
Yes.
I killed him.
Because he disappointed me.
Just like you.
You know, Jim...
oddly enough, I still care for you.
Beg me for your life.
Ask for forgiveness.
And we can start over.
Sofia...
go to hell.
James Gordon.
This is where our story ends.
- You.
- Yeah.
Me.
Stay with me, Jim.
Jim. Do you hear me?
Come on, come on!
Hey, I got a riddle for you.
What's got a bullet in his head
and sinks to the bottom of a river?
You.
The real torture...
is that those idiotic words
will be the last I ever hear.
Just do it!
Oswald.
How?
Did you already kill Sofia?
No.
She left the mansion to pursue
Jim Gordon.
Why don't you just stay at the home,
wait 'til she came there
and killed her?
Then I wouldn't have been here
on time.
You gave up your revenge for me?
Trust is so very hard to find
in Gotham.
But I trust you, Ed.
I have a strong desire...
to never, ever see this pier again.
Oh, I agree.
Hey.
Surprised you're alive?
Yeah.
- How?
- How do you think?
Lee.
She kept you alive
'til the medics get there.
Even one-handed
she's a damn good doctor.
Sofia?
In a coma.
Amazing she's not dead.
Harvey.
When I get out of here
I'm gonna confess.
My connection to Sofia,
my role with The Pyg, all of it.
I got to come clean.
No.
What do you mean?
Who would benefit from that? You.
You get to be the martyr.
Feel better about yourself.
The GCPD looses its hero. No!
You want to pay your debt...
you live with it.
Just like I do.
So, Sofia wins after all.
It's what the city needs.
Where's Lee?
She went back to The Narrows.
Said she had unfinished business.
Nobody knows? There, you like it?
Hit him again!
- Not so tough now?
- Get him!
Smash him up! Come on!
Alright, I'll go.
I'll go.
Oh, I know you'll go.
Just not yet.
Hold his hand.
No. No!
No!
What are you doing? No!
No. No!
No!
No. Stop!
With Sofia gone, Penguin is going to
try to take control of Gotham again,
maybe even try and kill us.
Could you just give me a second?
Barbara, we have to act.
We can't just stand around here
doing nothing.
I said shut up!