- I start a new job in the morning.
- A new job? Congratulations.
I'm coming to work at the G.C.P.D.
I'm your new medical examiner.
I have questions I need
to ask members of the board.
- What kind of questions?
- About Arkham.
It seems likely those gangsters were given
shares in Arkham by Wayne Enterprises.
This nightclub makes a lot of money. That's
why I wanna reopen it under your care.
- I can have the club?
- You're with me now.
What is this place? Where are we?
KELLY: Some people think it's a prison.
Some think it's hell.
They took my eyes.
KELLY: People call him Mace.
FISH: And he's the one in charge.
FISH:
Ah!
My name is Fish Mooney. I'm in charge now.
GERTRUD:
Yes, that's on. Heh.
GERTRUD [SINGING]:
When you're smiling
The whole world smiles with you
When you're laughing
What's she doing?
That sun
Comes shining through
But when you're crying...
MAN:
We have one more step. We're next.
Jim.
Hi.
Where's Jim?
He dropped off his keys, like, last week.
So screw him anyway, right?
So who are you guys?
[CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
Thanks.
[CROWD GASPS]
[GIGGLING]
RINGMASTER:
Ladies and gentlemen, The Flying Graysons.
Show them your appreciation.
WOMAN:
Thank you, from the Flying Graysons.
RINGMASTER:
Thank you. Thank you.
What are you doing?
[HORN HONKING]
[CLOWNS LAUGHING
AND CARRYING ON]
Coming through.
Get back in there. What the...?
[CROWD GASPS]
RINGMASTER:
Calm down. Stop that!
Come on!
Stop it. Calm down.
WOMAN:
I hate you!
G.C.P.D.
Everybody freeze.
GERTRUD [SINGING]:
That whole world
Smiles with you
[MUSIC STOPS]
MWah!
Boo!
Get off, you old bag.
Beautiful.
[GLASS SHATTERS
AND MAN YELPS]
[SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
Why did you attack Mr. Grayson?
No reason.
I don't like him.
I have no idea why he did it.
Beats me.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
You circus people don't mess around,
do you?
John Grayson, if you give me that look
one more time, I will slap you silly.
- You wish.
- Don't think I can't.
Whoa, kids.
What's the big problem, anyhow?
The Graysons are arrogant buttheads
is the problem.
The Lloyds are feckless drunkards
is more like it.
So it's a family feud.
Graysons don't get along with Lloyds.
Been that way for years.
- It's sort of a tradition.
- You guys fight like this every night?
No. That was just her idiot uncle
doing his thing.
You know damn well it must be Lila's fault.
- Mary.
- What?
Hey-
- Sorry the date went south.
- Are you kidding?
Best date ever.
Who gets to see a circus brawl?
True. None of them will talk, of course.
I still have no idea
what those two were fighting over.
I think they're rival lovers. Their
families have been fighting since way back.
But this particular fight was apparently
over a woman named Lila.
She's a snake dancer in the sideshow.
- Wow.
- I know. How cool is that? A snake dancer.
- No, I mean, wow, you're really good.
- People talk to doctors.
I guess so. I should find this woman Lila.
Make sure she's okay.
Might take a little while.
A patrolman will drive you home.
- Oh. I could come with you.
- Lee, this is police business.
Come on, Jim. I'm dying to meet Lila. Heh.
Well, bringing along medical personnel
is a justifiable precaution, I guess.
There you go. Heh.
Sir.
- Where's Lila?
- Lila?
Snake dancer.
G.C.P.D. We need to speak with Lila.
She's not here.
Why? What's happened?
Where is she?
Uh, I don't know.
- She was supposed to be home ages ago.
- You a relative?
- I'm her son, Jerome.
- Jerome, when did you last see her?
This morning.
She was here when I left for the library.
Relax, Jerome. This gentleman is just here
because Owen and Al had a disagreement.
Your mother's fine. Gone on a spree,
no doubt. You know how she is.
A spree? Without her hat?
Her coat? Her purse?
Look at Sheba.
She's distraught.
She knows somethings wrong.
- The snake does seem to be agitated.
- Sir, heh...
she's what you call a party girl.
Back in the morning with her knickers
in a handbag. Sure as eggs.
But she didn't take her handbag, did she?
How fast does an animal like that move?
Uh, fast walking pace.
They rely on surprise, mainly.
Let her out.
- I'm sorry?
- Let her out.
WOMAN:
Oh!
Oh, my God.
[JEROME WAILING]
You knew.
- You knew she was here.
- No.
Look at me.
She was like that when we found her.
Let's talk straight.
Those people out there are using us
as transplant donors.
We are simply spare parts.
Unless...
Unless we do something about it.
MAN:
How?
I have a plan.
But you must do exactly what I say.
You do as I say and I promise you,
I will get some of us out of here alive.
That's right. No, you heard me correctly.
I said some of us.
Because the truth of the matter is,
some will die.
But we will die with dignity.
We will die for a reason.
And we will die next to family.
And I tell you what...
we are family.
We are all we got.
That's family.
We have one simple choice.
We die here alone on our knees...
or we stand up
and we fight with our family!
ALL:
Yeah!
A couple of riggers found her right here.
We decided to hide her on the truck.
We were going to give her a proper burial
as soon as we got back on the road.
- Decent of you. Who's "we"? Who knew?
- Just me and the head of the families.
If an outsider killed her, what can you do?
An act of God?
If it was one of us, we always find out.
And we make sure they're punished.
- How?
- We have our ways.
And we have ours.
Hook him up.
[HANDCUFFS CLINKING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Morning, partner.
- Gonna need a little help here.
- No kidding.
I mean, you're kidding, right?
This isn't an elaborate prank or...?
Yeah.
Tell me about your mother, Jerome.
She's my mother.
What can I say? I love her.
She's perfect.
Not a very good cook. Heh. Except for that.
Did she have any enemies?
Someone with a grudge?
No.
- Boyfriends?
- No.
No?
She had lovers. Sex partners, really.
But not boyfriends.
- She didn't want the commitment.
- Alphonse Grayson?
- Yes, he was one of them.
- Owen Lloyd?
Yes.
- Any others?
- Uh, not that I could put a name to.
How did you feel
about your mother's love life?
I feel fine about it.
If not for my mother's love life,
I wouldn't be here, would I?
Sex is a healthy, human activity.
Yes, it is.
Do you have any other family?
The circus is my family.
One more time.
Why did you assault Mr. Grayson?
- You know why.
- Tell me.
- He killed Lila.
- Why would he do that?
She was gonna choose me over him.
And he's an arrogant son of a bitch.
Not gonna let a Lloyd humiliate
a Grayson that way.
How come your families don't get along?
His great grandfather falsely accused my
mother's Uncle Barry of stealing a horse.
- When was this?
- Before the Great War.
- World War I?
- Yeah.
For three generations, your families have
been feuding over a stolen horse?
Yes. And the Lloyds are still trash.
Blood is blood.
Must be a hell of a horse.
Why did Mr. Lloyd assault you?
He killed Lila
and fears I'm gonna kill him for it.
He says the opposite.
He says you killed her.
Yes, I supposed he would have to say that,
wouldn't he?
It wasn't Uncle Owen.
He could never do such a terrible thing.
Holy crap, Mary. How can you be so blind?
- Quiet, you.
- Yeah, quiet, you. You're the blind one.
My brother's a man of honor.
Your uncle's a violent drunk. Do the math.
My uncle is an artist.
Your brother is a conceited muscle-head
like the rest of you flying douche bags.
- I can't believe I ever thought I loved you.
- Enough. Huh?
[DOOR CREAKING]
They're coming. Are you ready?
ALL:
Yeah.
- I said, are you ready?
ALL: Yeah!
MA57A, raise your hand.
Five-seven-A...
raise your hand.
Step forward.
One moment please, sir.
We need to talk.
Back up, inmate. You're in violation.
Fifty-seven-A, step forward.
Excuse me. One moment, please.
I'm the new "shot-caller" here.
My name is Fish Mooney.
And with all due respect, for you and I
to have a good working relationship...
there are some things
that need to change.
- Is that right?
- What's your name?
None of your damn business
what my name is.
Right. Okay.
Well, I know you have a job to do.
And I am more than willing to give you 57A
in exchange for...
6O crates of water, 30 blankets, 50
pounds of fresh fruit and a few magazines.
What if I refuse?
What will you do?
Well, I'd be willing to give you 57A,
just not alive.
- We need them alive.
- Exactly.
I'm gonna count to three.
You'll disappear or get a severe beating.
I'm gonna take that as a no.
One...
Two...
[GRUNTING]
[MEN PANTING]
It's simple economics.
Our lives are worth something.
Sixty crates of water, 3O blankets...
You...
you're coming with me.
The manager is gonna be
very unhappy with you.
[SCOFFS]
I would think this manager
wouldn't be too happy with you either.
So if he wants to talk to
me, I'll be right here.
The manager doesn't come down here.
Well, looks like we have a standoff.
I tell you what.
I can be flexible.
So I'll go talk to this manager...
but while I'm gone, you're going to stay
right here as our guest. How's that sound?
We'll be back.
MAN: Yeah.
ALL: Yeah!
Yeah.
Wait. Back up a little.
- So you set the snake loose?
- Yes, ma'am.
- To track down the body?
- Snakes have an excellent sense of smell.
- Well, now I know.
And your prime suspects are a clown
and an acrobat?
- Yeah.
- Ain't this one a doozy?
Your victim, Lila Valeska,
was killed by a large knife or hatchet.
- Multiple blows to the head and upper torso.
- Around 3:00 yesterday afternoon.
From 2:30 to 4:15, both Grayson and Lloyd
were in the ring for the matinee.
- Well, how precise is that time of death?
- Give or take 45 minutes.
Still possible then, but cutting it close.
Hold and press your guys, but keep looking.
Yeah, boss.
Forensics is working the crime scene.
We're going through her phone records.
All right.
We're gonna send
the rest of you home now.
But the investigation is ongoing.
Nobody leaves town.
And listen up.
No more fighting.
Look where your friends are.
What good is this feud doing you?
I like it when you act all tough.
"Nobody leave town."
Sounds better when you say it.
[RAUGHS]
I feel like we should finish up our date.
Do you wanna come over tonight?
I can cook you dinner.
- Sure, that sounds good.
- Good.
- Get some rest.
- I will try. See you later.
I have to ask.
If you were to guess,
who do you think killed Lila?
I try not to guess. I work the
suspects and I wait on forensics.
Excuse me.
Am I speaking to Detective James Gordon?
Yes.
Then this must be Dr. Thompkins,
the medical examiner.
I'm sorry, how did you know who we were?
My name is Paul Cicero.
I'm a psychic with the sideshow.
Lila Valeska was an old friend of mine.
A psychic. I see.
How can I help you, Mr. Cicero?
I sense that you don't think
Owen or Alphonse are guilty.
You must be psychic.
In which case, perhaps you'd like to hear
the message Lila sent from the other side.
Thanks, Mr. Cicero. We're not quite
looking at the other side just yet.
As you wish. I'm merely a messenger.
What's the message?
Thank you, doctor.
Lila told me that the
servant of the devil...
lies in the garden of the iron sisters.
The iron sisters? What does that mean?
- I don't know.
- We'll get right on it.
I don't think sarcasm is your métier,
James.
Make of the message what you will.
Good day to you both.
[WHISTLES]
Well, that wasn't very open-minded of you.
Oh, come on, Lee. He's a fraud.
He's gonna go to the press
and say he's consulting on the case.
- He's looking for publicity.
- Maybe.
If you were gonna send a message
from beyond the grave...
don't you think priority number one
would be the killer's name, not a riddle?
Who knows how it works?
- All right. I'm not gonna argue with you.
- Good.
Later then.
Later.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
ALFRED:
They called to confirm.
You're meeting with the board
of Wayne Enterprises tomorrow.
Excellent.
- I was afraid they'd postpone again.
- Well, I'll say it one more time. I think that...
it's an incredibly
bad idea, Master Bruce.
I think it's reckless. I think it's premature.
Quite frankly, I think it's bloody dangerous.
We've already been over this
a hundred times, Alfred.
My mind is made up.
Can you pass me that file over there?
File.
Well...
I've said my piece.
If we're both found dead in a ditch,
don't blame me.
[PIANO PLAYING "CHOPSTICKS"]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Ta-da.
Nah.
No?
Jim loves me in this color.
It's too obvious.
You gotta dress like you're not trying.
Like you're on your way
to go meet some other guy.
To go...
sailing, or whatever.
Really? Sailing?
AlrightY-
LESLIE: Heh.
- Hm.
[POP MUSIC PLAYING SOFTLY
OVER SPEAKERS]
[GORDON CLEARS THROAT]
Oh, my God.
- Heh. You like?
- Oh, my God.
- What's wrong?
No, it's good. It's my sister's recipe.
She's a really brilliant cook.
I was thinking of my sister
and it came to me.
I think I know
what the blind-man's message means.
"The servant of the devil lies
in the garden of the iron sisters."
It's Arkham Bridge.
The iron sisters. Arkham Bridge.
The towers are called, uh, Mary and Betty.
Mm. I remember
as a kid we used to call them that.
Right. And there's park, um,
under the towers on the Gotham side.
A garden? It all fits.
Lee, it fits an impossible story.
- He didn't speak with Lila. She's dead.
- So you say.
- You're a doctor. A scientist.
- There are things in the world...
that can't be explained by science. - People
who like folk dancing, for instance.
- Doesn't mean ghosts exists.
- You're very arrogant in your certainty.
What if this is a clue to a murder?
The poor woman.
[SIGHS]
Fine. I'll go myself.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- I'll come with you.
- We'll go. First thing in the morning.
The morning?
Now? You wanna go now?
- It's only a half a mile away.
- It's dark.
I have a flashlight.
GORDON: So, what are we
looking for exactly, do you think?
LESLIE: I know. I know.
This is probably a complete waste of time.
- Thank you for doing this.
- Not a problem.
But, uh, let's not make a habit out of it,
okay? This is no place for a lady.
Ha!
- What do you mean, "ha"?
- You're a hypocrite.
You say you want a strong woman
to share this crazy life you've chosen...
but when push comes to shove, you want
me to stay home and bake cookies.
Not cookies, necessarily.
Pie. Any kind of pie.
Ha-ha.
So if someone threw something from a car
on the bridge, this is where it would land.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
[GORDON SIGHS]
Lee.
LESLIE:
"T-H-F-C."
- What does that mean?
- The Hellfire Club.
It's a Satanist cult that committed
a string of ritual murders.
They haven't been active
for a decade or more.
I guess they're back.
No.
No, I don't think so.
Hey, sarge. I'm gonna need a couple mobile
units to pick some people up, but listen...
they need careful handling.
MAN: Sir, they're in three and four.
- Thanks, Zeke.
- Neither knows the other one's here, right?
- Right, like you said.
Good work.
- Bear in mind you could be wrong about...
- Bear it in mind, I will. But I'm not wrong.
- So go on home now, lady.
- Hey.
We were having a perfectly lovely evening.
I am not the one who wanted
to go out searching for Satanist hatchets.
You know what I wanted to do.
- You're right.
- I'm sorry, what?
I tend to get enthusiastic about things.
It's an issue for me. My mom always said...
Who gives a crap what my mom said, right?
Have a good night, Jim.
Let me know how it all turns out.
Good night, Lee.
Wait.
What you said earlier about hypocrisy,
sharing lives...
you're right. Let's go.
I'm what?
[SOFTLY]
You're right.
[LESLIE CLEARS THROAT]
Good evening, Mr. Cicero.
Sorry to bring you down here so late.
Good evening, Detective Gordon.
Dr. Thompkins.
- How did you...?
- He smells your perfume.
- We solved the message Lila sent you.
- Oh?
Took us to Arkham Bridge Park.
We found a hatchet there.
- With Satanist symbols scratched into it.
- Dear Lord.
- Know what that hatchet means, Mr. Cicero?
- Tell me.
- It means you're an accessory to murder.
- I merely passed along a message.
A message from the dead. Didn't happen.
Which means you invented the message.
Which means you had someone plant
the hatchet for us to find.
You wanted us to think Satanists
were responsible for Lila's death.
You're protecting somebody.
Lila spoke to me. That's all.
No. The hatchet is a clumsy ploy.
You wouldn't try it
unless you were desperate.
Which suggests
you're protecting someone close.
Someone you love.
This fantasia was conjured
in your blinkered mind.
If you could only see what I see.
Hi, Jerome. Please, take a seat.
You know Mr. Cicero from the show.
Yes, sir.
- Hello, Mr. Cicero.
- Good evening, Jerome.
- Do you know why you're here?
- Did you find out who killed my mother?
You killed your mother, Jerome.
Me?
You killed her up on that hill and Mr.
Cicero let you clean up in his trailer.
He told you to scratch the Satanist stuff
on the hatchet and throw it off the bridge.
Sir, that's absurd and... And offensive.
But it's the truth.
What I don't know is why
this man risked so much to help you.
I think he's your father.
[SCOFFS]
You don't know what you're talking about.
My father was a sea captain.
Am I wrong, Mr. Cicero?
- Yes.
- He was a sea captain.
His name was Sven Karlsen. He died at sea.
What was the name of his ship?
He worked on a lot of different ships.
The one he went down in.
She never said.
We can do a blood test to prove I'm right.
Takes only half an hour to get a result.
- Isn't that right, Dr. Thompkins?
- Yes.
Save yourself a needle.
I do hate needles.
I'm sorry, Jerome.
What are you talking about?
He's right.
I am your father.
- No, you're not. Why would you say that?
- You must have suspected the truth.
- You're not my father. Mother would never...
- Your mother was a cruel woman.
She was often unkind to me,
but she did once love me in her way.
And she loved you very much.
That's why she gave you a better father.
[SOBBING]
[LAUGHING]
My mother was a cold-hearted whore
who never loved anyone.
And she'd never touch
a pathetic old creep like you.
All these years, do you think I was kind
to you because I'm such a good man?
If I wasn't your father, would I
help you as I have after what you did?
My father. Hm.
I'll be damned.
Oh, that's very funny.
[JEROME LAUGHS]
[IMITATES DRUMROLL]
Looks like the bitch got me
with a zinger in the end.
Why did you kill your mother, Jerome?
Oh, you know how mothers are.
She just kept pushing.
And I'm like, "Fine, Mom. Be a whore.
Be a drunken whore even.
But don't be a nagging, drunken whore."
You know?
"Don't come yell at me to do the dishes...
if you've been banging a clown
in the next room!"
You know?
[CACKLING]
Long night, huh?
Things got kind of ugly.
- Yes, it did.
- You okay?
I'm good.
[LESLIE SIGHS]
Truly.
It was ugly, but it was
also kind of thrilling.
- Thrilling?
- Thrilling and scary.
Like... Like looking down
a deep, dark tunnel.
Thanks for letting me be there.
You are an unusual woman.
You just don't know many women.
Can we go home now?
Mm-hm.
VICTOR:
Hello, Penguin.
Victor.
How nice.
Don Falcone thinks you're messing up.
You don't know how to run a club.
Your numbers stink.
- With all due respect...
- I didn't come here to talk.
Good manners cost nothing, you know?
Relax.
He's harmless.
Say hi, Butch.
Hi.
VICTOR:
Falcone didn't wanna throw him away...
so I worked on him in my basement
for a couple of weeks.
He's a whole new man. Right, Butch?
Yes, sir, Mr. Zsasz.
Butch knows the club scene up and down.
He'll help you out.
But he's...
He's Butch Gilzean.
He's loyal to Fish Mooney.
And he'll do exactly what you say.
- Really?
- Really.
Heh.
Hey, Butch...
dance for me.
I do good work.
- Good morning, everyone.
- Good morning, Bruce.
Welcome to Wayne Enterprises.
So happy to see you.
Thank you for meeting with me.
I have some questions regarding
Wayne Enterprises' business affairs.
Of course. It's your company after all.
Fire away, young man.
I have two main areas of concern.
Underworld involvement
in the Arkham project...
and chemical weapons manufacture
at our Wellzyn affiliate.
That's great. Congratulations.
We wanted to thank you.
If you hadn't figured out who killed Lila
and talked sense to us the way you did...
our families never would have reconciled
and we could have never gotten together.
- Just doing my job.
- If we have a son, we'll name him Gordon.
Well, we'll discuss that.
But we're certainly very grateful.
Sure.
- Why so happy?
- Happy customers.
That's not it. It's something else.
You got laid, didn't you?
That's impressive.
You slept somewhere without razors
and you smell like lady soap. Easy catch.
Mm.
I can only conclude that high-level persons
or groups within Wayne Enterprises...
have colluded in corruption, bribery,
racketeering and unethical medical research.
Thank you for that input, Bruce.
I'm so sorry if you've been alarmed
or upset...
by these shocking stories
and rumors you've been exposed to.
These are much more than rumors.
We'll look into them thoroughly
and carefully, of course.
Bruce, let's be fair.
You've told us nothing
with any substantive proof behind it.
- I haven't told you all I know.
- No?
What else is there?
I hope you do look closely into these
issues, because I'll be raising them...
at the next shareholders meeting
with possible legal action.
Dear me. Legal action?
These are all very deep waters
for such a young man.
My youth is not relevant.
Except that if I were a man...
I would be chairing this board.
And I would be sure
that Wayne Enterprises was run honestly.
Thank you for your time.
The manager says you have a deal.
You go up and see him. I stay here.
- What's your name?
- Schmidt.
Your first name.
Thomas.
Welcome.
Why don't you take off that heavy gear...
and relax?
My family's gonna show you a good time.