Previously on Gotham...
Last night,
some psycho froze a cop to death.
He was using
super-cooled liquid helium.
It's one of the most effective substances
in the world
for rapid temperature reduction.
He just wants to know where it comes from
so we can track down the guy.
- You confess to murder?
- Yes, I do.
I'm not a criminal, you know.
I'm just insane.
- I almost crossed the line tonight.
- How out of character.
- Scared me a little.
- Welcome to my world.
- I can freeze you, like we planned.
- But?
I can't bring you back.
Solution A14.
No, no, no, no.
I'm just thinking of all those
poor mice you're experimenting on.
What're you gonna do now?
Look for this Malone guy yourself?
Honestly,
I haven't thought that far ahead.
Nora.
You are gonna help save my wife.
My husband did terrible things.
But he did those terrible things
for my sake.
I'm dying. He wants to save me.
I'd like to make a confession.
I'm the man that's been freezing people.
A16. It worked.
- Am I dead?
- I can't believe it worked.
I'm coming for you, Nora.
I'm coming to save you.
Where is everybody?
Listen up!
Ace Chemicals makes the liquid helium
Victor Fries uses to power his weaponry.
Fries was spotted
entering the building 20 minutes ago.
He's desperate and extremely dangerous.
Let's do this.
Damn.
What the hell happened here?
Night janitor. Could be a hostage.
Detectives.
Canisters gone.
Looks like he got what he was after.
What's he planning?
"Free my wife."
How was Switzerland?
There are mountains, snow,
people are polite.
Alfred said you wanted to talk to me.
Alfred wanted me to speak with you.
He's worried about you.
He's worried that you might be concealing
any trauma you must be feeling.
He needn't worry.
I tell him I'm fine, which I am,
and he doesn't believe me.
You were violently abducted.
You nearly died.
You must have been very scared.
It's normal to feel trauma,
it's nothing you need to be ashamed of.
I wasn't scared.
No? What did you feel?
I felt alive. Intensely alive.
Do you think I'm abnormal?
You're certainly unusual.
If you're being honest.
I'm always honest.
That's a good way to be.
- Tough to pull off.
- I try.
- And how do you feel now?
- As I say, I feel fine.
Invigorated.
I have a second chance at life.
What do you plan to do with that chance?
My plans remain unchanged.
Find the man who killed my parents.
Bruce, you need closure.
Exactly.
Closure. Not a dangerous
and possibly endless obsession.
I'll find him.
You're a schoolboy,
not a homicide detective.
I believe people can be
two things at once. Don't you think so?
Yes, they can. So, you find the culprit.
What then?
I'll let the law take its course.
- Is that the truthful answer?
- It's the answer I'm giving you.
- What happened to Honest Bruce?
- That's a very good question.
I guess that's the other Bruce.
Sorry. I don't mean
to be flippant with you.
This conversation
has been very useful. Clarifying.
Perhaps we can do it again sometime.
Sure. We can do that.
"Free my wife?"
This guy thinks by killing seven cops,
he can get us to free his wife?
I'll free my boot up his frozen ass!
Tin can lunatic son of a bitch,
I'll tear his...
I'm gonna take a breath.
Well, what about the hostage, the janitor?
Any demands?
Not yet.
Obviously, we're dealing with a madman
and once he realizes
that we're not gonna release his wife,
he's gonna come to us,
try to get her, right?
What else would he do?
- I guess.
- When he does, we'll be ready for him
and we'll take him.
- Where is she now?
- In a holding cell.
Lee and a paramedic are seeing to her.
Lee says if she doesn't move
to a hospital soon, she could die.
Damn it.
We can't secure Gotham General.
It's too many access points.
Too many civilians.
Arkham.
They have a full ER facility, right?
We'll take her to Arkham.
This way, she can get the care she needs
and we can capture Fries
without endangering any civilians.
- Makes sense.
- Sense?
It's a lunatic asylum
filled with crazy people.
- You got any better ideas?
- No.
You prep her to travel.
I'll call the director at Arkham.
And get that out to the press.
I want Fries taking the bait.
I'll gonna let you tell Lee that
we're taking her patient to the nut house.
- She'll understand.
- Oh, yeah. Totally. Completely.
Let me get this straight.
You plan on using a dying woman as bait?
A tethered goat? At Arkham?
It's not like that.
Are you going to tell her husband
where you're taking her?
- Yes, but--
- Then it is like that.
It's the least bad of several bad options.
We could spread false word
that she's at Gotham General,
but what happens when Fries attacks?
It's filled with people
who are too sick to move.
This is the rational way to go.
Sometimes, the rational way
is not the best way.
If there were better way,
we would take it.
Just trust me,
Nora Fries will be perfectly safe.
- I got to go.
- I'm going with her.
Lee, there are doctors at Arkham.
She is my patient.
I used to work there.
I know those doctors. I'm going.
It's not safe.
It's safe for Nora,
but it's not safe for me?
- No, now, now, now, look--
- Yeah. Keep thinking, hotshot.
- I'm gonna get my stuff.
- No. You know what I meant.
If you use this on me, I'm gonna scream.
Who was that?
One of Fries' victims.
I'd hoped to extract traces of
Fries' formula from the man's tissue,
but no such luck.
Speaking of, you had a call.
The GCPD wants to transfer Nora Fries
to Arkham medical wing.
You mean, the wife?
Apparently, she's very sick.
The police think
Fries may try to break her out.
They need a more secure medical location.
Fries must be doing all this
to save his wife.
How romantic.
How perfect.
Here I am, desperately in need
of his cryonic expertise
and he's going to make a house call.
The fates are smiling on us.
Swiftly, Peabody, we must prepare.
...having recovered
from being frozen solid
before stumbling out
to the bewilderment of the GCPD.
He was taken to Gotham Memorial,
where he was treated for minor injuries
and released.
We are now getting word that Nora Fries,
wife of the infamous Mr. Freeze,
is being taken to the medical wing
of Arkham Asylum.
Arkham?
She belongs in a hospital.
Not thrown in among lunatics.
It's a trap. Of course it is.
They're using her to get to me!
The fools. They think
walls and guns can stop me?
They have no idea.
They'll learn.
Let me go, you brutes!
- I want to speak to Professor Strange.
- Director Strange is very busy today.
But rest assured,
nothing happens at Arkham
not according to his wishes.
What is this thing?
What're you doing to me?
You're to be the face
of our rehabilitation program.
If we can cure a man like
Oswald Cobblepot, we can cure anyone.
I refuse.
I refuse to be part of your program.
- You have no choice.
- Know this, woman.
Nobody yet has failed to regret
vexing the Penguin,
and you are vexing me!
Oh.
Make your next decision very carefully.
Duck.
- Thank God. It was only a dream.
- Duck.
It was only a dream.
Goose!
You're supposed to chase me.
You're the goose.
No, no. I'm a...
I'm the...
I'm a penguin.
Goose! Goose!
- Problem?
- He's not being the goose.
It's fun to participate
in group, Mr. Cobblepot.
You should try.
Yes.
Yes, I'd be glad to.
What is it they want me to do?
Be the goose.
Okay.
Sweet Mother. Is that Penguin?
Duck.
Seems drugged.
He's been quite agitated
since he arrived.
We put him on a mild sedative
to keep him from hurting himself.
Dr. Thompkins, my assistant, Miss Peabody,
will accompany you to the infirmary.
- She can provide whatever you need.
- Thank you.
Duck.
We'll set up by the main gate.
You should probably get
the inmates back in their cells.
Duck.
- Duck.
- Harv, come on.
Duck.
I trust you won't mind sharing the wing
with our dear Miss Kean.
You've got to be kidding me.
Oh, do you know Sleeping Beauty?
That's my name for her.
So lovely, so still. Like an angel.
Uh-huh.
Is there a problem?
No. No problem at all.
Pinkney, I want obstacles set up to keep
Fries from getting to the main building.
- Yes, sir.
- What about the bus?
Yeah, good idea.
And, Harvey,
I want a shooter up on that roof.
Jim? Jim, Jim, my old friend!
- Jim. Help, please.
- Wait! Wait.
Give us a minute.
Thank God you're here.
You have to help me. They're torturing me.
Torture is what you do.
- The doctors here are trying to help you.
- It's torture, I'm telling you.
- I don't see any signs of it.
- It's mental torture.
It's therapy. You're insane, remember?
That's what your lawyers said anyhow.
Goodbye, Penguin.
You owe me, Jim Gordon. I lied for you!
He killed Galavan! Not me! It was him!
It was him!
You owe me, Jim Gordon. I lied for you!
He killed Galavan! Not me! It was him!
It was him! It was him!
I should say,
that's learned him, Master Bruce.
We're supposed to have a training session.
Yeah.
Well, I got held up in the city, didn't I?
Besides, I thought your chat with
Dr. Thompkins would keep you occupied.
And I thought you were against therapy.
Well, that's before I realized
you're still keen on keeping secrets.
If I'd told you what Selina and I
had planned, you would have stopped me.
Because I didn't, I got the name
of my parents' killer from Silver.
Then you made us leave Gotham.
We lost more than a month we could have
spent searching for M. Malone.
We left the city because you were at the
end of your emotional and physical rope,
and quite frankly, you're incapable of
catching a common cold let alone a killer.
Will you stop?
Now, I need to ask you
a very important question.
Are we in this together,
or not?
Yes.
We're in this together.
Right, well, I told you
I had some business in the city.
I went to see a sergeant I know and
we did some digging in some GCPD files
for any M. Malones
that fit our particulars.
Age, size, height, race.
Whether they were free
during the murder of your parents.
And?
Patrick Malone.
Goes by the nickname "Matches."
Delightful chap, really.
Committed his first murder when he was 15.
Suspected of half a dozen since.
Now, I need to ask you,
if you were in charge, what next?
You could've gotten this information
from Detective Gordon.
Why didn't you contact him?
I'm the one asking the questions now,
Master Bruce.
We find this man, what do you plan to do?
- Kill him.
- No.
- You can't stop me--
- I bloody can, and I will.
You're too young to have a death
on your conscience, Master Bruce.
- But--
- I know how your parents deserve justice
and I know you're not gonna stop
till you find it.
But when we find this Malone,
I will kill him and not you.
That is the deal.
Do you accept?
- Yes.
- Say it.
We find him, we make him talk.
You kill him.
You have no idea what you're missing.
Bitch.
Where am I?
- Where am I?
- Nora.
Try not to exert yourself.
- You're in a hospital.
- Who are you?
This is not Gotham General.
No. You're in a more secure place.
I'm Doctor Thompkins. Lee.
They're scared of Victor.
Yes.
Victor only did these terrible things
because of me.
You're not responsible
for your husband's actions.
He's not an evil man.
He believes the good of saving me
outweighs the bad of his actions.
I understand.
But he's not my concern right now,
you are,
and you have to try and stay calm.
You're stable,
but you're still very fragile.
I could have saved him.
I saw him going down this path.
Becoming more and more obsessed.
Why didn't I do something?
I know what you mean.
It's hard when you love someone.
You see the person that they were,
the person they could still become.
You close your eyes to the truth.
He's coming for me, isn't he?
The police think so.
So stubborn, my Victor.
- You're pregnant.
- Yes.
Do you know yet if it's a boy or a girl?
Not yet.
I always wanted a girl.
You shouldn't be here.
Let's focus on you
and not worry about me. Okay?
Winter stakeout
at the loony bin. Fabulous.
Nora doesn't have long. Fries knows that.
He'll come soon.
He'd better.
We could freeze to death waiting.
Which would be ironic.
You hear that?
Take cover!
- Let's go. Heads up!
- Eyes open.
Open fire!
Move, move, keep going.
Get the door. Go.
- Hands in the air!
- I can't. I can't. Don't shoot.
- Where's Victor Fries?
- I don't know!
Please! Help me!
Let's go. Come on.
Mommy? Mommy?
Mommy!
Hello?
Huh?
Copy that.
Fries took out a wall in the east wing.
Have B team cut him off.
We'll head directly to the infirmary.
Alpha to Bravo. Continue pursuing suspect.
We're headed to the infirmary.
Copy that. Maintaining pursuit.
Take cover!
Nora!
What the hell?
Uh-oh.
Go!
Hello, Victor.
Forgive me
for getting straight to the point.
I'm a great admirer of your work and
I'd like to offer a way out
of your situation.
- Who are you?
- I'm a friend.
But let me ask you.
Once you rescue your wife,
what is your plan? To steal a vehicle?
Blast your way out?
There is a set of keys on the chair.
They belong to a vehicle
that is waiting by the loading docks.
- How do I know it's not a trap?
- It is not a trap.
It is an exchange.
You get your wife and your freedom.
I can keep the police at bay
while you escape.
As thanks, you will leave me one cartridge
of your cryonic formula.
What do you say?
The police are coming,
you can't beat them all
and time is running out for you
and for Nora.
Go fetch that, would you, Miss Peabody?
Fries is in the building. We have to go.
We can't leave her. The staff bailed
when the alarm went off, she'll die.
So, we take her with us. Come on.
Careful.
Thank you.
I'll take it from here.
Victor, Victor listen to me.
We're trying to help her.
- You're killing her.
- No, no.
- Victor.
- Victor, I understand
- why you're doing this.
- I'm saving her life.
At the cost of how many other lives?
Too many to turn back now.
Soon as I've done what I need to do,
I'll give myself up.
But now we have to leave.
Victor, I'm a doctor, if we move her now,
she might die.
A doctor, good.
You're coming with us
to push the wheelchair, let's go.
- No, no way!
- Jim, I'm going. She's my patient.
I can't let you do that. I'll go, take me.
Jim, it's not your call. She needs me.
I'm not gonna hurt her.
I don't wanna hurt anyone
unless I have to.
- Jim, I'm going.
- Victor, please, don't do this.
Nora, don't worry, it's all under control.
- Help.
- We have to go, now. You, in there.
- Do what he is saying. We'll be okay.
- Now!
Okay.
Okay, let's go.
Thank you so much.
Lee!
Apologies, officers, the extreme
cold has shorted the wiring.
We're working on it.
Well, work on it quick!
Oh, we are.
We are.
Please put that somewhere very safe,
would you, Miss Peabody?
Good news, officers.
Did Fries say anything,
anything at all about his plans?
No, nothing. He just said sorry.
Yo, partner! What'd we miss?
Fries got away with Nora and Lee.
I put a BOLO out on the vehicle,
but that's all we got.
Fries has to put his wife on ice
as quickly as possible, right?
He can't go home, there's cops
at the door. Where's he gonna go?
He's got the equipment with him.
He could freeze her anywhere.
Wait, now he could freeze her,
but he can't keep her frozen,
not without one of those cryo chambers
he built.
Then he is going home.
They're still at his house,
they were never taken into evidence.
It's where he went, has to be. Come on.
Victor, please think about this.
How will you take care of her
if you're in prison?
I won't, you will. Gotham will.
It's the law,
as long as she's legally alive,
she's a ward of the city and
the city has to keep her alive and safe.
Victor.
I'm here, darling. I've brought you home.
I'm so tired.
I know. It will all be over soon.
Victor...
I want you to let me go. Let me die.
Nora, you don't mean that.
I can do this, the process works.
So, I should wake up one day,
with you in prison?
Or dead?
A life alone isn't one that I want.
I'll be there when you wake up.
I'll be there, I'll find a way, I will.
There's always hope.
As long as you're alive,
there's hope, right?
Yes, there's hope.
Okay.
My necklace, the one that you gave me
on our first anniversary,
it's on the night stand.
Would you get it for me please, dear?
Go. I'm strong enough to use it
if I need to.
If you hurry, you can make it out
before he gets back.
I'm not leaving you.
This must be very stressful
for you and your baby.
We're fine.
Could I have some water?
Thank you.
You heard him,
he's not a bad man at heart.
- You have to tell them that.
- I will.
Please tell them that I'm very sorry
for my part in this.
I saw the man that he was becoming
and I did nothing.
Because I loved him.
You know what that's like, don't you?
I do.
Thank you.
You've been very kind.
God bless you and your baby.
Nora, I got it.
I've got it.
Victor.
I love you.
Please don't blame yourself.
See you soon.
You should stand back.
I felt the breeze
when you came in the window.
I'm glad you came. I need a favor.
Nice to see you, Selina.
Sorry for not telling you
that I was skipping town
to go to my castle in France.
- It's a chalet in Switzerland.
- Whatever.
Where's the King of Snotty England?
Alfred went to the city.
This is the man that Silver told us about.
Alfred tracked him down.
Patrick Malone.
I thought his name started with M?
The M stands for "Matches,"
that's a nickname.
That's a lame nickname.
So, you found him.
What do you need me for?
I need you to get me a gun.
- So, you're gonna kill him?
- Yes.
Your butler know?
Alfred thinks
he's gonna be the one to kill him,
that's why I'm asking you.
You couldn't even push that guy
out of the window.
So, how do you expect to do this?
Because this man killed my parents.
You ever even fired a gun before?
Please, Selina,
you're the only person I can--
You don't even know
what you're asking, Bruce.
Yeah, sure, the guy deserves it.
But doing this,
you won't ever, ever be the same.
That's what I'm counting on.
Crap, how'd you wanna play this one?
Slow and careful,
no gun play if we can help it.
Set up a perimeter, I'm gonna look inside.
Roger. Perimeter. Hey, set up a perimeter.
Give me one more moment, Doctor,
and I'll put myself in your charge.
No. No.
No, no, no, no, no!
Nora!
I don't understand, it works,
my formula works! How?
She switched cartridges.
She changed her cartridges?
Did you know?
Did you know she switched the cartridges?
No.
I'm so sorry.
Mr. Fries,
this is the GCPD, you're surrounded.
Please come out and give yourself up
and let's avoid any more sadness.
Yeah.
No more sadness.
Will you be very kind
and go tell the police
that I will do as they say?
Nora loved you very much.
I'm envious of the bond you had.
GCPD. Victor?
Oh, my God.
Hey. You should go back to bed.
Can't sleep.
Heard you on the phone.
Hugo Strange called.
Victor Fries died in Arkham infirmary.
They couldn't revive him.
You okay?
I am. Are you?
Wish you hadn't gone.
Wish you hadn't put our baby at risk.
You put us at risk
when you put Nora at risk.
- She was under my care.
- That was different, that was police work.
That was you, it's all you.
Arkham was actually Barnes' idea,
but it made sense,
- it was good police work.
- What about Galavan?
Was that good police work, too?
- What about him?
- The way he died.
Whatever the truth is,
it's not what you told me.
How do you know?
Because I know
when you're being dishonest.
And you know what?
If anybody deserves to die, it's Galavan.
But don't talk to me about police work,
it's you, you lied to me.
I know you say
there are no hopeless cases.
And there are none.
The beauty of life can spring forward
from even the harshest of climates.
We simply need to be more aggressive
in our treatment.
Now, I must go see to our newest guest.
Good morning, Victor.
Where am I?
Legally, your corpse
is in the Arkham morgue,
but obviously you're here. Indian Hill.
Indian Hill is a toxic waste dump.
A useful fiction.
You're the one who spoke to me in Arkham.
Hugo Strange.
Pleasure to meet you face to face.
How is it I am not dead?
It's simply astonishing, isn't it?
My guess is that you absorbed some of
your own formula over the past months.
Your body underwent
a profound cellular change,
when you were brought in here,
you were actually overheating.
Now look there, at the thermometer.
It's negative 20 degrees
and I'm not even cold.
The formula appears to have lowered
your core body temperature.
You can only survive
in severe hypothermic conditions,
anything above freezing will kill you.
But never fear,
you won't be locked in there forever.
We've made some modifications to your suit
to allow you to walk freely.
For now, rest. Tomorrow we begin work.
One project in particular
I think you will find fascinating.
I should have died with Nora.
This all should have ended.
Then take this opportunity, Victor,
pretend you did die.
Death is not an ending,
death is a new beginning.
English - SDH