Previously on Gotham...
Did Walker destroy Haven?
This part of the op is need-to-know.
I come bearing gifts.
Reunification with the mainland hangs
on by a thread.
Toxic chemicals rain down
onto the City,
and the government cuts us adrift
for good.
The filtration system
that Lucius designed is working.
It's not glamorous work,
but we are helping to save
the lives of thousands of people.
You're leaving Gotham.
I believe the time has come
for a change of scenery.
You found a way out of Gotham?
It's a submarine.
Jim Gordon and Lee Thompkins
are Man and Wife.
He will never see you as anything
but a dangerous woman
keeping his child from him.
Eduardo.
Walker.
Professor Strange will have
you fixed up in no time.
Rest easy, Eduardo.
I made you a promise when I found
you in that hole in Peña Dura.
And I intend to keep it.
To give you a true purpose
and the strength to see it through.
However, I'm afraid this process
will be agonizing.
And, unfortunately quite lengthy.
Apologies in advance.
You're going to be reborn.
And then you'll be the bane
of the unjust.
The bane of the corrupt.
The bane of anyone who opposes us.
Radio confirmation, General Wade's
landing-craft docked.
His convoy is on the way here now.
Reunification day is today.
Oh, that is great news.
But then what?
Just 'cause we rebuild
some bridges doesn't mean
things are gonna suddenly improve.
So, future got you spooked?
Yeah, I guess.
I mean, I wanna believe things
are gonna get better,
but sometimes it's just hard
for me to see it, you know.
Can't say I understand.
I don't have kids, at least none
that I know of.
But you got one coming.
So we got no choice but to believe.
It's gotta be better than what we've
been through, right?
It damn well better be.
Seven days in a row of point-oh-seven
water toxicity levels.
Lucius's filters did the job.
Good work. Hope it's not wasted.
Is there any reason to think
there's a problem?
Jim's got a lot on his mind.
And what with Gotham rejoining
the world
and a baby coming
into the world next week.
Give it a rest, Harvey.
All joking aside,
we're here because of you.
Now you're gonna be a father.
That's a future I'll take.
Well done.
Over the past year,
you've all done good work.
We've made Gotham a safe place
for kids and families.
You've given people the food
and medicine they needed.
But it's not over, yet.
So no matter what General Wade
says today...
work continues.
Give yourselves
one more round of applause...
and get back to work.
Here they come.
Captain Gordon.
Nice to finally meet you
in the flesh.
General, welcome to Gotham.
Good that you've re-established
some semblance
of law and order around here.
Seems like the Green Zone stretches
to every corner of the island.
General, Wayne Labs
show toxicity levels
way below the threshold
the government set for us.
With all due respect, Mr. Wayne,
but I gotta go with what
my people tell me on this.
Cutting it a little close, aren't we?
Is that under 27 pounds, 13 ounces?
It can't possibly make
that big a difference.
It's only the difference between
getting off this island
or sinking to the bottom
of the river.
Well, then Pengy can off-load
a few of his knick-knacks.
Not a chance.
Because you know what's worth
its weight in gold?
Gold.
Congratulations!
Go to the clinic, go have your baby.
What, so the two of you can high-tail
it off this rock without me?
I don't think so.
I assure you
we will not launch without you.
Ed and I will finish making
preparations
and we'll be ready to launch
the moment you get back here
with that little bundle of joy.
Or unless I should drive you
to the clinic in light
of your delicate condition?
I can do it.
I'm not that delicate.
Remember that, if you even think
about double-crossing me.
Very kind of you to offer
to drive her.
I knew she would never accept
my help.
Should I start the engine?
One less passenger to worry about.
No, two, actually.
You are so right.
Found it.
Oh, well done, Miss Kyle.
All right, let's have a look.
All right, here we go.
Oh, so this guy's the architect
who designed Wayne Manor?
Yeah, that's right.
With a reunification,
a new Wayne Manor must follow.
And it'll be just like the old one?
Oh, nothing is just like it was.
So why are we looking
at the old plans?
Perhaps I'm not ready to let
go of the past.
Well, if it makes you feel better,
I wish I could blow up my past.
Or maybe you will.
But one day
when you build something new,
the past will always be part of it.
As for me, now master Bruce is grown,
building a new manor might be
my last great service to him.
A home.
And then what?
You retire?
No.
I will stand guard.
As I've always done.
Well, I thought this was all settled.
This is bull.
My results are accurate, Jim.
We don't know this general.
Maybe he's with Walker.
Let's not get carried away.
Bruce, go and check on the tech.
It's Gordon.
It's Lee.
Everything okay?
Barbara just showed up here.
In labor.
You're kidding.
You better come quick.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'll try to get over there
as soon as I can.
Try to...
Try to wait for me?
It doesn't really work that way.
I know.
Okay.
Wait.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Jim!
What? What's wrong?
We did it.
You did it. We got through it, Jim.
Captain.
All clear.
Congratulations.
Reunification can begin.
Well, I'm glad
I could make you so happy.
Funny thing is, sir,
that's just the second
best news I've gotten today.
What's that?
- Jim?
- Incoming!
Everybody get back!
Get inside! Get inside!
Go! Go!
Eduardo?
Not anymore.
All right, people, listen up!
I want squads
headed for Knights Stadium,
Yeavely Park and Granton Station.
Work your way out.
We gotta find them, people.
What the bloody hell happened?
Seems that Jim's old army buddy
wasn't quite as dead as we'd hoped.
I got squads covering the North Side,
they're sweeping from Coventry
down to Miller Harbor.
But they could be anywhere.
Well, give us an area to search.
We'll get it covered.
Oh, take Reatton.
Work your way to South City Park.
Looks like you're not done protecting
Bruce yet, Alfred.
Eduardo?
What did Walker do to you?
When I was in Peña Dura prison,
Jim, the guards played a game.
They'd choose one of us
and they buried us alive.
They'd take bets on whether
you could dig your way out,
but then they'd bury you deeper
and play again.
I was the champion.
To survive that,
I had to stop being human.
I had become something else.
I became Bane.
Only I didn't know it yet.
But she knew and she showed me
the way.
If the world is full of monsters,
the only way to defeat them
is to become one yourself.
I'm sorry.
You were a good soldier.
Don't pity me, Jim.
We are building the future.
She's given me a purity of mission.
And unlike the Army,
she is willing to carry things out.
A new world is coming.
Strong, merciless, unyielding.
I've heard it all before.
Not gonna happen.
And how are you going to stop me,
Jim?
Not me.
You kidnapped Bruce Wayne
and a general of the US Army.
You talk about your future, Eduardo.
But you don't have one.
But Eduardo's dead, Jim.
There is only Bane now.
Rise.
I said rise!
Not so formal.
Captain and I are acquainted.
Get the other one.
I recognize your voice.
But I don't know what to call you.
I know it's not Walker.
So who are you?
That's a good question.
Perhaps Bruce Wayne can help us
figure that one out.
You okay?
Yeah.
You want hostages?
You've got me and the general
of the US Army.
Let him go.
This has nothing to do with him.
This has nothing to do with him?
But, Captain,
you don't even know what this is.
This, everything I have done here,
is about punishing Gotham.
For the sins of Bruce Wayne.
You can start now.
No! No!
And again.
So, Bruce Wayne.
I'm thinking of a name.
Can you guess whose it is?
What?
Wrong.
And again.
Wanna take another guess?
Farewell, my beloved Gotham,
city of my birth.
Parting is such sweet sorrow.
Though I leave you today,
my heart will always remain...
I do so hate good-byes.
Well, you're in luck.
We're not going anywhere.
- What are you talking about?
- Engine won't start.
Pressure regulator valve's missing.
Or rather, it's stolen.
Barbara!
Blood pressure's normal.
I'm glad something
about this is normal.
So how long is this gonna take,
Doc, soup to nuts?
Are you in a hurry or something?
No, it's just that...
I just feel like you've been so great
about this and, you know,
it's been awkward as hell for you
and...
I haven't even really said thank you.
I don't expect a thank you from you,
Barbara.
Then perhaps the best thank you
would be for me
to get out of here as soon
as possible.
Whatever's on your mind,
the health of the baby comes first.
I know that.
So long haul or short, we're here
until you have a healthy baby
in your arms.
That's all I want.
Okay.
Stop it!
A name.
A person.
The reason this is all happening.
Can't you guess, yet?
I don't know!
If you wanna punish me, then do it.
Hurt me, not him.
I am hurting you.
There's nothing more painful
than seeing your friends suffer.
But he's more than just a friend,
isn't he, Bruce?
Jim Gordon's been
like a father to you.
How awful it must be
to watch another father die.
Who am I doing this for?
Say the name.
When the ones you love die,
it's like a part of yourself
is cut off forever.
You know that.
So why do I hate you so much?
Who was cut away from me?
Last chance.
Yes.
Now you know.
Say his name.
Say it.
Ra's al Ghul.
This is revenge for his death.
And who am I?
You're his daughter.
My name is Nyssa al Ghul.
And revenge is just the beginning
of what I want.
The League of Shadows is everywhere.
Did you think my father's mission
would die with him?
Humankind will be purged of weakness.
I'm just starting with you and yours.
You're right.
I killed Ra's.
So whatever you need to do,
do it to me.
No.
You can't take all the blame
for killing my father.
I mean, you did have some help,
right?
Someone who quite literally
gave you a helping hand.
What are you doing?
Well done, Barbara.
Go get Barbara Kean.
Eduardo.
She's pregnant.
She's carrying a child.
A child.
One soul's future
weighed against the world's.
Your concern seems petty, Jim.
If he touches a hair
on that child's head,
I will destroy everything you have.
I don't have anything left.
Just my father's mission.
Bane wants you
to join that mission with us.
To see the world as he sees it.
Never.
Never say never, Captain Gordon.
No!
How does it feel, Bruce,
knowing that all of this
is your fault?
Tell me, I'd really like to know.
There must be something
you can give me.
We're out of the drugs that you need.
It's okay. You're almost there.
I'll get you some ice chips,
so you don't get dehydrated.
Gee, thanks.
Lee.
Ed.
Don't worry. I'm not here for you.
But for the record,
you stabbed me first.
If you two are quite done,
we are actually here for Barbara.
- Oh, no.
- Or more precisely,
what she stole from us.
I don't know what this is about
and I don't care.
You two need to get out of here
right now.
Gladly.
Just as soon as Barbara
gives us the...
- What's it called?
- Pressure regulator valve.
Right. That.
I should've known that you would
try to screw us over.
You only noticed because you tried
to screw me over first.
Second. Technically.
Okay, she's in the middle
of having a baby.
And we are in the middle
of trying to leave Gotham.
And we can't do that without
a crucial part of the submarine,
which will ferry us all away
from here.
That's why you were in such a rush
to get out of here.
As are we.
Hand over the part, now.
Don't point that at the baby.
What? No, I did not.
I...
I was merely trying to make a general
threatening gesture with the firearm.
But you did, though.
You pointed the gun at the baby.
All right. Fine.
I'm sorry! Now give us what we want!
Oh, you think I'm stupid enough
to have the part on me?
It's hidden away somewhere safe.
And if you think you can torture me
into telling you where,
there is literally nothing
more painful
then what I am going
through right now!
Hey! You stay out of here.
This is a hospital.
Mommy Kean.
Your time is up.
There is no place for you hide.
No one will save you.
No mercy that will spare you.
You certainly cannot run
from your sins.
And you cannot run from me.
What do you want from me?
Let me let you in
on a little military secret.
It's called Special Order 3-8-6.
In the event that Gotham
is irretrievably lost,
a contingency plan was put in place
to reduce this city to rubble.
No. There are still innocent
people here.
You asked me what I want from you.
I want you to suffer, Bruce Wayne.
And then I want you to die.
Spend a little time
with that thought.
We'll be starting soon.
- Who are those guys?
- No idea.
Exactly how many people have
you screwed over?
Present company excluded?
But there are 79 people
in this building.
Fortunately, they seem to only be
interested in trying to kill one.
So by all means,
let's gather around the target.
Maybe we can cut through
the abandoned wing
and we can get to the
ambulance bay that way.
It might take some time, but...
Oh, if only there were two able
bodied men who could buy us some.
And why, pray tell, should we risk
our necks for you?
For chivalry?
But if that's too much remember,
if I die, you will never find
that sub-part.
Fine.
We'll keep them busy.
- We'll meet you at the docks.
- Thank you.
- What?
- Keep them busy?
I only brought enough ammunition
for a light firefight,
not to repel a paramilitary assault.
What do we use, bedpans?
I was actually thinking of something
a little more flammable.
Why, Captain Gordon,
how nice that you're awake.
You picked the losing side, Strange.
The Army's coming to Gotham.
Help me and you can do
what you do best.
Survive.
I happen to think more
of Ms. Al Ghul's chances
for success than a man in your,
well, position.
You really think she can take
on the entire Army?
As a matter of fact, I do.
With my help...
you are just a few modifications away
from being a mighty soldier
in her forces.
Not unlike your friend Eduardo...
I will help you to realize
your full potential.
Give you true strength.
- I'll pass.
- Consent is hardly a prerequisite.
We will begin with,
physical improvements.
Sorry.
And finish with certain mental
adjustments.
Your contractions
are about a minute apart.
We gotta get you out of here.
Nice shot!
Keep breathing.
Some try to hide, some try to cheat.
But time will let us always meet.
What am I?
- Pregnant lady with a gun?
- Death. But close enough.
So, where to now?
Well, I believe
we have a sub to catch.
How long have you had that?
Long enough to know she'd never
let it out of her sight.
And you stuck around long enough
to risk both of our lives
to save Barbara's?
Or was it to protect Lee?
Do you want me to answer that or do
you wanna sail away from here?
Bon voyage.
Those bastards have stolen
the damn sub-part!
You mean stole it back.
Whose side are you on?
Clearly, I'm on the baby's side,
Barbara.
What was your plan, anyway?
You were going to be a fugitive
with Nygma and Penguin?
Well, I'm not exactly
the stay-at-home
and bake apple pie type.
Yeah, and running off on a submarine
seems like a great alternative.
Barbara, you can live here.
You can have this baby here.
Jim is not taking the baby away
from you.
You really believe that?
You really think Captain Jim Gordon
is gonna let a criminal raise
his kid?
People are already shooting
at my baby.
I have to protect him...
or her.
I have to be strong.
Hey. Being strong does not mean
you have to be a criminal.
Jim will help you.
And so will I, if you let me.
Well, that's just weird.
I know.
Hey, baby, this is your auntie Lee.
Mommy tried to kill her once.
Maybe twice.
All right.
Okay, that's enough of that. Come on.
We gotta keep moving.
I think this is happening now.
What's going on in there?
This is Bruce Wayne.
Can anyone read me?
Does anyone at the GCPD read me?
This is Bruce Wayne.
Can anyone read me?
Bruce. It's Alfred.
Where the devil are you? Over.
Some abandoned mansion
in North Side Park.
- On my way.
- No.
I'll get out myself.
I need you to get to the clinic.
The clinic?
It's Ra's al Ghul's daughter, Alfred.
She wants revenge.
She mutated Eduardo Dorrance
and sent him after Barbara.
Oh, gosh.
I'm fine.
I need you to get to Barbara
and the baby.
Now, you're going to feel
a slight discomfort.
That's the stimulant I've given you
to prepare your muscles.
You'll need it for what's comes next.
Which...
I'm afraid is going to be
excruciating.
Do you feel that?
Yes.
There's that fighting spirit
I've always admired so much.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
there's an alarm I must sound.
What the hell are you doing?
Checking to make sure Strange doesn't
have one of those chips in your head.
We gotta hurry up, get out of here,
before he trips the alarm.
Come on.
Alfred and GCPD are on their way
to the clinic.
- Where's Nyssa?
- I don't know.
But she's planning on using
the military to wipe out Gotham.
I can order them to stand down.
Then let's get you out of here.
She's beautiful.
Congratulations.
Hi, there.
Guess I have to figure out
what to call you.
Thank you.
Come on.
Get in the car now.
I'll hold him off.
Alfred and I got this.
Selina, get in the car.
- Selina, get back in the car!
- No!
Go.
Oh, my. Look at you.
You're big 'un ain't you?
Bloody baby.
Well then, let's see what you got!
Dirty bastard.
No!
Alfred.
Alfred? No.
Somebody help!
Somebody? Oh, no.
Atten-hut!
Welcome back, General.
Get me a secure line
to the mainland now.
Jim, hey.
Just got word from Lee.
She and Barbara made it out
of the clinic okay.
And your baby daughter, too.
Congratulations.
They're going to The Sirens.
You just had a baby girl, brother.
Say something.
Just can't believe it.
We won, didn't we? It's over.
We did.
And she's gonna have a better world
because of it.
She is.
- Mainland, sir.
- I promise.
- Is Alfred with them?
- Didn't say.
This is General Wade.
I am authorizing Special Order 3-8-6.
- No!
- Gotham City is lost.
Begin your bombing run on my order.
Wait, wait, wait.
Arrest them.
You can't do this.
Take them away.
You can't do this!
Okay, nice and slow.
Barbara Kean.
Run!
It's nice to finally meet you.
My name is Nyssa al Ghul.
I believe you knew my father.
I don't understand, how the general
could've been chipped?
I didn't see a scar
on the back of his neck.
- Did you?
- No.
Strange must have hidden it.
Nyssa let us escape.
She knew we'd bring the general here
and do her dirty work for her.
What now, Jim?
Son, if you're gonna stick a gun
in my face,
you should at least know
you're doing it wrong.
Come on, let's go.