NARRATOR:
Previously on Gotham:
I'm sorry you had to get mixed up in this
because I'm sure you're a good...
honest girl, really.
[LIZA GRUNTING]
- I'm gonna disappear.
- You can't do that.
- I wasn't asking.
- You can't. You have to come back with me.
When Detective Gordon finds the man
who killed my parents, you have to testify.
FALCONE:
I want these two alive for now.
You dare use my sainted mother
against me? You'll suffer for that.
Say your goodbyes quickly.
Miss Mooney has places to go.
Hello, Fish.
[COBBLEPOT LAUGHING]
[CHUCKLES]
Well, you must be the B-team.
We just handle transpo.
Bob will be taking care of you.
- Bob?
- One of our top guys.
You're in good hands.
Good morning.
- You're up early.
- I haven't made it to bed yet.
Word is you got caught
with Doc Thompkins in the locker room.
Strictly business.
- Any word on Fish?
- No.
Club's all shot up. Blood everywhere.
No sign of Fish. It's her own damn fault.
She played the game,
she knew the risks.
Sorry, I know you have a thing for her.
I don't got a thing for nobody.
My thing is for me.
If anyone can make it out of a scrape
like that, it's Fish. The woman's nails.
Come on. We got a case.
Yeah. So, what do we got?
Public service homicide. Vic's a douche.
Flass, Gordon. Gordon, Flass.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Flass works Narcotics.
Hence the bling and the no doubt expensive
yet somehow cheap-looking Italian suit.
Bullock. Still dressing in the dark
and smelling like a tap-house whore.
One of Flass's connections
tipped him off on the body.
- Tell Gordon about the kid.
- Pinky Littlefield.
Dealer from a crew known
as the Uptown Assassins.
He works this block. Well, at least he did.
- Any drugs on him?
- Didn't find any.
My big wild guess, deal gone bad.
Kid like this, bound to happen
sooner or later.
Like I said, public-service homicide.
Well, boys, I've got another case
I've got to attend to...
so if you don't need
any more hand-holding...
I'm gonna walk you out.
BULLOCK: Hey, unis think they may have
found a witness. Night janitor.
They're bringing him over.
- Jim, Mr. Winkler.
- Sir.
No need for formalities. Call me Leon.
Leon. We really appreciate
you stepping forward.
My wife Louisa always says
if you don't step forward, you step back.
- She sounds like a smart lady.
- Heh. Yeah. She is.
So, uh, do I give a statement?
A description of the killer?
I'm not sure how this works.
Would you be willing to come down
to the precinct? Work with a sketch artist?
That really is the best way to catch
the killer. It'd be a huge help.
Hmm. Of course.
Thank you, sir.
Yes, sweetheart. I'm still at the precinct.
I know.
Of course. Yeah.
But...
- Okay.
- They send in the sketch artist yet?
No, not yet.
Louisa, I have to go. Bye-bye.
But you did see the killer, right?
Uh, yes. That's what
I told the detectives earlier.
I'm sorry. Who are you? Agh! Ungh!
How the hell did this happen?
Security cameras inside and outside
were turned off.
Thoughts on the weapon?
What's strong enough to smash ships
but still fears the sun?
Can it with the riddles, Ed.
I don't have the patience today
or any day.
- Ice.
- Correct.
Gauging by the small circumference
of the wounds, the weapon is an ice pick.
Carbon steel. Six inches long.
Driven in deep enough...
it marked the surrounding tissue with an
imprint of a distinctive hexagonal handle.
It's not your standard kitchen fare.
Fun fact, gentlemen.
Mr. Winkler's wounds are the same as the
wounds on the victim from this morning.
- The drug dealer? Littlefield?
- Him. Same weapon.
Same killer. One would suppose.
Damn it. Right in our house.
Okay.
What is your name?
You know who I am.
It's just a formality.
I like to be sure.
- Bobnu
- Hmm?
Is that short for Robert?
You have any family, Robert?
Two lovely daughters.
I'm putting you down
as "Maria Mercedes Mooney" a.k.a. "Fish."
I'll be extracting a very sincere apology
from you today.
It shouldn't take too long.
How old are your girls, Robert?
I bet you they're some
ugly little creatures.
Heh.
[MOANS]
Now, come on, Fish.
No call for rudeness.
Only my friends call me Fish, darling.
And you and I, we're not friends.
Yet.
[FISH LAUGHING]
You go get him.
I gotta find the keys to the incinerator.
[HORN HONKING]
Hey, Marco.
Where's Fish Mooney?
How is anyone gonna trust us?
We can't protect people in our own house?
Upside is, place is crawling with criminals.
We got beaucoup suspects to choose from.
That's an upside?
Security cameras were turned off.
Could've been a cop. Probably was.
You do not even think something like that.
The second that those guys out there
hear that you're looking at a cop...
they are gonna turn on you.
Bullock's right. Point fingers,
you could jeopardize your reinstatement.
You need concrete evidence to even think
of accusing another officer of murder.
- I'll start with the guard duty logbook.
BULLOCK: Jim.
Winkler was my witness.
No way I'm letting this ride. I asked him
to come here. I'm gonna find his killer.
No matter who it is.
- Proceed with caution.
- Yes, ma'am.
No big moves without my say-so.
I do believe this is the second time
we've been around this block, Master Bruce.
Selina likes to hang out here.
It's worth doubling back.
Besides you got what you wanted.
I went out of town like you asked.
For weeks.
Yeah, well...
it wasn't safe here, was it?
The assassins weren't after me.
They were after her.
ALFRED: Yeah and we'll be back
on that plane, back...
to the bloody Alps,
first sign of trouble, I'll tell you.
Master Bruce.
- Master Bruce, get back in the car now.
- Can we walk around the block just once?
Then I'll get back in the car.
Please, Alfred.
- Once around the block and then home.
- Thank you.
Go risking your life like that, to get
whipped into a frenzy by the females.
- Why do you wanna start now?
- It's not like that.
IVY:
Out of my way.
Ivy?
Steady, Master Bruce.
Looks like she's got the mange.
Look who it is. Billionaire Bruce Wayne.
- Who are you? His bodyguard?
- If needs be, miss, yes.
What's in the bag?
It's for Selina.
- Have you seen her?
- Sure. I can give it to her if you want.
Perhaps you could pass on
a message for me?
- Tell her I'm looking for her?
- Twenty bucks.
Alfred.
Twenty bucks.
There we are, miss.
Delightful friends you have, Master Bruce.
Home.
[GASPS]
That's all you got?
You are gonna bore me to death, fellow.
That's impressive.
Different strokes, eh?
You know me, I can't stand hot spicy food,
but my wife, you know, she loves it.
Hotter the better.
Now, where, oh, where are we gonna begin?
Now, taking off a hand, that's devastating.
But I found...
that taking out a knee...
[PANTING]
You okay, Fish?
A page is missing from this logbook.
Now, that, in and of itself,
is grounds for dismissal from the force.
So my question to you is:
Who was on guard duty
outside of Interrogation this morning?
No idea, man.
Nobody's talking.
They're protecting their own.
- Or they just don't like you.
- Face it, Harvey.
Leon Winkler's killer is a cop.
Not proven.
Come on. You know these guys.
You know them since way back.
Give me some leverage. Give me an angle.
You really wanna work with a murderer?
Somebody gets whacked in the G.C.P.D.,
somebody's gonna get fired for this.
Not me, pal.
Grover.
We got a reliable guy.
Says it was you, pulled the page
from the guard duty logbook.
No way. Where did you get that?
- Who said that?
- Alvarez.
If he said that, that son
of a bitch is lying.
Why would he lie?
Look, six years ago, I had a thing
with his wife. Okay? Six years ago.
He is a vindictive bastard.
Well, look. That's none
of our business, huh?
Look at it from our point of view.
We gotta find the culprit.
Brass demands one.
But it wasn't me.
Then who was it?
Delaware. Anybody seen Delaware?
Saw him go to the garage.
Hey-
Delaware. Hey.
[TIRES SCREECH]
- You'll regret that.
- You were guarding Interrogation?
Screw off.
BULLOCK:
Jim.
Hell are you doing? You couldn't bring him
in here quietly, put him in some backroom?
You making some kind of statement?
Damn right I am.
I warned you, and you didn't listen.
I have evidence.
The same drugs I found in Littlefield's
shoe at the crime scene yesterday morning.
That evidence is part of an ongoing
undercover Narco investigation.
You expect us to believe that?
Jim, Marco's been knee-deep
in the uptown drug trade for months.
Got a matrix of undercovers that put their
lives at stake for this investigation.
Your little stunt gets out,
you unravel the whole operation.
Not to mention, the search was illegal.
So we're ignoring Delaware's involvement.
Is that what we're doing, cap?
No, but this isn't the way, Jim. I'm
turning over the case to Internal Affairs.
IA?
Two old drunks in the basement?
You and Bullock are no longer investigating
the Winkler murder.
What about the Littlefield murder? Or wait.
Is that also a part of an ongoing
Narco investigation?
All you, buddy.
Let me know if you need any help.
I'm sorry about the confusion.
[GASPS]
- Can I help you with something?
- Did you know, Miss Kringle...
that the earliest greeting cards
dated back to Germany in the 1400s?
I have a lot of work to do.
This is for you.
- Doesn't say anything weird, does it?
- No, ma'am.
[CONSTRUCTION NOISE
IN BACKGROUND]
[GROANING]
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Take it easy. Take it easy.
I'm fine, Butch.
Here. Try this.
[MOANS]
- You okay?
- I'm starving.
[RAUGHS]
Oh. You are one tough cookie.
Thank you, Butch.
Listen, we should hit the road. I figure
we've got about an hour before Falcone...
I'm not going anywhere
until I find Penguin.
He told Falcone about Liza.
Whoa. Boss, I don't know if you remember, but
as of last night, we don't have any men.
Falcone's gonna have
the whole city looking for us.
I'm not going anywhere
until I cut Penguin's throat.
One...
two...
three.
[GASPS]
What do you think, Mother?
Oh. It's beautiful.
It's so classy.
Like an opera house.
[GASPS]
[RAUGHS]
Oh!
A chandelier.
Like home.
Someone left a scarf.
Looks beautiful with my dress.
Finders keepers.
And now, you are in charge of this club.
Spoil my surprise.
No. Oh, no, no, please.
No, don't be angry, no.
Such good news.
My boy has a club.
Will have a club.
There's still a few loose ends to tie up,
but soon, it will be mine.
I am so proud of you...
I could spit.
[BOTH LAUGH]
BULLOCK: Listen, Jim.
There's something I gotta tell you.
A few years ago, Flass and his people
started busting drug dealers...
taking over their stash houses,
running them themselves.
Now? You tell me this now?
Look, I respond to crises as they arise.
I'm not a forward planner like you.
I didn't wanna get you riled up.
But I'm telling you now
because I want you to stop.
Flass is protected.
By who?
Serious people.
Really high up. Big money. For all I know,
the commissioner gets a piece too.
You mess with Flass,
you can forget going back to Arkham.
These guys do not play.
These stash houses,
think you can get me a location on them?
Did you not hear a word I said?
The stash houses can give us evidence
linking Flass to Littlefield's murder.
We nail him for Littlefield, we can nail him
for Winkler. I can't let it be, Harvey.
You should know that by now.
Mick. It's Harv.
Know that thing you and Donnie
were working on, the Flass thing?
I need your help.
Prime spot for a stash house.
Yeah.
GORDON:
Delaware.
Hand over the boxes.
- You don't learn, do you?
- Get out of my face.
[ALL GRUNTING]
DELAWARE:
Hey. Hey!
No need to rough each other up, gentlemen.
I got a warrant.
Giving us the legal right
to search and seizure.
It seems this warehouse was being used
as a home base for the Uptown Assassins.
He expects us to believe you got a signed
warrant to clear your own stash house?
On the commissioner's request.
Signed by Judge Bam-Bam.
I guess you don't have a leg
to stand on, Homicide.
- So, what's our next step?
- Next step?
We got nothing to tie Flass
to the drugs or the murders.
Murder.
Just one.
Internal Affairs just ruled Winkler's death
as a suicide.
They're releasing the body to his wife.
Leon was so very happy.
This just can't be right.
[SOBBING]
Can't be right...
A suicide?
He stabbed himself in the back
with an ice pick? That's absurd.
A ruling this quick means
the commissioner was involved.
Screw the commissioner.
Going forward with this
puts all of our jobs at risk.
Look. I wanna help you, Jim.
There are people here in G.C.P.D.
who wanna help you.
- So why don't they?
- They have.
I have, and we learned the hard way.
With men like Flass, you need more
than words. You need results.
And that's not gonna happen
this time around, so do us all a favor...
and move on to the next vic.
Please.
[WIDOW SOBBING]
Where are you going?
Back in an hour.
Listen to this. This is classic.
- Stop it. Come on. Give me that.
FLASS: Hey. Come on.
"Dear, Miss Kringle.
Your eyes are as green as a meadow.
Your smile is as bright as the sun.
Your skin is as white as a snowflake.
It seems like your life is fun."
[ALL LAUGH]
- Really?
- Oh, hey.
It's the writer himself.
FLASS:
Whew.
It's a real piece of work
you got there, perv.
I wouldn't quit your day job if I were you.
Roger, dodger.
- Roger, dodger?
- Stop it.
What a creep.
[BAND PLAYING SLOW JAZZ]
One, two, three.
One, two, three
- One, two...
- Oh!
Now. Now you are getting it.
You are so graceful for such a big man.
Isn't he graceful, Oswald?
Yes, Mother.
Jim.
Welcome.
Come in.
Another handsome man at the party.
I am so lucky.
This is Jim Gordon, the detective
friend I was telling you about.
So nice to meet a friend of Oswald's.
I am Gertrud Kapelput.
Nice to meet you too, Mrs. Kapelput.
Uh, Mother, Jim and I
have very important business.
No. How sad. How sad.
A little soon to be celebrating,
don't you think?
Well, don't just stand there. Sit.
This won't take long.
I insist. Sit.
Heh.
I'm so very glad you called, Jim Gordon.
It's been far too long
since we've seen each other.
I was beginning to think
you'd forgotten about me.
I need a favor.
Do you know anything
about a Narcotics detective, Arnold Flass?
- I've heard the name.
- I'm investigating him for murder.
But I've hit a wall.
He's too well-connected.
I figured since Maroni
runs the drug trade...
maybe you could find somebody
with the goods on Flass.
- But...
- Shh!
Say no more.
Favor is done.
I'll make some calls.
And what do I owe you in return?
Friends don't owe friends, silly.
They just do favors because they want to.
Because they're friends.
- Nobody gets hurt.
- Of course.
No one gets hurt.
Champagne?
[GLASSES CLINK]
ZSASZ:
Oh, dear me.
What happened here?
- Call Falcone.
- No kidding.
Thank you. Thank you, boys. Lovely.
Why? I am dancing still. Shh.
- You may go.
- Oh, why you make them go?
Gabe, on your way
to help my dear friend Jim...
could you be a gentleman
and take Mother home?
Sure thing, boss.
Come on, Mrs. K.
A palace.
My boy has a palace.
Such a good boy.
Don't worry.
I will be back.
[CHUCKLING]
[LAUGHING]
Ladies and gentlemen, friends...
celebrities from around the world.
My name is Oswald Cobblepot.
Here we are at last.
It is with deep and sincere pleasure
that I bid you welcome...
to the official grand opening
of my newest night spot, the...
[CLAPPING]
Not bad.
I do believe you need to project more.
Just to create a bit more excitement
for the audience.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome...
to Fish Mooney's.
Like that.
What kind of weirdo
plays chess with himself?
Don't you have a butler
to do that kind of stuff with you?
He's making lunch.
I got your message.
I'm glad you're safe.
Alfred made me go out of town.
Switzerland.
We have a house there. Chalet, I guess.
- A chalet?
- It's basically a house.
Why did you want to see me?
We're friends, aren't we?
You've been driving around looking for me,
sending messages.
What's up?
I got you a present.
It looks like the town we stayed in.
Whoa.
Thank you.
Also, I wanted to know if, um...
If you wanted to stay here in my house.
- Why?
- I figure we could help each other out.
You can help me find the man
who killed my parents...
and I can give you a
better place to live.
What's better about it?
Listen, kid.
Chill.
I came here to tell you
to stop hassling me.
Hassling you?
Yeah.
You're beginning to bug me.
I thought we were friends.
Listen, I lied.
I didn't see who killed your parents.
I didn't see his face.
I don't understand.
I lied so I wouldn't get
locked up in juvie.
So it's no use buying me presents
or sending me messages...
or trying to hang out.
There's no point because I can't help you.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Pinky Littlefield was light for two weeks.
You don't pay up, there's consequences.
Flass killed him to send the message.
Please, I swear that's all I know.
- You sure?
- I swear, man. I swear.
I believe you.
[GASPING]
- I think I need something more tangible.
- No, no, no. Please, no.
No! No, please no.
I swear, man. I swear.
[GRUNTING]
FISH:
How are you liking show business now?
Please, Miss Mooney.
You're making a mistake.
I beg of you.
Let me speak.
I know we've had our differences.
- Mm.
- We could combine our forces.
Think how we'd fool everyone.
Me? Work with you?
I found you.
I made you.
When you walked in here,
you were a sad little wannabe.
Remember that, Butch?
You were so afraid.
Shook like a leaf in fall.
You're a servant.
An umbrella boy.
You're a nobody.
This nobody still outfoxed you
at every turn.
I was working for Falcone the whole time...
and you didn't have the sense to see it.
[GUNSHOT]
ZSASZ:
Hello.
It seems like Mooney's
is the place to be today.
[YELPS]
BUTCH: Come on. Come on.
- No.
Come on.
[LAUGHING]
GO, g0!
Here.
[YELLS]
You gotta go. I'll slow him down.
FISH: No, no.
- Go.
Hello, again.
[YELLS]
Where is she?
[CHUCKLES]
What do you think, girls?
Should we kill him...
or should we take him home to play with?
[KRINGLE CLEARS THROAT]
Mr. Nygma?
- Miss Kringle.
- Am I interrupting?
Yes. I'm surgically removing the onions
from my takeout, so if you don't mind.
Mr. Nygma, I owe you an apology.
I didn't give Arnold the card.
He found it in my desk.
He has a strange sense of humor.
I thought your card was...
very, um...
thoughtful...
.“lguess.
Anyway...
I'm sorry.
- Miss Kringle, would you...?
- No, no, no.
Please, don't say anything else, just...
Please.
There's hope.
What's this?
Murder weapon and a tape
of Delaware rolling on Flass.
Smart cookie, that one.
Flass gave him the ice pick to throw away.
Delaware kept it
in case he had to cover his own ass.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
[BRUCE SNIFFLES]
Master Bruce?
She was lying.
Oh.
I see.
Shall I get a broom, then?
Or would you rather continue crying
over the shattered fragments...
of your young dreams?
Yes, Alfred.
A broom.
Very good, Master Bruce.
BRUCE:
I'll find other leads.
No doubt.
I knew she was a wrong one.
Arnold Flass.
You're under arrest
for the murder of Leon Winkler.
Keep walking, mutt. You got nothing.
That's 20 years upstate right there.
Delaware gave you up.
Jimbo?
You really think these guys
are gonna let you arrest me? Hm?
These are my friends.
- This is my house.
- This is not your house.
You're a drug dealer and a murderer.
You don't belong here.
You don't deserve the badge.
Heh. You believe this crap?
How long you been here?
A few months?
Why don't you come preach to me
in five years.
He murdered Leon Winkler.
An innocent man...
who trusted us.
Who trusted this.
WOMAN: That's right.
MAN 1: Yeah.
MAN 2:
Yeah.
Enough to step forward
and help us solve a case.
A man who died
so Detective Flass could protect himself.
IA ruled it a suicide.
I'm arresting this man.
Get real, dumb-ass. I'm protected.
GORDON: You can help me,
or you can try and stop me, either way...
I'm doing my duty.
Back off. I'm protected. Get out of here.
Shut up, Flass.
Arnold Flass,
you're under arrest for murder.
What the hell are you doing?
Are you crazy?
- Read him his rights.
- You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
- If you cannot afford one...
FLASS: You got nothing!
Thanks, captain.
Here.
So, what's the plan?
I'm gonna leave town,
lay low for a while.
I'm gonna come back and kill Penguin...
when the time is right.
Listen.
You know
I have your best interests at heart.
- Don't come back.
- No.
You will see me again.
And in the meantime, do me a favor.
Find Butch...
and if he's alive, help him.
I Will.
See you soon.
Be good.
Always.
- Good night.
- Good night, detective.
Yo.
A big guy visit you?
Give you the package I sent?
Yeah. Thanks, it was...
So this... This means we're even?
I ratted out Flass like you wanted.
So now you back off. Right?
Nothing more's gonna happen to my wife.
My family's safe?
- I don't understand what you're saying.
- Okay. Okay.
No worries. Look.
Never mind I pressed.
I won't say nothing to no one.
I'll pretend this conversation
neverhappened.
Okay? Just...
keep my wife and kids out of it.
I'm begging you.
Please.
[English - US - SDH]