GORDON: Previously on Gotham...
I'm assuming
the captaincy of Gotham Central.
HARVEY: You just better hope you can
pay up when your bill's due.
And it'Il come due.
ALFRED: Let me know how I can help you.
BRUCE: Stop trying to be my father.
(GROANS)
ALFRED: Master Bruce, I'm so sorry.
Alfred, you're fired.
This is your turf now.
NYGMA: You're new leader of The Narrows.
I am in control!
(LAUGHS WICKEDLY)
You're in love with Lee Thompkins,
you pathetic loser.
Shut up!
Where are they?
MAN: That's powerful stuff.
It can get in your DNA.
TABITHA: You're gonna
remember me, Butch...
(CLANGS)
I'm sorry.
I tried.
BUTCH: What the hell happened to me?
(eunsnor)
GORDON: That was you.
You sent this monster to my city?
HARVEY: Iheard you got the Pyg.
Turned out well.
You didn't even need me...
They, uh, believe in you.
Don't let them down.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(MUSIC PLAYING ON RECORD)
WOMAN: How can I help you,
Captain Gordon?
I assure you this is
a respectable establishment.
Relax, I'm not here to shut you down.
I'm looking for someone.
We are trusted for our discretion.
Mmm-hmm.
Was he here?
Who did he spend the night with?
He specifically
requested Tallulah and Pip.
That's him.
That's Bullock.
If he comes back,
please tell him to call me.
(TRAIN PASSING)
(UNLOCKING DOOR)
It was an old Chinese guy's place,
filled with rare drugs and stuff.
He split town. Place is empty now.
Where are the drugs?
You said there'd be drugs.
Holy crap.
What the...
Don't touch it, dude.
(SQUELCHING)
MAN: You just woke it up.
Hey, Tiffany,
who's the stiff at the counter?
New customer, nice guy, polite.
Leave him alone, okay?
Hey, new QUY?
Do I know you?
No, mate. Most definitely not.
Not from around here, huh?
And what gave you that idea?
Here, miss. Thank you very much.
Keep the change.
That stiff's shoes
are worth more than my car.
(DOOR opens)
LEE: I understand times are tough.
I understand you need to make a living.
But it's time to stop
punishing each other
for the situation
the city has put you in.
Instead of stealing from those
hurting as much as you,
this community needs to start
protecting one another.
We do what we do to survive!
ALL: Yeah.
And is that all you want, all of you?
Just to survive every day,
one day at a time?
Listen, Doc, down here,
it's every man for himself!
That's the way it's always been!
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
How many of you have kids?
I've been running a clinic down here
for the last nine months,
and I have been treating
your kids for things like TB,
hepatitis. pertussis, pneumonia.
Diseases that don't belong
in a modern city.
But there are no
functioning hospitals down here,
and doctors are too afraid to visit.
You're not stealing from the rich.
- You're stealing from each other.
- (TICKING)
You are fighting each other,
and you are living in a prison
of your own construction.
MAN: Well, hello, beautiful.
What's your name?
Ivy.
My name was Ivy.
Well, Ivy.
What's a nice girl like you
doing in a place like this?
(SCREAMS)
(MUFFLED GROANS)
(SHUSHING)
Well, that's a hell of a thing.
Let's
(nooa CLOSES)
Extraordinary.
MAN: Hey.
Little Lord Fuddy-duddy.
It's Fauntleroy.
What?
Little Lord Fauntleroy
by Frances Hodgson Burnett.
A tad saccharin for my tastes...
Shut up. Wallet, watch, jewelry.
Absolutely not.
I mean, you're a big man,
but you're out of shape.
And what, you're three beers in already?
GORDON: That's enough!
Get out of here.
Not who I was expecting to see here.
Likewise.
GORDON: Is Bruce with you?
No.
What are you doing here?
Well, it's not too bad down here really.
I mean, you can rent a lovely space
for next to nothing,
if you move around and you're patient.
You live here?
Nearby.
It's a long story.
Give me the chance to prove to you
(MAN COUGHS)
that I can turn The Narrows into a place
where you don't have to steal
from one another to live.
Yes.
CROWD: Yeah.
Yeah.
(CROWD CLAPPING AND CHEERING)
(nemme)
(ENGINE REWING)
(GRUNTS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(ALL COUGHING)
AII right.
Go, come on.
Go, go, 9°-
Go. Go.
Everyone, move away from the building!
(ALARM BLARING)
- (SIREN WAILING)
- UNDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
GORDON: There's your mom. Go ahead.
Mommy!
That's the last one.
- Building's clear.
- Okay.
- (MAN COUGHING)
- Oxygen. Please.
OFFICER: Over here, over here.
Listen up.
We need to set up a perimeter,
and start interviewing
witnesses. Let's go.
ALFRED: Well, they seem on it.
Appears like you turned around
the GCPD, Captain Gordon.
LUCIUS: Gordon!
Quite a mess.
Thought you might need help.
Thank you. We need to find
the source of the blast.
Alfred, I do want to talk to you,
but I have to deal with this first.
- You have my number. Call me.
- AII right.
Let's go.
GORDON: I'II ask you one more time.
Why were you here?
It was a wine and cheese mixer.
(CHUCKLES)
Laugh all you want.
They were trying to kill you.
This is The Narrows, bud.
That's every day around here.
MAN: Yeah. just another beautiful day
in The Narrows, Cap.
LUCIUS: Gordon.
Get him out of here.
What you got?
Well, it seems like
a piece of a toy plane.
And, yet, if I'm not mistaken,
it's covered in
plastic explosive residue.
There's also the remnants of
what seems like a trigger wire.
Whoever built it,
takes pride in their work
and has considerable talent,
historical knowledge even.
Look at the detail.
Pretty elaborate.
I can think of easier ways
to kill a room full of criminals
than with a toy plane.
Perhaps, it was intended
to fly to someone specific
and not destroy the whole room.
Like an assassination attempt?
If so, who was the target?
Whoever this was,
needs to be made an example of.
I mean, can't they tell
you were trying to help.
- Maybe it wasn't one of them.
- Oh, of course, it was.
Ijust think that maybe
the best thing for The Narrows
is to burn it to the ground! Start over.
Well, that would certainly
suit everyone, wouldn't it?
I'm just saying someone tried
to blow you to bits,
and I bet they're gonna try it again!
So I'm going to find them,
and when I do,
Grundy's going to
pull them apart, limb by limb!
Isn't that right. big fella?
Hey, Grundy?
You okay?
Okay.
(NYGMA SIGHS)
(DOOR opens)
- (SLASHES)
- (SCREAMS)
My name is Butch.
(eunsnor)
Butch Gilzean.
MAN: There he is.
(APPLAUDING)
That was so brave, sir.
It's Alfred, please.
It's the good stuff.
Our manager hides it in his drawer.
ALFRED: Thank you.
On the house.
(SIGHS)
What you did out there,
running into a burning building...
Well, I wouldn't have done it.
No hard feelings, eh?
No.
Good man.
Thanks.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
ALFRED: What happened there?
Ifell. No big deal.
There are a few places in the city
that collect and sell antique toys,
but only this one
also manufactures its own.
(BELLS CHIMING)
(TOYS WHIRRING)
(TOY CACKLING)
Um...
Can I help you, gentlemen?
LUCIUS: Yes.
We were wondering
if you recognized this plane?
One of yours?
Where did you find it?
Yours or not?
It's a pine and lead
1944 Mustang replica.
We have these, yes,
but it's been altered.
To carry a bomb, yeah.
GORDON: How many people work here?
Just me and my father.
GORDON: And where is he?
Upstairs.
Go get him.
LUCIUS: Got a hunch you'd like to share?
No.
Just a bad feeling.
Of course, I'd happily be wrong.
(SIGHS) Who buys these things?
GORDON: I'm not sure
any of it is for sale.
I don't see price tags on anything.
LUCIUS: Any word from Harvey?
Not yet.
Think he'll return to the GCPD?
To be honest, I'm not sure.
LUCIUS: Um...
- Gordon...
- Get down!
(GUNSHOTS)
ROBOT: Seek and destroy.
Seek and destroy.
- Seek and destroy.
- (BEEPING)
You've got to be kidding me.
(some BEEPS)
Wait, wait. No, no, wait,
wait, wait. Come on, he's...
He's my father.
I can't let you hurt him.
I swear to God, I had no idea
what my father was up to.
There's a machine gun built into
the wooden hand of this nutcracker here.
Excuse me
if I find that hard to believe.
I didn't know, okay?
My father, he hates to be disturbed.
He also built a bomb that almost
blew up a building this morning.
We need to know why.
- Who was the target?
- I don't know.
LUCIUS: Has anyone suspicious
been here recently,
asking for specialty toys?
No one comes in here,
this is just his workshop.
He mostly works at night.
See, he boxes the things he makes and
ships them.
What?
Like, three days ago,
I thought I heard him talking
to someone behind his door.
His voice was low, like
he didn't want me to hear him.
Did you hear a name?
I heard my father repeat something.
Like he was confirming a name.
He said, "The Doc."
The Doc? Who's that?
I have no idea.
(SIREN WAILING)
Hey, can you deal with this?
I'm gonna talk to somebody
who might know who the Doc is.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
This place is killing you.
- (HONKING)
- WOMAN: Honey, the taxi is here.
MAN: Let's go.
WOMAN: If we are late...
MAN: We need to pack the other stuff...
WOMAN: Okay. Of course it's my fault.
MAN: You only need, like,
five pairs of shoes.
WOMAN: Come on.
Let's go. Let's go.
- (CAR noon CLOSES)
- (ENGINE STARTS)
(TV REMOTE CLICKS)
REPORTER ON TV: the truck overturned
spilling its load of gasoline
into Gotham's Nature Park.
The GCPD is warning all citizens
to remain clear of the...
MAN ON TV: causing gas to leak into
the water supply
which then ignited,
setting fire to the residenfs kitchen
which set off a 24-acre blaze.
Wayne Enterprises can 't...
WOMAN ON TV: Now, there's no reason
to ever be alone in this city again.
The Sirens Club is back, with a passion.
Ladies drink for free whilst men don't.
You'll like it. It's nice.
I know you.
AII of you.
And I'm pretty sure I hated you.
(WOMAN LAUGHS)
You're funny, Alfred.
I honestly haven't laughed this much
in a very long time.
I'm glad I'm able
to amuse you, Ms. Gale.
- Your accent, I love it.
- (DOG BARKING)
Where are you from?
A charming place called
Whitechapel in East End, London.
Go back often?
No.
Sadly, no.
Well, perhaps, you should.
Why did you leave?
Well, I was in the military.
I was really proud to serve my country,
not so proud of some of the things
we had to do, though.
And when I left,
I found myself. um, lost.
You know, it was a tough transition.
Then I met this man who changed my life.
He brought me to America, gave me a job.
And where is that man now?
He's dead.
And I miss him.
I miss him very much.
(VEHICLE ARRIVING)
(BRAKES SCREECHING)
Who's that, your boyfriend?
MAN: Hey, you didn't call me back.
I was heading to the diner
to pick you up.
Oh, that wasn't necessary.
Alfred was kind enough to walk me home.
Thank you, sir.
I hate to think of Tiff alone
on these streets after dark.
(WOMAN SCREAMS)
Drop the act, sunshine.
I've seen her face!
It was your idea, was it?
Wear her hair down
and cover the bruising?
Oh, my. What a little tattletale
she's been.
- What am I to do with her?
- TIFFANY: Stop it!
Don't make things worse.
Ican handle it.
Listen to me! Listen! Listen to me!
You stay away from him.
He's dangerous. Let me walk you home.
I'II be fine.
MAN: Oh, Tiffany, what did I tell you
about talking to strange men?
It's time to go.
We have so much to discuss.
You be careful.
(ENGINE REWING)
(noe YELPS)
There was a fatality at the bomb site.
Ayoung man found in a room
below the impact site and...
- Well, perhaps I should just show you.
- Of course.
Yeah. (CLEARS THROAT)
The cause of death was ingested poison.
Now, see the discoloration
around the mouth?
LUCIUS: The poison entered
directly into the bloodstream?
But see, that's not what's unusual.
There seems to be something
emanating from within the victim's body.
Time of death was several hours ago,
but this foreign, organic material
is not only alive but growing.
LUCIUS: Seems like moss.
CORONER: Toxicodendron radicans.
Poison ivy?
Yes, and microscopic at first
but multiplying, growing.
Living off the victim's dead tissue.
Fascinating.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
BARBARA: So the commercial worked.
We're back and busier than ever.
Good, 'cause that's the last time
you're getting me on camera.
Who's that?
BARBARA: Who's who?
- (GLASS SHATTERING)
- (BARBARA SIGHS)
Selina, will you tell
those brats over there
to keep it down?
SELINA: Why me?
Because you're a partner now,
and also. the one paying
is a friend of yours.
Bruce.
What's up?
Champagne?
- No.
- Why?
They don't card you here,
and even if they did,
this is Gotham.
By "they" you mean me.
This is my place, too.
- Really?
- Yeah.
So you wanna tell
your little brat pack here
to reel it in a little,
or should I call your keeper?
Go ahead, call Alfred, he won't answer.
Why?
'Cause I fired him.
It was time to move on,
you know what I'm saying?
(SCOFFS)
You sure about that?
- I'm not buying it.
- Not buying what?
This.
You.
Firing Alfred.
What are you trying to prove?
MAN 1: I saw her first.
MAN 2: The lady was speaking with me.
(MEN GRUNTING)
Hey. hel/-
(MAN GROANS)
(GLASS SHATTERS)
Silly boys.
I'm really not sure what got into them.
You should leave.
Well, that's awfully rude.
But you always were.
Who is that woman?
She seems to know you.
Who cares?
Redheads, they're all crazy, am I right?
Ivy.
I like what you've done with the place.
Thank you. Though, it was hardly
a challenge
after what that crazy bird
passed for as taste.
What brings you here, my love?
Actually, you know,
I'm s0 proud to say that
I seem to maintain a very good
relationship with all my exes.
- You...
- Leave me off that list.
Hmm. What can I do you for, Jimmy?
The Doc? You know him?
Oh.
The Doc.
I believe he was the target
of an assassination attempt
in The Narrows this morning.
Do you now? And you want
to protect the Doc?
Iwanna know
who wanted to kill him and why.
You know him or not?
Oh, I know the Doc.
Dangerous character.
Someone like that,
you might wanna shoot first
then ask questions later.
Something you're good at.
- Where is he?
- With Ed Nygma.
They're partners.
- Where?
- The Narrows.
Place called Cherry's.
Careful, Jim.
Sometimes we search for things
we don't wish to find.
- (CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Harpen what's up?
HARPER: I'm at a murder scene
in The Narrows.
I'm busy, can you handle it?
You're gonna wanna
check this out in person.
I have the suspect in custody.
Alfred Pennyworth.
(HANGS UP)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
HARPER: Beaten to death.
Local girl.
Garbage collectors found her
about an hour ago,
she lived with her boyfriend
who was at work all night.
He told us that him and Pennyworth
got into it earlier.
Says that he was trying to keep him
separate from his girlfriend,
says that he made advances
towards the victim.
According to him, Pennyworth got rough.
Rough? That doesn't sound like him.
Come on, you and I both have seen
Alfred lose his temper.
There's more.
This was found next to the body.
It's an SAS signet ring.
Impressions of it
are on the victim's face.
My God.
Thanks.
Give us a minute.
Is this yours?
- Yes, but I...
- You hit this girl?
No.
How could you even ask that?
It was the boyfriend.
I mean, he's beat her before,
now he's gone and bloody killed her.
He says you were fighting with him.
Because he beat her!
I swear, he's a liar.
AII right, calm down.
You're in enough trouble as it is.
The last thing you need to do
is lose your temper.
Who was this girl to you?
She was a friend.
Just a friend.
What, you just met her?
Well, I know you find this
hard to believe, Gordon,
but we connected.
She was a beautiful, kind soul.
Her murderer's name is Rooney, right.
- Gil Rooney.
- He has an alibi.
I swear to God, I'm gonna kill
that son of a bitch!
Calm down.
Take a breath.
Go with Harper to the precinct.
Make a statement.
I'II find you later, yeah?
And you're gonna arrest
Rooney as well, yeah?
- He will make a statement, yes.
- HARPER: Cap.
Got a witness who saw
Pennyworth and the boyfriend
getting into it.
- She saw the whole thing.
- GORDON: AII right.
Take Alfred back to the precinct.
I'II come by after my last stop.
Okay, where is he?
Damn it.
(MAN CLEARS THROAT)
Tabitha.
Butch?
Oh, my God, it worked.
It hurt, I'II tell you that.
What happened to you?
And who turned you into this thing?
BUTCH: I don't remember much.
I remember Barbara
shooting me in the head.
Something in that swamp brought me back.
I'm a monster.
(SIGHS)
I came here...
Butch, tell me.
I came here
because the one thing
that's still very clear
in this thick head of mine
is my feelings for you.
I still love you, Tabby.
(SIGHS)
Okay.
Goodbye, Tabby.
- (Thank you for waiting.
- UNDISTINCT CHATTER)
It's worth it, you'll see.
Believe in her passion,
and your champion, she'II be.
Bombs can't stop her, nor bullets, too.
'Cause she's here to speak out
and fight for you.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Ready to battle,
ready to rock.
People of The Narrows,
here's the Doc.
(CROWD CHEERING)
CROWD: (CHANTING)
Doc, Doc, Doc.
This morning, someone tried to kill me.
(CROWD EXCLAIMING)
Maybe it was someone from the outside,
maybe it was one of you.
CROWD: No, no way.
LEE: You know what? I don't know.
And I don't care.
But what I do know
is that someone did not like
what I was saying.
Now why would the idea
of a united Narrows
scare people?
I'II tell you why.
Because a united Narrows
is a strong Narrows.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Guess what?
They should be scared.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Magnificent, isn't she?
- It's been forever, right?
- I should bust you, right now.
Oh, come on, Jim, don't be grumpy.
Your ex has my full support.
She's really gonna
change things around here.
Someone hired Griffin Krank
to kill her this morning.
You really think they won't do it again?
Krank?
A toy maker but also an assassin.
(CHUCKLES)
That is so Gotham.
Because together we have
the power to change our lives.
CROWD: Yeah!
MAN: That's right.
LEE: Imagine a hospital,
imagine schools.
Imagine these slums torn down.
(CROWD CHEERING)
Your children deserve better.
Your children deserve life!
(CHEERING)
Yeah!
(CROWD CHEERING)
Jim.
Doc.
I like to think of that
as a sign of respect.
Not just a lack of imagination.
How long you been back?
Awhile.
I wish you would have contacted me.
I've been busy.
I can see that.
You look great.
You look the same.
Are you here to arrest someone?
- Me?
- (NYGMA CHUCKLES)
I'm here because someone wants you dead.
The assassin's still on the loose,
as is the person who hired him.
You're not safe.
It's Gotham, is anyone ever safe?
S0, you're partners with Ed, huh?
Why?
I'm right here.
Why not?
Wouldn't have been my first choice.
But the universe has funny ways.
Still here.
I'II see you around, Jim.
I'm gonna take a look around.
That's...
Oh, boy.
I've been trying to get to you.
(PANTING)
You shouldn't be here,
you're a wanted man.
Better stay cool on me.
I've got friends...
- (GROANS)
- That was for Tiffany.
(GROANS)
- And that was for me.
- Help me!
This man killed my girlfriend.
He's a maniac.
- (GLASS SHATTERS)
- (GROANS)
You're making this too easy.
I'll just tell the cops
this was self-defense.
(MEN GROANING)
Sorry, it took me so long,
I was in thejohn.
I liked you better
when you were making tea.
(PANTING)
Harvey.
What the bloody hell are you doing here?
I work here.
Don't say it like that,
this place has history.
I love bartending, it involves
two of my favorite things,
- drinking and ignoring people.
- (CHUCKLES)
Who are these jokers?
Oh, he's a bloody murderer.
Then call a cop, I'm a bartender.
No, he's the murderer.
- I have an alibi.
- HARVEY: Oh! Yeah?
Let me guess,
one of these guys is your alibi?
- What do you say now, pal?
- Oh, I'm not an alibi.
I'Il call it in.
(CREAKING)
IW: Hi, kitty-cat.
You suck at following people.
By the way.
Ivy?
In the flesh.
Just different flesh.
What happened to you?
(SCOFFS)
Something wonderful.
(GROANS SOFTLY)
Can you feel that?
Coursing through your veins.
It's my essence.
Is your head swimming?
Your mouth drying up?
It lives within me now.
This power.
(GROANING)
Drink.
It'II counteract the toxin.
It took me a few tries,
but it'II work.
(COUGHS)
Sag?
(SELINA PANTING)
You have to trust me.
You've gone crazy.
No, I haven't.
I've been reborn.
And I will never be underestimated
or ignored ever again.
You always looked after me, Selina.
Now, let me help you.
Let's make Gotham our bitch.
Please, don't hurt me.
Why would I do that?
You tried to kill Lee.
Yeah, because you paid me to.
What?
You paid me good money to kill the Doc.
Used your alias. the Riddler.
(LAUGHING)
You want me to finish the job or not?
I came to you?
Paid in cash.
Said the Doc was holding you back,
she has to die, or you can't be free.
Oh, God.
I put myself at great risk for you.
Cops came to my workshop,
I can't go back there.
- My son...
- Let go of him!
Get down, Ed!
What the hell were you thinking,
going after him alone?
Well, clearly I wasn't thinking.
(NYGMA EXHALES)
Damn it.
Did he say anything about who hired him?
(STAMMERS) It was him, all him.
He was alone wolf. That's what he said.
He was afraid of what
Lee was gonna do to The Narrows.
Are you sure? His son said
he was talking to somebody
on the phone about the Doc.
(STAMMERS) He said that
he was calling around
trying to get support,
but no one would help him.
S0 he went alone. Crazy.
Crazy loon.
He told you all that?
Honestly, I'm not much of a threat.
I'm so lucky
that you came out here, Jim,
I don't know what I would have done.
This is Captain Gordon.
I have a suspect down,
outside Cherry's place,
on State Street, in The Narrows.
Send all available units.
Nice job, Ed, I guess.
I'm back. (LAUGHS)
(POLICE RADIO CHATTER)
OFFICER: Move.
HARVEY: Of all the beer halls
in the city, huh?
Who was it that that jerk killed?
(nooa CLOSES)
A lady.
[Ven] beautiful.
Kind, nice lady.
Then I drink to her.
(DOOR opens)
Heard the call on the radio.
Don't worry, we'II get him to talk.
How you been?
Awesome.
I've missed you.
Is that so?
Well, I haven't missed you.
I haven't missed begging you
not to do something
just to watch you go ahead
and do it anyway.
Haven't missed watching you
bang Falcone's daughter,
while she uses you
to get rid of Penguin.
S0mething's eating at you, Jim.
I don't know what it is,
but you're no good at keeping secrets.
And you're not gonna feel clean
till you get it off your chest.
You didn't come down here
because you miss me as a cop.
You came here to confess.
You want me. to be your priest.
Well, sorry, pal.
I'm not interested.
So hit the bricks,
take that with you.
English - SDH