Previously on Gotham:
I've been sober for a year.
That doesn't erase the things that I did.
But I still care about you.
Dear Jim, I thought I could be
strong and brave for you.
But I can't.
I'm going away for a while
to get myself together.
Trust me and I'll trust you.
In the meantime, each of your tariffs
will increase 25 percent.
Reach out to Saviano and Turski.
They're worried about ending up
like Bannion.
The old man is herding his sheep
toward me.
Arrogant clown!
Try to take me down!
You do not know where the edge is.
Arkham Asylum?
Security guard for nutjobs?
- It's that or quit.
- So quit.
That's what they want me to do.
Falcone, the mayor.
I'm not going to stop, Harvey.
I'm gonna get them.
If thou neglect'st, or dost unwillingly
What I command...
...I’ll rack thee with old cramps...
...fill all thy bones with aches...
...make thee roar,
that beasts shall tremble at thy din.
No, pray thee!
I must obey.
His art is of such power.
Such power.
"It would control my dam's god."
It would control my dam's god Setebos...
...and make a vassal of him.
So slave, hence!
Hence.
Full fathom five my father lies
Of his bones are coral made
Those are pearls that were his eyes
Nothing of him that doth fade
But doth suffer a sea-change
Into something rich and strange
Get back.
Stay down.
This is the fourth inmate outburst in as
many weeks as you've been stationed here.
I understand this is punishment duty
for you...
...but I expect professional standards,
nonetheless.
This is unacceptable, Gordon.
Unacceptable.
It was my fault, Mr. Lang.
The play was too upsetting.
We'll stick to comedies from now on,
I think.
Thank you, Nurse Duncan.
It's director...
...or Dr. Lang as you prefer.
Recreational activities are not
pertinent to this conversation.
Officer Gordon is responsible
for security on this wing...
...a task which he seems
unable to manage.
What have you to say about
this, Gordon?
This man needs medical attention.
I'd see to him myself, but there's rules.
I dispense meds, not treatment.
He needs a doctor.
Very well.
I'll send one in.
Any more incidents and I'll have you
placed on the remedial duty roster.
Think you can't fall any further?
Think again.
How is he?
He's fine. Will be.
And you?
I'm good. Few bruises.
What?
You're the famous detective Jim Gordon,
aren't you?
That's my name,
I'm not sure about famous.
Notorious then?
Nearer the mark.
Who are you?
Leslie Thompkins.
Doctor Thompkins.
You work here?
I'm not an inmate.
I haven't seen you
on infirmary duty before.
I work in the female ward. I come over
here when they're short-handed.
All the girls are talking about you.
Brave detective brought low
by fighting City Hall.
Ah. They say that, do they?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean
to make light of your situation.
It's okay.
Personally, I think what you're doing
is admirable.
I'm guarding lunatics.
No, you're not quitting.
Not yet.
Who are you?
Oh, sorry, I didn't mean to blurt all that
out like I did. It's none of my business.
Dr. Thompkins, you sure
this inmate is going to be okay?
He's fine.
He's just sleeping off his meds.
I'm trying.
Get a room, you guys.
I should go.
It was nice to meet you, Jim.
Likewise.
Ivy?
How are you doing?
I'm good. I'm good.
You look sick, like you need a doctor.
No doctor. Never ever again.
I'm fine, I'm just resting.
I got a place we can go, Ivy.
I'm shivery, is all.
Okay.
They're gone.
It's safe.
Sure?
Sure. Sure.
We'll only stay until you feel better.
Come and lay down on the couch there.
What if the real people come home?
There's dust on everything and, heh,
something smells rotten.
Nobody's coming.
Whose place is this, anyways?
How come you ask so many questions, Ivy?
I'm trying to help you.
Now, lie down and I'll get you a blanket.
Morning, gentlemen.
Have you considered my proposition?
- Uh, yeah, no.
- No?
We already pay enough.
Don Maroni set the rates last year.
And now I'm raising the prices.
Inflation is a bitch.
- Maroni said--
- Maroni, Maroni.
You're beginning to irk me.
You're talking to me, The Penguin.
You're a penguin, so what?
I called the cops on you.
It's The Penguin...
...and that was a very naive call
to make.
Hello, we own the cops on the waterfront.
Tell that to the cops, buddy.
Boys...
...why the frowns?
Jones?
Hey, Frogman.
Hey.
These are electrode wounds.
This man was given a crude,
invasive kind of electroshock therapy.
Metal needles were inserted into the brain,
electricity was applied to his frontal lobes.
What for?
It's used to modify aberrant behavior, but
in this case too much voltage was used...
...and his brain is completely fried.
Another under your watch, Gordon?
How did this happen?
You rushed into opening and now you're
running this place with skeleton staff...
...and zero surveillance in an unsafe
and unsecure 200-year-old maze.
Excellent excuses.
That's the nature of municipal operations.
You inherit problems and you use the
resources at hand to do what you can.
Well, our resources don't stretch far enough
to cover a criminal assault investigation.
We should call the GCPD.
Look, this is an in-house medical issue.
Is he still breathing?
Well, yes, but he is
effectively brain dead.
But...
...he's still breathing...
...unaided-
For all official purposes, well...
...he's still alive.
Keep him comfortable, doctor.
Officer Gordon...
...I want you to find out which one of our
charming inmates did this.
I want a report on my desk, Friday.
Another day, another dollar.
Really?
This is rather unusual and sinister,
isn't it?
Yes.
So who are we looking for?
What does it take to pull this off?
Uh, some basic knowledge
of human anatomy.
Um, basic electrical skills.
Circuit boards and wiring.
Is that all?
And the door keys, of course.
The door keys. Right.
No, man, I got my keys right here.
Look at me, Steven.
Look at me.
Tell me the truth.
Why you picking on me? There's five
other guards with keys to this wing.
True, and you're the only one who looks
and smells like a hunted animal.
Look, Steven,
whoever fried Frogman had keys.
Now, we've searched
all of the inmates' cells. No keys.
But I know they're out there
and I need to know where.
I'm backed up against a wall.
And I'm starting to lose my patience.
Do you understand?
That fight...
...during the play...
...right after I noticed my keys were gone.
You lose equipment, that's a big deal.
They'd dock me a week's pay.
- So I tracked down a spare set.
- Who took the keys?
I don't know.
Anyone could have taken them.
Walk away.
- Sorry--
- Walk away!
And then he raises our taxes,
after his money blows up.
Killed Bannion like he was nobody.
I'll say it.
...I wish something would happen to old man
Falcone before he comes after one of us.
- That's where this is going.
- Slow down.
Now, let's imagine-- God forbid anything happened to Falcone.
- -just for kicks.
Who would take over then?
Who'd take over? I do.
You?
Now, that never occurred to me.
What never occurred?
I'm next in line, seniority.
That's the way the system works.
That's how the system used to work,
back in the day.
It's a new dawn, new city.
I would believe we would need
some fresh thinking at the top.
And who is the fresh thinker
you got in mind?
Let me guess.
Who?
Her. She's talking about her.
Oh. Really?
You don't think I could run the family?
I don't know, why not?
Women's lib and all that.
But fair play, Jimmy is next in line.
Well, there's no need to argue.
This is all hypotheticals anyhow.
We're just talking, right?
Inmate 5075, Jack Gruber.
Inmate Gruber, did you take
Officer Wenger's keys?
You're looking into the sad demise
of the Frogman.
Frogman disrupted your play last night.
You didn't like him very much, did you?
I had no opinion of him.
He was called the Frogman
because he believed a giant bullfrog...
...lived inside his abdomen,
controlling his thoughts.
He was already dead.
I don't waste psychic energy on the dead.
Rape, murder.
You're no stranger to violence, Gruber.
Your psych evals say
you're a grade A sociopath.
Why should I take your word
for anything?
You shouldn't believe
everything you read, Jim.
May I call you Jim?
Did you take the keys?
Please. Search my cell
if you do not find me trustworthy.
But no, Jim, I did not take anyone's keys.
Thank you.
Guard.
Did you take officer Wenger's keys?
No.
Hey, hey!
Settle down.
Settle down!
Did you take officer--
Do you have the keys?
- Keys?
- Yes, keys.
Did you take the guard's keys?
No.
Am I in trouble?
No, Aaron, not unless
you're lying to me.
Lying?
Aaron never lies, Mr. Gordon.
He doesn't have the concept.
Poor, peaceful soul that he is.
He killed his family with an ax.
Isn't that what you did, Aaron?
Never harmed a fly before or since.
I said "Sorry."
Okay, Aaron, you're free to go.
Thank you.
Guard.
You saw how that went.
Saviano is the problem.
Now, on his own,
Janacek I can turn him around.
And the junior capos will follow him,
but that Saviano...
We gotta deal with him before
we make our move on Maroni.
Let me talk to Saviano on my own.
Me and Jimmy go way back.
That's true, you do go way back.
What would you tell him?
I'd say you're the best candidate.
He knows that.
He just can't admit it to your face.
Too proud.
Okay, then.
Talk to him.
Will do.
Butch.
You're not turning on me, are you?
No!
What kind of question is that?
Why would you joke
about something like that?
I'm just asking.
A girl gets insecure once in a while.
Royston, what are you doing
out of your cell?
Hey, cut it out!
Full fathom five thy father lies,
of his bones are coral made.
Ah, hell!
Royston. Is that your name?
Sea-nymphs hourly ring his knell.
Fascinating.
Poor man can walk and talk but
all he remembers are lines from the play.
Same electroshock technique as Frogman
but with less drastic results.
Looks like whoever is doing this
is improving their methods.
Or maybe their process is so haphazard they
don't know what kind of outcome they'll get.
One man ends up a vegetable...
...while the other
recites Shakespeare on a loop.
I don't understand what an inmate gains
from scrambling up another inmate.
You should stay on the female wing a while.
There's no reason to put yourself in danger.
I'm perfectly capable of protecting myself.
Besides, my patients need me.
There's going to be some
drama around here.
Missing keys made me focus on inmates,
but I think it's a misdirection.
I think I should be focusing on the staff.
Oh, I see.
There will be some drama.
But wait, I'm staff.
What if it's me?
- No, it's not you.
- How can you tell?
- You're not the type.
- Cop skills?
You can read people.
Some people.
A staff member? That's absurd.
- It was an inmate.
- I don't think so.
Your job is to oversee inmate security.
You're not authorized to conduct
an investigation of the staff.
Whoa!
You're trying to force my hand.
- You want me to call the police.
- No.
I already called them.
Barbara, you need to wake up.
Good morning.
I got you coffee.
Extra sweet.
You always remember.
Yeah.
Have you spoken to Jim recently?
Why would I?
Renee, you don't have to be jealous
of Jim.
I'm over him.
This was a mistake.
What was?
This. Us.
I should have never let it
go on for this long.
I'm sorry.
Oh, I see.
Barbara.
No, I mean--
No, you are absolutely right.
This was a mistake.
This has been a really
long process for me...
...and I've worked too hard
to get right with myself.
I wanted this to be good
but I can't fall back now.
The drinking, the drugs.
We are toxic together, you and me.
Please, Renee, stop.
There's no need to say another word.
I'm sorry that I interfered
with your process.
You need help I can't give you right now.
Let me call Jim for you, please.
No. Where's my purse?
You don't need to go. Stay here, take
time to get yourself together. I'll go.
I am perfectly together, thank you.
I am just toxic, that's all.
- Now where is my damn purse?
- Barbara, stop!
Calm down, please, all right?
I'll go. Please.
Fine.
Do what you want, go.
- I'm sorry.
- Just go.
Hey, pal.
In a cowslip's bell I lie.
There I crouch when owls do cry.
All right. I can dig that.
- Detective.
- Jim! Ha, ha! Partner!
Let me take a good look at you.
Lord have mercy, you're screwed.
- Excuse me!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, you weren't exaggerating.
Freaky as advertised.
Nobody of authority called on you, sir.
This is not a police matter.
You must be Director Dr. Lang.
See, I beg to differ.
This is third degree assault,
at the very least.
A friend of yours, is it?
Egregious insubordination.
Your job here was already
hanging on a thread.
This is the end of your career
in law enforcement, count on it.
Whoa, take it easy, hot shot.
Officer Gordon did the right thing.
Why wouldn't he call the police?
Anyone would think
you want to keep this business quiet.
Gerry-- It is Gerry, isn't it?
Now, did you do this terrible thing, Gerry?
That doesn't even merit a reply.
No, I did not do this terrible thing.
But you have the skill though, as a doctor.
You could do it lickity split.
- Now, why would I do this?
- Why would anyone?
Exactly, Officer Gordon.
Gerry, I think we'll have to
take you down to the precinct.
You're raising a lot of questions that need
clearing up in a more formal setting.
- But you can't do this.
- Shh, shh, shh.
As of this moment this is
an official GCPD investigation.
You, sir, will cooperate or face arrest.
Officer Gordon, would you mind
going through the, uh, staff records...
...while I take Gerry here
downtown for a chat?
Will do, detective.
Sir.
Jimmy.
Butch.
Good to see you.
Come on.
Like Old times, huh?
All we need is a bottle of applejack.
Ha, ha.
What happened, man?
In my head, we're still kids
chasing girls in Harlow Park.
Caught a couple of hot ones, huh?
Especially me. Ha, ha.
Thanks for meeting with me.
What did you tell your boss lady?
I suggested I reach out to you,
she agreed.
Talk some sense into me?
It's a "new dawn." What the--?
Yeah, like that.
She's not wrong, you know.
City's changing.
You really want Falcone's job?
Since we were kids
I love you like a brother.
I love you too, always, you know that.
I do. I do.
That's why I trust you...
...and that's why I say to you with love.
Fish is doomed.
There's no way she gets the chair.
It ain't gonna happen.
She's a smart cookie,
but she's overreaching.
I mean, Butch, without you
and your crew, what's she got?
Very little.
Everybody knows it, you know it.
Maybe.
What's it gonna take
to make you make a move?
- What are you offering?
- Name it.
Drop Fish, come over to us.
The club, all the businesses attached...
...they're yours.
That's day one. A welcome bonus.
What else do you want?
That's a good question.
Let me think it over.
Yeah.
Hey, brother.
Don't think too long, huh?
Detective Bullock!
Wait here.
Ha, ha. Penguin...
...it's good to see you.
- What are you guys doing?
- Old friend.
Thank goodness you're here.
There's been some silly mistake.
Looks like it. Unless you irritated
someone important.
You didn't do that, did you?
Me?
Of course not.
Are you sure?
Examine your soul, Penguin.
Wait!
Don't go.
Please, sir, I beg of you.
My patron, Don Maroni, is obviously
unaware of my predicament.
A simple phone call would resolve things,
I'm sure.
But see, I like having you here.
I can sit at my desk and look at you.
It's soothing...
...like a bonsai tree.
What's a bonsai tree?
So...
...did you see our friend?
I saw him.
And?
Enh. I'm working him.
He's a stubborn cuss, that one.
So give him a little time.
Time, hmm?
Okay.
He can have time.
I'm optimistic.
Good.
All right, doctor,
pretend I'm an ignoramus.
It shouldn't be too hard.
Explain to me this whole
electric needle business.
When a real doctor like you does it,
what's it supposed to do?
Electroshock therapy is a common procedure
for mood and behavior alteration.
- Like mind control?
- Of a sort.
Blue Sky experimentation on humans
is considered unethical.
- So we know very little of the hard science.
- Okay.
But skilled surgeons can elicit
very specific responses.
- Uh-huh.
- But those inmates...
...weren't treated by a skilled surgeon.
You sure about that?
There are no skilled surgeons
amongst the inmates.
- Or the staff.
- You're a skilled surgeon.
We've been over this.
I haven't opened a body since med school.
I'm just messing with you.
I don't think you're the man behind this.
No, you're not the type to break rules.
Too scared of authority.
But you're hiding something.
What is it?
- Well, everybody is hiding something.
- Don't play tag.
You're right, detective.
I am afraid of authority.
And the things I'm hiding,
I'll never tell you.
- Sounds heavy.
- Heavy? Yes.
And if you know what's good for you,
you won't dig deeper.
All right.
I don't want to hit any power lines.
You don't have to tell me twice no digging,
unless, of course, it had something to do...
...with the case at hand.
- Nothing.
Oh.
Great, thank you.
Oh, you poor thing.
You look so pale. Any joy?
Not so far.
The files seem to be incomplete.
I wonder if there's more in the basement.
Blueprint says
there's a records office there?
Oh, the basement's closed off.
Unsafe chemicals.
Nobody's been there for 10 years.
You know the way down there?
All right, suppose you had to pick out
one member of your staff...
...as the culprit. Who would it be?
- It wasn't a staff member.
- Whatever, first face that pops to your mind.
Nobody. They're good people,
I know them well.
They've all been with me
for more than five years.
We all came to Arkham together.
Wait. Hold that. You just saw someone.
Who was it?
- No, she couldn't.
- She?
Who?
What's that?
Everybody's in their cell.
Dorothy?
Jim, hi. What's up?
Hi, Leslie.
We're going on an adventure
to the basement.
Oh, well, that sounds fun.
- Can I come?
- No.
- But--
- Dr. Thompkins, what did I tell you earlier?
You should go home.
- Why? What's wrong?
- Nothing's wrong.
Go home.
I don't under--
You Okay?
I'm fine.
Find the main entry guard...
...tell him to lock down, then get out, quick.
- Hit lockdown, get out. Will do.
- Yeah.
- Jim, listen!
- Dorothy Duncan is an inmate.
- I know. Get over here now.
Leslie!
Guard! Guard, help!
Dr. Thompkins!
- Jim. Behind you!
- Unh!
Men! Men!
What the hell do you think
you're playing at?
Go back in your cells right now.
You hear me? That's an order!
- Remember, I'm a vegan. No butter.
- Yeah, yeah.
Hi.
Is this--?
Is Jim Gordon there?
Yes, he is.
But I'm sorry,
Jim's kind of busy right now.
Can I take a message?
No.
No, that's okay.
I--
Who is this?
I 'm a friend of Jim's.
Who's that?
Go to hell.
M.E.'s got her in the morgue.
When Dorothy Duncan was a 16 year-old
nursing student...
...she killed five kids with poison candy.
For homework, she said.
She's spent over half her life at Arkham.
When the asylum closed,
it was chaos.
Must have stayed
in the basement until it reopened.
Forensics is sweeping the basement,
looking for her lair.
Poor soul. What was she trying to do?
Who knows? Maybe she was
trying to cure her own madness.
She was crazy. Enough said.
It's good to see you, Jim.
And you got a win, huh?
- Still fighting. Nice work.
- Don't think my boss will see it that way.
He's working for
the king of cheese-grinders.
It's a crying shame, cap.
We need to get him back on the job.
You know I'd bring you back here
in a second.
If I could.
I know. It's all good, captain.
You do look spiffy in the uniform.
- Yeah, if spiffy means dorky.
- Thank you. Thank you very much.
How about a drink for old time's sake?
Sounds good.
Penguin.
Hi.
Sir.
Don Maroni.
- Thank heavens you're here.
- You look kind of frowsty.
Forgive me.
I've had nothing but a moist towelette
since yesterday morning.
A very sad picture.
You know why you're in there?
- I have no idea--
- Rhetorical question.
You're in there because I put you in there.
But Don Maroni, why?
What did I do?
Do you know what hubris is?
Do you know?
Sorry.
I thought that was another
rhetorical question.
Yes, I do.
Hubris. It's when--
It's when limping little chicken-butt
second bananas think they're hot stuff.
- Sir--
- When dumbass underlings...
...raise taxes without asking me first.
- Yes, sir.
- On fishermen.
You raised taxes on fishermen.
They're out there in the freaking ocean
risking their lives for us...
...and you raise their taxes
without asking me?
That's hubris, my friend.
I'm sorry, Don Maroni.
Deeply sorry.
I will never do it again.
All right, then.
Hey, you. Let my friends out.
- Excuse me?
- What, am I talking Hungarian?
Open the cage, mook.
Holy mother, you stink.
Let this be a lesson to you, yes?
Yes, sir.
You're a smart monkey.
But you're a monkey.
And I'm the Zookeeper.
Oh, you're all right.
Captain, you should see this.
Look here.
Dorothy Duncan.
Electrode wounds. Both sides.
Same gauge as the others.
About a month old.
They were hidden by her hair.
This is crazy.
How could she do this to herself?
She couldn't. Not humanly possible.
Which means
she was just another victim.
- She couldn't...
- Oh, crap.
Hey, Aaron.
What's up?
Hey, where'd you get those--
Hey!
Well done, Aaron.
Exactly like I told you.
Now, you are my best work so far.
Hello, Dr. Lang.
Lang?
- Lang!
- They're gone.
Get an ambulance. Go!
Not staff--
Don't speak. Just breathe.
- Breathe!
- Gruber.
Dear Officer Gordon:
Sorry I had to run.
I very much wanted to enjoy a proper chat
with you before I left...
...but that's show business.
I've been practicing my skills on these
sad creatures for a while now.
Electricity is an amazing thing.
It can work wonders.
Nurse Dorothy was an early success.
This last time,
I think I finally got one just right.
Bravo to me.
But time to go.
It was nice to meet you, Jim.
I hope to see you around.
All the best, Jack Gruber.
Barbara?
In the still of the night
I held you
Held you tight
- How you doing?
- Well.
- You?
- Tip-top. Always.
So what's the deal, brother? Are you in?
Yeah.
- I'm in.
- That's my boy!
Name your terms.
Remember when we were 14?
We stole all that meat from Satriani's?
Yeah, I do.
It was like 50 pounds of pork and whatnot.
Never seen my mom so happy.
Ha, ha. Yeah.
Thing is, when I was sharing it out...
...it was 15 pounds
of prime angus beefsteaks in there.
I kept it all for myself.
Didn't give you any.
Gave you all the cheap cuts.
I never knew that.
Yeah, it's been bugging me ever since.
Hey, we're talking a long time ago.
I wanna say I'm sorry.
I apologize
for cheating you out of your beefsteak.
- Forget about it.
- No.
No. Brothers don't do that.
Why did I do that?
Hey, forget about it. It's okay.
Apology accepted.
Thank you.