Previously onGotham...
Thousands will be infected
with the virus.
The G.C.P.D. are scrambling
to recover the antidote.
They are missing
one very important element.
I told you I would help you
find your darkness.
Take the virus.
It'll show you who you really are.
You're still Ed Nygma,
the Ed Nygma I made.
I'm the Riddler.
I became him when I killed you.
No one wants Nygma dead
more than me.
But I can't betray Barbara.
She's always got
your best interest at heart.
I don't know what you want from me.
The one I serve believes
you have a great destiny.
I am Ra's al Ghul.
But I need to know if you're ready.
Join me.
Alfred.
Alfred! Alfred!
Alfred!
You've broken through
- your conditioning.
- No!
Impressive.
You don't control me anymore!
- I will never be your heir.
- On the contrary.
Your strength only confirms
what the prophesy has foretold.
An heir to serve
as my knight in the darkness.
I will never follow you!
You made me kill, Alfred.
Use the waters, Bruce.
- Our time will come.
- No!
- Bruce.
- Alfred. Alfred.
A citywide lockdown
continues to remain in effect
with Gotham officials urging people
to stay inside their homes
as thousands of infected citizens
continue their rampage through
the city.
Local law enforcement...
Lee?
Where are you?
Why? You miss me?
The city's not safe.
That's why I'm packing a bag.
What are you talking about?
I'm leaving Gotham
and I want you to come with me.
I'll take your silence as a "yes"?
Lee, you can't leave. There are
checkpoints all over the city.
Who are you trying to convince, Jim?
I can hear it in your voice.
You want this as much as I do.
We can finally be together
without judgment
or secrets or jealousy.
After everything
we've been through...
Don't we deserve that?
I am leaving on
the afternoon train,
and I want you with me.
But I want the real you.
So tell me you'll stop fighting it.
Tell me I won't lose you again.
Tell me you'll be there.
I'll be there.
Hey, Jim.
Where are we with Tetch?
Barbara and Nygma gave
the mayor's office
a list of demands.
A friend snuck me a copy.
They also threatened
to kill Tetch
if we tried to take
him back by force.
Half of these would bankrupt
the city.
The alternative being there's
no city left to bankrupt.
We don't have
any cards to play, partner.
We got no moves.
Yes, we do.
Him.
- Penguin?
- This entire list
is Barbara's except for him.
Penguin is the only
thing Nygma cares about.
- The question is, how much?
- No way.
There is no way
we're turning him over.
- Why not?
- Because we don't have the authority
to broker some kind of secret
deal behind the city's back
much less one that leads to the
imminent death of its former mayor.
Nygma would betray Barbara
and hand over Tetch if given half
the chance.
I need to save Lee.
I don't have much time, Harvey.
It's now, or never.
You know, one of these days,
I'm gonna say never.
- Hello?
- Nygma, it's Gordon.
I'm calling with a proposition.
Can you talk?
I can listen.
We need to kill her.
How much longer
are we gonna wait?
Come on.
Nygma chopped off your hand.
He almost killed me,
and now, Barbara's partners with him?
That's the mother of all insults.
This city is gonna pay us
a lot of money to get Tetch back.
We need to let that play out
before we do anything rash.
I know you two were close...
But whatever you had,
she treats you like dirt now.
She treats us both like dirt
and you know it.
She doesn't deserve your loyalty.
What are you two whispering about?
Nothing.
- Any word from city hall?
- Trust me,
we're about to own this town.
Parts of it, quite literally.
Where's Ed?
He was just here a minute ago.
Tetch?
Nygma!
How could you let this happen?
Us? You're the one that trusted him.
I asked you to do one thing!
Watch a man tied to a chair!
You idiots can't even do that!
- Where are we going?
- Shut up.
Look, I'm not trying
to aggravate you.
It's just, this doesn't exactly have
an above the board feeling about it.
- What's going on?
- Barbara and Nygma have Tetch.
-They're ransoming the city.
- So, what does that
have to do with me?
You're handing me over to him.
You can't. You can't.
You cannot do this.
It's a small price to pay for saving
- the city.
- Yeah, for you.
For me, it's a very large price.
Look, he cannot be trusted.
You're risking everything
based on the word of a sociopath.
Yeah, yeah, get in the car.
What? It's gonna be fine.
Yeah, Penguin, Nygma, Tetch
all in the same place
For a high stakes hostage swap,
what could possibly go wrong?
Do you mind?
Look, if I'm gonna be
this city's sacrificial lamb
the least you could do
is lead me to
the slaughter with a little dignity.
No.
You don't think that I can cause you
trouble once we're inside?
- You do, and I'll kill you.
- No, you won't.
Not before you have Tetch. Not before
the exchange goes smoothly.
And after that,
what do you care what happens?
Let's just get this over with.
- Thank you.
- Shut up.
My three favorite men.
Don't feel bad, Oswald.
Your death at my hands
Was inevitable.
Is that what
you told yourself last time?
I'm assuming the grenade's
not a fashion statement.
Precaution.
You three try anything,
I pull the pin.
No more Tetch.
No hope for an antidote.
- Little crude, don't you think?
- Enough! Let's get this done.
You're infected.
Oh, how wonderful.
Nygma!
Did you really think
you could get away with this?
I knew you'd figure out
that this is about Oswald.
How'd you figure out where we are?
Please. You know how many cops
I got on the payroll?
Oh, baby, you might wanna use
your inside growl
whilst making secret calls
inside the G.C.P.D.
Now, hand him over.
Go!
Let him go!
We need to get Tetch!
Now!
That little bastard!
Coming through. Move out of
the way. Rita, move.
All right, let's have a look.
What did you do to cauterize this?
I don't know.
- Is he going to be okay?
- We'll do everything we can.
What's your relationship
to the patient?
Doc, BP's falling.
We're family.
All right, let's get him typed,
cross set and prepped for OR.
It looks pretty good.
I'll call the station.
Grab Tetch!
Split up.
Jim.
You and the ex are infected?
I've heard Lee wants to remove
my pretty little head from my body.
Is it weird that kind
of makes me like her?
You thinking about ripping
anyone's head off, Jim?
I bet you are.
You're so close.
The next time you give in,
the virus will have you.
- Stop talking.
- Jim!
Come out, come out, wherever you are.
Hey.
There's no back door into
a loading dock.
No way this ends well.
The virus will give you all
the strength you need.
It's the only option.
Give in to the darkness.
I said stop talking.
You want to kill me,
that I can see.
But without my blood,
no antidote will there be.
- Fight it, Jim.
- I don't know if I can.
He's right. We need him.
Yeah, but not all of him.
Where are they?
What happened?
What'd he do?
Oh, Jim.
You sick bastard.
Where's the lab tech?
Come on. Come on. Here. Here.
What? You've never seen a Mason jar
filled with blood before? Go!
Back to work!
You okay?
He's awake.
- I was getting lonely.
- Where are we?
Well, we ran into a police blockade.
Had to hunker down a minute.
Where are you taking me?
I don't know.
I'm sort of improvising here.
Why? You have some place
you have to be?
Does it matter?
I imagine you're planning on
dragging this out.
There are so few moments
of pure joy in one's life
I feel compelled to savor this one.
You mean gloat?
Yes, I do.
It was always one of your least
attractive qualities, Oswald.
- It's killing you, isn't it?
- What?
To know that you are not as
smart as you think you are.
All of that planning to drive me
crazy strip me of everything I had
revealing yourself with a "Ta-da!"
and then shooting me by the river.
That plan was perfect
and you know it.
You failed.
I am still alive
and you are handcuffed
in the back seat.
And now, you will never be able
to correct your mistake.
I guess not.
Now, that they have Tetch's blood,
they can make the antidote.
And after what we tried to pull
the whole city's gonna be
gunning for us.
Hell, I'm surprised the cops haven't
busted down our door already.
Relax. They've got better
things to do.
What are we supposed to do now?
We split up, go to the safe house,
and regroup.
Regroup? For what?
For whatever
the hell I tell you to do.
I'm not waiting anymore.
She's broken every promise
she's ever made to you.
- To us.
- I know.
Safe house is
the perfect place to do it.
Okay.
- I'll take care of everything.
- No.
We do it together.
Yeah.
Kowalski and Burrows
are gonna be pissed.
Tetch's blood is good.
The lab guys are starting work
on an antidote as we speak.
I need to get to Lee.
How long?
- How long before it's ready?
- They said we could head there now.
Where is it?
Detective Gordon, just in time.
If you'll take a seat
and roll up your sleeve.
We have a dose
ready for you right now.
The others will be ready shortly.
I need two.
Sorry. We could only make
one of these single shots so quickly.
No! Two.
All of Tetch's blood
is in the centrifuge machines.
The process can't be interrupted.
Just one or two hours max.
You can still catch Lee
before she leaves.
There's not enough time.
Jim. Jim. Jim.
Don't make me...
Jim! No!
Jim! Jim!
Someone call the bullpen.
Bruce?
I heard about Alfred.
Is he gonna be okay?
Go home, Selina.
What happened?
No.
No, you don't get to do this.
- Do what?
- Walk back into my life.
You think I need your pity?
I don't.
- That's not why I'm here.
- You wanna know what happened?
- You wouldn't understand.
- Why?
Because I'm not desperate
- to believe in something?
- Because you don't believe in anyone
or anything but yourself.
It's called surviving.
And unlike you...
I know who I am.
I don't need anyone to tell me.
What are you even doing here, Selina?
You don't give a damn about Alfred
and you sure as hell
don't care about me.
I know you better than that.
Yeah.
I thought you did.
Have a nice life.
Lee?
I don't like to be kept waiting.
You're still fighting it.
I can help you with that.
We both know that's not what I want.
I want you.
I want you and all your darkness.
Give in.
Give in to your darkness. Be free.
Don't you get tired of making
the same mistake over and over?
You think I'm making a mistake?
Instead of killing me
when you had the chance...
You've decided to feed your ego.
You wanna talk ego, Riddler?
You will always fail, Oswald.
Because you will always
let your base emotions drive you.
Hate.
Anger.
Fear.
- Love.
- Shut up.
You wanna know why I could never
love someone like you, Oswald?
- I'm warning you.
- Because you are a spoiled child
who throws a tantrum any time
he doesn't get what he wants.
Especially when what he wants
doesn't want him back.
You're right.
I shouldn't have waited.
But unlike you.
I'm in the position
to rectify my mistake.
Prepare for one massive tantrum.
No!
That is not possible!
It is my turn.
It is my turn to kill you!
Like I said...
You will always fail
because you'll never change.
Maybe.
But at least I know who I am.
That day by the edge of the river
that was the moment
you were reborn and that was a lie!
Your entire persona
is based on a lie.
And there is nothing
you can do to change that!
Actually...
Maybe there is.
All travelers must pass through
security checkpoints
before boarding the trains.
- Sir.
- This way, sir.
Anyone who might be
displaying signs of infection
to the nearest checkpoint
or security officer.
Hey, this isn't a public entrance.
Oh, crap.
Police! Excuse me! Police!
Move aside! Police! Move! Move!
Get out of my way!
He's trying to stop us.
You can't let him.
I'll see you on the train.
Police! Police! Move!
Out of the way, move!
Jim! Jim!
Now, we're gonna be delayed,
aren't we?
You gonna shoot me, Harvey?
This isn't you.
It is.
Please don't make me do this.
Lee and I belong together.
I know, I know how bad
you want that.
To forget about
everything that happened.
But you can't. It's not real.
This is who I am!
- This is who I've always been.
- No, it's not!
Who you are is a choice.
It always has been. It still is.
This is who you are.
You're the best cop
I ever worked with.
The best friend I've ever had.
If you love Lee...
Go save her.
Tickets.
To our great adventure.
I love you, Lee.
No! No.
What have you done?
Really? A hacksaw?
Even your disposal tactics
are idiotic.
Guess I'm just old fashioned.
Did you really think
I wouldn't figure it out?
The two of you have been whispering
like teenagers for weeks.
Oh, Butchie...
You shouldn't have waited.
Oh, believe me,
if it weren't for Tabbie...
You'd have been dead a long time ago.
You're trying to tell me
she had nothing to do with this?
- That's right.
- Oh, so you've just
gone behind her back,
have you?
I was gonna hit you
before we got to the safe house.
Play dumb when you didn't show.
Leaning into your strengths?
Wanna know why you're always
taking shots at me?
The giant size of the target.
It's because
for all your tough talk...
You miss her.
You miss her loyalty, her strength.
She made you better,
and you know it.
And she sacrificed that for what?
Play queen for a day?
Pathetic.
If it helps...
You never deserved her
in the first...
I guess we'll see.
I don't know if you can hear me...
But if you can...
Alfred, you need to fight.
I don't know what
I would do without you.
Alfred?
Please.
Please don't leave me.
Here we are...
Again.
I have to tell you...
This feels really great.
Glad I could help.
Any last words?
I'm fine for now.
I beg your pardon?
I'll wait.
I'm going to kill you, Oswald.
There is no later.
If you have something to say...
Now, is the time.
Duly noted.
Oh, whatever.
I'm not letting you ruin this for me.
You don't have anything to say...
But I do.
Goodbye, Oswald.
I removed the bullets
when you were knocked out.
Right before I called them.
In the back seat...
The pin I used
to unlock my cuffs?
My tie pin.
I thought it should be personal.
You were just trying to make me think
I had the upper hand.
It all fell into place.
How did you know that Barbara
would show up at the warehouse?
I didn't.
If it wasn't for her...
Gordon would have turned me over,
and I'd most likely be dead.
But fortune favors the bold.
You said you called them
after you knocked me out.
You knew that I'd bring you here.
I know you, Ed.
I may be driven by my emotions...
but you're driven by something
much more predictable.
A desperate, compulsive need
to complete
what you've started in
exacting fashion.
Why didn't you just kill me, Oswald?
You were the one time
I'd let love weaken me.
And I want you around
as a constant reminder
to never make that mistake again.
No!
Barbara?
Butch?
Was killing Nygma really
that important to you?
Did you kill Butch?
He said you didn't have anything
to do with him trying to kill me.
Is that true?
What does it matter?
All right, for argument's sake...
let's say I haven't been
the best friend.
Do you think we could put this
behind us and move forward?
Did you kill Butch?
That doesn't sound like a "yes."
I need to know.
It's the only way
we'll able to move forward.
Yes.
I killed him.
But it's not like you gave
me a choice.
There's always a choice.
How many times have I told you
not to bring a whip to a gunfight?
Now, we can move forward.
The Tetch antidote
has been released over the city
with a 90 percent cure rate
with individual antidotes
now, being manufactured.
You're awake!
God.
I'm sorry, Alfred.
Wasn't your fault, was it?
I completely lost my way.
I've been trying to find
who I am for so long
searching for some greater meaning.
I don't know who I am, Alfred.
Who am I supposed to be?
I can't help you with
that one, mate.
You're a man now.
You gotta find your own path.
I'm not like you.
You've always been
so sure of who you are.
Oh, I don't know about that.
I've been through some
very dark places...
As have you.
You need to find your true North
and let that guide you.
What's yours?
You.
It's always been you.
You gotta find something
that you really care about
and you protect it at all costs.
And when you find it...
You'll never be lost again.
And while the arrival of the antidote
is certainly welcome news...
The death and the destruction
the virus left in its wake
will no doubt reverberate
through the city for years to come.
Yeah?
Is Barbara around?
No.
And she's not coming back.
What do you want?
I'm not sure.
I just know I'm tired
of just surviving.
I want more.
I wanna move up.
I figured this was
a good place to start.
I'm at a bit of a crossroads myself.
You hungry?
You buying?
Give it a whirl.
That is the logo for my new club.
What are we gonna call it?
The Iceberg Lounge.
Clever. Because you're nicknamed
Penguin, right?
There's that.
And then there is
the club's centerpiece attraction.
Lee?
Lee.
Jim,
I knew if I saw you I might not have
the courage to leave.
And I need to.
I finally understand Gotham
in a way I suspect you always have.
It's a place where the strongest
and most cunning rule.
Where the cost of survival
is paid for by others.
And everyone feels alone.
Having the virus showed me
the city as it truly was.
As I truly was.
In so many ways.
The virus made me feel reborn.
He's a gangster.
Probably got what he deserved.
- He is?
- Sure. That's Butch Gilzean.
Really?
His chart lists his birth
name as Cyrus Gold.
Cyrus Gold?
He must've changed it at some point.
But if having the virus allowed
Gotham to embrace its worst self
the cure should remind us
there is always hope.
A chance to remember
who we can be
rather than who we are.
I don't know if Gotham
deserves saving
but I do know one thing.
If anyone can save it...
It's you.
And in return, I believe
it can save you as well.
And then maybe one day...
It will send you back to me.
Until then...
Love always...
Lee.
Can I come in, captain?
No.
You threw me against a train car.
- I know.
- Two,
actually.
I felt like a freaking cartoon.
I am really sorry about that.
You see Lee?
She's gone.
She left Gotham.
You okay?
I will be.
You wanna get a drink?
- It's noon.
- I didn't ask you what time it was,
I asked if you wanted to get a drink.
Sure.
I'm good.
Any word on Tetch?
Yeah, he stumbled
into some hospital.
They patched him up.
Shipped him back to Arkham.
You know, I'd actually like to get
back to being a detective.
Do some good old fashioned
police work.
The kind that doesn't involve
secret cults or blood viruses.
- Do we have anything like that?
- Not really.
Half the force is coming off
24 hour shifts, but we could...
Hit the streets like
a couple beat cops,
see if we could stir up some trouble.
I don't know, seems kind
of beneath me.
You know, seeing as I'm the best cop
you've ever worked with and all.
I was just telling you
whatever crap came to mind
so you wouldn't punch a hole
through my head.
Like a hostage negotiation, you just
tell someone what they wanna hear.
Sure. Sure.
You know, if you didn't have
- the virus, I...
- Is that right?
That was so good.
- That was such a good dinner.
- I've never had sushi like that.
It was great, whatever it was.
- Money! Now!
- Dad?
- It's okay, sweetheart.
- Now!
- No!
- Dad!