Previously onGotham...
Monsters are coming, Mr. Mayor,
who will cleanse this city.
If you sell me your company,
I will give you the name of the man
who killed your parents.
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm Bruce's friend.
And you're a piece of gutter trash.
You think that little minx is gonna
tell you something, do you?
Getting information
out of a girl like that requires
a level of deception
that you do not yet possess.
- You're under arrest.
- May I ask what the charge is?
The kidnapping
and torture of Aubrey James.
These were Ms. Kringle's.
A man with nothing to love is free.
Hey, Parks, you did good today.
Eduardo Flamingo killed Officer Parks
before they could
get him into lockup.
Bruce Wayne will die
and his company will be ours.
Everything is ready.
The brothers arrival is imminent.
Gotham will be redeemed in blood.
- Please don't hurt me!
- Shut up!
Forget your umbrella?
Thought visiting hours were over.
But what are rules to the man
who arrested the mayor of Gotham?
Any chance you're gonna tell me
what this little visit is about?
Tomorrow's hearing perhaps?
You're here to gloat.
Does the name Catherine Parks
mean anything to you?
No, can't say it does.
I'm gonna be there tomorrow.
I'm gonna watch them put you away.
Always a pleasure, detective.
-Hey.
You're soaking wet.
Do you wanna talk about it?
Catherine Parks was 23.
On the force a year.
Today we put her in the ground
because when I had the chance
I didn't do the only sensible thing.
- Jim.
- An assassin kills four cops.
Dares me to pull the trigger
and I don't.
Explain that to me.
That man was your prisoner.
You didn't have a choice.
I had a choice.
Yes, to uphold the law
or to become a murderer.
You made the right one.
You think Catherine Parks
feels the same way?
What about her family?
I went to see Galavan today.
And?
You're asking did I get the guards
to turn the cameras off? No.
But they would have.
Galavan as good as killed Parks,
Essen and a dozen other cops
and yet he sits there.
Smiling. Breathing.
And tomorrow, Aubrey James
is going in front of the grand jury
telling them that he was kidnapped
and tortured by Galavan.
He's gonna be put away
for a long time.
Maybe.
Just the way he acted
it wasn't a man looking at
a decade in prison.
- I have a bad feeling.
- Jim, it's over.
You did good.
Now, come to bed. Doctor's orders.
Where am I?
Who are you?
Day of reckoning is at hand.
The blood of the nine
shall wash away the sins.
Wait. Please.
And Gotham will be cleansed.
This isn't gonna work.
This girl is a world-class liar
from a family of world-class liars.
She'll see through you.
Or her uncle will.
Well, it's very possible.
And?
Bruce, they're playing nice with you
because they think you trust them.
Once they see you don't,
it'll get ugly fast.
- Your logic is flawless, Selina.
- It's not too late.
If there's even a chance
Galavan knows who killed my parents,
I have to take it.
I told Alfred I have fencing
practice after school
to buy us time if we need it.
Hey.
The best liars always tell the truth.
- Something to remember.
- Thank you.
That's her car. You better...
Alvarez, call the morgue.
See if any bodies turned up
matching Gertrud Kapelput.
She didn't just vanish.
- Galavan killed her.
- Did that yesterday.
And you're gonna do it again today.
I got my own cases, Gordon.
Turn up anything on that symbol
we found in the penthouse?
No, I'm waiting for Father Mike
up at St. Bart's.
Sent him a picture
of the cassock too.
He's up on all that religious
mumbo jumbo.
What exactly are we after here?
Something tying Galavan
to the murders of Essen, Parks,
any of the people he killed.
Not to state the obvious, Jim
but the guy is going to jail.
- I went to see him last night.
- Yeah?
Get the guards
to turn off the camera?
The look on his face, Harvey
- I don't know. I can't describe it.
- Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
The guy get stabbed, I thought
we'd have at least a week of peace.
Hey, cap, how you doing?
Did you get my flowers?
- Captain, how you feeling?
- Five by five.
Damn doc would've had me
in bed a week if I had let him.
Got something for you.
Munis found a dead body
down by the port.
Throat cut from ear to ear.
The vic's a career dirt bag
but the work's...
Sir, if it's all the same,
I'd like to stay on Galavan.
It isn't. Galavan's cooked.
So you're back on the rotation. What?
I just feel like
we're missing something, sir.
There's some piece of the puzzle
that's gonna come back and bite us.
Just give me a few more days.
Answer's no. Be pissed.
But it's for your own good.
Oh, and I'm sorry about Parks.
She deserved better.
Yo, Jim.
A message from Father Mike.
That symbol is from something
called the Order of St. Dumas.
They used to have an abbey downtown.
Barnes just told me
to lay off Galavan.
Well, then you probably don't care
that the mayor's office tried
to buy the abbey last week.
- Galavan tried to buy it?
- Yeah.
Some urban development nonsense.
New owner said no.
It's a Chinese slap-slap joint now.
- Hell with it. You got the address?
- Yeah. Let's go get lucky.
Your uncle made me an offer.
The name of my parents killer
in exchange for selling him
my shares of Wayne Enterprises.
I said no.
But circumstances have changed.
You're going to sell?
- No.
- Then...
Your uncle was arrested
and his assets were frozen.
Tell him I'll pay for his defense.
In exchange, he gives me the name.
You're taking advantage of him.
I have something he needs,
he has something I need. That's all.
Do you believe what people
are saying about him?
I don't care what people say.
My father was investigating
Wayne Enterprises
then he and my mother were killed.
I investigated Wayne Enterprises
and someone tried to kill Alfred.
Either I find out
who killed my parents
and stop whatever's happening
in my company, or I'm dead.
I need that name.
The grand jury hearing is today.
- He's going to be cleared.
- What if he's not? What then?
Silver, get him to tell you the name.
And I will make sure he has the best
defense money can buy, I promise.
You think he's guilty.
Why would you believe
anything he says?
Because it would come from you.
If you bring me the name,
I'll know it's real.
Do you mean that?
I'll call you after I talk to him.
Still gotta get the name.
I will. I'm late for school.
Not yet.
Are you sure about this?
Doesn't look much
like a massage parlor.
Maybe there's another entrance?
- Get these girls out of here.
- Come on, come on, come on.
GCPD.
Sir?
Stop!
Drop the knife.
The day of reckoning is at hand,
and the blood of nine
shall wash away the sin.
Who are you?
What's your connection to Galavan?
And Gotham shall be cleansed.
Hey. Hey!
The girls at the parlor say
they saw at least six monks.
They have to be a part of the same
Order of Saint Dumas.
Bullock's contact says
they're penitents.
Yeah, I forgot my dictionary
in my purse.
They believed in purification
through pain.
Blood.
They were big in the old days
in Gotham.
And about a hundred years ago,
vanished.
It was their crest we found
in Galavan's penthouse.
And now, they're back
and they're pissed off
that their home's a high-end
rub and tug joint.
Fine. Gather what you have
and give it to Alvarez.
Captain, these monks could be the key
to what Galavan is planning.
As I recall, detective,
I already gave you a case
and I expressly told you
to move away from Galavan.
The dead guy at the ports.
He attacked a woman
across town yesterday.
In her statement,
she said her attacker was pulled off
by man a dressed like a monk.
Does the universe normally
like you this much, Detective?
First time.
All right,
say they're the same monks.
Why would they kill
a bunch of bankers
and some nobody street thug?
The monk said, "The blood of the nine
shall wash away the sin."
It's obviously some sort of ritual.
And if Galavan is connected
what does he stand to gain?
I don't know.
We have to find a monk
and get him to talk.
Considering what this last one did,
that might not be so easy.
Captain, it's no coincidence
that this is happening
just as Galavan's
about to stand trial.
Whatever it is,
it's going down today.
The blood of the nine.
Five are already dead.
Okay.
But I still want you at the grand
jury to hear James testimony.
And Gordon,
whatever this is, stop it.
Bruce, it's Silver.
I just saw my uncle.
He agreed to your deal,
everything you asked.
He told me the name, Bruce.
Meet me across the way after school.
Don't scream. Don't run.
Just get in, or we kill the girl.
Go.
The scar tissue's old.
See how the wounds wrap
over his shoulder?
It was definitely self-inflicted.
When I stabbed him, he didn't flinch.
And there are thick
scars on the palms.
He cut himself there repeatedly.
Father Mike said
the leaders cut themselves
and mark the followers
with their blood.
- Like a blessing.
- Charming.
They got two more bodies
from the past three days.
Career hoods.
Killed somewhere, then dumped.
Both their throats cut.
- Seven down, two to go.
- It's weird.
How has nobody seen
these monks till now?
A, they're killing people
and carrying them across town,
and B, they are monks.
The woman who was attacked yesterday,
she said the monk vanished
with the attacker.
But that alley was a dead end.
The sewers.
Oh, no.
So the monk drags
the woman's attacker
into the alley above us.
Next thing, he's food for seagulls.
Ports are this way.
Again?
Well, did you try
jiggling the handle?
Well, what did you put down it?
- Dr. Thompkins, can I help you?
- Hi, Ed.
This is the autopsy on the dead monk.
Jim wants you to run toxicology.
Fascinating. The need to inflict
that kind of pain on one's self.
Is there anything else?
No. Yes.
Was that Kristen
you were just talking to?
- What?
- Sorry.
It sounded like you were talking
to somebody in your apartment.
- And who besides?
- I was talking to my plumber.
Have you heard from Kristen?
I know she said she was sick.
- I was thinking of...
- As it happens, she is not sick.
She lied, to all of us.
I just found out Miss Kringle
left town with Officer Dougherty.
She left Gotham with Dougherty?
But he was abusive.
Love.
I'm... I'm stunned.
- Do you need to get that?
- No, I don't think so.
Oh, Ed, you must be devastated.
Right now, I'm just trying
to focus on the job.
Well, let me know
if you ever wanna talk.
Thank you. That means a lot.
- Yes?
- Where is the spicy mustard?
You better not have finished...
Never mind.
Silver, are you okay? What happened?
You have one chance. You let us go.
You talk when I tell you to.
Understand?
Now, so you know,
we are outside of the city
and there is absolutely no one
to hear you scream except me.
You work for the people
inside Wayne Enterprises.
Whoever's paying you...
Again, you talk when I tell you to.
Now, my employers have heard
that you are thinking of selling
your company's shares
to the uncle of this one.
That's not good.
But not why we're here.
The issue is someone's been
nosing into the deaths
of Thomas and poor Martha Wayne.
And I wonder who.
Kidding.
We know it was Blondie's uncle.
So I've been tasked to find out
what dear old uncle
told little Bruce Wayne.
Nothing.
Galavan didn't tell me anything.
You think that I won't hurt you
because you're a kid?
Or because you're you?
How did that work out
for your mommy and daddy?
There are billions at stake here.
And that's with a B.
Do what you want to me.
- I don't know anything.
- Okay, so we start with Goldilocks.
You touch and I swear...
Yeah? I've been threatened
by the best, kid.
And you are not exactly terrifying.
Now, let me tell you
how this is going to go.
In a minute, I'm gonna take
one of you into the back
and start cutting off your fingers.
And you're gonna talk.
I've been doing this a very,
very long time and everyone talks.
So unless you're really
into wearing mittens,
this is your last chance.
What does Theo Galavan know?
Okey-dokey.
- Let's go.
- No! No! No!
No! Stop! Stop! Stop! Silver.
You have to tell them.
I'll hold my side of the deal.
Please. Please. I promise.
But my uncle didn't tell me anything.
But you left me a message.
I was supposed to keep you busy
until this evening.
He's sure he's going to be freed,
then he'll convince you
to sell your company.
I'm sorry, Bruce.
I don't know anything.
- Really?
- I don't!
That's a pity.
- No.
- Kids. Kids.
- No, please!
You really need
better taste in women.
- No!
- Please! Help me!
Stop. Bruce!
Just when you think Gotham's
shown her last jewel
she reveals herself like a flower.
You're mixing metaphors.
I'm in a freaking sewer.
Do you hear something?
It's a voice.
I know this bum. Muscle for hire.
Check out the finger painting
on the forehead.
The victim at the port
had the same thing.
Like a blessing.
Whoever did this can't be
too far away. We should...
Harvey.
Oh, no, no, no.
Please, please, don't. Hold.
He needs an ambulance.
We gotta wake him up
and make him talk.
Religious fanatic who doesn't feel
pain? What's our angle?
These nutjobs
have killed eight people.
Whatever their plan is,
whatever Galavan's up to,
it is happening now.
- We make him talk.
- What are we gonna do? Torture him?
Threaten to let him die?
He wouldn't care.
There's no signal down here.
I'll call it in but I gotta go up.
- Thank you.
- God!
The day of reckoning.
The day of reckoning, brother.
Bruce.
Well, if nothing else
today has given me a newfound
respect for boy billionaires.
Kid's tougher than he looks.
Didn't know a damn thing.
Did you kill him?
No. Not yet.
But the rest is kind of up to you.
I told you.
My uncle didn't tell me anything.
- Are you gonna stick to that story?
- It's the truth.
Bruce, I'm sorry.
I don't know anything.
You know...
I don't like you.
The Wayne kid,
he's got some sap in him.
But you, you know
when you meet someone,
and you just don't click?
That's the way I feel about you.
That's why this is gonna be
so much easier.
What are you doing?
I'm gonna make sure
that you are telling the truth.
Touch me and my uncle
will have you gutted.
Every person you love
will die screaming.
I've had enough of this.
Let me go now!
Well, hello!
Nice to meet you.
I knew there was someone
hiding in there.
Are you deaf as well as ugly?
I said, let me go!
I heard you, princess.
What are you doing? Stop!
Malone! It's Malone.
- What's that?
- Malone. That's the name.
The man who killed
Bruce Wayne's parents.
- So your uncle did tell you?
- Not today, before
when he first found out.
Malone's a very common name.
His first name begins with M.
That's all I know.
- Stop!
- You know what?
I believe you.
Are we good?
Yes.
We're good.
Hey.
Remember me? The gutter trash?
Bruce.
- What's happening?
- What does it look like, dummy?
We tricked you.
Though, if it was up to me,
you would have lost a few fingers.
- Going soft, Tom?
- Can't.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, Mr. Wayne.
Pleasure doing business.
Sorry for the slaps.
Now, you two gonna be
okay with this one?
Or would you like me to...
No. We're cool.
Mr. Wayne. Boys.
You're probably
very confused right now.
Probably have a million questions
going through your head.
- Bruce, please.
- Be quiet.
I trusted you, Silver.
Even after your uncle was arrested,
I still believed you were my friend.
It was finally Selina
who convinced me otherwise.
I never bought your stupid act.
She broke into your apartment,
found the file you had on me.
It was clear you'd been sent
to push me to sell my company.
That your entire family was corrupt.
But I still had to find out
what your uncle
knew about my parents murder.
Now, I do.
- Thank you.
- Bruce.
Wait. That name wasn't real.
It was just something
I made up to stop him.
That's funny.
You only made it up
when you were under the knife.
Not when Bruce was getting tortured.
- You little bitch...
- Please.
Try it.
You're right about my uncle.
He's everything everyone says.
Worse.
When he finds out what I told you,
he'll kill me.
You pretended to be my friend.
Goodbye, Silver.
Bruce.
The things you told me today.
I believed you.
Yes.
- That was the point.
- Bruce, you can't do this.
It isn't you.
That's what you think.
But you're wrong.
Bruce.
Bruce. Bruce!
The ambulance...
Drink brother.
- Can't see.
- You are hurt.
- Lay still.
- The police.
Dead. We got here just in time.
The blood of the nine...
Shall wash away the sin.
I fulfilled my task, brother.
All that remains is the son.
Yes. The son?
Give me your blessing, brother.
Please.
The Son of Gotham shall die...
and the city shall be cleansed.
Detective, where's the?
What?
- Who are you?
- GCPD. You're under arrest.
Take him to a hospital.
See if you can get anything from him.
I gotta see Barnes.
Bruce?
Bruce, you in here?
Master Bruce.
Master B, you here?
You're trespassing.
I'm looking for Bruce Wayne.
He's not answering his phone.
He's not at home. He's not at school.
My guess, he's with that
snotty little niece of yours.
Sorry.
Now, I suggest you leave
while you still can.
I see you're a bit of a player,
are you?
As it were, then, Tabby.
Big, bad Galavan barks the orders
and you scamper around
bringing him dead rabbits,
so you might get
a little pat on the head.
I wonder what he'd do
if I just disappeared you.
Honestly, I don't think he'd care.
If I learn anything's happened
to that little boy
we'll find out, won't we?
Stop it!
For the record,
I was telling the truth.
I have no idea where Bruce Wayne is.
But I'll tell him you were asking.
Mr. Dent, your witness.
So Mayor James...
Excuse me, Mr. Dent.
I think you mean former mayor.
I'm just a citizen of Gotham,
here to tell the truth.
Mr. James.
If you could begin by telling us
where you spent the month
of October this year.
Where the hell have you been?
Bullock and I captured
one of the monks.
I was right. They're completing
some sort of ritual
to cleanse the city of sin.
They have one victim left.
They're calling him
the Son of Gotham.
Did they say anything about Galavan?
- I was not kidnapped...
- They didn't, did they?
Quiet.
Mr. James,
please repeat what you've said.
Theo Galavan did not kidnap me.
Your Honor,
the witness has suffered...
Please explain yourself, sir.
Why did you lie?
Who held you captive?
Oswald Cobblepot, the Penguin.
He hates Theo Galavan.
He tried to kill him multiple times.
He told me what to say.
He threatened me
with terrible things.
- He's lying!
- Gordon. Gordon!
- Detective Gordon, silence!
- Your Honor
I move my client be released at once.
Your Honor,
the State requests a recess...
Quiet!
Mr. James, you do realize
you are under oath?
Oswald Cobblepot
tortured me, put my head in a box
and made me lie.
I'm so very, very sorry.
In light of Mr. James testimony
and the complete absence of any other
evidence provided by the State
I hereby order Theo Galavan released
and the case against him dismissed.
- Your Honor!
- There's nothing we can do.
Your Honor, may I say a few words?
I think that's only fair.
I'd just like to state that...
I harbor no ill will toward
Detective Gordon
or the GCPD.
They did their jobs.
They're still my heroes.
What do you say, Detective Gordon?
Can we move forward together
to fix this broken, beautiful city?
- Hey! Hey!
- You son of a bitch!
- Officers, arrest him.
- You're a son of a bitch!
I'm gonna get you! I'm gonna get you!
Come on! Get your hands off of me!
Relax! We're not arresting you.
Alfred?
He's probably out looking for me.
Thank you, Selina.
I couldn't have done
this without you.
I was just glad to see
the two-faced bitch get served.
What are you gonna do now?
You gonna tell the cops,
or look for this Malone guy yourself?
Honestly,
I haven't thought that far ahead.
So, when you whispered to her...
before she went to her uncle,
what did you say?
You wanna know what I said?
Hey, If you don't wanna tell me,
I can leave.
I told her I've never met
anyone like her.
I told her I trusted her
with my life.
And that I felt tied to her in a way
that I couldn't explain
but wouldn't change.
Ever.
The best liars always tell the truth.
That was true?
Yes.
Just not about her.
I'm... I'm gonna steal
one of your cars
to take to the city. Cool?
Sure.
It's good you're changing.
Just don't change too much.
Why did you keep her glasses
to begin with?
I told you...
I loved Ms. Kringle.
Just get rid of them.
Dr. Thompkins is suspicious.
Amateurs.
Gabe, when I gave you this address,
I was not inviting pop-ins.
Galavan's been let go.
Where is he?
My, my.
What a difference a day brings.
Here, you're the prisoner
and I'm free.
Fortune's wheel.
Turn, turn.
These cops, good men.
You can tell which way
the wind's blowing.
Now, we have a very small window.
I have places to be, you have to die.
But I know you must
have questions, so...
The monks. They work for you?
For centuries
the Order of St. Dumas
has protected my family.
They have been a light
in a dark world.
Shall I tell you a secret?
Theo Galavan is a mask.
My name is Dumas and my family
built this city out of nothing.
But we were betrayed,
driven out, erased.
So that's all this is about.
- Revenge.
- No.
This is about atonement.
The ground that Gotham
is built on is poisoned
by the wrongs done to my forefathers.
I will change that.
By killing nine random people?
You're insane.
I can see why you'd think so.
Ritual blood sacrifices,
a bunch of guys in robes,
chanting prophecies.
It's a bit too...
But belief itself,
that's what matters, detective.
Belief gives strength. Purpose.
And not all the victims are random.
Son of Gotham.
Goodbye, James.
I couldn't have done it without you.
What the hell?
I have a few minutes. Cut him loose.
Come on, Jim, give it your best shot.
Save Gotham.
Kill him.
Don't make it quick.
Alfred? Is that you?
You won't believe what I learned...
Sorry. Not Alfred.
Hello, Jim.
Lucky for you,
Gabe had people following Galavan.
Now, where is he?
Where's Galavan?
Tell me! Where is Galavan?
You've shown mettle
and ingenuity, my boy.
But that's all done with.
What do you want?
Why, your life, of course.