GORDON: Previously on Gotham...
I'm arresting you for the murder
of the boy you blew up
under the Crown Point Bridge.
You blew that kid sky-high.
You are lying! You are a lying traitor!
I need you at the head of the GCPD.
Let them think you're a hero.
GORDON: I screwed up, Harv.
Sofia hired the Pyg.
And I covered it up.
SOFIA: We all have to make sacrifices.
Thought i was all about family.
Never said it was a happy family.
(SCREAMING)
My friend thinks we're here to rob you.
But I know you torture plants
- in the name of science, Roland Charles.
- (GRUNTS)
Lee Thompkins may have made Ed strong,
but I see the other you.
- The Riddler.
- (NYGMA LAUGHING)
I'm back.
(LAUGHING)
(MAN COUGHS)
(MAN CONTINUES LAUGHING)
(MAN LAUGHING BOISTEROUSLY)
(MAN CLEARS THROAT)
(MAN COUGHS)
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
(MAN CONTINUES LAUGHING)
(GAS HISSING)
(SNIFFING)
What's that smell?
(MISSILE WHISTLING)
(MEN SCREAMING)
(ALARMS SOUNDING)
Uncle Penguin sent me to get you.
Come on, let's get ice cream.
(BLOWS LANDING)
The Narrows is under new management.
(GRUNTING)
- The Narrows is Sampson's turf.
- (WHIMPERING)
And Sampson...
Well, collects protection.
And people need to find out what happens
when you don't pay!
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH WHIMPERING)
(GUN COCKS)
Please. My family.
Do I look like an animal to you?
I wouldn't hurt your family.
(BOTH SCREAMING)
Unless they don't pay me!
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
GORDON: Before Don Falcone died,
he warned me, I had no idea
what I'd brought to the city.
I now know he was talking about the Pyg.
Somebody musfve told him.
My guess, that person has evidence
that links Sofia to the Pyg's murders.
Why not come forward with what you know?
It has to be more than just
my word against hers.
Or are you afraid the truth is
going to drag you down, too?
- Oh, Harvey, we've been over this.
- When did you know?
I swear, I had no idea
until after it was too late.
Now, you can be pissed,
but this is bigger than both of us.
I need to know I can count on you.
Yeah, Jim.
I'II help you take down Sofia.
But then you're gonna have to pay
for what you've done.
I personally guarantee it.
I know an ex-Falcone assassin.
Might have beans to spill.
Went by the name
"the Scandinavian Skinner."
Sit tight.
I have history with the Skinner.
(nooa CLOSES)
(OBJECTS CLA1'I'ERING)
SELINA: You know, you have. like.
No food in here, right?
BRUCE: Selina?
What are you doing here? What's...
What's wrong?
SELINA: Why does something
have to be wrong for me to come by?
Seriously?
I need help. (SIGHS)
You mean money.
(SIGHS) I stole something. fenced it,
now I want to get it back.
And I'd steal it,
but the fence is difficult.
So, I need money.
Why don't you just ask
Barbara Kean for the money?
'Cause I don't wanna get her involved.
Look, I'Il pay you back.
Ijust don't have time
because if the fence sells what I...
But you still haven't told me
why you wanna get it back.
Because it's what I stole
from Roland Charles.
- The Wayne scientist...
- That Ivy killed.
(SELINA SIGHS)
I didn't know
she was gonna do that, Bruce.
(STUTTERS) And l just...
You feel bad.
Look, if you don't wanna help me,
then I'II just find another way.
Let me get some cash.
There's oatmeal raisin cookies
in the blue tin.
(BUZZER SOUNDING)
Why are you dragging me here?
(BARKS)
Cobblepot.
A guy called.
Wanted me to give you a message.
Finally! (EXHALES)
"I can lend you a hand,
but you won't find me helpful.
"My name may sound tasty,
but the flavor is dreadful."
Is it "knuckle sandwich"?
- (CHUCKLES) Yeah.
- No.
- (MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
.(1005 GIGGLING)
Hello, Agnes.
Or should I say, "the Skinner"?
Detective Bullock.
I don't go by that name anymore.
I'm retired.
- You kids, don't spoil your dinner.
- Okay, Grandma.
I'm looking for someone
who might've been Don Falcone's
eyes and ears when he was down south.
Why would I tell you that?
Because we have history.
That history got me four years
in the gulag.
Either you help me,
or I tell your beautiful grandchildren
how their meemaw
used to skin people alive.
Hey, kids, you wanna hear
a really funny story?
AII right. No. it's all right.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
HARVEY: Never mind.
Falcone only really trusted
the bookkeeper.
The one who always smelled of fish.
- Mr. Penn?
- Yeah.
Penn.
And good luck finding him.
I heard he vanished.
Pooh
(GRUNTS ANGRILY) How is Martin gone?
(PANTS)
Never mind.
Penguin is coming.
Go to Arkham and kill him now.
Okey-dokey.
- Oh, by the way...
- (DO0R OPENS)
a buddy of mine
just got out of the hospital.
He's looking for work.
You mind if he tags along?
Hiya.
Just make sure Penguin dies
choking on his own blood.
HARVEY: Why is Cobblepot
in the infirmary?
Heard he mouthed off to a guard.
Then slipped and hit his head.
(GASPS)
Bullock. This is a surprise.
Hey, Oswald. Good to see you, too.
Ijust had a few questions about
a former employee of yours.
- (WOMAN SCREAMING)
- (GASPS)
WOMAN: They got guns!
Open that door!
(PANICKED CHATFERING)
GUARD: Everybody. split up.
HARVEY: Get out of the way. Clear out!
Move, move, move!
Hey!
You two, don't come any closer.
ZSASZ: Bullock?
Dude, I thought you stopped being a cop.
Guess it didn't take, huh?
Not s0 much.
- You remember Wendell, don't you?
- Howdy.
I don't know why you two are here,
and I don't care.
Walk away!
See, I'm afraid we can't do that.
(WEAPON WHIRRING)
We're not leaving here
without the Penguin.
ZSASZ: Harvey. Do yourself a favor.
Give us Penguin,
and live to get drunk another day. Hmm?
As tempting as that sounds, no.
- (BELL RINGING)
- (ALARM BLARING)
GUARD 1: Come on, let's go. Let's go.
(GUARDS CLAMORING)
It's okay.
We'II come back.
GUARD 2: He's escaped.
Oswald Cobblepot has escaped.
(CLAMORING CONTINUES)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
(PANICKED CHATTERING AND SCREAMING)
- (WHIMPERING)
- (GUNSHOTS)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
NYQma.
BRUCE: What?
You're just different.
Different how?
You were a complete douchebag to me
at the club.
And now you're not.
Listen, Selina, about that night...
Oh, no, you're not going to try
to apologize to me, are you?
No, Ijust wanted to say...
Save it.
Because you are probably going to be
a douchebag to me later anyway.
Missed you, too.
Kitty Cat, back so soon?
'Sup, Floyd?
I'm gonna need that stuff
I brought to you the other day.
FLOYD: Oh.
You mean this stuff?
The stuff you tried to break in
and steal last night?
You think I wouldn't check the camera?
Great.
You remember what I said
about being a douchebag?
I'II pay double what you gave me.
This your bank?
How about I take the money
and I keep your stuff?
(ALL GRUNTING)
(eunsnor)
Next time...
- (GRUNTS)
- take the deal.
(GRUNTS) Got it.
I knew that as soon as I rescued Martin
that she'd send her hitmen.
How is Martin?
Snug as a bug in a rug.
Here, will you hold this?
S0, do you wanna know how I found him?
So it turns out, Zsasz,
huge fan of the disco.
- So I dress up as an old Polish...
- Perhaps another time!
Now that Martin is safe,
we need to focus on killing Sofia.
We need a power base.
I know. That's why we're here.
(moon UNLOCKS)
Hello. (CHUCKLES)
Ed. You're back.
- Mmm-hmm.
- How are you doing?
Worlds better. Honestly, thank you.
I...
Oh, no. What happened to your hand?
Sofia Falcone.
Smashed it with a hammer,
and then threw me ou! on the street.
And put Sampson in charge
of The Narrows.
I see.
But together,
we can get that bitch back.
Show her that she can't
just take everything we've built.
Yeah, Oswald, she can't help.
LEE: What is this?
What is going on? What's wrong with you?
I let him out of his cage, and he,
in turn. helped me get out of mine.
You're him.
The Riddler.
(CHUCKLES)
Hi, Lee.
You know, I was really hoping that
you were still running The Narrows,
maybe could help us, but...
Guess not.
Yeah, so what's
your next brilliant idea?
Sofia will have turned Falcone Mansion
into a stronghold.
It will be impossible to get at her.
Oswald, you think
I don't have a backup plan?
I'm gonna have Victor Fries
put you in a block of ice.
I'm gonna take you to Sofia
Iike a chilly Trojan horse,
- pretend to hand you over...
- (CHUCKLES)
Are you kidding me?
It's a fantastic plan.
Try again!
AII right, let me help.
Look, all of your capos
have pledged their loyalty to Sofia...
Do you think I can't handle it?
I know you can't.
Look what she did to me.
I will pull the trigger
on that bitch myself.
That's some tough tongue,
but we both know that's just talk.
Enough! Both of you.
If we wanna fight Sofia, we need muscle.
I agree.
I can tell you where to look.
Don't you think he misses you?
Who... Who is she talking about?
NYGMA: Grundy!
You down here, big fella?
Your best friend and pal,
Edward Nygma.
Hey, guess what? I'm smart again!
(WATER LAPPING)
There he is.
Pale skin, nobody upstairs...
Who's my büddâl?
Correct. You.
Oh, boy.
So, we're corralling allies.
Penguin and I are going
to kill Sofia Falcone.
And we need a big galoot like you
for cannon fodder. How does that sound?
(GRUNTING SOFTLY)
What's your problem?
Why are you looking at me like that?
'(GASPS)
'(GRUNTS)
Oh, dear.
You're not the only one who got smart.
Okay. Butch, I helped you.
You remember?
Hot, hot arm.
Yeah, Ed put out fire.
But you're not Ed anymore.
(GRUNTS)
And I'm not Grundy.
PENGUIN: Where the hell is Ed?
LEE: He'II be here.
No. No, he's betrayed me, too.
I know it.
I never should have trusted him!
Calm down.
No, do not tell me to calm down.
You have no idea what I've been through!
Calm down! Ed will be here.
He will bring Grundy,
and we will make Sofia pay.
I can't wait any longer.
HARVEY: How did Nygma
get in touch with Penguin anyway?
GORDON: I don't know.
Nothing's ever easy with you, is it?
It's always like, "Find Lee,
and then she'Il point us to Ed.
"And then we'II find Penguin.
"And he'll tell us where to find Penn."
Or we could just
talk to Oswald right now.
What?
- (GLASS SHATTERS)
- MAN: Hey, you son of a...
(PENGUIN GRUNTING)
What are you doing here?
We're looking for an Arkham escapee
about yea tall. walks with a limp,
mommy complex?
Those trumped-up charges
you used to put me away
have lost their teeth.
- Martin is still alive.
- So produce him.
PENGUIN: Nope. He is not safe
until Sofia Falcone
has been dealt with permanently.
Ithink you and Iwant
the same thing, Oswald.
We both want Sofia to go away.
Then turn around and walk away.
Let me do what I do.
No. I want her in jail,
and for that I need evidence.
I want your bookkeeper, Mr. Penn.
What would he know about...
That little weasel was working for her!
Yeah, he was working for her,
for Don Falcone, everybody!
You might want to check
your management style, pal.
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
I'm gonna kill him.
Oswald. Oswald.
Calm down.
You show us where we can find Mr. Penn,
and I'II let you walk away.
I don't believe you.
HARVEY: Sofia sent Zsasz
to Arkham to kill you.
Her goons run The Narrows.
How long do you think it's gonna take
till she finds you?
(BREATHING SHAKILY)
(SIGHS)
I overheard Mr. Penn talk about a place
just out of town, near the tri-corner.
The Spa Bosh Sumka.
Offers special therapy.
If he's hiding, he's probably there.
Oswald.
Thank you.
That's really nice.
Now, put your hands behind your back.
No. No! No, we had a deal!
Harvey, what are you doing?
If you want to look
the other way, Jim, fine.
I didn't agree to squat. Come on.
PENGUIN: (soas) No! No!
- I will not forget this!
- Relax.
If your information on Penn is good.
At least you'll be free
of Sofia Falcone.
ZSASZ: Well, well, well.
Sofia's gonna be very curious to know
why you're looking for Penn.
Hey, Penguin. Remember me?
Oh, God, no.
Wait, is Penn important or something?
That's a yes. You see that?
That's his "yes" face.
Get him in the car.
Guess l'II have to go dig him up myself.
Now, you boys want to come quietly,
or do you want to do it the fun way?
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
- The fun way. Nice.
- (GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
(WHIMPERING)
(GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
- Lee.
- Shut up and get down.
(ENGINE STARTS)
- (TIRES SCREECH)
- Lee?
Come on. Let's get out of here.
We need to get to Penn
before Zsasz does.
We need a car.
(SIGHS)
Migraine still?
It's like I've been hit in the head
with a brick.
- (MUFFLED GRUNTING)
- What is that stink?
(MUFFLED, INDISTINCT SPEAKING)
Should've known.
Grundy smell like old dentures.
TABITHA: It's him.
I know. I can smell him.
- (BARBARA SNIFFING)
- Hey there, Barbara.
(GASPS)
Scary.
Nygma tried to recruit me against Sofia.
He's working for Penguin.
(LAUGHS)
I figured after all Ed did to you,
you should be the one to kill him.
Wait, Butch.
Don't just walk away again.
Tabby, I'm gonna find a way
to get back to the old me.
I promise.
(MUFFLED SPEAKING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
- (HIGH PITCHED RINGING)
- (GROANS)
- (MUFFLED, DISTORTED VOICE SPEAKING)
- (BARBARA WHIMPERING SOFTLY)
TABITHA: (ECHOES) Any ideas?
(GASPING)
You okay?
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
I'm fine.
We send Nygma back to Sofia.
She will torture him to get to Penguin.
Lee has no more allies.
Boom, rebellion quells, we're heroes.
Then what about Nygma?
Hejust gets to walk away?
(MUFFLED SPEAKING)
When Sofia doesn't need him anymore,
she'll kill him.
(SIGHS)
Same end result, none of the headache.
Well, we did find Penguin.
But then he got away.
S0 why aren't you looking for him,
instead of wasting my time?
Because I also found out that Gordon
is looking for Mr. Penn.
Find Penn before Gordon does.
Yeah, so, Penn, Penguin...
I mean, where are we priorities-wise?
Do both.
Thank you for coming to my rescue.
Don't bother.
Without you, I can't get to Sofia.
Touching.
- I cannot believe I'm doing this.
- Believe it.
No Ed, no Grundy.
We're running out of time.
You know this cockamamie scheme
will probably get me killed?
If it puts Sofia in the ground,
I'm okay with that.
(GUN cocxme)
VICTOR: The last time you came in here
with one of your schemes
to regain the city,
you promised every resource
I needed to reverse my condition.
So, that didn't happen.
An omission I regret,
and will rectify if given the chance.
Uh-huh.
- (GAS HISSING)
- (PENGUIN YELPING)
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(GRUNTS)
You cannot honestly tell me
you are happy here.
Tinkering away, on whateverthese...
Don't touch that.
You need money for your research,
Sofia wants Penguin.
S0 you deliver him to her,
you can name your price.
VICTOR: I may have something.
Keep this on you. It's on a timer.
Best I can do on short notice.
If being frozen effects my brain
the way it did Nygma,
- I cannot afford...
- Ready?
- Not yet! I...
- Don't care.
(METAL MUSIC PLAYING)
So now you're going to return it?
- Selina, you said...
- Can you do it?
That's really why you came to me.
It wasn't about the money.
You did not kill Roland Charles.
I was there, though.
And what am I supposed to say, I...
"I stole your jewelry. Sorry."
sometimes that's enough.
- (DRILL WHIRRING)
- (NYGMA SCREAMING)
(GRUNTS IN PAIN)
His strength of mind is impressive.
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
You are going to tell me
where to find Penguin,
or I will make all of this
look like a pleasant dream.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah. okay.
I can be done with the teeth,
the eyes or the mind. What am I?
Ican be humorous,
but I'm never funny! (LAUGHS)
What am I?
(conrmues LAUGHING)
(SCREAMS)
(GROANING)
Tell me where he is.
I am telling you! (LAUGHING)
You're just too stupid to figure it out!
(SCREAMING)
- Miss Falcone, you've got a visitor.
- Kind of in the middle of something.
Guy's got Penguin.
(NYGMA GROANS)
Bring him in.
(som scorrs)
(GASPS, CHUCKLES)
Well, this is unexpected.
Heard you were looking for Penguin.
He never was a great boss.
Well, well, Oswald.
Is he alive in there?
VICTOR: Maybe.
I want $100,000.
Pay him.
ZSASZ: I'm not even gonna ask.
Oh, by the way,
I found out where Penn is.
(GASPS)
Take him to the docks, shoot him,
and throw him in the river.
(GRUNTS)
Watch Penguin.
Let's go get Mr. Penn.
(KNOCKS)
MAN: Lovely, Miss Gonzalez, well done.
Pull a little harder. Right.
That's it, Miss McGee. Come on.
(LIVELY CHA'I'I'ER AND LAUGHTER)
What fresh level of hell is this?
WOMAN: Who is hungry?
(PEOPLE MIMICKING BABY NOISE)
GCPD!
We're looking for Arthur Penn.
What are you doing?
Anonymity is a strict edict here
at the resort.
I bet.
- HARVEY: That's him.
- Penn. Penn!
Oh, no.
Let's take a walk.
As you were.
(PEOPLE GIGGLING AND BABBLING)
(ICE CRACKING)
(MUFFLED BEEPING)
- Mr. Cobblepot.
- (SHIVERING)
You are working for her, too!
(CHUCKLING)
- I assure you...
- Of course you are!
Where is she?
- You don't understand.
- (YELLS) Where is she?
- (YELLS)
- (THE DENTIST GRUNTS)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Is it done?
- Sofia left before I could kill her.
She's on her way to stop Gordon.
Meet me at the Spa Bosh Sumka,
and we will kill her together.
(GASPS)
Nygma was here?
Miss Falcone tried to get him
to turn on you.
What?
He endured a tremendous amount of pain.
He wouldn't give you up.
Where is he now?
Her thugs took him to the docks
to kill him.
(GRUNTS)
I have worked for Don Falcone
for years, before Mr. Cobblepot.
When Sofia came to Gotham,
Don Falcone asked me
to keep an eye on his daughter.
She found out.
S0 you made another deal with her,
you weaselly. triple agent, you.
It's how you stay alive
in this business.
And she let me live.
As long as I informed to her
about Mr. Cobblepot.
That's how she was able to stay
one step ahead of Penguin,
with inside information.
Then what?
She asked me to put her
in touch with Lazlo Valentine.
The PYQ-
So I did.
But I told Don Falcone right away.
AII right, you're coming with us.
We need your statement for the record.
Get down!
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING)
- (GORDON GRUNTING)
(GUNSHOTS)
(GUNSHOTS CONTINUE)
Get Penn out of here.
He's all that matters.
We've got to get you to the hospital.
Gunshot would draw attention.
The cops will be here soon.
I can make it till they arrive.
SOFIA: James Gordon.
We could've had a good thing, you and I.
You just had to go and ruin it.
Go.
That's an order.
Get Penn.
Get Gordon.
- (ALL EXCLAIMING)
- Get out!
(GRUNTS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (GUNSHOT)
(GRUNTS)
(GUN CLICKS)
- (SHELLS CLATTER)
- (GRUNTING)
- (TIRES SCREECH)
- HARVEY: Lee!
- Where's Sofia?
- In there with Jim.
- Take the car.
- He's hurt bad.
Get in.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(POLICE SIRENS WAILING)
Can't catch a break today.
Let's go get a milkshake.
(GRUNTING)
SOFIA: Jim, you really are
such a disappointment.
(GRUNTS)
Would it have been so bad,
being in the palm of my hands,
having me. chip away
at your soul little by little?
Was it so important
to rob me of my revenge?
GORDON: That hurt.
- (GUNSHOT)
- (GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
It wasn't about me.
I wasn't going to give you the GCPD.
Of course, it was about you.
Your pride, your arrogance.
Do you think that what I was asking for
was any different than
what my father had for 30 years?
You mean your father who you killed?
Yes.
I killed him,
because he disappointed me.
Just like you.
You know, Jim,
oddly enough, I still care for you.
Beg me for your life.
Ask for forgiveness.
And we can start over.
Sofia...
Goto hell.
SOFIA: James Gordon,
this is where our story ends.
(eunsnor)
- You.
- Yeah.
Me.
Stay with me, Jim.
(ECHOES) Jim, can you hear me?
(NYGMA LAUGHING)
MAN: Come on, now. Come on.
Hey, I've got a riddle for you.
What's got a bullet in its head
and sinks to the bottom of the river?
- You.
- (BOTH LAUGH MANIACALLY)
The real torture
is that those idiotic horns
will be the last I ever hear.
Just do it!
- (GUNSHOTS)
.(30114 GRUNT)
Oswald.
How?
Did you already kill Sofia?
No. She left the mansion
to pursue Jim Gordon.
Why didn't you just stay at the home.
Wait till she came there and killed her?
Then I wouldn't have been here on time.
You gave up your revenge for me?
Trust is so very hard to find in Gotham.
But I trust you, Ed.
I have a strong desire
to never ever see this pier again.
(EXHALES) I agree.
(MONITOR BEEPING STEADILY)
(GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
(SIGHS)
Hey.
Surprised you're alive?
(comon GRUNTS)
Yeah.
- How?
- How do you think?
Lee.
She kept you alive
till the medics got there.
Even one-handed,
she's a damn good doctor.
- Sofia?
- In a coma.
Amazing she's not dead.
Harvey.
When I get out of here,
I'm going to confess.
My connection to Sofia,
my role with the Pyg. AII of it.
I gotta come clean.
No.
What do you mean?
Who would benefit from that? You.
You get to be the martyr,
feel better about yourself.
The GCPD loses its hero. No!
You want to pay your debt?
You live with it.
Just like I do.
So, Sofia wins after all?
It's what the city needs.
Where's Lee?
She went back to The Narrows.
Said she had unfinished business.
- (ALL CHEERING)
- (BLOWS LANDING)
- MAN 1: Not so tough now.
- Get him!
- Yesl Come on!
- MAN 2: You got him!
(GRUNTING)
SAMPSON: AII right.
I'II go. I'II go.
Oh, I know you'll go.
Just not yet.
Hold his hand.
No. No!
No!
What are you doing? No! No!
(GRUNTS) No!
- (GRUNTS)
- (YELLING IN PAIN)
- (LEE GRUNTS)
- (CROWD CHEERING)
Stop! Don't!
- (GRUNTING)
- (SAMPSON YELLING IN PAIN)
("FIRE" PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
(HIGH-PITCHED RINGING)
(GRUNTING)
(MUFFLED) With Sofia gone,
Penguin's gonna try and take control
of Gotham again,
maybe even try and kill us.
Could you just give me a second?
Barbara, we have to act.
- We can't just stand around...
- (SHOUTS) I said shut up!
(GASPING)
(SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)