Previously onGotham...
- Oink. Oink.
- What the...
A cop was murdered last night.
A bagman on your payroll.
I think someone is trying
to send you a message.
Grenade!
We have unfinished business.
Listen.
If you think you're going to...
Don't talk about my mother!
An opportunity awaits you.
With you and Barbara?
Three of us could give all those
creeps a run for their money.
She's making alliances
with politicians.
Building a fortress.
She's been planning a war.
Oswald, I want you to know,
I forgive you.
You started an orphanage?
I wanted to surprise you.
If you don't kill me,
I will kill every one you love.
It doesn't stop 'til
I've butchered every single
swine on Penguin's payroll!
Besides, we both know,
Captain Bullock, you deserve this.
Hold on, buddy.
How long have you been taking money
from Penguin?
You got to understand, Jim,
the debts I got...
It stops now.
Calling dibs on my office?
I ain't dead yet.
Just measuring for when you are.
Shouldn't you be resting?
Let me help you.
I'm fine.
Great. So we can talk
about you taking Penguin's money.
- I'm not that fine.
- I meant what I said, Harvey.
This stops. Today. You hear me?
Hey! Hey!
What the hell is that?
You're trying to change the subject.
Obviously. But seriously
what the hell is that?
Is that blood?
Some fancy-ass guy on the phone.
How was I supposed to know
what we were carrying?
Stench of death, for starters?
I got a cold.
44 boxes.
One for every cop in the precinct.
Pyg's escalating.
He's not just after dirty cops
anymore.
It's the whole GCPD.
- There are 45 cops here.
- Oh, yeah.
The instructions said
don't give nothing
to this one cop here named...
Jim Gordon?
Your support, I really appreciate it.
Enjoy the benefit.
I think as far as the foundation
is concerned...
Helping the needy.
Very good for the soul, Master Bruce.
I have to say I really appreciate
you allowing us to do
the fundraiser here.
The Society meant a great deal
to your father.
As long as I don't have to leave
the house...
Well, you're Bruce Wayne, ain't you?
The world can come to you.
Hey. What the hell?
- Excuse me?
- You knocked into me.
Bruce.
- Sorry, I didn't notice.
- Well, you should've.
- Bruce.
- Honestly. I'm really sorry.
I haven't wanted to push,
Master Bruce.
I mean, what happened with Ra's...
I know that you're hurting.
Just, please, tell me
what I can do to help.
You can get off my back.
I'm sorry.
I just...
I can't stop thinking about...
when I...
I should feel bad.
Guilty.
I... I... I just...
You're just angry.
That anger is concealing
what's really going on.
Unless you face it full-on,
it will consume you.
And it will erupt.
I know...
what you're capable of.
And I don't want to see you,
or anybody else get hurt.
I need some air.
All right.
Next time you see red stuff dripping
from a package,
consider calling the police.
We're COD.
Get the hell out of here.
Hey, Jim.
James! I am so happy
we are working hand in hand
to rid the city of this menace.
He just showed up to offer his help.
Did he?
Nice to meet you, Jim.
I'm Headhunter.
I'm sure you heard of me.
My new security consultant.
Recommended by Victor,
who is off visiting his bubbie.
You want to know
why I carry two pistols?
Overcompensation?
See, I always shoot twice.
The first one does the job.
Every time. But the second one,
well that's just my signature.
He has a signature.
Colorful, isn't he?
But effective.
Mr. Headhunter and my men
will help the GCPD
until this Pyg situation is resolved.
We don't want your help,
or that of your idiot hitman.
Pyg's actions threaten
the both of us.
He's killing my cops, my employees.
Allegedly.
Get this through your head, Oswald.
We don't work for you
and we don't work with you.
Ever.
Well, your captain says otherwise.
Excited to work with you, Jim.
Are you out of your fricking mind?
- Jim, listen...
- You are legitimizing him, Harvey.
He's been legitimized for years.
He was the freaking mayor!
Is it about the money? Is that it?
It's not about that.
How can I know that?
How can you even know that?
Take a look out there, okay?
Half the precinct skipped town
because they didn't want to wear
bacon-flavored death masks.
We need the help.
You are dangerously overreacting.
I'm overreacting because every cop
in this precinct got a death threat.
Except, of course, for you.
So, Penguin's guys are gonna beat
and torture their way
through the city?
Then execute Pyg if they find him?
And?
And the people need to know
they don't need gangsters
to keep them safe.
I'll tell you what,
I'm gonna find Pyg,
alive and I'll bring him to justice.
Good for you.
Three cops just went missing.
Where?
It's gonna be tough.
It's the Narrows.
So, that's it.
We're shutting up the shop.
So long. Farewell. Toodle-loo.
I can't believe this.
I can.
All this was so I could be Ra's eyes
and ears in Gotham.
He was bankrolling us
and now he's gone.
So I'm pulling the plug.
Help yourself to whatever.
So all of this being partners,
building something together, lies.
A sales pitch.
I couldn't do it alone.
We can still spy on the jerks who
come in here and get intel on jobs.
We can make it work.
What?
And the three of us stay together
like a plucky little family?
Well, how about a little parting
lesson from big sis.
In this life, you're on your own.
Always.
Bonus lesson,
never make Bellinis from a can.
I followed a buyer
from the Street Demonz.
They have a chop shop across town
and I saw exactly
where they hide their stash.
Let's hit it. Show her she's wrong.
We're not gonna rip off one
of Gotham's biggest motorcycle gangs.
Why not?
You and I will find something else.
All right, PD here,
Penguin's guys over there.
Three missing officers.
Patel from our precinct,
Fisoli and Perkov from the two-two.
Good Lord, there's blood all over.
He got them here.
Clear view from dozens of windows.
- Someone saw it.
- They sure did.
All right, bring it in, everybody.
Come on.
This is the Narrows.
The poorest of the poor,
the hardest of the hard.
Now, I don't need to tell you that
they got a code of silence down here,
which means we got to make them
more scared of us
than they are of their own people.
We go floor by floor.
- Air mail!
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
Let's get them! Move on out!
This is gonna be fun.
Get off of him! Get back.
Hey! Hey!
Get off! Get off of him.
They're potential witnesses.
They're not perps.
This is the Narrows, Gordon.
You think there's a difference?
- Step away, Ruseckas.
- Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Ruseckas, they need you upstairs.
You two, go. Now.
Working out great.
If it gets me my cop killer,
yeah, it is.
Right.
Bruce?
I just wanted to say hi.
I'm Grace.
We went to school together.
Grace Blomdhal.
Yeah.
Sorry I...
It's been years.
I didn't even recognize you.
I heard you were homeschooling.
Yeah.
I...
Why aren't you in school?
'Cause it's Saturday.
I don't mean to knock your fundraiser
but is there any chance
you're as bored as I am?
You'd have to be pretty bored.
So do you want to maybe go
somewhere?
Yeah.
May I?
Ma'am, please.
I'm Detective Gordon.
We didn't see nothing.
But you knew those missing cops.
Or knew of them.
Right?
Three officers, different precinct,
same patrol car
they were freelancing.
Look, I know how it is down here.
A lot of bad stuff happens.
Half the time it's the cops doing it.
They were running some sort
of protection racket, am I right?
You sit over here.
Yeah?
It gives you a pretty good view.
So, what did you see?
Please, I need you to leave.
No one's gonna know
you told me anything.
I give you my word.
- Can I help?
- Get out of here.
Now.
Will do, Jim.
Hey!
This is ridiculous.
We're all on the same team.
No, no, come on.
Come on. Come, come yeah.
If the old lady doesn't talk,
the old man gets it!
And after that, I go apartment
by apartment until I get an answer!
Drop it!
Back at you, Jim.
Everybody stand down!
I'm giving you three seconds.
I'm giving you two.
No one is counting!
You, drop your weapon!
I'll tell you what I saw!
He took them.
He was driving a hearse.
I didn't see the plate.
It's all right.
We don't need the plate.
Just tell me which direction
was he headed.
Down Seventh.
Heading west.
Hey, thanks, Jim.
You know, I never really did
the whole good-cop-bad-cop thing.
It's quite effective.
West on Seventh that's Hoover Island.
It's tiny, there's only a couple
of abandoned buildings.
We can canvas the whole area
in ten minutes.
Yeah.
And the second shot,
well, that's just my signature.
I know it doesn't look good
but no one got hurt too bad.
And we got what we needed, right?
You just, you got to trust me
on this one, partner, okay?
People, we're moving out
to Hoover Island right now!
Let's move! Go!
Go!
Come on!
Last door, let's go!
Empty.
I got two in here!
This man is alive. Call an ambulance.
- Help me.
- We will. We're here.
Jim! Pyg disappeared.
There's no sign of the third cop
anywhere.
All right. Get some help.
Hold on.
My God.
It's okay.
As you can see behind me,
we just had a major police operation.
A raid of some sort on this
abandoned...
- Sofia, look!
- Hoover Island.
Those are my men.
And there's that Headhunter person
I was talking about.
Kind of a moron but he is effective.
Another is in stable condition
and on his way to Gotham...
So, technically,
I saved that cop's life.
Such great PR.
Excuse me. Little person.
Scoot.
Is co-opting the police not the most
brilliant idea I have ever had?
It is Pax Penguina taken
to a whole other level.
Hello?
Isn't it?
You don't need to know what I think.
Well, now I definitely do.
Ears.
My father never would have publicly
aligned with the GCPD.
They are incompetent and unreliable.
Eventually, they will fail and fail
big and you will fail with them.
So, that's what I think.
Thank you for your input.
You're welcome, Oswald.
Because you have shown me
very clearly what not to do.
In fact I'm gonna get more involved.
Personally.
Don't ask for my opinion
if you don't want to hear it.
Okay.
Look at that!
Come on!
Yo! The alarm's going off!
What the hell!
Someone broke in?
I was... I was under the car.
The stash is gone.
Guy must've got out.
So, you must've messed up
your only job.
Guess it's time to burn rubber.
Wait! No!
No! Let me go!
No! No!
- Yeah?
- Hey.
We scanned the entire area still
no sign of Pyg or Officer Patel.
- You get anything off Fisoli?
- No. No.
I'll...
Wait a minute. He's coming to...
I'll call you back.
Officer Fisoli.
It's okay. It's all right.
You're on your way to Gotham General.
You're safe. I'm Detective Gordon.
I know who you are.
You were taken by the Pyg.
Did you happen to see his face?
I don't know. He wore a mask.
The others?
Perkov didn't make it.
Patel's gone missing.
- Do you remember anything?
- I don't know, man.
He was torturing us for hours.
He was singing nursery rhymes,
talking crazy.
Oh, geez.
I watched him bleed out Perkov.
- Did he say anything about Patel?
- I don't know. I don't remember.
Look at me.
Look at what he did to me.
Okay, all right, all right,
all right.
Let's take a break.
Why is he doing this?
'Cause he's insane.
But it's more than that.
I guess he's just reached
a breaking point.
There's so much rot in Gotham.
All of it, high to low.
Sometimes even I feel like breaking,
you know?
I was on Penguin's pad.
Started off small stuff deliveries
and payoffs and then...
it got bad.
I get it.
I've done bad stuff myself.
For Penguin, even.
But you and I can make it right.
Once I get Pyg, I'm gonna
take down the Pax Penguina.
And then I'm gonna go
after the dirty cops, one by one.
Now you have a chance...
to make right
what you've done wrong.
Help me.
Pyg is planning something.
Nearby. He was...
Maybe where he took Patel.
He... he... he kept saying
something about...
"I'll bring justice to where
there is... justice no more."
Justice. A courthouse.
There ain't no courthouse
in the Narrows.
There's one they abandoned
a few years back.
- Pull it over! I'm getting out.
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you, Officer Fisoli.
- Hey.
You are one of the good ones, Jim.
Hey, Brant. I ran into an old friend.
Bruce Wayne.
Bruce, this is Emma Hsueh
and Tommy Elliott.
- You two know each other?
- Oh, yeah.
Last time I saw this guy,
he punched me in the face.
- I should go.
- Okay.
Hey, hold on, bro.
I totally deserved it. If anything,
you should've hit me harder.
So true.
He was such a jerk back then.
- Okay.
- Little heads up,
next time you just bring
some random kid to my place.
Parents' place, Brant.
He's so jealous.
Brant wanted Grace all to himself.
Whatever. You want a shot?
- Maybe sample some party favors?
- I'm good.
Oh, I forgot about this guy.
Total animal.
So what do you do for fun?
I used to walk on rooftops
and fight crime.
Now I'm not so sure.
You're a bigger dork than I remember.
Just kidding.
Hey, whatever happened to that, that,
that creepy old guy, the butler?
Is he still, buttling?
I'm kidding.
It's a joke.
- Seriously, does he buttle with you?
- Bruce!
- Bruce! No!
- Stop!
So, does he buttle with you?
Brant, didn't you say you
had a hookup at that club?
Yeah. Yeah, this is lame. Let's go.
Brant's a tool but this'll be fun.
There partner.
- You followed me?
- Didn't have to.
Your captain told me
where you were headed.
I guess he thought
maybe you needed some help.
Hi, Jim. Thanks for leading the way.
We'll take it from here.
Keep watching me like that
and I'll think you don't trust me.
Just give me my money
so I can get out of here.
- Where are you?
- Okay, I don't want to hear
how I'm an idiot.
I'm at the Demonz' place.
It's, it's bad.
- What?
- I'm hiding but...
there are three of them, strapped.
And they just called backup.
You idiot.
How about you yell at me
after you come get me?
Just wait right there.
I kind of have to.
Selina's at the Demonz.
We got to get her.
Isn't this what they call
a teachable moment?
Let her claw her way out.
- We owe her.
- That is what her salary was for.
Look, she only went there to prove
that we can make this work,
us running heists together.
Oh. Then she might have considered
not getting caught.
She just wants a purpose.
She wants a home.
Then sucks for her.
You know, I thought you'd changed.
Like maybe you could think
about somebody
other than yourself for once.
Then sucks for you.
It was my idea to offer
my consulting services.
And I daresay it has been
a smashing success,
the Pax Penguina
taken to the tactical level.
And now we have reason to believe
that the notorious Pyg is trapped
in the courthouse behind us.
- So let me...
- Look I know it's a bit of a circus.
But there was no way in hell
I was gonna let you go in there
alone, all right?
The Pyg ain't gonna go down easy.
So, I say, we let Penguin's thugs
go in first,
let them be the cannon fodder
instead of our guys.
It's win-win.
End of conversation.
- Yeah.
- Did you know,
I spell my name with a "Y?"
I didn't. You want to meet me
somewhere, we can talk about it?
Please, Jim, I'm not that dumb.
Anyway, P-Y-G.
The "Y" is because it's short
for "Pygmalion."
Like I'm creating a new,
better Gotham.
- And I'm creating a new you, Jim.
- Really?
Yes, except there's a slight hitch.
I can't recreate you if you're,
you know, dead.
Which you will be if you go in there.
- In where?
- Oh, don't act dumb.
Only I get to do that.
Let them play cops and robbers.
It'll be fun.
But not you.
Why should I believe anything
you have to say?
Because,
"you are one of the good ones, Jim."
Harper! Call Gotham General.
Find out what the hell happened
to Fisoli!
Check again.
- Jones. Brant Jones.
- I heard you the first time.
You said we could get in.
Nope.
Stupid bouncer's acting
like he doesn't know who I am.
He knows who you are.
He just doesn't care.
I don't care how much money you have.
You're a dork and a freak, Wayne.
- You always were.
- Brant, chill.
Give me a second, guys.
- It's your fault for inviting him.
- Shut up, Brant.
Wait, who's Bruce talking to?
Let's go, guys.
Not him.
Let me talk to the owner.
You're standing next to him.
I bought the place.
- You guys in or out?
- In.
You can't find either of them?
No, they're not standing
over him anymore.
They can't find the ambulance.
Call it off!
Call off the raid.
Fisoli's dead.
The guy in the ambulance
was the Pyg in disguise.
What the hell are you talking about?
Pyg called me. He warned me off.
He used the same phrase
he used in the ambulance.
He fed us the clue to get us here.
It has to be a trap.
So the insane serial killer who hates
cops warned you to save your life,
- because why, now?
- Because I'm against dirty cops.
Oh! Except all of the times
you are one.
I'm telling you, Harvey, call it off.
Call it off.
I have another interpretation, Jim.
The Pyg is not trying to save you.
He's trying to save himself
by stopping the raid.
You are being played.
And not for the first time,
I might add.
We called Gotham General.
They can't locate Fisoli,
or the ambulance.
Jim, it's Gotham General.
It's a madhouse down there.
If I'm correct, the Pyg isn't even
in the courthouse.
I came directly from the ambulance.
There is no way he beat me here.
- You're wrong! Pyg is in there, Jim!
- He's right!
We got a spotter across the street
that got a visual on Pyg in there,
standing next to Patel
tied to a chair.
- I swear.
- Look, I can't explain it.
All I know is, this is a trap.
Now, you asked me to trust you.
I am asking you to trust me.
It's so tiresome!
Start the operation!
Jim, I'm sorry.
I'm with Penguin on this one.
We got to think about Patel.
Let's move out, people!
You better pray I can clean up
your mess on this one, Harvey.
You are out of line, pal!
And you are gonna get our guys
slaughtered!
Jim Gordon,
I am ordering you to stand down!
Finally, a good idea, Harvey! Boys?
We've gone over the game plan,
people.
You know what to do. Let's go.
When's our guys coming?
How should I know? You called them.
It's about time. Come on...
I'll draw their fire.
You see an opening, run.
Screw that. Whatever we're doing,
we're doing together.
Well, I guess, now we see
if I taught you how to use that whip.
Hello? Excuse me?
- Did you guys order Thai?
- No.
Good, 'cause I don't have any.
- Nice shooting.
- Obviously.
Give me my cut.
- Barbara.
- I'm sorry.
Did you want a hug?
I just killed five guys for you.
Actually, we did it together.
So that's it?
We're just over?
Over?
Think I came down here for kicks?
You're coming back to the nest.
We got a shipment coming in
and a business to run.
Well, come on.
Hey!
Got him!
Come on!
Harvey.
Damn it!
Oh, no.
Patel. Oh.
It's a setup!
Get out!
The exits are blocked!
That's not our guns.
They're pinned down.
Hey! Come on, back up.
Get in there.
Get in there!
Headhunter's hit!
Ruseckas!
Harper! Get Patel, now!
Shoot the chain!
Get down!
Come on.
I did not order the cops in there.
I do not have that authority.
I made a suggestion.
- It was Captain Bullock...
- Gordon. Gordon!
How did you find the courage to
run in and save all of those people?
If the Pyg is watching the GCPD
is gonna take you down.
And that was Detective James Gordon
with a very modest,
if I may say, statement
about his genuinely heroic...
- Way to go, Jim.
- Thanks.
They think Patel's gonna make it.
Congratulations, Jim.
You're a hero.
And I'm just the cop who shot a cop.
This is Gordon.
Wow. You were amazing.
Oh, I was right about you.
You are a "get things done" type,
Jim Gordon.
Oh, and those things
that you want to get done,
well...
they're the same things I want,
Only if you want to go to prison
for the rest of your life.
Well, now that's just mean.
I'm gonna find you.
Oh, I hope you do.
'Cause I want to thank you
in the flesh, flesh, flesh.
Because what you said
about the rot in Gotham,
high to low, so concisely phrased,
well, gave me an idea.
The next step in my plot.
It's a saga.
It's an epic.
It's a spectacle.
And you're my muse, Jimmy Gordon.
I'll see you soon.
Man!
Well, I guess Gordon was right.
You know, we should've...
Second one's my signature.
Dude.
This is awesome.
I always knew there was another side
to you, Bruce Wayne.
I think I'm gonna try it out
for a while.
Thanks. That's from all of us,
even if they're not saying it.
Thank you, Detective.
You'd have done the same.
Yeah, but not as well.
- We got an unlicensed robbery.
- I got a license.
Like I told him,
I just don't know where I put it.
Oh, wait. It's in my boot.
Oh, we ain't accepting these no more.