Previously onGotham...
That's for Reggie. Now I don't know
what you want with Master Bruce.
But I'm certain
that his life's gonna be damn
slight better without you in it.
I would be honored if you would
consider endorsing me for Mayor.
If you can give me your word,
we won't have to face it alone.
You'll have my endorsement.
It's been sometime
since I had a meal like this.
You should come over more often.
- We can, like, hangout or whatever.
- I'd like that.
Let go of me you freak.
Listen to me!
I did it for you.
Kristen.
And I've been following the goings on
at Wayne Enterprises.
- What have you learned?
- That your father was a good man
and in spite of that bad things
happen at this company.
You were looking
for Penguin's mother, weren't you?
I have to obey him in all things.
Penguin has brain washed
this poor soul.
Can we help?
I'll leave you two to it.
Father Creal.
- You have the Wayne boy?
- Not yet. But soon.
- I found your mother.
- Where?
In a warehouse, down by the port.
You're sure this is it?
I'm sure, boss.
Once my mother is safe,
we go after Galavan and his sister.
They're going to pay for what
they've done.
Mother?
Mother!
You're okay.
Thank God.
Oswald?
Is that really you?
Your sweet face.
Like a vision.
I'm taking you home.
Okay?
No, no, no.
And there I was thinking
you understood
the meaning of consequences.
Consequences, yes.
I assure you that my understanding
of consequences
will be made quite clear
once my mother is outside.
But we've had so much fun together.
My sister gets attached
to her playthings,
so I must insist she stay.
And those bolt cutters, useless.
The only way out of there...
is with this.
Very well. Butch?
Shoot them both in the head
and grab the key.
- Oswald!
- Mother, I'm sorry.
But what they've done to you
will not stand!
I gave you an order!
Shoot them both in the head!
No.
No, no, no. That's not possible.
You have to obey me.
You have to!
That time has passed.
They fixed me.
Tabi is well versed in the protocols
of conditioning.
There's always a trigger word
implanted during the process.
All I had to do is get Butch
to remember what it is.
I'll admit, it took a few tries.
And now...
here we are.
Please.
I can still be valuable.
You'll see.
I so wish that were true.
Then kill me
if you must but let her go.
I'm begging you.
Doesn't look like begging to me.
Indeed. Half-hearted at best.
Please.
I'll do anything.
Perhaps she has served a purpose.
Don't pout.
You still have the former Mayor.
He's so dull.
He just moans all the time.
I told you everything would be okay.
Didn't I?
And it will be.
No!
Oswald?
What is wrong?
You look so sad.
Nothing's wrong, mother.
Nothing at all.
We're together now.
That's all that matters.
That's all that's ever mattered.
Right?
Ever since, you were a little baby.
My little Cobblepot.
I'm sorry.
This is my fault.
Please forgive me. I'm so sorry.
For what?
You were always such a good boy.
No.
Kill him.
Dump the bodies...
anywhere.
You don't have the stomach
to kill me yourself?
No wonder your family
was run out of town.
You come from a long line of cowards!
Fine, fine.
Any last words?
Yes.
I am going to kill you.
You are a psychopath.
I am not the man you think I am.
I would never do anything
to hurt you.
Rise and shine.
What are you doing here?
- I banished you for good.
- Almost.
Love of a good woman and all that.
Though we both know
how that turned out.
Yikes.
That was an accident.
I'm not that man.
I'm gonna make this right.
See, I knew you'd wake up
all boo-hooey.
You probably have half a mind
to turn yourself in.
Luckily, I have the other half.
- Do you like magic tricks?
- What?
Of course you like magic tricks,
after all, I do.
Well, guess what?
I can make a body disappear.
Where is she?
Where is Ms. Kringle's body?
Open the envelope.
"I hid her body
while you were catching some Z's,
you'll need a helping hand, so look
for her initials down at the GCPD."
You went to my work last night?
Well, technically, you did.
I was just in the driver's seat,
so to speak.
How?
You're a figment of my imagination.
A projection of impulse.
Nothing more!
That is uncalled for.
Uncalled for?
You high-jacked my body
while I was asleep
and you stole my dead girlfriend!
Okay, yes.
It's true.
But I'm doing this for your own good.
If I was you.
Which, again, I sort of am.
I'd get cracking.
You do want to find the body first,
right?
Reporting live from City Hall
as we celebrate
the latest Mayoral election.
Early exit point confirm
that Gotham city's new Mayor
will be Theo Galavan,
who is projected
to win in a landslide,
helped by the endorsement
of many prominent citizens
including Police Union President,
James Gordon,
city Comptroller Edwin...
I can't believe you're going
to be Mayor of this sinkhole.
Can I go to the victory party
tonight?
You promised me fun.
When are we gonna unleash
a little hell?
There'll be plenty of time
for unleashing hell and parties,
once Bruce Wayne
has signed over his company
and met his unfortunate destiny.
Until then, I need focus.
Young Bruce has become fond of you.
His trust will be crucial
when the time comes.
I need you to ensure that no one else
is whispering in his ear
until I make my offer.
See this finger?
I've got little Bruce wrapped tight
around it.
What a vixen you've become.
You make me very proud.
And we have Penguin to deal with.
- I'm on it.
- No.
I'm about to become mayor.
I'm gonna have an army
at my disposal.
Time to use it.
Looks like you backed
the right horse.
- You trust him?
- A Gotham politician?
About as far as I can throw him.
But if he gives the GCPD
what it needs, he's all right by me.
You know, Selina said Penguin was
behind the Wayne Enterprise fires.
So?
So first, he's going after Mayoral
candidates, next thing you know,
he's burning down buildings.
It doesn't make any sense.
Guy's an abacus of crazy.
Nothing he does surprises me.
What the hell happened?
Penguin.
He tried to kill our next Mayor.
Mr. Cobblepot knew that I was poised
to win the election today
and he came to me
seeking an alliance.
And you refused.
I politely declined, yes.
So he stabbed you in the neck?
That seems like a pretty extreme
reaction. Even for Penguin.
We've been trying to build a case
against Penguin since I got here.
We assume that he's
behind the earlier attacks
on the other candidates as well.
And this is the second time
he's tried to kill me.
The man is a menace.
And one that I fully intend
to put behind bars.
I assume you have something for me?
Arrest warrant for Oswald Cobblepot,
as well as search and seizures on all
his properties and known associates.
Quite a list.
We'll get right on it.
- Anything else?
- Yes.
In light of recent events,
Judge Turnball has declared
a state of emergency
and granted the mayor's
office additional powers.
Meaning what, exactly?
The moment I'm sworn in,
I'm implementing a curfew
and I'm ordering your Strike Force
to begin door-to-door searches
until Mr. Cobblepot is apprehended.
You're talking about martial law.
We're talking about bringing
a dangerous fugitive to justice.
We'll be acting
within our legal rights.
- Am I right, Mr. Dent?
- Absolutely.
You'll have our full support, sir.
Thank you, Captain.
Captain Barnes.
Detective Gordon?
You seem hesitant.
Cautious.
You, you told me we needed to use
every method at our disposal to go
after men like Penguin.
Men who don't play by the rules.
Desperate times
call for a strong measure.
I have no problem going after Penguin
with everything we've got
but if we start kicking down
the doors of average citizens
and policing through fear,
we're no better than he is.
People still need to trust us.
And they will.
Because at the end of the day
all people want is to feel safe.
Just remember, Detective.
You came to me.
Congrats Mr. Mayor.
It is official.
Theo Galavan will be the Mayor
of Gotham.
A crowd has gathered outside
and the excitement is brimming.
And in just a moment we'll also be
talking to many of the supporters
that gave up their time
and effort to support...
What do you have against
the front door?
Nothing.
It's the ape who opens it
who I could live without.
I haven't seen you in a month.
Selina, what are you doing here?
You wouldn't believe
the week I've had.
This friend of mine, Bridgit,
decided to build this fire suit...
- Selina.
- Some people just don't...
Whose is that?
Sorry.
I got lost on the way back from...
Hello?
Hi.
Silver St. Cloud,
this is my friend Selina.
Selina this is Silver.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
Are you staying for lunch?
- No.
- Please say you are.
I just moved here
and don't know many people.
Bruce, go tell Alfred
to set another place for lunch.
Come on. It'll be fun! Go.
Shoo.
While it's just us girls,
let me give you a little advice...
you come around here again.
Well, that would be bad...
for you.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Bruce's friend.
His only friend.
And you're a piece of gutter trash.
Now tell me something, would anyone
miss you if one day you were just...
gone?
I didn't think so.
I told Alfred.
What are you guys talking about?
Nothing.
Just girl stuff.
"You'll need a helping hand...
Look for her initials
down at the GCPD.
down at the GCPD."
Kristen Kringle. K-K.
K-K. K-K...
Come on.
Hey, Mike, can you give me
a hand with this?
Putting Penguin in the crosshairs
of the GCPD
will drive him underground.
We can't kill him
if we can't find him.
We won't have to find him.
He's going to deliver himself to us.
And why would he do that?
Penguin's rage will consume
his better judgment,
leaving him with an insatiable
craving for revenge.
All we have to do is keep him hungry
and invite him to dinner.
And then I get to kill him.
Yes, kitten.
Then you get to kill him.
First, I want to thank this city
for the immense trust it
has placed in me.
I'm eager to get to work.
I'd also like to address
the recent attempt on my life
by the man known as Penguin.
It is true that he attacked me
and as of now, he is still at large.
Men such as Penguin
will no longer be tolerated.
These are men who scurry
from the light of decency
like cockroaches.
Men who not even a mother could love.
He dies.
Tonight.
Yeah. Got it.
Gilzean's holed up
in a booze joint downtown.
- Penguin?
- And get this.
Word on the street is,
Gilzean's started his own crew.
Sounds like they had a falling out.
Maybe he's ready to talk.
Yeah.
Hey. I heard about what happened
to our new Mayor.
- Never a dull moment, huh?
- No kidding.
You left your keys again
this morning.
What's this one?
A key to my apartment.
- Oh?
- I'll be in the car.
What? It's just a key.
Yeah. I know.
Do you want a key to my place?
Not even a little bit.
Wait. Do you have a place?
I think so.
Sorry. Caught me off guard.
I guess I do spend most nights there.
Which I love.
What I don't love is hauling ass
out of bed at 2.00am
when you come home from a stakeout
smelling of chili dogs.
I love to watch you squirm.
I was not squirming.
Little squirm.
I had no idea we were entertaining
today, Master Bruce.
Anyone else popping by?
No. Thank you, Alfred.
This is marvelous, Alfred.
I fell in love with Lapsang souchong
when I lived in Fujian.
Driving through the Wuyi region,
all you could smell is the burning
cedar they use to smoke leaves.
Right, well technically
it's, pinewood, miss
but I appreciate the enthusiasm.
That smell really does slap you
in the face.
Doesn't it? Alfred.
So, Selina?
Tell me about yourself.
Any family?
You're really buying her act?
I beg your pardon?
Let me ask you a question.
How long have you been
a two-faced slut?
- Selina!
- No seriously, what are you after?
It's the money, right?
I mean it's not his wacky sense
of humor.
- Think I should go.
- No wait.
Is that a tear?
You're good.
I'm sorry. Goodbye, Bruce.
Silver.
What did you just do!
I know you're not the best judge of,
like, you know, people.
But that girl is bad news.
I just did you a favor.
I want you to leave.
Fine.
- Whatever.
- Maybe you're right.
Maybe I'm not the best judge
of people.
Because all this time
I thought you were my friend.
But clearly you have no idea
what that means.
"I'm tired of hiding
and want to be free.
To locate her body
find the two things missing from me."
Back of her head kind of looks funny.
It's like the top of a pencil.
Why are you doing this?
Because it's fun!
And it's good for you.
How is it good for me to be tortured?
To be driven insane?
I'm trying to show you who you are.
How have you not realized that yet?
Though, to be honest,
I'm surprised you haven't
figured out this riddle yet.
Should I have made it easier?
You could start
by using proper grammar.
A period at the end
of a sentence is standard...
"Find the two things missing
from me."
M period, E period.
Oh, God.
"M.E." Medical Examiner.
You didn't!
I did.
I say we wait and see
if someone can walk us inside,
try and keep things civil.
Did I tell you I was thinking
about getting a cat?
- What?
- Hey, how are you?
Why don't you get your head
in the game here?
Sorry. It's just...
Do you believe Galavan's story?
Questions like that are above my pay
grade and below my sense of wonder.
Penguin's a pragmatist.
Hitting Galavan
for refusing an alliance,
that doesn't get him anything
but heat.
So, what really happened, you think?
Few months ago, nobody knew
who Galavan was, right?
Now, all of a sudden, he's Mayor?
Doesn't happen by accident.
It takes planning.
And it takes help.
Guys like Galavan
are born on third base.
Stealing home
is practically a birthright.
Think about the timing.
He shows up just after Mayor James
disappears.
A massacre at the gala turns him
into a hero.
Penguin's assassination attempts
on mayoral candidates
launched his campaign.
Everything that's gone down
up to this point
you could argue was orchestrated.
Look, what you're talking
about is Machiavellian-level crazy
even by Gotham's standards.
Yeah.
Here's our door pass.
Yeah, so your mother tells you.
Yeah, his mama stopped talking
to me ages ago.
Finally.
- Hey, hey!
- I wouldn't.
- Come on.
- I really wouldn't.
That's a lot of firepower
there, Butch.
You expecting company?
Neighborhood ain't
what it used to be, Jim.
Where's Penguin?
- How should I know?
- You're the boss's lap dog
and you don't know
where your owner is?
I ain't nobody's lap dog.
- Not anymore.
- Prove it.
Tell us why the hell Penguin
went after Galavan.
I ain't telling you anything
and unless you have a warrant
I'm gonna have to ask
you boys to leave.
Yeah, see the thing is,
our newly elected Mayor
kind of wants results on this.
So we drag you in, chances
are that's where you're gonna stay.
I'm here for Gilzean.
Anyone who leaves now, leaves alive.
Anyone who stays, dies.
You have 60 seconds to do the math.
Sorry, Butch.
Seriously?
No honor among scumbags, huh?
Hey, don't shoot. I'm out of here.
What are you doing?
You tell us what the hell
is going on with Penguin
or we leave you with Zsasz.
You can't do that.
- Bullock?
- We can totally do that!
Galavan was telling Penguin
what to do.
Knocking off the candidates.
Torching the buildings.
It all came down from Galavan.
Why the hell was Penguin
taking orders?
Kidnapped Penguin's mother.
He was keeping her for leverage.
Kidnapped?
Jim?
I think we need to go.
I didn't think Galavan would actually
go through with it...
Go through with what?
GCPD!
Put down your weapons!
We're outmanned here
big time, partner.
Yeah.
But not outgunned.
Oh, hell, yeah.
I'll take that as a no.
See you later, Butch.
That's a new one.
You think he was telling the truth?
Nobody's telling the truth.
This is Gotham.
Bruce.
What a lovely surprise.
Hello, sir. I was looking for Silver.
She's here.
Seemed a bit upset when she came in.
Yes, sir. A friend of mine stopped
by the house while Silver was there.
- They...
- Say no more.
I was your age once.
Your feelings do you credit.
I never met your father
but it's clear that he instilled
in you a sound moral compass.
He did.
You know we're both very alike.
Born into wealth and privilege.
Yet forced to walk our lives alone.
Haunted by loss.
Driven to prove ourselves worthy
of those who came before.
Be careful, Bruce.
That way of thinking, the need
to fill the void, it can consume you.
Does it ever go away?
No.
But you can find closure.
A way to move on without letting go.
How?
Well, I don't want
to make any promises
but when the time is right
we'll talk again.
I, need to get ready for the party.
Excuse me.
I knew you'd come.
No one is to kill Galavan but me.
- Understand?
- Boss, I got what you're feeling.
Mother's love, it's the most
beautiful, most simple...
Gabe!
Cops aren't gonna let you
within a 100 feet of Galavan.
Let us whack him for you.
Please.
No.
He's mine.
Now, let's get dressed.
We've got a party to attend.
Listen up, people.
Our newly elected Mayor
is going ahead
with his victory celebration tonight.
He will be exposed.
He will be vulnerable.
And he will be protected by you.
The brave men and women
of this police force.
You all have your assignments.
Detective Gordon here
will be running point.
Detective.
Penguin has already made one attempt
on Galavan's life today.
We should be ready for anything.
Let's show this city
what it means to carry a badge.
As you were!
I want check-ins from perimeter teams
every five minutes.
Martinez, how's the Avenue looking?
All clear.
Sniper teams Alpha and Bravo report
all clear as well.
Copy that.
What'd you find out?
Spoke to the Super
at Gertrud Kapelput's building.
Turns out, no one has seen her
for two weeks.
Timeline matches Gilzean's story.
Maybe. Or maybe the old broad
is on a sunset cruise.
You know, there's something
that Gilzean said that I can't shake.
He said he never thought Galavan
would go through with it.
Go through with what?
I don't think Gertrud Kapelput
is on a cruise.
Ladies and gentlemen,
let me be the first
to officially introduce you
to the Honorable Theo Galavan.
The new Mayor of Gotham!
Ed?
- Oh, my...
- What are you doing?
Dr. Thompkins? Hello.
I'm just double-checking notes
for a Jane Doe case I'm working.
Do you need help?
No. No, no, no. She's all gone.
She's, I'm sorry. I'm, I'm all done
with checking my notes.
What notes?
It's all up here.
Do you realize that by assigning
simple mnemonic devices
to case files
you can produce recall capacity
equal to that of photographic
or even eidetic memory?
Ed? What's going on?
Okay. Sorry.
Truth be told...
I was hoping to run into you here.
Alone.
It's Ms. Kringle.
Just...
We had a fight.
I'm sorry.
Every relationship hits a rough patch
now and then.
And you've been so supportive
and I was hoping that maybe
we, we could go grab a coffee
and you could give me some advice.
Do you want to finish up
what you were doing first?
No, no, no.
No, I, I can come back another time.
It's not like they're gonna go
anywhere, right?
- You'd think so.
- Yeah, okay.
- Detective Gordon.
- Okay. That's it, sir.
Perfect. Thank you so much.
I, heard about your shootout today.
Something about one of Penguin's
former Lieutenants, a Butch Gilzean?
Some men ambushed us
as we were questioning him.
He escaped.
Did you get anything
out of him before the attack?
No.
It's a pity.
Well...
Mayor, Mayor.
Mr. Mayor!
Detective, I have a large group
of men approaching
from off the main road.
I have eyes on the target.
Appears to be Cobblepot, sir.
Hold your fire.
Perimeter units, prepare to engage.
- The target is down!
- Martinez! I said hold your fire!
It wasn't us.
We have an unknown shooter
on the roof.
I repeat we have an unknown shooter
Martinez? Is Penguin dead?
No. It wasn't him.
Find the other shooter
and find Penguin!
We need him alive!
Detective, all the targets
are dressed as Penguin
and all are heavily armed.
Positive ID is impossible.
Martinez, you're clear to engage.
All perimeter units crash
our location. Now.
Drop it.
Turn around.
Hands above your head. Now.
So forceful.
I like a strong, confident man.
Help!
Oh, my God!
We got to get you out of here.
Radio his driver.
Have him pull the car around
to the back service entrance.
- Got it?
- Yes, sir.
- Cover us?
- No problem.
Southeast building.
Remaining officers stay inside
and clear the lobby.
Confirmed. Primary is on the move.
Initiating exit plan
near the south entrance.
Roger that.
Detective Gordon is en route
to the rear entrance with the Mayor.
Need their limo at the back service
entrance, stat.
Copy that.
Get him out of here!
Go!
Hello, Jim.
Please step aside.
You know I can't do that.
You would if you knew what
kind of man you were protecting.
Shoot him, Detective.
Oswald, listen to me.
You have to put the gun down!
He killed my mother, Jim.
I know.
Detective Gordon, I am ordering you
to put that man down! Now!
He had her murdered in front of me.
I held her.
Watched her die.
Do you know what that's like?
It changes a person.
I'm sorry about your mother, Penguin
but I'm gonna need you to put
the shotgun down on the ground.
Slowly. Now.
One of us is going to die tonight.
I have made my peace with that.
I suggest the new Mayor does as well.
Don't make us shoot you.
Shoot me and you have no idea
what his endgame is, Jim!
And you should.
Because it concerns someone you know.
Someone you care about.
Shoot him.
Duck!
Jim! Oswald!
Penguin smashed the Mayor's ride
through the main checkpoint.
The good news is, with the gunshot
wound to the shoulder and the APB,
I doubt he'll make it
out of the city.
He won't be trying to make it out.
We lost more people tonight,
good people, including Martinez.
Sometimes the good guys
have a bad night.
This ain't your fault.
I know.
It's his.
My ancestors were swordsmiths.
They knew that to make good steel
it had first to be forged.
I look at tonight...
I look at tonight
as a baptism of fire.
A fire from which we will emerge
stronger.
Our resolve forged to bring
about a new day in Gotham!
I've felt pretty alone
since moving here.
Until I met you.
But...
I don't want to come
between you and a friend.
You won't.
Selina's never going to like me.
I don't care.
I like you.
Detective Gordon.
Mr. Mayor.
You catch my speech?
I think I've heard enough speeches.
I had high hopes for you.
I thought you were prepared
to make the hard choices.
To do whatever it takes
to rid Gotham of its monsters.
I am.
I've just decided...
I'm going to start with you.
Dangerous words when addressing
the man who now controls this city.
Desperate times.
They are indeed.
I want to know why you did this.
When Doctor Thompkins walked
in the room.
How did it feel?
I was terrified.
She could have discovered the body.
But she didn't.
You got away with it.
That's not the point!
That is absolutely the point!
You can still feel the rush,
can't you?
Coming so close to getting caught.
Knowing what you would
have been forced to do
if she had discovered the body.
Discovered what you had done.
The pulse of that moment.
Standing, standing
at the edge of uncertainty
and peering into the void.
Now tell me.
How did it feel?
Beautiful.