JIM: Previously on Gotham...
FALCONE: I heard
they let you out of Arkham.
Yes. I'm sane.
- I'm Elijah Van Dahl.
- Oh, Oswald Cobblepot.
- You're related to Gertrud?
- My mother.
She never told me.
Told you what?
That I had a son.
ELIJAH: You have a home now, and a father.
A big happy family.
- (WHISPERS) Is this a dream?
- It's not a dream, my boy. You're home.
- Hello, Officer Pinkney. Can I come in?
- Sure.
- (CLANGS)
- (PINKNEY GROANS)
BARNES: Murder weapon was a crowbar.
Your fingerprints were on it.
I was set up!
FEMALE REPORTER:
Detective Gordon guilty on all counts.
How can you not be with us?
THOMKINS: (SOBS) Birthdays,
and first steps,
and skinned knees.
You need to go somewhere.
Start a new life.
Jim, don't do this. I love you.
- I'm so, so sorry.
- Jim, I love you. Don't do this. Jim!
- PRISON GUARD: On your feet. Let's go.
- (CLANKING)
(PRISON GATE CLANGING)
Step out.
Line it up.
- Face your right. Walk.
- (ALARM RINGING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(PRISON ALARM BUZZING)
- PRISON GUARD: Lights out!
- (PRISON GATE CLOSES)
(PRISON GATE CLANGING)
(PRISON ALARM BUZZING)
(PRISON GATE CLOSES)
- (CLANKING)
- PRISON GUARD: Get out there.
(ALARM RINGING)
(PANTS)
Lights out!
(PRISON ALARM BUZZING)
(PRISON GATE CLOSES)
- (GATE CLANKING)
- (GATE CLOSES)
PRISON GUARD: Keep it moving.
Stay in line.
Stop.
WARDEN: Prisoner Gordon,
step out of line and remain silent.
(DOOR BUZZING)
PRISON GUARD: Let's move.
(WARDEN BREATHES SHARPLY)
Several weeks with no incidents, Gordon.
I'm impressed.
Not what I expected.
Word was you were a troublemaker.
I just wanna do my time.
Well, it's time to move you.
Where to?
F Wing.
World's End,
general population.
This should not come as a surprise to you.
Protective custody
is just a temporary privilege.
One which can't be sustained
for a sentence as long as yours.
Now, perhaps you have an appeal pending.
In which case,
I can prolong this arrangement.
That's got to sting just a little, no?
Your people seem to have abandoned you.
Being convicted for murder
has its downsides.
Don't fret so.
I'm sure you'll see a lot
of familiar faces over in F Wing.
Many of which you arrested yourself.
(PRISON DOOR BUZZES OPEN)
- (INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
- (PRISONERS WHISTLING)
PRISONER: It's payback time.
(DOOR OPENS AND BUZZES)
PRISONER: What's up?
- And there goes the flying scissor kick...
- (CHEERING ON TV)
That one wasn't mine?
If you show yourself to be a team player,
anything's possible.
You a team player, Gordon?
I love it.
Oh, and I forgot to pass on
my good friend's regard.
Ex-Commissioner Loeb says hi.
Follow the rules
and perhaps you'll survive.
Break them and you most certainly won't.
It's why they call this wing
"World's End."
For most here, it's exactly that. The end.
Only way out, parole,
or a body bag.
(WARDEN INHALES SHARPLY)
And nobody gets parole.
- (BIRDS CHIRPING)
- (PEOPLE LAUGHING)
It's true, I swear it. Clear as day.
A ghost.
She was this pale old woman
in a long black dress.
- She was this close.
- What did you do?
- Oh, I ran away screaming of course.
- (MUSIC PLAYING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Do you believe in ghosts, Oswald?
Yes, I do. I've seen them.
This house has several of them.
But don't worry,
they're all quite friendly.
Don't listen to him.
There are no ghosts here.
ELIJAH: Oh, there's ghosts all right.
This house was built by my grandfather.
He died here. His wife and two sisters
also passed away upstairs.
And my poor, dear parents.
Yes, many ghosts.
Hmm.
How did you meet?
That's a boring story, really.
No. Let me tell it, dear.
ELIJAH: After my mother died,
I sat alone in this house for months,
barely got out of bed in fact.
Finally, I found a diner
not too far from here.
I'd go there every day at the same time,
order the same thing.
Chicken soup and a seltzer.
Grace was my waitress.
ELIJAH: And I grew very fond of her.
She told me of her two poor children,
Sasha and Charles.
And how they suffered at the hands
of their abusive father.
I had to help.
I offered her refuge and she accepted.
And this house heard laughter once again.
Then one thing led to another.
Love blossomed.
And here we are.
(CHUCKLES)
But you are my only true blood relative,
Oswald.
- (GLASS SHATTERING)
- (GRACE GASPS)
- Oh, my poor dear! Are you hurt at all?
- No, no, I'm, I'm fine.
Clumsy girl.
- To family.
- (CHUCKLES)
- Family.
- To family.
- (CHUCKLES) To family.
(GLASSES CLINKING)
Dent, they got him
in general population now, F Wing.
You know what that means?
Everyone we've ever put away is in there.
BULLOCK: Stop saying that!
There's always something you can do.
A retrial.
Or have him transferred to another prison
for God's sake.
You know what. Just keep doing
what you always do, which is nothing!
(TYPEWRITER CLACKING)
Ed.
(SIGHS)
He's wasting away in that place while
the real killer is out there somewhere
eating donuts and getting laid.
The real killer?
The fingerprints on the murder weapon...
Jim is innocent.
He didn't kill Pinkney.
Well, gee, I mean,
that's unfair. If that's true.
What are you gonna do about it?
I wish I knew. I wish I knew.
ELIJAH: My health forbids me
from drinking,
but at least I can watch you
enjoy this sherry.
- Hmm.
- It was my father's favorite.
Is that him?
ELIJAH: No, that's my
great grandfather Manfred.
He started a small tailor's shop
in Gotham many, many years ago.
Made suits for the city's elite.
My father became an apprentice
like every son before him.
- You were an apprentice, too?
- I was.
Had rather a flair for it.
But it was not to be.
When my father succumbed to illness,
my mother held me close to her.
Homeschooled me.
She felt a need to protect me
from the temptations of the city.
All this time I've been afraid to ask
about your mother.
I'm so sorry I abandoned her.
Had I known I was also abandoning you...
Dear God, I'm such a cowardly fool.
Did she have a happy life?
No. Not a happy life. But a good one.
She never hurt a soul.
I was not always a good son
and she never spoke a word of reproach.
"Not always a good son"?
I find that hard to credit.
A nice, young man like you?
Believe me.
I've done bad things.
We're all sinners, my boy.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
(GRACE CLEARS THROAT)
It's time for your medicine, my love.
Thank you.
Doctor gave them to me for my heart.
Better safe than sorry.
(OPENING BOTTLE)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
You have a visitor, Mr. Gordon.
This way, please.
YOUNG INMATE:
I'm not going back to the hole.
- He promised.
- The warden's the one who's moving you.
What? This wasn't our agreement.
YOUNG INMATE: No, you listen.
This isn't fair, I paid for this cell.
It's mine, you feel me? Mine!
This way, please.
A lot of business going on.
The warden get a cut?
- Almost there.
- (GATE BUZZING)
I want the boy scout dead by week's end.
Damn, you look good, brother.
- This place agrees with you.
- (BUZZING)
Maybe I'll check in and lose a few pounds.
Hmm? Get a cool tat.
You don't need to check up on me.
You kidding? Highlight of my week
to see your smiling face.
Look, I spoke to Dent,
he's looking into reopening the case.
But you got to keep your nose clean.
Last thing you can do is do more time
'cause you lost your temper, all right?
Shouldn't be that hard,
everyone seems really nice around here.
I've been looking for Penguin,
see what he's got to say.
He's laying low someplace.
But don't worry. I'll find him.
How's Lee?
She's been writing to me a lot.
The letters stopped a few weeks ago.
Know why?
I didn't want to be the one
to tell you this.
Tell me what?
They lost the baby, Jim.
I'm so sorry.
How is she?
I don't know.
I think she's fine. She moved down south.
No one's heard from her since.
Hey. Don't let this beat you.
It was good to see you, Harv.
Jim, I'm gonna get you out of here.
I promise.
Jim, don't let this break you.
Don't give up hope.
- Jim! Jim!
- (PRISON DOOR BUZZES OPEN)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(PRISON DOOR CLOSES)
Where you going, pig?
My little brother ran with the crew
that pulled off a few bank jobs last year.
The papers called them the Red Hood gang.
Remember them?
You put a bullet in my brother's head.
Whoa!
Who's this?
How about I have my friends
on the outside pay her a visit?
Show her what she's been missing.
(PRISONERS CLAMORING)
Hey, hey, hey guys, cool it, cool it. Huh.
Peace. Peace.
JIM: Don't.
It's all right, Mr. Gordon, I got this.
Now, come on now, guys,
let's just take a deep breath.
- (GRUNTS)
- (PRISONERS GASP)
Yeah! (LAUGHS)
(GRUNTING)
Get back to your cells!
(GUNSHOT AND SHELL CLANKS)
You!
Assume the position. Now. Now.
BULLISH GUARD 1: Disperse.
BULLISH GUARD 2: Back it up. Back it up.
Take inmate Weaver to the hole
and these two to the infirmary.
BULLISH GUARD 1: Get up. Get up.
BULLISH GUARD 2: Let's go. You heard him.
(GATE SLAMS)
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
- (RAIN PATTERING)
(SIGHS)
- (GRUNTS)
- (SCREAMS)
(SCREAMS)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPS)
- (SCREAMS)
- (GASPS)
(SCREAMING)
(GASPS AND PANTS)
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
- Father?
- What? Who?
It's okay. You, you were sleepwalking.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh.
Oh, I was.
My father's office.
- Here, let me, let me get you a chair.
- No, help me back to bed, won't you?
Of course.
ELIJAH: They're for my condition.
- Your heart?
- I have a hole in it.
Keeps getting bigger apparently.
I think my demons are feeding on it.
You have demons?
Sadly, I do.
You, too, I fear.
There is so much I haven't told you.
So much that I'm ashamed of.
I was a criminal.
I've done horrible things.
(SOBS) Hurt people, manipulated, lied.
For power, for revenge.
(VOICE BREAKING)
I've killed people, Father.
Our lives together started
the moment I met you at the cemetery.
Nothing before that concerns me.
I forgive you
for all of your past transgressions.
Be free of them and live here in peace.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
PUCK: We showed them, huh?
- Look, uh, whatever your name is--
- Puck.
Well, Peter, actually.
But people call me Puck.
Stay away from me, okay?
I don't need your help.
Can't do that, Detective Gordon.
- I'm not a detective anymore.
- Oh, I know.
You're way more than that.
You're a true hero.
Two winters ago my little sister
was abducted by child snatchers.
Three days she was gone.
Then you found her,
and you busted the scum that took her.
You saved her life and dozens of others.
Right there, that's a true hero.
I was just doing my job.
No, sir.
- What are you in for?
- A girl.
Beautiful girl.
I asked her out and she said yes.
She was classy.
I couldn't make her take the bus,
so I snatched a car.
Well. Borrowed it.
I was gonna take it back.
Cops didn't believe me.
So, here I am. (CHUCKLES)
What'd they give you?
- Six years.
- Steep.
Hey, I can't complain. (CHUCKLES)
I broke the law, right?
And the law is the law.
I'm not gonna be like my grandfather.
He died in here.
Wouldn't let me and my father visit him
after a while, but finally we did.
Last time I saw him
he was different.
Didn't recognize him.
That's not gonna happen to me, no, sir.
I won't die in here.
(THUNDER RUMBLING CONTINUES)
(SIGHS)
Then stay away from me.
(PRISON DOOR BUZZES OPEN)
What are these prisoners still doing here?
Get them to their cells immediately.
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
And watch this one.
He just lost a child.
Makes him mad. That's right.
I hear everything, I see everything.
Everything you know, I know.
I know something you don't know.
Yeah? What's that?
I know what kind of man you are.
Get him out of here. Now.
- Gin!
- Oh.
Elijah, brace yourself.
I'm afraid we have some bad news.
Oh, dear.
Charles was at the public library today.
Research for the novel I'm writing.
I was reading some old newspapers
and I made an alarming discovery.
My dear, Oswald is not the nice,
young man he says he is.
If we didn't lead
such sheltered lives here,
we would know what the whole world knows.
He's a notorious criminal.
We've been sheltering a killer.
We could've all been raped
and murdered in our beds.
Raped and murdered.
They call you the Penguin?
To be fair,
I never raped anybody.
Oh, well, that's a mercy, now isn't it?
My son told me about his past.
He just didn't tell me how famous he was.
You're too modest, son.
Elijah. A violent criminal in our house?
Grace, relax. He's changed. Redeemed.
- You're not this man anymore. Are you?
- No, sir.
But how? How do you know?
How do you know he's not?
I've looked into his soul.
I've seen his beautiful heart.
"The Dapper Gangland Kingpin"! Oh!
- What now?
- (SIGHS)
What now?
Plan B.
What's plan B?
You are, my dear.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(GASPS SOFTLY)
Good morning.
Uh, good morning.
I was hoping to spend
a little time with you, Mr. Penguin.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
But, um, uh, please, call me Oswald.
I'm not that man anymore.
There isn't a little bit of Penguin left?
A little bad boy?
No.
I got a little bad girl in me.
Whatever you've got planned
for the old man, I want in.
"In"?
We could do great things, you and me.
I suppose. I hadn't--
If you and me work together,
we could have it all.
We could squeeze my mom and brother out.
Why would we do that?
- I don't know.
- (GRUNTS)
I guess we're just
a couple of crazy, mixed up kids.
(GRUNTS)
- Good heavens!
- (OBJECTS CLATTER)
Restrain yourself, woman.
I'm practically your brother.
What are you thinking?
(SCOFFS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
He didn't bite.
Should I try?
No. I don't think he's faking.
I think he's kind of simple.
Huh.
BISHOP: Gordon. Gordon.
Watch yourself.
Weaver's coming out the hole. Now.
Already?
Nothing happens around here
like it's supposed to.
Your day's coming, Gordon.
You're a dead man!
- Take a look at your boyfriend over there.
- (GRUNTING)
JIM: Puck! (GRUNTS)
Who's gonna help you now, pig?
PRISONER: Hey, you like that, Gordon?
Let it go. Don't extend your sentence.
(PRISON DOOR BUZZES CLOSED)
- (SLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
- Ah.
Jim didn't kill that kid, we all know it.
Thing is, who did?
I mean, who'd set him up that way?
I just don't know how much longer
he can stay alive in that place.
I guess I'm asking for your help.
Funny, huh?
You have every right to tell me
to go to hell.
But I...
I got no one else to turn to.
Hmm.
You know, Harvey,
it's very rude to wear a hat indoors.
(OPERA MUSIC PLAYING)
You like the fabric? It's Italian.
(LAUGHS) I love it.
A man can say so much about himself
by what he wears.
I couldn't agree more.
I weep for today's casual youth.
(LAUGHS)
I'm so glad you suggested we do this.
It's been so long.
- (SIGHS)
- (COUGHING)
Are you all right?
- (THUDS)
- (GASPS)
Father? (GASPS)
Help! Help! Someone call for an ambulance!
COBBLEPOT: Charles!
Help! Help, Grace!
What did you do to Elijah?
- Nothing.
- CHARLES: Help!
Coming, my dear!
Clean up this mess and call the doctor.
Go on.
Hard at it, I see.
Thanks for getting me my old job back.
Your friend Puck is pretty banged up.
Might do him some good if you were
to come see him in the infirmary.
Yeah, no.
I'm not his friend.
He thinks you are.
The kid's gonna die in here
one way or another.
(DOOR CLOSES AND BUZZES)
- We'll be quick.
- (INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
(EKG BEEPING)
Hey.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
How you holding up?
Cool.
They said I have a clot or something.
But I just feel seasick. (CHUCKLES)
Thanks for coming to see me.
Means a lot.
I'm sure they'll take
good care of you in here.
- You hang in there, huh.
- Listen.
Don't give up hope.
I feel your sadness.
I do.
But you gotta choose life, you know?
Okay.
Choose life.
Good.
But listen, kid, uh,
when you get better,
you learn the lesson here
and you stay the hell away from me.
I'm not a hero and I'm not your friend.
I'm just a convict.
Tonight's movie night.
Everyone in the main hall together
with the lights off.
Be ready.
- For what?
- Just be ready.
His condition has gotten worse.
The hole has gotten bigger,
- and now there's an infection.
- (ELIJAH COUGHING)
I've given him antibiotics
and rehydrated him,
but I fear it will have
little consequence.
It's time for him
to get his affairs in order.
He may not have long.
(DOOR OPENS)
I'm going to have them
make you some nice chicken soup.
You need your strength.
How kind.
ELIJAH: Come here, my boy.
Don't listen to doctors, son.
I've proved them wrong
so many times I've lost count.
(LAUGHS)
You and I will have many more years
to spend together.
Trust me.
But perhaps we should speak
with my lawyer, dear.
I have some things
I'd like to go over with him.
So much has changed these past weeks.
Of course. I'll have him stop by. Mmm-hmm.
(PRISON DOOR BUZZES)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS)
(PRISONERS WHISTLING AND CHEERING)
(PROJECTOR WHIRRS)
(MOVIE STARTS PLAYING)
(PRISONERS LAUGHING)
(WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY)
- Right.
- (GRACE SIGHS)
He's called for his lawyer.
- He's going to change his will?
- GRACE: Yes.
And when he dies,
Cobblepot will get what's rightfully ours.
That old man was a shriveled up wreck
when I met him.
I made him feel young again.
I brought him back to life,
and what has this gutter rodent done?
Played stupid board games
and whined about his wretched mother.
(GRACE SIGHS)
That vermin has to go.
But he likes it here.
CHARLES: How can we persuade him to go?
How do you get rid of rats?
- Glue traps?
- No, silly.
Hello, hello.
Father is feeling much better,
but he is resting
so he will not be joining us tonight.
Well, that's fine. Let's eat, hmm?
- (CHUCKLES) Thank you.
- Oh...
(MUSIC PLAYING)
PRISONER: I'm a pretty bride.
Look, everybody. (LAUGHS)
(PRISONERS LAUGHING)
Yo, show's over.
Come on, Officer.
(PRISONERS BOOING)
Yo, get down.
- (GRUNTING)
- (PANICKED SHOUTING)
What are you doing? He's mine!
He's mine.
(STABBING)
Stay down. You're dead. You understand?
You understand?
You're done, pig.
PRISON GUARD: Get him out of here.
Clear them out of here.
- Come to order.
- (ALARM RINGING)
Get them out of here.
BISHOP: We're gonna need a body bag.
(PRISON DOOR OPENS AND BUZZES)
(GORDON GASPS)
(GRUNTS)
Bullock? What the hell are you doing here?
What's it look like?
We're getting you out of here.
BULLOCK: Come on, let's go.
Fake blood, retractable knife.
I can't believe it worked.
JIM: Wait. Wait.
Harvey, what if this is
where I'm supposed to be?
What? Let's go.
Bullock.
You sure?
Are you tripping?
A lot of good men put their butts
on a live rail for you.
Me, him, Don freaking Falcone.
Where walking around somewhere is
the guy that killed Pinkney,
framed you and destroyed your family. Hmm?
He's walking around while
you're standing there all blue and misty.
Well, screw your self-pity and let's go!
Amen.
All right.
But I need one more favor.
(EKG BEEPING)
(MAN WHISTLING)
Hello?
(GROANS)
- (OBJECT CLATTERS)
- Detective Gordon?
We're out of here.
We need to move as quickly
and quietly as you can.
- You mean like escaping?
- Like that.
But that's against the law.
Yeah. Like you said, choose life.
- Told you, didn't I?
- (BEEPING)
Whether you like it or not, you're a hero.
Prisoner Gordon.
You're supposed to be dead.
I'm as surprised as you are.
What brought you back to life?
- Friends.
- WARDEN: Friends.
It's good to have friends.
But where are they
when you need them, huh?
Man, that felt good.
- JIM: Sorry I got you into all this.
- Are you kidding?
Never felt more alive. Now.
Hit me hard, make it look good.
Just don't touch the teeth.
I just had them fixed.
My dear mother. She was so young.
GRACE: Oswald.
(COBBLEPOT SIGHS)
- Thank you so much, Grace.
- (CHUCKLES)
(CHUCKLES)
I lied to you, son.
Oh.
My father was never physically ill.
He only suffered a deep melancholy.
He was plagued by dark impulses,
evil thoughts of violence.
Mother said many in his family
had the same affliction.
I remember the sound of the gunshot.
I was outside his room.
I screamed for my mother to get the key.
I saw the warm gun in his hand.
The blood.
His face.
(INHALES)
Mother said never to talk about it.
For years after the funeral
we never left the house.
I don't pretend to understand
my father's torment.
(SOBS) But I think that perhaps you do.
I feel for you and I beg of you, my son.
Never give in to the pain as he did.
You are loved
and you are not alone.
And the sun will come up tomorrow.
(SOBS)
Thank you, Father.
(BREATHES SHARPLY)
- Now, I feel like a drink.
- (CHUCKLES)
(SNIFFLES AND CLEARS THROAT)
But, but, your health?
To hell with that.
(LAUGHS)
I want you to have it all, my son.
This house and all that's in it.
Keep it just the way it is,
a piece of history,
our history...
Gotham's history.
First thing tomorrow
I'll have my lawyers draw it up.
(GROANING)
Father?
- Father, no.
- GRACE: Elijah!
- Did he, did he drink that?
- Yes.
Why? Why? He's not supposed to.
Sasha, call an ambulance. Call an...
(SCREAMING)
(SOBS) Stay with us, Father,
help is on the way.
No!
We made it, buddy.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
Wait here.
(TRUCK DOOR CLOSES)
Don Falcone had all the contacts
inside of Blackgate.
He made this whole thing happen.
Thank you.
I'm not sure I can ever repay you.
That won't be necessary.
I'm happy to help an old friend.
What now?
You're asking me?
Two hours ago I was a dead man.
I have people that will get you
out of the country.
Or I can arrange
a safe place for you in Gotham.
Your choice.
(LOON CALLING)
What do you wanna do?
I wanna go find Lee.
And to do that I have to clear my name.
And to do that
I have to go to back to Gotham.
So there's your answer.
Part of me says run.
JIM: I'm breathing fresh air.
I can't go back inside.
If you run, you've got to keep running.
Some people can live with that.
You're a fighter, Jim.
You got knocked down.
Do you stay down?
Or do you get back up?
What do you think, kid?
Puck?
No, no, we made it. Come on, come on, no.
Come on, don't give up. Puck.
He's gone.
Jim, he's gone.
English - SDH