Previously onGotham...
But you are my only
true blood relative, Oswald.
- That vermin has to go.
- How can we persuade him to go?
How do you get rid of rats?
- Did he drink that?
- Yes.
Why? Why? He's not supposed to.
No!
Awake at last.
Well, hello, dear.
Someone call Professor Strange!
We'll see about your clever
little plan, Jim Gordon.
- I can make plans of my own.
- Hello, Officer Pinkney.
- Can I come in?
- Sure.
- Murder weapon was a crowbar.
- Your fingerprints were on it.
I was set up!
Being convicted for murder
has its downsides.
- It's good to see you, Harv.
- Don't give up hope.
What the hell are you doing here?
What's it look like we're doing?
We're getting you out of here.
Come on, let's go.
I have to clear my name.
To do that,
I have to go back to Gotham.
You little cunts!
Don't you take that bag!
Do you have any idea
who you're stealing from?
Leave it.
- That's my money!
- You stole it.
Now, you got stole, chump.
I catch you, you're dead.
Both of you.
By the way, you're a terrible crook,
letting two kids rob you,
You really don't deserve
this money.
What the hell are you doing,
you little freak?
- What the hell are you doing?
- You're both dead.
Nobody ever try to touch my money!
I'm not a thief.
I don't steal for the money.
This is research.
I can't understand Gotham
until I understand its criminals.
Okay, this whole
understanding-criminals thing
is getting on my nerves.
That was your half you threw out.
I saved enough for burgers.
Gotham is on high alert today
after former G.C.P.D. detective
and convicted murderer
James Gordon escaped.
Detective Bullock,
have you heard the news?
- Yeah, Ed, I heard.
- So, what do you think he'll do?
Knowing Jim Gordon,
I'd say he's not gonna rest
until he finds the son of a bitch
who framed him for murder.
Good luck with that.
Bullock.
This is your one and only chance.
And tell me where he is.
- Hand to God, Cap, I have no idea.
- Stop it.
You're not smart enough to play dumb.
We both know
Jim did not kill Pinkney.
I know that a court found him guilty.
He wants to prove
his own innocence? Great.
I hope he does.
The public, the people of Gotham,
the ones you and I serve,
they have to know,
they have to see that we're
impartial. Do you understand?
The people of Gotham
can eat my socks.
Hey. Hey! Nice try.
Walk away in a huff?
Now, I know you know something.
If you're providing aid
and shelter to Jim Gordon,
anything, a glass of water,
I will bust you
like a bum I never met.
Cap, I wish I knew where he was.
But I don't.
Go.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah.
Let's get to work.
And I'm going over and over this
a thousand times in my mind,
it all has to be connected.
The theft at the art museum,
the bombing at the train station,
the I.A. tip-off, Pinkney's murder,
it's all a part
of an elaborate frame.
So he's smart, meticulous.
Got technical skill and access.
- An active cop?
- Has to be.
Only way he could have access
to a crowbar
after it was put into evidence.
It doesn't really narrow
the suspect list too much.
I mean, come on, Jim, be honest.
You probably got 500 cops
who have beef with you.
Yeah. But enough to frame me
for murder?
Maybe ten. You got to admit,
you do have
a little bit of a knack for
making enemies.
My number was 12.
Many Loeb loyalists.
Who knows, maybe Loeb himself
is behind this.
Before you go down that rabbit hole,
I gotta say something to you
as a friend.
You can still run.
Go to an island, buy a banana boat,
grow a beard, find Lee, have a life.
Look,
I've been working this thing
since you went away,
and I'm not saying it's hopeless,
but Barnes is on the hunt.
- You don't have much time.
- Did he threaten you?
Hey, I'm the one who busted you
out of jail, remember?
- I made my choice.
- All right, let's say I run.
I find Lee, I somehow
convinced her to take me back.
What then?
I get her to live as a fugitive?
I have to clear my name.
Otherwise I might as well be in jail.
But how? Starting where?
Dent once told me
I.A. secretly records and archives
all their incoming calls on tape.
Which means the eyewitness
who called into I.A.?
The one they assumed
that was Pinkney?
There could be a tape
with his voice on it.
That's a hell of a long shot,
brother.
And if, okay, just saying if,
a tape like that exists,
it's gonna be locked up tighter
than a duck's ass
in I.A. evidence.
It's why it's lucky for you,
Uncle Harvey has connections.
Hey. Ginny.
How's my favorite I.A. sugar plum?
Well, why do you think
I'm calling, baby?
Heard you're getting married.
- She changed her mind.
- Smart girl.
You're an animal, Bullock.
- You know that?
- Ma'am, I do, I do.
- Come on, Bullock.
- Yeah, baby.
I'll be right there.
Slow down for me for a sec.
Hey. An hour.
Slip them under the door.
Come on, Bullock.
Ain't got all night.
Don't say a word.
Daddy's coming.
Give me that.
Oh, what's up, sweetheart?
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- Now, do it. Do it!
Somebody help!
- Do it!
- Hey!
Get out of here. Go!
Ma'am, are you okay?
- You're welcome.
- Hands up.
Or I'll blow your head off.
G.C.P.D. You're under.
- You're Jim Gordon.
- Listen to me.
This is Barkley,
over at Fifth and Spring.
I got Jim.
- Don't kill me.
- I'm innocent, you hear me?
All units,
it's Jim freaking Gordon.
I need backup now.
Father, I only knew you a short time.
But you came to me when I was alone
in this cold, dark world.
You gave me a family.
I will never forget you.
As long as I...
Oh, Father.
What a bore that was.
Yeah, but the house is ours now,
and we're rich.
Quiet.
- He loved us all so much.
- Indeed.
But, Oswald, Oswald,
as painful as this is,
we need to talk practicalities.
Can I call you a cab,
or will you take the bus?
I don't understand.
Well, you're not returning
to the house with us.
- But where shall I go?
- Anywhere but there.
Oswald, I'm so happy that you
and your father reconnected.
But he left the house
and the estate to me.
And I'm simply not comfortable
sleeping under the same roof
as a notorious murderer.
But I'm not like that anymore.
I couldn't hurt a fly,
even if I wanted to.
Please, my father was all that I had.
We shared the same blood.
And he wanted us to be together.
He told me.
Let me stay. I'll do anything.
You are his blood.
We do need help around the house.
- Mother.
Why waste good money on servants
when we have Oswald?
I'll do anything.
Well, you could start by getting rid
of those disgusting flowers.
I've always detested lilies.
Yes. Of course.
You're not really letting him stay?
He's Elijah's only natural son.
If he found the right lawyer,
he could make things difficult.
Especially, if people look
into how his father died.
- So, we just live with him then?
- Yeah, we keep him close.
And after a suitable
amount of time goes by,
poor Oswald, overcome with grief,
will take his own life.
Till then, we have a free servant.
I could fire the maid.
I murdered my...
Parents.
I cut their throats.
I joined
a gang of psychopathic killers.
I tried to kill Jim Gordon
and Lee Thompkins.
I was a puppet...
Of these demons in my head
and they were forcing me
to do these terrible things.
I wish I could go back
and undo what I've done.
Only I can't.
I don't feel insane...
Now...
I just...
I feel sad.
Thank you, Barbara.
That was very brave.
What do you suppose
made this helpful change in you?
Maybe I just...
Really needed some sleep.
It's a good act.
So, sure it's an act are you?
- Aren't you?
- I have no idea.
One way or the other,
she intrigues me.
Well, if you would allow us
to apply rigorous dream therapy,
- we would know for sure...
- No, no, no.
We do have very useful hammer,
Ms. Peabody,
but not all of our patients
are nails.
Thank you.
What the hell happened last night?
Stumbled onto a mugging.
And Jim Gordon couldn't just walk by.
- Where'd you sleep?
- Didn't. Just walked around.
- How's Barnes?
- He's on the warpath.
Governor announced
a 10,000-dollar reward
for anyone who helps catch you.
Ten thousand? You should turn me in.
If he doubled that to 20?
I'll give it some thought.
- Okay, here.
- Internal Affairs.
I, I want to report a crime.
- You recognize that voice?
- Sounds like it's been disguised.
I saw Detective James Gordon
shooting Mayor Theo Galavan.
On the Southside Docks.
The Penguin was beating him
with a bat,
but it was Gordon
that pulled the trigger.
Is that a bird?
Run it back.
We gotta find somebody
to clean up the tape.
Isolate the sound.
Maybe do something to the voice.
I gotta get going.
Barnes is watching me like a hawk.
All right.
Hey.
You've done more
than any partner could ask.
From now on, stay away from me.
For your own sake.
If Loeb was behind this,
you don't wanna be mixed up in it.
What are you gonna do?
I still have some friends
I can ask for help.
Where you going?
Jim.
Hi, Ed.
- Please. Please don't hurt me.
- Relax.
I'm not going to hurt you.
- I need your help.
- My help?
I didn't kill Pinkney.
You need to believe me.
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
I need to find the man who framed me.
Whoever it was,
he covered his tracks well.
But I may have something.
A recording of his first call to I.A.
I.A. secretly records everyone
who calls in.
They do?
The sneaky little buggers.
And what did you hear?
If you don't mind me asking.
Not much. He disguised his voice.
But there are other sounds
on the tape.
I figure you've worked with audio.
I was hoping you could help me.
Jim.
My friend.
You've come to the right place.
Please have a sit.
I will get my stuff.
And make some tea.
Well, let's pray Helga hasn't
signed on anywhere new yet.
It's a family recipe.
I'm sorry you don't like it.
I'm sure my cooking will improve
over time.
It's not that bad.
Tomorrow, you'll need
to go to the butcher.
I'd like a nice roast
for Sunday dinner.
Not your slut mother's goulash.
A nice roast. Yes, ma'am.
Oh, and clean up this mess
tonight.
I can't stand
the sight of dirty dishes.
Good shot, Charles.
I must get to these dishes.
But this has been delightful,
really.
Yes, it does sound like a bird.
And he's doing his best
to mask his voice.
It's too bad the quality's so poor.
Well, I'm afraid it's a dead end.
We should at least clean the tape.
Right.
We need some more tea.
So the person who killed Pinkney
and framed you
is the same person
that attacked the art museum
and planted the bomb
in the train station.
Amazing.
And you don't have any leads?
I think that Loeb was behind it.
Payback.
He still has lackeys in the G.C.P.D.
Is that so?
Everything points to a cop.
Or someone who worked
with the police.
Had access.
You all right, Ed?
Right as rain. Just thinking.
Surely, you don't think
that Loeb killed Pinkney himself?
No.
He had some psychopath do it for him.
Psychopath seems a strong word.
He bludgeoned a man to death
with a crowbar in cold blood.
- He's sick.
- You say that, yet...
You've killed lots of people,
haven't you?
That was in the line of duty.
And a person who would kill
in cold blood is a psychopath.
See, I knew the rumors weren't true.
- What rumors?
- About you killing Galavan.
You would never do that.
That would make you like
the people that you're hunting.
Sick.
Diseased.
Thar she blows.
Shut up, you're talking too much.
Ed.
Did Penguin ever say anything
about that night?
Did Penguin ever tell you anything
about the night that Galavan died?
No. Remember, I nipped
that friendship in the bud.
And you didn't talk to him
in the G.C.P.D.
when Barnes brought him in?
Yes. No. I mean, just to say hi.
Oh, tape's finished.
I'm gonna give that a listen.
Let's both listen.
Swell idea.
Internal Affairs.
I, I want to report a crime.
I saw Detective James Gordon
shooting Mayor Theo Galavan.
On the Southside Docks.
The Penguin was beating him
with a bat,
but it was Gordon
that pulled the trigger.
It's not a bird.
It was mechanical.
Without fingers, I point,
without arms, I strike,
without feet, I run.
What am I?
- You're a clock.
- Correct.
I know it was you, Ed.
- Me?
- You.
Guess what?
I knew that you knew that I knew.
That's why your chair is wired
to the mains.
Over the pavement and down the alley,
while this wind is cold.
It plays with my toes
and nips my nose,
as over the ground, we go.
I hope you like the outdoors,
Jimbo.
I know just the spot.
Come out, come out wherever you are.
I bet you're wondering,
"Why would Ed do this to me?
Set me up.
Ruin my life."
I'll give you a hint, Jimbo.
K.K.
Kristin Kringle.
Rats.
Hey.
Have you seen my jacket?
It's freezing outside.
Sorry. I was fixing the sleeve.
- You'd ripped it.
- You know how to sew?
Alfred says it's an important skill
for young bachelors.
Okay.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- What the...
- Detective Gordon.
Bruce? What are you doing here?
I could ask the same about you.
I found the man who framed me.
I need a pho.
Great. A dead cop in my crib now.
Don't forget the cherries, Oswald.
Right. Cherries, cherries,
cherries, cherries.
Oswald.
My drink?
- I'm sorry there's no cherries.
- No cherries?
The next time I ask for cherries,
there better be cherries.
Yes, Grace. Ma'am. Of course.
Mother said to remind you
of tomorrow's dinner.
- What's wrong with him?
- Who knows?
- Mother wants a roast.
- And make it good this time.
Yes, I will.
- He's still sleeping.
- Nice thing for him.
Thank you for coming
when I called, Alfred.
Of course I came. Not a question.
You're looking thin.
- I'm getting plenty to eat.
- I very much doubt, Master Bruce.
There're things
that we must discuss.
- I'm not coming back.
- I understand.
- Not yet.
- And we need to talk.
Good morning.
Detective Gordon, should you be up?
I'm fine. You stitched me up?
Actually, Master Bruce,
he called from Selina Kyle's
when you passed out,
so I thought I'd bring you here.
I saved a space for you.
Master Bruce,
I wanna leave you my coat
and get the detective his clothes
in the laundry room, please.
I'm glad you're okay.
So I've made breakfast. Take a seat.
- Want some coffee?
- Yes, please.
There we go.
How long has Bruce been living
with Selina Kyle?
Ever since
the Matches Malone debacle.
Turns out
staring into the cold-dead eyes
of the man
that killed your parents,
doesn't bring
the right amount of closure.
Bruce never should've been
in that room.
- I should've gotten to Malone first.
- Yes. You should've done.
But you didn't, did you?
"You can't unfry an egg,"
as my dear old mum used to say.
So, why don't we leave
Master Bruce's situation alone
and why don't we discuss yours?
It's a long story.
Right, so you were framed
for the murder
of that other police officer.
You escaped from prison,
you then tracked down
the man who framed you
and you were promptly shot
in the leg.
Right, so answer me this, Detective.
Do you have any idea
how you're going to get out
of this awful pickle?
Yes, I do.
Come, my dear. Your future awaits.
You're sure?
I run a hospital, not a prison.
You're sane.
It would be unethical and illegal
to keep you confined.
- What if I?
- Hush now.
Life is full of uncertainty.
And if something does happen,
we're always here.
Off you go.
If you keep releasing lunatics
so liberally,
you're going to get a bad reputation.
I'm not looking
for a good reputation.
We're releasing Barbara Kean
into the wild
to observe her behavior.
She's a beautiful experiment.
You know what she's going to do,
don't you?
I don't, actually.
But I do know it will be interesting.
Nygma was right about one thing.
I can't just go to the cops.
They'll never believe me.
- I need hard proof.
- Cops, right?
Jerks.
Nygma said he met Penguin
for the first time in the woods.
It was right around the same time
his girlfriend went missing.
I think he was burying her.
Just like he was going to bury me.
Or he wanna find her body.
Tops the old
needle in a haystack, isn't it?
Nygma knows where she is.
What, you think he's gonna,
what, straight tell you?
That's exactly what he's going to do.
But I need help.
Whatever we can do.
Thanks, but I need someone
Barnes knows will betray me.
What?
Who do I talk to
about the reward for Jim Gordon?
Hey. Come here, come here.
- Come here.
- Let go of me.
- I'm here for my reward.
- I'll give you a reward.
Bullock!
- Have you seen Jim Gordon?
- Depends.
- There really a ten grand?
- Depends on your information.
He's at my place
a couple of hours ago.
- He'd been shot.
- Shot?
- Who shot him?
- Didn't say.
- He wasn't making a lot of sense.
- Is he still there now?
No. He took off. I don't know where.
But he was just looking for a place
to lie low for a while, I guess.
That's not worth 10,000 dollars.
Fine. Before he left,
he said he'd found out
where the Penguin was hiding
- and he's gonna go see him.
- Why would he go see The Penguin?
I don't know. Something about
"Penguin knows
where the body is buried."
- What bodies?
- I don't know.
- Where's The Penguin now?
- No one knows.
- You gonna pay me or what?
- Or what?
Relax, relax.
Maybe Gordon won't even find Penguin.
You idiot.
He's a detective.
He finds people for a living!
Penguin won't tell him.
He's my friend.
Who am I kidding? You're stupid.
Stupid. Stupid!
Okay, okay.
Okay, calculate it, calculate.
Chances of Gordon finding Penguin?
Let's say 80 percent.
Chances of Penguin telling Gordon?
Also 80 percent.
So that's a 60 percent chance
of Gordon finding Kristin.
That settles it.
Hello, Kristin.
I know,
didn't expect to see me again.
But circumstances.
Now, I'm afraid
I'm going to have to move you.
Jim Gordon. So you did find Penguin.
- And that little bird sang.
- No, I just followed you.
You fed the information
to that little miscreant.
Assuming that I'd hear. Or no.
No, no, no.
Of course, you were in cahoots.
Of course, you're in cahoots.
Well, either way, bravo, Jim.
I'd clap,
but I have your gun in my hand.
How did this happen to you?
How did you become this?
You dummy.
This is who I am.
It was just finally admitting
the truth to myself.
Well, that
and murdering some people.
- I don't believe that.
- You don't believe it why Jim?
Because it would make you
incompetent
to know that I was right
under your nose the whole time?
Or you don't want to admit that
there's a monster in all of us?
Because you, of all people,
should know that!
Because that's what made it
so easy to frame you.
- I was your friend.
- Were you, Jim?
Were you my friend?
Or did you just pity me?
Oh, poor, weird little Ed
with his little silly wordplay
and his little riddles.
You're completely insane.
Yeah. It's probably easier
for you to think that.
How about one last riddle
for old time's sake?
A nightmare for some.
For others, a savior, I come.
My hands, cold and bleak...
it's the warm hearts they seek.
Death.
Right again.
- Goodbye, Jim.
- Drop the gun!
Drop it!
Captain Barnes, I'm arresting Jim.
Stop it, Ed. We heard everything.
Now, drop the gun
and get on your knees!
No, this is... I... He's...
Last chance!
Oh, great.
How is it? Not too gamey?
Overcooked.
Try the other joint.
It is much more tender.
It's the same.
Still, beats my slut mother's
goulash, no?
Where are the children?
Ring the bell again.
I doubt they'll hear it.
You look different.
And you noticed.
Yes.
I'm doing my hair a different way.
Charles. Sasha. Where are they?
I found the sherry decanter, Grace.
The one with poison in it
that you used to killed my father.
What on Earth
are you talking about?
You should have thrown it away.
Guess you're a little too mean
to waste good poison?
- Don't go.
- Charles.
- Sasha, help.
- They won't come.
Where are they?
You thought they tasted the same.
But Sasha...
- No. No. No.
- "Definitely more tender.
- No.
- In my opinion."
No. No!
You said you were innocent.
And you were.
I'm glad.
- I guess I owe you an apology.
- No.
You were doing your duty.
I can't fault you for that.
Yeah, well, I owe you one.
Yeah,
not necessarily but I'll take it.
Can you do me a favor?
And take it easy on Bullock.
Thanks.
So, when are you coming back to work?
I'm not coming back. Not yet anyhow.
No?
There's something I have to do first.
Lee Thompkins' number.
She's working for an
M.E. department down South.
I promised Bruce Wayne
I'd solve his parents' murder.
I have to do that first.
Then I'm free.
The Wayne case is closed, Jim.
The perp is dead.
But who hired him? Why?
I need to find out.
Sometimes we never find out.
It happens.
I need you
to give me the Wayne files.
You take this, and I'll give you
the Wayne files.
Call her.
I'll go get it.
It was nothing that you did
or didn't do, Alfred.
Why I went away.
I want you to know that.
I do.
Thank you very much.
I'll be going back to the city
as soon as Selina's ready.
She is taking a hot shower.
You didn't know
that Mr. Lucius Fox fixed
your old man's computer
a couple days ago, don't you?
And when were you going
to tell me, Alfred?
Well, I tried telling
you this morning.
I'm telling you again now, am I?
What are you doing?
She could walk in here, have a word.
- I trust her.
- It's not about trust, is it?
Whatever your father was doing,
he did it in secret for a reason.
To protect those he loved.
It quite doesn't matter
about my personal opinion
about that young girl,
but she has been
a bloody good friend to you,
and she's been loyal.
So, you know, you go ahead,
continue your father's work,
I can't stop you.
Man, I've tried, haven't I?
But I will not have you
put that little girl's life
in danger.
It's either the work or it's her.
You can't have both.
Do you understand?
Man, rich people
have great water pressure.
So, Jeeves,
any chance we can get a ride
back to the city?
Right. Well, I'll be in the...
I'll be in the kitchen, Master Bruce.
Miss.
What's with him?
Bruce, what's going on?
- I'm not going back.
- What?
I'm grateful for everything
that you taught me.
My place is here.
So, that's it?
I don't expect you to understand.
Right, because you're Bruce Wayne
and I'm street trash.
- Selina, it's not like that.
- Yeah, it is.
It is.
It's fine.
Have a great life, Bruce Wayne.
System enabled.
Thompkins.
Hello?
Hi, Jim.