Previously on Gotham...
How I ever let him lay a hand on me...
(GRUNTS)
ED: I'm glad he's out of your life.
Keep that guard up! Jab, jab.
Lead jab, jab, right.
- What are you doing?
- Alfred's teaching me to fight.
I need you to take me
to the Pike brothers.
The firebugs from the Narrows?
SELINA:
I used to hang with their sister, Bridgit.
Hey, boys. We need the best,
and you guys are the best.
JOE: Bridgy. You just got a promotion.
- G.C.P.D.!
- Run!
- I've got her! Drop it!
- No!
- (SCREAMS)
One moment, Mr. Penguin.
- Mother!
- Please! I don't know nothing.
You are going to go to Galavan.
Once you're inside his organization,
you will find my mother and rescue her.
He'll buy it, if we sell it right.
(SCREAMS)
And then Penguin just went crazy.
I mean, like,
crazier than I've ever seen him.
He said it was me
that set up the count house raid.
Said I was a traitor and a rat.
And he came at me with a cleaver.
I tried to protect myself
and he did this, that sick bastard.
How'd you get away?
BUTCH: There was a lot of blood. A lot.
And he tried to take another swing and
he slipped and fell, and so I just ran.
And I ran and I ran and then, next thing
I knew, I woke up in the hospital.
Hmm.
Give me a shot, Mr. Galavan,
let me show you what I can do.
Well, I'd like to help you out, Butch,
but I already have several capable
two-handed thugs in my employ.
They don't know Gotham like I do.
I got brains, you ask anyone!
What do you think, ladies?
I think he's cute. Like a sad bear.
I suppose he's telling the truth.
The little man was cracking up
last time I saw him.
He was very mean to me once.
Held me hostage in my own apartment.
Said some nasty things.
Isn't that right, Stumpy?
That's right, ma'am. And I'm sorry for it.
Business is business, you know?
- Please. Let me work for you, Mr. Galavan.
- (CHOKING AND GRUNTING)
I got nobody else to turn to.
(GASPS) Oh, yes!
We can put cool things on his stump,
like knives and mallets and stuff.
Ooh!
How about a little tiny chainsaw?
Yes!
Huh.
Well, that settles it.
Welcome aboard, Butch.
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY) Thank you, sir.
(GROANS)
Oh! Oh! Bravo, Congressman. Well saved.
You really are quite spry for a big man.
Have you reconsidered your position?
Can I count on your support this election?
Yes, yes! You have my full support!
Thank you so much.
(GRUNTS)
(GASPING)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
Freeze!
Man, I didn't do nothing!
Why are you chasing me?
A police officer died last night.
Killed by a firebug crew on a spree.
You're a firebug, aren't you?
No, man, I been out the game a long time!
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
- Don't lie to me, Nino.
- I swear.
Sir, that's a violation
of the officer conduct regs.
Luke Garrett burned to death
in front of me twelve hours ago.
I'll conduct myself as I see fit.
This crew's working with a kid. A girl.
Wears a homemade fire suit.
Hey, for real, never heard
of a female firebug before.
It's mad rare, like a...
Like a unicorn or something.
(GROANS)
Sir, Captain Barnes says
we must report any infractions.
Even by superior officers.
You do that.
What are you doing?
I can't sleep.
I don't know what to do with myself.
(SIGHS)
That's the point of being free.
You get to do whatever the hell you want.
What am I gonna do?
I killed someone last night.
I can't go home. I can't go to the police.
You gotta get out of town.
How? I got no money.
No problem. We'll get some.
You mean, like, crime?
(CHUCKLES SOFTLY) Man, you are square.
(SIGHS)
I guess I got no choice.
Why are you helping me?
Maybe you remind me of me
if I was a doofus.
(CHUCKLES)
This crime...
What exactly you got in mind?
AUCTIONEER:
Ladies and gentlemen!
- Or should I say pimps, hos and thieves?
- (ELECTRONIC MUSIC PLAYING)
Do I have some product for you today!
Do you like what you see?
- (CROWD CHEERING)
- Come on, now, let me hear you!
Do you like what you see?
All right. Oh, check it out, check it out!
Yes! Nice and sturdy
- I want her!
- Bidding will start at $800 apiece!
- And we got $800! Can I get--
- Yo, $850!
We got $850. Can I get $900?
Can I get nine?
(VOICE FADING)
Those girls are for sale?
Told you this place was freaky.
We need to help them.
We're here to help you.
'Cause you killed a cop, remember?
We get the money, we go.
- But--
- Listen. Listen.
You go down the stairs.
The lock on the back door is busted.
I know, 'cause I busted it.
You go in, wait for me to make my move.
How will I know when?
Pay attention.
Sold for $2,500
to the gentleman in the burgundy hat!
Yes, indeedy! Come on, ladies.
Found you a nice new home!
Oh, you'll be very satisfied!
You'll be very, very satisfied!
Next up, check her out as she walks
down the stage, see how graceful she is!
Look at this one!
I'll start the bidding here at $900!
- Can I get $900? $900 over here.
- (GRUNTS)
- Hey, pervs! This is a robbery!
- (GIRLS CLAMORING)
Milo! Kill that punk!
She's with me.
Now, each of you
put all your cash in the bag.
Or what? I ain't scared of you.
Yeah, all right.
Anybody else got a problem?
Yeah, I didn't think so.
(CLAMORING)
And for the record, all y'all suck!
(INDISTINCT SCREAMING)
WOMAN:
Come on! Please! Get me out of here!
WOMAN 2: I can't stay here.
Hey, you! Hey! Stop!
(SCREAMS)
(LAUGHING) Oh, my God.
I know, right? Let's go!
A note in my file? Are you serious?
Do I look like I'm joking?
We do not beat suspects. Ever!
I get it. Luke was a good kid.
We took him out of the academy.
Told him he was ready. Now he's dead.
You lose people in war. You know that.
Make no mistake, this is war.
But that doesn't give you or me
the license to break the law.
There's a line.
I learned that the hard way.
Respectfully, sir, this is Gotham.
There are gray areas.
I've learned that the hard way, too.
And did you even get a lead
while you were out avenging Luke?
No, sir.
"No, sir." Well, you got one now.
Bodega owner called this in.
His security camera caught it.
She's our firefly.
We don't know who the other one is.
I do. Damn it.
(BRUCE GRUNTING)
Focus. Focus. Keep your head down.
Head down! Distractions will be
the death of you, Master Bruce.
Now, get on your toes. On your toes. Move!
Well, don't dance around
like a bloody showgirl. Come on.
That's better. Better.
Now, big left. Big left. Go on.
- Right. I've got you!
- (GASPING)
- Now, your enemies...
- Hey!
...are gonna fight
a lot dirtier than that.
Ow! Ow!
Bloody hell.
(CHUCKLES)
Very good, Master Bruce.
Eh?
Have you spoken to Mr. Fox
about the computer?
That I have, yeah.
How much longer till it's fixed?
(GRUNTS)
I'll tell you when it's done,
won't I? Patience.
I'm tired of patience, Alfred.
I'm ready to begin!
I'll tell you when you're ready,
Master Bruce.
I'm ready now. I know I am.
Oh, by the way, by the way,
Miss Silver called.
She wants you
to go for dinner this evening.
- Silver called?
- Yeah.
(GROANS)
Told you. Not ready.
- Let's go.
- Left.
KRINGLE: Well, he just up
and moved out of town.
It was rude and inconsiderate.
And perfectly in character
for Tom Dougherty.
Do you ever wonder where he went?
He could be dead in a ditch,
for all I care.
- DR. THOMPKINS: Kristen!
- And I mean it, too.
He, um... He wasn't very nice to me.
That's awful. I'm so sorry.
KRINGLE: Thank you. (SIGHS)
But it all worked out for the best.
DR. THOMPKINS: I know!
You and Ed seem to be getting along.
He is so gentle and kind.
Almost too gentle.
I think a man needs to have a little fire,
a little danger in him, don't you think?
- Oh, I don't know about that.
- (CHUCKLES)
And sometimes I feel like
he's holding something back from me.
DR. THOMPKINS: Like a secret?
I don't know.
I just... I guess, I just wish
he would open up a little more.
Good morning!
Miss Kringle, Miss Thompkins.
Hi.
What do you call a three-legged cow?
- I am terrible with--
- Lean beef!
Or supper. At my place.
Oh, Ed.
- Aw
- (CHUCKLES)
Ginger to ginger, we both know
you know where Selina Kyle's at.
So, why don't you tell me now
and save us the hassle?
Who's Selina Kyle?
- Cat.
- Cat?
Look, Ivy, want me to call the children's
home and have 'em come get you now?
Or should I get a candy bar
and forget to have someone watch you?
Candy bar.
I struck out. None of the street kids
I talked to have seen Selina.
Relax. Your Uncle Harvey has you covered.
She's in a squat off Jenkins.
Condemned SRO.
I know it.
Hey, last time we saw this chick,
she had a shotgun pointed at us.
Maybe you should take
the Fascist youth, huh?
Nah, with Selina, it's best to go quietly.
Come on!
When you get to the bus station,
take the first bus south.
Stay on till the end of the line.
Well, what do I do then?
You got plenty of money.
You can do what you like.
Thank you. For everything.
You've been a really good friend.
I got my cut. (CHUCKLES) No biggie.
(VAN APPROACHING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Bridgit, you need to run!
Bridgit, run! Run!
- Bridgit!
- No! Selina! No! Selina! No! No!
(BRIDGIT YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
BRIDGIT: Help me! No! Stop!
Hey!
Hands in the air!
- Drop the gun.
- Like hell I will.
- Where's your girlfriend?
- Who?
We got both of you on tape.
Don't know what you're
talking about, Gordon.
She's burned down half a dozen buildings.
Killed a cop.
You're running with a bad partner, kid.
You don't understand.
She was forced to do all of that!
Okay.
Let me help her. Who is she?
Who's forcing her to do this?
Look, there's a lot of
angry cops out there.
She's gonna get shot on sight
unless I get to her first.
Her name is Bridgit Pike.
Her brothers took her back.
Joe and Cale Pike.
They, like, kidnapped her.
They're the ones who made her
start burning stuff in the first place.
It's their fault the cop died!
The Pike brothers?
Why'd they burn down Wayne
Enterprises' buildings? Who paid them?
Why the hell should I know
why the Pikes do anything?
They're freaking nuts.
They treated Bridgit like a slave,
chained her to the wall.
And you're angry about it.
Is that why you're armed?
You gonna go after the Pikes?
Rescue your friend?
- No.
- That's a yes.
Look, you're gonna get your friend and
yourself killed. Let me handle the Pikes.
No offense, Jim, but I like
my chances better than yours.
Why get involved? Why risk your neck?
Who is this girl to you?
No one. Just a girl in the neighborhood.
I give you my word, I will do
everything I can to keep her safe.
But you have to stay out of it.
Tell me where she is.
(GRUNTS)
Damn. She's got six grand here.
Little Bridgy put on her big-girl pants.
You can take all of it, I don't care.
Oh, I'm taking it. That's not the issue.
The issue is you thinking it's cool
to just ditch your brothers. Hmm?
Oh, snap! Bridgit's gonna get it!
Joe, please...
Did you even think about us, hmm?
Did you even think how we would feel?
(SCREAMS) No, don't!
Joe, I didn't mean anything by it!
I'm a sensitive guy
and you hurt my feelings.
(SCREAMS)
I mean, without family, what do you got?
You got nothing, right?
You wanna be part of the family again?
I said...
(LIGHTER CLICKS)
Do you feel like
being part of this family again?
(SCREAMS)
Yes!
Damn! Damn, (LAUGHING)
that hurt! Bridgit's back.
(PANTING)
If you try anything like that again,
I'll kill you.
And I'll skin that little cat-bitch, too,
you hear me? You're never leaving.
Yes.
Good. Go make our supper.
All right, let's pack it up.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
(BUTCH SPUTTERS)
Dear me. A mallet. That's, um... Useful?
Don't even start.
Tell me you bring good news.
I'm in. I'm in good.
And? And?
I'm asking questions. But it's dangerous.
If I push too hard, Galavan will be
onto me. I told you, he's a smart guy.
Look at me, Butch.
Are you my servant?
(SNIFFS)
Yes.
Do you obey me in all things?
Then why do you bring me excuses?
Go find my mother
before I chop off your other hand.
Yes, boss.
(SIGHS)
CALE: Come on, harder!
(CHUCKLES)
(CALE GRUNTING AND LAUGHING)
Come on, Joe.
What are you gonna do? Kill us?
Yep.
(CALE AND JOE SCREAMING)
JOE: Oh, God!
I'll check the other room.
(DOOR OPENS)
(SIGHS)
Clear! She's not here.
Damn. I hate how it
smells like good barbecue.
- (GASPS)
- (SCREAMS)
Bitch.
(GRUNTING)
Bullock! Hey!
What? He scared the hell out of me.
(WHIMPERS)
And now he's dead. Nice work, Bullock.
Oh, yeah, my kicks did it?
Maybe it's because
he's fried like a taquito!
- It's not on me.
- Uh-huh.
Looks like Selina was telling the truth.
Look, I don't want to speak ill of the
dead, but these ass-hats had it coming.
These ass-hats were professional
arsonists. Somebody hired them.
But why Wayne Enterprises?
Who cares? All right?
There's a freaky firefly chick
on the loose with a flamethrower.
Let's start there.
(GROANS)
(GROANING)
Hallelujah.
(BUTCH EXHALES)
GALAVAN: Hello, Butch.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I just wanted to check in.
See how things were going. Any complaints?
No. No, sir.
I'm fine like a bottle of wine.
(CHUCKLES) Good.
You could have a real future here.
You are a hard worker,
and you're loyal to a fault.
Thank you, boss.
If only you were loyal to me.
I... I don't know
what you're talking about.
Come on, Butch, have some dignity.
I know what you were doing.
You were looking for Penguin's mother,
weren't you?
The hand was a nice touch.
Almost fooled me.
How on Earth did Penguin
get you to do that?
I'm his servant.
I have to obey him in all things.
Penguin's done a number on you, huh?
Tinkered with your wiring.
Perhaps we can help. Tabby?
Tabby, could you come here, please?
Penguin has brainwashed this poor soul.
Can we help?
Be my pleasure.
All right, look, let's...
Let's talk about this.
Can we talk about this?
Take it easy, what are you doing?
Relax. We just want to help.
(GRUNTS)
(SCREAMS)
I'll leave you two to it.
Uh, remember, dinner's in an hour.
(GROANS)
(SIGHS)
We've set up a perimeter.
She can't have gotten far.
And we're sitting on Selina Kyle's place.
Keep me posted.
Bridgit Pike was abused her whole life.
Forced to set those fires. I promised
my informant I would keep her safe.
(SIGHS)
Weren't you the one saying
that Luke Garrett was just a kid?
That we owe him justice?
- I know that's what I said--
- And you were right.
And now she killed him.
Now she has two more dead bodies on her.
So I don't care about the hows
and the whys and the boohoos.
You don't make promises you can't keep.
Now, you find her and
you take her down. Clear?
Yes, sir.
(COOING)
We must have spent years up here,
watching these birds.
Remember when Mickey Slattery
called us orphan bastards
and we tried to throw him off the roof?
The cops are outside my place.
You need to get out of town.
I'm not scared of them.
Bridgit, I know what you did
to your brothers.
Not that they didn't deserve it, but...
Whoa.
I was surprised.
Cale flamed up good, but it was Joe
who burned the brightest.
You don't sound like yourself.
I'm not myself anymore. I'm free.
Just like you told me I was.
So what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna go after the rest of them.
The rest of who?
The pervs and the bullies.
The ones who hurt people like us.
No one's ever gone after me or hurt me.
Yeah, right.
Rule number one, look after number one.
That's you.
Don't be crazy,
or you'll get yourself killed.
Don't worry about me, Selina.
This is what I was meant to do.
Bridgit, please, don't do this.
It's nice to have someone
who cares about me. Thank you.
I don't care.
I just think you're being dumb.
But... Hey. Good luck.
I'll see you around.
A toast.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING)
I'm so sorry.
Something came up last minute.
- (CLEARS THROAT)
- As I was saying...
- To family.
- Mmm.
In the end, it's all that matters.
(CLINKING)
Family.
I hope, in time, you'll come to think
of us as family, Bruce.
Thank you. It's...
It's been some time
since I had a meal like this.
You mean with girls?
You should come over more often.
We can, like, hang out or whatever.
- I'd like that.
- (SOFT CHUCKLING)
Look how cute they are.
Don't you just want to eat them?
Tabitha, leave the young people alone.
Well, they are cute, and they know it.
(SOFT JAZZ PLAYING)
These were the best
mashed potatoes I have ever had.
I swear I'm gonna get plump.
I like that you have an appetite.
Stop it, you're spoiling me.
I won't stop it.
I want nothing more than to spoil you.
Oh... Ed! So forceful.
There's something else
that I want to tell you.
But I just...
I don't want to scare you away.
Please. Tell me anything.
Do not hold back.
Kristen...
I like you very much.
I... I feel the same way about you.
And, um...
"And..." Shh.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
Mr. Nygma, is that your bedroom
over there?
Why, yes, it is.
Gordon, phone call for you.
This is Gordon.
Do you remember your promise?
Yes.
I think I know where she's going.
(MAN SCREAMING)
(CLAMORING)
No! No, please!
- Go! Go! Go! Just go! Go! Go!
- (CLAMORING)
Help me!
Come on!
- All right! Go, go, go!
- (SIREN WAILING)
All right, no one gets hurt tonight.
We follow protocols and stay safe.
Yes, sir.
- Freeze! Hands in the air!
- (GUNS COCKING)
Hold your fire!
Bridgit Pike?
Stay away!
My name's Jim Gordon.
I know what your brothers did to you.
I know you didn't mean
for any of this to happen.
You don't know anything.
You put your weapon down and come with me,
I can help you.
There are places you can go.
I'm not going to jail!
You're a juvenile,
we can work something out.
- Wait, wait!
- I said hold your fire!
(FLAME THROWER WHIRRING)
Bridgit! Stop!
Take cover!
(GASPS)
Bridgit! Wait!
(BRIDGIT SCREAMING)
I'm glad we have a moment alone.
There is something I need to discuss.
Oh?
An executive at Wayne Enterprises
has been reported missing.
Sid Bunderslaw. Do you know him?
Yes. We've met several times.
What happened?
No one knows. But it doesn't look good.
How did you hear?
Let's just say
I have friends in high places.
And I've been following the goings-on
at Wayne Enterprises very closely.
What have you learned?
That your father was a good man.
A great man, even.
But in spite of that,
bad things happened at his company.
Unfortunately, I think you're right.
I can tell you're very mature
for your age.
Ready to tackle the problems
of your company head-on.
But you'll need help. Once I'm mayor,
I would very much like to be that person.
Thank you, Mr. Galavan. I appreciate it.
(SMACKS LIPS)
Butch? What has happened?
I found your mother.
Where?
In a warehouse down by the port.
But they caught me looking.
You half-wit, if they kill my mother--
Look, they don't know I'm here.
The tiger lady, she wanted to take
her time with me, so she chained me up.
And I got out. We gotta go now.
(CHUCKLES) Yes. Yes. Yes. Good, Butch.
You've done well. Your loyalty will
be rewarded handsomely. I swear it.
Yes, boss.
Rest here for a minute
and I'll go gather the troops.
DR. THOMPKINS: How old are you?
Old enough to shoot you,
if that's what you're thinking.
No, that's not what I was thinking.
You don't have to point the gun at me.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Damn right you're not.
- My name is Lee.
- I know what your name is.
What's your name?
You're cute. For a doctor.
Thanks! You're cute, for a gangster.
(DOOR OPENS)
Hi, Selina. Sorry about this, Lee.
Oh, hey. No problem.
(SIGHS)
So? Is Bridgit okay?
I'm sorry. She's not gonna make it.
You said that you'd help her!
I tried, Selina. I tried.
But she didn't wanna go quietly.
I think she wanted it to end this way.
(SNIFFLES)
Look, Selina--
Don't touch me. Don't touch me.
I know you were
telling the truth about Bridgit.
That her brothers put her up to this.
I need to know who hired them.
I already told you I don't know.
And I still don't believe you.
What do you care?
You don't care about people like us.
It's not like you're really gonna
go after your little friend.
My friend?
Do you mean Penguin?
Why would he set those fires?
That doesn't make any sense.
Ask him yourself.
I'm done talking to you.
(SNIFFLING)
I should have never trusted a cop.
I tried to help her.
It just went a different way.
Is that what you call it
when someone dies?
Is that what you tell yourself?
I'm sorry.
(SCOFFS)
Whatever.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
You're so sweet.
Kristen, what's the matter?
Um...
I'm scared.
Of what?
Of Tom Dougherty.
He used to tell me, if he ever saw me
with another man, he would kill me.
I'm terrified of what will happen
when he comes back.
- You don't need to worry about that.
- Mmm.
You don't know him. He is a monster.
Listen to me. You do not need
to worry about Tom Dougherty.
(CHUCKLES)
You are sweet. But...
You're not a fighter.
You couldn't possibly take him on.
Trust me, he's been taken care of.
What does that mean?
Um...
Some time ago,
he and I had an altercation.
I asked him
to treat you with more respect.
Oh, my God.
And he said he would treat you
any way he liked, and he assaulted me.
Oh, my God!
So, anyhow, long story short...
I killed him.
(LAUGHING) Oh, Ed. That's...
You had me going for a minute, there.
It was outside of your apartment,
under the elevated train.
I stabbed him and he died.
Ed, that's not funny.
I'm not being funny.
"T. Dougherty."
Do you believe me now?
Oh, my God.
What's wrong? Where are you going?
- Ah... How could you?
- No, please, sit down.
Don't touch me!
Would you please let me explain?
There is nothing to explain.
I don't even know who you are.
No, that's wrong. You are a murderer.
He was a monster!
You said so. He was abusing you!
I can't believe I even fell for you,
you sicko!
I'm not sick! I love you.
I did it for you.
Everything I ever thought about you, I was
right! I should have my head examined!
Don't say that.
Wait, what were you doing
outside my house?
I was worried for you.
You were stalking me!
You are a psychopath!
That is not true! That's not who I am.
Don't say that about me.
You are going to prison where
they will do horrible things to you.
Things that you deserve.
Don't say that to me!
No, let go! Don't touch me!
(GRUNTS)
Let go of me, you freak!
Please don't call me that!
Ow!
Help!
Listen to me!
I am not the man that you think I am.
- I would never do anything to hurt you.
- (MUFFLED BREATHING)
I had to kill him. Because he hit you.
Do you understand that?
- I did it for you.
- (STRUGGLING AND CHOKING)
I promise I will never do anything
to hurt you ever again.
I love you. I've loved you since
the first moment that I saw you.
Kristen. Kristen? Oh, no, no, no, don't.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no!
Please! Please, no!
No! No!
(SOBBING)
No!
(GUNS COCKS)
(SNIFFLING)
(SOBBING)
No!
(DOG BARKING)
ORDERLY 1: Damn, this girl looks rough.
They tell people she dead,
but that's a lie.
I heard the suit she was wearing
melted to her.
- They say she's fireproof.
- Come on.
Yeah, man. Fireproof.
That's why they sent her down here with
the rest of the monsters. For testing.
(ALARM BLARING)
(WHIMPERS)
(SCREAMING)
(CRACKLING AND WHIRRING)
(LABORED BREATHING)
English - SDH