Previously onGotham...
We will create a legacy in this city.
Gotham falls, we rise together.
Why don't you understand?
You need me!
I'm the answer
to your life's question.
All this happened because of me.
They were trying to hurt me
and the people I care about.
With reunification underway,
and the bridges being rebuilt,
it is my honor to bestow
upon Captain James Gordon
the title of Commissioner.
What do you mean you're leaving?
Gotham's in good hands.
Thank you, Bruce.
And you're the only son
that I will ever have,
and I could not be more proud.
Alfred,
I'm writing to let you know,
I'm okay.
And that you won't hear from me
for some time.
But I will return...
when I know I'm able to protect
the people I love.
When Gotham needs me...
I will return.
It began a few weeks ago.
Someone attacking the gangs downtown.
No deaths so far, at least.
Hoods couldn't give a description,
but they did mention a growling.
A growling?
It's a rumor. Ignore it.
Oswald Cobblepot gets out
of Blackgate tomorrow.
One theory is, he's sending someone
to put the fear of God
into the underworld.
And you choose this moment
to hand in your resignation?
I told you that months ago.
That's not the point!
Look, things are unstable.
Isn't there some break in
at a government warehouse
that you guys haven't solved yet?
Yeah, because the feds
won't tell us squat.
I'm not looking for excuses!
Look, you mean something
to this city.
You can't quit.
Not now.
Because of Wayne Tower.
Bruce Wayne is returning home
for the first time in a decade
for its opening.
The new Wayne Tower represents hope
for Gotham.
So yeah, I need you.
Mayor James...
I told you I would stay
until after the Wayne Inaugural.
Then I'm done.
If you'll excuse me,
I have a fundraiser
I have to get ready for.
Good day, gentlemen.
Jim.
I've had ten years, Harv.
It's time for someone else
to have a chance.
Did you wait for Bruce to come back
to hang it up?
That's a coincidence?
I'm late.
- I have to meet Barbara.
- Yeah.
The queen of Gotham.
Tell me something.
Why didn't I buy up half of Gotham
on the cheap after reunification?
Become a tycoon?
Give a kiss to the little one
from Uncle Harv.
Will do.
Hey, slugger.
Daddy.
I don't think the weight of the...
- Just do it.
- Yes, ma'am.
Hi, sweetheart.
So, did you hear from Bruce?
No.
Ten years, not a word.
But I'm assuming he'll be at the gala
for Wayne Tower tomorrow?
I wanna see the look on his face
when I tell him, in three months,
he won't have the tallest building
in Gotham anymore.
Think he'll recognize you with
that caterpillar on your top lip?
Okay, munchkin, I love you.
Don't let her stay up too late.
- Ice cream?
- Yes.
Look. Look.
It's right under there, under my arm.
You guys, move!
Bruce is back?
Big deal.
I knew him.
Back in the day.
Saved Gotham together.
Oswald's being freed?
Hey! I've been in here ten years!
Ten years!
I deserve to read the newspaper,
you mouth breather!
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Do you not know who that is?
Jeremiah Valeska.
And yeah...
he's been a vegetable for a decade.
Can't think, can't feel.
But he is a legend.
And if you're gonna screw
with a legend...
do it properly.
This never gets old.
Hey, buddy, I got something for you.
Hey! What are you doing?
Where are you taking me?
Come on.
Out of the way.
Whoa.
Yep. It was time to admit it.
I was trying something.
It didn't work.
You liked it, right?
Totally.
At least now,
Bruce will recognize you.
That's very funny.
I wonder how much he's changed.
Well, it's been ten years,
I'd imagine a lot.
Well, we haven't.
I'm still a doctor.
You're still a cop.
Not for long.
Are you having second thoughts
about leaving?
Well, I'm all for it.
But I know
how much this job means to you.
And how much the city looks to you.
It always has.
You know, that's just it.
I was hoping Gotham would outgrow me.
But it hasn't exactly happened.
No one's stepped forward.
Well, maybe you need to step down
to allow someone to step up.
Jim Gordon,
clean-shaven man of leisure.
Ten years.
I wonder what Bruce will think
of Selina.
She's become quite the it girl
around town.
So, they have no idea
when Nygma actually escaped?
He wasn't in his cell this morning.
This is where the guard lives.
The one that didn't show for work.
All right. I got it.
Stay here in case something else
comes in.
All right.
GCPD!
- No! Okay, okay...
- Shut up!
Talk to him.
This is Detective Bullock.
You understand?
Oh, my God.
You understand what you have to do?
I don't have a choice!
What the hell happened, Harvey?
What did Harper say?
I wanna hear it from you.
We tracked down this Arkham guard
we thought maybe helped Nygma escape.
I shot him.
End of story.
You're confessing to killing
an unarmed suspect in cold blood.
It's what happened.
You got to let it go.
Harvey, I don't know if you think
you're protecting yourself
or someone else,
but you need to change your story,
otherwise you're going to Blackgate.
And you know what happens to cops
in Blackgate.
That's what happened.
So let it go.
I just can't believe
he'd do anything...
All right, first things first,
whoever here doesn't believe
Harvey Bullock is innocent can leave
right now.
Good.
- You think Nygma's behind this?
- Maybe.
But he's been inside Arkham
for ten years.
It's not like he suddenly decided
to break out.
He had help.
Penguin gets released today.
- You think?
- Yeah.
Put a tail on him.
In the meantime,
I want every other cop in the city
on the hunt for Edward Nygma.
We looked into the dead guard.
He used to be associated
with a south side gang.
Got an address. An old warehouse.
All right, you and I will hit it.
Rest of you have your orders.
Let's go.
Hello?
Anybody?
"Dear Ed, My old friend.
Half of Gotham thinks you a madman.
The other half has forgotten you.
It's time to remind them
who the Riddler is.
I've given you all you need.
Follow the instructions. Oswald."
Oswald, what are you planning?
Mr. Cobblepot, what's the first thing
you'll do as a free man?
I will lay flowers on the grave
of my beloved mother.
But what of Jim Gordon's role
in your incarceration?
Will you seek revenge?
The best revenge against Jim Gordon
will be a life spent serving the city
I love.
What do you say, young man?
How would you like an exclusive?
- Yeah, sure.
- Yeah.
Your jacket and hat.
- What?
- Now!
GCPD!
GCPD.
This is the place.
Good God.
Did your lead say anything
about this?
About a gangland bloodbath?
No.
What the hell is going on?
Someone's covering their tracks.
There was a break-in at a government
warehouse last week.
Those crates have US Army markings.
Find the back stairs.
GCPD!
I know you're here.
Show yourself.
I am not your enemy.
Don't touch the bodies.
Don't move!
Grenade!
Bomb squad said the bodies
were rigged with C-Four.
Whoever that was, saved our lives.
Suggesting that he wasn't the one
that killed them.
Could be he's hunting the same person
we're hunting.
Whoever's really behind all this.
- You're thinking he's on our side?
- Yeah, maybe.
That C-Four has to have been what was
stolen from the government warehouse.
Which means most of it's still
missing.
Just got a call.
Mayor James vanished
and our tail lost Penguin.
Sir, what the hell is going on?
First Nygma, now Penguin.
Keep it simple.
Imagine all that C-Four.
What's the biggest target in Gotham
right now?
Double security for tonight's event.
I have to talk to Bruce Wayne
and Alfred Pennyworth.
Hello, old friend.
- Oswald...
- One more word,
and I will put a bullet in you here
and now.
Drive.
- Oswald...
- Don't talk!
Turn around!
Remember when we stood here, Jim,
all those years ago?
Don Falcone wanted you to shoot me,
you refused.
Now don't you wish you'd done it?
Everyone will know you did this.
Let them!
We both know that this has been
a long time coming.
Our story is over, old friend.
You wanna kill me? Fine.
There's no need to attack
the Wayne gala.
What are you talking about?
Breaking Nygma out of Arkham,
the attacks on the gangs.
What? Do you think you're gonna
be able to destroy Wayne Tower
and no one's gonna notice?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
You and I stood shoulder to shoulder
on those barricades,
ready to die for this city.
Six months later,
you locked me up like an animal!
This begins and ends with you and me!
You're telling the truth.
Goodbye, Jim.
Turn around!
You know, you made a mistake bringing
me out to this pier...
Don't talk!
Or maybe you just have
a short memory.
So this is Bruce's new Gotham?
I like the old one.
Selina?
How wonderful to see you again.
It's been far, far too long.
Where is he?
Well, I'm afraid travels abroad
haven't increased Master Bruce's
respect for punctuality, Miss Kyle.
I came here to tell him
to stop spying on me.
I don't understand.
I was out the other night
and I felt someone watching me.
I know it was Bruce.
Oh, I see. Right.
Well, that makes perfect sense.
So, you come here tonight,
dressed to the nines to tell him
that you want nothing more
to do with him.
Is that the kind of gist of it?
He left, Alfred.
Everything we went through,
and one day he's just gone.
He doesn't get to come back
after ten years
and act like nothing's happened.
On this, we absolutely agree.
I do, however,
feel it might be something
that you wanna tell him yourself.
He needs to stay away.
Nygma?
Well, look at you.
I think Bruce is gonna regret being
gone all these years.
Follow me.
Credit to Bruce.
He did not skimp on the caterers.
Hungry?
Your loss.
Not long now.
Bruce Wayne's first public appearance
in nearly a decade.
- Lucius.
- Lee.
Heard about Harvey. How is he?
- How's Jim?
- I don't know.
I was hoping he would be here.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
my name is Alfred Thaddeus
Crane Pennyworth.
And I'd very much like to welcome you
on behalf of Wayne Enterprises
and Bruce Wayne,
to the future of Gotham.
As you know, 10 years ago,
the battle...
Oh, come on.
Where is that brat?
- Bruce Wayne.
- Hello, Ed.
Barbara Kean.
In red?
Oh, no.
Please tell me you're not here
to stop me.
Barbara, do you even remember
how amazing you used to be?
Honey, I'm still amazing.
I just made a choice.
You made a choice?
Some of us don't get to make choices.
I am the Riddler.
And tonight,
Gotham will remember that.
By blowing up this ding-dong?
Didn't you do that already?
It's a call back!
I was waiting for Bruce
to begin his speech.
You know, come out, present a riddle.
Only Bruce doesn't seem
to wanna show.
So, I think I'm gonna have to imp...
Sorry, Ed.
Not tonight.
Wayne Enterprises will devote itself
to making this future a reality.
Lee.
Gotham joining.
- Jim?
- I'm fine.
Evacuate the building!
Get these people out of here!
Help!
Gordon!
- Gordon!
- Everybody, get down!
Gordon, help!
This lunatic, he kidnapped me again!
He tried to blow me up! Again!
But we stopped him. You're welcome.
Take care of the mayor, please.
Get that thing off him.
Excuse me.
There were four crates of C-Four.
Where are the rest?
That's all he gave me.
He said Penguin broke him out.
No. It wasn't Penguin.
Get him out of there.
What?
Hey! Get off me!
Nygma's not just a patsy,
he's not even a real threat.
Which means there must be...
If this bomb goes off
and Wayne Tower falls,
it'll take out other buildings.
A lot of people are gonna die.
You all need to leave right now.
So you can stay? Absolutely not.
It's too late.
We'd never get far enough away.
Miss Kean is right.
This stops right here.
So, how do we defuse it?
We'd have to sever the connectors
to the detonator.
But the bomber must've hidden it.
The wires go up inside the model.
It must be in one of the buildings.
I tracked down a gang today.
They had bomb-making materials,
pictures of buildings.
One in particular.
Gotham clock tower.
Let's go.
In here.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait. This particular detonator
has a gyroscope,
which means someone
will have to hold it up and steady
while you detach the wires
from below.
I have doctor's hands. I can do it.
Fine. Lucius.
All right.
The trigger connection should be
different than the others.
Okay, I see two green wires.
I'm gonna cut this one?
- The other one!
- Yes, the other one.
I never doubted you for a minute.
Strange.
We'd designed a new clock tower,
but this is the old one.
That's the answer.
Who's behind all this, but...
it's not possible.
Sir?
Sir, Nygma's vanished.
There's more.
Mayor James ordered Bullock sent
to Blackgate.
He's about to be moved.
Stop!
The person who framed you,
the one behind Nygma's breakout.
Is it who I think it is?
- Has he been faking it?
- Jim, do not say his name.
Is it Jeremiah Valeska?
Harvey!
- Check him for a wire!
- What?
Under his shirt! Check for a wire!
Oh, God. It's too late.
He's mic'd.
Jim, you don't know what he'll do.
I don't know about this.
How much is it again?
Ten bucks is a body punch.
Twenty, you get the face.
Stabbing him is a C-note.
Bad news, boss.
Our cover's blownskies.
Edward Nygma.
It is very good to see you.
Oswald.
I thought you weren't behind this.
I'm not.
But I thought you might
need some help and...
what else are friends for?
You look well.
You too.
A little thicker in the middle.
Damn, it's good to see you, Oswald.
What was that? What was that?
No!
What the hell was that?
Alfred.
When Bruce came to me the day
he got back
and told me what he was planning,
I didn't hesitate.
I believe in what he's doing.
But he's going to need some help.
Has he thought about telling Gordon?
Lucius, my old friend,
whoever Bruce decides to take
on this journey with him,
it's his decision.
Our role is to serve.
Let me go. I have to...
Down!
Get me down!
Something happened tonight,
didn't it?
Why won't you tell me?
Because everything worked out okay.
Didn't it?
So, why are we at your old club?
Because Mommy just needs
to get something.
Wait here, okay?
But I think I could love her
Turn around.
I won't ask again.
Surprise!
Easy. It's just a surprise party
for you,
Barbara Kean. Queen of Gotham.
Business titan.
How exciting.
But there was another you, I...
I seem to recall.
Wasn't there? Then again,
there was another me, too.
Oh, so hard holding
on to what's real.
It's enough to drive you mad.
Mom!
Cute.
She has your eyes.
For now.
No! Put me down!
I think she nicked me, Daddy.
I...
Oh, boy.
Oh, dear me.
My sweet Ecco no longer my echo.
There'll never be one like you.
Really?
But I suppose there are other fish
in the sea.
Let me down!
Mom!
Little Barbara! Don't say a word.
Now we're going to play
a little game.
By now, James Gordon should
have made it to your apartment.
When he gets here I want you
to deliver a message. Okay?
Okay?
Barbara?
I'll call an ambulance.
He took her!
That lunatic took her!
He said you have to come,
and if you don't come,
he's gonna kill her.
Where?
The place where he was born again.
He means Ace Chemicals.
You promise me.
I'll bring her back.
Come along, Commissioner.
We're waiting.
The party's raging,
but it's well past
the princess' bedtime.
It's funny being back here.
I can still feel my flesh sizzle
as it melted away.
Burns even now. Hold on.
I'm here.
Everything's gonna be fine.
You think so?
Personally, I'd say things are about
as far away from fine
as they could possibly be,
Barbara Lee.
What do I know?
I did just spend the last ten years
in the funny farm.
What do you want, Jeremiah?
Is there a Jeremiah here?
So, what do I call you?
Well...
I don't know. Call me Jack.
No, no, no, that's not right.
Joseph. John. Jay...
I don't know. I just...
I feel something new crawling
from the primordial ooze that was me.
Something beautiful.
How long have you been pretending
to be brain dead?
How long have you been pretending?
That's a joke.
I know you're not pretending.
That's far enough, James.
But you still haven't told me.
Why?
Why keep pretending?
I was waiting for him to come home.
We're bound together, he and I.
It's the one thing I knew
for certain.
The one thing I knew was true.
And then he just abandoned us.
Do you know how it feels
to have the one,
the only thing you love
ripped away from you?
- Feels like this.
- No!
Disappointing as tonight was,
I will say it is fun carving up
Filet Commissioner.
Who's there?
What do you want?
Show yourself!
You?
It's okay. It's all right.
I got you. Okay?
So, he comes out of nowhere,
saves you and Barbara Lee,
and just disappears?
Yeah.
So, the dude's on our side?
I think so.
This old thing?
I thought we mothballed this
after reunification.
I had them dig it out
for old times' sake.
I sent a note to Wayne Manor.
I thought Bruce might wanna be here
when we light it.
Good evening, gentlemen.
Master Bruce sends his profound
apologies.
He's otherwise engaged.
He's been busy a lot
since he came back.
Yes, indeed.
And I hear that you're retiring.
I may stick around a while yet.
You're there, aren't you?
Do you have any idea what you did?
Just leaving?
You were all I had.
And I know you wanted to protect me.
But I didn't want to be protected,
I wanted you.
Say something.
There was no other way, Selina.
I had to go.
So, what happens now?
I don't know.
But I'll never leave Gotham again.
Return the diamond.
Like hell.
Gotham is mine,
that's what he said.
I was there, Oswald.
I did not spend ten years
in Blackgate
to give my city to a man dressed
like a bat!
Yeah.
Go!
We have to find out who he is,
and show him that this is our city.
Agreed.
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow.
Yet in the darkness,
there will be light.
That's what you promised Master Bruce
all those years ago in the alley.
You saved him.
Gave him hope.
Holy mother.
Who is he?
Friend.