Previously onGotham...
We're onto you, Professor Strange.
Bad guys come in and monsters
come out.
I am Firefly.
Selina. Hugo Strange has Selina.
Do you remember your name?
My name is Fish Mooney.
Make me a grilled cheese sandwich.
You made me a sandwich?
- Why?
- I don't know.
And how exactly do you plan
on getting into Arkham?
- I'll ask for a tour.
- From the man that ordered
the assassination of your father?
He'll wanna find out what we know.
He won't see me and Lucius
as a threat.
I call Bullock, he comes busting in
with 100 cops.
Take them.
Move everything you can
to the facility upstate.
You have an explosive device.
Use it.
Destroy Indian Hill.
Basil is a chameleon of sorts.
Would you like to see?
You son of a bitch.
I'm Jim Gordon.
Right. Go get our guys.
No sign of Gordon.
How long do you want us to wait?
Give him 10 seconds.
If you don't see Jim,
bust that joint open and find him.
Entry team. We go on one.
Go. Cover me.
Go. Go!
Four, three, two...
Stand down.
- Stand down, officers.
- Hold.
- Stand down.
- All clear.
- Stand down. Stand down.
All clear?
Sorry to waste your time, hoss.
How about a ride to HQ?
Sure thing, Jim. You okay?
You look kind of hinky.
Never better.
Strange!
Strange! Strange!
Strange, you son of a bitch,
come back here!
So.
- You're really doing this.
- Not my call.
Prepare patients for transport
to the upstate facility.
If one of your patients
were to escape...
They won't. The police
won't be delayed much longer.
Prepare the patients and move fast.
As soon as we're done with Gordon and
Wayne, we'll detonate the bomb.
Yes, sir.
Okay, quiz kids.
Who's ready to play Life or Death?
Sir. Mr. Nygma.
You are Nygma, aren't you?
This is absurd. Police
know we're here. You can't kill us.
Are you ready to play?
Yes.
Good.
You have one guess.
Five minutes to talk it over.
Who runs Indian Hill?
You have one guess.
Think carefully, fellas.
Answer correctly...
or die.
Strange.
Strange?
Hi.
What is that?
Honesty serum.
I need to know what you know.
Wait. Wait.
So how do you feel now?
Not good.
Can you be more specific?
I feel vulnerable.
Naked.
Your feelings are entirely natural
and normal.
There is nothing to be ashamed of.
You are in a helpless situation.
There is nothing you can do.
Do you understand that?
Yes.
- No.
- No?
What can you do?
James, what can you do?
Made a plan.
Tell me your plan.
If I don't check-in
with the GCPD by noon
tell them I'm safe
they will come after you.
Yes.
Yes, I know.
You did check in with the GCPD.
Nobody's coming.
You can relax.
Jim.
Harv.
Strange is clean?
What the hell happened?
Dead end.
Dead end?
What are you talking about? Dead end?
He's connected.
So is my mechanic. Who isn't?
- Connected to people we can't cross.
- What people?
You don't wanna know.
Trust me.
You feeling all right?
You look like a sack of fish.
Little flu, maybe.
Keep your distance.
I'm getting laid this weekend,
fingers crossed.
You have 60 seconds left.
Who runs Indian Hill?
I say Hugo Strange.
Wayne Enterprises.
- Wayne Enterprises runs Indian Hill.
- That surmise.
Why would he ask that question
if the answer's obvious?
He wants to know what we know.
- What we think we know.
- Which is Wayne Enterprises.
Is that your answer?
Running out of time here.
Yes.
Correct!
Wayne Enterprises runs Indian Hill.
Bravo, Brucey.
You're almost safe.
Just one more question.
- You ready?
- Yes.
You have five minutes, quiz kids.
Answer correctly or die.
Wayne Enterprises runs Indian Hill.
But who runs Wayne Enterprises?
Move them out
in order of security grades.
Lowest risk first.
Tranq them, immobilize them,
and put them on the bus
and do it fast but very,
very carefully.
Security is our number one priority.
Yes, ma'am.
- Hey, lady.
- Busy day, busy day.
We'll get to you, Number 13.
Your mama may be Number 13
but I'm a human being.
Fish Mooney, bitch.
Here, you're re-animant test case
Number 13.
And I'm Miss Peabody.
And you'd best not talk
about my mama.
Miss Peabody.
I apologize.
I'm a bit stressed.
I don't like being locked up.
It's against my nature.
I understand. I do.
But you are a priceless
scientific miracle.
You are history.
Seclusion is regrettable
but inevitable.
Look.
I've been here before.
All you mad scientists
say the same kind of stuff.
I don't care.
Let me go.
Sorry, 13.
Let's go.
You're messing with the wrong woman.
You hear me?
The wrong woman.
Here?
A little too central, maybe.
You don't want one piece
to overpower the room.
Try over there.
You're absolutely right.
See? I told you she'd be useful.
Isn't that better?
Interior design ain't my thing.
News on the hour with WTGC.
Police sources say that reports
of an impending raid
on Arkham Insane Asylum
and its controversial chief,
Professor Hugo Strange,
are inaccurate.
Despite the disclaimers,
flurries of police activity around
the troubled facility
have fueled rumors
- that arrests are imminent.
- Hugo Strange.
How interesting.
Answer quickly, please, Jim.
Without thinking.
Who did you love more,
your mother or father?
- Mother.
- Why?
I resented my father's strength.
I see. Yes.
- And when he died
- Yes?
how did you feel?
- Guilty.
- For a car crash?
Why? It was not your fault.
I imagined he was gone.
And then, he was.
You lost a child recently.
- Yes.
- How does that make you feel?
Guilty.
Guilt again.
- You blame yourself?
- It was my fault.
Oh, I see. I didn't know that.
And what happened to the mother?
- Lee, was it?
- She's
down south somewhere.
- Do you still love her?
- Yes.
- Do you want to be with her?
And why aren't you with her?
I've put her through enough pain.
Jim.
I need you to relax.
Close your eyes.
Imagine that I am God.
All-powerful.
I am God.
And I absolve you
of all of your guilt.
I put that guilt on you.
And now
I take it away.
It's gone.
Your burdens are gone.
So how do you feel?
Good. Better.
Good.
Good, good.
Jim.
Now that we're relaxed
and speaking honestly, tell me.
What do you know about our work
here at Indian Hill?
You're building monsters
for military use.
Oh, we're doing much more than that.
But for who?
Who owns Indian Hill?
Wayne Enterprises.
And who controls Wayne Enterprises
behind the scenes?
Who controls everything in Gotham
I don't know.
The rich?
Oh, they are rich, I'm sure.
But can you be more specific?
Who controls Gotham, Jim?
You never heard of a
secret council?
Secret council?
No.
Excellent.
Excellent. Thank you.
That's what I needed to know.
Professor Strange.
Yes, Jim?
What you said about Lee.
I should have gone after her?
Oh, no doubt.
Guilt has compelled you to sacrifice
your heart to your conscience.
But guilt is useless.
Love, Jim.
Love is our guide.
Time's up, I'm afraid.
In the spirit of intimacy
and honesty,
I have been speaking about your life
as if it had a future
and that is not so.
You have a few hours.
You have 30 seconds left.
Who runs Wayne Enterprises?
The devil, maybe? Is that the deal?
Communists? Witches?
No, there's truth behind
this question. A big secret.
I've worked for Wayne Enterprises
for 10 years.
There is no secret. The board
of directors runs Wayne Enterprises.
- Fifteen seconds.
- That can't be the answer, Lucius.
Ten seconds.
Give us more time!
- Five seconds.
- The board of directors.
Incorrect.
Oh, what a shame.
The correct answer is...
Sorry, fellas, you lose.
And what happens to losers?
Yowza!
Death by poison gas.
Jim.
Hi.
Are we alive?
So far so good.
I had to be sure.
I thought we were dead.
Wow, that was unpleasant.
How are things going for you?
We've had a hell of a time.
Same.
- You okay?
- A little groggy.
He drugged me. Made me talk.
About Wayne Enterprises, right?
About everything.
Bruce,
I never should have made that
oath to you.
- That's not really...
- I was arrogant and naive.
And I'm sorry.
I tried to do the right thing but
what a fool I've been.
What kind of drugs did they give you?
Well done, Ed.
I'm impressed. You were a
shaman of sorts. A witch doctor.
So just between us,
who does run Wayne Enterprises?
I could tell you. But then I would
have to lobotomize you.
Got you.
Still moving forward, sir,
I would be more than happy
to help you with any
of your other cases.
You would be a wonderful addition
to my staff, Ed.
A wonderful addition
if you were only sane.
- No, seriously.
- Yes, seriously.
You have been very useful.
And we arrogant physicians have much
to learn from a madman like you.
But not that much.
No, no, no. No, no, no.
You will not treat me
like a crazy person! No!
Madam, I bring good news.
Gordon and Wayne and Fox
know nothing but mundanities.
They have told no one the truth.
Because they have none of the truth.
Our secret is safe.
Kill them all.
Then continue with the evacuation
of your test subjects.
Yes, madam.
The destruction of Indian Hill
will proceed as scheduled.
Releasing Galavan was a grave error
on your part.
No more of your patients
will see the light of day
under any circumstances.
At any cost.
I understand, madam.
These people
to whom Strange is connected
they must be pretty heavy, huh,
to make you back off.
Oh, they're heavy.
I don't want anything dangerous,
I just like being titillated.
Seriously, you don't wanna know.
Remember the time you called me
from the hospital
when you had Falcone on the gurney?
And the whole town and their uncle
were looking to kill you both?
How could I forget?
Remember what I said to you
on the phone?
Remember what I said?
I forget.
That's funny.
Gordon, you're back. What happened?
Where's Master Bruce? Where's Lucius?
Where are they? Have you seen them?
- Hey, Alfred, take it easy.
- Where are they?
Alfred. Alfred, relax.
Master Bruce and Lucius are
headed back to Wayne Manor.
Yeah, well, that's a load of obtosh
for starters, isn't it?
I just come back from there.
What can I tell you?
Maybe they stopped to get a snack.
So, what about Strange?
It's complicated.
Well, go on, then. What?
Complicated police business.
He's got a touch of the flu.
You.
How you doing?
Middling.
What's your deal?
Chilling.
They're gonna blow this dump sky high
and the whole circus
is moving upstate.
- When?
- Soon. Like, an hour.
- Can you escape?
- Of course.
Firefly thinks I'm her sidekick.
- So I got trusty status.
- Then please do so.
- Get out and call the police...
- I'll do what I like.
I led you into this mess.
I was self-righteous and arrogant
and manipulative.
- I used you and I'm sorry.
- Like you can use me.
I got you wrapped around my pinky.
Always have.
Be that as it may.
If you can escape, do it.
Manipulative.
As if.
What did she say?
She'll do what she likes.
And there's a bomb.
Hello, Number 13.
Stay calm.
No one's going to hurt you.
It's time to go on a trip.
Give me your right arm.
Say my name.
Fish Mooney.
That's right.
What's your name?
Ethel Peabody.
Ethel
you seem sad and anxious.
You got that right.
You let me out of here
and I'll be your friend.
Oh, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Interesting.
Miss Peabody, what are you doing?
What she says.
Why?
I don't know.
Miss Mooney,
you have special talents.
Some form of psychotropic chemical
agent on your skin, I imagine.
You are marvelous.
Yes, truly marvelous.
- Always was.
- Indeed.
Would love to chat about me
but we have a bus to catch.
No. Ms. Mooney,
if you and the others on that bus
were to appear in public,
it would cause a revolution.
An apocalypse.
I simply can't allow you
to just walk out of here.
Watch me.
Please don't go.
Please, you're breaking my heart.
I love you like my own daughter.
No one could love you more.
But I will have to kill you
before I let you go.
Please choose life.
You would have made a great pimp.
No, no, no.
No!
Bring him back.
Hugo, I order you to stop. Now.
Stop. Now!
You hear me?
Security systems activated.
No!
I've tried calling about
a thousand times.
Still no answer.
Strange has them. I'm positive.
Holy crap. Are you still here?
I told you a thousand times,
Strange is clean.
You're in charge of that, are you?
Strange though, isn't it?
I mean, strange they're MIA.
That's funny.
- Strange.
- Funny?
You know, maybe I should send
the strike force back into Arkham,
- have a little look-see.
- No, no, you don't wanna do that,
bad idea.
Trust me, that's a terrible idea.
How long you known me?
All right. If you're good,
I guess I'm good.
I don't know who's got to you,
Gordon, but you're just, just...
Weird.
Hey, Alfred.
- Ms. Kean.
- How's the buttling business?
- To what do we owe the...?
- Jimmy, my love,
I'm sure you're ever so busy,
but could we have a word in private?
You bet.
Well, you look terrible.
Gee, thanks, Barbara.
You look pretty good.
Well, shucks.
Question, what the hell is going on
down at Arkham?
Two questions back at you, gorgeous.
Why you asking?
And what's in it for me?
I'm asking because a dear friend
of mine wants to know the answer.
And what would you like to be
in it for you?
Hey, spring is here, baby.
So now you like me again?
What's not to like?
- So you've forgotten about Lee?
- Lee?
Lee Thompkins.
Screw that hoe.
Water under the bridge.
You're not Jim.
Say what, now?
Hold on there, woman.
- Holy mother of saints.
- Holy cow.
Kill the captives. We have to go.
Whoa, whoa, where are we going?
- What's the hurry?
- Silence.
Freeze, get it done.
- Jeez, relax. What's with him?
- Quiet.
Quiet yourself.
Why do you have to kill them?
Why are you so mean?
I knew I shouldn't have spared you.
Freeze, kill her.
- Wait a minute.
- I'm sorry, Firefly.
I told you, she was an experiment.
But she's my friend. I need her.
We don't have time for this.
Please don't let him hurt me.
Firefly.
Please help me.
Don't you dare.
Out of the way, sparky.
- Make me.
- Firefly. No.
Stop!
What now?
Sounds like warfare.
What's going on?
Simple psychology.
Been waiting for the right moment.
You coming or what?
Fifteen minutes to detonation.
Strange!
Wake up!
Alpha and Charlie squads to Arkham.
Bravo and Delta to Indian Hill.
Move!
Hey, Penguin.
So it turns out
our Mr. Strange is a very bad man.
The police are onto him now.
They figure he's planning to run
but he won't.
Thanks to me.
Thank you, Barbara.
You have pleased me.
Saddle up, Butch.
We've got an old friend to catch.
Wake up, Strange.
I know you're in there. Wake up.
Gordon. I surmise my plan
must have gone awry.
You could say.
I'm gonna stand you up now
and you're gonna give us a tour
of your secret lab.
- No.
- You don't have a choice.
- It's this way, right?
- We can't go there. I set a bomb.
The lab is going to blow up.
We have to get out of here.
In 10 minutes, everything within
a quarter-mile radius will be dust.
- That's madness.
- If you want to live,
which I do, frankly,
we had better leave.
We detected radioactive material.
You got it out first, right?
There wasn't enough time.
They forced my hand.
But I calculated the chances
of a radioactive cloud as fairly low.
If you're wrong,
thousands of people could die.
Yes, yes, yes.
But paying that price will be better
than releasing what's down there.
- How do we shut it down?
- The security walls are up.
- The lab is sealed.
- There must be some way in.
We have to go.
We have to leave, now!
Tell me how to get that bomb
and shut it off,
or I'll batter you to death
right here!
In which case, young man,
I suppose I will just have to die.
Wait, Nygma knows the way down there.
- Could use some help.
- Yep.
You two, you've got nine minutes.
Get as far away from here as you can.
- No.
- Go, go!
Lucius, this way.
Yes, of course, I know how,
but what is with all the hoo-ha?
- What is the rush here?
- Just do it.
What do I get if I do it?
You get to live.
Fair enough.
Security systems deactivated.
You any good at defusing bombs?
I don't know yet.
You?
Two minutes to detonation.
Oh, my.
Got any ideas?
You got a knife?
No.
We're on approach to Arkham
for patient evacuation.
We need that bomb squad ASAP.
What now?
You're asking me?
How about we just
pull all this stuff off,
see what happens?
There's no cut-off program.
Maybe there's no tamper-proofing
program?
Yeah.
No.
Water.
- Need water.
- Water.
What's going on? Hello?
25 seconds.
15 seconds.
Please.
I need water.
Water?
Hello?
Hello? Guys!
What's going on?
Hello?
Where are my people?
You don't understand.
We have to find my people.
There will be,
there will be consequences.
You heroic son of a bitch.
A nuclear bomb, huh?
You'll never guess what took us
so long.
Problem.
Whatever was down there,
whoever was down there in Indian Hill
they're not there anymore.
Couple of squad cars are in pursuit
of a bus
that left the Indian Hill's compound.
That's gotta be them.
That bus cannot get away.
This is Unit 12 in pursuit
of the Arkham bus
heading south along the D-line.
Granting you aid, Unit 12.
Gonna take him at the next block.
Get ready.
Don't have a lot of space here.
Civilian traffic ahead.
It's blocked in.
Hold them at the cross street.
Nothing. I'll check up ahead.
Car 32 to Captain Bullock,
heading east toward Pittsburg.
Damn. Damn. What's on the bus, Jim?
Tell me what's on the bus.
Monsters.
Come on. Monsters?
Hugo Strange would rather destroy
half the city than let them out
and now they're out.
Code red. Code red, all units.
Pittsburg Highway.
All units be on the lookout for
Indian Hill bus on Pittsburg Highway.
Captain Bullock,
I've got eyes on the bus
under the south Burnside Expressway.
Well then, stop the damn thing.
Don't let it get away.
Come to mama.
Professor Strange!
Come out.
Strange, we need to talk.
You did a very bad thing to me
and now you're going to pay.
Impossible.
Nothing
is impossible.
Holy...
- Let's go.
- Let's do this.
No.
This city is in deep trouble
if we don't find that bus.
So let's find it.
- Yes, sir.
I want squadrons of 20
in these quadrants here.
I want choppers in the air.
And I want tac units
on all the east side bridges.
Bruce.
I have to go.
I might not see you for a while,
but I'll try to stay in touch.
Where are you going?
I have to find Lee.
Right move, mate.
Do me a favor
say goodbye to Bullock for me?
I don't really want
the whole Celtic farewell.
He's gonna have his hands full.
But I think he can handle it.
Will do.
Chocolates.
Girls like chocolates.
I'll keep that in mind.
There's a man
who's got his priorities straight.
The love of a good woman
and all that.
Well,
I hope you learned your lesson,
Master Bruce.
And that's the end of your adventures
with the police, eh?
There's a secret council, Alfred.
A council that runs everything
in Gotham.
Oh, bloody hell.
It's them that wanted me dead.
We're so close, Alfred.
We're so close to the ultimate truth.
Oh, bloody hell.
Hey, don't look at me.
Right.
Jim, hey!
Hey, where you going?
Hey.
We got monsters to find.
And you'll find them. I have to go.
But the city is in danger.
You got this. I know you do.
And I have more important things
to do.
- And, Harvey.
- But... Yeah?
You're the boss now.
Maybe get a haircut?
That's my car.
That's, that's my car.
Hey, Jim!
Help.
Oh, those poor souls.
Hello?
Thank you.