- Previously on "Gotham"...
- We will bust Penguin one day,
I promise you.
Harvey, we cannot let this slide.
You find someone
with the license, they walk.
Ms. Falcone, I need
to know that you are not
on some fool's errand to
rebuild your father's empire.
An example needs to be made.
SOFIA: You may think
you have everything,
but there is one thing you don't have:
the Falcone name.
GORDON: Was that your plan?
Get close to Penguin.
Gain his confidence. What then?
NYGMA: I used to be smart, brilliant,
and now that's gone.
MAN: Never seen nothing like him before.
(roaring)
Who are you?
MAN (on recording): Solomon Grundy.
You... know... Grundy?
We're the very best of friends.
NYGMA: With your muscles,
we can make money.
- We'd like to put our hat in the ring.
- Go get the doc.
(indistinct shouting)
MAN: Come on!
(grunting)
(indistinct, overlapping shouting)
(audience groaning)
Hey!
(audience cheering)
(bones crack, man grunts)
Good as new.
Dr. Lee Thompkins.
Oh... my. (laughing)
Now, what is a girl like you
doing in a place like this?
I heard a rumor you were frozen.
Should've known
it was too good to be true.
Oh, you're not still mad at me, are you?
Mad at you for what?
Killing Kristen Kringle?
Or framing Jim for murder
so he would be in prison
when I lost our child? No.
I'm over all that.
Let's be friends.
I'm sensing sarcasm.
(pours drink) Just as sharp as ever.
Actually, funny that you mention that.
Good-bye, Ed.
- Wait.
- (groans)
Holy hell.
Butch Gilzean?
What have you done to him?
Nothing, believe it or not.
And he goes by "Grundy" now.
Hey, why don't you hang
over there, big fella?
Make sure that wall doesn't wander off.
(growls): Mm.
I have no idea what happened to him,
but he's freakishly strong,
can't remember anything
about his past life,
and he seems to love me,
so, big improvement.
But, I, on the other hand...
I'm, uh... I'm really hoping
to get back to who I was.
When I was on ice, my head
got a little... scrambled.
Why should I care?
Okay, I came here with Grundy,
gonna fight, make some money
to get me smart again.
But... you...
Dr. Leslie Thompkins...
you can fix me.
You want me to fix you?
Oh, you really are dumb.
Okay, okay.
You're here for some reason.
I don't pretend
to know what that is, but...
if you help me,
I will help you.
I know you're not
really smart right now,
so just try to understand this.
I will never help you.
- I was raised to be a gentleman.
- (thunder rumbles)
SOFIA: But you're also practical.
We were seen at dinner, as we
have been the past three nights.
All of Gotham knows you have the
support of the Falcone family.
And I'm fairly certain
no one's watching us now.
I...
(thunder rumbles)
I just... I just like
to know where I stand.
This isn't easy for me.
To have someone I can trust.
A real friend.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
You can trust me.
Let's have lunch tomorrow, just us.
Till then.
(door opens, rain falling)
(door closes)
Have a nice dinner?
How long have you been here?
Long enough.
It's time you tell me
what you're planning.
This again?
Ever since you've come to Gotham,
all you've done is make Oswald stronger.
- (drink pouring)
- It's time I know your end game.
And if I refuse?
I'll put you on a train home.
I want to make you a promise.
In a matter of days,
I'll have Cobblepot
in the palm of my hand.
If I fail, I'll stay, I'll go,
whatever you want.
(distant sirens, rolling thunder)
Look, the count's good.
Oh, now, go on. Get out of here.
- I'll see you next month.
- Yeah.
(growling)
Someone down there?
(low, rolling thunder)
(door creaks open)
(mewing)
(chuckles)
Freakin' cats.
(mewing)
MALE VOICE: Oink. Oink.
What the...?
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com
(indistinct radio chatter, siren blaring)
Hey.
It really one of ours?
Seems so. He was in the uniform,
but the killer took his badge.
No one recognizes him?
Well, that part
we have not figured out yet.
Let me show you.
(camera snapping)
Good God.
Freaky, huh?
Let's find out who this guy is.
(distant siren blaring)
Here we go.
Dave Metzger. You know him?
Seen him around.
Not to speak ill of the dead,
but he was a grade A bastard.
- He have enemies on the force?
- No. No cop would do this
to another cop, but he was the candyman.
Penguin's bagman. He was
the one delivering
payoffs to cops in the precinct.
- I mean, that-that's the rumor.
- Yeah.
So someone killed him to send a message.
(helicopter passing overhead)
- Where you going?
- To see Penguin.
Maybe he knows why someone
wanted to kill his employee.
Don't go stirring the pot!
Enjoy your lunch, Mr. Cobblepot.
I need to talk to you.
If it takes less than three
minutes, I'm all ears.
A cop was murdered last night.
Dave Metzger?
A bagman on your payroll.
Oh, and you think I
might know something.
Well, sadly, this is the
first I'm hearing his name.
A general does not need
to know every foot soldier.
You don't need to know him.
I think someone is trying
to send you a message.
What sort of message?
The killer placed a severed
pig's head over Metzger's own.
Not a very clear message.
Could have all sorts of meanings.
Metzger may have been dirty,
but he was still a cop.
Someone killed him and is using
his death to make a point.
If that is in relation
to you, I need to know.
(laughs)
Jim, if someone had a problem with me,
I would know about it,
and I would deal with it.
I guess you're always
one step ahead, Oswald.
It's why I'm alive.
But I would like to help.
- Mr. Penn!
- Right here, Mr. Cobblepot.
Do we have anything that
could assist Detective Gordon
in doing his job?
As a matter of fact, sir,
a few days ago,
Mr. Wally Clarke applied
for a burglary permit.
The Pork Barrel.
It's a butcher on Third Street.
They specialize in offering
- the whole...
- Thanks... for the lead.
Enjoy your lunch, Oswald.
- (sniffs)
- Don't thank me, Jim.
Thank the licensing
system you hate so much.
Now, be sure to let me know if
I need to get more involved.
Till then, I'm rooting for you, Jim!
(opera plays with man singing
in foreign language)
(man sings along with recording)
(singing continues)
(man on recording holding final note)
(man on recording laughs)
Ah, have a seat, Wally.
You know how much trouble you're in? Huh?
You know what we do to cop killers?
- Just told him, I didn't kill nobody,
- (handcuffs tighten)
specifically not no cop.
Oh, so you didn't lure
Dave Metzger into that alley,
split open his skull,
and stick a pig's head on him?!
(laughing): What?! Are you crazy?
It's funny, because we
searched the Dumpster
behind your apartment.
Guess what we found.
BULLOCK: Whoa-ho!
Look at that. Porky don't have no head.
GORDON: What do you want to bet
that head was on the dead cop we found?
BULLOCK: Screw it!
I have enough.
I don't need a confession.
I'm charging you
with the murder of Dave Metzger!
Wait! No. It wasn't me.
It must have been the Prof.
Who?
The Professor. That's what I called him
because he-he talked all fancy.
He was the one who got
me to rob the butcher's.
We need a name, a description.
We did it all over the phone.
The whole deal.
I-I dropped the heads under
the Midtown Bridge.
The money was there.
I never met the guy,
never got no name.
What do you mean, "heads"?
As in more than one?
How many did this guy want?
It was... there was four.
You'd think he could've told me
that he only needed the heads.
But, no, I had to drag 'em
to my house, chop the heads...
Hey, shut up!
You know what this means?
Yeah. It means there's
three more victims out there.
How many bagmen did
Penguin have on the GCPD?
Wild guess, I'd say four.
The only one I knew was Metzger.
Yeah, well, the people who
got paid by those bagmen,
they'll know who they are.
They're not gonna talk.
We'll make 'em.
Hey! Don't leave me back
here with this thing!
Hey!
(chains rattle)
♪ ♪
♪ I found out... ♪
She's not coming.
- What?
- Sofia.
Your lunch date.
It's not a date.
Whatever.
She called.
She's not coming.
Did she say why?
Something came up. I don't know.
I wasn't listening.
- ♪ And I knew ♪
(bread crunches)
It's just gonna go to waste.
♪ Only you... ♪
I want you to follow her.
Find out who she's with.
You think she's two-timing you?
She and I are not...
♪ Lover boy... ♪
(exhales)
This lunch was her idea.
Now she cancels all of a sudden?
I want to know why.
That's all.
♪ So attentive ♪
♪ Not like other guys... ♪
Now, Victor!
(cheering and applause)
Today, we have ourselves a treat.
Our beloved Hammer
will take on a new challenger.
Just in from...
Grundy come from swamp.
(audience laughs)
CHERRY: Rules are simple.
Last man standing wins.
Besides that,
anything goes!
(cheering, whooping)
(whoops loudly)
WOMAN: Yeah!
- Fight!
- (cheering)
- (grunting)
- (crowd gasping)
(shouts)
(cheering)
(laughs)
What are you doing?! Fight!
Grundy fight now?
Yes! Now!
(shouts)
- (audience gasping)
- (grunting)
(audience cheering)
(gasping, cheering)
AUDIENCE:
Grundy! Grundy! Grundy! Grundy!
Grundy! Grundy! Grundy!
Grundy! Grundy!
NYGMA: Yes!
Yes! Yes!
Grundy Ed's best friend! (laughs)
AUDIENCE:
Grundy! Grundy! Grundy! Grundy!
Looks like I got a new cash cow.
Take good care of him, Doc.
And clean up what's left of Hammer.
BULLOCK: We're not looking
to bust nobody.
We just want the name of the bagman.
Who delivers Penguin's money?
Don't know what
you're talking about, man.
- Wish I could help.
- Oh, yeah?
Hey, hey. Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa. Relax.
I know a couple
of other guys we can talk to
who aren't such douche nozzles.
OFFICER: Seems like
you should be looking
for whoever killed Dave Metzger,
instead of shaking down other cops.
We're trying to save other cops.
More lives are on the line here.
Or you're using a cop getting killed
to go on a fishing expedition.
(sniffs) Smells like I.A. to me.
Hey. (grunts)
Hold on! Hey, hey!
Just say you're not helping.
We get it, okay?
Get off me.
BULLOCK: We're trying to stop
cops from getting killed.
How can none of you nitwits see that?
You're asking a cop to
snitch on another cop.
It ain't gonna happen.
- (chuckles)
- Fine.
We'll do it your way.
Yeah, yeah.
(groaning)
Come on. Geez!
- (detective groans)
- (whoops)
- Gonna be a hot one today, huh?
- Oh, yeah.
(grunts) It's got to be 90 out here.
A lot hotter in there. Probably 100.
DETECTIVE: Let me out, you bastards!
You know what, Jim,
I think we forgot to get lunch.
Think we got time?
I could go for a burger.
All right, Culpepper!
We're gonna be back in a couple hours.
Bullock! Let me out!
- (thumping)
- I'm warning you!
Bullock! Bullock?
Bullock!
Okay! (pounding)
(panting)
Chris Whitlock.
Makes deliveries for the West Side.
- But don't say I told you.
- Where can we find him?
He's supposed to be in court all day.
BULLOCK: My contact
on the South Side said
their bagman's Jenny Butler.
Trying to reach her.
GORDON: Good. I just want
to find this guy Whitlock,
hope he gives us the last name.
Should be getting out of court soon.
You ever think you'd be running around,
trying to save cops
on Penguin's payroll?
Bad cops. They deserve to be prosecuted
and stripped of their
badges, not butchered.
(woman screaming)
WOMAN: Call the police! (screaming)
(indistinct police radio chatter)
Hundred thousand people
in a square mile,
and, of course, nobody saw nothing.
Or is willing to admit it.
(siren wailing)
Butler got off duty last night.
Not seen since she clocked out.
Whitlock was due in court at 9:00.
Never showed.
So, they were both abducted,
taken somewhere, killed,
then brought to pose
in front of this building.
- Probably for us to find.
- That's a hell of a lot of work.
The killer believes
his message is important.
What, that he's got to rid
the city of dirty cops?
Specifically, the ones
who work for Penguin.
No wonder these guys look on edge.
Where are we on our fourth bagman?
- We need an I.D.
- I'm working on it.
(saxophone playing nearby)
(saxophone resumes playing)
Good afternoon, sir.
Sir.
Detective James Gordon.
GCPD.
You been playing here all morning?
On and off, you know?
Guy's got to take a break
every now and then.
Yeah, sure.
You see anything?
Anything out of the usual?
Sorry, uh, Detective,
I ain't seen nothing since the war.
- Right.
- All right. Have a good one.
- Yeah.
♪ ♪
(keys jangle)
(clicks tongue) Aw, man.
Aw, man. Really?
Let's try this again.
Did you see anything?
An old van.
"Filippelli Plumbing" on the side.
Parked up the street
a good part of the morning.
Guy just sitting there.
Guy? What'd he look like?
White dude.
Didn't see his face.
I took a break.
I came back. The van was gone.
All right, thanks.
Keep the tip.
(stapling)
What happened to you, Butch?
Grundy.
Look at your hand.
It grew back.
How is that even possible?
Look at this.
It's not even blood.
It's like swamp water.
Grundy from swamp.
Yeah. I heard.
You know, you don't
even have a heartbeat.
But you seem to be doing okay.
You know,
Ed is not your friend.
He's just using you.
No.
Ed Grundy friend.
Ed Grundy best friend.
He just wants you to fight
so he can make money
and make his brain better again.
Once he doesn't need you anymore,
he's just gonna discard you or kill you.
If that's even possible.
Do you understand?
Ed Grundy best friend.
NYGMA: That's right.
Best buddies.
A-Team.
- (grunting)
- Ow.
Not to mention,
your boss' biggest new attraction.
Smells like we're sticking
around for a while.
Fabulous.
Unless, of course,
you were to fix the broken
connection in this noodle,
then we wouldn't have to stick around.
We'd be...
- Gone? That's the word you're looking for?
- Yes, thank you.
- Yeah.
And, of course, I'd pay you.
(sighs) I'm patching up Grundy
as long as Cherry tells me to.
That's it.
Keep your money.
CHERRY: How's my best new fighter?
He gonna be ready
to go again tonight, Doc?
Yeah, sure.
I got to step out for a while.
I'll be back.
Just make sure you're here.
We got a deal, you know?
Yeah. I know.
(door opens)
(door shuts)
Hi, everyone.
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
I'll be right with you, okay?
(woman coughing)
All right, you can come on in.
Okay, have a seat right there.
I'll help you up. One, two, three, up.
(quietly): All right.
♪ ♪
THOMPKINS: Let's have a listen.
(chuckling)
(camera shutter clicks)
(clicking)
Sofia Falcone.
What are you doing?
- (ship's horn blowing)
- BULLOCK: Yeah.
All right. That was the mayor's office.
Press has gotten wind.
Things are gonna heat up fast.
Then we catch him fast.
All the cops who haven't called in.
Hahn. Peterson.
King. Nakajima. Messengale.
Yeah. So, their precincts
are already looking for them,
but I say we take this list to Penguin,
- have him point to a name.
- No need.
Nakajima's the bagman.
How do you know?
Peterson and Messengale are
both hard-core Bible-thumpers.
That leaves three.
And I've heard Nakajima's dirty.
Units are already
on the way to his apartment,
same as the others.
I say we retrace his beat.
Concentrate our resources. Jim, hold on.
Doesn't something about this
feel weird to you?
Whoever set the trap for
Metzger knew where he'd be.
And the killer also knew Butler
and Whitlock's schedules.
Are you saying it's one of our own?
Someone who's fed up with the
corruption, decided to make a stand.
But to kill them,
- display their bodies that way...
- I know,
brother, but it's something
we at least have to consider.
Which means anything that we
say out there... (knocking)
Got a lead on the plumbing van
your blind man saw.
Spotted near the abandoned dairy
on Commerce.
Should I get the Strike Force?
No, Gordon and I'll cover it.
If we need backup, I'll give you a call.
And until then, don't say a word.
And that's an order. You got it?
Let's go.
Come on.
(engine turns off)
(slow footsteps approaching)
(hinges squeaking)
(panting)
Oink, oink...
little piggy.
(man roaring)
♪ ♪
(roaring continues, crowd shouting)
(roars)
(indistinct shouts)
(growling)
(grunting)
(strained grunting)
(crowd shouting)
(groaning)
(cheering, whistling)
Our... new...
champion!
(cheering, shouting, whooping)
CROWD (chanting): Grundy! Grundy!
Grundy! Grundy! Grundy!
ZSASZ: So, it turns out Sofia
broke her date with you...
It was not a date!
...to have lunch with the mayor.
They went to Angelo's.
She had the lobster ravioli;
he had the tagliatelle.
After they parted ways,
Sofia went to the old
Gotham Heritage Hotel.
I don't understand... that place
has been vacant for years.
If I may? A couple months ago,
I'd gotten word
a secret buyer had purchased
the hotel at six percent
over asking.
I think it's safe to assume
that buyer was Ms. Falcone.
But... why?
ZSASZ: When she got there,
she met with this clown.
The zoning commissioner.
She'd have to have had his approval
for the wall and gate she built.
(chuckles quietly)
She's making alliances with politicians,
building a fortress.
All the while she's pretending
to be my friend...
she's been planning a war.
(whimpers)
(exhales)
(takes deep breath)
Victor, we will be having
a chat with Ms. Falcone.
Just so we're clear...
is this a chat-chat or a...
shovel-in-the-trunk
kind of chat?
Get the shovel.
(door opens)
(indistinct chatter)
Mmm, mmm.
I think I should rent an apartment
with all this money we're making.
Do you have any openings in your building?
You know, Ed, what you should
be doing with your winnings
is finding yourself
a neurologist, which I am not.
It has to be you. You know me, Lee.
You know what this coconut's
truly capable of.
Which is why my answer is no.
I know...
about your clinic.
I'm guessing that Cherry
lets you keep that as long
as you work these fights.
That's the deal that you have, right?
So?
So I'm guessing that
that means something to you,
which makes you vulnerable to...
to, um...
Blackmail?
- Yes.
- Threats?
Yes, both of those.
All right, so, let's hear it.
What's your brilliant scheme?
- What?
- You said you wanted
to force me to help you.
So what is your threat?
Hit me.
If you don't help me,
I am going to...
...do something to that...
- clinic.
- (sputtering laugh)
- Oh, my God, you really aren't smart.
- Oh!
(huffs)
(train whistle blowing in distance)
(door closes)
♪ ♪
(whispers): Jim.
(muffled grunting)
BULLOCK: Nakajima?
Hang tight, buddy, we're
gonna get you out of here.
(grunting, gasping)
(grunting)
Grenade!
Run...!
Harvey?
Detective James Gordon.
I hope you don't mind if I say
I'm tickled pink to meet you!
I would shake your hand...
if it were possible.
I'm a big fan.
Big, big fan.
Right. My biggest fan is a pig.
Tell me where Harvey Bullock is.
(groans): Oh.
That dirty pig.
Why do you waste your time with him?
He's holding you back.
Or can you not see that?
Oh. Never you fret.
He's still alive.
For the time being, anyway.
But you, Detective, you...
you are safe as safe can be.
You a cop?
(laughing, snorting)
What?
What makes you think that?
The things you knew...
the routes and schedules
of the cops you killed.
If...
I were a policeman,
you could what?
Reason with me? Hmm?
Appeal to what we have in common?
(chuckles)
Well, Jim...
may I call you Jim?
Jim,
that's exactly what I was going to do.
We have nothing in common.
Oh.
I beg to differ, mon frère.
You and I both see all too well
the corruption,
the filth...
inside the GCPD.
You and I know
that Gotham cannot survive
unless the cancer is cut out.
We both share the same mission.
Only I do it
with a little bit more flair.
Killing Penguin's bagmen
won't change anything.
But it will for them.
It will quite a bit.
But in the larger scope, you're right.
Which is why...
it doesn't stop there.
Not until I've butchered
every single swine
on Penguin's payroll.
That could be half the department.
I never said it would be pretty.
Oh, it's the same old story.
No one wants to see
how the sausage is made,
but once it is made... (chomping) Mmm.
Isn't it delicious?
Bite?
You're delusional.
You're not doing this for
Gotham, you're doing it
for your own demented reasons.
My reasons...
are as real as they come, Jim.
I have suffered profound loss
at the hands of
the greedy pigs in power.
Profound.
Then tell me.
Let me help make it
right without all this.
BULLOCK: Jim!
Oops. Got to go.
BULLOCK: Jim, where are you?!
Never you fear, Detective.
You and I,
we'll meet anon.
Don't you touch him!
Harvey!
BULLOCK: Jim!
Backup's coming!
Harvey!
You heard Gordon, you freak.
Backup's on the way.
You got one chance to run.
Lies from a liar.
They would have been here by now.
Besides, we both know, Captain Bullock,
- you deserve this.
- (Gordon screams)
(groans)
GORDON: Harvey!
Ooh, I do hate to cut and run.
(Bullock grunts)
- Oopsy-daisy.
- Hold on, partner.
(choking)
Hold on, buddy. Hold on.
You're gonna be all right.
- Jim.
- You're gonna be all right.
- I promise you.
- (approaching sirens wailing)
You're gonna be all right.
Hold on. Hold on, buddy.
- Hold on, pal.
- (sirens wailing)
(coughing)
I can't miss any more work.
- They'll fire me.
- It's okay.
I'm gonna put you on
strong antibiotics, okay?
(woman coughs)
Come on.
(baby crying)
Oswald.
I didn't know you were coming over.
I thought I'd surprise you.
I'm sorry I had to cancel
our lunch yesterday.
It was unavoidable.
You have to let me make it up to you.
How about now?
I was actually on my way out.
Oh. Hmm. Where to?
This is going to sound strange,
but I can't tell you.
Not yet. I-I want it to be a surprise.
The thing is...
...cat's out of the bag.
I don't understand.
I know what you're doing!
The old Heritage Hotel.
The fortress from which
you're going to attack me.
What? No.
Oh. Oh, so you weren't
pretending to be my friend
while building your power base?
(laughing)
I should have known.
But, you know,
your father's blood definitely
runs through your veins.
Luckily, not for long.
Oswald, you're making a mistake.
I'm your friend.
We'll see, won't we?
Now, let's go see what you're building.
I can't wait!
(indistinct chatter)
Barkeep, another grasshopper.
Those won't help.
- All right, give me your money.
- What?
The money you made...
well, that he made...
give it to me.
I don't make any promises,
but I'll see what I can do.
Lee. Lee.
I just got to know.
Why did you change your mind?
Is it my charisma?
Close.
You asked what I was doing
in a place like this.
I don't want to be here.
I don't want to be anywhere near Gotham.
I left.
But I couldn't stay away
because of the Tetch virus.
It hit the Narrows
harder than anywhere else.
So?
So? It was my fault.
Jim tried to stop the
virus and I didn't let him.
I was infected, but nonetheless,
I was there.
I don't have a choice.
I have to be here.
Wow.
If you wanted to
blackmail me, by the way,
what you should have
done was taken advantage
of Grundy being popular,
threatened to take him away,
and then Cherry, afraid
of losing her star,
would have forced me to help you.
Come by the clinic tomorrow.
We'll get started.
Hi, pretty lady.
Ed's gonna be smart again.
Ed's gonna be smart?
Ed's gonna be very smart.
Hey.
It's okay, Charlie.
Oswald.
I want you to know I forgive you.
(children yelling and laughing)
ZSASZ: Uh, boss.
OSWALD: What is this?
What's happening?
(chuckles) Kids.
You started an orphanage?
I wanted to surprise you next week
when everything was finished.
I...
- I...
- WOMAN: Children. Back inside, please!
Oswald, I want you to know
I understand the pressure you face.
Your very survival
depends on seeing everyone
as a potential threat.
And I watched my father
bear that weight for years.
I don't want you to end up like him.
Sofia, please forgive me.
How can I?
(chuckles) When I've
already forgiven you?
But you do owe me one thing.
Anything.
Lunch.
How do you feel about mac and cheese?
I love it.
(train whistle blows)
(monitor beeping rhythmically)
GORDON: Hey.
Hey.
(exhaling): You gave me
quite the scare back there.
How are you feeling?
I've had better days.
Doc says you're gonna be okay.
That shows what he knows.
Pyg?
Son of a bitch.
He could have killed me,
but he cut me just deep enough
to make you choose to go after him
or save my worthless hide.
It wasn't a choice.
Either way, I owe you.
So pay it back now.
Tell me the truth.
How long you been taking money
from Penguin?
You knew Metzger was the bagman.
You knew Nakajima was dirty.
The Pyg says all this stuff
about you deserving to be killed.
I don't know why I didn't see it before.
Maybe I didn't want to.
I just need to know how long.
We talking years?
No.
Just since this license crap started.
The commissioner ordered us to comply.
Then Metzger started showing up
with these envelopes
stuffed full of cash.
I didn't do nothing I
wouldn't have done anyway.
You got to understand, Jim.
The bills I got, the debts I got.
It stops.
It stops now.
(sniffles)
TV REPORTER:
...has the city on high alert.
Gotham finds itself gripped by terror
at the hands of a
ritualistic cop killer,
being called Professor Pyg.
He is still at large
after evading the police.
The GCPD are urging people
to remain calm
and to report any suspicious activity
to GCPD's Central Command.
(crickets chirping)
PYG: Two mother pigs
lived in a pen.
They each had four piglets.
And that made ten.
All the piglets loved to play.
And they rolled and they rolled
in the mud, all day.
At night,
with their mothers,
crawled up in a heap,
they screamed and they screamed
until they went...
to sleep.
And sleep well for tomorrow
the ***.
Synced & corrected by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com
Watch all episodes for free on
www.FlixTor.to