Previously on Gotham...
Mooney: Killing falcone
would only create chaos.
I need to siphon his strength.
So, when the time is right,
Taking over his organization
Will be like
slipping on a glove.
I'm so angry all the time.
Will that ever go away?
Alfred, can you teach me
how to fight?
You've been
through a lot.
I'm scared, jim.
Everywhere I go,
I can feel that monster, zsasz.
Alvarez: Gordon,
some unis brought in a perp.
Claims to know you.
Hey, detective.
Miss me?
Barbara?
Whoa.
Sweet crib.
You must be one rich cop.
It's my girlfriend's place.
Where is she?
I don't know.
Barbara?
So... What?
I get to stay here alone?
I'm hungry.
Barbara:
Dear jim,
I thought I could be strong
and brave for you, but I can't.
Every place I go,
I see falcone and zsasz.
I'm nervous and needy
and screwed up,
And I know that's not
what you need or want,
So I'm going away for a while,
to get myself together.
(cell phone ringing)
This is gordon.
Uh... Uh, right.
Yeah.
We're in the penthouse.
Come on up.
Sounds like your girlfriend's
not coming back, huh?
Why's she worried
about falcone?
None of your business.
So what happens now?
You gonna get the charges
against me dropped?
I will, but you're my only
witness to the wayne murders.
You gonna cuff me
to a drainpipe again?
No, I'm not gonna hold you
against your will.
GCPD, juvie...
you'd just break out.
So I do get to stay here.
No, I have someplace
else in mind.
(knocking on door)
That's the sketch artist.
I need you to describe
the man who shot the waynes.
Wait, where am I going to stay?
Wayne manor.
Do not speak
to the inmate.
Do not touch the inmate unless
in the service of your job.
Do not accept anything from the
inmate under any circumstances.
Who is this guy,
anyway?
Name's ian hargrove,
some genius bomb maker.
Took out over a dozen buildings
in and around gotham.
He's the one that blew up
the commissary last month?
Yeah, and he did it
with match shavings
And apple cider vinegar.
So no mistakes today, got it?
Put your hands up.
(latch slides, clicks)
She said this is the man
who killed your parents.
She said she saw his face.
Do you recognize him,
bruce?
No.
What's her name?
Selina kyle.
Do you believe her?
Yes, I do.
So, she saw...
Everything?
And you want her to live here
with us, do you?
A common street criminal.
She's hardly older than bruce.
She's just a kid
who's seen too much.
This is for her safety.
GCPD is full of moles...
Right, and how long would you
have us put her up, then?
I don't know.
No.
The answer is no.
Her being here will put
master bruce in great danger.
Alfred.
She is the witness
to a murder, master bruce.
You do understand that,
don't you?
She's also
the best chance we have
Of finding
who killed my parents.
Isn't she?
Yes, she is.
Then she can stay.
As long as it takes.
I've made my decision.
Yes, master bruce.
Look, I know this is a lot.
But I'm doing
everything I can.
Montoya and allen
and I are meeting
With an ada they trust
this afternoon.
Oh...
A trustworthy lawyer.
In gotham.
Look, if we find this guy,
we'll need her.
She'll have to testify.
Go before a judge.
It won't be easy.
Witnesses back
out all the time.
The ones that stick it out do so
Because they care
about the victims.
We'll do our best to be nice
to her, then, won't we?
It's from the chinese
ming dynasty.
Five...
500 years old.
You can get one just like it
for five bucks, in chinatown.
I'm bruce wayne.
Selina kyle.
People call me cat.
Nice to meet you, cat.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
What's in your hand?
I said, what's in...
What the hell...?
(tires screeching,
horn honking)
Hargrove!
Ian hargrove, time to go.
Man:
Kid, you screwed up, big-time.
But you're still young,
you deserve a second chance.
So I have a
bet for you.
You call heads
or tails.
You lose, you go to jail.
You win, we let you go.
Bet.
Hold on.
There's a catch.
You have to make a promise
to god right now.
If you win, you're gonna
take this as a sign from him
Telling you that you need
to go back to school
And get your
life straight.
Can you promise that?
Do you promise that?
Yes, sir.
Okay then.
Call.
Heads.
Walk away, kid.
Somebody up there loves you.
Hey, harvey.
Go.
Remember your promise.
Jim gordon, GCPD.
I hear good things
about you, counselor.
Harvey dent, likewise
about you, detective.
That was some trick
with the coin.
What if the kid guesses wrong?
You gonna send him to jail?
Teenagers, they nearly
always call heads.
I don't know why.
Two-headed coin.
Whatever works, right?
Dent:
So who is he, jim?
Who really killed the waynes?
This is what we have.
No I.D.
But this is from an eyewitness?
That you have in safe custody.
It's not nearly enough
to go to the law with.
Even if we had I.D. On this guy,
It's the people who hired him
we really want.
I agree.
Your eyewitness is useless
in a courtroom.
But the idea
of your witness
Could be immensely valuable.
Ever hear the name
dick lovecraft?
Sure. Billionaire.
Property, construction,
chemicals.
And as corrupt
as they come.
Falcone, maroni,
even wayne enterprises,
Lovecraft has dealings
with all of them.
Since the waynes' deaths,
he's doubled his fortune.
Including a huge piece
of the arkham deal.
Dent: Lovecraft had a long
feud with thomas wayne
Over deals
and politics.
They couldn't have had a more
different vision for gotham.
I'm willing to bet my career...
On his involvement
in the wayne murders.
That's a big bet.
I want to use your witness
To go after lovecraft.
How? My witness can't connect
lovecraft to the perp.
Lovecraft doesn't know that.
I'll let it leak out
That we have a
secret eyewitness
Who's going to blow
the case wide open
And connect lovecraft
to the wayne killings.
Lovecraft will get very nervous.
And the people around
him will get nervous.
And that's when people start
talking; you know how that goes.
Unless lovecraft wasn't involved
in the wayne murders.
If so, which I doubt,
we still win.
Whoever was involved
in the wayne killings
Will get their
cage rattled
Like the dickens, won't they?
I bet he makes a move.
You like to bet a lot.
Well, what do we got to lose?
My witness becomes a target.
No.
That's the beauty of it.
We never actually file papers.
We never name names.
It's just a
powerful story.
Your witness is perfectly safe.
And you're on board with this?
We've been on board, jim.
Harvey's one of us.
I want what you want, jim.
I want to make this city
a better place.
No names.
Not mine, not my witness,
nothing... just a story.
Just a story.
All right.
Let's try something.
Hey, I thought I was gonna have
to work this case without you.
Where the hell have you been?
You know what?
On second thought, never mind,
I don't want to know.
What do we got?
A biggie.
Blackgate prisoner escaped
while in transit to st. Mark's
For psychiatric care.
His name's ian hargrove,
clinically insane,
With a compulsion for
blowing things up.
He exploded a bunch of
old buildings around gotham.
Last one,
two janitors were killed.
Says here he was busted out
by four gunmen?
Yeah, which is odd...
hargrove never used accomplices.
All right, so who did hargrove
spend time with at blackgate?
Who did he communicate with
on the outside?
His entire stretch,
he was isolated from gen pop.
Never made
or received phone calls.
Only one visitor
in those two years...
His brother john.
Got an address?
We do.
Unis are bringing him
in right now for questioning.
We're lucky you deigned
to show up.
Yeah, sorry.
No problem.
Girl trouble?
Yeah.
I told you.
Those high society dames...
get you all twisted.
Keep your guard up.
Knock lumps out of ya.
Watch your feet.
Right...
Jab, jab, right.
(grunting)
Lead with the...
Hey!
Jab, jab, right.
(grunting)
jab, jab, right.
Keep that guard up...
Lead...
Jab, jab, right.
Now keep that...
(grunts fiercely)
yes.
(laughing)
oi!
Sorry, alfred.
Hello.
Bruce.
That hurt.
Yeah, it's supposed to,
isn't it?
Taking a punch is
Just as important
as throwing one, master bruce.
What you doing?
Alfred's teaching
me to fight.
Why?
So I'll be prepared if
something bad happens.
Yeah, 'cause you live
in a pretty rough neighborhood.
Not here,
in gotham.
In gotham, people don't fight
with gloves on.
How's your room?
Everything good?
It'll do.
I'm hungry, though.
Right.
Well, breakfast was
served at 8:00, miss,
Which you slept through.
Lunch shall be
served at 12:00.
There's plenty to
eat in the kitchen.
And alfred will be happy
to fix you something.
No, he won't be, will he?
Because it's not
a bloody hotel.
Relax, old man.
I'll figure it out.
Yeah, you can mind
your manners as well,
You cheeky little minx.
Be nice to her, alfred,
she's our guest.
Well, I'm terribly sorry,
master bruce.
Didn't realize you fancied her.
What do you mean?
N-no.
Well, it's nothing
to be embarrassed about.
It's only natural, isn't it?
But you watch her.
She's a lairy one.
Right... Left, left, right.
(grunts)
keep your guard up, son.
You know about girls,
do you, alfred?
Fair sight more than you.
And she, mate,
Is trouble...
watch.
Oi! Oi, oi!
Liza, liza...
What are you up to?
(inhales deeply)
(inhaling)
(quiet laugh)
Lilacs.
♪ ♪
I'm telling you, I don't know
anything about his escape.
I haven't talked to him.
Your own baby brother
Busts out of prison,
and doesn't call you,
The only person he's
talked to in two years?
What happened?
You two have a falling out?
No, ian and I are close.
Always have been.
Even after he bombed
those janitors?
That was an accident.
Bullock:
That's what they all say.
John hargrove:
It's the truth.
(timer dings)
My brother's not a killer.
He never was.
He blew up 12 buildings
in gotham.
Yes, munitions factories
and their offices.
Places that made guns
and bullets and missiles.
I know he was wrong,
But ian thought that
what he was doing was good.
He didn't hurt a soul
until the last bombing.
And he felt terrible about it.
He practically handed himself in
to the cops and pleaded guilty.
Ian has had mental problems
ever since he was a kid.
My parents didn't
have the money
To get him the help he needed.
And he sure as hell wasn't
getting it at blackgate.
Look...
My brother's not a bad man.
Then what is he?
He's sick.
There's a difference.
Gordon: Okay...
So who would want
to bust him out?
I don't know.
But my brother
needs help.
You have to find him.
(door opens)
It's done.
I have a delivery
for you.
I'll take that.
Oh.
Who sent this, anyway?
Who cares?
Hmm.
(timer ticking)
Wait a second.
You hear that?
Sounds like ticking.
(timer dings)
(explosion booming,
men screaming)
Good morning.
Uh-huh.
How'd you sleep?
Your house makes noise.
It's old.
You didn't come here with much.
If you want, alfred can
buy you some clothes.
Pass.
Detective gordon told me
you live on the streets.
Yeah.
So?
What's it like?
Not as nice as here.
Do you live alone?
Are you going to ask me
questions all morning?
Aren't you supposed to be
in school or something?
I'm developing
my own curriculum.
It lets me move at my own speed
And focus on academic areas
that interest me.
Why?
You're a billionaire,
what's to learn?
That's a strange attitude.
So, where are your parents?
They alive?
Um...
Sure.
They're around.
Where?
What's that to you?
Nothing, I just thought...
Yeah, well, you thought wrong.
I'm not an orphan.
I got family all over.
This was bad enough when it
was just a prison escape.
Now we've got five
dead security guards,
And the press is calling
hargrove an urban terrorist.
Did you get anything
from the bombing site?
Bullock: Forensics is still
looking into it,
But the entire office
was destroyed.
Gordon:
Including all security footage.
Yeah.
We do know that hargrove
and his guys made off
With a compound
called hmx.
Gordon:
It's military grade.
Ten times more powerful
than c-4.
Nasty stuff.
Using explosives
To steal explosives.
What's that about?
Trading up?
He must have
another target in mind.
Some place difficult to crack.
You know what I'm gonna say.
So, go, do it.
(cell phone ringing)
This is gordon.
Alfred:
Yes, detective.
It's alfred.
Alfred, is everything all right?
Is selina okay?
Well, she's safe.
But?
But I'm afraid, detective,
this isn't gonna work out.
She's a... A tough nut,
this one.
Well, look, we need her help
If we have any chance
of catching the waynes' killer.
Just hold onto her for now,
and I'll be out to check on her
As soon as I can.
We shall patiently await
your arrival,
Detective.
Everything good?
Right as rain.
You sure you want to go
through with this?
Butch, don't you go getting
scared on me now.
Never, boss.
(door opens)
Oswald, you're back.
(chuckling)
I'm starting to think
you enjoy being hurt.
(chuckles)
I was passing by.
Thought I'd say hello.
Well, you said it.
Now why are you here?
Honestly, I'm just trying
to be friendly.
(inhales deeply)
(sighs with satisfaction)
Lilacs.
Mmm.
You smell good.
You don't.
(laughing)
Snappy as ever.
Oh! (chuckles)
Well, good-bye then.
Sorry you're still
grumpy with me.
But, you know,
Reaching out in friendship
is never wrong.
Man, that dude's creepy.
Forget him.
He's nothing.
Hargrove's contacts
and phone records
From before he went
to blackgate.
Uh-huh. Yeah.
You all right?
Yeah, yeah.
Barbara left.
Left left?
Yeah.
Where'd she go?
I don't know.
It's a ploy.
She wants you to set a date.
It's a standard move.
She'll be back.
Do you play video games?
Ed, don't ever
do that again.
My apologies, detective.
Do either of you
play video games?
I do, I...
(giggles)
I love video games.
I find that each one presents
a new challenge, a puzzle.
It's a lot like detective work
in that way.
Ed.
Oh, sorry.
Uh, I had a chance
to analyze the shrapnel
From the security office.
And I found something.
It's a nameplate.
It was damaged in the bombing,
But you can still
read the information.
It's from an abandoned
metal factory
Here in gotham.
That's really good work, ed.
Thanks.
Thank you, detective.
Let's go check this out.
GCPD!
Freeze!
Don't shoot!
You found the nameplate,
thank god.
Bullock:
Is anyone else here?
No, but they'll be back soon.
Please, you got to help me.
They broke me out of prison,
they kidnapped me, they told me
They'd kill my brother and his
family if I didn't help them.
Who's "they"?
Russians.
One of their names
is-is kasyanov.
They're planning something
against falcone.
Falcone?
Yeah.
It's a, it's a big job, a vault.
That's why they needed me
to build explosives.
(men shouting)
Behind you!
Get down, get down!
(man shouting)
(men shouting)
help me!
Bruce: If you want
to go somewhere,
We can call you a taxi.
You move quiet.
So do you.
Are you leaving?
Thinking about it.
I'm sorry if talking
about your family upset you.
I wasn't upset.
You seemed kind of upset.
That's your mom, huh?
She looks nice.
She was.
You saw her...
The night she was killed?
Uh-huh.
And you saw me?
What I did?
What I didn't do?
What are you talking about?
What could you have done?
I don't know... something.
You're dreaming, kid.
A gun's a gun.
My mom's in show business.
Oh?
Yeah.
She sings and dances
and does magic tricks.
Gets paid,
like, millions.
But that's just a cover.
Really, she's a secret agent
for the government.
Wow.
Yeah.
She's on a secret mission.
But when she's done,
she's coming back to get me.
That's good.
Yeah.
Did you ever kiss a girl?
No.
Do you want to?
Why-why do you ask?
Just curious.
Time for your studies,
master bruce.
Thank you, alfred.
You're more than welcome
to join, miss kyle.
Right.
I'll see you later.
Do you have any idea
how many angry phone calls
We've been
getting this week?
Got a terrorist
out there.
And that's our fault?
Jim!
No, no, please.
You tell me, detective...
How is this my fault?
Well, for starters,
You have the mentally ill
housed at blackgate,
A prison with
no facilities for them.
So, you send them
out for treatment,
Which was exactly where
Hargrove was headed
when he was broken out.
I want him found.
Yes, sir.
Today.
What is wrong with you?
By the way,
hargrove's brother john,
I went ahead and put him and his
family in protective custody.
That'll help.
Yeah, only problem is...
Hargrove doesn't know that.
All right, dent.
You dragged me
down here, now what?
I got the last piece
of the puzzle in place.
I'm bringing charges
against you.
Oh, that old song again?
You will never prove fraud.
You know that, and I know that.
Fraud charges are only
part of it.
Oh, really?
What, then? Jaywalking?
Conspiracy to commit
first-degree murder.
Murder?
So, tell me, dent...
Who did I kill?
Thomas and martha wayne.
(scoffs):
Oh, god...
I have an eyewitness who
can tie you to the crime,
You and all the
others involved.
That's absurd.
Help yourself
out here, dick.
Think about your options.
This is gonna get ugly.
(scoffing laugh)
You're a fool.
And you have no idea who or
what you're even dealing with.
Don't you ever
threaten me!
I will rip you open.
It was good to see you, dick.
Bullock:
Jim!
Got it.
Yeah?
Meet gregor kasyanov.
Long rap sheet.
Worked for nikolai
before he died.
Who does he work for now?
Beats me.
All right.
Hargrove said it's a big
job, right? A vault.
Somebody's got to
be bankrolling it.
Yeah, someone with cash
and pull and beef with falcone.
Problem is... in gotham,
Anyone with cash and pull
has beef with falcone.
Gordon:
Hmm.
So, who is it?
(mooney clicks tongue)
You kept me waiting.
Ran into a little trouble.
Nothing to worry about.
Good, I've got a lot
riding on this job.
You've said.
Mooney:
Your boss nikolai is dead
Because of falcone.
You want to get back at him,
You hit him where it hurts...
his money.
Ain't that right, butch?
Yep.
The root of all evil.
We'll take his money.
No problem.
As long as it's there,
like you said.
Oh, it's there.
I'm positive.
The truck you needed.
And gregor...
...Break a leg.
(water burbling)
(heart beating)
(heartbeat increases)
(selina scoffs)
You're the weirdest
kid I've ever met.
Why are you doing that?
Training.
Oh...
Like the boxing.
So, if anyone mugs you
with a diving board,
You'll be ready, huh?
Yes.
I mean, no.
I'm developing
self-discipline and willpower.
Why?
So I can be strong.
I get you, but it won't work.
Not on the streets,
not in gotham.
Why's that?
Out there on the streets,
It's not enough to be strong.
You gotta be mean.
Gotta be ruthless.
Do you know what ruthless means?
Of course I do.
Yeah?
Well, you ain't.
You're a nice kid.
Five minutes on the street,
you'll be mincemeat.
And holding your breath
won't do a damn thing.
Host: The subject of today's
category is numbers.
Here we go.
How many bones in the human arm?
Thirty-two.
Woman:
(bell dings)
Host:
Correct.
Next, how many elements
in the periodic table?
118.
Woman:
Uh... 118.
(bell dings)
Host:
Yes, again.
Now for a tough one.
How many eyes are there
on cards in a deck?
Forty-two.
Woman:
21.
(buzzer sounds)
Host:
No, I'm sorry.
The number you were
looking for is 42.
You forgot to double it
for two eyes.
(lively music playing)
(whoops, laughs)
Host: Well, that concludes
our show for today.
We'd like to thank
all the contestants
That participated here in studio
And those of you
playing along at home.
We'll be back right after this.
Bullock:
Okay, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What about the explosives?
It-it's a very
specific type.
It's highly volatile,
And it's very difficult
to manufacture.
It's for one use,
and one use only.
To penetrate iron.
Like a vault
in a bank.
Mm-mm, no, they're all steel.
No one makes anything
out of iron anymore.
Not for...
A hundred years, at least.
The gotham armory.
Yeah.
Yeah, they have
those iron vaults
They used to keep
the gunpowder in.
A few years ago,
A private investment
group bought it.
Ten to one,
falcone's behind it.
Hmm...? Do you...?
How much longer?
It's ready.
It didn't work.
(laughter echoing)
Hey, hey...
Promise me nobody else
is gonna get hurt.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sure, no problem.
Cross my heart.
You're surrounded!
(sirens approaching)
There's no way out!
(sirens whooping)
Drop your weapons!
Kasyanov:
Don't do it! Get back!
Hargrove!
Ian hargrove!
Your brother
and his family are safe.
We have them in
protective custody.
Kasyanov:
If he runs, shoot him!
Don't shoot!
Man: You shoot him,
they shoot us!
Drop your weapons!
(cell phone ringtone playing)
Get away from the truck!
Everybody down!
Why'd you do that?
Bet you can't hit me.
I could.
But why would I want to?
Try.
What for?
Hit me, and...
Hmm...
I'll let you kiss me.
Ha!
You didn't get me.
Ah, no!
Oh!
(laughing)
(bruce shouting playfully)
(cell phone ringing)
Gordon:
Morning, alfred.
Ah, detective.
I've been trying
to get out there.
I'm sorry, uh...
Is everything okay?
Is she behaving herself?
Well, uh, not really, no.
That's all right.
It is?
Yes, well, she's...
A breath of fresh air,
I might say.
Glad to hear it.
I'll be out there
as-as soon as I can.
Very good, sir.
(surprised gasp)
Oh...
Forgive me for the intrusion,
But it's urgent
that I speak with you.
(laughs)
You know who I am.
Yeah.
And falcone would kill you
if he knew you were here.
Perhaps.
What would he do if I told him
That you were spying
on him for fish mooney?
You don't have any proof.
No.
But suspicion,
it's a funny thing.
Hmm?
Falcone might not choose
to believe me at first,
But every time
he looked at you,
He'd ask himself... is she?
Could she?
Would she?
You're wrong.
He cares about me.
Let's call him and find out,
shall we?
(keypad beeping)
Stop!
Your secret is safe with me.
I won't tell,
Because you...
Are gonna keep working for fish.
And you are not going
to tell anyone.
Or you'll die.
Gordon:
Messages for gordon.
Thanks.
Jim.
You have a minute?
Uh, yeah.
I met with lovecraft.
How'd it go?
He was scared.
He's involved, all right.
Scared isn't proof.
You didn't see him.
Told the same story
in a few other spots.
All the big players
will know by now,
Someone will start talking.
If and when they do,
Neither of us makes a move
without talking first.
We move together on this.
Absolutely.
Hey, nice work
on the hargrove case.
You saved the poor
guy's life.
You're a regular saint.
Thanks.
Uh, we'll be talking
again soon, I hope.
You bet.
Thanks, counselor.
Finish up with hargrove?
Yeah.
He's on his way to arkham.
Arkham?
Mayor's directive.
He's taking all the criminally
insane inmates from blackgate,
Sending them to arkham,
So they can get
appropriate treatment.
That's nuts.
Appropriate tr...
The building's 200 years old.
Welcome to gotham.
Oh, and get this...
hargrove said that the bomb
That blew up the money
wasn't his.
Whose was it?
He didn't know.
How did it go?
Cops were everywhere.
Our guys had
no way out.
I had to make
the call.
Is everybody dead?
Gregor? All his men?
Every last one.
Good.
I can't stand loose strings.
You're not mad?
That's a hell of a lot
of money we just lost.
Mad?
I couldn't be happier.
The point wasn't to steal
that money, butch.
It was to hurt falcone.
Well, that you did, fish.
That you did.
Good afternoon, everyone.
Thank you all for coming.
As you well know,
The people of gotham
Have been shaken
by tragedy in recent days,
Tragedy no citizen
should have to endure.
What has happened these past
few days is a direct result
Of gotham's criminally
insane not getting
The appropriate treatment
and help that we owe them.
That is why I am moving
forward with plans
To turn the recently
renovated arkham asylum
Into a remedial facility...
All right, let's go,
here, man; let's go.
...For the criminally insane.
Gordon:
Barbara...
It's me.
I got your letter, and I, um...
I know you said you needed
some time away from gotham.
From me.
But I want you to come back.
I need you... To come back.
I don't have anything
without you.
And I love you.