Previously on Gotham...
The guys call him The Ogre.
He's a serial killer.
Whoever did this, he's a monster.
The blood of his next victim is on my hands!
If you don't drop it, that blood could be Lee's.
Because The Ogre retaliates against any cop who investigates
and kills the people they love.
The man who stabbed Alfred, he's in Gotham.
And you need my help to find him.
Who sent you?
You want me to tell Bunderslaw that you're onto him?
You look far from home.
Get away from him.
Or what?
Whatever.
Come on.
Did you go back?
Yeah. The cops are there.
And?
What do you think?
He fell out of a five-story window. He's dead.
Why'd you do it?
He told us what we wanted. He told us about Bunderslaw.
You didn't have to go and kill the guy!
Yes, I did! 'Cause the moment we'd left,
he was gonna go tell his boss!
Who works for you, by the way.
He's the one who tried to kill me,
who tried to kill your butler...
who probably killed your parents.
I saved your life.
Besides... you wanted to do it, too.
You just didn't have the guts.
- Wait...! - Just go home.
We still have to find out who Bunderslaw is and what he wants.
You mean you do.
You really think this is over?
He's gonna come after us.
So what's next?
His safe.
What?
Every senior executive at Wayne Enterprises
has a safe in their office.
A-Any secrets Bunderslaw has, that's where they'll be.
Key or combination?
Key. My dad had one.
He'll probably keep it on him, then.
Figure out a way to get me close, and I'll steal it.
Can you do that?
I think so.
And what happened tonight,
you tell no one.
Not your buddy Detective Gordon,
not your butler.
No one.
Punctures on test subject are consistent with those on the victim,
indicating the killer was right-handed.
Yum.
Where's Thompkins?
Detective Gordon, Dr. Thompkins said I was free
to use this room. She's very nice.
She's not like the old medical examiner.
Ed, just tell me where she is.
No riddles.
Home. She went home.
Hope you find her.
Jim?
Jim, is that you?
You're lucky I don't skin you.
Go on.
- I... slow down. - Lee, please.
Start over.
This case you caught, the dead woman,
she was murdered by a serial killer?
Yes. Who's killed a dozen women, maybe more.
And Loeb gave you this on purpose?
He wants to hurt me.
And how am I in danger?
He murders the loved ones of any cop
who investigates him.
It's how he's been able to get away with it so far.
Anyone who comes after him,
he's killed someone they love
and the investigation's been buried.
Bullock knows a cop--
came home and found his wife.
Her throat had been cut.
That's why Loeb gave me the case.
Either I give up, like everyone else...
and live, knowing I let a killer go free...
or I keep on,
and someone I love is killed.
You're not giving up, are you?
I can't.
That's why I need you to get out of Gotham right now.
Tonight.
No.
You want to protect me? Find him.
I'm gonna stay here and do my job.
But I do like that you think of me as a loved one.
I do.
Love you.
And it only took a serial killer to get you to say that.
- Thanks. - Yeah.
This is it.
Home sweet, you know.
This is a great space.
Selina?
Sort of a roommate.
She comes and goes.
Wayne Enterprises Charity Ball.
Didn't you know I'm a member of society?
I go every year.
Get my picture taken in a pretty dress.
Smile.
Aren't you scared of my being here?
Should I be?
Are you dangerous?
I don't know -- is your boyfriend gonna come home?
I never said I had a boyfriend.
I assumed a woman as beautiful as you...
You assumed I had a boyfriend
and you assumed I would be the kind of woman
who would cheat on him.
Well, I'm not.
And I don't have a boyfriend.
And if a bus hit me tomorrow,
no one would care.
That change things?
Yes, actually, it does.
Make it more illicit?
Or would there be less chance of us getting attached--
one night and done.
Only that would happen anyway.
Because once you saw the real me,
you would run screaming, like everyone else.
I have to say, you're not who I imagined you'd be.
Surprise.
You can let yourself out.
*Love, love*
*Love...*
But you promised to dance with me.
And I will.
But first I have to finish with that gentleman.
Who knew running a nightclub was so much work?
My poor darling.
As I was saying,
you and your crew are the best gun and knife men in the city.
Your hit on Councilman Klein--
a thing of beauty.
- And I'm a fan, so... - Cheers.
What do you want?
For you to help me kill Don Maroni
and all of his lieutenants.
You're having a laugh.
I'm fairly certain I'm not.
And Falcone's good with this?
He will be.
When it's done.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
So you like being number two.
Falcone gives Victor Zsasz first dibs on every new contract.
You bring him the bullet-riddled corpse of his enemy
and all of that will change.
This is your chance to move up.
You're a mad fella, aren't ya?
Fair enough.
Come by the bar tomorrow.
We'll talk details.
What's this about, Harvey?
Have a seat.
This is my partner Jim Gordon.
Detective.
Eight years ago, you investigated the murder
of a woman named Julie Kemble.
- That was a long time ago. - It was the Ogre.
Julie Kemble was his first victim.
But you dropped the investigation,
and because of that,
11 more women have been murdered.
Seriously, guys, you know...
Stop.
We also know the Ogre
kills the loved ones of the cops that hunt him down.
That pattern started with you.
We think you found something that spooked him.
Your notes from the investigation.
The last page,
something's been scratched out.
I want to know what.
He killed my wife.
I still got a daughter, Harvey.
Beth Tudor.
Katherine Wood.
Jessica Parker.
11 women.
Each one was someone's daughter.
It has to stop.
Yeah. I was doing background on the dead girl.
Someone told me she was a nurse
for a private medical clinic uptown.
It was on Grant and 80th.
Some cosmetic place.
We'll put cops on your daughter until this is done.
So you forgive me?
I'll see you tonight.
How's it hanging, Riddle Man?
Uh, it's hanging...
fine.
Mr. Nygma,
did you need something?
Oh. Yes. Uh...
Detective Gordon wanted me to go through the forensic evidence
of these old murders.
Okay.
Are those bruises?
Did Officer Dougherty do that?
Um, he was... upset, and he didn't mean to.
I-I said some things I shouldn't have, and...
Miss Kringle, this is not right.
He can't just...
Mr. Nygma,
it is none of your concern.
Now, I-I need to get started on these files, so...
Alfred.
Should you be up?
Oh, thank you, Master Bruce. I feel...
I feel much better.
Can I get you anything?
Yes, actually.
I've decided to attend the Wayne Enterprises Charity Ball tonight.
All the senior management will be there,
and I think people should see
that a Wayne is still at the head of the company.
I shall set your tux out for you.
Alfred...
Yes, Master Bruce.
Wh-When you were in the army...
you had to kill people, right?
Yes.
Yes, I did.
And it was necessary?
Oh, I see-- so you overheard the conversation
that Reggie and I had that was best left unsaid.
But in answer to your question, yes.
Yes, it was necessary.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I better go and find my good cufflinks,
if we're stepping out.
No, but, uh, you're-you're still recovering.
What, I'm supposed to let you walk into that nest
of vipers on your tod?
There'll be hundreds of people there, Alfred.
I won't be in any danger.
So you say. But you're not gonna go alone.
I won't be alone.
I've invited Selina Kyle.
Selina Kyle?
To the Wayne Enterprises Ball?
I see.
What do you see?
Nothing. I mean, you know... I mean, you're...
a healthy young lad and she's a very pretty young girl
with a penchant of wearing, well, a little too much leather.
Alfred, it's not like that.
Then what's it like?
Well...
well, what if it is, huh?
What's wrong with that?
Absolutely nothing.
So, I will wait in the car outside,
so you don't feel my watchful eye,
but I will be close by, if there needs be.
That is the deal.
Fine.
Could you call around and send
some dresses and shoes to where she's staying?
This is the address.
It's a charity ball, Alfred.
I'll be fine.
Freaky, huh?
You wonder how they recognize themselves after.
Doc Thompkins is fine.
No one's gonna touch her at the precinct. Relax.
You do understand it's because of me that she's in danger.
Anything that happens is my fault.
You can't hold yourself responsible
for the actions of a psychopath.
Sure, I can.
Detectives... I'm Dr. Cushman.
How can I help you?
We're looking into the murder
of a woman named Julie Kemble.
She worked here about eight years ago.
Of course. Terrible thing.
Julie was a talented nurse.
But she'd only just started here when it happened.
She'd been recommended by one of our patients.
The patient's name?
Well, I'm afraid I can't give you that.
Confidentiality.
Really?
You're gonna make us get a warrant?
Yes.
"I specialize in fake boobs, but I got ethics.
I need a warrant."
We'll talk to Judge Harkness. I'm sure...
That car was in front of the precinct.
Jim, wait up.
You sure about this?
It was him.
You saw his face?
No. I should've been looking for a tail.
It's obvious he tracks our investigations.
Called in a description of the car and a partial plate,
but I'm not too hopeful.
So what's the next move?
Gordon, you got a call.
Says it's urgent.
Gordon.
Detective.
I didn't get a chance to say hello properly in the alley.
- Listen to me... - Don't bother tracing this. I won't be long.
I'm giving you one chance to turn yourself in.
You make me come after you, and I will put you down.
Something tells me you've begun to buy your own press, Detective.
The hero cop who's gonna clean up Gotham.
The rising star of the GCPD.
I'll stop you, that's for damn sure.
No, Detective, you won't.
But keep on your present course,
and I will kill someone you love.
This is your only warning.
Oh, no.
Tell me that wasn't him.
He's used to intimidating cops.
We have to show him we're not afraid.
And how do we do that?
You're okay with this? You're sure?
Yes.
It's the right thing to do.
I called you here today...
because the people of Gotham deserve to know
that there's a serial killer in their midst.
For years, he's killed with impunity,
aided by a culture of silence and fear among the police.
That ends now.
We'll be providing the names and photos of all of the victims.
Please call with any information.
And to the man who committed these horrific crimes,
your days of hiding are over.
I'm coming after you.
And I'm not gonna stop.
What are those for?
The Wayne Charity Ball.
It's boring but good for the gallery's business.
Well, I'll probably see you there.
What?
I'm going with Bruce Wayne.
Wait, what?
Delivery for Selina Kyle.
Uh, over there.
Thank you. Enjoy.
Am I really supposed to wear these?
Okay...
we have a lot of work to do.
Got it.
That was the doctor.
Harkness sent over the warrant.
The dead girl came to the clinic
by way of a Miss Constance van Groot.
Van Groot-- that's one of Gotham's oldest families.
- Shipping. - Yeah.
We thought the Ogre might be rich.
Could be the old lady had a son.
You got an address?
Right here.
Well, Butch, Connor and his crew are on board.
They hate Maroni even more than I...
Shut up. Maroni and his crew are here.
I couldn't turn 'em away.
- No, of course. No matter. - No.
She was already here.
Is that my buddy Oswald?
Come here.
Oh, Oswald.
There he is.
Mother, what are you doing?
I'm having a drink with Mr. Mar...
I told you-- Sal.
With Sal.
But we shouldn't impose any longer...
No, you're not taking my Gertrud.
Oh, his Gertrud.
Sit. Join us.
Oswald, sit.
Sit, Oswald.
Hello.
I'm Bruce Wayne.
Barbara Kean.
Selina never said you're who she's staying with.
Detective Gordon spoke of you.
Well, Selina can be a little guarded.
Yes, I know.
Stop talking about me.
Selina.
You look very nice.
The shoes hurt.
Have fun.
Look for me at the ball.
It was nice meeting you.
Think she's here?
Miss Van Groot!
GCPD!
I need to say this is not exactly legal.
We're running out of time.
Over here.
He's good.
Call it in. I'm gonna go check the rest of the house.
He told me...
but I was too slow.
Hello?
Miss Van Groot?
I'm a police officer.
Gordon!
Jim!
Jim Gordon,
Constance Van Groot.
Everyone's staring at us.
Well, I am Bruce Wayne.
Well, I am.
Anyway, I don't see Bunderslaw anywhere.
He's probably not coming.
But he's on the guest list.
Just keep dancing.
And smile, maybe?
Name's Jacob Skolimski.
He's not talking, but near as we can tell
he was the old lady's butler.
And you're thinking the Ogre's this guy's son,
not the dead woman's?
Yeah, yeah. Coroner said the old bird's been dead for years.
My guess, Ogre killed her, daddy pretends she's still alive,
so crazy serial killer son can keep living off her money.
He tried to kill himself.
He knew you were closing in.
- He has to be in contact with his son. - Yeah.
Listen, Gordon's running pretty hot on this one, Cap.
Can you blame him?
Thinks Thompkins is the next victim.
Still, watch him.
Alvarez called.
Nothing on the son in the system.
We have to make him talk.
Make this simple.
Give us your son's name and address.
Or what?
I'm not afraid of you.
Only because you don't know me.
Listen, I get wanting to protect your son,
but how many more women is he gonna have to kill
before you realize he needs to be locked up?
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me. You were hiding
a rotting corpse upstairs for years,
but no, no, my son's an angel,
he didn't murder close to
a dozen women that we know of.
My son--
he made one mistake.
One.
Anything else is lies.
So tell us the truth.
Selina, what happened last night--
that can never happen again.
I told you I didn't have a choice.
I don't accept that.
I knew you wouldn't be able to handle it.
You're right. I did want to kill him.
Keep your voice down.
But there's a line, Selina.
And you can say I don't have guts, but the fact is
I will never cross it.
I guess that's where we're different, then.
'Cause if I had to do it again, I would.
And it wouldn't bother me one bit.
That's Bunderslaw.
Riddle Man.
Officer Dougherty, a word.
I can start a war or end one.
I can give you the strength of heroes
or leave you powerless.
I might be snared with a glance,
but no force can compel me to stay.
What am I?
Got me.
Love.
Miss Kringle has given hers to you.
And in return, you hurt her.
I saw the bruises.
And?
And you cannot do that.
The next time you do that, I'll...
Calm down.
You'll give yourself a girly fit.
Have you ever been with a woman?
Didn't think so.
They need a firm hand.
That goes double for Kringle.
Girl's got a tongue.
I won't let you hurt her.
Oh, yeah?
What are you gonna do?
That's what I thought.
Later, Riddle Man.
Care to dance?
- You. - Me.
It was not a place for a boy to grow up.
Miss van Groot kept herself sealed off from the world,
but she doted on my son.
Treated him as her own.
Still, I...
I didn't realize how deep it went.
This kid's own mom was out of the picture,
so it seems he started thinking
he was this van Groot woman's secret son.
I tried to tell him it wasn't true,
but he had built this fantasy, and...
Miss van Groot led him on.
She was deranged.
Cruel, even.
So, about ten years ago, he confronts her,
he demands that she acknowledge him,
give him her last name, put him in the will.
She laughs at him,
said it was all just a big joke.
So he kills her.
His dad feels guilty, helps him cover it up.
So the old woman rejects him,
he kills her-- bang, you got a serial killer
with a "mommy didn't love me" complex.
But there's a wrinkle.
I don't know where my son is.
He called me today, told me the police would be coming.
But I haven't seen him
since the day he killed Miss van Groot.
My son is not a bad man.
Your son has been seducing and killing women
for almost a decade.
Why is he laughing?
My son...
seducing women?
Oh, let me show you my son-- two pictures.
It's all I managed to save.
You've heard "a face only a mother could love"?
Well... his mother couldn't.
She left us after he was born.
Oh, yes... my son, the seducer.
Now you can see why it makes sense
he scratched his face out of those pictures.
But that means this can't be the Ogre.
We're chasing the wrong guy.
Jim had an idea.
Judge Harkness's warrant was very specific.
I don't have to say anything.
Then nod.
Did you operate on this man?
I need to know what he looks like now.
Or the next woman he kills will be on your head.
Never, never,
would he play with the other children.
You know, even then,
he was too good for them.
And now, he is a respectable man of business--
my Oswald.
Well...
this has been a delight.
But it's late.
One thing...
Gertrud, my love.
A question that's been bothering me.
Oh, no. Oh... no, no.
Is this an act?
Are you pretending that he's just a nightclub owner?
Or are you really that stupid?
Stop!
I don't understand. I...
- Your son... - Don Maroni, I am warning you!
is a cold-blooded psychopath.
No, no, no, no, no...
I can't count how many men he's killed.
My own friend, Frankie Carbone,
he stabbed him a dozen times.
What kind of person plunges a knife
into someone over and over?
He is a filthy liar, Mother!
He's just angry because I played him for a fool!
Oswald...
You know, don't you?
Oh, I can see it.
Let go of her!
Did you catch him, one night,
washing the blood from his hands?
When did you realize that you had given birth to a monster?
You are going to pay for this!
Maybe.
Or maybe this ends with me
dumping your lifeless body into the river.
Either way, you and Momma Gertrud can stop pretending.
Place is looking good.
The other night, when you saw my invitation,
why didn't you tell me you were coming?
I wasn't.
I didn't get invited.
Oh, so you're crashing.
Oh, no, I'm... on the list.
It's amazing what a $10,000 donation will do.
You donated $10,000 to this?
Why?
I was hoping that would be apparent.
And what if I decided not to come?
Well, then, I'd have been making a generous donation to charity,
and I would've been very... disappointed.
The way things ended last night,
it was my fault.
But I felt something.
I couldn't let it slip away.
Well, that's very sweet, but...
You said that when people see the real you,
they run screaming.
Someone said the same thing to me once,
that no one would ever love me.
Who?
The woman I thought was my mother.
Barbara...
I know what it's like...
to be one person on the inside,
and have the world see another.
I lived like that.
And it almost destroyed me.
I can see it destroying you.
I don't want to dance anymore.
The person that I am now, I created.
I brought him into being.
I can do the same for you.
Aren't you tired of playing games?
Of hiding?
Yes.
- Good-bye. - See you soon.
Hello. I'm Bruce Wayne.
Sid Bunderslaw.
I'm going around,
trying to get to know everybody who works for the company.
You do work for Wayne Enterprises, don't you?
I do.
I'm the Director of Physical Operations.
Which, I'm afraid, is a bit dull.
There are many much more interesting people here.
Ah, yes, well, I'm sure I'll get to meet everyone, eventually.
If you'll forgive me, Bruce,
I have an early flight tomorrow.
It's been a pleasure.
It was, um...
it was nice meeting you.
Sorry.
See?
Nothin' to it.
What is it?
Nothing.
Stop right there, buster!
Riddle Man?
What the hell are you doing, creeping around here?
You need to leave Miss Kringle alone.
What?!
I'm not gonna let you hurt her.
Ever again.
I think you need to leave Gotham...
tonight.
I get it now.
You got a thing for my girl.
That's too funny.
Don't take this personal.
You want some more?
Upsi-daisy...
Oh, dear.
Riddle Man...
Oh, no.
Oh, dear.
Oh, dear...
Oswald.
Feeling better?
I made tea.
I'm afraid you had...
well...
a little too much to drink.
Mr. Maroni, he...
he has a strange sense of humor...
Oswald...
I am not some bumpkin from the country,
with hay in my brains!
No...
I am your mother...
and I will love you, no matter what.
But lie to me now...
you will break my heart.
Oswald...
have you done things...
you should not?
I...
Mother...
I'm a nightclub owner.
That's all.
I'm tired now.
I'm tired.
Yeah, I got a delivery for Gertrud, from Sal.
Tip's not included.
You tell Sal it's over.
The guns are bought.
The killing room is waiting.
He doesn't know it, but he's a dead man.
On second thought...
I'll tell him myself.
O-Oswald?
Who was that?
It's Mr. Yatsko, from next door.
He needs help taking out some trash.
You, you... please, you help him, then.
Jason van Groot?
His real name is Jason Skolimski.
He used the old woman's name when he went to the clinic.
But there's no Jason van Groot or Skolimski in Gotham.
The guy's a ghost.
So, the old woman rejects him, he goes to the doctor,
gets himself a pretty new face.
That's where he runs into the nurse.
And we're off to the races.
I don't suppose you got a picture.
Missing from the file. No surprise there.
But the good doctor was kind enough to do a sketch.
It's been ten years since he last saw him,
but at least it's a start.
So we have his real name,
but not what alias he's using,
or what he looks like beyond a decade-old sketch.
Did he say anything else on the phone today?
Anything we might've missed?
Nah, just warned me to back off.
Told me not to believe my own press
as the rising star of the GCPD.
What is it?
The paper that said that--
they ran an old photo of me, from a charity gala.
I wasn't alone.
Barbara!
Is Barbara here?
No. Why?
Where is she?
When's the last time you saw her?
At the Wayne Ball. She left with some guy.
Was this the guy?
It's kind of a crappy drawing.
Yeah, I think so.
Why? Who is he?
What's through there?
See for yourself.