Previously on Gotham...
Jim, meet my daughter, Sofia.
Do you ever think about
walking away from it all?
Sometimes.
This drawing depicts a man
being healed by water.
That's Ra's al Ghul.
He wants the knife.
Opening bid will begin at $50,000.
A hundred thousand dollars.
$2 million!
Sold to Mr. Bruce Wayne!
I guess you could say
I'm your number one fan.
What's black and white and red all over?
Zebra with a gaping hole.
I think something is
wrong with your brain, Ed.
Gordon, you got a visitor.
- You shouldn't have come back here.
- I'm a Falcone.
You came looking for a gangster;
that's exactly what you found.
That knife is the key
to everything.
Well, not everything.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Mmm...
Beautiful.
And you bought this at auction?
Supposedly, it was the embalming knife
of the first century Mesopotamian king.
- Balahsi.
- Ah.
And what is it that you
want of me, Mr. Wayne?
Anything you can tell me, Dr. Winthrop.
I want to know exactly
what it is I bought.
Perhaps you should have considered that
before you dropped $2
million on it, shouldn't you?
Leave it with me overnight.
I'm back.
Man, you really need
to clean that room.
My delightful grandson.
I have access
to the very clean
historical records room
at Gotham Central Library,
and he uses it for his homework.
Oh, Alex, let me introduce you.
Mr. Bruce Wayne and his guardian,
- Alfred Pennyworth.
- What's up?
Whoa.
Where'd that come from?
That cuneiform is
definitely pre-Phoenician.
Alex is an avid student
of history, and sometimes assists me.
A word, Master Bruce.
Now, it's all very well
involving that old
geezer, but a young man?
Just you remember
who's after that knife.
What's so important about it
that Ra's al Ghul wants it
so badly? We need to know.
Dr. Winthrop.
Alex.
I have to ask you to keep
this matter between us.
Of course.
Yeah. Cool.
I mean...
yes, Mr. Wayne.
I'll check back tomorrow.
Until then.
No!
Come on, Ed, come on.
You can do it.
This has to be...
the perfect... riddle.
No!
Yes.
Yes! Yes!
You...
Tomorrow night, Oswald,
is the night you die.
Alex, bring me the Palmerian Codex.
Ah.
What is it?
"he who rises from the waters,
whom death shall not touch.
With this sacred blade,
his final savage destiny
shall be fulfilled.
The earth will quake.
Blood will flow.
All tremble...
before the Demon's Head."
What's the Demon's Head?
Not what, my boy. Who.
There is a legend in
the time of this knife
of a man who could not die.
Or who died but was reborn.
Have you ever in your
reading come across the name,
Ra's al Ghul?
He was a warlord.
But those guys always had
stories invented about them.
They're just stories.
My boy, people believe in these stories.
They kill for them.
I think Bruce Wayne has stumbled across
something much more
complex than he imagined,
and infinitely more dangerous.
No one should be here.
Here. Take this into my office.
Stay quiet.
Quickly.
Dr. Niles Winthrop. What a pleasure.
Who are you?
Museum's closed.
How did you get past the guard?
My apologies.
But my business is pressing.
Greek vase, second century.
Oh.
This was made by a forger in
Marrakesh in the 15th century.
He had some talent, but
told the most obscene jokes.
Tell me who you are, or
I shall call the police.
I'm looking for a knife
Bruce Wayne brought you earlier today.
I don't know what you mean.
Hmm. The best liar I ever
met ran a brothel in Shanghai.
Her quite considerable
gift was that you knew
she was lying but didn't care,
you so badly wanted to believe her.
You, Dr. Winthrop, are a terrible liar.
Where's the knife?
Oh, the-the police, they're coming.
I imagine they are.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
End of crime, my ass.
Harper? Where's Bullock?
He asked me to fill in.
He took a sabbatical for a few days.
You babysitting me?
Do you need babysitting?
What do we got?
Dr. Niles Winthrop.
Curator of antiquities.
Looks like somebody snapped his neck.
No witnesses, of course.
Fire alarm triggered security.
Maybe the dead guy pulled
it right before the...
Yeah, thanks. Anything else?
Yes, actually.
According to Professor
Von Dead's logbook,
the last person who visited him...
I'm talking just yesterday afternoon...
Bruce Wayne.
It's all right. Let him in.
Detective Gordon.
What...
What happened?
We were thinking we would
ask you the same thing.
You met with Dr. Winthrop
just yesterday, correct?
I, um...
I-I bought an old knife at auction.
Dr. Winthrop agreed
to examine it for me.
I was coming by
to check on his progress.
- When was he killed?
- According to the fire alarm,
just past midnight.
Whoever did it must have
slipped past security.
His grandson.
Alex. He's my age, a little bit younger.
- Have you talked to him?
- No one's seen any kid.
I'll get on it.
Where's the knife?
Alfred was right... I
shouldn't have left it.
Bruce, slow down.
What's this knife?
You think someone would
actually kill for it?
Detective Gordon, I'll tell
you what you want to know,
but all I ask is that
you let me come along.
If this is because of the
knife, then I'm responsible.
Bruce, a man is dead.
A child is potentially missing.
This is not time to play detective.
What do you know?
What's so special about this knife?
As far as I know, it's
just an old knife. But...
I paid a great deal for it,
and there was another bidder,
a very aggressive one.
Barbara Kean.
Right.
Well, Harper will
track down the grandson.
I'll deal with Barbara.
You go home.
I'll call you when I need you.
♪ ♪
You're here, finally.
I've kept you waiting.
Apologies.
I see my guests have arrived.
Oh, yeah.
Got to say, they don't do
much for the vibe of the place.
If you had acquired the knife
when I first requested it,
they wouldn't be necessary.
What's so special about
this knife, anyway?
Sentimental value?
Only a destiny born of blood and magic
2,000 years in the making.
Uh-huh.
Now Dog-Boy here is gonna fetch it...
His name is Anubis.
And yes.
Bring me the knife.
And you...
can kill the boy.
Boss.
Knocking, Victor. We discussed this.
Uh-huh.
She's here.
Show her in.
Ms. Falcone,
welcome to Gotham.
Mr. Cobblepot, it's a
pleasure to meet you.
Call me Oswald.
Please, have a seat.
Thank you
for coming to see me.
I learned from my father,
when the king of Gotham
summons you, you come.
And how is Carmine?
Can we hope to see him sometime soon?
Shall we just address
the elephant in the room?
By all means.
My father's
illegal businesses
hold no interest for me.
I'm here because the Falcone
family has a number of charities
that need my attention.
And you can only provide that attention
by being here personally... in my city.
I understand your concern...
Oh, do you?
But I assure you... it's unfounded.
You know, your father
taught me many things.
Among them was to nurture
a healthy paranoia.
For example, when I took over,
some of his old capos went underground.
Now, perhaps they've vanished for good,
or perhaps they're waiting
for a Falcone to return
to lead the rebellion.
Uh... Who knows?
But I hear your father's voice
whispering in my ear.
"Be careful."
Now... I need to know
that you are not on some fool's errand
to rebuild your father's empire.
Otherwise...
I'm gonna stab you.
I was 13 when my father
first sent me away.
He said that Gotham was too dangerous.
This is my home.
I wanted to come home.
That's why I'm here.
Is that enough?
Gotham.
Mother to us all.
I think we have nothing to worry about.
Give your father my best, will you?
Jim.
What a lovely surprise.
Barbara.
I heard you popped up.
Seems like you landed
on your feet as usual.
Hmm.
A woman has to stay busy.
You seem different.
You like this me better?
You recently bid on a knife at auction.
Hmm.
So much for catching up.
The knife is now missing and
the person who had it is dead.
What were you doing last
night around midnight?
I was here... with witnesses.
We done?
No.
♪ And if you go chasing rabbits... ♪
This place, the money you
used to bid on the knife.
Who's bankrolling you?
A client.
And no, though tempting,
I can't give you the name.
Is it Ra's al Ghul?
♪ Has given you the call... ♪
If it is Ra's al Ghul,
you don't know who
you're dealing with.
I don't know who or what
you're talking about.
Now, should I call my lawyer?
♪ Feed your head ♪
We'll be in touch.
Come on.
♪ Feed your head. ♪
You followed me? After
I told you to stay away?
What the hell were you thinking?
I told you I'm responsible.
You should have let me come with you.
It's clear she's lying!
I can help you find
the killer, find Alex!
That's my job!
You want to help?
Who is Ra's al Ghul?
And why didn't you mention him before?
I wasn't certain he was involved,
but the way she talked...
You're lying. Again.
Ra's al Ghul is the real
leader of the Court of Owls.
He is the one responsible for the virus
and having me kidnapped.
And you didn't think to
mention any of this before?
Why would he want the knife, huh?
What's so important about it?
I have no clue.
That's what I've been
trying to find out.
Yeah.
Gordon, the kid's not at home.
Apparently, Granddad
was looking after him
while the parents were traveling.
He's not at school. No one's seen him.
Great. Listen, I need
all the info you can get
on a man named Ra's al Ghul.
He could be connected.
Sure. But how do you spell...?
No one's seen the boy.
He's either hiding,
or the man who killed
his grandfather has him.
Police were triggered by
a fire alarm at the museum.
Alex could've pulled
it, taken the knife.
If so, he'd be hiding,
scared.
Where could he be?
Think.
I only met him for a second.
You want to play detective?
Now is your chance.
What was he wearing? What
did he say? Give me anything.
He... had on his school uniform.
He just came from studying at...
Gotham Central Library. His
grandfather had a room there.
Alex has a key.
If he's hiding, he's made a
choice not to trust the cops.
If I show up, he might run.
He needs to see a
face he knows. Come on.
Ed Nygma sent you?
The Edward Nygma?
Do it again.
♪ My once friend Oswald, now my foe ♪
♪ It's me, Ed, just so you know ♪
♪ It's time we meet,
I think you'll agree ♪
♪ You'll find me where
the Earth meets the sky ♪
♪ Where water flows and birds fly by ♪
♪ At dusk we'll meet,
I'll see you there ♪
♪ We'll settle things,
unless you're scared. ♪
What the hell was that?
We should torture 'em, just get
'em to tell us where Nygma is.
No, he just found us on the street.
Well, that's exactly what you would say.
Leave!
That barmaid who kidnapped
Ed said he'd lost a step.
Clearly, she was mistaken, he's
up to all of his old tricks.
So, I'll meet him.
You and your men will hide nearby.
Attack when I say.
Do not kill Ed, though!
I want Victor to freeze him again.
- Huh?
- Not you. The other Victor.
Oh.
Earth meets sky, water flows, birds fly.
Obviously, he means the pier.
Gather your men.
I want Ed Nygma.
Historical Records room?
In the back.
Alex?
It's me, Bruce Wayne.
You can come out. It's safe.
Alex, please. I...
I just want to help you.
Alex, this is Detective Gordon.
You can trust him.
Okay. Okay, all right.
I'm so sorry.
That-that-that man, he killed him.
- He killed my grandfather.
- It was a man?
- You saw his face?
- I only saw him
from behind. It was the knife.
Did-did you know it was dangerous?
No.
I had no idea.
Alex, we need to get
you down to the station.
I-I-I can't. That man,
he'll think I saw him.
- He'll come after me.
- I will protect you.
- I promise.
- He'll keep coming till he gets the knife.
Alex, do you have the knife with you?
No. I hid it.
Take Alex and meet
me at the station. Go.
Who sent you?
Thanks for clearing that up.
Bruce? Run!
- Bruce Wayne call in?
- No. We released a citywide BOLO.
What about that name I gave you?
Zip. I tried Richard
Gull, Ralph Ghoul...
Detective Gordon?
Ra's al Ghul.
Minister of Antiquities
attached to the consulate
of Nanda Parbat.
Thanks for coming in.
Nanda Parbat, that's
in the Himalayas, right?
Well done, Detective.
Few in your country have
even heard of our tiny nation.
Why don't we speak in
my captain's office?
A bit more private.
Of course.
I'll be with you in a minute.
Thank you.
I don't get it. This is the guy that
you're looking at for murder?
Why does he just walk in?
Barbara must have told him
we were looking for him.
- Yeah, but...
- Two thugs at the library.
If they're working for him,
they would have told him
that we've contacted Alex.
He could think that
Alex gave us the knife.
I can use that.
Call Alfred Pennyworth, see
if he's heard from Bruce Wayne.
Th-That thing bit me.
- I need to get you to a hospital.
- No, no.
Then the police. Detective Gordon...
No, I can't. I can't. They'll find me.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared.
I don't know how you do it.
You fought those men, and I...
I just froze.
Same as when that man
killed my grandfather.
Fear is normal.
In the alley, when my
parents were killed...
I was terrified.
I just stood there.
There's nothing wrong with being afraid.
Once you realize it's normal,
then you can put it in its place.
Then you can act.
Fight back.
I felt bad for you.
When that happened to your parents.
You were all the kids
at school talked about.
What do they say?
That you live alone in a mansion.
Don't go to school.
Fly around in jets.
They make you sound weird.
Maybe I am.
No.
You're-you're cool.
I'm weird.
And you're a little weird, too, I guess,
but...
you're weirdly cool.
I'll take you to the knife.
Can I get you anything?
Coffee?
That won't be necessary.
I think you know why I'm here.
Enlighten me, Minister.
Barbara Kean,
with whom you spoke, was acting
on behalf of my government
to procure a certain property.
Said property is the cultural
patrimony of my people.
Why not bid on the knife yourself?
There were competing claims.
And if we'd bid officially,
alarms may have sound,
and so it seemed
better to do it quietly.
But...
Ms. Kean... failed.
And now, regrettably,
I understand there's been a murder?
Dr. Niles Winthrop,
curator at the Gotham
Natural History Museum.
That's awful.
But the reason I'm here, Detective,
is to press my claim on
behalf of my government,
and entreat you to
return the knife to me.
You say this knife is
important to your country,
please explain.
Hmm.
There is an ancient
story amongst my people
of a man...
who could not die.
In his time, he committed terrible acts,
raised a great kingdom,
and then vanished.
What happened to him?
If the legend is to be believed,
he walked away from his
throne vowing that one day
he would return and
complete his destiny,
but that would require
a particular knife.
This knife.
A story, as I said.
But to my people...
very meaningful.
I hope that satisfies your curiosity.
Some.
But you see, Minister,
my chief concern,
is there's a boy, the
grandson of the curator.
He's being hunted.
Now, perhaps that's
because of the knife.
Or perhaps the killer thinks
he saw something.
Did he?
No.
Well, then he's safe.
Yes, but you see,
I would have to know that for certain,
before I would do anything
that might affect the case,
such as release the knife.
May I see the knife, Detective?
It would so set my mind at ease.
Hey.
Where the bloody hell is Gordon?!
Gordon. Incoming.
Gordon! Where the hell is Bruce?
You...
Alfred!
- Wait, wait, wait!
- Back off!
Take your hands off of me.
You don't know what you got in there!
I'm starting to, but
you are not helping.
I need you to calm down.
Let me finish talking to him.
- Gordon.
- Not now.
Gordon!
He's bloody vanished.
He knows we don't have the knife.
We have to find Bruce.
Donna Falcone.
Do not call me that.
- You got to hear us out.
- No, I don't.
I didn't invite you here.
We're not having this meeting.
Now, I'm gonna ask you, please,
politely, to leave.
We served your father for years.
When Penguin took over,
we had to go underground.
Then we heard a Falcone
was back in Gotham.
We knew it was time.
Did you ignore my father
like you're ignoring me?
I just told you to leave.
Just tell us when your
father's coming back
to put that Penguin in his place.
Please understand me, my
father is not coming back.
This is Penguin's city.
And I want you to leave before
he finds out you're here...
Too late, I'm afraid.
Victor, how many graves did you dig?
Two.
But they're roomy.
And there we are.
My paranoia
is put to rest.
Whew.
You used me.
You had me come to your club.
You knew word would get out,
that my father's loyalists
would find me.
I was the worm on your hook.
With one difference, my dear.
The worm is usually eaten.
So you trust me now?
You're alive, aren't you?
I would plant roses...
they cover up the smell.
My father wouldn't
have killed those men.
He would have invited me
to his club, as you did,
but then gone further.
He would have invited me to dinners.
Had us seen in public.
Sent the message that
the old order supports me.
And those men you killed
would have pledged you loyalty.
Now they're fertilizer.
See, my father, he knew how to
build on the strength of others.
But it's your city.
New times, new methods.
There was an ancient
Sumerian jewelry box here.
I had just replaced it.
Hiding in plain sight.
Good thinking.
Bruce, there's a
legend about this knife.
That terrible things
happen because of it.
But what if it's not just a legend?
My grandfather is dead.
The man that killed him,
he can't have this.
I won't let him.
I promise.
We have to get out of here.
Run. Run.
The Nanda Parbat consulate's
giving us the runaround,
and we can't get in
there without a warrant.
Bruce still hasn't called you?
No. And what the bloody
hell were you doing
letting him tag along with
some murder investigation
- in the first place, eh?
- No, no, no.
You do not get to lecture me
about a lack of honesty and openness.
You and Bruce have been
up to something for weeks.
What have you two
gotten yourselves into?
Damn it, Alfred. I'm on your side.
Well, that may be, mate,
but whatever Master Bruce
decides to tell you is
his decision, isn't it?
You are his guardian.
You are allowed to violate his privacy
if it is gonna keep him out of danger.
Stick to the point.
What are you doing to find my boy?
What can I do? Huh?
I have every cop in the city on alert,
but as long as Ra's al Ghul
thinks he has that knife,
- his life is in danger.
- Yeah, right, and what about
the other boy? Did he tell
you where he put the knife?
No. But I have to assume
Bruce is taking him to get it.
Right.
Well, there's got to be a
clue or something inside here.
What?
- You stay here.
- What?
The access I gave you depended on trust.
If you can't be honest with
me, there's nothing I can do.
Harper.
If Mr. Pennyworth tries to leave,
arrest him.
On what charge?
She'll think of something.
I went to the pier.
I waited.
Ed didn't show.
He...
Oh, just get on with it.
Right.
- One, two...
- ♪ Ooh... ♪
♪ I waited and waited ♪
♪ But you never came ♪
♪ You must be a coward ♪
♪ Or worse, a lamebrain ♪
♪ I'll give you one chance ♪
♪ To make it right ♪
♪ Meet me again, this time ♪
♪ At midnight ♪
♪ I'll make this one easy ♪
♪ This place makes some people lie ♪
♪ Some people speak ♪
♪ And some people cry. ♪
- Honestly, that could be anything.
- Can we please
just torture them now?
Why not?
W-Wait, man.
Run.
Bruce?
Down!
Let's go.
Take him. Take him, go!
Aah!
Get off of me!
It's time you tell me what's going on.
What is so important about this knife?
Why are people dying for it?
Excellent question, Detective.
And you shall have your answer soon.
Just give me the knife,
and I will release the boy.
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
Of course.
Bruce, hand me the knife.
Bruce.
Hand me the knife.
You don't understand.
He killed Alfred.
And then brought him back to life.
And Alex's grandfather
was afraid of this knife.
I can't give it to him.
If we don't hand it
over now, Alex is dead.
- That is all that matters.
- No!
You don't know who he is.
I can't.
Well done, Bruce.
You're finally beginning
to see things clearly.
The question is...
are you strong enough?
No!
Drop the weapon. Hands
in the air. On your knees.
Arrest me.
Ra's al Ghul is on his way to Blackgate.
And we made contact with Alex's parents.
It's gonna take them a
couple days to get home.
Bruce...
Ra's is a psychopath.
You're not responsible for his actions.
I want to help.
But everything you've said so far...
Alfred dying and coming back to life,
magical waters...
Give me something I can believe.
Perhaps now you understand
why we held back.
It doesn't matter what
you say, Detective.
This is all my fault.
Alex is dead because of me.
I killed him.
Oswald!
I waited for you.
Again.
And you didn't show!
You coward.
Where are you?!
Here.
And I may be many things,
but I am not a coward.
Your riddles suck.
This place may make some people lie,
some people speak, and some people cry.
That could mean anything!
Lying, speaking, crying...
You're just describing a
range of human behavior!
No!
I meant lying,
as in lying d...
laying dow... lying down!
As in dead!
Oh.
The answer was Stoker Cemetery.
Clearly.
Only an idiot wouldn't see that.
Face it, Ed...
You can't make riddles
to save your ass anymore.
I guess she was right.
What? Who was right?
Your number one fan.
She said that there was
something wrong with you.
Took me a while to believe it, but...
you're not smart.
I am too smart.
I'm the Riddler.
Oh, God, that name again? Tell me,
how long did it take you to
come up with those riddles?
I don't know.
A minute? Two minutes?
A few hours.
Six hours.
Six hours?
- Yes.
- For two bad riddles?
Does that sound anything
like the old you?
Well, perhaps I'm still recovering
from being frozen in a block of ice!
But revenge will certainly
make me feel better.
You'll never have revenge on me.
Uh, yeah, I will.
- Uh, no, you won't.
- Oswald...
I'm gonna shoot you.
Yes.
You might shoot me.
"Kill me."
But only he can get revenge on me.
The man I froze on that pier.
The man who would've killed himself
before writing those idiotic riddles.
The man whose name I
still will not speak.
But he's gone.
You're just Ed Nygma.
And not even Ed Nygma.
Because Ed Nygma would've
noticed something.
What?
Doesn't it feel kind of chilly in here?
Oh!
You remember him?
My other Victor?
I'm going to put you on ice.
Again.
You want the same
pose or something else?
No. Wait, please.
Got it. Same pose.
No!
Okay, Oswald.
I'm not the Riddler.
Do it.
Stop.
I've changed my mind.
I'm not gonna freeze you.
I would only be freezing
Ed Nygma. Who cares about that?
No.
A better revenge is having you live,
knowing that you are not him,
and you never will be again.
Good-bye, Ed.
Who am I?
I must've been seven or eight.
It was late.
I snuck downstairs to find my father
with a man before him on his knees,
begging for forgiveness.
My father stabbed him in his neck.
The next morning there
wasn't a trace of blood,
and we had breakfast at that table.
Now, you'd think I'd want
to stay far away from Gotham,
but this house,
this city, is in my veins.
I'm home, Jim.
The word on the street
is three Falcone capos
- have gone missing.
- Hmm.
They were in hiding.
Penguin used me as
bait to draw them out.
And kill them.
And you let him?
Don't act the innocent, Jim.
You came to Carmine Falcone for help.
It was never gonna be bloodless.
So is that your plan?
Get close to Penguin.
Gain his confidence. What then?
I need to know what you're going to do.
No.
You don't.
You want the city back from Penguin.
I'll give that to you.
But you have to trust me.
Get ready. Prisoner walking.
Guards, stay sharp!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/a6qmm
Help other users to choose the best subtitles