- Previously, on Gotham...
- The guys call him the Ogre.
He's a serial killer.
Whoever did this, he's a monster.
The blood of his next victim
is on my hands.
If you don't drop it,
that blood could be Lee's.
Because the Ogre retaliates
against any cop
who investigates him,
kills the people they love.
The man who stabbed Alfred,
- he's in Gotham.
- And you need my help to find him.
Who sent you?
You want me to tell Bunderslaw
that you're onto?
Hey.
You look far from home.
Get away from him.
Or what?
Whatever.
Come on.
- Did you go back?
- Yeah, the cops are there.
And?
And what do you think?
He fell out of a five-storey window.
He's dead.
Why did you do it?
He'd told us what we wanted.
He told us about Bunderslaw.
- You didn't have to...
- Yes, I did!
Because the moment we'd left,
he was gonna go and tell his boss
who works for you, by the way.
He's the one who tried to kill me,
who tried to kill your butler,
who probably killed your parents.
I saved your life.
Besides, you wanted to do it too,
you just didn't have the guts.
- Wait.
- Just go home.
We still have to find out
who Bunderslaw is and what he wants.
You mean you do.
You really think this is over?
He's going come after us.
So, what's next?
- His safe.
- What?
Ev... Every senior executive
at Wayne Enterprises
has a safe in their office.
Any... Any secrets Bunderslaw has,
that's where they'll be.
Key or combination?
Key.
My dad had one.
He'll probably keep it
on him then.
Figure out a way to get me close
and I'll steal it.
- Can you do that?
- I think so.
And what happened tonight,
you tell no one.
Not your buddy Detective Gordon,
not your butler.
No, one.
Punctures on test subject
are consistent
with those on the victim,
indicating
the killer was right-handed.
Yum.
- Where's Thompkins?
- Detective Gordon.
Dr. Thompkins said,
I was free to use her office.
She's very nice. She's not like
the old Medical Examiner...
Ed, just tell me where she is.
No, riddles.
Home. She went home.
Hope you find her.
Jim?
Jim, is that you?
You're lucky I don't skin you.
Go home.
- All right, slow down.
- Lee, please.
Start over.
This case you caught,
the dead woman,
she was murdered
by a serial killer?
Yes, he's killed a dozen women,
maybe more.
And Loeb gave you this
on purpose?
He wants to hurt me.
And how am I in danger?
He murders the loved ones
of any cop who investigates him.
So he's been able
to get away with it so far.
Any cop who's come after him,
he's killed someone they love,
and the investigation's
been buried.
Bullock knows a cop who came home
and found his wife
her throat had been cut.
That's why Loeb gave me the case.
Either I give up
like everyone else,
and live knowing
I let her killer go free
or I keep on...
And someone I love is killed.
- You're not giving up, are you?
- I can't.
That's why I need you
to get out of Gotham right now.
Tonight.
No.
You want to protect me?
Find him.
I'm going to stay here
and do my job.
But I do like that you think of me
as a loved one.
I do.
I love you.
You know, it took a serial killer
to get you to say that.
Thanks.
Hi.
This is it.
Home sweet, you know.
This is a great space.
Selina?
Sort of a roommate.
She comes and goes.
Wayne Enterprises Charity Ball.
Didn't you know
I'm a member of society?
I go every year.
Get my picture taken
in a pretty dress.
Smile.
Aren't you scared
of my being here?
Should I be?
Are you dangerous?
I don't know. Is your boyfriend
gonna come home?
I never said, I had a boyfriend.
I assumed a woman
as beautiful as you.
You assumed I had a boyfriend
and you assumed
that I would be the kind of woman
who would cheat on him.
Well, I'm not.
And I don't have a boyfriend.
If a bus hit me tomorrow,
no one would care.
Does that change things?
- Yes, actually, it does.
- Yeah, make it more illicit?
Or would there be less chance
of us getting attached?
One night and done.
Only that would happen anyway.
Because once you saw the real me,
you would run screaming
like everyone else.
I have to say, you're not
who I imagined you'd be.
Surprise.
You can let yourself out.
But you promised
to dance with me.
And I will.
But first I have to finish
with that gentleman.
Who knew running a nightclub
was so much work?
My poor darling.
As I was saying,
you and your crew are the best gun
and knifemen in the city.
Your hit on Councilman Klien,
a thing of beauty.
- And I'm a fan.
- Cheers.
What do you want?
For you to help me
kill Don Maroni
- and all of his lieutenants.
- You're having a laugh.
I'm fairly certain I'm not.
And Falcone's good with this?
He will be.
When it's done.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
So you like being number two.
Falcone gives victor's ass
first dibs on every new contract.
You bring him the bullet-riddled
corpse of his enemy,
and all of that will change.
This is your chance to move up.
You're a mad fellow, aren't you?
Fair enough.
Come by the barge tomorrow,
we'll talk details.
- What's this about, Harvey?
- Have a seat.
- This is my partner, Jim Gordon.
- Detective.
Eight years ago,
you investigated the murder
woman named Julie Kemble.
- It was a long time ago.
- It was the Ogre.
Julie Kemble was his first victim.
But you dropped
the investigation,
because of that,
11 more women have been murdered.
- Seriously, guys, you know...
- Stop.
We also know
the Ogre kills the loved ones
of the cops that hunt him down.
That pattern started with you.
We think you found something
that spooked him.
Your notes
from the investigation.
The last page,
something's been scratched out.
I want to know what.
He killed my wife.
I still got a daughter, Harvey.
Beth Tudor.
Katherine Wood.
Jessica Parker.
11 women.
Each one was someone's daughter.
It has to stop.
Yeah, I was doing background
on the dead girl.
Someone told me she was a nurse
for a private medical clinic uptown.
Some Grant and 80th.
Some cosmetic place.
We'll put cops on your daughter
till this is done.
So, you forgive me?
I'll see you tonight.
- How's it hanging, Riddle Man?
- It's hanging...
Fine.
Mr. Nygma.
- Did you need something?
- Oh, yes.
Detective Gordon want me to go
through the forensic evidence
- of these old murders.
- Okay.
Are those bruises?
Did Officer Dougherty do that?
He was upset
and he didn't mean to.
I... I said some things
I shouldn't have...
Miss Kringle, this is not right.
- He can't just...
- Mr. Nygma.
It is none of your concern.
Now, I... I need to get started
on these files, so...
Alfred. Should you be up?
Oh, thank you, Master Bruce.
I feel, feel much better.
- Can I get you anything?
- Yes, actually.
I've decided to attend
the Wayne Enterprises Charity Ball
tonight.
All the senior management
will be there,
and I think people should see
that a Wayne is still at the head
of the company.
I shall set your tux out for you.
- Alfred.
- Yes, Master Bruce?
When... When you were
in the army...
You had to kill people, right?
Yes.
Yes, I did.
And it was necessary.
Oh, I see,
so you overheard the conversation
that Reggie and I had
that was best left unsaid,
but to answer your question, yes.
Yes, it was necessary.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I better go
and find my good cufflinks
if we're stepping out.
No, but you, you...
You're still recovering.
What, I'm supposed to let you
walk into that nest of vipers?
There'll be 100's of people there,
Alfred.
I won't be in any danger.
So you say,
but you're not gonna go alone.
I won't be alone.
And I've invited Selina Kyle.
Selina Kyle?
To the Wayne Enterprises Ball?
I see.
- What do you see?
- Nothing.
I mean, you know, I mean,
you are a healthy young lad
and she's a very pretty
young girl
with a penchant of wearing
a little too much leather.
- Alfred, it's not like that.
- Then what is it like?
Well.
What if it is?
What's wrong with that?
Absolutely nothing.
So I will wait in the car outside
so you don't feel
my watchful eye.
But I will be close by
if there needs be.
- That is the deal.
- Fine.
Could you call around
and send some dresses and shoes
to where she's staying?
This is the address.
It's a charity ball, Alfred.
I'll be fine.
Freaky?
You wonder how they recognize
themselves after.
Doc Thompkins is fine.
No, one's gonna touch her
at the precinct. Relax.
You do understand
it's because of me
that she's in danger.
Anything that happens,
it's my fault.
You can't hold yourself responsible
for the actions of a psychopath.
Sure I can.
Detectives.
I'm Dr. Cushman,
how can I help you?
We're looking into the murder
of a woman named Julie Kemble.
She worked here
about eight years ago.
Of course.
Terrible thing.
Julie was a talented nurse.
But she'd only just started here
when it happened.
She'd been recommended
by one of our patients.
The patient's name?
I'm afraid I can't give you that.
Confidentiality.
Really?
You're going to make us
get a warrant?
Yes.
I specialize in fake boobs,
but I got ethics.
I need a warrant.
We'll talk to Judge Harkness,
I'm sure.
That car was in front
of the precinct.
Jim, wait up.
- You're sure about this?
- It was him.
- You saw his face?
- No.
I should've been looking
for a tail.
It's obvious
he tracks our investigations.
We called in a description
of the car and a partial plate,
- but I'm not too hopeful.
- So, what's the next move?
Gordon. You got a call.
Says, it's urgent.
- Gordon.
- Detective.
I didn't get a chance
to say hello properly in the alley.
- Listen to me.
- Don't bother tracing this.
I won't be long.
I'm giving you one chance
to turn yourself in.
Make me come after you,
and I will put you down.
Something tells me you've begun
to buy your own press, Detective.
The hero cop
who's going to clean up Gotham.
The rising star of the G.C.P.D.
I'll stop you,
that's for damn sure.
No, Detective, you won't.
But keep on your present course,
and I will kill someone you love.
This is your only warning.
Oh, no.
Tell me that wasn't him.
He's used to intimidating cops.
We have to show him
we're not afraid.
And how do we do that?
You're okay with this?
You're sure?
Yes.
It's the right thing to do.
I called you here today,
because the people of Gotham
deserve to know
that there's a serial killer
in their midst.
For years,
he's killed with impunity,
aided by a culture of silence
and fear among the police.
That ends now.
We'll be providing the names
and photos of all the victims.
Please call with any information.
And to the man who committed
these horrific crimes,
your days of hiding are over.
I'm coming after you.
And I am not going to stop.
- What are those for?
- The Wayne Charity Ball.
It's boring but good
for the galleries business.
Well,
I'll probably see you there.
What?
- I'm going with Bruce Wayne.
- Wait, what?
Delivery for Selina Kyle.
Over there.
Thank you. Enjoy.
Thanks.
Am I really supposed
to wear these?
Okay.
We have a lot of work to do.
Got it. That was the doctor.
Harkness sent over the warrant.
The dead girl came to the clinic
by way
of a Miss Constance van Groot.
Van Groot.
That's one of Gotham's
oldest families.
- Shipping.
- Yeah.
You thought
the Ogre might be rich.
Could be the old lady had a son.
- You got an address?
- Right here.
Well, Butch, Connor
and his crew are onboard.
They hate Maroni even more...
- Shut up.
Maroni and his crew are here.
I couldn't turn them away.
- No, of course. No, matter.
- No, she was already here.
Is that my buddy, Oswald?
- Come here.
- Oh, Oswald.
There he is.
Mother, what are you doing?
I'm having a drink with Mr. Mar...
I told you. Sal.
With Sal.
But we shouldn't impose
any longer.
No, you're not taking my Gertrud.
Oh, his Gertrud.
Sit. Join us.
- Oswald, sit.
- Sit, Oswald.
Hello.
- I'm Bruce Wayne.
- Barbara Kean.
Selina never said,
you're who she was staying with.
Detective Gordon spoke of you.
Well, Selina can be
a little bit guarded.
- Yes, I know.
- Stop talking about me.
Selina.
- You look very nice.
- The shoes hurt.
Have fun.
Look for me at the ball.
It was nice meeting you.
Think she's here?
Miss van Groot.
G.C.P.D.
I need to say,
this is not exactly legal.
We're running out of time.
Over here.
He's good.
Call it in. I'm gonna go check
the rest of the house.
He told me.
But I was too slow.
Hello?
Miss van Groot?
I'm a police officer.
Gordon!
Jim!
Jim Gordon.
Constance van Groot.
Okay, charming!
Every one staring at us.
Well, I am Bruce Wayne.
Well, I am.
Anyway, I don't see Bunderslaw
anywhere.
- Did you see this?
- He's probably not coming.
Well, he's on the guest list.
Just keep dancing.
And smile, maybe.
Name's Jacob Skolimski.
He's not talking,
but near as we can tell,
he was the old lady's butler.
And you're thinking
the Ogre's this guy's son,
- not the dead woman's.
- Yeah, yeah.
Coroner said, the old bird's
been dead for years.
My guess, Ogre killed her,
daddy pretends she's still alive
so his crazy serial killer son
can keep living off her money.
He tried to kill himself.
He knew you were closing in.
He has to be in contact
with his son.
Yeah, listen, Gordon's running
pretty hot on this one, Cap.
Can you blame him? He thinks
Thompkins is the next victim.
- Still, watch him.
- Alvarez called.
Nothing on the son on the system.
We have to make him talk.
Make this simple.
Give us your son's name
and address.
Or what?
I am not afraid of you.
Only because you don't know me.
Listen, I get wanting
to protect your son,
but how many more women
is he gonna have to kill
before you realize
he needs to be locked up?
- What are you talking about?
- Don't play dumb with me.
You are hiding a rotting corpse
upstairs for years,
but "No, no, my son's an angel."
He didn't murder close
to a dozen women
that we know of.
My son, he made one mistake.
One.
Anything else is lies.
So tell us the truth.
- Cheers.
Selina, what happened last night,
that can never happen again.
I told you,
I didn't have a choice.
I don't accept that.
I knew you wouldn't be able
to handle it.
You're right.
- I did want to kill him.
- Keep your voice down.
But there's a line, Selina.
And you could say,
I don't have guts
but the fact is
I will never cross it.
I guess that's
where we're different then.
Because if I had to do it again,
I would.
And it wouldn't bother me one bit.
That's Bunderslaw.
- Riddle Man.
- Officer Dougherty, a word.
I can start a war or end one.
I can give you
the strength of heroes
or leave you powerless.
I might be snared with a glance,
but no force can compel me
to stay.
What am I?
- You got me.
- Love.
Miss Kringle has given hers
to you.
And in return, you hurt her.
- I saw the bruises.
- And?
And you cannot do that.
The next time you do that, I'll...
Calm down.
You give yourself a girly fit.
Have you ever been with a woman?
Didn't think so.
They need a firm hand.
And that goes double for Kringle.
Girl's got a tongue.
I won't let you hurt her.
Oh, yeah?
What are you gonna do?
That's what I thought.
Later, Riddle Man.
Care to dance?
- You.
- Me.
It was not a place
for a boy to grow up.
Miss van Groot kept herself
sealed off from the world,
but she doted on my son.
Treated him as her own.
Still, I, I didn't realize
how deep it went.
The kid's own mom
was out of the picture
so it seems he started thinking
he was this van Groot woman's
secret son.
I tried to tell him
it wasn't true,
but he had built this fantasy.
And Miss van Groot led him on.
She was deranged.
Cruel even.
It's about ten years ago,
he confronts her,
he demands
that she acknowledge him,
give him her last name,
put him in the will.
She laughs at him.
So it was all just a big joke.
So he kills her.
His dad feels guilty,
helps him cover it up.
So the old woman rejects him,
he kills her, bang.
You got a serial killer with
the mommy-didn't-love-me complex.
But there's a wrinkle.
Look,
I don't know where my son is.
He called today, told me
the police would be coming.
But I haven't seen him
since the day
he killed Miss van Groot.
My son is not a bad man.
Your son has been seducing
and killing women
for almost a decade.
Why is he laughing?
My son?
Seducing women?
Let me show you my son.
Two pictures.
That's all I managed to save.
You've heard,
"a face only a mother could love?"
Well, his mother couldn't.
She left us after he was born.
Oh, yes, my son, the seducer.
Now, you can see
why it makes sense
he scratched his face
out of those pictures.
But that means
this can't be the Ogre.
We're chasing the wrong guy.
Jim had an idea.
Judge Harkness's warrant
was very specific.
- I don't have to say anything.
- Then nod.
Did you operate on this man?
I need to know
what he looks like now.
Or the next woman he kills
will be on your head.
And never, never would he play
with the other children.
He knew even then
he was too good for them.
And now he is a respectable man
of business,
my Oswald.
Well, this has been a delight.
But it's late.
One thing, Gertrude, my love.
A question
that's been bothering me.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Is this an act?
Are you pretending
that he's just a nightclub owner?
- Or are you really that stupid?
- Stop!
I don't understand. I...
- Your son...
- Don Maroni, I am warning you!
- Is a coldblooded psychopath.
- No, no, no.
I can't count
how many men he's killed.
My own friend, Frankie Carbone,
he stabbed him a dozen times.
What kind of person
plunges a knife into someone
over and over?
He's a filthy liar, Mother!
He's just angry
because I played him for a fool.
You know, don't you?
Oh, I can see it.
Let go of her!
Did you catch him one night,
washing the blood from his hands?
When did you realize
that you had given birth
to a monster?
- You're going to pay for this!
- Maybe.
Or maybe this ends with me
dumping your lifeless body
into the river.
Either way, you and Momma Gertrud
can stop pretending.
The place is looking good.
The other night,
when you saw my invitation,
why didn't you tell me
you were going?
I wasn't.
I didn't get invited.
Oh, so you're crashing.
Oh, no, I'm on the list.
It's amazing, what a
10,000 dollar donation will do.
You donated 10,000 dollars
to this?
- Why?
- I was hoping
that would be apparent.
And what if I decided
not to come?
Well, I'd have been making
a generous donation to charity
and I would have been
very disappointed.
The way things ended last night,
it was my fault.
But I felt something.
I couldn't let it slip away.
Well, that's very sweet, but...
You said that when people see
the real you, they run screaming.
Someone said,
the same thing to me once,
that no one would ever love me.
Who?
The woman I thought
was my mother.
Barbara, I know what it's like
to be one person on the inside
and have the world see another.
I lived like that.
And it almost destroyed me.
I can see it destroying you.
- I don't wanna dance anymore.
- The person that I am now,
I created it.
I brought him into being.
I can do the same for you.
Aren't you tired of playing games?
Of hiding?
Yes.
- Goodbye.
- See you soon.
- Hello, I'm Bruce Wayne.
- Sid Bunderslaw.
I'm going around
to try to get to know everybody
who works for the company.
You do work for Wayne Enterprises,
don't you?
I do. I'm the Director
of Physical Operations
which I'm afraid is a bit dull.
There are many much more
interesting people here.
Yes, well, I'm sure I'll get
to meet everyone eventually.
If you will forgive me, Bruce,
I have an early flight tomorrow.
It's been a pleasure.
It was...
It was nice meeting you.
Sorry.
See?
Nothing to it.
What is it?
Nothing.
Stop right there, buster.
Riddle Man?
What the hell are you doing
creeping around here?
You need to leave
Miss Kringle alone.
What?
I'm not gonna let you hurt her.
Ever again.
I think you need to leave Gotham.
Tonight.
I get it now.
You got a thing for my girl.
This is too funny.
Don't take this personal.
You want some more?
Upsy-daisy.
Oh, dear.
Riddle Man.
Oh, no.
Oh, dear.
- Oswald.
- Feeling better?
I made tea.
I'm afraid you had,
well, a little too much to drink.
Mr. Maroni, he, he has a strange
sense of humor
Oswald.
I am not some bumpkin
from the country
with hay in my brains.
- No.
- I am your mother.
And I will love you
no matter what.
But lie to me now...
And you will break my heart.
Oswald.
Have you done things...
You should not?
Mother.
I'm a nightclub owner.
That's all.
You're a liar now.
I am tired.
Yeah, I got a delivery
for Gertrude from Sal.
Tip's not included.
You tell Sal it's over.
The guns are bought.
The killing room is waiting.
He doesn't know it,
but he's a dead man.
On second thought,
I'll tell him myself.
Oswald?
Who was that?
It's Mr. Yatsko from next door.
He needs help
taking out some trash.
You, please, you help him then.
Jason Van Groot?
His real name is Jason Skolimski.
He used the old woman's name
when he went to the clinic.
But there's no Jason Van Groot
or Skolimski in Gotham.
- The guy's a ghost.
- So the old woman rejects him,
he goes to the doctor,
gets himself a pretty new face.
That's where he runs
into the nurse.
And we're off to the races.
I don't suppose
you got a picture?
Missing from the file.
No, surprise there.
But the good doctor
was kind enough to do a sketch.
It's been ten years
since he last saw him,
but at least it's a start.
So we have his real name,
but not what alias he's using
or what he looks like
beyond a decade-old sketch.
Did he say anything else
on the phone today?
Anything we might have missed?
No, just wanted me to back off.
Told me not to believe
my own press
as the rising star
of the G.C.P.D.
What is it?
The paper that said that,
they ran an old photo of me
from a charity gala.
I wasn't alone.
Barbara?
- Is Barbara here?
- No, why?
Where is she?
When's the last time you saw her?
At the Wayne Ball.
She left with some guy.
Is this the guy?
That's kind of a crappy drawing.
Was this the guy?
Yeah, I think so.
Why? Who is he?
What's through there?
See for yourself.