Last season on Gotham...
It's in here. It's in this room.
My father's secret, it's in this room.
Going after Loeb is suicide.
Plain and simple.
As usual, wrong place, wrong time.
You're a disgrace, Loeb.
What's black and white, and red all over?
Stop talking like that.
Why did you kill your mother, Jerome?
Barbara, Jason Lennon killed your parents.
- You didn't kill them.
- Yes, I did.
Goodbye, Fish!
I'm the King of Gotham!
What is it, do you think?
Bloody hell.
No, wait, wait, wait!
There must be a million possible
combinations, Master Bruce.
Drink it all.
Thank you, master.
Now go.
Come on through. Let's go! Let's go.
I am Zaardon,
the Soul Reaper!
Foolish slaves! You cannot escape me!
Sir, drop the guns!
You! You!
Your primitive weapons cannot hurt me.
Prepare to die, insect.
Hey, listen.
I don't want to shoot you, man, all right?
Too much paperwork.
So why don't you just put the sword down?
Stay down. Relax.
- Yo, Gordon, what's up? Busy shift?
- You're late.
Jeez, relax will you?
What's the matter with you, man?
Hey! Bad idea.
How can this be?
Zaardon drank dragon's blood
from the master's chalice.
- "Zaardon," that spelled how it sounds?
- Two A's.
Close enough.
- You dare send me to prison?
- Oh, no, you're a cinch for Arkham.
Hear me, Gordon.
You might have won this battle,
but the war has just begun.
The master will unleash
hell upon you.
Dark days are coming.
Thanks for the heads-up.
Ed.
- You okay?
- Never better.
Officer Gordon 2-3-6-1-1.
Report to
the captain's office immediately.
I'm up. See you.
He's gone. Relax.
Holy moley, look at you.
Everyone's gonna think you're going nuts.
I get nervous when you talk to me
with other people around like that.
Stop doing that!
- What?
- That!
Copying me.
Dude. It's a mirror.
That's how they work.
You know what I think we need?
I think that we need
a little more fun.
Some romance.
Stop. I know where this is going.
I told you, leave Ms. Kringle alone.
Imagine her in our arms.
Those big eyes looking up at us,
and soft, trembling flesh...
Be quiet!
It's a simple question, Officer Gordon.
Did you or did you not
put your hands on Officer Franks, here?
Yes. I did.
From the first day on the job,
you've been an insubordinate troublemaker.
I hoped demotion to uniform duty
would suffice to make you quit.
It worked for your partner, Bullock.
However, you've now
confessed to violation of section 12.
Immediate dismissal is mandatory.
Commissioner, this is not just.
Officer Franks sustained no harm,
and Officer Gordon
showed admirable restraint
in defusing a dangerous hostage situation.
Thank you so much for your input, Captain.
The facts speak for themselves.
The facts say he deserves
commendation, not dismissal.
You're letting gutter politics--
That's enough, young lady.
Take Officer...
Mr. Gordon's badge and gun.
That's an order.
All good. Let it go.
Thanks, though.
It's been an honor working for you.
This is all for the best, you know.
Some men are just not meant to be cops.
I told you I'd break you.
I will.
What did you say to Loeb?
Did you get mad?
Well, I disagreed with his decision.
Come on, you know I need the details.
I said I'd break him.
Words to that effect.
Hey. You went out with a bang.
Maybe it's for the best.
That's what Loeb said.
Should've walked away.
I just hate to quit.
You didn't quit, you were fired.
What can you do?
There's things I can do.
I thought you said
you didn't have any legal moves left.
I don't.
You wanna be a cop so bad,
you're willing to break the law?
Willing to bend it a little, yeah.
You're happy I got fired, huh?
You got me.
But only because
I know that you'll never quit.
And I love that about you.
But they have you directing traffic, Jim.
Why keep beating your head
against the wall?
I'm a cop, Lee.
I'm a cop.
Hi, gorgeous. I'm Jerome.
Keep moving, ginger.
Just being polite.
So what you in for?
Killing my parents.
Oh.
Me, too! Well, mom, anyhow.
Liberating, right? Oh, what a rush!
All righty then.
You see the big handsome fella
staring at you like you're fried chicken?
Richard Sionis. He's a millionaire.
Got his own airplane.
Got a boat with a hot tub on it.
And he killed 25 people,
just for fun.
So what?
So, he likes you.
- He wants to be your friend.
- Hmm. Let me think. No.
A girl needs a good friend in here.
See, the guards, they don't care.
They figure bad things
happen to bad people.
And they happen all the time.
All the time.
Hey, you. Hello!
Baldy! Here, here. Hello, yes.
Hi. Come here.
Hi.
My name is Barbara.
- Would you be my friend?
- Yes.
Hey. If someone here tries to hurt me,
would you protect me?
Yes.
Thank you so much.
Cutie.
- Now I have a friend.
- You're bad.
Yeah, so why don't you
go make me a sandwich?
Your friend is a gorilla.
My friend runs the joint.
And he can get you things
that other people can't get you.
- Things like what?
- Anything you need.
I need a telephone.
Odgen Barker, in for 70 grand
plus two months' vig,
250 and change.
Says he owes Falcone,
Falcone's gone, so his debt's forfeit.
Well, we can't have him saying that.
What if everybody started saying that?
There'd be anarchy.
What is it?
Oh, splendid.
Jim, come on in.
My dear old friend.
We need to talk.
Oh. Leave us.
Hey, Selina.
Moving on up, huh?
Trying.
Isn't she darling?
It's like having a cat around the house.
But no horrid dead mice.
I need a favor.
I figure you owe me one.
I do?
I'm always happy to help you, Jim,
but I don't recall--
The hospital.
I saved you from Maroni's men.
But I was only there
because you arrested me.
For attempted murder.
Remind me again why I let you go.
Enlightened friendship.
I'd call us even, but let's not quibble.
I'm so happy you came to me for help, Jim.
The answer is yes.
Your wish is granted.
You don't know what it is yet.
You want Loeb fired
and your old job back. No?
Yes.
For a good friend like you,
it can be done.
If you're sure that's what you want.
I'm sure.
May I ask why?
Police work in Gotham
is such a thankless job.
Good pension.
What does Lee think?
Who?
- Are you gonna help me or not?
- Relax. I already said I would help.
He is so brusque, isn't he?
Thank you. Oh, while I think on it,
perhaps there's a small favor
you could do for me in return.
I know how you hate to owe favors.
I am having a small business dispute
with a friend of mine, Odgen Barker.
You have a persuasive personality.
Perhaps you can talk to him.
You want me to collect a debt for you?
I want you to prove to me
that our friendship is a real one.
Based on trust and equity.
That's fair.
No, sorry. Can't help you.
Congratulations on all your success.
Be good, Selina.
Always.
Don't say no now, Jim. Sleep on it.
Screw Penguin,
screw the G.C.P.D., and screw this city.
Amen.
You're doing the right thing, brother.
Walk away, Jim, just walk away.
You would do the same thing, right?
Me? I'd serve a sandwich to Beelzebub,
but that's just me.
You are a moralist.
You could never work for Penguin.
The shame would eat away at your guts.
Yeah.
- Whoa. Slow down, slurpy.
- Mmm.
- You're not joining me?
- I've been sober 32 days.
Thirty-two days, huh?
It's no biggy. Once I quit the job,
quitting drinking was easy.
It's the job, Jim.
Makes us angry. Makes us hard.
Yeah, it does.
It's hard to walk away,
but it can be done.
I just couldn't carry that badge anymore.
Look at me now. Hmm?
I'm sober.
I have a woman who does not dislike me.
I live in a house. I sleep at night.
I've never been happier in my life.
Here's to civilian life.
I'm proud of you, bro.
Gotta go.
I really am most frightfully sorry it took
so long to answer the door, sir. Strange.
Normally, a buzzer sounds
when a car comes through the gates.
I walked.
You two are dirty.
What have you been doing?
I imagine you have
something important to say.
Yes.
I've been fired from the G.C.P.D.
I won't be able to keep the promise
I made you. I wanted to apologize.
Your apology is accepted, of course.
But you didn't need to walk here.
A phone call would've been fine.
I needed the air.
- No hope for reinstatement then, sir?
- No.
Well, there is a way, but it's too ugly.
I would have to collect
a debt for Penguin.
To prove our friendship.
Ah.
But you can't do that,
because he's a bad man.
- And the task would be demeaning.
- Well, yes.
You were going
to find my parents' killers.
You were going to fight for justice.
You were going to clean up the G.C.P.D.
- Change Gotham.
- I had hoped to do that.
If you remained at the G.C.P.D., you might
still be able to do all those good things.
But first, you must do something ugly.
And your personal honor forbids that.
Yes.
Are you not sacrificing the greater good
for the sake of your dignity
and self-esteem?
- For vanity?
- Steady on, now, Master Bruce.
- Manners.
- He walked all the way here
to discuss the issue, Alfred.
I'm simply asking a question.
Surely, sometimes the right way
is also the ugly way.
Sometimes a man can't take the right way.
He is dealing with all kinds of business
you can't possibly understand yet
because you're still a child.
Yes, Alfred, there is still
a great deal I don't understand yet.
Please forgive me
if I've offended you, Jim.
No, no.
That's okay.
I'll show you out, sir.
Screw it.
Jerome says you can get me a telephone.
I try and help my friends.
What do your friends do for you?
Well, that depends on how much you want
a telephone.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hold it right there.
Odgen Barker.
Penguin asked me to talk to you.
Damn, boy!
You had me worried there for a minute.
I know you. You're Jim Gordon. Cop.
Supposed to be a cold stone hard-ass.
But you're Penguin's bitch, huh?
Who the dickens can you trust anymore?
He wants his money.
How many times
do I got to tell you people? No.
To Don Falcone, I'll pay.
To that fruitcake leprechaun?
Nish. Not a penny.
Falcone's retired. Times change.
Penguin's boss now.
- Like hell. The freak won't last the year.
- Don't underestimate him.
Advice, now.
I'm trying to be nice here.
Let's work this out.
Yeah? Let's not.
Walk away.
Before I kick your ass,
you crooked punk bitch.
How much money you got there?
Looks like a lot.
- What is your problem?
- I don't have a problem.
Give me the money you owe.
How about I put a hole in your face?
- I'm gonna count to three.
- You're crazy.
One...
Put the money in the bag.
Do it!
Oh, get him, man.
Stop! Thief!
Out of the way!
Hey, cop.
Fertilizer?
What is your game?
I would have thought that's obvious
to a man of your perception.
It occurred to me
to follow my own advice.
Sometimes the ugly way
is also the right way.
I mean, a bomb, inside the house?
I mean, you're a having a laugh, ain't ya?
A bomb?
I was going to tell you.
I wanted to present it as a fait accompli.
Don't start talking French to me.
You don't know the first thing
about bomb-making anyway, do you?
I read a book, Alfred.
It seems simple enough.
A book.
I mean, you're gonna blow your bloody head
off before you put a dent in that thing.
You know, maybe that door is trying
to tell us something.
Maybe you're not ready
to find out what's behind it.
Maybe we should wait until you're older.
I mean, who knows what your dear old Dad
was up to down there, anyway?
Like what?
Like things I wouldn't want to describe
to a child, which is exactly what you are.
I'm building a bomb
to blow down that door.
You may assist me...
Or not, as you wish.
But if not, some tea would be nice.
Right, well, you're gonna need 10 more
sacks of that gear for starters,
three more jerricans, two lengths
of timber, and a heavy tarpaulin.
And I'll put the kettle on.
Excellent. Excellent.
I'm so sorry things got messy.
What a foolish fellow.
Never mind. I will make sure that there's
no follow-up from your colleagues.
Don't worry about a thing.
You knew. You knew Odgen would go off.
What a devious mind you have.
I had no idea.
We have a deal.
We do. We do.
You okay, Jim?
Oh, yeah. Daydreaming.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
- Hello.
Jim?
- Hello, are you still there?
- I'm here.
Hi! How are you?
How did you get to a phone?
Who cares? We're talking at last.
That's the important thing.
What do you want?
Jim, there's been a terrible mistake.
I never told Lee...
That I killed my Mom and Dad.
And I never attacked her.
She attacked me, Jim!
She's completely insane!
That's enough. Don't call again.
Who was that?
Sales call.
They can drive you crazy, huh?
Sales call?
Don't!
- What?
- Don't answer it.
- Jim, you're scaring me.
- It's Barbara.
Go ahead and leave a message.
Hey, girlfriend. Guess who?
Sorry I missed you. Bummer, hey?
I just wanted to say...
That I hope you die screaming, bitch.
Bye!
- Nice.
- All right, look.
She's safely locked up at Arkham.
She can't hurt you.
I know. I know. She's just a sick person,
spreading sadness.
Screw her. Let's be happy.
Let's go away some place.
We can't let a crazy woman drive us out.
Why not? Pride? Who cares?
We could go away and never come back.
What's keeping us here?
- I can't leave.
- Why not?
- Jim.
- I did a bad thing.
I did a bad thing.
Hi.
Do you have any peanut butter?
What?
Peanut butter? Smooth, for preference.
Guards! Help! Help!
Oh. Hi, boss.
How about a bottle of beer?
Let me share a dilemma with you.
May I?
I need you to do something for me
that I know you won't want to do.
What is it?
With most people, there's no problem.
I find their weak spots and use violence
or blackmail to persuade them.
But you...
You are a man of monkish virtue.
You have no vices to expose.
So, threats of personal violence
will only harden your resolve, huh?
- No, that--
- Come, sir, don't be modest.
You are a rare animal.
But that does lead us to this sad pickle.
Since I can't persuade you to do as I ask,
the only rational option is to kill you,
and negotiate with whomever
replaces you as Commissioner.
Now, chief?
One moment, Victor.
The Commissioner deserves time
to process all this.
Say a prayer or what have you.
What do you want me to do?
It's not worth talking about.
- You wouldn't do it.
- Tell me.
I need my friend Jim Gordon
reinstated as a detective.
See? You hate that idea.
No, I'll... I'll do it.
Mmm-mmm.
I can tell that you're not sincere.
Even if you do as I ask,
someday down the line, you'll change
your mind and you'll turn on him again.
You want me to kill him now?
No, make him a nice cheese toastie.
Yes, kill him now, please.
Just wanted to be clear.
No, wait! Let's talk about this!
Sorry. Least worst option.
Unless, of course--
No. You would never agree.
To what? Agree to what?
Lovely, lovely. Bravo.
Mayor James regrets
he's unable to attend today,
but he's sent a dear friend in his stead.
Please welcome,
distinguished businessman,
visionary scientist,
acclaimed philanthropist,
and new Chairman of Development
at the Gotham Chamber of Commerce,
Mr. Theo Galavan.
Thank you so much. Uh...
What an honor it is to be here today,
to help bid farewell to a great man,
and a faithful servant of this city.
What can I say about Gillian Loeb?
Someone tell me a funny story.
I have a good one.
So, when I was in college,
I played for the varsity polo team.
And I had a string of ponies...
Greetings!
I am Zaardon the Soul Reaper.
So, I had these ponies...
I'm an adopted son of this city.
I haven't lived in Gotham very long,
but I already love her like a native.
It just kind of grabs hold of you,
doesn't it?
There's magic here. Magic.
And that is down
to everyday heroes like Gillian Loeb.
Mister Commissioner,
thank you for your service.
Thank you very much, everybody.
My best wishes to...
Commissioner Essen.
And the maître d' says,
"You can't bring them in here..."
Hear me, slaves.
My patience is wearing thin.
Surrender your souls to my mercy,
or I swear by the Master,
I shall feast on your pain!
I shall gorge on your torment!
I shall crush you like a bug.
Backup Area Five. Area Five!
Welcome back, Jim.
I don't know how you pulled this off,
but I'm glad you did.
He's a resourceful man.
- Congratulations, to both of you.
- Thank you.
And it is a new day, Jim.
We're going to do great things.
Yes, we are.
It is a new day.
Things are gonna be all right. I promise.
- I hope it was worth it.
- I hope so, too.
Jim.
What's wrong?
There's been an incident at Arkham Asylum.
Six inmates have escaped.
- Barbara Kean was one of them.
- Oh, my God.
- What the hell is this place?
- It ain't Arkham, anyhow.
Things are looking up.
Welcome, everyone.
My name is Theo Galavan.
This is my sister, Tabitha.
I understand you're feeling confused...
Scared, a little groggy,
but please, relax.
Today is the first day
of a wonderful future for all of you.
- If you want it.
- Who are you?
Well, now, the question is, who are you?
The world sees criminal lunatics.
I see brilliance.
I see charisma.
And power.
I see power.
Yes! Exactly, my man.
That is so spooky. That is me to a T.
These other bozos, I don't know,
but you're singing my song.
Quiet, Jerome.
Keep talking.
Imagine a group
of brilliant outlaws like yourselves,
each selected for a unique ability,
all working together as a team.
Imagine the synergy.
Imagine the impact.
Gotham would tremble before you.
Well, that sounds fabulous,
but I'm not a brilliant outlaw.
I just have...
Hmm... Issues.
You have ferocity and beauty and desire.
And that's enough.
Come with me, Barbara.
Whatever you want in the world,
it's yours.
Theo? That's your name, right? Theo.
You're getting way
ahead of yourself, here.
First of all, keep your hands off her.
Second, this whole "magic team"?
I gotta pass. I don't take orders.
Good luck on everything, though.
It's an intriguing concept.
This is very disappointing.
Oh.
Fair play. You want a reward for
busting us out of Arkham. I'm grateful.
How's a million bucks sound? Pretty good?
I can get it for you today...
As soon as I hit the street.
Money's not the concern.
I had such high hopes for you.
I didn't anticipate sexual jealousy.
That always poisons the well.
You have to go.
Tabitha will see you out.
Miss Kean is coming with me.
Oh, She doesn't want
to go where you're going.
Anyone else wanna leave?
There. You're absolutely sure about this,
Master Bruce? I strongly advise--
Alfred, I need to know.
Let's do this.
Right, sir.
Yes!
Great! Yes!
"Dear Bruce...
"These last weeks I begin
to feel very mortal,
"which prompts this note to you.
Perhaps I'm being paranoid.
"I hope so. In any case,
if you're reading this, then I'm dead,
"and you figured out
that the entry code is... Bruce.
"I'm sorry I had to hide this part
of my life from you.
"Because this place only exists
because of you.
"Becoming a father made me want
to be a better man,
"and I started asking hard questions
about the family business.
"So here we are.
"As I write this, you're 12,
and a fine, good-hearted boy,
"so I'm sure you'll be a fine,
good-hearted man.
"But that's all I know.
"I don't know what happened
to me or your mother,
"or how life has turned out for you.
"I don't even know how old you are.
"So I'll resist giving
you much fatherly advice.
"Only this. You can't have both
happiness and the truth.
"You have to choose.
"I beg of you my son,
please, choose happiness.
"Unless you feel a calling.
"A true calling."
English - SDH