Previously on Gotham...
Shall we begin?
I'm not Bruce
- and I won't let you tell Alfred.
- How you gonna stop me?
I'd like to introduce
our newest member
James Gordon.
Welcome to The Court of Owls.
- Are you okay?
- I just remembered.
There's someone I need to kill.
This virus isn't a disease
it's the best thing
that's ever happened to me.
I don't need a cure.
I will purge Gotham
and the innocents will thank me!
Their savior, their executioner!
Guilty. Guilty.
What's this I see?
Captain Barnes being escorted
away by the orderlies.
Who is this new player
that enters the fray?
And with that, it was over.
Leaving me to wonder what
mysterious forces are
at play in the middle
of the night.
Captain Barnes, at last we meet.
- Who are you?
- Let's just say I'm a fan.
- What do you want?
- The same thing you do.
For Gotham to be judged
and the guilty punished.
Well, then release me,
and I'll do just that.
Unfortunately...
we're looking to pass sentence
on a much larger scale.
And to do that,
we need what's inside of you.
- The virus.
- Precisely.
But don't worry, I'll make sure
he doesn't drain you completely.
Hello, Captain.
- Strange.
- I'm sorry, Captain.
This might sting.
Hey, Lee?
- What's this?
- My final report on Frank Gordon.
Cause of death...
Homicide.
I thought Jim's uncle killed
himself.
Did you?
Look, I know you're upset.
After everything
you've been through...
Don't. Don't you do dare do that.
- This is not about Mario.
- Then what's it about?
Why are you... why are you here?
- What do you want me to do?
- Harvey, you are acting captain.
I want you to open
an investigation
into the murder of Frank Gordon.
And I think
Jim should be questioned.
You're accusing Jim
of killing his own uncle?
- Why would he do that?
- I don't know.
But I know that he is involved
somehow.
Maybe not in his death
but maybe in covering it up
making it look like a suicide.
And I wanna know who else
is involved?
Are you implying
I'm involved as well?
Tell me I'm wrong, Harvey.
Tell me there's nothing else
going on.
Look me in the eyes,
and tell me I'm crazy.
You're not crazy, Lee.
You're hurt.
And there's nothing going on.
We used to be friends, Harvey.
I know you're covering for him.
I don't know what he's involved in
but I'm gonna find out.
The ruling council has decided
to suspend all Court activity
in order to focus our attention
on the preparations at hand.
Gotham's judgment is imminent.
To that end, any members
who have not submitted their list
for review and approval
should do so today.
We are adjourned.
Excuse me?
Yeah?
I'm looking for a friend of mine.
Knock yourself out.
Her name's Selina. Selina Kyle.
She knew Barbara Kean?
She used to hang out here, I think.
You think?
You don't sound real close.
Oh, no, we were.
Kind of, but she was always
really bossy, you know?
And then we got into this fight,
I was gone for a while...
Yeah, I don't care.
Try Gotham General.
Did something happen to her?
I heard she fell out a window
and is in pretty bad shape.
What are you doing in here?
I'm supposed to put down
my list of names
but nobody told me what for.
Loved ones are to be spared
from the coming judgment.
Thank you.
No.
It can't be.
I'm sorry, this ward is restricted.
What happened to her?
No idea.
Police found her on the street.
Looks like she fell.
Fell? That's impossible.
Is she gonna be all right?
No.
What do you mean no?
Tell me she's gonna be all right.
- She's gonna be all right.
- No.
You're just saying that because I...
Just tell me the truth.
We've tried everything.
All we can do now
is make her comfortable.
Leave us, and don't come back.
Don't listen to them, Selina.
They don't know what I know.
They can't do what I can do.
I will heal you.
I promise.
Isn't it enough?
You holding me against my will?
Must you also hover while I work?
I'd think you would prefer this
to playing nurse maid
to Fish Mooney.
I was able to save Fish Mooney
despite the fact that she had
one foot in the grave.
I took it
as a personal challenge.
Grandstanding doesn't suit you.
Were you able to accomplish
what we asked?
See for yourself.
Hello?
What do you want from me?
Someone tell me what's going on.
Previously, the Alice Tetch Virus
could only be transmitted
through direct contact
with her blood.
What is that?
Someone, please, help!
You've done it.
You've weaponized the virus.
Pick it up.
No.
You win, and you go free.
Pick up the stick
and defeat this man.
You're lying.
This is just another way
of manipulating me.
Pick it up. Prove me wrong.
All that pain and anger.
You think it's strength.
It's not.
You think you can harness it.
You can't.
You think it's a part of you,
but it doesn't have to be.
Do you know why
you were so easily defeated?
No.
Your rage, Bruce. It blinds you.
You seek to control it, and yet,
it controls you
and has ever since that night.
Rage and pain are two sides
of the same coin.
I can release you from the pain
of that night.
And when I do,
nothing will be able stop you.
Listen, Jim, we got a hit on the
prints you lifted off the mask.
Kathryn's last name is Monroe.
She's from one of Gotham's
oldest families.
Her address is 450 Clinton Ave.
Nice work, Harvey.
Kathryn seems to be the only one
who knows what the weapon is.
So, what's the plan?
Break-in, see what I can find out.
What do you think? She's keeping
it on her fireplace mantel?
I've searched the court chambers.
She isn't taking any chances
with the rank and file
knowing what the weapon is.
If there is something to find,
it'll be at her house.
That's a big risk.
You get caught, ballgame over.
I don't have a choice.
Listen, Jim, about your uncle.
Lee came into my office wanting to
open an investigation
into his death.
She asked me point-blank
what you were doing.
- What'd you say?
- Nothing.
I lied.
Jim, she seemed like
she was in a pretty dark place.
Anything else?
Yeah, not to add on
but I got a call from a buddy
of mine at Arkham last night.
Barnes was transferred.
- Transferred? To where?
- We don't know.
I got Alvarez looking into it.
But don't worry,
we will find him.
- Thanks, Harvey.
- Jim, be careful.
Oswald?
Hello, Jim.
Guess I shouldn't be surprised
you're still alive.
Yes, I am quite hard to kill.
I take it this isn't
a social call.
I'm looking for Ed.
We have some unfinished business.
And it turns out, you were
the last one who saw him.
Yeah, before he escaped police
custody.
Escaped from the great
Detective Gordon?
I think not.
Ed went on television
demanding information
about a group that runs Gotham.
A group called The Court.
And you called-in and said
you had that information.
- A ruse to get him to the G.C.P.D.
- Perhaps.
But then you arrest him
and voila, he disappears.
Sorry, escapes custody.
Can you see how I might think
you may have handed Ed off
to this all-powerful group
for some reason?
For your own sake, Oswald,
drop it.
I knew it.
You don't know anything.
Trust me. Let it go.
Sorry. No can do.
I assume the Court
doesn't like publicity
hence, Ed's sudden disappearance
after his television debut
but that is exactly
what they're going to get.
Unless they deal with me
in a civilized and professional
manner.
I'm sure you wouldn't mind
facilitating something
on my behalf?
My number is the only one
in here.
I'll expect a call
by the end of the day.
Why do I get the sense
I'm being threatened?
This is a favor, Jim.
After all, we're old friends.
Right?
Carlos?
Yes, ma'am?
Kathryn.
Detective Gordon?
What's the meaning of this?
Who let you in here?
Oswald Cobblepot is alive
and back in Gotham.
He paid me a visit this morning.
He knows Nygma's disappearance
has something to do
with The Court.
Is that all?
I'm tired of being kept
in the dark.
I want a seat at the table.
How ambitious.
You asked me to be on the court.
Now, I have done everything
you've asked.
I think I've proved
my commitment.
I want to know what's going on.
I want to know
what the judgment entails.
And if you don't like
what you hear?
Try me.
Gotham is sick.
Crime and violence is so common
the people have become numb
to it.
To heal the city, we have to
force them to take notice.
Force them how?
By showing the people of Gotham
their darkest selves.
I'll consider your request.
Now, leave my house at once.
- It's Harvey. Leave a message.
- Harvey,
I know what the weapon is.
I know how they're gonna pass
judgment on Gotham.
The weapon
is the Alice Tetch virus?
Kathryn said the weapon would
show Gotham its darkest self.
Alice Tetch was at Indian Hill
for years.
They would have known about her.
It's the virus. I'm sure of it.
Is that even possible?
Well, that's why you're here,
Lucius.
I'm sorry to throw you into the
deep end of the pool like this,
but I need to know
what we're up against.
You mean, beyond a secret society
that controls all of Gotham?
Well, if they could
isolate the virus,
they could transform it
into any number of compounds
that could be released
on a large scale into the city.
All they need is a sample
of her blood.
Well, they ain't getting it
from the source.
After Mario broke
into the hematology lab,
they destroyed the rest
of Alice's blood.
I mean, where do they get
a sample?
They don't need a sample
of Alice's blood,
just a sample of the virus.
The virus that she passed along
to the people she infected.
- Barnes.
- Exactly.
Barnes wasn't transferred
out of Arkham.
Kathryn kidnapped him.
So if we can find out where he
was taken, we can stop this.
How do we go about doing that?
I found this in Kathryn's study.
- Any idea what lab it belongs to?
- No.
But when I was running the Wayne
Enterprises R and D division,
we only had a half dozen off-site
labs.
Barnes isn't exactly the kind of
guy who's gonna blend in.
It have to be somewhere isolated
and small enough
for them to control.
I think I know
where they took him.
Just put them down
wherever there's space,
and then go back
to where I found you.
Yes, ma'am.
Selina, I would like to introduce
you to
Nepeta Cataria,
or rather a very specialized
strain of a plant
that I've been cultivating.
This guy is a break in case
of emergence type of deal.
You've always been there for me.
Even when I screwed things up.
Which was most of the time.
Just breathe deep
and I'll be
here when you wake up.
Just wake up, okay?
Are we going back to the alley
where my parents were murdered?
No, there's another memory
I wanna start with.
The first time you felt the rage
after your parents' death.
- Do you remember?
- Yes.
The rage from that day continues
to burn inside of you,
feeding on your pain, blinding
you from everything else
and if left unchecked,
will one day consume you.
We need to remove it
before that happens.
You want me to give up my memory
of that day?
No.
The events themselves
will remain.
I'm only talking about releasing
you from the destructive emotions
connected with them.
And if I don't wanna be released?
You have chosen your prison,
Bruce.
- I'm offering you a way out.
- Why?
You said I was to become
the protector of Gotham.
- Why me?
- Because you need each other.
Gotham needs a protector
and you need a purpose.
I'm only trying to show you
the way.
But it has to be...
Your choice.
You know, where you are?
- My parents' wake.
- Yes.
You were surrounded by friends
and family, and yet...
I felt alone.
This was the first time
I truly processed
that my parents were gone.
The first time I thought
of myself as an orphan.
Is that why you left?
- No.
- Then why did you?
I heard what they were saying.
He witnessed the whole thing.
He must have been terrified.
- Devastated.
- Traumatized.
My parents were dead but all anybody
was talking about was me.
How concerned they were about me.
My parents had been murdered.
Gunned down, left for dead,
nobody seemed...
Angry?
- Yes.
- And so you left.
I hid in my parents' room.
My father was supposed to be
buried in a pair of cufflinks
that I bought him for his
birthday the year before.
He always said
they were his favorite.
But when it came time
to give them up...
I couldn't let them go.
It's time to let them go.
Here, you can lock it away,
and once you do you'll be free
of the power it holds over you.
I've been waiting a long time
for this, Bruce.
Together we will make Gotham pay.
No guards.
No security.
I don't like it either.
I guess we know
where the guards went.
Hello?
G.C.P.D. freeze.
The police. Thank god.
Keep your hands
where we can see them!
I didn't wanna kill these people.
I just lost control.
On the
ground, now. Now!
I'm the good guy here.
You're just like them.
You're out to get me.
What have you done
with the virus?
Who has it?
A woman named Kathryn.
Where is she?
Where she taking it?
I don't know. As I told you, I
was brought here against my will.
I know nothing
of their other plans.
Hugo Strange, you're under arrest
for attempts to weaponize
a viral...
- Hell, you know why.
- Oh, you don't want to do that.
The delivery mechanism that they
plan to use to release the virus.
It just recently arrived.
The shipment that came
into dock 9C.
Yes, it still needs to be tested
which means you still have
enough time
to keep them from unleashing it
citywide.
But, of course, if they discover
that their lab
has been compromised...
He's right.
They might unleash it right away.
We can't take him in,
or The Court will know
we're onto them.
Are you crazy?
What if he's yanking our chain?
What stops him from picking up
the phone
and calling the owl brigade
the second we walk out the door?
My research...
And a vial of my virus compound,
which I secreted away
unbeknownst to my captors.
A token of good will
which I hope will be remembered
when the time comes.
Good will?
You're playing both sides.
You help us take down The Court
and, what, we cut you a deal?
But we fail and you appear to be
loyal to The Court, is that it?
You logical bastard.
Don't worry about the mess.
We have our poor test subject
to blame for that.
Good luck, detectives.
Give Lucius the virus compound
and the research.
See if he can find anyone we can
trust to start working on a cure.
Where are you going?
I gotta find out where Kathryn
is testing the bomb.
- Kathryn.
- I've thought about what you said.
You have done what we've asked.
Maybe it is time
to take the next step.
Meet me at 331 Smith Place.
You can't give me more than that?
You said you didn't want
to be kept in the dark.
Let's see if you're worthy
of the light.
Is that all you have?
I thought you wanted to leave
this place?
That's it. That's it.
Yes.
See what you can accomplish once
you remove destructive emotions?
Tell me, how did you feel
when you were fighting this time?
I felt...
Nothing.
I beat him.
Does that mean I can leave?
Is that what you want?
The pain to go away.
I can take it away, Bruce.
I can take it away
and you can return to Gotham
with a power you never thought
possible.
It's your choice.
Get up.
We're not done.
James.
Glad you could make it.
I'm not sure I had a choice.
I'm afraid I'm going to have
to ask you
for your gun
and your phone.
- Nice party.
- The daughters of Gotham.
Socialites who believe
they hold the power in this city.
When what they really are
is window dressing.
My family was one of the first
in Gotham.
We've been on The Court
since its founding,
making the difficult decisions
to ensure its long-term survival.
Which is why I've brought you
here.
Interesting centerpiece.
It's an aerosol dispersal bomb.
Dispersal bomb for what?
For the Alice Tetch Virus.
So that's what you meant by
showing Gotham its darkest self.
- Precisely.
- Infecting 200 people
- won't change anything.
- True,
but the virus compound
only lives in aerated form
for a matter of minutes, so,
in a closed space
like the room below,
it will be contained
to our guests.
But in an open space,
the radius
of infection is a half mile.
This is merely a test.
Place it
in the middle of the room.
Don't worry,
you'll be safe up here.
I need to trust that you're ready
to make the difficult decisions
when the time comes.
- That's why I'm here.
- Good.
Because if it's not,
if you try to stop the bomb
or interfere in any way,
Talon has instructions
to execute you on the spot.
Talon, right?
I'm assuming that's a nickname.
Right.
Wouldn't want to miss out
on the sounds of 200 people
tearing each other's throats out.
The device is in place.
Hello, Jim?
I was beginning to think
I wasn't going to hear from you.
I met you the other night,
didn't I?
- When you took Nygma?
- Jim?
I keep wondering, what it is
The Court is planning
- to do with him?
- Stop talking.
This used to be a bank, right?
First Bank of Gotham.
I just hope it can withstand
whatever that bomb's
going to do to it.
Sounds like we don't have
much time.
Shut up.
Sure.
Where's Jim?
He's not responding to my calls.
I'm heading to the bullpen,
see if anyone's heard from him.
- What's going on?
- Hey, Lee.
Are you helping Jim?
Bullock, I get.
But has Jim also pulled you
into his madness?
- It's not madness, Lee.
- Then what is it?
How many people
does he have to kill
- before you all see what I see?
- You've got it wrong.
Jim's trying to make sure
that what happened to Mario
- never happens to anyone again.
- What are you talking about?
Lucius, please,
just tell me what's going on.
I can't.
I'm sorry, Lee.
You're just like everybody else
here.
Screw it.
Everyone out. Now!
Took you long enough.
I need to get these people
out of here.
And I need to talk to The Court.
Have them turn over Ed, remember?
There's a bomb down there
with a weaponized version
of the Alice Tetch Virus.
If you want to be here
when it goes off, be my guest.
What about our deal?
You just torched their assassin.
My guess is, they'll be in touch.
- Yes, sir?
- Hello, Kathryn.
My apologies for the time.
Not at all.
How are things progressing
with Bruce Wayne?
Excellent.
He believes in the destiny
I have promised.
In a life free from the pain
of his past.
The boy and I will be leaving
tonight.
I trust everything will be
in place by the time we arrive?
Of course.
Why haven't they made contact?
And where the hell is Ivy
and the human popsicle?
Hello? Are you listening to me?
You're awake. Selina?
Are you okay?
Say something
so I know you're okay.
Why does my room smell
like a giant bag of potpourri?
You're back.
Oh, I can't believe it.
Oh, wait.
What are you doing?
You just got out of a coma.
You need to rest!
This can't wait.
What are you talking about?
Where are you going?
To Wayne Manor.
To kill someone.
What are you doing?
What does it look like I'm doing?
I'm leaving.
Well, actually, I'm resigning,
and then I'm leaving.
Don't. You belong here.
I thought I did.
But then you infected this place
and everyone around you.
I'm done.
I am done with you,
with the G.C.P.D...
With Gotham.
What are you talking about?
You've taken everything
away from me.
Everything. There's nothing left.
And for what?
I would ask you for the truth
but I honestly don't even think
you know what that is anymore.
You want the truth?
Fine.
I killed Mario.
I'm done apologizing for it.
He was gonna kill you.
- No.
- I saw the knife.
I saw the knife and pulled the
trigger, and I would do it again.
- He was infected.
- Yes.
Because Jervis Tetch
wanted to punish you.
You, not Mario.
Mario didn't deserve what happened.
You wanna blame me
for Mario's death, fine.
You wanna walk out that door
and never come back,
I can't stop you.
But it will not help.
Believe me.
The other day, you asked me
at Mario's grave
how I could walk away...
Move on.
I guess you know how.
My name is Oswald Cobblepot.
You cannot do this to me.
I demand to speak to the person
in charge!
Oswald?
You're alive?
I want to apologize
for my curt behavior earlier.
We both want the same thing
for Gotham.
Judgment.
But I have just discovered
someone I thought was loyal
has been deceiving me
from the start.
Detective James Gordon
now threatens to undo
what we both seek.
I need you to kill him
before he can do that.
Jim Gordon is guilty.
And I will be his executioner.