Previously on Gotham:
- Unh.
- Guys call him The Ogre.
He's a serial killer.
Whoever did this, he's a monster.
- The blood of his next victim is on my hands.
- If you don't drop it, that blood could be Lee's.
The Ogre retaliates against any cop
who investigates him...
kills the people they love.
- The man who stabbed Alfred, he's in Gotham.
- And you need my help to find him.
Who sent you?
You want me to tell Bunderslaw
you're onto him?
Hey.
You look far from home.
Get away from him.
Or what?
Whatever.
Come on.
- Did you go back?
- Yeah. The cops are there.
And?
And? What do you think?
He fell out of a five-story window.
He's dead.
Why did you do it?
He told us what we wanted,
about Bunderslaw. You didn't have to...
I did. The moment we left,
he was gonna tell his boss!
Who works for you, by the way.
He's the one who tried to kill me,
who tried to kill your butler...
who probably killed your parents.
I saved your life.
Besides, you wanted to do it too,
you just didn't have the guts.
- Wait...
- Just go home.
We have to find out who Bunderslaw is,
what we wants.
You mean, you do.
You really think this is over?
He's gonna come after us.
So, what's next? Hm?
- His safe.
- What?
Every senior executive at Wayne Enterprises
has a safe.
Any secrets Bunderslaw has,
that's where they'll be.
- Key or combination?
- Key.
My dad had one.
He'll probably keep it on him, then.
Figure out a way to get me close,
and I'll steal it.
- Can you do that?
- I think so.
And what happened tonight...
you tell no one.
Not your buddy, Detective Gordon.
Not your butler.
No one.
Punctures on test subject are consistent
with those on the victim...
indicating the killer was right-handed.
Yum.
Where's Thompkins?
Detective Gordon, Dr. Thompkins said
I was free to use this room.
- She's nice, not like the old medical examiner...
- Ed, just tell me where she is.
No riddles.
Home. She went home.
Hope you find her.
Jim?
Jim, is that you?
You're lucky I don't skin you.
Go on.
- All right, slow down.
- Lee, please.
Start over.
This case you caught, the dead woman,
she was murdered by a serial killer?
Yes. He's killed a dozen women, maybe more.
- And Loeb gave you this on purpose?
- He wants to hurt me.
And how am I in danger?
He murders the loved ones
of any cop who investigates him.
That's how he's been
able to get away with it so far.
Anyone who comes after him...
he's killed someone they love,
and the investigation's been buried.
Bullock knows a cop
who came home and found his wife.
Her throat had been cut.
Oh.
That's why Loeb gave me the case.
Either I give up like everyone else...
and live knowing I
let a killer go free...
or I keep going...
and someone I love is killed.
- You're not giving up, are you?
- I can't.
That's why I need you
to get out of Gotham right now.
Tonight.
No.
You wanna protect me? Find him.
I'm gonna stay here and do my job.
But I do like that you think of me
as a loved one.
I do.
Love you.
It only took a serial killer
to get you to say that.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
Hi.
This is it.
Home sweet, you know?
This is a great space.
Selina.
- Hm. Sort of a roommate.
- Hm.
She comes and goes.
- Wayne Enterprises Charity Ball.
- Hm.
Didn't you know I'm a member of society?
I go every year,
get my picture taken in a pretty dress.
Smile.
Aren't you scared of my being here?
Should I be?
Are you dangerous?
I don't know.
Is your boyfriend gonna come home?
I never said I had a boyfriend.
I assumed a woman as beautiful as you...
You assumed I had a boyfriend...
and you assumed I would be
the kind of woman who would cheat on him.
Well, I'm not.
And I don't have a boyfriend.
And if a bus hit me tomorrow...
no one would care.
- That change things?
- Yes, actually, it does.
Make it more illicit?
Or would there be less chance of us
getting attached one night and done?
Only that would happen anyway,
because once you saw the real me...
you would run screaming,
like everyone else.
I have to say,
you're not who I imagined you would be.
Surprise.
You can let yourself out.
Love, love
Love
But you promised to dance with me.
And I will. But first, I have
to finish with that gentleman.
Who knew running a nightclub
was so much work?
My poor darling.
But the soul is not deceived
In this world...
As I was saying...
you and your crew are the best
gun and knifemen in the city.
Your hit on Councilman Klien...
a thing of beauty.
- I'm a fan.
- Cheers.
What do you want?
For you to help me kill Don Maroni
and all of his lieutenants.
You're having a laugh.
I'm fairly certain I'm not.
And Falcone's good with this?
He will be when it's done.
Thank you. No thank you.
So you like being number two.
Falcone gives Victor Zsasz first dibs
on every new contract.
You bring him the bullet-riddled corpse
of his enemy and all of that will change.
This is your chance to move up.
You're a mad fellow, aren't you?
Fair enough.
Come by the bar tomorrow...
we'll talk details.
- What's this about, Harvey?
- Have a seat.
This is my partner, Jim Gordon.
Detective, eight years ago...
you investigated the murder
of a woman named Julie Kemble.
- Yeah, that was a long time ago.
- It was The Ogre.
Julie Kemble was his first victim.
But you dropped the investigation...
and because of that,
11 more women have been murdered.
- Seriously, guys, you know...
- Stop.
We also know The Ogre kills the loved ones
of the cops that hunt him down.
That pattern started with you.
We think you found something
that spooked him.
Your notes from the investigation.
The last page,
something's been scratched out.
I wanna know what.
He killed my wife.
I still got a daughter, Harvey.
Beth Tudor.
Katherine Wood.
Jessica Parker.
Eleven women.
Each one was someone's daughter.
It has to stop.
Yeah. I was doing background
on the dead girl.
Someone told me she was a nurse
for a private medical clinic uptown.
It's on Grant and 80th,
some cosmetic place.
We'll put cops on your daughter
until this is done.
- So you forgive me?
- Mm.
- I'll see you tonight.
- Mm-hm.
- How's it hanging, Riddle Man?
- Uh, it's hanging...
fine.
Mr. Nygma, did you need something?
Oh, yes. Uh...
Detective Gordon wanted me to go through
the forensic evidence of these old murders.
Are those bruises?
Uh...
Did Officer Dougherty do that?
Um, he was upset, and he didn't mean to.
I said some things I shouldn't have.
- Miss Kringle, this is not right. He can't just...
- Mr. Nygma.
It is none of your concern.
Now, I need to get started
on these files, so...
Alfred. Should you be up?
Thank you, Master Bruce.
I feel... I feel much better.
Can I get you anything?
Yes, actually. I've decided to attend
the Wayne Enterprises Charity Ball tonight.
All the senior management will be there.
People should see that a Wayne
is still the head of the company.
I shall set your tux out for you.
- Alfred.
- Yes, Master Bruce?
When you were in the army...
you had to kill people, right?
Yes. Yes, I did.
And it was necessary?
I see. So you overheard the conversation that
Reggie and I had that was best left unsaid.
But in answer to your question, yes.
Yes, it was necessary.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I better find
my good cuff links if we're stepping out.
No, but you're still recovering.
What, I'm supposed to let you walk
into that nest of vipers?
There'll be hundreds of people there,
Alfred. I won't be in any danger.
- So you say, but you're not gonna go alone.
- I won't be alone.
I've invited Selina Kyle.
Selina Kyle?
To the Wayne Enterprises Ball?
I see.
What do you see?
Nothing. I mean, you know,
you're a healthy young lad...
and she's a pretty girl with a penchant
of wearing too much leather...
- Alfred, it's not like that.
- Then what's it like?
Well, What if it is, huh?
What's wrong with that?
Absolutely nothing.
So I will wait in the car outside
so you don't feel my watchful eye.
But I will be close by if the need's be.
That is the deal.
Fine.
Could you call around and send some
dresses and shoes to where she's staying?
This is the address.
It's a charity ball, Alfred.
I'll be fine.
Freaky, huh?
I wonder how they recognize
themselves after.
Doc Thompkins is fine.
No one's gonna touch her at the precinct.
Relax.
You do understand
it's because of me that she's in danger?
Anything that happens is my fault.
You can't hold yourself responsible
for the actions of a psychopath.
Sure I can.
Detectives. I'm Dr. Cushman.
How can I help you?
We're looking into the murder
of a woman named Julie Kemble.
- She worked here about eight years ago.
- Of course. Terrible thing.
Julie was a talented nurse.
But she'd only just started here
when it happened.
She'd been recommended
by one of our patients.
- Patient's name?
- I'm afraid I can't give you that.
Confidentiality.
Really?
You're gonna make us get a warrant?
Yes.
"I specialize in fake boobs,
but I got ethics, I need a warrant."
We'll talk to Judge Harkness. I'm sure...
That car was in front of the precinct.
Jim, wait up.
- You sure about this?
- It was him.
- You saw his face?
- No.
I should've been looking for a tail.
It's obvious he tracks our investigations.
Called in a description of the car
and a partial plate.
So, what's the next move?
Gordon. You got a call, says it's urgent.
- Gordon.
- Detective.
I didn't get to say hello
properly in the alley.
- Listen to me.
- Don't bother tracing this.
I'm giving you one chance
to turn yourself in.
You make me come after you
and I will put you down.
Something tells me
you've begun to buy your own press.
The hero cop who's gonna clean up Gotham.
The rising star of the G.C.P.D.
- I'll stop you, that's for damn sure.
- No, detective, you won't.
Keep on, and I will kill someone you love.
This is your only warning.
Oh, no. Tell me that wasn't him.
He's used to intimidating cops.
We have to show him we're not afraid.
And how do we do that?
- You're okay with this, you're sure?
- Yes.
It's the right thing to do.
I called you here today...
because the people of Gotham deserve to know
that there's a serial killer in their midst.
For years, he's killed with impunity...
aided by a culture of silence and fear
among the police.
That ends now.
We'll be providing the names and photos
of all of the victims.
Please call with any information.
And to the man
who committed these horrific crimes...
your days of hiding are over.
I'm coming after you...
and I'm not gonna stop.
What are those for?
The Wayne Charity Ball.
It's boring but good for
the gallery's business.
Well, I'll probably see you there.
What?
I'm going with Bruce Wayne.
Wait, what?
- Delivery for Selina Kyle.
- Oh.
Uh, over there.
Thank you. Enjoy.
Am I really supposed to wear these?
Okay. We have a lot of work to do.
Got it. That was the doctor.
Harkness sent over the warrant.
The dead girl came to the clinic
by way of a Miss Constance Van Groot.
Van Groot? That's one of Gotham's
oldest families. Shipping.
We thought The Ogre might be rich.
Could be the old lady had a son.
- You got an address?
- Right here.
You're the cream in my coffee
Well, Butch,
Connor and his crew are on board.
- They hate Maroni even more than I...
- Shut up.
Maroni and his crew are here.
- I couldn't turn them away.
- Of course. No matter...
No. She was already here.
Is that my buddy Oswald?
- Come here.
- Oh, Oswald.
You will always be my necessity
I'd be lost without you
There he is.
Mother, what are you doing?
- I am having a drink with Mister...
- Ah, ah, ah.
I told you. Sal.
With Sal.
- But we shouldn't impose any longer...
- Ah, ah, ah.
- You're not taking my Gertrud.
- Oh, his Gertrud. Heh-heh-heh.
Sit. Join us.
Oswald, sit.
Sit, Oswald.
Hello.
I'm Bruce Wayne.
- Barbara Kean.
- Oh.
Selina never said
you're who she's staying with.
Detective Gordon spoke of you.
Well, Selina can be a little guarded.
- Yes, I know.
- Stop talking about me.
Selina...
You look very nice.
The shoes hurt.
Have fun. Look for me at the ball.
It was nice meeting you.
Think she's here?
Miss Van Groot?
I need to say this is not exactly legal.
We're running out of time.
Over here.
He's good.
Call it in.
I'm gonna go check the rest of the house.
He told me...
but I was too slow.
Hello?
Miss Van Groot?
I'm a police officer.
Oh.
Gordon!
Jim!
Jim Gordon...
Constance Van Groot.
Everyone's staring at us.
Well, I am Bruce Wayne.
Well, I am.
I don't see Bunderslaw anywhere.
He's probably not coming.
But he's on the guest list.
Just keep dancing.
And smile, maybe.
Name's Jacob Skolimski.
He's not talking, but near as we can tell
he was the old lady's butler.
You think The Ogre's this guy's son,
not the dead woman's?
Yeah. Coroner said the old bird's
been dead for years.
My guess, Ogre killed her,
daddy pretends she's alive...
so his crazy serial killer son
can keep living off her money.
He tried to kill himself.
He knew you were closing in.
He has to be in contact with his son.
Yeah. Listen, Gordon's running pretty hot
on this one, cap.
Can you blame him?
Thinks Thompkins is the next victim.
Still, watch him.
Alvarez called.
Nothing on the son in the system.
We have to make him talk.
Make this simple.
Give us your son's name and address.
Or what?
I'm not afraid of you.
Only because you don't know me.
Listen, I get wanting to protect your son.
But how many more women will he have to kill
before you realize he needs to be locked up?
What are you talking about?
Don't play dumb with me. You were hiding
a rotting corpse upstairs for years...
but no, no, my son's an angel.
He didn't murder close to a dozen women
that we know of.
My son, he made one mistake. One.
Anything else is lies.
So tell us the truth.
Selina, what happened last night...
can't happen again.
- I didn't have a choice.
I don't accept that.
I knew you wouldn't be able to handle it.
You're right.
- I did wanna kill him.
- Keep your voice down.
But there's a line, Selina.
You can say I don't have guts...
but the fact is I will never cross it.
- I guess that's where we're different, then.
Because if I had to do it again, I would.
And it wouldn't bother me one bit.
That's Bunderslaw.
- Riddle Man.
- Officer Daugherty, a word.
I can start a war or end one.
I can give you the strength of heroes
or leave you powerless.
I might be snared with a glance,
but no force can compel me to stay.
What am I?
- You got me.
- Love.
Miss Kringle has given hers to you,
and in return you hurt her.
- I saw the bruises.
- And?
And you cannot do that.
- The next time you do that, I'll...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Calm down. You'll give
yourself a girly fit.
Have you ever been with a woman?
Didn't think so.
They need a firm hand.
That goes double for Kringle.
The girl's got a tongue.
I won't let you hurt her.
Oh, yeah?
What are you gonna do?
That's what I thought.
Later, Riddle Man.
Care to dance?
- You.
- Me.
It was not a place for a boy to grow up.
Miss Van Groot kept herself sealed off
from the world...
but she doted on my son.
Treated him as her own.
Still, l... I didn't
realize how deep it went.
This kid's mom was out of the picture,
so he started thinking...
he was this Van Groot
woman's secret son.
I tried to tell him it wasn't true,
but he had built this fantasy...
and Miss Van Groot led him on.
She was deranged. Cruel, even.
So about 1O years ago, he confronts her.
He demands that she acknowledge him, give
him her last name, put him in the will.
She laughs at him.
Said it was all just a big joke.
So he kills her.
His dad feels guilty,
helps him cover it up.
So the old woman rejects him,
he kills her, bang.
You got a serial killer
with a mommy-didn't-love-me complex.
But there's a wrinkle.
I don't know where my son is.
He called today,
told me the police would be coming.
But I haven't seen him
since the day he killed Miss Van Groot.
My son is not a bad man.
Your son has been seducing and
killing women for almost a decade.
Why is he laughing?
My son? Seducing women?
Let me show you my son. Two pictures.
That's all I managed to save.
You've heard
"a face only a mother could love"?
Well, his mother couldn't.
She left us after he was born.
Oh, yes. My son...
the seducer.
It makes sense he scratched his
face out of those pictures.
But that means this can't be The Ogre.
We're chasing the wrong guy.
Jim had an idea.
Judge Harkness' warrant was very specific.
- I don't have to say anything.
- Then nod.
Did you operate on this man?
I need to know what he looks like now,
or the next woman he kills will be on you.
Never, never would he play
with other children.
He knew even then he was too good for them.
And now he is a respectable
man of business...
my Oswald.
Well, this has been a delight.
But it's late.
One thing...
Gertrud, my love.
- Oh.
- A question that's been bothering me.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
Is this an act?
Are you pretending
that he's just a nightclub owner?
- Or are you really that stupid?
- Stop!
I don't understand.
- Your son...
- Don Maroni, I am warning you!
- Is a coldblooded psychopath.
- No, no, no.
I can't count how many men he's killed.
My own friend, Frankie Carbone,
he stabbed him a dozen times.
What kind of person plunges a knife
into someone over and over?
He's a filthy liar, Mother!
He's just angry because I
played him for a fool.
You know, don't you?
- I can see it.
- Let go of her!
Did you catch him one night
washing blood from his hands?
When did you realize
that you had given birth to a monster?
You're going to pay for this.
Maybe.
Or maybe this ends with me
dumping your lifeless body into the river.
Either way, you and Mama Gertrude
can stop pretending.
The place is looking good.
The other night, when you saw my invitation,
why didn't you tell me you were coming?
I wasn't. I didn't get invited.
Oh, so you're crashing.
No, I'm on the list.
It's amazing
what a $10,000 donation will do.
You donated $10,000 to this?
Why?
I was hoping that would be apparent.
And what if I decided not to come?
Well, then, I'd have been making
a generous donation to charity...
and I would have been very disappointed.
The way things ended last night,
it was my fault.
But I felt something.
I couldn't let it slip away.
Well, that's very sweet, but...
You said that when people see the real you,
they run screaming.
Someone said the same thing to me once,
that no one would ever love me.
- Who?
- The woman I thought was my mother.
Barbara, I know what it's like...
to be one person on the inside
and have the world see another.
I lived like that...
and it almost destroyed me.
I can see it destroying you.
I don't wanna dance anymore.
The person that I am now...
I created.
I brought him into being.
I can do the same for you.
Aren't you tired of playing games?
Of hiding?
Yes.
- Goodbye.
- See you soon.
- Hello. I'm Bruce Wayne.
- Sid Bunderslaw.
I'm going around trying to get to know
everybody who works for the company.
- You work for Wayne Enterprises, don't you?
- I do.
I'm the Director of Physical Operations...
which I'm afraid is a bit dull.
There are many
much more interesting people here.
Well, I'm sure I'll get to meet everyone
eventually.
Forgive me, Bruce,
I have an early flight tomorrow.
It's been a pleasure.
It was...
It was nice meeting you.
Sorry.
See? Nothing to it.
What is it?
Nothing.
Stop right there, buster.
Riddle Man? What the hell are you doing
creeping around here?
- You need to leave Miss Kringle alone.
- What?
I'm not gonna let you hurt her, ever again.
I think you need to leave Gotham tonight.
I get it now.
You got a thing for my girl.
That's too funny.
Don't take this personal.
You want some more?
UPSY-daisy!
Riddle Man...
Oh, dear.
Oh, no.
- Oswald.
- Feeling better?
I made tea.
I'm afraid you had, well,
a little too much to drink.
Mr. Maroni, he has a
strange sense of humor...
Oswald.
I am not some bumpkin from the country
with hay in my brains.
I am your mother...
and I will love you no matter what.
But lie to me now...
and you will break my heart.
Oswald...
have you done things...
you should not?
Mother...
I'm a nightclub owner.
That's all.
I'm tired now.
I am tired.
Yeah, I got a delivery for Gertrude
from Sal.
Tip's not included.
You tell Sal it's over.
The guns are bought.
The killing room is waiting.
He doesn't know it, but he's a dead man.
On second thought, I'll tell him myself.
Oswald?
Who was that?
It's Mr. Yatsko from next door.
He needs help taking out some trash.
You, you... Please, you help him, then.
Jason Van Groot?
His real name is Jason Skolimski.
He used the old woman's name at the clinic.
But there's no Jason Van Groot or Skolimski
in Gotham. The guy's a ghost.
So the old woman rejects him,
he goes to the doctor...
gets himself a pretty new face.
SThat's where he runs into the nurse.
And we're off to the races.
- I don't suppose you got a picture?
- Missing from the file. No surprise there.
But the good doctor was kind enough
to do a sketch.
It's been 1O years since he last saw him,
but it's a start.
So we have his real name,
but not what alias he's using...
or what he looks like
beyond a decade-old sketch.
Did he say anything else
on the phone today?
- Anything we might have missed?
- No, just wanted me to back off.
Told me not to believe my own press
as the rising star of the G.C.P.D.
What is it?
The paper that said that...
they ran an old photo of me
from a charity gala.
I wasn't alone.
Barbara?
Is Barbara here?
- No. Why?
- Where is she?
- When's the last time you saw her?
- At the Wayne Ball. She left with some guy.
- Was this the guy?
- That's kind of a crappy drawing.
Was this the guy?
Yeah, I think so.
Why? Who is he?
What's through there?
See for yourself.