Previously on Gotham...
Did Walker
destroy Haven?
This part of the op
is need-to-know.
I come bearing gifts.
Reunification with the mainland
hangs on by a thread.
Toxic chemicals rain down onto
the city, and the government
cuts us adrift for good.
The filtration system
that Lucius designed
is working.
It's not glamorous work,
but we are helping to save the
lives of thousands of people.
You're leaving Gotham.
I believe the time has come
for a change of scenery.
You found a way out of Gotham?
It's a submarine.
Jim Gordon and
Lee Thompkins are man and wife.
He will never see you
as anything but
a dangerous woman
keeping his child
from him.
Eduardo.
Walker.
Professor Strange'll have you
fixed up in no time.
Rest easy, Eduardo.
I made you a promise
when I found you
in that hole in Peña Dura.
And I intend to keep it.
To give you a true purpose
and the strength
to see it through.
However, I'm afraid
this process
will be agonizing
and, unfortunately,
quite lengthy.
Apologies in advance.
You're going to be reborn.
And then you'll be
the bane of the unjust.
The bane of the corrupt.
The bane of anyone
who opposes us.
Radio confirmation.
General Wade's
landing craft docked.
His convoy's
on the way here now.
Reunification day is today.
Harv, that is great news,
but then what?
Just 'cause we rebuild
some bridges
doesn't mean things are
gonna suddenly improve.
So, uh, future got you spooked?
Yeah, I guess.
I mean, I want to believe
things are gonna get better,
but sometimes it's just hard
for me to see it, you know.
Can't say I understand.
I don't have kids, at
least none that I know of.
But you got
one coming,
so we got no choice
but to believe.
It's got to be better than
what we've been through, right?
It damn well better be.
Seven days in a row of
.07 water toxicity levels.
Lucius' filters
did the job.
Eh, good work.
Hope it's not wasted.
Is there a reason to
think there's a problem?
Jim's got a lot on his mind.
What with Gotham
rejoining the world
and a baby coming
into the world next week.
Give it a rest,
Harvey.
All joking aside.
We're here because of you.
Mm-hmm.
And you're gonna be a father.
That's a future I'll take.
Over the past year,
you've all done good work.
We've made Gotham a safe place
for kids and families.
We've given people the food
and medicine they needed.
But it's not over yet.
So, no matter what
General Wade says today,
the work continues.
Give yourselves
one more round of applause.
And get back to work.
Here they come.
Captain Gordon.
Nice to finally
meet you in the flesh.
General,
welcome to Gotham.
Good that you've reestablished
some semblance
of law and order around here.
Seems like
the Green Zone
stretches to every corner
of the island.
General, Wayne Labs
show toxicity levels
way below the threshold
the government set for us.
All due respect,
Mr. Wayne,
but I got to go with what
my people tell me on this.
Cutting it a little
close, aren't we?
Is that under 27 pounds,
13 ounces?
It can't possibly
make that big a difference.
It's only the difference
between getting off this island
or sinking to the bottom
of the river.
Well, then Pengy can off-load
a few of his knickknacks.
Not a chance.
Because you know what's worth
its weight in gold?
- Gold.
- Ah!
Congratulations!
Go to the clinic.
Go have your baby.
What? So the two of you
can hightail it
off this rock without me?
I don't think so.
I assure you we will not
launch without you.
Ed and I will finish
making preparations
and we will be ready to launch
the moment you get back here
with that little bundle of joy.
Or unless I should
drive you to the clinic
in light of your
delicate condition?
I can do it.
I'm not that delicate.
Remember that
if you even think
about double-crossing me.
It's very kind of you
to offer to drive her.
I knew she would
never accept my help.
Should I start the engine?
One less passenger
to worry about.
Oh, two, actually.
You are so right.
Found it.
Ah, well done, Miss Kyle.
All right, let's have a look.
Uh, here we are.
Oh, so this guy's the architect
who designed Wayne Manor?
Yes, right.
With the reunification,
a new Wayne Manor must follow.
And it'll be just
like the old one?
Oh, nothing is
just like it was.
So why are we looking
at the old plans?
Perhaps I'm not ready
to let go of the past.
Well, if it makes
you feel better,
I wish I could
blow up my past.
Well, maybe you will.
One day, when you
build something new,
the past will always
be part of it.
As for me,
now Master Bruce is grown,
building a new manor might be
my last great service to him.
A home.
And then what?
You retire?
No.
I will stand guard,
as I've always done.
I thought this was all settled.
This is bull.
My results are
accurate, Jim.
We don't know this general.
Maybe he's with Walker.
Let's not get carried away.
Bruce, go and check on the tech.
This is Gordon.
It's Lee.
Everything okay?
Barbara just showed up here,
in labor.
You're kidding.
You better come quick.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
I'll try to get over there
as soon as I can.
Try to.
Um... try to wait for me.
It doesn't really work that way.
I know.
Okay.
Wait.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Jim!
What? What's wrong?
We did it.
You did it. We got
through it, Jim.
Captain.
All clear.
Congratulations.
Reunification can begin.
Well, I'm glad
I can make you so happy.
Funny thing is, sir,
that's just the second best
news I've gotten today.
What's that?
- Jim.
- Incoming.
Everybody get back!
Get inside! Get inside!
Go, go.
Eduardo?
Not anymore.
All right, people, listen up.
I want squads
headed for Knights Stadium,
Yeavley Park,
and Granton Station.
Work your way out.
We got to find him, people.
Bloody hell happened?
Seems that Jim's
old army buddy
wasn't quite as dead
as we'd hoped.
I got squads
covering the north side.
They're sweeping from Coventry
down to Miller Harbor,
but they could be anywhere.
Well, give us an
area to search
- and we'll get it covered.
- Uh...
Take Reatton,
work your way
to South City Park.
Looks like you're not done
protecting Bruce yet, Alfred.
Eduardo.
What did Walker do to you?
When I was
in Peña Dura prison, Jim,
the guards played a game.
They'd choose one of us...
and they buried us alive.
They'd take bets on whether
you could dig your way out.
But then they'd bury you deeper.
And play again.
I was the champion.
To survive that...
I had to stop being human.
I had to become...
something else.
I became Bane.
Only I didn't know it yet.
But she knew
and she showed me the way.
If the world is full
of monsters,
the only way to defeat them...
is to become one yourself.
I'm sorry.
You were a good soldier.
Hmm.
Don't pity me, Jim.
We are building the future.
She's given me
a purity of mission.
And unlike the army,
she is willing
to carry things out.
A new world is coming.
Strong...
merciless...
unyielding.
I've heard it all before.
Not gonna happen.
And how are you going
to stop me, Jim?
Not me.
You kidnapped Bruce Wayne and
a general of the U.S. Army.
You talk about your future,
Eduardo, but you don't have one.
But Eduardo's dead, Jim.
There is only Bane now.
Rise.
I said rise!
Not so formal.
Captain and I are acquainted.
Get the other one.
I recognize your voice,
but I don't know
what to call you.
I know it's not Walker.
So who are you?
That's a good question.
Perhaps Bruce Wayne can help us
figure that one out.
You okay?
Yeah.
You want hostages?
You've got me and a
general of the U.S. Army.
Let him go.
This has nothing
to do with him.
"This has nothing
to do with him"?
But, Captain, you don't
even know what "this" is.
This, everything
I have done here,
is about punishing Gotham.
For the sins
of Bruce Wayne.
You can start now.
No... no!
And again.
So...
Bruce Wayne.
I'm thinking of a name.
Can you guess whose it is?
What?
Wrong.
And again.
Want to take another guess?
Farewell, my beloved Gotham.
City of my birth.
Parting is such sweet sorrow.
Though I leave you today...
my heart will always remain.
I do so hate goodbyes.
Well, you're in luck.
- We're not going anywhere.
- What are you talking about?
Engine won't start; pressure
regulator valve's missing.
Or rather it's stolen.
Barbara!
Blood pressure's normal.
I'm glad something
about this is normal.
So how long's this gonna take,
Doc, soup to nuts?
Are you in a hurry
or something?
No, it's just that, uh...
I just feel like
you've been...
so great about this, and,
you know, it's been
awkward as hell for you,
and... I haven't even
really said thank you.
I don't expect a thank you
from you, Barbara.
Then perhaps the best
thank you would be for me
to get out of here
as soon as possible.
Whatever's on your mind...
the health of the baby
comes first.
I know that.
So, long haul or short,
we're here.
Until you have
a healthy baby in your arms.
That's all I want.
Okay.
Stop it!
A name, a person.
The reason
this is all happening.
Can't you guess yet?
I don't know!
If you want to punish
me, then do it.
Hurt me, not him.
I am hurting you.
There's nothing more painful
than seeing
your friends suffer.
But he's more
than just a friend,
isn't he, Bruce?
Jim Gordon's been
like a father to you.
Oh.
How awful it must be
to watch another father die.
Who am I doing this for?
Say the name.
When the ones you love die...
it's like a part of yourself
is cut off...
forever.
You know that.
So why do I hate you so much?
Who was cut away from me?
Last chance.
Yes.
Now you know.
Say his name.
Say it.
Ra's al Ghul.
This is revenge
for his death.
And who am I?
You're his daughter.
My name is Nyssa al Ghul.
And revenge is just
the beginning of what I want.
The League of Shadows
is everywhere.
Did you think my father's
mission would die with him?
Humankind will be purged
of weakness.
I'm just starting
with you and yours.
You're right.
I killed Ra's.
So whatever you need to do...
do it to me.
No.
You can't take all the blame
for killing my father.
I mean, you did have
some help, right?
Someone who quite literally
gave you a helping hand.
What are you doing?
Well done, Barbara.
Go get Barbara Kean.
Eduardo...
She's pregnant.
She's carrying a child.
A child.
One soul's future
weighed against the world's.
Your concern seems petty, Jim.
If he touches a hair
on that child's head,
I will destroy
everything you have.
I don't have anything left,
just my father's mission.
Bane wants you to join
that mission with us.
To see the world as he sees it.
- Never.
- Never say never,
- Captain Gordon.
- No!
How does it feel, Bruce,
knowing that all of this
is your fault?
Tell me.
I'd really like to know.
There must be something
you can give me.
We're out of the drugs
that you need.
It's okay. You're almost there.
I'll get you some ice chips
so you don't get dehydrated.
Gee, thanks.
Lee.
Ed.
Don't worry,
I'm not here for you.
But for the record,
you stabbed me first.
If you two are quite done,
we are actually here
for Barbara.
Or more precisely,
what she stole from us.
I don't know what this is about,
and I don't care.
You two need to get
out of here right now.
Gladly.
Just as soon
as Barbara
gives us the...
What's it called?
- Pressure regulator valve.
- Right.
That.
I should have known that you
would try to screw us over.
You only noticed because you
tried to screw me over first.
Second, technically.
Okay, she's in the middle
of having a baby.
And we are in the
middle of trying
to leave Gotham,
and we can't do that
without a crucial part
of the submarine
which will ferry us
all away from here!
That's why you were
in such a rush
- to get out of here.
- As are we.
Hand over
the part... now.
Don't point that at the baby.
What? No, I did not!
I... I was merely trying
to make a general
threatening gesture
with a firearm.
But you did, though.
You pointed the gun at the baby.
All right, fine. I'm sorry!
Now give us what we want!
No! You think I'm stupid
enough to have the part on me?
It's hidden away,
somewhere safe.
And if you think you can torture
me into telling you where,
there is literally
nothing more painful
than what I am going
through right now!
Hey, you stay out of here.
This is a hospital.
Barbara Kean,
your time is up.
There's no place
for you to hide.
No one will save you.
No mercy that will spare you.
You simply cannot run
from your sins.
And you cannot run from me.
What do you want from me?
Let me let you in
on a little military secret.
It's called Special Order 386.
In the event that Gotham
is irretrievably lost,
a contingency plan
was put in place
to reduce the city to rubble.
No.
There are still
innocent people here.
You asked me what
I want from you.
I want you to suffer,
Bruce Wayne.
And then I want you to die.
Spend a little time
with that thought.
We'll be starting soon.
- Who are those guys?
- No idea.
Exactly how many people
have you screwed over?
Present company
excluded.
There are 79 people
in this building.
Well, fortunately, they seem
to only be trying to kill one.
So, by all means,
let's gather 'round the target.
All right.
Maybe we can cut through
the abandoned wing
and we can get
to the ambulance bay that way.
Might take some time, but...
Oh, if only there were
two able-bodied men
who could buy us some.
And why, pray tell, should we
risk our necks for you?
Chivalry?
But if that's too much,
remember, if I die,
you will never find
that sub part.
Fine.
We'll keep them busy.
We'll meet you at the docks.
Thank you.
- What?
- Keep them busy?
I only brought enough ammunition
for a light firefight,
not to repel
a paramilitary assault.
What should we use,
bedpans?
I was actually thinking
of something
a little more...
flammable.
Why, Captain Gordon,
how nice that you're awake.
You picked
the losing side, Strange.
The army's coming
to Gotham. Help me,
and you can do
what you do best:
survive.
I happen to think more
of Ms. al Ghul's chances
for success
than a man in your...
well...
position.
You really think
she can take on the entire army?
As a matter
of fact, I do.
With my help.
You are just
a few modifications away
from being a mighty soldier
in her forces.
Not unlike
your friend, Eduardo...
I will help you to realize
your full potential,
give you true strength.
I'll pass.
Consent is hardly
a prerequisite.
We will begin...
with, uh, physical improvements.
Sorry.
And finish...
with certain mental adjustments.
Your contractions are
about a minute apart.
We've got to get you
out of here.
Nice shot!
Keep breathing.
Some try to hide,
some try to cheat.
But time will let us always meet.
What am I?
- Pregnant lady with a gun?
- Death.
But close enough.
So, where to now?
Well, I believe...
we have a sub to catch.
How long have you had that?
Long enough to know she'd never
let it out of her sight.
And you stuck around long enough
to risk both of our lives
to save Barbara's?
Or was it to protect Lee?
Do you want me to answer that or
do you want sail away from here?
Bon voyage.
Oh, those bastards have
stolen the damn sub part!
You mean, stole it back.
Whose side are you on?
Clearly,
I'm on the baby's side, Barbara.
- Ooh!
- What was your plan, anyway?
You were going to be a fugitive
with Nygma and Penguin?
Well, I'm not exactly the stay-
at-home-and-bake-apple-pie type.
Yeah, running off on a submarine
seemed like a great alternative.
Barbara, you can live here.
You can have this baby here.
Jim is not taking
the baby away from you.
You really believe that?
You really think
Captain Jim Gordon
is gonna let a criminal
raise his kid?
People are already
shooting at my baby.
I have to protect him...
or her.
I have to be strong.
Right, being strong does not
mean you have to be a criminal.
Jim will help you.
And so will I if you'll let me.
Well, that's just weird.
I know.
Hey, baby,
this is your Auntie Lee.
Mommy tried to kill her once,
maybe twice.
All right.
Okay, that's enough of that.
Come on. We got to keep moving.
I think this is happening now.
What's going on in there?
This is Bruce Wayne.
Can anyone read me?
Does anyone at the GCPD read me?
This is Bruce Wayne.
Can anyone read me?
Bruce, it's Alfred. Where
the devil are you? Over.
Some abandoned mansion
in North Side Park.
- On my way.
- No.
I'll get out myself.
I need you to get to the clinic.
The clinic?
It's Ra's al Ghul's
daughter, Alfred.
She wants revenge.
She mutated Eduardo Dorrance
and sent him after Barbara.
Oh, gosh.
I'm fine.
I need you to get
to Barbara and the baby.
Now, you're going to feel
a slight discomfort.
That's the stimulant I've given
you to prepare your muscles.
You'll need it for
what comes next, which,
I'm afraid, is going
to be excruciating.
Do you feel that?
Yes.
There's that fighting spirit
I've always admired so much.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
there's an alarm I must sound.
- What the hell are you doing?
- Checking to make sure
Strange doesn't have one of
those chips in your head.
We need to hurry up,
get out of here
before he trips the alarm.
Come on.
Alfred and GCPD are on their way
- to the clinic.
- Where's Nyssa?
I don't know.
But she's planning on using
the military to wipe out Gotham.
I can order them to stand down.
Then let's get you
out of here.
She's beautiful.
Congratulations.
Hi, there.
Guess I'm-a have figure out
what to call you.
Thank you.
- Come on.
- Get in the car now.
I'll hold him off.
Alfred and I got this.
Selina, get in the car.
- Selina, get back in the car!
- No.
Go.
Oh, my, look at you.
You're a big'un, ain't you?
Bloody baby bully,
let's see what you got.
Dirty bastard.
No!
Alfred.
Alfred. No.
Somebody help!
Somebody. Oh, no.
A-ten-hut!
Welcome back, General.
Get me a secure line
to the mainland now.
Jim! Hey.
Just got word from Lee.
She and Barbara made it
out of the clinic okay.
And your baby daughter, too.
- Congratulations.
- They're going to The Sirens.
You just had a baby girl, brother. Say something.
Just can't believe it.
We won, didn't we? It's over.
We did, and she's gonna have
a better world because of it.
She is. I promise.
Is Alfred with them?
Didn't say.
This is General Wade.
I am authorizing
Special Order 386.
No!
Gotham City is lost.
Begin your bombing
run on my order.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
- Arrest them.
You can't do this.
Take them away.
You can't do this!
Okay, nice and slow.
- Barbara Kean.
- Run!
It's nice to finally meet you.
My name is Nyssa al Ghul.
I believe you knew my father.
I don't understand how the
general could have been chipped.
I didn't see a scar on the
back of his neck. Did you?
No. Strange must've hidden it.
Nyssa let us escape. She knew
we'd bring the general here
and do her dirty work for her.
What now, Jim?
Son, if you're gonna stick a gun
in my face,
you should at least know
you're doing it wrong.
Come on, let's go.