Previously on Gotham...
You need to leave
Ms. Kringle alone.
I get it now.
You got a thing for my girl.
Oh, dear.
Who sent you?
You want me to tell Bunderslaw
that you want her?
- I'm Bruce Wayne.
- Sid Bunderslaw.
The people of Gotham deserve
to know
that there's a serial killer
in their amidst.
I'm coming after you.
He murders the loved ones
of many cop who investigates it.
You wanna dance?
Morning. How'd you sleep?
The hour we slept?
Great.
You hungry? I have quiche.
No, thanks.
At least have some coffee,
let me tell you about the day
I had plan for us.
I think I'm just gonna get out
of here.
Wait.
We had fun last night, right?
Stay.
Listen, you don't have
to do this.
Do what?
Last night at the ball,
you talked a good game.
But let's not pretend
this is more than what it is.
Barbara, I'm not pretending
with you.
I want you to stay with me.
I don't think so.
Just... Wait, wait, wait.
Let go.
Look...
I was pretending with you.
But...
Not in the way you think.
The night we met...
I was going to kill you.
- That's not funny.
- But then,
I saw something in you.
Barbara, I saw...
Who are you. You.
You are the woman
that I've been searching for.
You're lying.
I'm gonna let you go now,
and you're going to sit down
and have breakfast with me.
So we do it the hard way.
- Hey, how are you doing?
- Been better.
- Have you seen Harvey?
- No.
Any word on Barbara?
They haven't found her body yet.
There's a chance she's still alive.
- When's the last time you slept?
- I don't know.
- Last time you ate?
I know better than to try
to get you to sleep,
but you really should eat something.
- I'm not hungry.
- Jim.
It's not your fault.
I did this. I pressed Loeb,
he sent the Ogre after me
and I didn't stop.
It was bad enough.
I knowingly put you in danger.
I didn't even think of Barbara.
- You were doing your job.
- But I should have known.
How? You weren't together.
Do you blame yourself
for falling out of love?
Lee, it's my responsibility.
There's nothing you can say
that changes that.
Whatever happens to Barbara,
it's on me.
- I understand.
- Jimbo!
Meet Jake the J.V. pimp.
He's been bragging on the street
that he knows who the Ogre is.
I keep telling you, man,
you been lied to.
- I don't know nothing.
- Yeah? We'll see about that.
Okey-doke.
No body. No crime.
No. Never seen him before.
We think this is a serial killer
called the Ogre.
He's kidnapped a woman
and he's gonna kill her
unless we find him first.
- Bummer.
- Just so you understand,
the lady in question
is a real good friend of ours.
Supposing, for the sake
of argument,
I did see him before.
What's she worth?
Yeah, you know...
If you had to assign
a dollar amount.
Harvey, I'm about to violate
departmental policy
on interrogation techniques.
I think I saw some donuts outside
with my name all over them.
Hey, now, okay.
Okay, now, sir, there's nothing
you need to go...
Jake, worked as a barman
at a brothel called The Foxglove.
Said the Ogre was a regular.
He can't give us a location.
Yeah, because it never uses
the same place twice.
- And you know it?
- Not personally.
The Foxglove is very high-class,
very extreme.
You've gotta know someone
who knows someone.
- I might. Know someone.
- You're thinking Penguin?
Hey, you get in any deeper
with that clown, he will own you.
I don't have a choice.
The Ogre has Barbara.
Let me shake a few trees.
Take the time grab some Z's.
You're burnt.
The first one was the hardest.
But it wasn't her fault.
She just wasn't the one.
I also couldn't let her go.
Still, it strengthened my resolve
to never stop till
I found my soul mate.
The person I could share
everything with.
I think that person
is you, Barbara.
But I need your help me.
So...
Let's begin again, shall we?
This just came for you by messenger,
Master Bruce.
Thank you.
Right, well...
I'll do the off.
Do you want company?
To identify Reggie?
No, I don't think so.
Best on alone.
I'm sorry, Alfred.
- I know, he was your friend.
- Just doesn't make any sense.
Reggie topping himself like that.
You said, he fell out of a window.
He might have been drinking.
Lost his balance.
That Reggie was a legend.
He could be blind drunk
and walk a tightrope
It doesn't matter
what he's like in the end.
I wanna see
he gets a proper send-off.
I'll see you this evening, sir.
What, your boss doesn't trust
his partners?
It's called due diligence.
He just wants me
to look the place over.
So look.
I got a gravy going.
Special party today.
Don't let me keep you.
Piece of work.
I'll put the pistol behind
the bar.
Machine gun behind the juke.
Now, Connor and his guy gotta do
is get to them.
The day is finally here.
Maroni.
Jim!
So lovely to see you.
To what do I owe
this wonderful surprise?
I need to know
where the Foxglove is
and I need an invitation.
Well, someone's in a mood.
Can you help me? Yes or no.
Jim, I do so love our
give-and-take relationship.
But it's starting
to feel a bit one-sided.
Fine. I'll owe you a favor.
- You already do.
- Then I'll owe you another.
Cards on the table.
The Foxglove makes a lot of money
for some important friend
of mine...
You think you know who I am.
What I'm capable of.
You have no idea.
Today is an important day for me,
so I will accommodate your request.
But, Detective, mark my words,
You owe me a big favor.
Here, we have
the Physical Operations department.
The Physical Operations department
handles logistics
for the corporation,
- management of our properties...
- Excuse me.
- I need to use the restroom.
- Of course, Mr. Wayne.
- It's right here.
- Thank you.
The Foxglove is in the old
Klondike Building on Mayflower.
- You score a ticket?
- Yes, but only one.
I figure you go in.
Pose as a john, find something
to bust them on
and squeeze them till they talk.
Smart move sending me.
You couldn't look more like a cop
if you wore the blue uniform.
You got something to wear?
You'll gonna need to fit in.
Don't worry.
Alvarez busted some guys
smuggling Italian suits last week
and a couple fell in my locker
on their way to the evidence room.
I'm sorry, I left you alone.
But...
You needed time to think
to accept that this was real.
This apartment is sound-proofed,
by the way, so save your lungs.
Look at me,
my hands are shaking.
That's never happened before,
with any of the other women
that I've had here.
You know why that is?
- Do you know why that is?
- You're a psycho.
I don't know
what you're thinking.
It's because
I always somehow knew deep down
the others weren't the one.
They weren't the one.
I want this to work, Barbara.
You're scared. That's okay.
Jim will find me...
The only way you're going
to make me angry
is if you mention his name.
Drink this.
It's water. You're dehydrated.
Barbara, come here.
I want you to see something.
Barbara, I love you. I love you
like no one else ever loved you.
But if you try to escape,
I will chain you
to the ceiling and gut you.
Now, come here.
Are those...
When you're looking for love,
you have to kiss a lot of frogs.
Still, I should be thankful,
they led me to you.
All those women...
They died here.
You killed them.
Here...
Yes.
Don't worry.
We're gonna set you free.
You're the one, Barbara.
You're the one.
Hello, Bruce.
I've been expecting you.
Ever since your friend borrowed
my key, I've been expecting you.
Even canceled my trip.
Cookie?
When I was a boy
I'd always take a cookie
when I had the chance.
You hired a man to kill Alfred.
I hired your guardian's comrade
to find out what you knew.
I never intended harm
to come to anyone.
I told the board
you were a special case.
That you need the talk early.
The talk.
Bruce, when a member of the Wayne
family reaches a certain age,
some facts of life
and business are explained.
Wayne Enterprises,
is committing serious crimes.
Oh, my yes.
This is a multinational corporation
operating in hundreds
of jurisdictions.
We do our best to subvert
all of them if it means profits.
So...
You admit it?
Just like your father.
He came in with his "secret files",
demanding justice. At first.
Then he changed his mind.
You're lying.
Your father came to understand
the reality of this business.
As did his father.
And as you will.
My father was a good man.
You have the opportunity
to live a blessed life.
The life your father and mother
wanted for you.
I beg you to reconsider.
Pardon me.
Lucius, come in.
Bruce Wayne,
meet one of our junior executives,
Lucius Fox.
There is a public relations
person out there
desperately searching
for this young man.
Then you'd best reunite them.
Bruce?
Don't forget your cookie.
Now...
I'm going to tell you something,
and I'd appreciate if you kept
your face perfectly still.
There are cameras everywhere.
I know because I put them there.
What I'm about to say,
must be a deep secret
between you and me.
I knew your father well.
He was a good man.
He wasn't the man
the company thought he was.
- I don't understand you.
- Bruce.
Your father was a true stoic.
He kept his best self-hidden.
That's all I'll say.
Good luck.
- Mr. Nygma?
- Ms. Kring...
- Ms. Kringle.
- Would you open the door, please?
I'm...
One sec.
I need the Hendricks case files.
Yes. Hendricks. Wait right there.
Hendricks, Hendricks, Hendricks.
Oh, my goodness!
What happened to him?
Ax... Accidental death.
At a sheet metal factory.
Industrial saw.
The poor man.
I don't... I don't know
how you do this job.
Death all around you.
Yes, one must have
a sense of humor.
- The file?
- Yes.
Mr. Nygma, you haven't by chance,
seen Tom,
Officer Doughtery?
We were...
We supposed to have dinner last night
and he didn't show, no surprise
- but I haven't seen him today.
- Me neither.
Excuse me. I really need
to get back to work.
- Oh.
- Now.
Okay.
Oh, dear.
You're sure?
The guns are there.
Butch placed them himself.
Do you remember what to say to Maroni
before you do the deed?
I never saw the point
in telling a man something
right before you gonna whack him,
but you're not the first
to ask for it.
I appreciate you humoring me.
So, how'd you know,
Maroni's gonna be in this bar
on this exact day?
I follow current events.
There he is.
Tommy "freaking" Bones.
Nine years up the river
and you get better looking,
you big animal.
Took care of myself.
I was hoping you'd remember.
Come over here!
Listen, you leave the joint,
you come Lidia's for dinner.
That's tradition. Welcome home.
Lidia! Look who's here.
Welcome to the Foxglove.
The evening's entertainment
is about to begin.
Then I guess I'm just in time.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
you attention please.
I know you've been
eagerly awaiting
tonight's main attraction.
So please let's give
a big Foxglove welcome
to Ingrid and Gareth.
Hell no.
GCPD, nobody move!
Especially you two!
Barbara.
Wake up. Barbara.
Wake up.
Come here.
Don't cry.
There's no need to cry... Okay.
You're gonna kill me.
- Do you want me to?
- No!
Then tell me who to kill.
What?
You still don't believe
I love you.
You think I'm crazy.
That's fine.
I see the truth.
I see your truth.
I see that you've spent
your whole life
trying to kill it but you can't.
It's too strong.
You revealed it to me
the other night.
I want to set that free,
I want to set you free,
You think that me making
you murder someone
will make me like you?
That's insane.
You say that
because you don't know
what it is to live without fear.
But you'll learn.
Now, tell me
who you want me to kill
or though it breaks my heart,
I will take your life right now.
I can't.
I can't
Tell me...
Who to kill!
You run this place?
I'm looking for this man.
Arrest me if you want to,
I don't talk about my clients.
One call to the gazette.
They'll send a reporter down here.
And I perp-walk each
and every one of your clients
in front of the cameras.
How's that sound?
Talk to Sally.
Do you know him.
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
He said, his name was Jason.
He was sweet.
As soon as I got into his car
he pulled a hood over my head
and tied my wrist.
He took me back to his apartment,
that's where he did this.
I don't know why he let me go.
- When was this?
- Almost nine years ago.
A year before his first murder.
He was working his way up.
Why didn't you go to the police?
I did. I was a hooker
he was a rich man with no name.
Anything else you can tell us?
Anything about his apartment?
The smallest detail might help.
The elevator opened
right into the apartment.
You could see out into the city.
We were in midtown.
And there was a neon sign
on a building across the street.
I can only read
the last four letters
O-Y-A-L.
"O-Y-A-L".
- Loyal, Royal?
- Royal?
Gotham Royal Hotel.
That's in midtown.
Tenth and Gainsly.
Thank you, Sally.
Promise me when you find him,
don't arrest him.
Kill him.
You got it.
Oh, fellas. Private party.
Just here to pay respects.
Connor from the wild North East.
What's that old man
Falcone want now?
Don Falcone sends
me with his respects
and a small gift for you
and Tommy Bones on this happy day.
Cheech.
Forgive my suspicious nature.
Of course. Can't be too careful.
Madre Di Dios.
My favorite.
You tell Falcone
I appreciate the gesture.
Don Falcone knew
this was a special occasion.
We got time for a drink.
Lidia, clean glasses please.
- The gift comes with a message.
- Oh, yeah. What's that?
He wants you to know
that it wasn't easy for him
to decide to kill you.
- Son of a bitch.
- What business is business.
You believe it?
You're both jammed.
If that is a sign from god,
I don't know what?
- Please.
- Shut your mouth.
You're gonna take Don Falcone
message from me.
You're gonna let him know
that you messed up.
And you're gonna let him know
that I'm coming for him.
Of course, you don't need
to be alive to tell him that.
- Tommy, do the honors.
- Wait...
Connor blew it.
Maroni is still alive.
This is flat.
Did you not hear me?
Maroni is still alive.
You got to get out of town.
And miss all the fun?
You knew.
You set him up?
I took the firing pins out
of the guns before you hid them.
A spin on a trick
I learned from Maroni.
But you could have
had Maroni dead.
True, but I still would've been
under Falcone's thumb.
And that has grown intolerable.
No,
I'd much rather Maroni be alive.
And out for blood.
Alas, Officer Dougherty.
She's gonna wonder
where you went.
Perhaps a letter.
You could say goodbye,
give her some advice.
Something that might lead her
to make better choices
in the future.
Chief!
Place is empty
but there's something you should see.
You see anything
that connects to Barbara?
Maybe she was never here.
She was here.
I can still smell her perfume.
Hey, we're gonna find this guy,
but you need to prepare yourself...
That we might not be
in time to save her.
- That is not an option.
- It's the most likely option!
- Hello?
- Detective Gordon?
I assume you're the one
who triggered the alarm.
You son of a bitch.
Where's Barbara?
With me, of course.
- If you've hurt her...
- She's as safe as milk.
Safer than she ever was
when she was with you.
What the hell does that mean?
She doesn't need
your protection, Jim.
Fact is, she never did.
- See you around.
- Wait...
- He was driving.
- To Tahiti, if he's smart.
There was a noise, right?
A thumping,
like he was going over a bridge.
You know, I heard a, a horn.
Like a train horn.
Okay, so, which bridge has a train?
Damn...
Whitecross.
But that's the upstate train.
Upstate?
That's where our parent's live.
Barbara, please.
What's happening?
What's happening is your daughter
is finally waking up.
Please.
Barbara,
we're doing this for you.
Jim?
Barbara.
What are you doing here?
You're not supposed to be here.
Where is he?
Drop it.
Drop the knife or I'll shoot.
Just an ounce of pressure
and she'll spilt right open up.
I don't want that.
Do you want that?
It's gonna all right, Barbara.
It's gonna all right.
If you care about this woman
you have never would
have come after me.
- I loved her more than you ever did.
- Drop the knife.
It won't be me to slit her throat.
Detective, that's gonna be you.
- Drop it.
- Jim, please.
Just leave us alone.
Hey, jerk-o!
Barbara? Barbara.
- He's dead?
- Yeah, he's dead.
It's gonna be okay.
Look at me, Barbara?
Alfred, I never ask you...
How it was yesterday,
seeing Reggie?
Not really an experience
I'd care to repeat, Master Bruce.
But then again, the Reggie
I knew died years ago.
Alfred,
I haven't been honest with you.
After you were hurt...
Selina and I went looking for Reggie.
We found him.
Did she know?
He didn't jump or fall.
Selina pushed him.
And why did she do that?
Reggie was sent here by a man
named Sid Bunderslaw.
Bunderslaw works
for Wayne Enterprises.
Reggie gave us the name,
but said,
he was gonna tell Bunderslaw
about what we were doing.
I see.
And the rest?
The charity ball presumably
to have access to Mr. Bunderslaw.
Selina stole the key
to his office safe.
I went there today. It was empty.
But Bunderslaw
was waiting for me.
- What did he do? What did he do?
- Nothing. Nothing!
But he said,
that my father and grandfather
knew about the illegal things
that the company was doing
and chose...
They chose to stay quiet.
Your father was a good man.
I know.
But even good man have secrets.
Congratulations. You're a hero.
It won't last. Tomorrow they'll
go back to hating me.
Well, then I'll remind them.
Yesterday, you were trying to help.
I couldn't hear it. I'm sorry.
I would never try
to change you, Jim.
Your sense of mission
that's part of what I love about you.
I thought it was
my devastating good looks.
It's a joke.
I was scared.
Scared that Barbara would get hurt
and you would blame yourself
for protecting me first
and then whatever
we had would die.
It wasn't heroic. It was selfish.
Lee, I love you.
Not her.
If I had it to do again,
I'd still protect you first.
What'd you do?
I grabbed a knife by the blade.
Of course, you did.
Let me see.
Miss Kringle,
are you okay?
I got a letter
from Officer Dougherty.
He left town.
"Don't wait around for me.
Go have some fun
and maybe I'll give you a call
when I get back..."
Couldn't even tell me to my face.
I mean,
why do I keep picking creeps?
Sometimes with men you need
to read between the lines.
Sometimes with men
you need a drink.
Good day, Mr. Nygma.
Read between the lines.
Everybody listen up.
We just got wind
of three separate attacks
on Falcone businesses
in different parts of town.
Word is...
It's Maroni.
As of right now,
all leaves are canceled
and all units are called in
for active duty.
We're in a shooting war, people.