GORDON: Previously on Gotham...
You can trust me.
We don't work for you
and we don't work with you.
Your captain says otherwise.
GORDON: So Penguin's guys are gonna beat
and torture their way through the city.
Get off of him.
You better pray.
I can clean up your mess
on this one, Harvey.
- It has to be a trap.
- (MUFFLED SCREAMING)
Hey! Got him!
Oh, no, Patel.
SELINA: The Demonz.
They have a chop shop across town.
- Let's hit it.
- (GROANS)
BARBARA: We've got a business to run.
NYGMA: I came here with Grundy,
to make some money
to get me smart again.
I'm looking for the person
in charge here.
You're looking at her.
Hey, go get the doc.
Fight!
(GROANS)
Grundy fight now?
Yes!
Yes! Grundy, Ed's best friend. (LAUGHS)
MALE ANNOUNCER: And now,
the most hated man in Gotham.
The Penguin.
(CROWD BOOING)
(IMITATING PENGUIN)
I'm so happy to be here.
You love me, I knew you loved me.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
You don't love me?
You don't love me? You've asked for it.
I'm going to sic my lackeys onto you.
My hoods and the GCPD.
Get 'em, boys.
Get 'em.
You work for Penguin.
NYGMA: You gotta do what I want
or they're gonna enter your homes
and terrorize your families.
Get 'em.
You do what I say.
CROWD: (CHANTING)
Grundy! Grundy! Grundy!
Grundy! Grundy!
(ROARS)
Now, you leave me alone, you monster.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
(CHOKING)
- Stupid lame bird brain.
- CROWD: Bird brain!
He'll never learn.
You can't mess with The Narrows.
(ALL CHEERING)
It is time,
for the main event,
a title defense.
No refs, no rules.
CROWD: No rules.
Our challenger, Mr. Murderface.
Yeah!
(CROWD BOOING)
And our champeen,
straight from the slaughter swamp.
- It's Solomon Grundy.
- (CROWD CHEERING)
They really ate it up tonight.
(LAUGHS)
I think they hate Penguin
almost as much as I do.
You know what, I may or may not
find a cure for you
but at the rate you're going
you may not have a chance.
What does that mean?
You don't just have
these people laughing,
you have them ready for a fight.
- So?
So what happens when Penguin
hears about all this?
Well, let that bird waddle in here,
I have Grundy.
I'm gonna be fine.
And what about them? Your fans?
Not my problem.
Ed, you put yourself on
the front line of something.
You can't just bail
when fighting starts.
Okay, Doctor, if you would like
to stop hiding from your past
and do some leading, you go right ahead.
- It's not what I'm here for.
- Well then, case closed.
Neither of us are willing
to put our necks out.
(BELL DINGS)
(CROWD SHOUTING)
(GROANS)
(YELLS)
TABITHA: Hey, Butch.
Yeah! Yeah!
Hey, Butch.
CROWD: Oh!
(CROWD CHEERING)
- (BONES CRACKING)
- (GROANING)
(CROWD GASPING)
(SCREAMS)
ALL: Stop hitting yourself,
stop hitting yourself!
Stop hitting yourself,
stop hitting yourself.
Stop hitting yourself.
I love this. (LAUGHS)
I love it!
Congratulations, Captain Gordon.
A promotion?
Harvey Bullock is captain
of Gotham Central.
Bullock's lost the rank and file, Jim.
That debacle in The Narrows,
teaming up with Penguin's goons?
Sending cops into The Pyg's trap.
You know, he's a disgrace.
What does that make you?
- Excuse me?
- Last time I checked,
you signed over the entire GCPD
to Penguin, wholesale.
What does he think of this?
Well, perhaps I've earned
that kind of cynicism, Jim.
But I wanna assure you
with hand on heart
that this has nothing to do
with Mr. Cobblepot.
- I won't take Harvey's job.
- Someone is going to,
and trust me, none of our
other candidates share
your misgivings about Penguin.
Why don't you just take it with you?
When you decide, all you have to do
is sign on the dotted line.
And you'll be the new captain
of Gotham Central.
DEMONZ BOSS: Nobody steals
from the Demonz, Mr. Penguin.
Why do I pony up for a license
if some crook
who can just swoop in
and rip off our swag?
Your swag might as well have
been a lollipop in a baby's hand.
You admit it.
She admits it, Mr. Penguin.
Oswald, what say we resolve
this like professionals?
The ladies and I will take out
the rest of these so called Demonz
and split their goods with you 50/50.
DEMONZ BOSS: Uncivilized is what
these girls are.
Outside the bounds
of a proper criminal society.
- (WHISPERS)
- (SHOUTS) What?
Repeat that for my guests.
Uh...
Ed Nygma, who owes his life
to Mr. Cobblepot's mercy,
is repaying that generosity by aping
his benefactor in a crude
commedia dell'arte.
What?
He's making fun of me
in a clown show in The Narrows!
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
(LAUGHING)
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
Pretty funny,
the Riddler's doing a Penguin act.
(CHOKES)
PENGUIN: That is not his name.
His name is Ed. Plain, dumb, Ed.
And you don't know him,
so you don't get to laugh.
Well, thank you, Oswald,
for clearing our account.
Not cleared, Babs.
The debt you owe him, you now owe me.
Of course, what will it be?
Seeing as you love a good laugh,
I would like you to go
to The Narrows
and see Ed's act for yourself.
Then I would like you to bundle him up
and bring him back to me by nightfall!
We're not your toadies.
(LAUGHS) Dear child,
what was that you said?
What do we get if we bring you Nygma?
Very well.
In exchange, I will not set every
criminal in this city after you.
I will not let them cut out
your eyes and feed 'em to you
along with your ears and then your noses
and then your tongues.
That is what you get.
- Acceptable?
- Yes, Oswald, that is acceptable.
Ladies.
Mr. Penn will put you in contact
with my Narrows informer.
If those three do not have
Ed in hand promptly,
you will go down there
and burn them all to cinders.
What about feeding them their eyes
and all that?
Trust me, it's a great idea.
But far too messy to be practical.
BARBARA: So give me the scoop
on this Cherry's joint.
SELINA: It's mainly crazy prize fights.
Chainsaw matches and stuff.
Well, back in the day,
we'd settle our beefs in the ring.
Winner takes all.
The code of The Narrows.
Right, well, I want to get in, grab Ed,
deliver him to his doom
and then go find a martini.
Okay?
Hello? Earth to Tabby?
Sorry, thinking about
getting my hands on him.
BARBARA: Yeah, as much as I hate doing
Penguin's dirty work,
this job is like
a little dream come true.
TABITHA: Gonna be Ed's nightmare.
Aren't we worried about him
setting a trap though?
He's a genius.
Well, word is, Ed lost a step
when Penguin put him on ice.
But, we should be ready for anything.
(IMITATING PENGUIN) You insist
on persisting in this misbehavior.
You leave me no choice,
but to scold you.
You've asked for it!
I'm going to sic my lackeys upon you.
Get 'em, boys, get 'em.
ALL: Grundy! Grundy! Grundy!
Grundy! Grundy!
- Grundy! Grundy!
- (GRUNDY ROARS)
Butch?
(CROWD CHEERING)
(OPPONENT SCREAMING)
(ROARS)
(OPPONENT WHIMPERING)
ALL: Stop hitting yourself!
Stop hitting yourself!
Butch, it's Butch.
Do you know what this means?
Yeah, it means you owe me
an apology for electrocuting me.
(ALL CHEERING)
I gotta find a way to go talk to him.
Have fun.
Tell him, it was nothing personal
when I shot him in the head.
Wow, I have got to know
what is up with this outfit.
(INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Could've sworn we had a job to do here.
ALL: Grundy! Grundy!
Good morning, Harv.
- Where have you been?
- Sorry, got stuck in traffic.
What you got there?
It's the Bullet Hole Club today.
These are the slugs they pulled
from the wounded cops
in The Narrows raid.
It was the Pyg that set the trap.
But I was the one who sent
those cops in.
Yeah, you did.
But now we gotta move on,
and we gotta catch the Pyg
before he can hurt somebody else.
Yeah.
You're right.
- Captain Bullock, Detective.
- What's the word, Lucius?
The word is "absence," as in
all of Professor Pyg's crime scenes
demonstrate a marked absence
of useful physical evidence.
- How is that possible?
- HARVEY: He's a loony.
But a crafty one.
We have to dig deeper,
try and get ahead of whatever
he's planning.
I'm at your disposal.
Hey, Jim, uh,
about the Bullet Hole Club today.
I'd really appreciate it
if you could be there, too.
- It would just help me a lot if...
- Of course.
I knew you had my back, partner.
Of course, Harv, I got your back.
LUCIUS: The Bullet Hole Club?
GORDON: Cops shot in the line of duty.
- New members joining today.
- How does that work?
It's unofficial,
little ceremony in a bar.
Commanding officer hands them
the bullet they were shot with.
This batch of cops were wounded
in Pyg's trap.
And Harvey has to give them
their bullets?
Yeah, including the officer he shot.
No wonder he wants a friend there.
Yeah, no wonder.
Leave it to Ed Nygma
to find a way to turn his idiocy
into a tool for revenge.
And everything was running so tidily.
Now I have nothing but headaches.
No one appreciates how hard
it is to be a crime lord.
I did actually spend my childhood
being raised by one.
My very point.
In fact, I thought we would
have lunch together
and talk over the vagaries
of this capricious calling.
I'd love to help,
but I have to see the caterer
for the orphanage fundraiser.
Of course, can't expect you
to be at my beck and call.
You need a different source
of relaxation, Oswald.
You need chickens.
I'm sorry?
Do you remember my father's chickens?
(CHUCKLES) I seem to recall
the Don's predilection for poultry.
He understood that life
couldn't just be about business.
When his troubles were greatest,
he spent time with his birds.
You think I need chickens?
An interest outside the business.
Give it some thought.
We can talk about it when I get back.
Chickens.
Chick, chick, chickens.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(BOYS LAUGHING)
Boy, come here this instant.
What do you think you're doing?
You cannot do things like that.
Your enemies will know it was you.
CROWD: (CHANTING)
Grundy! Grundy! Grundy! Grundy!
(SOFTLY) Butch.
(SIGHS)
Oh, you're alive.
Huh?
Oh, Butch.
What happened to you?
(GROWLS)
Guess who?
Psycho killer stalker?
Got it in one.
Please, if you were going to pop me,
you would've done it already.
(GRUNTS)
Oh. That felt good.
I've been waiting
a long time to do that.
Other cheek?
I'm good, thanks.
So what are you doing
down here, Barbara?
This is a low rent neighborhood for you.
Yeah, if it wasn't for Penguin,
you wouldn't catch me dead
- in a place like this.
- Oh.
You're working as Penguin's flunky?
That suits you.
Yes and you seem to be thriving
with your current life choices.
We don't all make decisions
based on what it can get us.
There are other people in the world.
Wow. Sexy and self-righteous.
What does Jim think of this new you?
Jim who?
Well, I have to go see a man
about a kidnapping,
but this has been interesting.
Toodles, poodle.
Kidnapping. Oh, crap.
SELINA: You play
a great Penguin, mister.
Yeah. Sure, sure, thanks, kid.
Oh, crud.
(THUDS)
I thought you were supposed to be smart.
Relax, Jim, no one followed me.
I have Oswald wrapped around my finger.
If you have such a good grip on him,
explain that.
Why would he want me promoted?
What's his plan?
SOFIA: Oswald has nothing
to do with this.
The Commissioner and the Mayor
can feel the winds changing
and they want to be out
ahead of it before it blows.
It was you, you put them up to this.
You must've made a hell
of a contribution to get the Mayor
to defy Penguin.
No contribution necessary, Jim.
Just the Falcone name
and everything that it implies.
Well, I won't do it. Not like this
and not at Harvey's expense.
Harvey is weak.
How much longer do you plan
on propping him up
and how many more cops need
to die because of his incompetence?
I need to go and you need
to stop pretending
like you're not taking that job.
I'm not pretending.
So you say, Jim, but I don't see you
rushing to throw that piece of paper
in the trash.
Come see me tonight,
after you take command
and we'll celebrate.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGING)
Revenge is never as simple
as a mere tit for a tat.
Revenge must be specific in nature.
Now when you imagine revenge
against your two juvenile tormentors,
what do you see?
(PENGUIN CHUCKLES)
That might be a little overly ambitious.
We must be crafty.
For instance, friendship can be
an especially deadly tactic.
How do you think you might use
friendship to drive a wedge
between your two antagonists?
"They're both flunking math."
And you, I imagine,
are very good at math?
Excellent, tell me more.
Psst! Psst!
GIRL: Hey, Martin.
Thank you.
(SCHOOL BELL RINGS)
GIRL: What's wrong, Martin?
Who did that to you?
Hey.
Are you picking on Martin?
BOY: You like that dummy so much,
go play with him.
He's not a dummy.
- Yes, he is.
- (INDISTINCT SHOUTING)
Yeah, get him, get him!
PENGUIN: Well done.
Feels good, does it not?
Minions are so much better than friends.
"But I'm your..."
The greatest friend I ever had
turned into my worst enemy.
Shun friendship.
You and I, we're more than friends.
We're conspirators.
Peekaboo.
(MUFFLED PROTESTING)
Well, look at the little go-getter.
Yeah, well, you and Tabby
decided to freak out.
So someone had to be the professional.
Teenagers, Ed, don't you love 'em?
Do you remember anything, Butch?
Do you remember anything about us?
Doesn't this mean anything to you?
(DOOR OPENS)
- Ed?
- TABITHA: Butch.
Tell zombie Butch to back off.
Grundy kill everyone!
Butch, Ed is not your friend.
Rip 'em to pieces.
- (GROWLS)
- TABITHA: Butch!
All right, everybody, just take it easy.
Selina, what are you doing
with these two?
Looking for trouble.
Well, you found plenty of it
trying to take Ed.
- Let him go.
- You're such a bleeding heart, Lee.
I thought you changed, but turns out
(CLICKS TONGUE)
- you just got a new hairdo.
- (GROWLS)
Code of The Narrows,
code of The Narrows.
Let's settle it in the ring,
champion against champion.
The winner would take Ed.
So, your best fighter
against my fighter?
(SCOFFS)
Yeah, let's do that.
NYGMA: (IMITATING PENGUIN)
Honk-honk, honk-honk.
You Narrows trash have been very,
very naughty.
You've been hiding someone from me.
Don't listen to him, he's not my friend.
No, Ed, no one's gonna save you.
(GROANS) Grundy.
No one can save you. Save me.
Help, help, save me.
(CROWD CHEERING)
(GRUNDY ROARS)
Ladies and Grundy fans.
Tonight is a special edition
of Fight Night.
A good old Narrows grudge match.
Winner takes me.
(LAUGHS)
And featuring your champion,
Solomon Grundy.
Versus Tabby.
The tigress. (MEOWS)
- Tabs, I know this was my idea...
- No, it's okay.
Butch is still in there, I know he is.
He loves me too much to hurt me.
Grundy kill!
Babe, I love your faith,
but I really think you should take this.
No, he won't hurt me,
I'll just choke him out, no problem.
(BELL DINGS)
(CROWD SHOUTING)
Tabitha and Grundy were lovers,
before he got this way.
What if he goes easy on her?
Grundy will win,
not that it makes a difference anyway.
What does that mean?
The Penguin wants Ed,
he's gonna get him.
Come on, Butch,
I know you could never forget me.
You're still in there, I know it.
Grundy.
(GRUNDY ROARS)
BARBARA: Tabby, get up! Come on, Tabs.
Come on, get up!
Get up. Tabby, get up.
- No! No, Butch! No! Butch!
- Tabs!
(GROANS)
TABITHA: Hey, Butch.
Tabby?
CROWD: Oh!
Butch?
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Come on, buddy.
FEMALE BARTENDER:
Are you Detective Gordon?
Yeah.
Harvey said as how
I should give this to you.
Said you'd know what to do with it.
When was he here?
A couple of hours ago,
before you all started coming in here.
Thanks.
(SIGHS)
(CROWD SHOUTING)
Come on, Butch. Come on, baby, wake up.
- Come on, Butch, come on, baby.
- Tabitha, we gotta go, now.
Ladies, let's am-scray.
- Come on.
- I'll come back for you, Butch.
What happened to this
code of The Narrows?
Give me up, Barbara.
You're getting out of here empty-handed.
In the name of Penguin,
everybody back the hell off.
Look at that, cavalry.
BRIDGIT: Not so fast.
Boss gave you a deadline.
- You missed it.
- So what?
We got Ed,
we are literally champions here.
What you are is
four courses of barbecue.
Crispy skin.
NYGMA: Grundy, wake up.
Grundy, get up, big guy. Come on.
(FIRE CRACKLING)
Grundy kill!
(GRUNDY WHIMPERING)
What's the matter, gruesome?
Afraid of fire?
Come on, Bridgit, don't do this,
you're from The Narrows.
Yeah, and I couldn't be happier
to be out.
Penguin's right about this place.
It's a sewer.
Only way to kill the stink
is to burn it.
Hey, Firefly, you're the only thing
that stinks around here.
(LAUGHS)
(GROANS)
You know what you've done?
Firefly is Penguin's enforcer.
And who is the one that
got Firefly down here, Cherry?
She informed on Ed to Penguin.
What?
(PANICKED CHATTERING)
Shut up.
This is my club, it's my turf.
You guys just do what you're told
like the scum you are.
They're the ones that are the problem.
They work for Penguin.
CROWD: Oh!
I would like to announce
that we just quit working for Penguin.
(ALL CHEERING)
Whoo!
Well, they sure love their
cold-blooded murder down here, huh?
Yeah, well, we better split
before they decide they want more.
Hey, it's okay, big guy, Fire Lady,
she can't hurt you.
GRUNDY: Grundy safe.
Where were you, Harvey?
Hey, Jim.
I was just having a
little drinkie-poo.
Why don't you join me?
- Not right now.
- Come on, Jim,
don't be like that, come on, sit down
and have a drink with me.
Those cops were waiting for you.
Yeah, to spit in my face.
If that's what they wanted to do,
you owed it to them to be there.
You stand in front of them,
look each one in the eye.
If you'd have done that,
maybe you couldn've
gotten their respect.
I don't deserve their respect.
Jim, I shot Officer Patel,
what the hell was I supposed to do?
Stand in front of her and hand her
the bullet that I shot her with
that came from my gun?
That's the job.
Take responsibility for what happens
to your cops, that's the job.
Oh.
So now,
you're telling me what the job is?
Yeah.
Today, Jim, I just couldn't do the job.
So I sent you, because I knew you could.
It's not good enough.
Not today.
They needed you there.
Well, ain't nothing
that I can do about it now.
You got a pen?
For what?
Harvey Bullock,
you are relieved of duty.
As of this moment, I'm assuming
the Captaincy of Gotham Central.
Well, well,
look who finally got
what he always wanted.
But what I'm wondering is,
what did you have to do to get it?
- All I did was my job, same as...
- Nothing in Gotham is free.
Captain Gordon.
You just better hope you can pay up
when your bill's due.
And it'll come due.
Huh?
Now you try.
Ah. You've met Martin, I see.
Shh. He's practicing.
No, it's...
Upward, Martin, so that way you drive
the blade under the ribs
- and into the heart.
- Oswald.
Entirely theoretically speaking,
of course.
- Mr. Penn?
- Urgent matters, Mr. Cobblepot.
It seems that Miss Kean
and her associates have failed
to retrieve Mr. Nygma.
- Did you dispatch Firefly?
- I did.
And Ms. Firefly was herself
in turn, disabled.
(LOUDLY) What?
- There's more.
- Yes!
The mayor at his own discretion
has seen fit to promote
Detective Gordon to the rank of Captain.
That is, um...
That is quite a lot
to go awry in one day.
Very good, Mr. Cobblepot.
You see, Oswald,
business is not the end-all of life.
There are other rewards to be had.
Companionship, peace of mind.
Friendship.
Oh. I have to get back to the estate,
I still have so much to do
for the fundraiser.
Will you be joining me later for dinner?
I think not.
- Martin needs some more practice.
- Okay.
Martin.
Remind me.
What did we learn today?
What did we learn about friendship?
Exactly.
Sometimes if you're not very careful,
friendship can blind you
to what is staring you
right in the face.
NYGMA: "Hey, Firefly.
"You're the only thing
that stinks around here."
I get melodramatic under pressure.
How are you feeling, big fella?
Grundy confused.
Yeah, tell me about it.
What's with them?
They're, uh...
They're acknowledging their new leader.
Well, like I said, they love you.
Uh, Lee, I'm supposed to be
the stupid one.
You heal their children,
you stitch up their warriors.
You've slain a fire breathing monster
and you've helped topple the queen.
This is your turf now.
No, no, no, I am not a leader.
Okay, well, if you don't do it,
somebody else will.
Probably worse than Cherry.
Where do I start?
I don't know, just make 'em happy,
give 'em something to cheer for.
Drinks on the house!
(ALL CHEERING)
Good move.
SOFIA: Why, Captain Gordon,
you came to celebrate after all.
I'm not here to celebrate.
What's wrong?
I made you captain, didn't I?
You made me?
Is that what you think?
Jim.
You can toy with Penguin all you want.
But I am not your puppet.
No, you're not. You're my partner.
Your partner?
I just stuck a knife
in my partner's back.
A mercy killing, if you ask me.
Grow up.
You wanted a gangster to help you
get rid of Penguin.
This is what that help looks like.
Harvey had to go.
I don't need your help anymore.
I think it's time you left Gotham.
I'm not going anywhere, Jim.
I came to restore the Falcone name
and that's exactly
what I'm going to do.
So, do you want to come in
and celebrate, Captain?
I think I'll stay out here
where I can breathe.