Previously on Gotham...
LOEB: My best wishes to
Commissioner Essen.
Welcome back, Jim.
I don't know how
you pulled this off,
but I'm glad you did.
BRUCE: Sometimes the right way
is also the ugly way.
ESSEN: There's been an incident
at Arkham Asylum.
Six inmates have escaped.
Barbara Kean
was one of them.
Oh, my God.
The world sees
criminal lunatics.
I see brilliance.
Gotham will tremble
before you.
BRUCE: "I beg of you, my son,
please choose happiness.
"Unless you feel a calling.
A true calling."
THEO:
Mr. Mayor,
you want to know
what I really am?
JAMES (muffled):
Yes, sir.
Shall I tell you?
Please, please.
(sobs)
At heart...
I'm an ardent student
of human nature.
Fascinating paradox,
we are.
So wise, and yet so foolish.
So brave, and yet so fearful.
For instance,
this is a glass jar.
Inside of it is a hairy spider.
A tarantula, I guess,
but I'm no expert.
(sobs)
In a minute, I'm gonna
open that little hatch
in the front of your box, I'm
gonna drop the spider inside,
and I'm gonna close it.
(sobs)
That's choice A.
Choice B:
I open the hatch,
you speak to your
lovely secretary Maggie
on the telephone,
you tell her you've run away
with some woman,
you'll be sending written
instructions shortly.
So which is it,
choice A or choice B?
Choice B, please.
Please, choice B.
The telephone.
Of course.
It's human nature.
See?
There is no spider.
But if you don't do what I ask,
you'll wish there was one.
Why are you doing this to me?
Don't fret so.
You're part of a great endeavor.
A great cleansing.
Monsters are coming, Mr. Mayor.
Monsters.
Who will
cleanse this city
in blood and fire.
(urgent chatter, phones ringing)
What the hell is this?
(man screams outside)
"Where is Mayor James?
Who is his mystery lover?"
No one cares
who the mayor is banging!
(man screams outside)
You can do better
than this, people.
Now go out and get me
some headlines, damn it!
(man screams outside)
(people murmuring)
Yeah. All right,
all right.
Oh, my God.
(man screams)
(body thuds)
Perfect.
Next.
Mr. X.
(muffled whimpering)
(laughs)
(grunts)
Uh, a little to the right.
Okay, that's the spot.
(man screams)
(body thuds)
(crowd gasps in distance)
Perfect.
What shall we do
with the... spare?
Ooh!
I know.
(sighs)
Aaron.
Would you kindly?
(man screams)
(body thuds,
crowd gasps in distance)
"Maniax!"
(laughs)
Now that's a headline.
(cackles)
You all know
what we're facing here.
48 hours ago,
six criminally insane inmates
were busted out
of Arkham Asylum.
Yesterday, four of those inmates
broke into Yellen Shipyard,
kidnapped seven workers,
then dropped them off the roof
of the Gotham Gazette.
As of now,
we still have no leads
on the person or persons
behind the breakout.
Jim Gordon's lead. Jim.
These are our targets.
Jerome Valeska, 18 years old.
Matricide.
Arnold Dobkins,
schizophrenic.
Poisoner,
rapist.
Aaron Helzinger.
Killed his entire family
with his bare hands.
Robert Greenwood.
Killed and then ate
a dozen women.
Barbara Kean.
Killed her parents.
We're gonna work this
in groups of four.
I'll hand out assignments
throughout the day.
Alvarez is
my coordinating officer.
Any questions?
Let's get to work.
Fine job yesterday, gentlemen.
We opened big.
The whole city knows
your name now.
So, bravo. Let's give
ourselves a round of applause.
Now that we have
Gotham's attention,
it's time for the Maniax
to make a grand entrance.
Wasn't that it?
That was the overture.
Now the audience is hushed,
expectant.
The curtain rises...
Then what happens?
Oh, then we
confront Gothamites
with their most
primal fears.
Take from them all they
hold dear and sacred.
And then what happens?
Why, then,
we offer them salvation.
And then they are ours.
Let's get busy, man.
Patience.
First, you gentlemen
need to learn
a little stagecraft.
Stagecraft?
You're going to be on TV.
You have to present yourselves
with style and vigor.
Dobkins, say "Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen."
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
Again, with a smile.
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
(sighs) You.
(clears throat)
Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen!
Not bad.
Sinister and authoritative.
Never mind.
Jerome.
(clears throat)
Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening!
Very good.
Boyishly charming.
(cackles)
The laugh is fabulous.
Use that.
(whip cracks)
JAMES:
Ow!
Ow! Ow!
(women laughing)
(laughing)
BARBARA:
Now me.
Ow!
I am so glad that
you two are getting along,
but we're
a little busy here,
so if you could
leave the poor mayor alone...
We're bored.
Yeah. Why do the boys
get to have all the fun?
Your time is coming.
I told you.
You haven't killed him,
have you?
No, I don't think so.
(muffled groaning)
Nope. Hanging in there.
When?
When is my time coming?
Soon.
Very soon.
Why don't you tell me
about James Gordon.
What do you want to know?
It's hard to believe.
My father's been
sneaking down here for years,
and I never even knew about it.
That makes two of us,
doesn't it?
Wait.
Let's just think
about this.
Are you certain you want
to turn that bloody thing on?
Of course I'm certain.
Have you thought it through,
Master Bruce?
This computer could contain
all my father's research
into Wayne Enterprises.
All this time, I've been
looking for a smoking gun,
and here it is.
Exactly. A smoking gun.
Now, guns are for grown-ups,
aren't they?
That's a metaphor, Alfred,
not an argument.
(computer whirring, beeping)
Here it is.
It's working!
What are you...
What are you doing?!
Alfred, stop!
No, what are you
doing, Alfred?!
Alfred, stop it!
It's ruined!
What's wrong with you?!
Why would you do that?!
Answer me!
It had to be done, Master Bruce!
This was the key
to exposing Wayne Enterprises.
Everything that
I've worked for,
everything my... everything
my dad worked for is now gone!
Because of you!
If I'd known what was down here,
I would have never
helped get you in.
I mean, look around you.
Look, look. Liters of blood.
A bulletproof vest
with two slugs in it!
Guns, weapons!
I mean, whatever's
on that computer
probably killed your father,
and I'll be damned
if I see you suffer
the same fate,
Master Bruce.
(sniffles)
I'm trying
to protect you.
(sobs softly)
I'm trying to keep you safe.
I want you to go.
Look, I know that you're...
No.
that you're upset, you...
Alfred.
I want you to go
and never come back,
do you understand me?
You're fired.
Very well, Master Bruce.
As you wish.
(footsteps receding)
Ooh! Shiny.
(laughs)
Give that back.
I saw it first.
No, you didn't.
I said give it back.
Make me, you little brat.
DOBKINS:
Ooh.
Ooh. (chuckles)
JEROME:
Your samurai skills
are excellent Greenwood San,
but they are nothing
compared to me.
(chain saw buzzing)
Prepare to die!
Rum, rum, rum! (laughs)
That's enough! That's good.
I tried
to stop them.
Boys, we're a team.
We don't fight
amongst ourselves.
Yeah, we're a team, boys.
And I'm the captain.
Captain of my foot.
I've murdered
a dozen women.
Terrorized the city.
What have you done?
Chop up your mommy?
Everybody has to start
somewhere.
See, I have vision
and ambition and brains.
You're just
a nutty old cannibal.
How many people can you eat
before that shtick gets old?
I could eat one more.
THEO:
I can see we're gonna have
to resolve this one
once and for all.
You all know
this game,
right?
Oh, love it.
Who wants to be
the boss?
Ladies first.
(gun clicks)
(chuckles)
Hey, Greenwood,
what's the secret
to good comedy?
(gun clicks)
Timing.
And what's courage?
(gun clicks)
Grace under pressure.
And...
...who's the boss?
(gun clicks)
I'm the boss.
(laughing)
I believe you
are, Jerome.
I believe you are.
Arigato, sensei.
Whoo! Hee!
(music playing)
Thank you.
Four lunatics and Barbara?
Brother, you got no luck.
I told you civilian life
was better, didn't I?
Yeah, you did.
Actually, that's kind of
why I'm here.
Yeah?
Yeah.
SCOTTY:
What are you doing here?
Jim, you remember
Scotty, my girlfriend.
Fiancée.
Right, my fiancée.
Yeah, Scotty, good to see you.
Relax, honey bun.
We're just talking.
Oh, like hell you are.
He's gonna ask you
to come back to work.
He didn't ask
me anything.
We're just having a chat.
Oh, is that right?
Is that why you're here,
Detective?
Just to have a chat?
No, no. She's right.
Harvey, I need your help.
The case is a bear.
We're short-handed, and, uh, I
was thinking maybe you could...
He has a life.
The answer is no.
He is not coming back.
BULLOCK:
Hon.
I'm telling him no.
But it's like she said,
I have a life.
I get it.
I'm happy for you.
Just a thought.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
Jim, one last thing.
One last thought
from your Uncle Harvey.
These Maniax killed
a bunch of people
from the shipyard, right?
Yellen Shipyard, yeah.
Why there?
They could've gone anywhere,
killed anyone.
But these lunatics specifically
chose that shipyard. I...
wonder why.
Good to see you.
Scotty.
GORDON:
Yeah. Call you back.
Commissioner!
Tell me something good. Please.
Harvey isn't coming back.
That's not good.
But he did suggest a lead
that panned out nicely.
Turns out, the Maniax
stole a refueling truck
from the shipyard yesterday.
Why wasn't it reported?
It was one of over a hundred
service vehicles.
Took a while to track down
the entire fleet.
But when we did,
we found that one was missing.
Fully loaded with gasoline.
You get a license plate?
And a description
of the vehicle.
Put out an APB.
God, I'm so glad
you're back, Jim.
Me, too.
Wish I could say
the same for Bullock.
I-I can't believe
he's really gone.
He's a cop.
He was born to be a cop.
Not anymore. He's a happy man.
I didn't have it in me
to push him.
You ever think about that?
Walking away, I mean.
No.
You?
I did, for a long time.
But not anymore?
I've sat back and watched
all the corrupt, lazy men
buy their way into this job
and waste it.
Not me, Jim.
Not me.
A new day.
You're damn right.
I'd just like to say
it's been an honor
and a privilege to serve
you and your family, sir.
Thank you.
If you need any references,
I'll be happy to provide them.
Is that all
you're taking with you?
It's all I have, sir.
Right. Well, um...
Oh, dear, yes. I best be off.
I've got a train to catch.
Good-bye, sir.
Good-bye, Alfred.
Beg your pardon, sir?
I said good-bye.
Yes.
Good-bye, sir.
I spy with my little eye
something that is...
...yellow.
(chanting):
Score, Gotham, score!
We want more!
Hit 'em where it hurts
and knock 'em to the floor!
(whooping)
Yay, Gotham!
Oh. Hello, Ms. Kringle.
(door closes)
Hello, Mr. Nygma.
How's your day going?
(chuckles) Fine.
Um, question for you.
Y-Yes?
Um...
(laughs)
Did you know that
houseflies hum
in the key of F?
(sighs)
No.
(clears throat)
No, I-I did not know that.
Okay, then.
Well, uh... bye.
Bye.
Damn it!
We agreed you were
going to ask her out.
No, we didn't agree to ask her.
We agreed to think about
asking her.
But there's no point.
She doesn't like you.
NYGMA:
Maybe she'll like me.
You ever consider that?
I got confidence.
Ladies love that.
No, she won't like you.
She won't.
Go away.
Please, just go away!
Hey.
(cheerleaders cheering)
(horn honking)
Ooh!
(cheerleaders murmuring)
(sighs)
(cheerleaders screaming)
We got a sighting
of the stolen truck.
Yeavely Park.
(cheerleaders whimpering)
JEROME:
I want you all to know
this was a very difficult
decision for us.
It was between you and
a senior citizen bingo party.
In the end,
we decided
to skew a little younger.
Youth won the day.
Sorry.
Give me an "O"!
(cheerleaders whimpering)
(cheerleaders screaming)
I said give me a "O."
CHEERLEADERS:
"O."
JEROME:
Give me an "N."
CHEERLEADERS: "N."
Give me another "O"!
CHEERLEADERS: "O."
What does that spell?
"Oh, no!"
(cheerleaders screaming)
Do it! Do it! Do it!
Ready?
Okay!
(cheerleaders screaming)
This is so embarrassing.
Anyone got a light?
I do. I got...
(sirens approaching)
(tires screeching)
JEROME:
Stand your ground, boys.
They can't shoot at a bus.
Hold your fire!
Aaron, Greenwood, get
the truck started.
We're gonna blow
this barbecue.
Oh.
(gun clicks)
Light 'em up!
(Jerome cackling)
(cheerleaders screaming)
(cackling)
(engine starts)
(explosion in distance,
cheerleaders scream)
(cheerleaders sobbing)
Everybody okay?
Who broke you out,
Dobkins?
Gonna have to talk sooner
or later; tell me now.
I'm a victim here,
sir. I was coerced.
Abducted and coerced.
By who?
If I tell you that,
I got to get some
kind of guaran...
(silenced gunshots)
(man speaking indistinctly
over P.A.)
I understand you were just
trying to protect me.
But there's nothing...
nothing that you
can do to stop me
from carrying out
my father's work.
I know that now.
I don't want you to go, Alfred.
But you're either with me
or you're against me.
And if you're against me,
I don't have a choice.
I'm with you, Master Bruce.
I've always been with you.
But what you're doing
is tantamount to suicide.
This is big boy stuff.
You're too young;
you're not ready.
Then make me ready.
You-You've lived
a dangerous life,
and you survived.
So teach me.
Teach me how to do the same.
I'll do whatever it takes.
I'll train every day.
Yeah, well, you said that
before, didn't you?
That was before.
Now I know the truth.
And I know what I have to do.
I'll even go back to school
if you want.
School, even?
If I agree to help you,
to make you ready,
you must do exactly
as I say and when I say it
with no exceptions,
is that understood?
Understood.
But, in return, you
must fix that computer.
Fix it?
How on earth
am I gonna do that?
That's not my problem.
I'm not the one
who broke it.
High caliber, high velocity.
Judging by the size
of the wounds,
it was definitely shot
from some distance.
Someone knew how to shoot.
Who, damn it?
And why cheerleaders?
Where's the motive?
They didn't even ask
for a ransom.
They want headlines.
They want mass panic.
Well, they got it.
ESSEN: Yeah.
Let's see if we can't
I.D. that bullet.
Never know your luck.
(door opens, closes)
(sighs) Holding up?
Holding up.
Love you.
Likewise.
(door opens, closes)
("In a Sentimental Mood" by Duke
Ellington & John Coltrane plays)
Gin and tonic, please,
uh, governor.
Ice and a slice.
Nice place.
It is.
Been here before,
then, have you?
It's my regular spot.
Oh, right,
you're a local.
Nice.
Don't I know you?
Do you?
Yeah.
You're that Mr. Fox,
that scientific chap from
Wayne Enterprises, ain't you?
That is me.
Alfred Pennyworth.
Young Master Bruce Wayne's
guardian.
Ah, yes.
It's a funny old game
though, isn't it?
Coincidence, I mean,
me bumping into you like this.
I mean...
I was just
thinking about you.
Hmm.
Okay, Mr. Pennyworth,
I'll bite.
What were you
thinking about me?
Oh, no. "Alfred," please.
Please, "Lucius."
Lucius. Lucius.
You know...
I once knew this geezer
called Onslow
in the Isle of Dogs
in the East End of London.
Lairy little scallywag, he was.
He was, uh, too smart by half;
never trusted him.
Anyway, one day, Lucius,
he comes bowling up to me,
and he asks me to do him
this right iffy favor.
Oh, it doesn't matter
what it was.
The point being,
against my better judgment,
I agreed to do it.
But, Lucius, I told him,
I told him straight, I said,
"You let me down, Onslow,
I'll tuck you up, sunshine,
like a kipper."
He swears blind,
swears on his mother's grave
he'd never do such a thing,
but of course he did.
Couldn't help himself;
he let me down.
So I tucked him up.
Like a kipper.
What is a kipper?
It's a type of smoked fish.
Very nice with eggs
and brown toast for breakfast.
But what I learned
from Onslow is this.
There are two types of people
on this planet, you see.
Them you can trust...
and them you can't.
I cannot disagree.
Which kind are you?
Both kinds of people
would give you
the same answer,
wouldn't they?
Exactly.
Exactly right.
There lieth
the problem, Lucius.
You see, I need
to confide in you.
But I need to know
that you're trustworthy.
Perhaps I should decline
your confidence.
I don't like the sound
of these kippers.
Yeah, well, it's a bit late
for that, unfortunately.
I mean, it's you, after all,
Lucius, that created this mess
when you told young Master Bruce
that his dear old dead dad...
was a stoic.
Ah.
"Ah," exactly.
You see,
there's a problem.
I got no one else to turn to.
I have to confide in you.
I see.
Do you?
Let me just be
crystal clear about this.
If it turns out...
that I can't trust you,
I swear
on my mother's grave,
you, my old sausage...
...are a dead man.
I have only the best
intentions for Bruce Wayne.
Well, another gin and tonic
please, uh, governor.
And whatever this young man
is drinking, one for yourself.
How are you
at fixing computers?
(phone ringing)
Hey, Alvarez!
Yo.
Let ballistics know we got
a red ball for them, will you?
On it.
Gordon.
BARBARA:
Hello, Jim. It's Barbara.
Hi, Barbara.
How are you?
BARBARA:
Oh, me? I'm fabulous.
How are you?
I'm good. What's new?
Oh, Mr. Cool Guy, huh?
You must be so mad at me.
Listen to me.
If you turn yourself in,
I can help you.
(scoffs) How, Jim?
By taking me back to Arkham?
I don't think so.
You're sick.
Oh. Of course.
Everything's always my fault.
So typical.
Listen to me.
I know you, Barbara.
I know you.
You're a good, kind woman.
This isn't you.
(laughs)
Oh, you could always
make me laugh.
(laughing)
How do I look?
I need to talk to
Commissioner Essen right away.
It's an emergency.
Yeah, go ahead.
She's right upstairs.
Yo, Commish.
Yeah?
Heard you were looking for us.
(explosion, gunfire,
officers shouting)
(Kringle screams)
Barbara!
Don't move.
You're wrong about me, Jim.
I tried telling you,
but you never listen.
I'm listening now.
Yeah, sure you are. Now.
Come on.
Let's go talk this through, huh?
Oh, it's too late for that.
(Aaron yells)
Ow.
(thudding, grunting continues)
Aaron.
That's enough.
(groans)
I'm not sick. I'm free.
You don't get that.
I could explain it,
but you should probably
get back to work.
Who knows what went wrong
while you were gone?
(gasps)
(kisses)
(man grunts)
(gunfire, screaming continues
in distance)
(laughs)
(whistles)
Hell of a first week
you're having,
Commissioner.
I wish I could tell you
that things were gonna
get better for you.
They're not.
Here, bring that up here.
Get a better angle
of the room.
Why are you doing this?
To rule the world.
Blah, blah, blah.
But we'll settle
for some dead cops
and some good P.R.
(chuckles)
Kidding.
Yeah.
Whatever. I get it.
You're just crazy.
"Crazy"?
Look at me.
You can see I'm not crazy.
Very soon,
little man,
you will be dead.
And the world will go on
without you.
You'll be nothing.
No one will even
remember your name.
Mm.
No.
That is where you're wrong,
old lady.
We will leave a mark
on this city.
We will spread across it
like a virus.
Do you know why?
There's nothing more
contagious than laughter.
My line.
There's nothing
more contagious than laughter.
(laughs loudly)
That was strangely pleasant.
Do it again.
Oh!
That's gonna leave a mark.
(laughing)
You got me.
My turn.
(laughing)
(grunting)
♪ ♪
(sighs)
Lee?
Jim!
You hurt?
No. I... I-I was in my office,
and I heard gunfire and I hid.
Where were you?
Barbara was here.
She lured me away.
Essen!
(panting)
Hang on, Cap, hang on.
Boss, boss,
stay with me.
Breathe.
It's a new day...
Jim.
This is...
indeed broken.
I have a lot of
questions for you.
Ah, I imagine so.
Did my father tell
you everything?
Heavens no.
Your father,
he was a very private man.
He had to be.
I simply helped
with technical resources,
like this computer.
Do you know
what's on it?
No.
I didn't want to know,
to be honest.
But you can fix it?
Mm, I should think so.
But it is going
to take some time.
Well, um, thank you
for your help.
I loved your father.
I regret that I never
told him so.
I regret that
I didn't help him more.
Hand me the soldering iron,
will you?
Yeah.
(footsteps approaching)
Master Bruce?
What is it, Alfred?
Uh, how you doing,
Mr. Nygma?
I got you an aspirin.
Thank you.
Detective Gordon!
Bruce.
I heard the news. I...
I was worried
something happened to you.
I'm very relieved.
Me, too.
Th-The last time that we met,
I was... I was very hard on you.
I wanted to apologize.
You've been
a really good friend.
(helicopter whirring outside)
BULLOCK:
She was a good woman.
Good cop.
It's good to see you, but
you don't have to do this.
Let's not talk about it.
We are who we are, right?
No use fighting it.
What does Scotty say?
She'll understand.
Or she won't.
OFFICER:
Guys.
You need to see this.
I'm reporting live from
the scene of the GCPD massacre.
We have just obtained
video footage of the attack
recorded by
one of the assailants.
I want to warn
those of you watching,
what you're about to see
is very graphic.
Hello, Gotham City!
We're the Maniax.
And I'm Jerome, the shot caller
of our little gang.
We're here to spread
the message of wisdom and hope.
(man groaning)
(gunshot)
Some people have no manners.
You're all prisoners.
What you call sanity,
it's just a prison in your minds
that stops you from seeing
that you're
just little tiny cogs
in a giant absurd machine.
Wake up!
Why be a cog?
Be free like us.
(laughing):
Just remember, smile.
(laughing)
(sirens approaching)
Oh! Time to go.
But don't worry.
We'll be back very soon.
Hang on to your hats, folks.
'Cause you ain't seen
nothing yet!
(laughing)