Previously onGotham...
Valerie Vale, Gotham Gazette.
This isn't the first time
that a bounty hunter
has apprehended an escapee.
Is the GCPD incapable of handling
this threat themselves?
Your body is beginning to reject
the changes we made to your DNA.
How do I fix it?
Strange. He's the only one.
You remember Marv.
He's one of yours.
Hey, kid. Take it.
Keep feeding strays
and one's gonna follow you home.
While trapped in Indian Hill,
I was led to believe an unnamed group
had taken control of my company.
I want to talk face-to-face.
The information that I've gathered
will be sent to every newspaper
and television station in Gotham.
We caught a spy!
- Ivy!
- Marv.
No!
Ivy?
Alfred!
Bruce.
You wanted to talk?
Forgive me.
Better?
I know you.
I've seen you
at Wayne Enterprises events.
You've been inside of my home.
My name is Kathryn.
I represent the group
you've asked to speak with.
You didn't need to hurt Alfred.
He would not have permitted you
to meet with us alone.
You tried to kill me.
You were behind Indian Hill.
Hugo Strange was hired by you.
Is that why you're here, Bruce?
To ask questions
you already know the answers to?
Who are you?
What do you call yourselves?
Our name is unimportant.
Now, you made a threat.
Referring to evidence you'd uncovered
of our existence.
We would like to know what you found.
Nothing certain.
Until now.
A bluff.
Nicely played.
It wasn't just a bluff.
The more I studied
my company's doings,
the more there were things that could
only be explained by your existence.
Still, I had to know for sure.
- Now I do.
- And what now?
According to you,
we tried to kill you once.
I began all this because I wanted
to solve my parents' murder.
Six months ago, I concluded
your organization responsible.
- Have you changed your mind?
- No.
But there are other considerations.
Such as your own life?
The lives of those close to you?
You're here to make a deal.
What do you have to offer?
Wayne Enterprises.
You cannot give someone
what they already possess.
I'm not finished.
If I die, my shares will be turned
over to the federal government.
Investigators will comb
through every file.
Every asset.
Are you prepared
for that kind of scrutiny?
That would be unfortunate
but we would weather the storm.
- What else?
- The Wayne name still has meaning.
It's a symbol of light and hope.
For a group such as yours,
I could provide a useful distraction.
You are an impressive young man.
Still your offer is not sufficient.
We will also require that you cease
all investigation into our existence
and your parents' murder.
Any violation of that,
in the slightest...
and our agreement is void.
I need your answer now.
- I agree.
- I'm happy to hear that.
Needless to say,
you will not see me again.
Goodbye, Bruce.
Morning. Surprised to see me?
Not really. What do you want?
I have a proposition.
- Not interested.
- Oh, come on.
Think of it as a way to say I'm sorry
for handcuffing you to a car door.
Except I'm not!
Wow. So this is where you live.
Anyone considering a life
in bounty hunting should see this.
Preferably wearing a hazmat suit.
You don't bring women here, do you?
All right.
Fish Mooney.
Penguin's million dollar bounty.
I can help you get it.
Oh, see, now you're thinking,
a million dollars can buy me
a lot of Scotch.
But hey, when you're rich,
do everyone a favor,
spring for a maid, will you?
Or just fire-bomb the place
and be done with it.
- What's in it for you?
- A story.
That's it?
It shocks you that I love my job
and I want to be good at it?
Kind of.
Why not just bring her in yourself?
Why give me a million dollars?
Because I'm a bigger person than you.
And... because I couldn't find her.
You lost touch with your source.
The one working for Mooney.
I did not lose touch with my source.
I just have no way of contacting her.
She always found me.
Oh! Well, that's better.
It's a million dollars.
Don't be so damn lazy.
I mean, it's your job, right,
your specialty.
You find people.
You're a bounty hunter.
- Who's your source?
- So we have a deal?
No handcuffing this time.
Who's your source?
She's a petty thief.
A street kid.
I like her though. She's got style.
- What's her name?
- Selina Kyle.
You two ever cross paths
when you were a cop?
- Once or twice.
- Well, that's great!
So, you know where she lives?
No. Not a clue.
But I know someone who might.
Oh, my God!
Hello, Barbara.
Hello, Barbara?
Is that all I get?
How you been?
How've I been?
Well, see for yourself.
I mean, it's no art gallery
but there's less chance
of me dying of boredom.
How's Lee?
We're not together.
No.
I thought by now
you would've chased her down.
Put a ring on it.
Did you dump her?
Oh, I bet you dumped her, didn't you?
You're such a heartbreaker.
I feel like I walked into something.
'Cause you did. Who are you?
Valerie Vale, I work for The Gazette.
- We're working on a project.
- I bet.
- She's your new girlfriend?
- No.
Jim and I were engaged.
Till I called it off.
We're looking for Selina.
Oh, wait, I remember this.
You kidnapped him and his girlfriend.
Held them hostage in a church.
Aren't you supposed to be in Arkham?
I was.
But, turns out I'm totally sane.
Got a paper proving it.
Yeah, signed by Hugo Strange.
Again, Selina, have you seen her?
A kiss.
That's my price.
Is she serious?
Are... are you serious?
Do it.
Never mind.
You're honestly no fun.
Try her squat,
down on Drake and Powell.
That's it? I've already been there.
Well, she may have mentioned
an old bank near Kane Sound.
Jim?
I had a dream
about you the other night.
You were in this horrible accident
and you lost both of your legs.
And then, I had to push you around
in a giant baby carriage.
Good seeing you, Barbara.
Do not.
So you really think Fish
is using the bank as an old base?
If I had to bet? Yeah.
Me too.
So how about I call the GCPD,
give them the exclusive,
they take in Fish and you get squat?
Hey! Open the door!
You should've let me come
to find Peabody.
- Vale!
- And you know what?
- I like your ex.
- Vale! Hey! Hey!
Hey, there. You all right?
Thirsty.
I don't have anything on me
but I live just up the road.
What's your name?
Ivy.
My name's Ivy.
Barnes is gonna want to know
where you got this.
Oh, come on, you know
I can't give up my source.
- Don't forget our deal.
- Yeah... yeah... yeah,
soon as Fish Moon's booked,
you get first crack at her.
But, for now stay out of the way.
All right, all right, fellas,
listen up.
We don't know
what we're going to find in there.
So rule number one, is be careful.
And keep your eyes peeled
for Ethel Peabody.
She's the state witness
that was abducted last night.
I don't have to tell you guys
that this is the call
we've been waiting for.
Let's go in there
and end this thing once and for all.
Guys, let's go! Be sure to...
- Police!
- Stay right there, you freaks!
Back up!
Stay right where you are!
Oh! We have company!
GCPD!
Don't nobody move!
Get Sebring a medic now.
Anyone see Mooney?
For months, I warned the police
about the threat to our city
posed by Hugo Strange's freaks
by the murderer of Fish Mooney
and how did they protect you?
They said that Fish Mooney
wasn't real.
That these "escapees"
were victims who need our help.
Well, Fish Mooney was real.
And once she was cornered by the GCPD
finally, they let her escape.
And these "victims,"
well, I for one am not afraid to call
them by their proper name: monsters!
Our city is being invaded
by monsters!
Attacking our brothers and sisters!
And it is up to us! To you!
To kill every monster you see!
Who is with me?
Master Bruce, wake up!
Come on, wake up, Master B.
Master B, wake up!
Hey there, sunshine.
Morning!
- You all right?
- How did I get back here?
I don't know,
I haven't got the foggiest,
I mean, I just came in here
to call the police when I,
but I then found you.
- Alfred!
- Hey!
You all right?
You all right, B?
You know, I reckon,
it was that same masked bastard
that knocked me spark out.
You know, I mean he came in and out
without so much as a peep.
I saw them, Alfred.
I spoke to them.
- And?
- It worked.
They agreed.
What? Just... just like that?
I mean you talked about the stuff
that we... we talked about, right?
Yes.
But I had to promise not
to investigate them anymore.
Not Indian Hill.
Not the corruption within my company.
Not my parents' murder.
I see.
Alfred.
It was the only way.
You weren't the only one
they threatened, were you?
No.
Do you intend on keeping your word?
Yes.
I do.
And how do you know
they'll keep theirs?
Hey, Alvarez, where's Bullock?
He's not back from the old bank yet.
You missed a big payday, Gordon.
We nabbed five of those freaks.
Yeah, trusted the wrong person.
I know the feeling.
Can we call this even?
You got me. I got you. It's over.
Let me buy you a drink.
You need to get out of here.
Yeah.
It's over when I get Fish.
You can read about it.
I do not want to get in trouble.
Odd as it might seem,
I do enjoy working here.
I'm just looking to find Fish.
I do that, everybody wins.
Fine.
You know she's sick.
That's the reason for those drugs
she and the others were stealing.
That's what Peabody said.
I figured that was why Mooney
was trying to find her.
To see if she could fix her.
Well, it appears something
went wrong.
This is Ethel Peabody.
You're sure?
Two separate tests confirmed it.
You remember there was a body
at the pharmaceuticals warehouse,
a worker ID'd as 35 years old
but who looked a 100?
I remember.
So... Mooney kidnaps Peabody
and then has one of her creatures
kill her.
Why?
Did Peabody give her what she wanted,
she no longer needed?
It seems unlikely.
My bet, Peabody simply
couldn't fix her.
Leaving Mooney still searching
for the cure.
You're thinking what I'm thinking.
That there's only one person
in Gotham who can help her.
Hugo Strange.
Detective Bullock.
Yeah, that's me.
Fish Mooney wants to see you.
All right... all right... all right!
I'm going!
Hello, Harvey.
Long time.
Hey, Fish.
- How you doing?
- Not so good.
Sorry to hear that.
You know there's a lot of people
out there looking for you.
Yeah.
I need to find that bastard, Strange.
Yeah, well... you know
I can't help you with that.
Oh, yes, you can.
And you will.
I'll help you find Strange.
Good boy.
This is it.
Nothing special but it's home.
You hungry?
Just thirsty.
Beer? Pop? Tea?
Water.
The home side
has something going now.
The crowd is...
So sad.
Poor things.
My ex-wife left a box of clothes
when she moved out.
You're welcome to them,
if you want to change.
Okay.
So where are you from?
Gotham.
Listen, if you need to use the phone,
go ahead.
Why would I need to use the phone?
Someone's got to be looking for you.
No.
- No one.
- Really?
A beautiful girl like you?
You think I'm beautiful?
So who are you?
Just a girl.
Cops killed my dad.
My mom left.
I was alone.
Abandoned.
But then...
something happened and...
I changed.
Grew.
I'm different...
inside and out.
So sad.
Let me get rid of that.
I've never been that good
at taking care of things.
What are you doing?
Relax. They're just plants.
I'll get those clothes.
You don't know that Mooney has him.
Or that she's looking for Strange.
And, again, you shouldn't
even be here.
Harvey isn't answering his phone.
Nobody knows where he is.
Well, you could start by looking
in every place in Gotham
that serves booze.
And we found this beside his car.
She's looking for him.
With Peabody dead,
that'd be her next logical step.
Damn... damn... damn.
You have to call someone,
tell them Fish is on her way.
Call who? The Feds?
I don't even know
which department has Strange.
But you do know
where they're hiding him, don't you?
You and Bullock both know.
They took him to a place
outside the city.
It's like an old mansion.
But on the inside,
it's a high-tech research facility.
The government has scientists
debriefing him, don't they?
They want to know
what he discovered in Indian Hill.
You have to tell us where it is.
The hell I do.
I'll take you there.
- Are you sure this is the place?
- Yeah.
This is where I dropped Strange off
a few months ago.
All right, show time.
Hey, fellas, at ease, soldiers.
Detective Bullock, GCPD.
- Where's your badge?
- My badge?
Oh, man, I must've dropped it.
I'm here to see Strange.
- We haven't heard anything.
- You haven't?
That's strange.
I mean, Strange weird,
not the guy Strange.
You have ID?
Yeah.
Who the hell? Hold it!
I said hold it!
Stop right there!
Professor Strange, you and I
have some unfinished business.
Look at you.
Amazing.
You were my greatest creation.
Your greatest creation who's dying.
What?
You're going to fix me, Daddy.
And when that's done,
you're going to make me an army
so I can have this city kneeling
at my feet.
But I can't...
fix you.
Fish... cops. Lots of them.
You have a few minutes
to rethink your answer.
I'd suggest you do.
Go... go, check that door.
Move out to your perimeter!
It's Bullock.
Harvey... Harvey you all right?
Oh, he's fine.
But this ain't Harvey.
- I want to talk to him.
- Sure.
- You don't control me anymore.
- Sid.
Hey, Cap, how are you? Sorry!
One chance, Mooney.
You let him go,
you might just make it out of this.
Chump, don't you know
you're speaking to a dying woman?
Which severely limits
your negotiating position.
So here's how it's going to go down.
One cop comes within 20ft
of this place and Harvey,
although I love him,
will eat a bullet.
You had to come back, didn't you?
Like a bad penny.
- Now, where were we?
- Fish, you got to give it up.
You're surrounded,
you got nowhere to go.
Shut up, Harvey.
What's going on? How's Bullock?
Listen up.
I want you to create
a full perimeter.
Snipers on every corner.
Mooney does not make it out of this,
understood?
- Yes, sir!
- Now, go.
- Captain...
- What?
You cannot just leave him in there.
You think that's what I'm doing?
I'm just not charging through
the front door so he gets killed.
And I'll remind you,
you are no longer a police officer.
Get in my way
and I'll have you arrested.
The press.
Keep the press back, keep them back.
We are standing outside the mansion,
and preliminary reports
are that wanted Indian Hill escapee,
Fish Mooney,
has barricaded herself inside
and is holding a hostage.
This is it, Butch.
She's finally cornered.
Like a rat.
Yeah, but what are you gonna do?
The cops are already there.
The GCPD is not Gotham.
And Gotham listens to me.
It's time to round up our friends.
Believe me,
if I could fix you, I would.
I think of you
as one of my own children.
But I can't.
So what am I supposed to do?
Give up?
Do you not understand what you are?
What you represent?
You are the first of a new
generation, a new Eve.
You know, I owned a club once.
Ran protection on the side.
Every first of the month,
people would pay me.
Every once in a while, someone
would come up short and they'd say,
"Mooney, I don't have the money,
Mooney, I need more time,"
and they'd cry and cry.
And then I discovered when I squeezed
them and squeezed them
and squeezed them
they always had more.
You are going to fix me...
or swear to God,
I will make you pray for your death.
Fish!
What're the cops doing now?
It's not the cops.
What the hell is this?
Cordon off this entire area.
No one gets near the house.
Hold on... hold on...
Cobblepot what the hell
are you doing here?
You have proven to be incapable of,
time and time again.
This is a GCPD operation.
I am ordering you and this mob
to disperse immediately.
Fat chance.
I will not let those monsters
escape again.
Fish Mooney dies tonight!
Damn it, Cobblepot.
One of my detectives is inside.
This is the last time I'm gonna ask.
Back up.
You've had your chance, Barnes.
Now it's my turn.
Who's with me?
Stay back.
You killed a lot of our friends,
Gordon.
A lot of your friends had it coming.
So do you.
That's enough!
Bring him in.
Kill them now.
Everyone stay back.
Jim! What the hell
are you doing here?
Saving you.
- Thought that was obvious.
- Oh, yeah. Totally. Thank you.
Why're you here, Gordon?
Did your little cop friends send you
to get me to turn myself in,
'cause that's not going to happen.
I'm here on my own.
I only want Bullock.
Really?
You'd risk your life
for this broken down old thing?
Thanks.
- He'd do the same for me.
- I would. It's true.
Well, you've helped me.
'Cause now I have two hostages.
Barnes won't see it that way.
Hell, you kill me,
he'll probably thank you.
I been nothing
but a pain in the ass to him.
Also true.
Then you better
give me one good reason
why I shouldn't have
my friends kill you.
Because I can get you out of here.
And exactly how do you plan
to do that,
considering this whole place
is surrounded?
That's my problem.
I get you out of here,
you give me Bullock.
That's the deal.
I get this one.
- Wait a sec...
- Deal.
You have two minutes.
We won't go. We won't go.
Jim? You just keep surprising me.
Shut up.
How'd you like to have Fish
all to yourself?
Don't tease.
She'll be in the woods
behind the mansion in five minutes.
All you have to do is one thing.
Name it.
Cobblepot, get this crowd
to disperse.
Or I'll make them disperse
and there will be bloodshed.
Promise?
People of Gotham!
The time for action is now!
Kill the monsters!
Kill them now!
We need all units
for the front of the house!
Immediately.
Get back, now!
- You need back up!
- Stop!
The mob's broken through the front
but the back is clear.
We can make it to the woods.
Time to go.
You two hold them off
as long as you can.
And Harvey, no hard feelings.
Fish?
Screw you.
Fair enough.
Jim. You can't let her take me!
- Goodbye, Professor.
- She's going to kill me!
She's gonna kill me!
Stop!
Go.
That's better.
Just old friends.
- Oswald.
- Don't call me that!
My name is Penguin!
Do you know how long
I've been looking for you?
How long I've waited
for this very moment?
- Mr. Cobblepot.
- Quiet!
So this is it?
I spare your life and you shoot me
dead in the woods like an animal?
Pretty much, yes.
But I will admit, that night
under the bridge stayed with me.
- Why?
- Why what?
Why didn't you kill me?
I have gone over that night a 1,000
times and it doesn't make any sense.
Why didn't you kill me?
I would've killed you in an instant!
- Answer me.
- Because you're mine.
You were my umbrella boy, remember?
You rubbed my feet
when they were tired.
And now look at you,
the terror of Gotham.
Everything I've done in my life...
possibly the best thing
was turning Oswald Cobblepot
into The Penguin.
I couldn't destroy that.
Ask him.
He understands what it is to bring
something into being.
It is a part of you.
Forever.
Goodbye, Fish.
Don't come back.
We got them. We got them.
Got some more fuel for the fire.
- Show them now.
- Monsters burn!
Monsters burn!
Burn! Burn! Burn! Burn! Burn! Burn!
Yeah!
- Yeah!
- Tell Barnes something, would you?
I'm going home.
Next time...
remember to water.
Well, I for one am personally
very glad not to be staring
at those bloody box files
and that flaming bulletin board.
Tramping down those stairs
to that dank cave.
Does leave one question unanswered
though, doesn't it, Master Bruce?
What's that?
Well, you know, with all this
spare time on your hands,
how are you gonna fill it?
Well, I imagine you have some ideas.
I do.
Dancing lessons.
That's right, I mean,
a man of your station,
should be able to guide
gracefully a beautiful
young girl across the dance floor,
don't you think?
And I suppose that you're going
to be teaching me these lessons.
Well, I certainly could, you know,
I was quite well regarded as a bit
of a dancer in my day actually.
But I think I'll leave
that particular ordeal
to someone more qualified.
Right!
Step out!
Slowly.
Who are you?
Oh, my word.
Please don't hurt me.
You don't quit, do you?
I came by to let you know
that tomorrow's paper
is going to lay out Bullock's story
of how Fish got away.
How she just vanished
while you two were escaping.
Great. Can't wait to read about it.
And it's a load of crap.
You want to know what I think?
Got a feeling you're gonna tell me
either way.
I think you made a deal with Fish,
you let her escape with Strange
in exchange for Bullock's life.
And how would I manage that?
I saw Penguin get a call
before the riot started.
When the mob attacked, Barnes
ordered all the cops to the front.
And that's when Fish slipped
into the woods with Strange.
By that logic,
Penguin helped Fish escape.
Why would he do that?
Because he wanted Fish
all to himself.
I mean, that is what you offered him,
wasn't it?
You promised to help Fish escape
but you did it by double-crossing her
and delivering her to Penguin.
If that were so,
I'd be a millionaire by now.
Except Fish isn't dead.
Penguin would've dragged her
in front of the mob if she was.
So, what happened in the woods?
I don't know.
I do know that you're gonna have
a hard time collecting all that cash.
'Course that wasn't why you
did any of this, was it?
Who the hell are you, Jim Gordon?
- What are you doing?
- Shut up for once.