Bad guys in this town are changing.
Hi.
Welcome, everyone.
The world sees criminal lunatics.
I see brilliance.
Theo Galavan,
the new mayor of Gotham!
- No! Mother.
- Any last words?
I'm going to kill you.
They're gonna pay for
what they've done.
Hello, Jim. Please step aside.
This is the name of the man
who killed your parents.
- You're under arrest.
- No! Tell me who killed them!
Hello, sleepyhead.
My mother was a saint!
A man with nothing to love is free.
Silver is bad news, Bruce.
What are you doing? Stop!
Malone! It's Malone. That's the name.
Goodbye, Silver.
Bruce, you can't do this.
It isn't you.
That's what you think...
but you're wrong.
You're right about my uncle.
He's everything everyone says.
I don't know how bad it's gonna get.
There is no line.
There's just the law.
Jim, you see an abyss
and you run toward it.
I'm pregnant.
We need every method at our disposal.
If there was ever a time for us
to work together, now is that time.
Gotham needs him dead!
Think of the greater good.
Think of Gotham.
Goodbye, Jim Gordon.
After searching the premises,
I, along with Alfred Pennyworth
and Selina Kyle,
was able to locate the abductee,
Bruce Wayne.
Where was he?
Theo Galavan's residence.
- That's when you opened fire?
- Yes.
We eliminated the threat posed
by Father Creel and his men
and were able to recover Bruce Wayne.
Sacrilege!
You then left to search for Galavan
on your own?
That's correct.
- Did you find him?
- Yes.
Theo Galavan, you're under arrest.
- Did you detain Galavan?
- No.
Why not?
Captain Barnes
and Officer Vargas arrived
and placed me under arrest.
Jim. Jim!
Put your gun on the ground
and put your hands on top
of your head.
That's because at the time of this
incident, some four weeks ago,
you were a fugitive from the law.
That was a misunderstanding.
What happened next?
Oswald Cobblepot
and two of his associates arrived,
rendered Officer Vargas
and Captain Barnes unconscious.
Cobblepot and his associates escaped
with Galavan.
Are you 100 percent sure
that he won't beat this
and walk free again?
You then pursued Cobblepot
and his men, correct?
Yes, but I was unable to locate them.
You're a man of conscience, Jim.
You'll regret this.
I have many regrets.
This won't be top of the list.
At which point you decided
to flee the city
before law enforcement
could question you?
Yes. For that, I have no excuse,
other than to say...
I was concerned for the safety
of my fiancé.
She had informed me earlier
that day that she was pregnant.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Detective Gordon,
within hours of your encounter,
Theo Galavan was found beaten
and shot to death.
Were you present
at the time of his murder?
Well, here we are.
No, I was not.
Do you have any information
regarding the case
that you have not shared with us?
This is for my mother.
No, I do not.
Detective,
did you have anything to do
with the murder of Theo Galavan?
Detective, answer the question.
Were you involved
in Theo Galavan's murder?
No, I was not.
Charges are lifted.
I'm cleared of all wrong-doing
and reinstated.
I knew they would see sense.
I didn't.
You told the truth.
What choice did they have?
Yeah.
Are you sure this is what you want?
After everything
this job has put us through?
Positive.
- Then what's wrong?
- Nothing. Long day.
Promise?
Promise.
- Barnes.
- Dent.
- Captivating story.
- Yes, it was.
Do you believe him?
I believe your investigation
has found no evidence
of criminal wrongdoing.
Careful. You're starting
to sound like a lawyer.
Any leads on Cobblepot?
His men have deserted him.
He's all alone.
It's only a matter of time
before we find him.
It's now day 27 of the manhunt
for the crime lord Oswald Cobblepot.
GCPD officers continue
to comb the city
in search of the man they say
killed controversial mayor
Theo Galavan in cold blood.
With public enemy number one
on the lam, the question remains,
just who is running
Gotham's underworld?
Take him away.
Hello, Butch.
Hey.
How you doing?
Your security stinks.
People are usually trying
to get out of this place, not in.
Why so glum?
- You're the king of Gotham now.
- I'm not glum.
I'm just... thinking.
I got a lot of responsibilities.
Not as much fun
as you thought it'd be, huh?
What do you want, anyway?
You got a lot of nerve showing up
after what you did to me.
Is that your mean face?
What are you gonna do?
Kill me?
Maybe I will.
What I did for you, Butch,
is make you a free man.
If it wasn't for me,
you wouldn't be king.
I bet that was your plan all along,
huh?
You're just that fond of me.
Strangely enough,
I am kind of fond of you.
I mean, normally, I go for handsome,
intelligent men, not brutes, but...
you have an amazing...
animal vitality about you.
- I'm smarter than I look.
- Oh, you must be.
A funny lady.
What do you really want?
I wanna be your partner in crime.
Lonely, huh?
You and I would make a good team.
I'm not looking for a relationship
right now.
Honeybun, look at me.
We have history.
And you and I both know,
deep down in your heart,
that whatever I want, you want.
All units, all units,
Reported armed abduction near
the 300 block of Kearny Avenue.
Any and all available officers
in the area, please respond.
GCPD!
Is there a problem, officer?
There's been an abduction
in the area.
How awful.
Have you seen anything tonight?
Anything out of the ordinary?
No. Can't say that I have.
- Do you live in the area, sir?
- Not far.
What's your address?
Well, what I mean to say,
I used to live in the area.
I moved.
Would you open the back of the van,
please, sir?
Sure thing.
Happy to.
What the...
Somebody get me a glass of water!
Hey! Mitch, separate those two.
It's a good thing you're here.
Caught a weird one last night.
That's it?
No hug? No kiss? No welcome back?
You don't deserve these lips.
Way I see it, you finagled yourself
a month-long,
paid vacation, you bastard.
Besides,
Captain's pressing me on this case.
Oh, yeah? What is it?
You didn't hear?
Last night, some psycho froze a cop.
To death.
Froze her?
Yeah. Told you it was weird.
Come on. Nygma's waiting for us.
Frozen.
Interesting.
It took nearly five seconds to freeze
this rose using liquid nitrogen.
- So?
- Well so, it'd take a human body
significantly longer, depending on
mass and body fat, of course.
So why would a cop stand around
for hours waiting to get frozen?
She wouldn't.
Which means your suspect wasn't using
liquid nitrogen.
He was using supercooled
liquid helium.
It's one of the most effective
substances in the world
for rapid temperature reduction.
This liquid helium,
where do you get it?
Why do you need it?
He doesn't, dummy.
He just wants to know
where it comes from
so we can track down the guy
that blasted our colleague with it.
I don't like being called names,
Detective.
Easy, Ed.
I'm sure
Harvey was just being colorful.
Yeah.
I was just being colorful, Ed,
I'm sorry.
It's extremely rare and expensive.
Can't imagine there's more than one
or two producers in Gotham.
I could research manufacturers,
if you would like.
That's be really nice. Thank you, Ed.
- You coming?
- Give me a minute.
Listen, Ed, there's something
I wanted to talk to you about.
- Penguin.
- Yes.
You want to know the nature
of my relationship with him.
- Yes.
- Because you're concerned
I aided and abetted a known criminal.
Did you?
I found Mr. Cobblepot wounded
and dying in the woods.
I nursed him back to health.
He owed me his life which is why
I trusted him
when he said he had changed his ways.
It was an innocent mistake.
Got him! We got him!
Wonder what that is.
Silence!
What are you, a
bunch of cheerleaders?
This is not a game.
This is our job.
And this... specimen,
this is just one sad, pathetic skell.
There are plenty of scumbags
out there.
Plenty.
So stop waving your pom-poms
and go catch some.
Yeah, stare all you want.
Big whoop.
- You got me. I'm cool.
- Get in there!
It's all good.
- I said I'd catch him, and I did.
- Yes, sir.
Now we'll learn the truth of
what really happened to Galavan.
All right, Cobblepot.
Tell me what happened at Galavan's
that night.
Well... A lot of things happened.
Why don't you start with the moment
right after you knocked me out
with that vase.
I'm sorry for that.
Such an exquisite vase.
This is my amused look.
Keep talking.
I took Galavan to the river
and I killed him.
Slowly.
- You confess to murder?
- Yes, I do. Proud of it.
I'm not a criminal, you know.
I'm just... insane.
- What did James Gordon do?
- What did he do when?
What did he do
after you knocked me out?
What does he say he did?
I'm asking you.
You have something you wanna tell me?
No, sir.
Cobblepot backed your story.
You mean, he told the truth.
Yeah.
That's what I'm gonna choose
to believe.
It's the right thing to do.
- Good to have you back.
- Good to be back, sir.
Jim, I'm trusting you.
Don't make a fool out of me.
Yes, sir.
I was having a dream about you.
We were at that little red cabin
by the beach. Remember?
I remember.
Six summers ago.
You looked like a movie star.
- You look tired.
- Work.
How's it coming?
Good. Good.
Slower than I'd like, but good.
Tell me.
I'm having trouble with reanimation.
I need to find the correct ratio
of liquid helium
to glycerol cryoprotectant.
Now tell me what that means
in English, honey.
It means I can freeze you,
like we planned.
I can bring your temperature down
to 200 degrees below zero,
and I can stop this disease
from killing you.
But?
I can't bring you back.
Not yet.
But I will.
I'm sorry.
No, it's not that.
I'm just thinking of all those poor
mice you're experimenting on.
They don't feel anything.
I just need more time.
- A little more time.
- Hey.
I'll find a way. I promise.
- Got some good news and bad news.
- Good news.
Nygma did some digging and found
one company in all of Gotham
that makes liquid helium.
- Wayne Enterprises.
- That's the good news?
It's not, but I thought bad news
and more bad news
didn't have the same ring.
What's this?
Three abductions in the past month,
all tied to a blue van,
same as our suspect's.
Three abductions?
- They find any of them?
- Not a one.
Which makes you wonder what's
this guy doing with all those people?
Nora?
I'm going to work for a few hours.
- Knock if you need anything.
- Okay.
- Ed?
- Don't look at me.
I'm not supposed
to be talking to you.
You doing okay?
You look kind of funky.
I confess I've felt better.
Is there anything I can do to help?
I'm beyond help.
Forget me, my friend.
But, if you would take care of my
mother's grave, I'd be very grateful.
If you'd visit occasionally...
- Tell her I'm thinking of her.
- I will.
She likes lilies.
Occasional visits, lilies, check.
Thank you.
On your feet, Cobblepot.
What's going on?
- Where are you taking me?
- Arkham.
You are insane, right?
It is now Thursday, February
21st, 3.44pm.
Test subject 014 is in his 40s,
appears to be in good health,
and shows no signs of damage
sustained during Vitrification.
I'm now ready to commence
the reanimation experiment.
You are correct.
Wayne Enterprises
does manufacture liquid helium.
For years it was used as part
of our cryogenics program.
Cryo-whatics?
It's the branch of physics
dealing with the production
and effects of extremely
low temperatures.
My understanding is that there were
some promising experiments
being carried out in the program.
But, alas, it was shut down.
When was that?
Two or three years ago.
Thomas Wayne killed it, along
with a few other odd programs.
Any idea why?
No idea.
It was all kept very quiet.
- Thanks, Lucius.
- Detectives.
Penguin pie!
There seems to be some confusion.
My name is Oswald Cobblepot.
Many of you, no doubt,
will have heard of me.
Some of you, clearly, have not.
For those poor ignorant souls,
I offer illumination.
I am not a man to be trifled with.
Oh, no.
I am powerful.
I am vicious.
I'm King of Gotham.
I am King of Gotham!
I'm the King of Gotham!
I am! I am!
Look at me!
I'm the King of Gotham!
I'm King! I'm King!
Here ye, here ye!
The subject's core temperature
is now 39 degrees.
We are approaching
the critical threshold.
41 degrees!
We hit 41 degrees.
Solution A14, I knew it would work.
I knew it.
Yes, yes, yes.
No.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
Not again, please. Not again, no. No.
Nora?
Breathe, Nora. I'm right here.
Look at me.
Where's the formiterol?
That was the worst one yet.
That was the last pill.
Why didn't you tell me?
I'm sorry. I forgot.
I have so many.
So many.
If you have another attack
and you don't have this medication,
you could die.
You can't let this happen again,
Nora.
Why?
Does it matter?
It matters.
I'll be back.
I need to get this refilled.
- Next.
- I need to get this refilled.
- Do you have the prescription?
- I have the bottle.
That's not the same thing, is it?
Please. I just need it refilled.
The original prescription doesn't
have a refill order.
If it doesn't have a refill order
I can't refill it.
This medication is for my wife.
She's sick. She's in pain.
Everyone that comes in here is sick
or in pain.
Have your doctor write a new
prescription, then I can refill it.
Just give me the medication.
No.
- You son of a bitch!
- Get out!
Get him out of here!
Get out of here
before I call the cops, you kook!
You shouldn't have done that.
I'll be back.
Goodbye, Nigel.
Oh, and remember what I told you.
See no evil.
Do no evil.
Yes, sir. I will.
Mr. Cobblepot.
My name is Hugo Strange.
Chief of Psychiatry here
at Arkham Asylum.
Please come in.
You're not listening.
Maybe you should get a new
hearing aid while you're here.
Hey!
- Formitorol. Now!
- Oh, okay. Okay.
Take it all.
Please, don't kill me. Please.
I'll do anything you want.
You and your friend here...
are going to help save my wife.
No! No!
Excuse me!
Going to need some help out.
Yeah?
Our guy just hit a pharmacy on ninth.
That's it. Just slide him in there.
Hey, careful.
Blue van.
Go, get out of here.
- Go, go, go, go, go!
- I got it, I got it!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, slow down!
What is this, anyhow?
Am I being punished?
Oh, no.
I make it a point
to meet all new inmates.
It's part of the intake protocol.
Though I will ask you to refrain
from making speeches atop
cafeteria tables in the future.
I'll do my best.
How has your adjustment been so far?
Fine, I suppose.
Oh, come now, Oswald.
Periods of great transition can bring
on great stress.
Surely, this must be a traumatic
experience for you.
Please.
This is a pillow fight compared
to what I've been through.
Yes.
I have read of your tribulations
of late.
Attempts on your life,
having to survive being a fugitive...
The death of your mother.
Troubled times.
Is that your clinical diagnosis?
I know that if
I were in your position,
I would be feeling some
strong emotions.
Anger, grief, regret, even.
For what?
The murder of Theo Galavan.
My mother died in my arms
because of Galavan.
The only thing I regret is that
I couldn't kill him more than once.
I see.
Perhaps we could pick it up
right there next time.
I so look forward
to our work together.
And don't worry.
Here at Arkham, we have a number
of intensive treatment programs.
I am more than confident
that we'll be able to facilitate
your rehabilitation.
My what?
Rehabilitation.
That's why you're here, after all.
To be cured of your sickness.
You are sick, aren't you?
Victor?
Honey?
You down here?
Victor?
My God!
Oh, my God!
- Surveillance system wasn't even on.
- What's that?
Some witnesses saw our guy
throw this at the pharmacist.
It's probably
his prescription bottle.
Fries, Nora Fries. His wife, maybe?
Yeah, maybe, but it's "Fries."
What do you mean?
- It's pronounced "Fries."
- How do you know?
- I'm really good with names.
- Yeah, whatever.
There's an address on here.
Come on, let's go.
GCPD, we have a search warrant!
Ma'am, don't move.
Holy moly.
He told me they were mice.
Get her out of here.
Ms. Fries.
Nora.
You all right?
Nigel?
See no evil, do no evil.
- No, no.
- See no evil, do no evil.
We need to find your husband, Nora.
Before he hurts someone else.
I was asleep.
I woke up when I heard him leave.
That's all I can tell you.
If you don't cooperate,
we'll be forced to charge you
with obstruction of justice.
You're going to jail, Nora.
You get that, right?
My husband did terrible things.
But he did those terrible things
for my sake.
I'm dying.
He wants to save me.
I can't tell you how sorry I am.
But I can't betray him.
Oh, one more thing.
What's the correct pronunciation
of your last name?
It's Fries.
Fries. Thank you.
Told you.
- Excuse me?
- Yeah, what can I help you with?
I'd like to speak
with Detective Gordon, please.
What for?
I'd like to make a confession.
I'm the man
that's been freezing people.
You too, huh?
That makes five in one night.
Must be a full moon.
Tell you what.
Why don't you have a seat
with the others.
Detective Gordon will be out
in a minute.
No, no. You don't understand. I'm...
Oh, I understand. Have a seat.
Am I dead?
Hello?
- Don't touch me! Don't touch me!
- Take it easy, come on! Down!
A-16.
It worked.
Go get a blanket!
I can't believe it worked.
All right. I got him.
You?
You!
I'm coming for you, Nora.
I'm coming to save you.
New inmate Oswald Cobblepot
exhibits signs of extreme narcissism
and megalomania.
Also seems to have
had a rather unhealthy relationship
with his deceased mother.
Treatments will include immersive
aversion therapy
and radical psychotropics.
How are we this evening, Ms. Peabody?
Busy.
The formaldehyde pump
in silo F needs replacing.
Our young lady arsonist refuses to
co-operate with our experiments.
And I had to reschedule your
appointment with Councilman Carter.
- Again?
- It's the third time.
- How very rude.
- Indeed.
And there's this.
Seems someone has solved the problem
of post-cryonic reanimation.
Oh, nonsense!
I'm still years from solving that.
Fascinating.
Do you realize what this could mean
for our program?
- Who is this man?
- His name is Victor Fries.
But the newspapers have already
given him a nickname.
Hello, Mr. Freeze.