ESSEN: Previously on Gotham...
My best wishes to Commissioner Essen.
Welcome back, Jim.
I don't know how you pulled
this off, but I'm glad you did.
(GUNSHOTS)
BRUCE: Sometimes the right way is
also the ugly way.
ESSEN: There's been an incident
at Arkham Asylum.
Six inmates have escaped.
Barbara Kean was one of them.
Oh, my God.
The world sees criminal lunatics.
I see brilliance.
(CHOKING)
Gotham would tremble before you.
BRUCE: "I beg of you, my son,
please choose happiness,
"unless you feel a calling.
"A true calling."
THEO: Mr. Mayor.
- MAYOR JAMES: (MUFFLED) No!
- You want to know what I really am?
- Yes, sir.
- Shall I tell you?
MAYOR JAMES: Please, please. (WHIMPERS)
At heart,
- I'm an ardent student of human nature.
- MAYOR JAMES: Oh.
THEO: Fascinating paradox, we are.
So wise, and yet so foolish.
So brave, and yet so fearful.
For instance, this is a glass jar.
Inside it is a hairy spider.
A tarantula, I guess, but I'm no expert.
(MAYOR JAMES WHIMPERS)
In a minute, I'm going to open that little
hatch in the front of your box,
I'm going to drop the spider inside
and I'm going to close it.
- MAYOR JAMES: No, no!
- That's choice A.
Choice B, I open the hatch,
you speak to your lovely secretary
Maggie on the telephone,
you tell her you've run away
with some woman,
you'll be sending
written instructions shortly.
So which is it, choice A or choice B?
MAYOR JAMES: Choice B, please.
Please, choice B.
The telephone. Of course.
It's human nature.
(GASPS)
See? There is no spider.
But if you don't do what I ask,
you'll wish there was one.
Why are you doing this to me?
Don't fret so.
You're part of a great endeavor,
a great cleansing.
Monsters are coming, Mr. Mayor.
Monsters who will cleanse this city
in blood and fire.
REPORTER: Can you confirm that?
Yeah? Okay.
Because we're going to roll with that
right away.
You've got to confirm it though.
Do you understand?
Otherwise, you can get in
a lot of trouble.
- What the hell is this?
- (SCREAMS)
"Where is Mayor James?
Who is his mystery lover?"
- No one cares who the mayor is banging.
- (SCREAMS)
You can do better than this, people.
Now go out and get me
some headlines, damn it!
(SCREAMS)
(STAFF CLAMORING)
Yeah. All right, all right.
MAN: Oh, my goodness!
Oh, my God!
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
- (BODY THUDS)
- Perfect.
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING)
- Next.
Mister X.
(WHIMPERING)
(LAUGHING)
(GRUNTS)
A little to the right.
Okay, that's the spot.
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
- (BODY THUDS)
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Perfect.
What shall we do with the spare?
Oh.
I know. (EXHALES)
Aaron, would you kindly?
(SCREAMING)
- (BODY THUDS)
- (PEOPLE SCREAMING)
(PEOPLE CLAMORING)
(CHUCKLES)
Now, that's a headline.
(LAUGHS HYSTERICALLY)
You all know what we're facing here.
Forty-eight hours ago,
six criminally-insane inmates
were busted out of Arkham Asylum.
Yesterday, four of those inmates
broke into Yellen Shipyard,
kidnapped seven workers,
then dropped them off
the roof of the Gotham Gazette.
As of now, we still have no leads
on the person or persons
behind the breakout.
Jim Gordon's lead. Jim.
These are our targets.
(PROJECTOR CLICKS)
Jerome Valeska, 18 years old. Matricide.
Arnold Dobkins, schizophrenic.
Poisoner, rapist.
(PROJECTOR CLICKS)
Aaron Helzinger. Killed his entire family
with his bare hands.
(PROJECTOR CLICKS)
Robert Greenwood.
Killed and then ate a dozen women.
(PROJECTOR CLICKS)
Barbara Kean. Killed her parents.
(PROJECTOR CLICKS OFF)
We're going to work this
in groups of four.
I'll hand out assignments
throughout the day.
Alvarez is my coordinating officer.
Any questions?
Let's get to work.
(OFFICERS CHATTING INDISTINCTLY)
Fine job yesterday, gentlemen.
We opened big.
The whole city knows your name now.
So, bravo.
Let's give ourselves a round of applause.
(CHUCKLING)
Now that we have Gotham's attention,
it's time for the Maniax
to make a grand entrance.
Wasn't that it?
That was the overture.
Now the audience is hushed, expectant.
The curtain rises...
Then what happens?
Oh, then we confront Gothamites
with their most primal fears.
Take from them all they hold
dear and sacred.
And then what happens?
Why, then we offer them salvation.
And then they are ours.
Let's get busy, man.
Patience. First, you gentlemen
need to learn a little stagecraft.
- Stagecraft?
- You're going to be on TV.
You have to present yourselves
with style and vigor.
Dobkins, say,
"Good evening, ladies and gentlemen."
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Again, with a smile.
(SIGHS) You.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(LOUDLY) Good evening,
ladies and gentlemen.
Not bad. Sinister and authoritative.
Never mind.
Jerome.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(PLAYFULLY) Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening!
Very good. Boyishly charming.
(LAUGHS)
(CHUCKLES) The laugh is fabulous.
Use that.
MAYOR JAMES: Ow!
- (WHIP CRACKS)
- MAYOR JAMES: Ow! Ow!
(TABITHA LAUGHING)
- (WHIP CRACKS)
- (LAUGHING)
MAYOR JAMES: Oh!
- Now me.
- (WHIP CRACKS)
- (MAYOR JAMES YELPS)
- (TABITHA LAUGHING)
I am so glad
that you two are getting along.
But we're a little busy here, so if you
could leave the poor mayor alone.
- We're bored.
- Yeah.
Why do the boys get to have all the fun?
Your time is coming. I told you.
You haven't killed him, have you?
No, I don't think so.
- (WHIP CRACKS)
- (MAYOR JAMES WHIMPERING)
Nope, hanging in there.
When? When is my time coming?
Soon, very soon.
Why don't you tell me about James Gordon?
What do you want to know?
It's hard to believe.
My father's been sneaking
down here for years,
and I never even knew about it.
That makes two of us, doesn't it?
Wait. Let's just think about this.
Are you certain you want to turn
that bloody thing on?
Of course I'm certain.
Have you thought it through, Master Bruce?
This computer could contain all my
father's research into Wayne Enterprises.
All this time, I've been looking
for a smoking gun, and here it is.
Exactly, a smoking gun.
Now, guns are for grown-ups, aren't they?
It's a metaphor, Alfred, not an argument.
(COMPUTER STARTING UP)
Here it is.
(BEEPS)
It's working! It's working.
(CLANGING)
What are you doing? Alfred, stop!
What are you doing?
What are you doing, Alfred?
Alfred, stop it! It's ruined!
It's ruined! What's wrong with you?
Why would you do that? Answer me!
It had to be done, Master Bruce.
This was the key to exposing
Wayne Enterprises.
(GASPING) Everything that I've worked for,
everything my dad worked for
is now gone! Because of you!
If I'd known what was down here,
I would have never helped get you in.
I mean, look around you. Look, look.
Liters of blood.
A bulletproof vest with two slugs in it!
Guns, weapons!
I mean, whatever's on that computer
probably killed your father,
and I'll be damned if I see you suffer
the same fate, Master Bruce.
(SOBBING)
I'm trying to protect you.
I'm trying to keep you safe.
(VOICE BREAKING) I want you to go.
- Look, I know that you're--
- No.
- Upset, and it's been--
- Alfred.
I want you to go and never come back.
Do you understand me?
You're fired.
Very well, Master Bruce. As you wish.
- Ooh, shiny!
- (LAUGHS)
Give that back.
I saw it first.
No, you didn't. I said give it back.
Make me, you little brat.
DOBKINS: Ooh!
Your samurai skills are excellent,
Greenwood-san,
but they are nothing compared to me.
(CHAINSAW WHIRRING)
Prepare to die!
(LAUGHS)
That's enough! I said...
I tried to stop them.
Boys, we're a team.
We don't fight amongst ourselves.
Yeah, we're a team, boys.
And I'm the captain.
Captain of my foot.
I've murdered a dozen women,
terrorized the city.
What have you done? Chop up your mommy?
(WHISPERS)
Everybody has to start somewhere.
See, I have vision,
and ambition, and brains.
(IN NORMAL VOICE) You're just a nutty
old cannibal. (CHUCKLES)
How many people can you eat
before that shtick gets old?
I could eat one more.
I can see we're going to have to
resolve this one, once and for all.
(CHUCKLES)
You all know this game, right?
Oh, love it.
(BULLET CHAMBER WHIRRS AND CLICKS)
Who wants to be the boss?
Ladies first.
(CLICKS)
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, Greenwood, what's the secret
to good comedy?
(CLICKS)
Timing. And what's courage?
Grace under pressure.
And who's the boss?
(CLICKS)
I'm the boss. (LAUGHS)
I believe you are, Jerome.
I believe you are.
Arigato, sensei.
Whoo! Hee!
Thank you.
Four lunatics and Barbara?
Brother, you got no luck.
I told you civilian life was better,
didn't I?
Yeah, you did.
Actually, that's kind of why I'm here.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
SCOTTY: What are you doing here?
Jim, you remember Scotty, my girlfriend?
- Fiancée.
- Right, my fiancée.
Yeah. Scotty, good to see you.
Relax, honeybun. We're just talking.
Oh, like hell, you are. He's going to ask
you to come back to work.
He didn't ask me anything.
We're just having a chat.
SCOTTY: Oh, is that right?
Is that why you're here,
Detective, just to have a chat?
No. No, she's right. Harvey, I need
your help. The case is a bear.
We're short-handed, and I was thinking
maybe you could...
He has a life. The answer is no.
He is not coming back.
Hon. I'm telling him no.
But it's like she said.
I have a life.
I get it. I get it.
I'm happy for you. Just a thought.
- Wish me luck.
- Good luck.
Jim, one last thing.
One last thought from your Uncle Harvey.
These Maniax killed a bunch of people
from the shipyard, right?
Yellen Shipyard, yeah.
Why there? They could've gone
anywhere, killed anyone.
But these lunatics specifically chose
that shipyard. I wonder why.
Good to see you. Scotty.
Yeah, I'll call you back. Commissioner.
Tell me something good, please.
- Harvey isn't coming back.
- That's not good.
But he did suggest
a lead that panned out nicely.
Turns out the Maniax stole a refueling
truck from the shipyard yesterday.
Why wasn't it reported?
It was one of
over a hundred service vehicles.
Took a while to track down
the entire fleet.
But when we did,
we found that one was missing.
Fully loaded with gasoline.
You get a license plate?
And a description of the vehicle.
Put out an APB.
God, I'm so glad you're back, Jim.
Me, too.
Wish I could say the same for Bullock.
I can't believe he's really gone.
He's a cop. He was born to be a cop.
Not anymore. He's a happy man.
I didn't have it in me to push him.
You ever think about that?
Walking away, I mean.
No. You?
I did, for a long time.
But not anymore?
I've sat back and watched
old, corrupt, lazy men
buy their way into this job and waste it.
Not me, Jim.
Not me.
- A new day.
- You're damn right.
I'd just like to say it's been an honor
and a privilege to serve
you and your family, sir.
Thank you.
If you need any references,
I'll be happy to provide them.
Is that all you're taking with you?
It's all I have, sir.
Right. Well, oh, dear.
Yes, I best be off.
I've got a train to catch.
Goodbye, sir.
Goodbye, Alfred.
Beg your pardon, sir?
I said goodbye.
Yes.
Goodbye, sir.
I spy with my little eye,
something that is...
Yellow.
ALL: Score, Gotham, score! We want more!
Hit them where it hurts
and knock them to the floor!
ALL: Whoo!
Yay, Gotham!
(GRUNTS)
- Oh, hello, Ms. Kringle.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
Hello, Mr. Nygma.
How is your day going?
(CHUCKLES) Fine.
Um, question for you.
- Yes?
- Um... (LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
Did you know
that house flies hum in the key of F?
(EXHALES)
No. (CLEARS THROAT)
No, I did not know that.
Okay, then.
- Well, uh, bye.
- Bye.
(FOOTSTEPS RECEDING)
Damn it!
We agreed you were going to ask her out.
We didn't agree to ask her,
we agreed to think about asking her.
But there's no point.
She doesn't like you.
ED: Maybe she'll like me.
You ever consider that?
Maybe she'll like me.
I got confidence. Ladies love that.
No, she won't like you.
She won't. Go away.
Please, just go away!
Hey.
(CHEERLEADERS CHATTERING)
(HORN BLARING)
Whoo!
Ah!
(CHEERLEADERS SCREAMING)
We got a sighting of the stolen truck.
Yeavely Park.
(CRYING)
I want you all to know
this was a very difficult decision for us.
It was between you
and a senior citizen bingo party.
In the end, we decided to skew
a little younger.
Youth won the day. Sorry.
Give me an O!
(CHEERLEADERS CRYING)
- (GUNSHOT)
- (SCREAMING)
- I said give me an O.
- CHEERLEADERS: O.
JEROME: Give me an N.
CHEERLEADERS: N.
- Give me another O!
- CHEERLEADERS: O!
What does that spell?
- "O" no!
- CHEERLEADERS: "O" no!
(SCREAMING)
Do it, do it, do it!
Ready? Okay!
(SCREAMING HYSTERICALLY)
This is so embarrassing.
Anyone got a light?
(CRYING)
I do.
(SIRENS WAILING)
Stand your ground, boys.
They can't shoot at the bus.
- (GUNFIRE)
- Hold your fire! Hold your fire!
(GROANS)
Aaron, Greenwood, get the truck started.
We're gonna blow this barbeque!
(EMPTY CHAMBER CLICKS)
Light 'em up!
- (LIGHTER CLICKS)
- (LAUGHS)
(SCREAMING)
(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
(YELPS)
(CHEERLEADERS SCREAMING)
(GROANS)
(STARTS ENGINE)
- (EXPLOSION)
- (CHEERLEADERS SCREAMING)
(CRYING)
GIRL: I want to go home!
- Everybody okay?
- CHEERLEADERS: Yeah.
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
Who broke you out, Dobkins?
You're gonna have to talk sooner or later.
Tell me now.
I'm a victim here, sir.
I was coerced, abducted and coerced.
- By who?
- If I tell you that,
I gotta get some kind of guaran--
- (GUNSHOTS)
- (GROANS)
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
OFFICER: Get back! Get back!
I understand
you were just trying to protect me.
But there's nothing,
nothing that you can do to stop me
from carrying out my father's work.
I know that now.
I don't want you to go, Alfred.
But you're either with me,
or you're against me.
And if you're against me,
I don't have a choice.
I'm with you, Master Bruce.
I've always been with you.
But what you're doing
is tantamount to suicide.
This is big boy stuff.
You're too young. You're not ready.
Then make me ready.
You've lived a dangerous life,
and you survived.
So teach me. Teach me how to do the same.
I'll do whatever it takes.
I'll train every day.
Yeah, but you said that before,
didn't you?
That was before. Now I know the truth!
And I know what I have to do.
I'll even go back to school, if you want.
School, even?
If I agree to help you, to make you ready,
you must do exactly as I say
and when I say it, with no exceptions.
Is that understood?
Understood.
But, in return,
you must fix that computer.
Fix it? How on Earth am I gonna do that?
That's not my problem.
I'm not the one who broke it.
High caliber, high velocity.
Judging by the size of the wounds,
it was definitely shot from some distance.
Someone knew how to shoot.
Who, damn it?
And why cheerleaders? Where's the motive?
They didn't even ask for a ransom.
They want headlines. They want mass panic.
- Well, they got it.
- ESSEN: Yeah.
Let's see if we can't ID that bullet.
Never know your luck.
- (SIGHS) Holding up?
- Holding up.
Love you.
Likewise.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Gin and tonic, please, uh, guv'nor.
Ice and a slice.
Nice place.
It is.
- Been here before, then, have you?
- It's my regular spot.
Oh, right, you're a local. Nice.
Don't I know you?
Do you?
Yeah...
You're that Mr. Fox, that scientific chap
from Wayne Enterprises, isn't ya?
That is me.
Alfred Pennyworth.
Young Master Bruce Wayne's guardian.
Ah, yes!
It's a funny old game, though, isn't it?
Coincidence. I mean,
me bumping into you like this. I mean...
I was just thinking about you.
Hmm.
Okay, Mr. Pennyworth, I'll bite.
What were you thinking about me?
Oh, Alfred, please.
Please, Lucius.
Lucius. Lucius.
You know,
I once knew this geezer called Onslow
in the Isle of Dogs,
in the East End of London.
Lairy little scallywag he was.
He was too smiley by half.
Never trusted him.
Anyway, one day, Lucius,
he comes bowling up to me
and he asks me
to do him this right, iffy favor.
It doesn't matter what it was.
The point being,
against my better judgment,
I agreed to do it.
But Lucius,
I told him, I told him straight.
I said, "You let me down, Onslow,
"I will tuck you up,
sunshine, like a kipper."
He swears blind, swears on his mother's
grave he'd never do such a thing.
But, of course, he did.
Couldn't help himself. He let me down.
So I tucked him up.
Like a kipper.
What is a kipper?
It's a type of smoked fish.
Very nice with eggs
and brown toast for breakfast.
But what I learned from Onslow is this.
There are two types of people
on this planet, you see.
Them you can trust
and them you can't.
I cannot disagree.
Which kind are you?
Both kinds of people would
give you the same answer, wouldn't they?
Exactly. Exactly right.
There lieth the problem, Lucius.
You see, I need to confide in you.
But I need to know
that you're trustworthy.
Perhaps I should decline your confidence.
I don't like the sound of these kippers.
Yeah, well,
it's a bit late for that, unfortunately.
I mean, it's you after all,
Lucius, that created this mess
when you told young Master Bruce
that his dear old dead dad was a stoic.
- Ah.
- Ah. Exactly. See, there's the problem.
I got no one else to turn to.
I have to confide in you.
- I see.
- Do you?
Let me just be crystal clear about this.
If it turns out (CLICKS TONGUE)
that I can't trust you,
I swear on my mother's grave,
you, my old sausage,
are a dead man.
I have only the best intentions
for Bruce Wayne.
Well, another gin and tonic,
please, uh, guv'nor.
And whatever this young man's drinking,
one for yourself.
How are you at fixing computers?
Hey, Alvarez.
- Yo.
- (PHONE RINGING)
Let Ballistics know
we got a red-ball for them, will ya?
ALVAREZ: On it.
Gordon.
BARBARA: Hello, Jim. It's Barbara.
Hi, Barbara. How are you?
Oh, me? I'm fabulous. How are you?
I'm good. What's new?
Mr. Cool Guy, huh?
You must be so mad at me.
Listen to me.
If you turn yourself in, I can help you.
(SCOFFS) How, Jim? By taking me back
to Arkham? I don't think so.
You're sick.
Of course. Everything's always my fault.
So typical.
Listen to me. I know you, Barbara.
I know you.
You're a good, kind woman.
This isn't you.
(CHUCKLES DERISIVELY)
You could always make me laugh.
(LAUGHING EVILLY)
How do I look?
I need to talk to Commissioner Essen
right away. It's an emergency.
OFFICER: Yeah, go ahead,
she's right upstairs.
I'm sorry, sir, you said this was...
Yo, Commish.
ESSEN: Yeah.
Heard you were looking for us.
(CLATTERS)
OFFICER: What the hell are...
- (GUNFIRE)
- Put him down!
(GRUNTS)
(GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
(YELLS)
JIM: Barbara! Don't move.
You're wrong about me, Jim.
I tried telling you, but you never listen.
I'm listening now.
Yeah, sure you are. Now.
Come on.
Let's go talk this through, huh?
Oh, it's too late for that.
(MAN YELLS)
(JIM GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Ow.
(GRUNTING)
- (PUNCHING)
- (JIM GRUNTING)
- (GROANS)
- BARBARA: Aaron.
That's enough.
(GROANING)
I'm not sick, I'm free.
You don't get that.
I could explain it,
but you should probably get back to work.
Who knows what went wrong
while you were gone.
(KISSES)
- MAN: No, please!
- (GLASS SHATTERING)
(GUNFIRE)
(LAUGHING)
- (GUNFIRE CONTINUES)
- (MAN SCREAMING)
(GUNSHOT)
(WHISTLES)
Hell of a first week you're having,
Commissioner.
I wish I could tell you
that things were gonna get better for you.
They're not.
OFFICER: (WEAKLY) Help.
Here, bring that up here.
Get a better angle of the room.
Why are you doing this?
To rule the world.
Blah, blah, blah. But we'll settle
for some dead cops and some good PR.
- Kidding.
- Yeah, whatever, I get it.
You're just crazy.
Crazy?
Look at me.
You can see I'm not crazy.
Very soon, little man, you will be dead,
and the world will go on without you.
You'll be nothing.
No one will even remember your name.
Mmm...
No. That is where you're wrong, old lady.
We will leave a mark on this city.
We will spread across it like a virus.
Do you know why?
There's nothing
more contagious than laughter.
- (GUNSHOT)
- (GROANS)
(BODY THUDS)
My line.
There's nothing
more contagious than laughter.
- (LAUGHS)
- (SPITS)
That was strangely pleasant. Do it again.
- (GRUNTS)
- Oh!
That's gonna leave a mark.
(LAUGHS MANICALLY)
You got me.
My turn.
(LAUGHS MANIACALLY)
(EARS RINGING)
(GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Lee.
Jim!
You hurt?
No, I was in my office
and I heard gunfire, and I hid.
Where were you?
Barbara was here. She lured me away.
Essen!
OFFICER: It's okay. Just breathe.
Breathe. Come on.
(GASPING)
Hang on, Cap. Hang on.
Boss. Boss. Stay with me.
Breathe.
(CONTINUES GASPING)
It's a new day, Jim.
(GASPING STOPS)
This is
indeed broken.
- I have a lot of questions for you.
- Ah, I imagine so.
Did my father tell you everything?
Heavens, no.
Your father, he was a very private man.
He had to be.
I simply helped with technical resources,
like this computer.
Do you know what's on it?
No. I didn't wanna know, to be honest.
- But you can fix it?
- Mmm, I should think so.
But it is going to take some time.
Well, uh, thank you, for your help.
I loved your father.
I regret that I never told him so.
I regret that I didn't help him more.
Hand me the soldering iron, will you?
Yeah.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Master Bruce.
What is it, Alfred?
Okay. How you doing, Mr. Nygma?
Okay, two aspirin for you. You're welcome.
Detective Gordon!
Bruce.
I heard the news.
I was worried something happened to you.
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
I'm very relieved.
Me, too.
The last time that we met,
I was very hard on you.
I wanted to apologize.
You've been a really good friend.
(SIRENS WAILING)
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
BULLOCK: She was a good woman.
Good cop.
It's good to see you,
but you don't have to do this.
Let's not talk about it.
We are who we are, right?
No use fighting it.
What did Scotty say?
She'll understand,
or she won't.
Guys. You need to see this.
I'm reporting live from
the scene of the G.C.P.D. massacre.
We have just obtained
video footage of the attack
recorded by one of the assailants.
I wanna warn those of you watching,
what you're about to see is very graphic.
Hello, Gotham City! We're the Maniax.
And I'm Jerome,
the shot-caller of our little gang.
We're here to spread the message
of wisdom and hope. (CHUCKLES)
(MAN GROANING)
- (GUNSHOT)
- (MAN GROANS)
Some people have no manners.
You're all prisoners.
What you call sanity
is just a prison in your minds
that stops you from seeing
that you're just tiny, little cogs
in a giant absurd machine.
Wake up!
Why be a cog?
Be free like us.
Just like him!
Smile!
(LAUGHS MANICALLY)
(SIREN WAILING)
Oh, time to go.
But don't worry, we'll be back very soon.
Hang on to your hats, folks,
'cause you ain't seen nothing yet!
(LAUGHS MANIACALLY)
English - SDH