Please verify that the P-one ATA removal
on replacement cap part
one and two are complete.
DMA M-one, M-two, M-three and M-four
are complete.
Ok. Copy that, Explorer.
Dr. Stone, Houston.
Medical is concerned
about your ECG readings.
I am fine Houston.
Well, Medical doesn't agree Doc.
Are you feeling nauseous?
Not any more than usual Houston.
Diagnostics are green.
Link to communications card
ready for data reception.
If this works,
when we touch down tomorrow,
I am buying all you guys
a round of drinks.
That's a date, Doctor.
Just remember,
Houston is partial to margaritas.
Booting comms card now.
Please confirm link.
That's a negative,
we are not seeing any data.
Standby Houston,
I am gonna reboot the comms card.
Standing by.
Houston, I have a bad feeling
about this mission.
Please expand.
Ok, let me tell you a story.
It was ninety-six.
I had been up here for 42 days.
Every time I passed over Texas,
I looked down,
knowing that Mrs. Kowalski
was looking up,
thinking of me.
6 weeks I am blowing kisses at that woman.
Then we land at Edwards and I find out
that she is run off with this lawyer.
So, I packed my car,
and I headed to Tijuana.
You have told this story, Kowalski.
As Houston recalls,
she... took off in your 74' GTO.
Engineering requests fuel status
on the jetpack prototype.
Five hours off the reservation
and I show 30 percent drain.
Give my compliments to Engineering.
Except for a slight malfunction
in the nulling of the roll axis,
this jetpack is one prime piece of thrust.
Engineering says thank you.
Tell them I still prefer
my 67' Corvette, though.
Speaking of which, did I ever tell you...
We know the Corvette story, Matt.
Even Engineering?
Especially Engineering.
We are going to miss you, Matt.
Comms card reboot in progress.
Thank you, Doctor.
Shariff, what's your status?
Nearly there.
Replacing battery module A-one and C.
Could you be a little more specific?
Indeterminate estimates
make Houston anxious.
No, no, no, Houston.
Don't be anxious.
Anxiety is not good for the heart.
System is ready to reactivate.
Hubble telescope engaged.
Upgrade fully functional.
That applause you hear is for you Shariff.
Congratulations.
Kick back, take the rest of the day off.
Matt, do you have a visual on just what
Mission Specialist Shariff is doing up there?
He appears to be doing
some form of the Macarena.
But that would be just a best-guess
scenario on my part.
Dr. Stone, Houston.
Medical now have you with
a temperature drop to 35.9
and a heart rate rise to 70.
How are you feeling?
Houston, I am fine.
It's just keeping your lunch down
in zero-G is harder than it looks.
Dr. Stone, Medical is asking
if you want to return to Explorer.
Negative.
We have been here a week, Houston.
Let's just finish this.
Card is up.
No, that's a negative.
I am afraid we are getting
nothing on this end, Doctor.
Try again.
No, still nothing.
Houston, can you
please turn that music off?
Kowalski?
Not a problem.
Thank you, Kowalski.
Now, Houston?
That's a negative.
Could Houston be misinterpreting the data?
Well, we are not receiving any data.
Engineering is recommending
a vis check for component damage.
Let me see what's going on.
What have we got?
Visual examination doesn't
reveal any damaged components.
The problem must be originating
from the comms panel.
Yeah, that seems to be the case.
Engineering admits that you
warned us that this could happen.
That's as close to an apology
as you are going to get from them.
We should have listened to you Doc.
Well, looks like we are going
to have to improvise.
I am on it.
How long do you think it will take you?
One hour.
Outstanding.
Installing your system in the Hubble
is the purpose of this mission
and so we appreciate
your patience Doctor.
Kowalski, we... we know you don't care
about things like this,
but, for your information this delay
is not gonna be long enough
for you to break Anatoly
Solovyev's spacewalking record.
It seems like you are gonna be left...
Seventy-five minutes shy?
Never crossed my mind.
Matt...
it's been a privilege.
Right back at you, Houston.
Enjoy your last walk.
Am I a go to assist Dr. Stone
in removing the panel?
Assistance appreciated.
Permission granted.
Thank you Houston.
Mind if I join the fun?
Certainly.
How you feeling?
Like a Chihuahua
that's being tumble dried.
Well, it's been a rough week.
If it makes you feel any better,
I coughed up everything but,
my kidneys on my first ride.
Shit.
Sorry.
I am used to a basement lab in a hospital
where things fall to the floor.
Thank you.
Well, you are the genius up here.
I only drive the bus.
Yeah, well..
Call me a genius if I can get
this board initialized in the next hour.
Explorer, this is Houston.
Go ahead, Houston.
NORAD reports a Russian satellite
has incurred a missile strike.
The impact has created
a cloud of debris,
orbiting at 20,000 miles per hour.
Current debris orbit does not
overlap with your trajectory.
We will keep you posted
on any developments.
Copy that Houston.
Should we...
Should we be worried?
No, let's let the boys down
there worry for us.
Explorer, engage arm
and pivot to cargo bay.
Stand by for arm maneuver.
So doc, now that you work for NASA,
how do you like us?
Kind of like winning the lottery?
I was just happy that
they didn't cut the funding to my research.
How long was your training?
Six months.
Including holidays?
So,
what is this scanning system?
Oh, nothing Matt.
It's just a new set of eyes
to scan the edge of the universe.
It's designed for hospital use,
but this one is a prototype.
Stand by for locking.
Listen...
they don't bankroll prototypes.
Even for your pretty blue eyes.
Well,
my eyes are brown.
Right now, your eyes are bloodshot.
Kowalski!
Is this great or what?
And to think he went to Harvard.
You got to admit one thing.
Can't beat the view.
So, what do you like
about being up here?
The silence.
I could get used to it.
Terrific.
Houston, from first inspection,
comms panel appears to be dead.
Am I a go to cut link to auxiliary?
You are the expert, doctor.
It's your call.
Houston, I have a bad feeling
about this mission.
Please elaborate.
It's the same feeling I had
about Mardi Gras in 1987.
That is affirmative.
Surprisingly, Control hasn't heard
the Mardi Gras story.
Please proceed.
Well, it's day one and I am bumping
my way down Bourbon Street
looking for a sister of a friend of mine.
Streets are full of people, I am thinking
there is no way I am gonna find this girl.
Proceeding to override.
Then all of the sudden I look up,
and there she is
and I am about to yell out,
and I see she is holding hands
with some short,
hairy guy in board
shorts and a Margaritaville shirt.
And then I realize,
that this guy is not a guy.
That my girl is holding hands with...
ISS, this is Houston.
Proceed Houston.
Explorer, this is Houston.
Go ahead Houston.
Mission abort.
Repeat. Mission abort.
Initiate emergency disconnect from Hubble.
Begin reentry procedure.
ISS, initiate emergency evacuation.
Copy all Houston and in work.
Matt, immediate return to Explorer.
Repeat, immediate return to Explorer.
Copy.
Explorer prep airlock.
Airlock engaged,
Ready to receive.
Houston elaborate.
Debris from the missile strike
has caused a chain reaction,
hitting other satellites
and creating new debris.
Traveling faster than a high-speed
bullet up towards your altitude.
All copy?
Copy all.
Put a bow on it, Dr. Stone.
I can't.
The board is still initializing.
I am not gonna ask you again.
One second.
Not one second.
Now!
Shut it down.
That's an order.
Ok, I am sorry.
I am sorry, I am done.
I am done.
Kowalski, initiate emergency
disconnect from the Hubble.
Alright Shariff, let's do this.
Roger Matt.
Houston update.
Well, we have a full on chain reaction.
It's been confirmed that it's
the unintentional side effect
of the Russians striking
one of their own satellites.
They shot down their own satellite?
Right of disposal.
Most likely a spy sat gone bad.
Now it's shrapnel.
Explorer, ready to disengage HST.
Locks releasing in three... two... one.
Explorer, new data coming through.
What's the blowback, Houston?
It's not good.
Most of our systems are gone.
Debris chain reaction
is out of control and rapidly expanding.
Multiple satellites are down,
and they keep on falling.
Define 'multiple satellites.
Most of them are gone.
Telecommunication systems are dead.
Expect a communication blackout
at any moment.
Kowalski, visual of debris at 9 o'clock.
Half of North America
just lost their Facebook.
Explorer, repeat,
expect a communication
blackout at any moment.
Copy that, Houston.
Explorer, this is Kowalski,
confirming visual contact with debris.
Debris is from a BSE sat.
Heads up!
To repeat, I have...
Dr. Stone requesting faster transport.
We have to go.
We have to go, go, go!
Kennedy reports meteorological conditions
no-go for re-entry.
Houston, Explorer, Copy.
Explorer, Dr. Stone requesting
faster transport to bay area.
Explorer, do you copy?
Explorer, permission to retrieve Dr. Stone.
You are a go, Kowalski.
Houston, this is Explorer, copy.
Alright.
We have lost Houston.
Unstrap.
Look, we need to get the hell out of here.
Alright.
Need some help there, Matt?
No, don't wait for us.
It's stuck!
Man down! Man down!
Houston, this is Explorer, copy.
Kowalski, repor...
Explorer is been hit!
Explorer, do you read?
Explorer, over!
Explorer!
Astronaut is off structure!
Dr. Stone is off structure!
Dr. Stone, detach!
No!
You must detach!
If you don't detach,
that arm is gonna carry you too far!
Listen to my voice!
You need to focus!
I am losing visual of you.
In a few seconds,
I won't be able to track you.
You need to detach!
I can't see you anymore!
Do it now!
I am trying! I am trying!
Houston, I have lost visual of Dr. Stone.
Dr. Stone, do you copy?
Repeat, do you copy?
Yes, yes, yes, I copy.
I am detached.
Give me your position!
I don't, I don't, I don't know!
I don't know!
I am spinning!
I can't...
Report your position.
GPS is down, I can't.
It's down, I can't...
Give me a visual.
I told you, nothing.
I see nothing!
Do you have a visual of Explorer?
No. No.
Do you have a visual of ISS?
No.
You need to focus.
Anything, use the sun and the Earth,
give me coordinates.
I can't breathe! I can't breathe!
Give me coordinates?
Dr. Stone, do you copy?
Repeat, do you copy?
Give me your position!
Report your position.
Do you have a visual of Explorer?
Do you have a visual of ISS?
I need you to focus. Anything.
Use the sun and the Earth,
give me coordinates.
Give me coordinates.
Kowalski?
Kowalski, do you copy?
Kowalski... I have... have a vision.
Kowalski, I have a visual.
I have... have a visual of Explorer.
With north at...
at 12 o'clock
and the shuttle is at...
at the center of the dial.
I can see...
I can see the Chinese station.
No, it's the International Space Station.
ISS is at...
ISS is at 7 o'clock.
Lieutenant Kowalski, do you copy?
Explorer, do you...
do you copy?
Houston, do you copy?
Houston this is...
Mission Specialist Ryan Stone.
I am off structure and I am drifting.
Do you copy?
Anyone?
Anybody?
Do you copy?
Please copy.
Please.
Dr. Stone, do you copy?
Yeah, Lieutenant Kowalski, yes.
Yes, Lieutenant Kowalski.
Repeat, do you copy?
Yes, yes, I copy, I am here!
I am here.
Flash your light!
My light. my light.
Flash it so I can see you.
Ok.
I...
Ok, ok.
Here, here.
Alright.
Am here.
There you are.
Hang on tight.
Report your status.
I am fine, fine.
I am alright.
Your status.
Give me your readings.
3... 3...
3.6 PSI.
Your O2, give me your O2.
Oxygen is going down.
It's going down fast.
It's going down fast, 9.
No, 8-8 percent.
Ok, you are breathing too fast.
83.9 percent.
You are burning oxygen,
and we don't want to do that.
We want to relax. Copy?
Ok, sorry. Yes, copy, copy.
Alright. Nearly there.
Please hurry.
You can holster
that torch, Dr. Stone.
Sorry.
Got you. Alright.
Now, I am gonna tether you to me.
I know, you never realized how
devastatingly good-looking I am.
But I need you to stop staring
and help me with the tether.
Ok?
Ok, ok.
I got it.
Alright, here we go.
Alright.
Now, to clear you from the jets,
I am gonna give you a little push.
No, no, no, no. No, no, no.
Not a push.
No, no.
A nudge.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Damn it, no! No!
See?
Where you go I go.
Better.
Let's get out of here.
Goddamn it.
I know what you mean.
Damn it.
You are burning oxygen.
We are going back to the shuttle.
How is that for a plan?
Copy?
Fuck!
Right. Copy that.
Houston, in the blind.
This is Kowalski.
Dr. Stone and I are gonna
make our way back to base.
Can you get the Explorer
to prepare the airlock for arrival? Copy.
Houston, this is Kowalski.
How do you copy?
Houston, in the blind.
This is Kowalski.
They can't hear us.
We don't know that.
That's why we keep talking.
If somebody is listening,
they might just save your life.
Set your watch for 90 minutes.
Why 90?
Well, Houston clocked that debris
at 50,000 miles an hour.
If you factor in our current orbit,
then I figure we got about 90 minutes
before we get our asses kicked again.
O2 down to 6 percent.
Ok.
Pretty scary shit being
untethered up here, isn't it?
Yeah, pretty scary shit.
Well, you did alright.
Well, you were not so bad yourself.
Houston, in the blind.
This is Kowalski.
Our current location
is approximately...
900 meters out from the Explorer.
Dr. Stone and I would like to retrieve
the body of Mission Specialist Shariff
and return it to the shuttle.
Am I a go to retrieve?
Roger that.
Where is he?
Oh, my God.
Grab him!
I am trying, I am trying!
You are pulling me away.
Got... I got him!
Clutch him like he is your Valentine.
I got him.
I can't engage my thrust with you
two yo-yoing around.
Jesus Christ.
Here is hoping you have a hell
of an insurance policy, Houston.
The damages to Explorer...
are catastrophic.
Will commence search for survivors.
O2 down to 5 percent.
Alright, here we go.
Careful of the edges!
Here. Here!
Houston in the blind.
To confirm.
Mission Specialist Dr. Stone
and Mission Commander Matthew Kowalski
are the sole survivors
of the STS-1-5-7.
I apologize for not complying.
I should have stopped working as
soon as you instructed me to.
We were gonna get hit no matter what.
There was nothing you could
do to change that.
Hey?
Yes.
Alright.
We have to make our
way to the Space Station.
Over there.
It's a bit of a hike, but we need
to use their escape pod,
the Soyuz, to get back to Earth.
Agreed?
Dr. Stone,
agreed?
Agreed.
Alright. After you.
Oh, God.
Houston, in the blind.
This is Kowalski.
Dr. Stone and I have determined
to proceed to ISS
and use one of their Soyuz for re-entry.
ISS, if you hear us...
we could sure use a rescue mission.
O2 down to 2 percent.
We are getting there.
Beautiful, don't you think?
What?
The sunrise.
That's what I am gonna miss the most.
So where is home, Dr. Stone?
Ryan, where is home?
Home?
Down there.
Mother Earth.
Where do you pitch you tent?
Lake Zurich.
Where the hell is that?
Illinois.
Central Time Zone.
That would make it roughly...
8 p.m.
What are the good people of Lake
Zurich doing at 8 o'clock?
I don't know.
I am not gonna make it.
I am slowing you down.
What would you be doing?
Come on, Ryan.
It's 8 o'clock.
You have just left the hospital
after an 18 hour shift.
Driving home.
The radio.
I listen to the radio.
There we go.
Let me guess.
NPR?
Classical?
Top 40?
Anything.
I don't care, as long as they don't talk.
I just drive.
And where are you driving to?
What do you miss down there?
Is there a Mr. Stone?
No.
Nobody special?
Somebody down there looking up,
thinking about you?
Ryan?
I had a daughter.
She was four.
She was at school playing tag.
Slipped, hit her head and that was it.
Stupidest thing.
I was driving when I got the call, so...
Ever since then, that's what I do.
I wake up.
I go to work.
And I just drive.
O2 down to 1 percent.
Well, I have got good news and bad news.
The good news is, we are about
five minutes
from the ISS and I know where
the Russians stash their vodka.
And that is good, because
I am running on fumes here.
The bad news is, I am gonna be about
10 minutes short of breaking Anatoly's record,
and...
I...
What?
I am redlining my O2 tank pressure is low.
Your tank is out of oxygen
but you still have it in your suit.
Got it.
So you have to sip, not gulp.
Wine, not beer.
Sip, Ryan.
Houston, in the blind,
we have a visual of the ISS.
The station must have been evacuated
because the first Soyuz is missing.
The second Soyuz exhibits surface damage,
and its chute has been deployed.
Any use as an escape pod
for re-entry
is impossible.
Shouldn't we be turning we are drifting again.
Not yet.
I was not kidding about those fumes.
This can has one or two good thrusts left...
if we are lucky.
Steady.
Aim.
Fire!
Brake! Brake!
You have to brake!
I can't, the can is empty.
We are gonna hit hard!
Grab a hold of anything you can!
What do I do?
Ryan!
The tether broke, I am detached!
I am detached!
Grab a hold!
Grab anything!
Ryan!
Give me five!
I have got you.
Right here,
Shit!
No, no. No, no, no, no, no.
Got you.
You just hold on..
And I am gonna start pulling you in.
Hey, Doc.
Just hold on, hang on.
I am gonna pull you in.
Ryan, listen.
You have to let me go.
No.
The ropes are too loose.
I am pulling you with me.
You have to let me go,
or we both die.
I am not letting you go, we are fine!
No.
Ryan, let me go.
No. No.
You are not going anywhere.
It's not up to you.
No, no, no, no...
Please don't do this.
Please don't, Matt.
You are gonna make it, Ryan.
No!
I had you. I had you!
I had you.
Ryan, do you hear me?
Do you copy?
My CO2 alarm went off.
Look, you need to board the station.
Do you see the airlock?
Hey Ryan,
you copy?
Look for the airlock.
It's above you, next to the Zarya module.
You see it?
Yes.
Yes, I see it.
I see it.
Alright, good.
That's where you want to go.
Now you are getting lightheaded, right?
Yeah.
Yes.
That's because you are breathing CO2.
You are losing consciousness.
You need to board the station.
Ok.
That second Soyuz
is too damaged for re-entry,
but it's perfectly fine
for a little Sunday drive.
Sunday drive?
Look to the west.
You see that dot in the distance?
That's a Chinese station.
Yes.
You are gonna take the Soyuz,
and you are gonna cruise over there.
Chinese lifeboat is a Shenzhou.
I have never flown a Shenzhou.
It doesn't matter.
Its re-entry protocol is identical to the Soyuz.
Ok.
You never flown the Soyuz either?
Only a simulator.
Well, then you know.
But I crashed it.
It's a simulator,
that's what it's designed for.
Every time.
I crashed it every time.
You point the damn thing at Earth.
It's not rocket science.
And by this time tomorrow,
you are gonna be back in Lake Zurich
with a hell of a story to tell.
You copy?
Ryan, you copy?
I am gonna take the
Soyuz and come get you.
No, you are not.
I am coming to get you
No, I have got too much of a head start on you.
I am coming to get you.
I am afraid that ship already sailed.
Ryan, you are gonna have to learn to let go.
But I...
I want to hear you say you are gonna make it...
Come on Ryan, say it.
I am gonna make it.
Alright.
Keep going.
What kind of name is Ryan for a girl?
Dad wanted a boy.
Are you close to the airlock?
Not yet.
Keep going.
So now that we have some distance between us...
you are attracted to me, right?
What?
Well...
people say I have beautiful blue eyes.
You have beautiful...
You have beautiful blue eyes.
I have brown eyes.
You want to know the good news?
What?
I am gonna break Anatoly's record,
and I think mine is gonna stand for a long,
long time.
No.
I am coming to get you.
Oh, my God.
What? What?
Hey Ryan?
Yeah?
You should see the sun on the Ganges.
It's amazing.
Where are you?
Comms. Comms.
There you are, Ok.
Matt, this is Ryan, copy.
Matt, I made it, I am here, I am on the station.
Do you copy?
Come on, Matt, talk to me.
Tell me where you are, give me your position.
Where are you? Give me a visual.
Just tell me what you see.
Come on. You have been yammering
since we left Cape Canaveral,
and now you decide to shut up?
Talk to me.
Just say something, say anything!
I don't care!
Hey...
Tell me about Mardi Gras.
Tell me about the hairy guy?
Tell me what happened.
What happened to the hairy guy?
Please talk to me.
Please.
Houston, in the blind...
this is Mission Specialist Ryan Stone
reporting from the ISS.
All communications
with Mission Commander
Matthew Kowalski have been lost.
Radio transmission absent.
Visuals nonexistent.
To confirm,
I, Ryan Stone, am the sole survivor
of STS-1-5-7.
What now?
Ok.
Where is it?
Where is the power?
Here you are.
Great, just like training.
Undocking.
Red.
Ok.
Ok, where is it?
Where is it?
Come on.
Ok.
Ok, I remember this, I remember this.
You don't have four minutes.
We are going manual
Come on.
Ok.
Active. Activate, undock.
7 minutes to get out of here.
Alright, ok.
What? What, what?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on!
That's right, that's right, right, right, right.
That's right, that's right, that's right,
that's right, that's right.
Come on.
Great.
Clear skies with a chance of satellite debris.
Ok, we detach this, and we go home.
Piece of cake.
Ok.
Ok, what do we have?
Ok, alright.
Shit.
Ok, come on.
Come on, come on.
Alright.
I hate space.
Shut up.
Ok.
Alright.
That's good.
Ok.
Let's stabilize you.
Let's go visit the Chinese station.
Houston, in the blind,
Tiangong is approximately,
100 kilometers...
to the west,
and I am off its...
course by about...
30 degrees. I will correct trajectory.
Ok.
I will engage S-Ka-Dae in five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
What's happening, what's happening?
Come on, come on.
One.
You got to be kidding me.
You got to be kidding me!
No!
Don't you fuck...
Houston, in the blind.
Houston, in the blind, this is Dr. Ryan Stone.
I am calling from the Soyuz TMA-1-4-M.
I am currently out of fuel and adrift, do you copy?
Houston.
This is Dr. Ryan Stone.
Do you copy?
Houston. This is Ryan Stone.
Houston, this is Missish...
Mission Specialist Ryan Stone, do you copy?
Houston?
Houston, please confirm identity.
Houston, you are coming in over
an A.M. frequency. Copy.
Do you copy?
Is this the Chinese station?
Is this Tiangong? Copy.
Mayday, can you copy?
Mayday, mayday.
Mayday!
Yes, yes.
Mayday, mayday.
Aningaaq.
Aningaaq said... Is that your...
Is that your name?
Aningaaq is your... is your name?
Aningaaq, Aningaaq, Mayday!
No, no, no. No, my name is not Mayday.
I am Stone.
Dr. Ryan Stone, I need help.
I am...
Those are dogs.
They are calling from Earth.
Aningaaq,
make your dogs bark again for me,
would you please?
Your dogs. Dogs,
you know. Woof, woof. Dogs.
Oh, I am gonna die, Aningaaq.
I know, we are all gonna die.
Everybody knows that.
But I am gonna die today.
Funny, that.
You know, to know...
But the thing is, it's that I am still scared.
I am really scared.
Nobody will mourn for me,
no one will pray for my soul.
Will you mourn for me?
Will you say a prayer for me?
Or is it too late?
I mean, I would say one for myself,
but I have never prayed in my life, so...
Nobody ever taught me how.
A baby.
There is a baby with you?
Is that a lullaby you are singing?
That's so sweet.
I used to sing to my baby.
I hope I see her soon.
That's nice, Aningaaq.
Keep singing, just like that.
Sing me to sleep and I will sleep.
Keep singing.
And sing and sing.
No, no, no, don't!
Check your watch.
13 hours and 11 minutes.
Call Anatoly and tell him he is been bumped.
It's a little gloomy in here, isn't it?
How did you?
Trust me, it's a hell of a story.
But how...
That's better.
I found a little extra...
a little extra battery power.
It helps that I didn't
have you around to distract me.
I have to say.
I am glad to see you, I didn't think
you were gonna make it.
Did you find the vodka?
You...
You never told me where...
Oh well.
Where it was so...
To Anatoly.
Na zdorovje.
No?
Alright.
Let's get out of here.
The Chinese station is about
a hundred miles.
Just a little Sunday drive.
We can't.
Sure we can.
There is no fuel, I tried everything.
Well, there is always something we can do.
I tried everything.
Did you try the soft landing jets?
They are for landing. So...
Well, landing is launching.
It's the same thing.
Didn't you learn about that in training?
I never got to land the simulator.
I told you that.
But you know about it.
And I crashed it every time.
Listen.
Do you want to go back,
or do you want to stay here?
I get it, it's nice up here.
You can just...
shut down all the systems,
turn out all the lights...
and just close your eyes
and tune out everybody.
There is nobody up here that can hurt you.
It's safe.
I mean, what's the point of going on?
What's the point of living?
Your kid died.
Doesn't get any rougher than that.
But still, it's a matter of what you do now.
If you decide to go,
then you got to just get on with it.
Sit back, enjoy the ride.
You got to plant both your feet on
the ground and start living life.
How did you get here?
I am telling you, it's a hell of a story.
Hey, Ryan?
What?
It's time to go home.
Landing...
Landing is launching.
I said...
Ok, landing, landing.
Landing is green.
Ok.
Ok,
landing.
Alright.
Ok.
Soft landing jets trigger automatically
at 3 meters before landing, so...
You are a clever son of a bitch, Matt.
I need to...
I need to get rid of the B.O and...
the engine module.
Right.
Ok.
Tri-module separation.
Go.
Ok.
Houston, here is the tricky part.
Soyuz has to think
we are 3 meters...
off the Earth.
Alright.
Ok.
Hey Matt?
Since I had to listen to endless
hours of your storytelling this week,
I need for you to do me a favor.
You are gonna see a little girl,
with brown hair,
very messy, lots of knots.
She doesn't like to brush it.
That's ok.
Her name is Sarah.
Can you please tell her
that Mama found her red shoe?
She was so worried about that shoe, Matt.
But it was just right under the bed.
Give her a big hug and a big kiss for me,
and tell her that Mama misses her.
You tell her that she is my angel.
And she makes me so proud.
So, so proud.
And you tell her that I am not quitting.
You tell her that I love her, Matt.
You tell her that I love her so much.
Can you do that for me?
Roger that?
Here we go.
You are losing altitude, Tiangong.
You keep dropping and you are gonna
kiss the atmosphere.
But not without me,
because you are my last ride.
Ok.
Wait.
5.
4.
3.
No more just driving.
Let's go home.
Steady.
Ok, come on, come on.
Steady, steady.
Come on. Come on.
Where are you?
Where are you? 45...
90, 180.
180.
Come on.
Ok, ok.
Alright.
Damn it.
Down, down, down.
Come to Mama.
Ok.
Ok. Shit!
Shenzhou, come on.
Shenzhou. Shenzhou.
Fuck.
Ok, this way.
Shenzhou.
In the Soyuz, the power button is...
here.
Ok...
undocking, undocking.
Eeni, meeni...
Ok, that doesn't sound good.
Miny...
moe.
No hablo chino.
Miny...
moe.
Ok.
Ok, good.
Houston.
Houston, in the blind.
This is Mission Specialist Ryan Stone
reporting from the Shenzhou.
I am about to undock from Tiangong...
And I have a bad feeling about this mission.
Reminds me of a story, Houston...
Never...
Never mind the story, Houston.
Never mind the story.
It's getting hot in here. Ok.
Alright.
Ok.
Alright, the way I see it,
there is only two possible outcomes.
Either I make it down there in one piece
and I have one hell of a story to tell,
or I burn up in the next 10 minutes.
Either way, whichever way...
no harm, no foul!
Because either way...
it will be one hell of a ride.
I am ready.
Shenzhou, in the blind,
this is Houston.
Indicate FM frequency.
Our radars detect you
on a re-entry trajectory.
If you copy, please confirm identity.
This is Houston.
It's freezing, it's boring as hell.
Is: No money down!
Messages, we will be right...
Please confirm identity.
Skies over the Midwest are completely clear...
We have deployed a rescue
mission to retrieve you.
Rescue mission is on the way.
Shenzhou, in the blind, this is Houston.
We have deployed a rescue mission
to retrieve you.
Thank you.
By LESAIGNEUR
Sync & corrections May 2022