Tomar-Re: BILLIONS OF YEARS AGO, A RACE OF IMMORTALS HARNESSED
THE MOST POWERFUL FORCE IN EXISTENCE:
THE EMERALD ENERGY OF WILLPOWER.
THESE IMMORTALS, THE GUARDIANS OF THE UNIVERSE, BUILT A WORLD
FROM WHERE THEY COULD WATCH OVER ALL OF EXISTENCE --
THE PLANET OA.
THEY DIVIDED THE UNIVERSE INTO 3600 SECTORS.
A RING POWERED BY THE ENERGY OF WILL
WAS SENT TO EVERY SECTOR TO SELECT A RECRUIT.
IN ORDER TO BE CHOSEN BY THE RING,
IT WAS SAID ONE MUST BE WITHOUT FEAR.
TOGETHER, THESE 3600 RECRUITS FORMED
THE INTERGALACTIC PEACEKEEPERS
KNOWN AS THE GREEN LANTERN CORPS.
OF ALL THE THREATS THE CORPS EVER FACED,
THE GRAVEST WAS AN ENTITY OF FEAR KNOWN AS PARALLAX.
ONLY THE LEGENDARY GREEN LANTERN ABIN SUR
WAS CAPABLE OF CAPTURING AND IMPRISONING THIS BEAST,
WHICH HE DID ON THE LOST PLANET OF RYUT.
[ BEEPING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ ALL SCREAM ]
[ ALL BREATHING HEAVILY ]
YOU ARE AFRAID.
GOOD.
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
[ ROARS ]
[ BEEPING ]
SINESTRO, I'M TRAVELING AT MAXIMUM VELOCITY.
TELL FENTARA I SHOULD --
FENTARA IS DEAD.
THE PLANET'S INHABITANTS?
YOUR MISSION TO EVACUATE THEM IS NO LONGER NECESSARY.
IT'S JUST AS IT WAS ON TALOK.
EVERY LIFE FORM DESTROYED AND THEIR ESSENCE ABSORBED.
TRACES OF YELLOW POWER EVERYWHERE.
AND THE GUARDIANS?
THE GUARDIANS ARE SILENT.
I'VE DEMANDED AN AUDIENCE WITH THEM.
[ RING PULSING ]
Parallax: ABIN SUR.
[ ROARS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
I'M BADLY WOUNDED.
HEADING TO THE NEAREST INHABITED PLANET
FOR THE SELECTION PROCESS.
TELL THE GUARDIANS IT'S PARALLAX.
MM.
[ SUM 41's "BABY YOU DON'T WANNA KNOW" PLAYS ]
NO. NO.
♪ OH! ♪ [ MUSIC STOPS ]
SORRY, I GOTTA RUN. MAKE YOURSELF AT HOME, OKAY?
THERE'S, UH, WATER IN THE TAP.
[ MUSIC RESUMES ]
♪ I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU WANT, AND I DON'T WANNA KNOW ♪
♪ I GOT YOU WHERE I WANT, AND I WON'T LET GO ♪
♪ SO GET YOUR KICKS OUT QUICK WHILE YOU STILL GOT TIME ♪
♪ WELL, DO WHAT YOU WANT ♪
♪ BUT DON'T BE PROUD ♪
♪ 'CAUSE, BABY, YOU DON'T WANNA KNOW ♪
♪ I GOT YOU RIGHT WHERE I WANT ♪
♪ BUT, BABY, YOU DON'T WANNA KNOW ♪
♪ BABY, YOU DON'T WANNA KNOW ♪
OH! [ TIRES SCREECH ]
[ HORN HONKING ]
ASSHOLE.
Carl: THE FERRIS SABRE III IS STATE-OF-THE-ART
OF ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE FIGHTER PLANES.
IT HAS ALL OF THE FLYING AND COMBAT CAPABILITY
OF A HUMAN PILOT
BUT WITH NONE OF THE HUMAN ERROR THAT COMES WITH IT.
CARL ISN'T JUST BLOWING SMOKE
TO GET A CONTRACT, GENERAL.
YOUR STAFF, THESE CONTRACTORS, MY OFFICE,
WE'VE ALL BEEN PART OF THIS FROM THE GROUND UP.
WELL, I APPRECIATE THAT, SENATOR.
BUT TODAY THE RUBBER MEETS THE ROAD.
WE HAVE A SIMULATED COMBAT SITUATION.
TWO SABRES AGAINST CARL'S TWO BEST PILOTS.
[ HORN HONKS ]
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ] HEY, CAROL.
WAS GONNA MAYBE DO A LITTLE FLYIN' TODAY, WHAT DO YA THINK?
I THINK YOU'RE LATE.
YES, BUT THAT'S ONLY BECAUSE I SLEPT IN.
I USED TO SLEEP IN. THEN I TURNED 11.
LET ME GIVE YOU A LITTLE HEADS UP.
I'VE GONE UP AGAINST THESE SABERS ALL WEEK
AND THEY HAVE SMOKED ME EVERY TIME.
THERE ISN'T ANYTHING YOU CAN DO
THAT THEY CAN'T DO BETTER, FASTER,
AND WITHOUT DISAPPOINTING WOMEN EVERYWHERE.
I, UH, THINK WE BOTH KNOW THAT'S NOT TRUE.
THIS IS EXACTLY WHY I DIDN'T WANT YOU FOR THIS.
MY FATHER DID.
YOU KNOW, I WOULD'VE GONE WITH JENSEN.
I'D HAVE GONE WITH JENSEN TOO,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY HE'S BUSY... NOT BEING GOOD ENOUGH.
AT LEAST HE SHOWS UP.
HAL...
THIS TEST TODAY, IT'S IMPORTANT.
I GOT IT. I'M GONNA MAKE YOU LOOK GOOD UP THERE, DON'T WORRY.
OKAY? NOW LET'S GET THESE PANTS OFF AND FLY SOME PLANES.
HIGHBALL, WEAPON CHECK NOW.
ROGER THAT.
[ INDISTINCT CHATTER ]
GOOD MORNING, MR. FERRIS.
Carl: MORNING, EVERYBODY.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
GENTLEMEN.
WE ABOUT READY, TOM?
YES, MR. FERRIS. WE ARE GO FOR TEST.
SAPPHIRE, CLEARED WEAPONS HOT AT THE MERGE.
FERRIS TEST, SAPPHIRE. WEAPONS ARE HOT.
FLY SAFE, HIGHBALL.
UM...
NO.
GODDAMN IT! TOM, WHAT THE HELL YOU FEED THOSE THINGS?
F-35s, WHAT ELSE?
[ CHUCKLES ]
Hal: WAKEY, WAKEY, SAPPHIRE.
IF YOU GOT A CLEAN SHOT, NOW WOULD BE A GREAT TIME TO TAKE IT.
EASY, HIGHBALL. JUST LININ' IT UP.
[ BEEPING ]
[ BEEPING QUICKENS ]
THERE'S NO WAY WE'RE TAKIN' THESE OUT SOLO, SAPPHIRE.
GET OVER HERE. LET'S FIGURE SOMETHIN' OUT.
ON MY WAY, HIGHBALL.
NOW STAY RIGHT THERE AND LOOK REAL PRETTY.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ BEEPING ]
OH!
HIGHBALL, DID YOU JUST USE YOUR WINGMAN AS A DECOY?
[ CHUCKLES ]
HIGHBALL, THOSE SABRES HEADED UP YOUR 6
CAN FLY ANYWHERE YOU CAN.
THEN LET'S GO SOMEWHERE I CAN'T FLY.
WHAT THE HELL IS HE UP TO?
COFFIN CORNER.
HIGHBALL, RULES OF ENGAGEMENT
SET CEILING AT 50,000 FEET.
YEAH, THAT'S BECAUSE THE SABRES WILL STALL
IF THEY GO ANY HIGHER, RIGHT, TOM?
AND SO WILL YOU.
COMPRESSOR STALL. COMPRESSOR STALL.
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLES ]
[ GASPS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ BEEPING ]
YES!
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
UH, I MEAN, DAMN IT, HAL.
YOUR BOY CERTAINLY TAKES HIS JOB SERIOUSLY.
Ailerons, Hal. Side to side.
I GOT IT.
[ ALARM BEEPING ]
Martin: HAL.
KEEP IT WARM FOR ME.
GOING THROUGH 25,000.
HEY, YOU OKAY THERE, HIGHBALL?
YEAH, JUST TAKIN' MY VICTORY LAP.
[ GRUNTS ]
GOING THROUGH 20,000.
'KAY, HIGHBALL, GIMME SOME ROLL.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YEAH, DAD!
Hal, do you read me?
[ GRUNTS ]
Highball, you're approaching minimum ejection altitude.
Highball, you're below 10,000 AGL.
Spin is unrecoverable.
Eject, eject, eject!
YOU'RE NOT SCARED, ARE YOU, DAD?
LET'S JUST SAY IT'S MY JOB NOT TO BE.
DAD!
OH!
AAH! [ GRUNTS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ COUGHS ]
YOU STUPID SON OF A BITCH.
Carl: STAND DOWN, BOB. IT DOESN'T MATTER NOW.
IT DOES MATTER. NEVER MIND THAT YOU CRASHED A BRAND-NEW F-35.
YOU BROKE THE RULES OF ENGAGEMENT.
YOU SACRIFICED YOUR WINGMAN.
AND YOU BLEW THE CONTRACT THAT THIS COMPANY
AND HALF THE STATE WAS DEPENDING ON.
I'M SORRY. I THOUGHT THIS WAS A DOGFIGHT.
I WAS UNDER THE IMPRESSION THE OBJECTIVE WAS TO WIN.
Bob: NO, THE OBJECTIVE WAS TO SHOW
WHAT THE SABRES COULD DO IN ACTUAL COMBAT.
AND IN COMBAT NO PILOT IS GONNA CRATER HIS OWN PLANE.
I DID.
NOW YOU KNOW YOU GOTTA BOOST THE CEILING ON YOUR ROBOTS.
I ALSO SHOWED YOU WHAT THEY CAN'T DO.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO MAKE THAT POINT
IN FRONT OF THE COMMANDER OF AIR FORCE ACQUISITIONS.
THAT'S ENOUGH, CAROL.
SINCE I'M GOING TO HAVE TO LAY OFF MOST OF MY COMPANY ANYWAY,
YOU'RE FIRED, HAL.
IT'S TOO LATE, CARL. I QUIT. YOU DON'T GET OFF THAT EASY.
HE'S NOT FIRED. AND YOU DON'T QUIT.
THANK YOU FOR THE OPPORTUNITY, SIR. I APPRECIATE IT.
YOU'RE GROUNDED, PENDING THE RESULTS OF AN INVESTIGATION.
WATCH YOUR BACK.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE, BOB.
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
[ ELEVATOR BELL DINGS ]
YOU WANT TO TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED UP THERE?
MY CONTROLS LOCKED UP. DON'T GIVE ME THAT, HAL.
YOU HAD A WINDOW WHEN YOU COULD'VE RECOVERED.
DID YOU CHOKE?
YOU WOULDN'T BE THE FIRST PILOT IT HAPPENED TO.
BUT I NEED TO KNOW. MY CONTROLS LOCKED UP.
WHAT THE HELL IS ALL THIS ANYWAY, HUH?
WHAT'S WITH THE RIDICULOUS SUIT?
I KNOW THAT YOUR DAD'S BEEN BUCKING FOR YOU TO TAKE OVER THE COMPANY...
THE MERITS OF MY CAREER CHOICES... ...BUT THIS IS TAKING THINGS A LITTLE BIT FAR,
DON'T YOU THINK? ...ARE NOT ON THE TABLE RIGHT NOW.
YOU'RE A -- YOU'RE A PILOT, CAROL! AND A GOOD ONE.
GIVIN' THAT UP TO FLY A GODDAMN DESK IS BULLSHIT.
HAL, I LIKE THE BUSINESS PART AND I'M GOOD AT IT!
WHICH, BY THE WAY, DOESN'T MEAN I'LL NEVER GET IN A COCKPIT AGAIN.
IT ISN'T ONE WAY OR THE OTHER.
THAT'S THE WAY A CHILD LOOKS AT THINGS,
AND WE AREN'T CHILDREN ANYMORE.
AT LEAST...
I JUST DON'T WANT TO SEE SOMEONE I CARE ABOUT GETTING HURT.
LEAST OF ALL YOU.
[ DOOR OPENS ]
[ WHIRRING ]
[ SEAGULLS CRYING ]
[ BREATHING RAGGEDLY ]
[ PULSING ]
CHOOSE WELL.
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ ENGINE SHUTS OFF, MUSIC STOPS ]
[ CHILDREN SHOUTING PLAYFULLY ]
Girl: NO, THAT'S MY TURN NOW!
A TEST PILOT'S DARING MANEUVERS ALMOST ENDED IN TRAGEDY.
[ DOOR OPENS, CLOSES ] WITNESSES SAY PILOT HAL JORDAN
EJECTED AT THE LAST POSSIBLE SECOND
BEFORE HIS JET CRASHED IN THE OPEN DESERT.
HE'S THE SON OF THE LATE MARTIN JORDAN,
WHO WAS KILLED IN HIS OWN ILL FATED TEST FLIGHT
BACK IN 1993.
NOW, WE ARE TOLD THAT HAL JORDAN IS DOING FINE RIGHT NOW,
THOUGH WE HAVE YET TO HEAR AN OFFICIAL STATEMENT FROM FERRIS AIR.
HEY, GUYS. BUT THE INCIDENT HAS BEEN A DEVASTATING BLOW
TO A NEW HIGH-TECH AIRCRAFT PROGRAM.
HEY. HOW WAS WORK?
OH, IT WAS AMAZING, JACK. THANK YOU FOR ASKING.
HEY, JANICE. HOW'S TEACHING GOING?
JUST, UH, HELP ME OUT HERE,
BECAUSE I'M REALLY TRYIN' TO UNDERSTAND THIS. MM-HMM.
DO YOU WANNA BE LIKE HIM SO BAD YOU NEED TO DIE LIKE HIM TOO?
I LOVE HOW YOU JUST ASSUME IT'S MY FAULT.
I TALKED TO CARL, HAL. OH. [ LAUGHS ]
HE SAID YOU PUSHED THE PLANE SO FAR PAST ITS LIMITS --
BUT THAT'S MY JOB.
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT. EVERYBODY WALKED AWAY.
LIKE YOUR MOTORCYCLE ACCIDENT?
THE ONE THAT PUT YOU IN THE HOSPITAL FOR A MONTH?
YOU KNOW, I MISS ALL THIS QUALITY FAMILY TIME.
GOOD TALK, JACK.
God.
JACK, COME ON.
Jim: YOU OKAY?
WHERE'S JASON?
[ SIGHS ] IN HIS ROOM.
WHY?
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
HEY, IT'S UNCLE HAL.
WHAT'S UP THERE, ACE?
THIS IS THE WORST 11th BIRTHDAY PARTY I'VE EVER BEEN TO.
NO DANCIN' GIRLS? WHAT'S GOIN' O--?
HEY.
I'M FINE.
I GUESS I GOT A LITTLE FREAKED OUT OR SOMETHING.
IT HAPPENS.
NOT TO YOU.
LOOK...
I TOLD YOU THAT YOU DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
YOU WANNA KNOW WHY?
YEAH, I MAY BE A TOTAL SCREW-UP
IN EVERY OTHER PART OF MY LIFE...
BUT THE ONE THING I DO KNOW HOW TO DO IS FLY.
HEY, GOTCHA SOMETHIN', BIRTHDAY BOY.
WRAPPED IT MYSELF.
COOL. IT'S AN X-1, RIGHT?
IT'S A STARFIGHTER. MY DAD GAVE ME THAT.
LET'S PUT IT UP.
WHAT HAPPENED TODAY? I MEAN, WHEN YOU CRASHED.
NOT REALLY SURE, EXACTLY.
WERE YOU SCARED?
IT'S MY JOB NOT TO BE.
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE TOTALLY MISSING
YOUR SUPER-LAME BIRTHDAY PARTY.
BEAT IT.
GO, GO, GO, GO, GO, GO, GO, GO, GO!
I'M GLAD YOU'RE OKAY.
ME TOO, ACE.
[ CHILDREN SHOUTING PLAYFULLY IN DISTANCE ]
[ PULSING ]
NO! GET OFF!
HELP! NO!
[ GRUNTING, STRAINING ]
AAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ PANTING ]
Hal: [ STRAINS ]
COME ON, STAY WITH ME.
STAY WITH ME. I'M GONNA GET YOU SOME HELP.
YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY. YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY.
OKAY, HOLD ON.
YOUR NAME. YOUR NAME.
IT'S HAL. HAL JORDAN.
HAL JORDAN...
I AM ABIN SUR, PROTECTOR OF SECTOR 2814.
OKAY, HEY, LISTEN.
WE'RE GONNA GET YOU TO A HOSPITAL, OKAY? OKAY?
ONE -- ONE THAT -- THAT -- THAT CARRIES PURPLE BLOOD.
THE RING...
IT CHOSE YOU.
TAKE IT!
PLACE THE RING IN THE LANTERN.
PLACE THE RING, SPEAK THE OATH.
WHAT? GREAT HONOR... RESPONSIBILITY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND. HEY, HEY, BREATHE.
YOU JUST GOTTA BREATHE, OKAY? ALL YOU GOTTA DO IS BREATHE.
JUST -- JUST BREATHE, OKAY?
HEY, HEY, HEY. NO, NO, NO, NO. HEY, HEY.
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY, COME ON, MAN.
NO, NO, NO, NO, DON'T DO THAT.
HEY, NOW, DON'T -- DON'T -- DON'T -- DON'T DO THAT.
AW, COME ON.
[ PANTING ]
[ TELEPHONE RINGING ] X-97 SYSTEMS CHECK COMPLETE.
YO.
COME AGAIN?
[ ENGINE REVS ]
[ IGNITION BEEPING ]
HMM. [ GULPS ]
IS THAT A SPACESHIP?
YEAH.
IS IT REAL?
IT'S REAL.
OKAY. DID YOU SEE WHAT KIND OF POWER SOURCE THIS THING USES?
TOM. TOM. HEY, WE CAN'T STAY HERE.
I MEAN, DO YOU UNDERSTAND WHAT WE COULD LEARN FROM IT? WE CAN'T STAY HERE.
WHAT? GOTTA GO.
WHAT? PILOT.
HE WORE A UNIFORM. I THINK HE WAS A SOLDIER.
HE GAVE ME THIS.
HE PROPOSED?
[ HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING ]
WE'RE GONE. WE'RE GONE, NOW!
[ ENGINE TURNS OVER ]
[ TIRES SCREECHING ]
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ PANTING ]
THEY'RE GONNA KNOW SOMEONE WAS OUT THERE.
I MEAN, ALIEN PILOTS DON'T JUST BURY THEMSELVES.
I COULDN'T JUST LEAVE HIM THERE.
WELL, I HOPE THIS THING ISN'T RADIOACTIVE.
YEAH, WELL, YOU'RE THE GENIUS. YOU --
OH! WHOA! JESUS!
WHOA! WHOA!
GOT IT!
HE SAID THAT THE RING CHOSE ME.
HE SAID IT WAS A GREAT HONOR.
RESPONSIBILITY.
RESPONSIBILITY? YEAH.
YOU?
WELL, MAYBE ON THEIR PLANET
"RESPONSIBILITY" JUST MEANS "ASSHOLE."
LET'S HOPE SO.
A GREAT LIGHT HAS GONE OUT IN THE UNIVERSE.
ABIN SUR IS DEAD.
FOUR OF MY LANTERN BROTHERS KILLED.
THE INHABITANTS OF TWO WORLDS ANNIHILATED BY AN UNKNOWN ENEMY.
AN ENEMY THAT POSSESSES THE YELLOW POWER OF FEAR.
WE KNOW IT ORIGINATED
FROM SOMEWHERE WITHIN THE LOST SECTOR.
WE KNOW IT GROWS MORE POWERFUL WITH EACH ENCOUNTER.
ACCORDING TO ABIN SUR'S LAST TRANSMISSION,
HE SEEMED TO KNOW WHAT IT WAS.
HIS ONLY WORDS WERE, "IT'S PARALLAX."
WE ARE AWARE OF THE THREAT.
WE ARE ASSESSING THE SITUATION.
WHILE YOU ASSESS, INNOCENT LIVES WILL BE LOST.
LET ME TAKE THE FIGHT TO THIS NEW ENEMY.
THERE IS MUCH OF WHICH YOU ARE NOT AWARE, SINESTRO.
IF THE DANGER IS AS GREAT AS WE SUSPECT --
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
YOU BELIEVE THIS ENEMY CAN DEFEAT US?
GUARDIANS, IF YOUR FAITH IN OUR POWER HAS FALTERED,
LET ME RENEW IT.
LET ME TAKE A SQUADRON OF MY STRONGEST LANTERNS
AGAINST THIS ENEMY AND I'LL PROVE TO YOU:
OUR BEST DAYS ARE NOT BEHIND US.
[ MOUSE CLICKS ]
[ BEEP ]
[ DOORBELL BUZZES ]
[ DOORBELL BUZZES TWICE ]
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
DR. HAMMOND?
DR. HECTOR HAMMOND?
WE NEED TO ASK YOU TO COME WITH US.
DID ADAM PUT YOU UP TO THIS?
[ CLANG ]
[ WHIRRING ]
[ RINGING ]
[ CLANG ]
[ BUZZER ]
[ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
GET OUT OF THE CAR, PLEASE.
[ BEEPING, WHIRRING ]
[ BUZZER ]
[ GASPS ]
[ BEEP ]
DR. HAMMOND?
DR. AMANDA WALLER.
I MUST APOLOGIZE FOR THE THEATRICS,
BUT THE GOVERNMENT DOES LIKE ITS PROTOCOLS.
PLEASE, FOLLOW ME.
IS THAT WHAT I THINK IT IS?
AN ALIEN LIFE FORM, DOCTOR.
THE FIRST THAT MANKIND HAS EVER ENCOUNTERED,
DESPITE WHAT THE CONSPIRACY THEORISTS
WOULD HAVE YOU BELIEVE.
WE WANT YOU TO DO THE INITIAL ASSESSMENT OF ITS PHYSIOLOGY.
MY GOD.
WHY ME?
AS A XENOBIOLOGIST,
YOUR SKILLS ARE SPECIFICALLY SUITED TO THE TASK.
BEYOND THAT...
I'M NOT AT LIBERTY TO TELL YOU.
HELLO.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GASPS ]
THE EYES, NOSE, EARS, AND MOUTH ARE HUMANOID.
IN THE LEFT ANTERIOR THORACIC REGION
IS A TEN-CENTIMETER WOUND...
WITH JAGGED EDGES
CONTAINING ATTACHED CYANOTIC-COLORED COAGULUM.
[ SIGHS ] OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
PLACE THE RING, THEN SPEAK THE OATH.
THE OATH.
'CAUSE EVERYBODY KNOWS THE OATH.
USED TO SING IT IN CAMP.
[ SIGHS ]
I, HAL JORDAN...
DO SOLEMNLY SWEAR...
TO PLEDGE ALLEGIANCE...
TO A LANTERN...
THAT I GOT FROM A DYING PURPLE ALIEN...
IN A SWAMP.
Hector: THE EPIDERMIS IS MAGENTA.
IT APPEARS TRANSPARENT AND IS EXTREMELY THIN,
ALLOWING VISUALIZATION OF MUSCLES
AND INDIVIDUAL MUSCLE FIBERS.
"TO INFINITY AND BEYOND."
"BY THE POWER OF GRAYSKULL!"
WHAT THE HELL?! COME ON!
IF YOU CAN FLY ME 100 MILES IN THE MIDDLE OF NOWHERE,
YOU'D THINK THAT YOU --
NO!
[ GASPING ]
"IN BRIGHTEST DAY, IN BLACKEST NIGHT...
"NO EVIL SHALL ESCAPE MY SIGHT.
LET THOSE WHO WORSHIP EVIL'S MIGHT..."
Hector: [ GASPS ]
"...BEWARE MY POWER: GREEN LANTERN'S LIGHT."
[ PULSING ]
[ WIND RUSHING ]
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
[ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
CAROL.
EVERYTHING OKAY IN THERE?
IT'S FINE.
WELL, CAN I COME IN?
NO.
YEAH, YEAH, YE-- NO, 'CAUSE WE'RE --
UH, DO YOU WANNA GET A DRINK?
CAN WE TALK?
YEAH.
WE CAN TALK AND DRINK.
MY INITIAL ANALYSIS.
THANK YOU, DOCTOR.
I DON'T NEED TO TELL YOU
THAT THE MERE FACT THAT IT'S HUMANOID
IS EXTRAORDINARY.
IT'S INDICATING A CONVERGENT EVOLUTION,
OR PERHAPS A COMMON ANCESTRY,
AND THE IMPLICATIONS OF THAT ARE STAGGERING.
I MEAN, WHERE DID IT COME FROM?
THIS COULD COMPLETELY CHANGE
THE WAY THAT THE WORLD VIEWS ITSELF.
YOU IMAGINE THE WAY THAT THE PUBLIC WILL REACT TO THIS?
UM, BUT I KNOW THAT THAT WON'T HAPPEN. I DO.
LIKE YOURSELF, DOCTOR, I'M A SEEKER OF TRUTH.
BUT THE PEOPLE WHO PAY FOR FACILITIES LIKE THIS
HAVE OTHER PRIORITIES AND THE POWER TO ENFORCE THEM.
SO I KEEP IT A SECRET.
PEOPLE LIKE US HAVE TO WORK WITHIN THE SYSTEM, DOCTOR.
WE DO THE BEST WE CAN.
RIGHT.
♪ THAT'S WHERE IT'S AT ♪
PICKED THAT UP.
♪ YEAH ♪
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ON TV ]
I, UM...
I'M REALLY SORRY.
DID YOU JUST APOLOGIZE?
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN REPLACED BY AN ALIEN OR SOMETHING?
NO.
I'M GOOD.
OH. I'M GOOD.
I'M GOOD, TOTALLY GOOD. I, UH...
DO YOU THINK I'M IRRESPONSIBLE?
[ LAUGHING ]
YOU DON'T NEED TO ANSWER. THAT'S -- THAT'S FINE.
♪ ...TIME WILL PASS ♪
HAL. [ CHUCKLES ]
♪ THAT IT LASTS ♪
♪ THAT'S WHERE IT'S AT ♪
YOU LOOK PRETTY.
♪ OH, YEAH ♪
AND WE -- WE HAVEN'T BEEN IN THIS PLACE TOGETHER SINCE...
THAT NIGHT.
YOU FORGOT IT WAS MY BIRTHDAY.
DID I? MM.
THAT WAS ALSO THE NIGHT -- THE FIRST TIME THAT WE EVER...
♪ THAT'S WHERE IT'S AT ♪
...FLEW TOGETHER.
♪ PRETTY BABY ♪♪
WELL, YOU'VE BEEN FLYIN' EVER SINCE
WITH ANYONE WHO'D GET IN THE PLANE.
♪ DAHM DAHM, DAHM DO DAHM, OOBY DO ♪
♪ DAHM DAHM, DAHM DO DAHM, OOBY DO ♪ OH, YEAH.
♪ DAHM DAHM, DAHM DO DAHM ♪ OH, NO. COME ON.
♪ OOBY DO ♪ NO, YEAH, LET'S GO.
♪ DAHM DAHM ♪ DANCE WITH ME.
♪ DAHM DO DAHM ♪ NO.
♪ OOBY DO ♪
♪ DAHM DAHM, DAHM DO DAHM ♪ NO.
♪ OOBY DO, DAHM DAHM ♪
♪ DAHM DO DAHM ♪ NO.
♪ OOBY DO, DAHM DAHM ♪ HAL.
NO. ♪ DAHM DO DAHM, OOBY DO ♪
♪ DAHM DAHM ♪
♪ DAHM DO DAHM ♪ NO.
♪ OOBY DO ♪
♪ COME SOFTLY, DARLING ♪ [ LAUGHS ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
I REALLY AM SORRY.
IT'S OKAY. THE CONTRACT ISN'T QUITE DEAD YET.
I TOLD YOU I WAS GOOD AT THIS.
I WASN'T TALKIN' ABOUT THE CONTRACT.
♪ DAHM DO DAHM, OOBY DO ♪
♪ COME SOFTLY, DARLING ♪
I WOULD'VE SCREWED THIS UP.
YOU KNOW?
EVEN IF I DIDN'T GO TO THE AIR FORCE, I...
I WOULD'VE FOUND SOME WAY TO...
YOU AND ME, I WOULD'VE BLOWN IT.
YEAH, IS THAT WHAT YOU TELL YOURSELF?
MM. WHAT DO YOU TELL YOURSELF?
♪ I LOVE, I LOVE YOU SO ♪
THAT YOU WERE SCARED I WAS GETTING TOO CLOSE.
♪ HOLD ME SO TIGHT ♪
♪ ALL THROUGH ♪
YOU KNOW WHAT I SPENT MY AFTERNOON DOING?
WHAT?
WORRYING ABOUT YOU.
♪ HEAR WHAT I SA-AY ♪
HAL, I WENT OVER EVERY INCH OF THE FLIGHT DATA.
THERE WAS NOTHING WRONG WITH THE PLANE.
WHAT HAPPENED UP THERE?
THANKS FOR THE DANCE.
[ VEHICLE APPROACHES ]
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING IN DISTANCE ]
[ INSECTS CHIRPING ]
[ KEYS JINGLE ]
[ GRUNTING ]
I TOLD YOU TO WATCH YOUR BACK, JORDAN.
YOU COST US ALL OUR JOBS, YOU SON OF A BITCH.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
PATHETIC.
BASTARD'S BEEN LIVING OFF HIS OLD MAN'S REPUTATION
HIS WHOLE LIFE.
HEY.
HEY!
MY FACE IS JUST GETTING WARMED UP.
[ MEN GRUNTING ]
[ CAR ALARMS BLARING ]
[ PULSING ]
OH!
[ GRUNTING ]
OHH!
AAAAAH!
AAH!
AAAH!
[ GROANING ]
AAH!
[ BEEPING ]
[ ENERGY CRACKLING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GASPING ]
WHOA.
[ WHISTLING ]
HA!
HAVE YOU CONCLUDED ADMIRING YOURSELF?
UH...
YEAH.
WELL, YOUR RING TRANSLATOR IS FUNCTIONING PROPERLY.
YOUR MASK WILL APPEAR
WHEN PROTECTION OF YOUR IDENTITY IS REQUIRED.
THERE IS NO NEED FOR IT ON OA.
A TALKING FISH.
ACTUALLY, MY RACE IS XUDARIAN.
OUR DNA DOES SOMEWHAT RESEMBLE
YOUR OWN ICHTHYOLOGICAL SPECIES.
I AM TOMAR-RE,
PROTECTOR OF SECTOR 2813 AND HOME TO --
80,012 GALAXIES, 2.34 MILLION SENTIENT SPECIES.
HOW DO I KNOW THAT?
THE INDUCTION PROCESS.
IT ACTIVATES THE RING'S HIGHER FUNCTIONS,
INCLUDING A WORKING KNOWLEDGE BASE.
IN TRUTH, WE WERE CURIOUS.
THE PROCESS HAD NEVER BEEN ATTEMPTED
ON A SPECIES AS YOUNG AS HUMANS BEFORE.
[ SIGHS ]
AS YOU ARE THE FIRST TO BE CHOSEN,
I'VE BEEN SENT TO WELCOME YOU HERE.
AND HERE IS?
WELCOME TO OA.
THIS PLANET HAS BEEN OUR HOME FOR COUNTLESS MILLENNIA.
IT WAS CREATED FOR US BY THE GUARDIANS.
GUARDIANS?
THERE STANDS THEIR CITADEL.
THEY ARE IMMORTALS, AMONG THE MOST ANCIENT OF RACES.
THEY MADE ALL YOU SEE
AND ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR ALL WE ARE AND DO.
SINCE TIME IMMEMORIAL,
THE GREEN LANTERN CORPS HAS SERVED
AS THE KEEPERS OF PEACE, ORDER AND JUSTICE
THROUGHOUT THE UNIVERSE.
TO BE CHOSEN TO JOIN ITS RANKS
IS THE HIGHEST OF HONORS
AND THE GREATEST OF RESPONSIBILITIES.
YEAH. YEAH, THAT PART I HEARD ABOUT.
WE'RE GOING TO FLY NOW.
FLY?
ABSOLUTELY.
ALL RIGHT.
I CAN DO THAT.
JOIN ME.
[ BREATHING SHAKILY ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
YEAH!
OH!
[ Laughing ] OH!
WHAT IS THAT?
IT'S THE ENERGY THAT'S GENERATED FROM THE CENTRAL BATTERY.
ITS POWER COMES FROM THE WILL
OF EVERY LIVING CREATURE IN THE UNIVERSE.
IT, IN TURN, CHARGES YOUR LANTERN,
WHICH, IN TURN, CHARGES YOUR RING.
EVEN YOUR SUIT IS COMPRISED ENTIRELY OF ENERGY.
WHAT'S WITH ALL THE GREEN?
GREEN IS THE COLOR OF WILL.
THE GUARDIANS HARNESSED WILL,
BECAUSE IT'S THE STRONGEST SOURCE OF ENERGY
IN THE UNIVERSE.
THERE'S SO MANY.
THE STARS YOU CAN SEE
FROM YOUR HOME PLANET ON THE CLEAREST NIGHT...
YOUR SECTOR IS A THOUSAND TIMES LARGER.
AND 3600 LANTERNS,
EACH WITH A SECTOR JUST AS VAST.
[ SPEAKING NATIVE LANGUAGE ]
LANTERNS, I'VE CALLED YOU HERE TO THIS UNPRECEDENTED GATHERING
BECAUSE WE FACE AN UNPRECEDENTED DANGER.
OUR FOUR LANTERN BROTHERS WERE KILLED
BY AN ENEMY CALLED PARALLAX.
AN ENEMY WE DON'T YET FULLY UNDERSTAND.
WE DO KNOW IT'S POWERFUL ENOUGH TO DESTROY ENTIRE CIVILIZATIONS.
POWERFUL ENOUGH TO DEFEAT EVEN ABIN SUR...
OUR FINEST WARRIOR...
WHOSE LIGHT CAN NEVER BE REPLACED.
[ ALL MURMURING IN NATIVE LANGUAGES ]
THE GUARDIANS HAVE CHARGED ME TO LEAD A SQUADRON
OF OUR STRONGEST LANTERNS IN AN ASSAULT ON PARALLAX.
WE WILL SEEK OUT AND FIND THIS ENEMY.
AND WE WILL DESTROY IT.
ALONE, WE ARE NOW VULNERABLE.
UNITED, WE ARE STILL INVINCIBLE.
WE HAVE NEVER BEEN DEFEATED.
WILL WE BE DEFEATED NOW?
All: NO!
Sinestro: IT WAS FOR THIS MOMENT THAT WE WERE CREATED.
BUT I DON'T NEED TO TELL YOU YOUR DUTY.
I DON'T NEED TO TELL YOU WHO WE ARE.
[ ALL SHOUTING IN NATIVE LANGUAGES ]
All: WE ARE THE CORPS!
WE ARE THE CORPS!
Tomar-Re: YOUR WILL TURNS THOUGHT INTO REALITY.
TO MASTER THE RING, YOU MUST LEARN TO FOCUS YOUR WILL
AND CREATE WHAT YOU SEE IN YOUR MIND.
THE RING'S LIMITS ARE ONLY WHAT YOU CAN IMAGINE.
DO THAT AGAIN.
NOW YOU TRY.
CONCENTRATE.
[ BLOWS ]
[ PULSING ]
THE RING WILL INFORM YOU
WHERE THERE IS AN IMMINENT THREAT.
[ GRUNTING ]
Tomar-Re: THIS PARTICULAR THREAT'S NAME IS KILOWOG.
HE'LL BE YOUR COMBAT TRAINING OFFICER.
WHOA!
NEVER LET YOUR GUARD DOWN, POOZER.
WELCOME TO RING SLINGIN' 101.
OR AS I LIKE TO CALL IT:
THE WORST DAY OF YOUR WORTHLESS LIFE.
[ SNORTS ]
THE HUMAN. AIN'T NEVER SEEN ONE BEFORE.
[ SNORTING, SNIFFING ]
YOU SMELL FUNNY.
I SMELL FUNNY?
YEAH, I HEARD ABOUT HUMANS.
THINK YOU'RE THE CENTER OF THE UNIVERSE.
YOU WANT TO BE A LANTERN? YOU GOTTA COMMIT TO THE CORPS.
Kilowog: ALL RIGHT, POOZER. LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT.
[ METAL CLINKS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
YOUR CONSTRUCTS ARE ONLY GONNA BE AS STRONG AS YOUR WILL.
AND YOUR WILL IS PATHETIC.
[ GROANS ]
I'M GONNA WORK YOU.
THEN I'M GONNA HIT YOU UNTIL YOUR WILL
IS STRONG ENOUGH TO BE WORTHY OF THE CORPS.
[ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
NEXT LESSON.
[ GRUNTING ]
Kilowog: FEEL THAT?
IT'S THE GRAVITATIONAL PULL OF YOUR AVERAGE SUN.
MAKES FLYING THROUGH SPACE VERY DANGEROUS.
THE BIGGER YOU ARE, THE QUICKER YOU BURN.
[ GASPS ]
GRAVITY'S A BITCH.
[ GROANING ]
HERE, LET ME HELP YOU.
REMEMBER, YOUR ENEMY, HE'S NOT GONNA PLAY FAIR.
[ GRUNTING ]
WELL, THAT'S GOOD ADVICE.
THANKS, GORGEOUS.
Sinestro: SO...
[ PANTING ]
...THIS IS THE HUMAN.
WHEN I LEARNED ABIN SUR'S RING HAD CHOSEN YOU,
I SAID THERE HAD TO BE A MISTAKE.
[ GROANING ]
I SEE NOTHING TO CHANGE MY MIND.
I'LL TAKE IT FROM HERE, KILOWOG.
THE CORPS IS ONLY AS STRONG AS ITS WEAKEST LINK.
AND I WILL TOLERATE NO WEAK LINKS.
YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
ARE YOU AFRAID, HUMAN?
ARE YOU AFRAID?
DON'T. [ CHUCKLES ]
DON'T DO THAT.
SHALL WE?
SURE.
A SWORD?
HOW HUMAN.
[ GRUNTING ]
I DO BELIEVE I SMELL FEAR.
AAH!
[ PANTING ]
I'M A GREEN LANTERN.
I FEAR NOTHING.
FEAR IS THE ENEMY OF WILL.
WILL IS WHAT MAKES YOU TAKE ACTION.
[ CHAINSAW BUZZES ]
FEAR IS WHAT STOPS YOU AND MAKES YOU WEAK.
MAKES YOUR CONSTRUCTS FEEBLE.
Sinestro: YOU MUST IGNORE YOUR FEAR.
WHEN YOU'RE AFRAID, YOU CAN'T ACT.
WHEN YOU CAN'T ACT, YOU CAN'T DEFEND.
IF YOU CAN'T DEFEND, YOU DIE.
[ PANTING ]
YOU REEK OF FEAR, HAL JORDAN.
ABIN SUR WAS A GREAT WARRIOR.
MY MENTOR.
MY FRIEND.
YOU INSULT HIS MEMORY BY WEARING HIS RING.
I'M DONE. HE'S RIGHT. I'M ONLY HUMAN.
WE'RE NOT READY TO DEFEND THE UNIVERSE.
UP UNTIL A FEW DAYS AGO,
WE THOUGHT WE WERE THE ONLY ONES IN THE UNIVERSE.
THE RING CHOSE YOU.
IT WOULDN'T HAVE DONE SO IF IT HADN'T SEEN SOMETHING IN YOU.
OH, YEAH?
SOMETHING YOU YOURSELF DON'T YET SEE.
THE RING NEVER MAKES A MISTAKE.
THIS TIME IT DID.
[ KEYS JINGLE ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
Hector: -- THAT UNTIL RECENTLY, WE DIDN'T REALIZE THAT
MANY OF THESE LITTLE CRITTERS THAT WE'VE BEEN CALLING BACTERIA
WEREN'T BACTERIA AT ALL.
THEY WERE AN ENTIRELY DIFFERENT TYPE
OF PRIMITIVE PROKARYOTIC CELL.
THESE LITTLE BUGGERS, CALLED ARCHAEANS,
ARE STILL POORLY UNDERSTOOD.
[ Thinking ] [ INDISTINCT WHISPERING ]
UM, BUT MIGHT TURN OUT TO BE DIFFERENT...
[ WHISPERING CONTINUES ] ...FROM BACTERIA
BUT MIGHT TURN OUT TO BE AS DIFFERENT FROM BACTERIA
AS BACTERIA IS FROM US.
[ YAWNS ] SOME PEOPLE CALL THEM EXTREMOPHILES
BECAUSE THEY LIVE IN THE MOST EXTREME ENVIRONMENTS ON EARTH,
SUCH AS... GOD, HE'S SO BORING.
...THE BOILING WATERS OF A GEYSER.
WHAT A LOSER.
MICHAEL!
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
I DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING.
DID YOU JUST CALL ME A LOSER?
HOLY SHIT. WHAT KIND OF FREAK IS THIS GUY?
"FREAK"?!
[ SCOFFS ]
WHOA! OH!
Woman: AAH! WHOA!
WHAT HAPPENED? WHAT HAPPENED? OH, WHAT HAPPENED?
[ ALL MURMURING ]
THAT'S CRAZY!
OH!
CLASS DISMISSED.
[ WHIRRING ]
[ CELLPHONE BEEPS ]
[ CELLPHONE CLOSES ]
SO HOW YOU BEEN?
BEEN A WHILE.
SO YOU HAD A ROUGH NIGHT LAST NIGHT.
DID YOU GET HER NAME, HUH?
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
YOU NEED TO GET SOME SLEEP, SON.
HAVE A SEAT.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU, DAD?
WELL, ACTUALLY, YOU'VE ALREADY DONE IT.
FOR ME AND FOR YOUR COUNTRY.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'M TALKING ABOUT YOU
IMPRESSING A WHOLE LOT OF VERY IMPORTANT PEOPLE.
WHERE DID YOU GET THAT?
I'M ON A SUBCOMMITTEE OVERSEEING THE AGENCIES INVOLVED.
TOP SECRET, OF COURSE.
IT WAS YOU.
THAT'S WHY THEY CHOSE ME.
AND BECAUSE OF THIS, WE'RE GONNA BE ABLE
TO GET YOU A TOP POST ON THE INSIDE NOW,
HELPING TO OVERSEE THE ENTIRE OPERATION.
THERE ARE SCIENTISTS THAT WORKED THEIR WHOLE LIVES FOR THIS.
MM-HMM.
PEOPLE MORE QUALIFIED.
AND LESS CONNECTED.
DON'T BE NAIVE, SON. IT'S THE WAY THE WORLD WORKS.
YOU HAVE TO SEIZE AN OPPORTUNITY WHEN IT PRESENTS ITSELF.
HE'LL NEVER GET IT.
JUST WASTING HIS LIFE AWAY.
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ] WHAT AN EMBARRASSMENT.
[ BEEP ]
BILL!
[ CHUCKLES ] HOW ARE YOU?
I'M TERRIFIC.
NO, NO, NO.
JUST FINISHING UP A MEETING. GOT PLENTY OF TIME.
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
[ SEAGULLS CRYING ]
[ BREATHES DEEPLY ]
[ GROWLING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ ROARING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
Sinestro: WITH MY OWN EYES,
I SAW THIS CREATURE INDUCE FEAR IN OUR FINEST WARRIORS
AND THEN FEED ON THAT FEAR.
THERE'S MORE.
WE'VE TRACKED ITS TRAJECTORY.
PARALLAX IS HEADED FOR OA.
NEVER BEFORE HAS AN ENEMY DARED ATTACK US HERE.
YOU MUST TELL ME WHAT YOU KNOW.
First Guardian: WILL HAS ALWAYS BEEN OUR SOLE WEAPON
AGAINST THE FORCES OF DARKNESS IN THE UNIVERSE.
BUT AS THAT POWER BEGAN TO SEEM INSUFFICIENT...
A GREAT DEBATE AROSE AMONG US.
SHOULD WE EXPLOIT ANOTHER SOURCE OF POWER,
ONE WE HAD LONG SINCE SWORN SHOULD NEVER BE USED?
FEAR.
BUT THE POWER OF FEAR WAS TOO UNPREDICTABLE.
THE CHANCE OF CORRUPTION TOO GREAT.
AND SO WE DECIDED AGAINST IT.
ALL OF US, THAT IS, EXCEPT ONE.
ALONE, THIS GUARDIAN ENTERED THE FORBIDDEN CHAMBER.
HE WANTED TO PROVE THE LIGHT OF FEAR COULD BE MASTERED.
HIS INTENTIONS WERE PURE...
BUT HIS HOPES WERE NAIVE.
CONSUMED BY THE YELLOW POWER OF FEAR,
THE GUARDIAN BECAME THE VERY EVIL
HE HAD WISHED TO DESTROY.
HE BECAME PARALLAX.
FOR THE UNIVERSE'S SAFETY AND HIS OWN,
ABIN SUR WAS CHARGED
WITH IMPRISONING PARALLAX IN THE LOST SECTOR.
BUT HE ESCAPED.
FEEDING ON THE FEAR OF OTHERS,
HE GREW LARGER, MORE POWERFUL.
AND IS NOW HEADED HERE TO TAKE HIS REVENGE ON YOU
AND DESTROY THE CORPS.
THEN WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
WE MUST PREPARE TO HARNESS THE POWER OF OUR ENEMY
AND FIGHT FEAR WITH FEAR.
TO PROTECT OUR SECTORS WE MUST BE ABLE TO DEFEND OURSELVES.
WE MUST FORGE A YELLOW RING.
[ HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING ]
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
WATCH YOUR STEP.
♪ DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME NO MORE ♪
♪ I'M GONE ♪
♪ I'M GONE, I'M GONE ♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
[ JOINT'S JUMPIN'S "BAREFOOTIN'" PLAYS ]
HELLO. HI.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
♪ EVERYBODY GET ON YOUR FEET ♪
♪ YOU MAKE ME NERVOUS WHEN YOU'RE IN YOUR SEAT ♪
ROUGH NIGHT, HUH?
HECTOR.
HOW YOU DOIN'? WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN UP TO?
SAME OLD, SAME OLD.
YEAH. ME TOO.
HAL JORDAN. WORST PILOT I'VE EVER SEEN.
OR THE BEST. NOT QUITE SURE.
I'VE BEEN CALLED BOTH, SIR.
GLAD YOU COULD MAKE IT, SON.
FRANKLY, I WAS A LITTLE SURPRISED I GOT THE INVITE.
NO, YOU'RE FAMILY, HAL.
YOU KNOW, I ALWAYS SAY
THERE ARE THINKERS IN THIS WORLD AND THERE ARE DOERS.
AND YOU ARE ONE OF THE DOERS.
YEAH, BUT, YOU KNOW,
THE THINKERS MAKE WHAT I DO POSSIBLE.
I WOULDN'T HAVE A PLANE TO FLY IN
UNLESS SOMEONE THOUGHT IT UP.
OF COURSE.
EXCUSE ME, I NEED A DRINK.
AND I GOTTA GET BACK TO WORK. THIS IS WORK.
YES, SIR.
NICE TO SEE YOU, SON. YOU TOO. YOU TOO.
[ LAUGHTER ]
♪ HEY, LITTLE GAL WITH THE RED DRESS ON ♪
NICE.
[ CLEARS THROAT ]
YEAH, MY DAD USED TO TRAIN IN THEM.
I WAS TALKING ABOUT YOUR DRESS.
♪ COME BACK AND GET THEM ANOTHER DAY ♪
NICE JACKET.
LAST TIME I CHECKED, YOU DIDN'T EVEN OWN ONE.
YEAH, I'VE BEEN SHAKING UP THE WARDROBE LATELY.
CONGRATULATIONS ON THE CONTRACT.
HOW'D YOU MANAGE TO PULL THAT OFF?
I POINTED OUT YOU ONLY WON
BECAUSE YOU BROKE THE RULES OF ENGAGEMENT.
AND TOM FIGURED OUT HOW TO GIVE THE SABRES MORE ALTITUDE.
SO I GUESS IN A WAY, WITHOUT EVEN MEANING TO,
YOU ACTUALLY DID US A FAVOR.
LOOK,
I'M UNCOMFORTABLE WITH THE WORD "HERO."
♪ HEY ♪
[ LAUGHS ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ] Woman: WHOO!
Man: YEAH! WHOO!
Carl: THANK YOU. THANK YOU ALL FOR JOINING US.
GREAT EVENING.
SOMEBODY VERY SPECIAL I'D LIKE TO THANK
FOR HELPING US TO NAIL THIS CONTRACT:
MY DAUGHTER, CAROL FERRIS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ] COME ON.
COME ON! LET'S GO, CAROL!
CAROL! WHOO!
[ CHUCKLES ] MM.
CONGRATULATIONS, CAROL.
I TAKE ONE LOOK AT YOU, YOUNG LADY,
OR AT HAL JORDAN OVER THERE,
THE SPITTING IMAGE OF HIS DAD...
Man: YEAH, HAL! YOU GIVE US HOPE.
A TOAST TO OUR FUTURE.
HEAR, HEAR! TO THE FUTURE!
WE'RE IN GOOD HANDS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
YEAH! YEAH!
WHOO!
[ GROOVE ARMADA'S "HANDS OF TIME" PLAYS ]
HECTOR!
[ Laughing ] OH, MY GOD! HEY!
[ SIGHS ]
CONGRATULATIONS.
UM. THANK YOU.
HERE'S TO YOU AND HAL, THE FUTURE.
YEAH, I -- I'M SORRY.
I-I KNOW IT COULDN'T HAVE BEEN EASY
GROWING UP WITH YOUR DAD.
BUT HEY, YOU'RE -- YOU'RE DOING GREAT, SO --
[ CHUCKLES ]
I AM. I'M DOING GREAT.
[ CHUCKLES ] HE'S RIGHT, THOUGH. I'M NOT A DOER.
[ CHUCKLES ]
ALTHOUGH I DID GET TO EXAMINE AN ALIEN BODY RECENTLY.
THAT WAS VERY COOL.
I CAN'T TELL ANYONE ABOUT IT,
BUT, HEY, YOU KNOW, YOU CAN'T HAVE EVERYTHING.
IS HECTOR TELLING YOU
ANOTHER ONE OF HIS SCIENCE FICTION STORIES?
WHAT THE HELL'S WRONG WITH HIM?
CAN'T KEEP HIS MOUTH SHUT.
YOU REALLY DO HAVE A CREATIVE IMAGINATION.
BYE.
SENATOR. I APOLOGIZE.
WE REALLY MUST GO.
GOOD NIGHT, CAROL.
GOOD NIGHT.
[ SIGHS ]
Man: SENATOR!
HEY.
SENATOR, THANKS FOR EVERYTHING.
[ HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING ]
THANK YOU. THANK YOU.
BYE, SENATOR!
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
[ ENERGY PULSES ]
[ ALARM BLARING ]
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ]
GET THE CRASH CREW HERE. OUR HELICOPTER'S GOING DOWN.
AAH! AAH! AAH!
OH, MY GOD.
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
OH, MY GOD!
AAH!
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ]
[ PANTING ]
AAH! AAH!
Woman: WHAT IS THAT? WHAT IS THAT?
[ ENERGY PULSING ]
[ DOOR CREAKS ]
[ INDISTINCT TALKING ON TV ]
[ DOOR CLOSES ]
[ HIGH-PITCHED WHINING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GROANING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
Reporter: WHAT HAPPENED TONIGHT
TOOK PLACE IN JUST A MATTER OF SECONDS.
BUT PEOPLE WILL BE TALKING ABOUT IT FOR YEARS TO COME.
A HELICOPTER CAREENING OUT OF CONTROL,
HEADED TOWARD CERTAIN TRAGEDY, WHEN ALL OF A SUDDEN,
A MYSTERY MAN, A HERO, SAVES THE DAY,
INCREDIBLY DIVERTING THE HELICOPTER
FROM DESTROYING INNOCENT PEOPLE
AND MIRACULOUSLY RESCUING CAROL FERRIS FROM BEING CRUSHED
BY A COLLAPSING BILLBOARD.
THE REAL QUESTION TONIGHT IS:
WHO IS THIS AMAZING HERO AND WHERE IS HE NOW?
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
[ GROANING ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
[ POUNDING ON DOOR ]
START TALKING.
A RACETRACK?
YEAH. MM.
THAT'S THE BEST YOU COULD COME UP WITH
FOR YOUR FIRST BIG APPEARANCE?
RACETRACK.
OH, I'M -- I'M SORRY. DID I DISAPPOINT YOU?
I MATERIALIZED A RACETRACK OUT OF PURE ENERGY,
SAVING HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE, AND -- AND YOU'RE DISAPPOINTED.
I'M -- I'M -- I'M SORRY ABOUT THAT.
NO, I WANNA SEE THIS STUFF. YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO SHOW ME.
OH, I DON'T THINK THAT'S A GOOD IDEA. COME ON, I WANNA SEE THIS STUFF, YOU KNOW?
LIKE, I WANNA SEE THE OUTFIT, THE FLYING... I'M SITTING HERE IN MY APARTMENT.
WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO DO? YOU GOTTA SHOW ME.
HAL, I LOVE YOU BUT BEING YOUR BEST FRIEND'S NO PICNIC.
I JUST GOT UP. GIVE ME A BREAK.
IT'S FOR EMERGENCIES! YOU OWE ME!
HAL, I WANNA SEE IT.
FINE.
HOLD ON TO YOUR GLASSES.
[ CHUCKLES ]
ALL RIGHT.
QUESTION:
YOU READY TO HAVE YOUR MIND BLOWN?
YEAH.
RING. FINGER.
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
HERE WE GO.
[ GRUNTS ]
DID YOU BREAK IT ALREADY?
I DIDN'T BREAK IT, OKAY? IT'S JUST...
IT'S OUT OF JUICE. I HAVE TO RECHARGE IT.
NOW PAY ATTENTION.
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
AAH! GREEN!
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ] WOW.
I KNOW! RIGHT?!
[ LAUGHS ]
WHOO!
AH.
[ LAUGHS ]
NOT BAD, HUH?
YOU'RE A SUPERHERO.
[ LAUGHING ]
DON'T THEY ALWAYS GET THE GIRL?
EVENING, MA'AM.
DIDN'T GET A CHANCE TO SAY GOODBYE.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, NO, I'M -- I'M GLAD TO HAVE A CHANCE TO THANK YOU.
JUST DOING MY JOB.
NO THANKS NECESSARY, MISS.
NO, IT -- IT IS.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
YOU SAVED ALL OF OUR LIVES.
THAT WAS A VERY...
HAL?
MISS?
HAL?!
OH, MY GO-- OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD! HAL!
HOW DID YOU KNOW IT WAS ME?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?! I'VE KNOWN YOU MY WHOLE LIFE!
I'VE SEEN YOU NAKED!
YOU DON'T THINK I WOULD RECOGNIZE YOU
BECAUSE I CAN'T SEE YOUR CHEEKBONES?!
WHAT IS THIS?! WHY -- WHY IS YOUR SKIN GREEN?
WHY ARE YOU GLOWING?
WHAT THE HELL IS WITH THAT MASK?!
IT CAME WITH THE OUTFIT.
COOL, HUH?
SO IT ALL WORKS BECAUSE OF THIS MAGIC RING?
NO, THERE'S NO SUCH THING AS MAGIC.
INTERGALACTIC GREEN PEACEKEEPERS, THOUSANDS OF THEM.
[ CHUCKLES ] BUT, UH, NO.
I'M NOT MAKING IT UP.
[ CHUCKLES ] WOW.
I MEAN, WHEN WE WERE KIDS, WHO'D HAVE THOUGHT?
I DID, ACTUALLY. I CALLED THIS EARLY ON.
[ LAUGHS ]
I SAID, "ONE DAY I'LL BE A GREEN SPACE COP."
HERE I AM.
OKAY, SO AT THE PARTY,
HOW DID YOU MAKE THAT BIG GREEN RAMP THING?
ANYTHING I SEE IN MY MIND, I-I CAN CREATE.
I JUST HAVE TO FOCUS.
ANYTHING?
ANYTHING.
[ CHUCKLES ]
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
BETTER LATE THAN NEVER.
UM.
OKAY, SO HOW DOES IT WORK?
THEY JUST, UM, CALL YOU ON YOUR CELL,
"CAT IN A TREE, DOWNTOWN MILKY WAY"?
NO. I DON'T -- I DON'T THINK IT WORKS EXACTLY LIKE THAT.
WELL, TECHNICALLY SPEAKING, UM,
I ACTUALLY SORT OF, UH, QUIT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN? HOW?
WELL, I MEAN, IT'S A -- IT'S A LOT LIKE
QUITTING ANYTHING ELSE, REALLY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
HOW DO -- HOW DO YOU WALK AWAY FROM SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
IS -- IS THAT EVEN POSSIBLE?
OH, I THINK WE BOTH KNOW I'M PRETTY GOOD AT WALKIN' AWAY.
IF FOR ONCE YOU DIDN'T QUIT SOMETHING YOU CARED ABOUT,
WHAT'S THE WORST THAT COULD HAPPEN?
WELL, THANK YOU. THIS HAS BEEN REALLY SOMETHING.
I KNOW I'VE -- I'VE MADE A LOT OF MISTAKES --
LOOK, HAL, I'M NOT MAD AT YOU.
I FEEL BAD FOR YOU, REALLY.
YOU'VE BEEN GIVEN SO MUCH SO OFTEN.
AND YOU JUST...
GOOD NIGHT.
[ SIGHS ]
[ PULSING ]
[ SNIFFLES ]
[ GROANING ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ DOOR OPENS ]
Dr. Waller: DR. HAMMOND?
THERE IS SOMETHING I'D LIKE TO SHOW YOU.
SOMETHING I'M FAIRLY CERTAIN YOU'LL WANT TO SEE.
Boy: LATER, MOM.
Girl: I LOVE YOU. Man: BYE, BABY.
[ GUNSHOTS, SHELLS CLATTERING ]
Dr. Waller: NO!
[ CRYING ]
PHYSICAL CONTACT ACCESSES MNEMONIC DATA.
I CAN SEE YOUR MEMORIES.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]
[ WHEEZING SOFTLY ]
DAD.
SON, THIS IS MY FAULT.
BUT I'M GONNA FIX IT.
WE'RE GONNA GET YOU WELL AGAIN.
WHATEVER IT TAKES.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
WE DETECTED TRACES OF A SECOND ALIEN LIFE FORM
BURIED WITHIN THE BODY OF THE FIRST.
YOU'VE BEEN EXPOSED.
I'VE NEVER FELT BETTER IN MY LIFE.
WE KNOW EVERYTHING, SON.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GROANING ]
Tomar-Re: TO BE CHOSEN TO JOIN ITS RANKS IS THE HIGHEST OF HONORS...
AND THE GREATEST OF RESPONSIBILITIES.
THE RING NEVER MAKES A MISTAKE.
[ PULSING ]
[ GROANING ]
IT'S GONNA BE ALL RIGHT.
THEY JUST NEED TO RUN SOME TESTS, THAT'S ALL.
KEEP HIM UNDER.
I ONLY WANT WHAT'S BEST FOR YOU.
[ PULSING ]
OH! AAH!
AAH!
RUN.
[ BLOWS ] AAH! UGH!
AAAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ GASPING ]
AAH!
[ ENERGY CRACKLING ]
[ ALL GROANING ]
HECTOR.
Hector: Shh, shh.
DON'T WORRY.
I ONLY WANT WHAT'S BEST FOR YOU.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ GASPS ]
Dr. Waller: [ GROANS ]
AAH!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ ROARS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ LAUGHING ]
THE RING... IT CHOSE YOU.
TAKE IT!
HAL.
HI.
[ CHUCKLES ]
THE ALIEN WAS ONE OF YOU.
HOW DID WE END UP SO DIFFERENT, HMM?
HMM?
SIT DOWN!
OH!
NOW...
HOW'S CAROL?
THAT CAME OUT WRONG. PLEASE.
I KNOW I'VE -- I'VE MADE A LOT OF MISTAKES --
LOOK, HAL, I FEEL BAD FOR YOU, REALLY.
GOOD NIGHT.
[ SIGHS ]
YOU'RE JUST AS MUCH OF A FAILURE AS I WAS.
AND JUST AS AFRAID.
WELL...
[ CHUCKLES ]
...I USED TO FIGHT MY FEAR.
BUT NOW THAT I'VE TASTED ITS TRUE POWER...
...I'LL NEVER GO BACK.
AAAAAAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
NO!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
Parallax: YOU WEAR THE RING OF THE LANTERN THAT IMPRISONED ME.
YOU WILL SUFFER THE SAME FATE.
ONCE I HAVE DEVOURED YOUR WORLD,
I WILL HAVE ALL THE STRENGTH I NEED... AAH!
TO DEFEAT THE CORPS AND DESTROY THE GUARDIANS.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ HECTOR SCREAMING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
Tom: LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
THIS THING THAT'S OUT THERE ATTACKING PLANETS
IS CONNECTED TO HECTOR?
SOMEHOW IT INFECTED HIM AFTER IT KILLED ABIN SUR.
WELL, YOU'RE JUST GONNA HAVE TO STOP IT.
OH, I'M JUST GONNA HAVE TO STOP IT, HUH?
WELL, I TRIED THAT, AND I FAILED.
AND THE SENATOR DIED.
I TOLD YOU, THE RING MADE A MISTAKE.
WAIT, GO BACK. HOW DID THE RING MAKE A MISTAKE?
THE ONE THING THAT A GREEN LANTERN IS SUPPOSED TO BE
IS FEARLESS.
FEARLESS IS THE JOB DESCRIPTION.
THAT ISN'T ME.
SO YOU'RE JUST GONNA WALK AWAY AGAIN?
EXPLAIN THIS TO ME, HAL.
PLEASE EXPLAIN TO ME JUST ONCE, WHY.
BECAUSE I'M AFRAID!
YOU DON'T THINK YOUR DAD EVER FELT AFRAID?
IF HE DID, HE FIGURED OUT SOME WAY TO BEAT IT.
YEAH, WELL, THERE'S A WORD FOR THAT:
COURAGE.
THEY SAID THAT THE RING WOULDN'T HAVE CHOSEN ME
IF IT DIDN'T SEE SOMETHING.
SOMETHING I DON'T SEE.
YET.
I SEE IT.
I ALWAYS HAVE.
THE RING DIDN'T SEE THAT YOU WERE FEARLESS.
IT SAW THAT YOU HAD THE ABILITY TO OVERCOME FEAR.
IT SAW THAT YOU'RE COURAGEOUS.
WHICH YOU ARE.
JUST LIKE YOUR DAD.
[ CHOKING ]
Parallax: THE LANTERN IS A THREAT.
ELIMINATE HIM.
Sinestro: OUR NEW WEAPON IS READY.
ONCE I'VE MASTERED ITS POWER,
I'LL BEGIN TRAINING THE CORPS TO DO THE SAME.
THOUGH EARTH WILL BE LOST,
WE'LL BE READY TO MAKE A STAND AGAINST PARALLAX
BEFORE IT REACHES OA.
THEN THE POWER OF THE ENEMY WILL BE OURS.
AT WHAT COST?
YOU DARE ENTER THIS CHAMBER?
I NEED YOUR HELP.
YOU GOTTA HELP ME SAVE MY WORLD.
I KNOW THAT HUMANS AREN'T THE STRONGEST SPECIES,
OR THE SMARTEST.
WE'RE YOUNG, WE HAVE A LOT TO LEARN.
BUT WE'RE WORTH SAVING.
THIS NEW WEAPON OF YOURS, YOU CAN'T USE IT.
ONCE YOU CROSS THAT LINE, ONCE YOU'VE GIVEN IN TO FEAR,
YOU'LL NEVER GO BACK.
I'VE SEEN IT.
LOOK, I KNOW RIGHT NOW YOU'RE AFRAID.
YOU DARE ACCUSE THE GUARDIANS OF FEELING FEAR?
YES, I DO.
AND THAT'S EXACTLY WHY PARALLAX IS BEATING YOU,
BECAUSE YOU'RE AFRAID TO EVEN ADMIT YOU'RE AFRAID.
I KNOW.
I SPENT MY ENTIRE LIFE DOIN' IT.
YOU KNOW, WE HAVE A SAYING ON EARTH.
WE SAY: "I'M ONLY HUMAN."
WE SAY IT BECAUSE WE'RE VULNERABLE,
WE SAY IT BECAUSE WE KNOW WE'RE AFRAID.
IT DOESN'T MEAN WE'RE WEAK.
HELP ME SAVE MY PLANET.
DON'T GIVE IN TO FEAR.
FIGHT IT. FIGHT IT WITH ME.
YOUR WORDS ARE COMPELLING, YOUNG HUMAN.
BUT AS IMMORTALS, WE MUST MEASURE OUR ACTIONS
OVER BILLIONS OF YEARS, AND THE FATE OF THE UNIVERSE.
WE SIMPLY CANNOT RISK LOSING EVERYTHING
ON THE CHANCE YOU MIGHT BE RIGHT.
THEN DON'T. DON'T RISK ANY MORE LIVES.
JUST MINE.
LET ME GO FIGHT FOR MY WORLD,
AND I'LL SHOW YOU THAT WILL IS STRONGER THAN FEAR.
THERE IS NO WAY YOU CAN SUCCEED.
YOU WILL DIE, HAL JORDAN.
THEN I'LL DIE TRYING.
GOOD LUCK, GREEN LANTERN.
[ PULSING ]
[ WHIRRING ]
I WOULDN'T DO THAT.
LOOK CLOSELY.
SHE'S BEAUTIFUL, ISN'T SHE?
I LOVED HER FROM THE MOMENT I FIRST SAW HER.
BUT SHE COULD NEVER SEE ME,
AS YOU WERE ALWAYS STANDING IN THE WAY.
BUT NOT ANYMORE.
NO! NO! DON'T! DON'T DO THIS, HECTOR.
PLEASE.
I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
[ SCOFFS ]
COME ON, LOOK AT YOURSELF!
NO, I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE...
TO NOT LIVE UP TO EXPECTATIONS,
TO FEEL LIKE NOTHIN' THAT YOU DO WILL EVER BE GOOD ENOUGH.
I KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE TO BE AFRAID.
LET ME HELP YOU.
HAL.
[ CHUCKLES ] YOU'VE CHANGED.
HOW WONDERFUL THAT ALL IT TOOK FOR YOU TO GROW UP
WAS THE END OF THE WORLD.
[ Singsong voice ] NOW IT'S MY TURN.
AND IF I CAN'T BE LIKE YOU,
I'M GONNA MAKE HER LIKE ME.
AND LET'S FACE IT, ONCE SHE'S LIKE ME,
THEN YOU WOULDN'T BE VERY INTERESTED, HM?
NOW, WOULD YOU?
WHY CAN'T YOU?
HMM?
WHY CAN'T YOU BE LIKE ME?
[ CHUCKLES ] HUH?
LET HER GO...
...AND YOU CAN HAVE IT.
YOU CAN DO ANYTHING.
BE ANYTHING.
TAKE IT.
LET HER MAKE THE CHOICE.
OKAY.
[ PULSING ]
OH!
[ GROANING ]
[ GASPING ]
WOW.
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
NOW BRING HER DOWN.
OH.
HAL.
I LIED.
I LIED TOO.
SEE, THE WAY IT WORKS IS:
YOU HAVE TO BE CHOSEN.
AAAAAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GROANING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ ROARING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ ROARS ]
[ GASPS ]
YOU HAVE FAILED ME.
[ SCREAMING ]
[ ENERGY CRACKLING ]
[ WAILING ]
STAY HERE.
NO PROBLEM.
[ GRUNTING ]
NO! AAH!
[ BEEPING ]
YOUR WILL IS STRONG, BUT NOT STRONG ENOUGH.
YOU ARE NOTHING WITHOUT THE RING.
AAH! AAH!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ BEEPING ]
[ ROARING ]
[ PULSING ]
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
Officer: YOU MUST MOVE OUT OF THE AREA NOW.
PLEASE CLEAR THE STREETS.
CLEAR THE STREETS IMMEDIATELY.
YOU CAN NEVER BEAT THIS. YOU'LL DIE.
AT LEAST I CAN GET IT AWAY FROM HERE.
HOW DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GONNA DO THAT?
I DON'T KNOW. I DON'T -- I DON'T KNOW.
I...MAYBE I CAN OUT-- OUTTHINK IT, OR...
THE DOGFIGHT, REMEMBER?
THOSE WERE A COUPLE OF JETS.
UNBEATABLE JETS.
THE RING CHOSE ME FOR A REASON.
THIS IS WHY.
LOOK, I'M PROBABLY NOT --
[ Voice breaking ] PLEASE DON'T.
NO. HEY.
[ CRYING ]
[ AIR RUSHES ]
THIS IS A MANDATORY EVACUATION.
EVERYONE MUST CLEAR THE STREETS IMMEDIATELY.
[ CROWD MURMURING, SIREN CHIRPS ]
POLICE EMERGENCY, EVERYONE MUST CLEAR THE STREET NOW.
[ ALL GASPING ]
[ ROARING ]
[ ALL SCREAMING ]
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
Man: GO! GO!
Woman: GO! GO!
[ SHOUTING CONTINUES ]
AAH!
Woman: EVERYBODY OFF NOW! NOW!
GO! GO!
Man: RUN!
[ ROARING ]
[ WEAPONS POWERING UP ]
RUN! AAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ CAR ALARM BLARING ]
I FEEL YOUR FEAR GROWING.
YOU WILL BE DEAD SOON.
[ Straining ] IN BRIGHTEST DAY, IN BLACKEST NIGHT...
AND WHEN YOU'RE GONE,
I'LL DESTROY EVERYTHING YOU EVER LOVED.
...NO EVIL SHALL ESCAPE MY SIGHT.
YOUR FAMILY, YOUR HOME, YOUR PLANET WILL BE NO MORE.
LET THOSE WHO WORSHIP EVIL'S MIGHT...
THE ENTIRE HUMAN RACE WILL BE WIPED OUT
BECAUSE YOU, HAL JORDAN, WERE AFRAID.
...BEWARE MY POWER:
GREEN LANTERN'S LIGHT!
[ SCREECHING ]
[ SCREECHES ]
THE BIGGER YOU ARE, THE FASTER YOU BURN.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ ROARS ]
[ SCREECHING ]
Sinestro: THOUGH HIS TIME WEARING THE RING HAS BEEN BRIEF,
HAL JORDAN'S DEFEAT OF PARALLAX
WILL BE REMEMBERED AS LONG AS THE CORPS EXISTS.
HIS ACTIONS ARE A REMINDER OF WHY THE RING CHOSE EACH OF US.
TO OVERCOME FEAR,
AND DESTROY EVIL WHEREVER IT MAY HIDE.
[ CROWD MURMURS ]
AS LANTERNS, WE MUST FIGHT WITH ALL OUR WILL.
OUR WILLS HAVEN'T ALWAYS BEEN UNITED.
IT'S TIME THEY WERE.
[ GRUNTS ]
CAN I TRAIN 'EM OR CAN I TRAIN 'EM? [ CHUCKLES ]
YOU'RE IMPERTINENT, HAL JORDAN.
YOU'RE RASH, VOLATILE, OPINIONATED.
IT SEEMS ABIN SUR FOUND ANOTHER JUST LIKE HIMSELF.
[ SEAGULLS CRYING ]
[ PULSING ]
WOW.
I AM NEVER GETTING USED TO THAT.
MY NEW JOB REQUIRES THAT I -- THAT I TRAVEL.
[ CHUCKLES ]
BE AWAY FOR A WHILE.
AWAY.
NEVER GONE.
HAL.
YEAH?
CAN YOU TAKE OFF THE MASK?
THAT'S REALLY COOL. [ CHUCKLES ]
[ SIGHS ]
SO WHAT HAPPENS NOW?
I'M GONNA GO LOOK FOR TROUBLE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ SIGHS ]
Tomar-Re: OF ALL THE LANTERNS WHO HAVE EVER WORN THE RING,
THERE WAS ONE WHOSE LIGHT SHINED BRIGHTEST.
AT FIRST, HIS HUMANITY WAS THOUGHT TO BE A WEAKNESS.
AND YET IT PROVED TO BE HIS GREATEST STRENGTH.
[ PULSING ]
[ EXHALES SHARPLY ]