Come on, Drax. Dance.
Only idiots dance.
I'm a weirdo
I want to have control
I want a perfect body
Hey!
I told you a million times...
you keep your grimy raccoon hands
off my Zune.
I told you a million times,
I'm not a damn raccoon.
Again?
I love you, Gamora.
So, what are you gonna do about Quill?
Me? Why not you?
I got emotionalistical issues.
What am I gonna do?
Why are you on the ceiling?
I wanted to see if these new gravity
boots worked on a slope.
Here we go.
Sorry.
Bozhe moi, Kraglin.
You must know you will never learn.
You think you could do better?
Telekinesis is cheating!
That's a stupid little pebble!
I could do that with my dang finger!
You're a bad dog.
Do not say that to me.
You are. You're a bad dog.
Take that back.
Come on, that's not cool.
Nebula, did you hear?
He called me a bad dog,
and he refused to take it back.
I don't care, Cosmo.
- Is Peter okay?
- I don't know.
What are you going to do?
Me? He's your brother.
It doesn't matter,
he still doesn't listen to me.
Yeah, he has been pretty mopey
ever since Gamora died.
She's not dead.
She just doesn't remember anything
from the past few years.
Nobody tells me nothing.
Mantis, why don't you just touch him
and, you know, make him happy?
I am Groot?
- Dude!
- Gross!
No, not like that.
Touch him with her powers.
It is wrong to manipulate
the feelings of friends.
'Bout that time you made me
fall in love with my sock?
Well, that was funny.
I guess it's back to one of us
touching him the other way.
Maybe we should draw straws.
No one ever meant that, Drax.
- What was that?
What the hell?
Oh, my God!
Is he okay?
Hey!
Where did you go, squirrel?
On the ground!
No, stop! Don't!
Stop, please! No! Stop, please!
Please!
Who is that maniac?
Some super douche with ray gun hands,
I don't frickin' know.
Who threw this thing at me?
Shut up.
Baby.
Pick on someone your own size.
Peter!
We need Med-Paks!
Nebula!
Piss off.
Rocket.
That hurts.
What a pity.
No!
All I did was activate the Med-Paks!
Get them off! Now!
Oh, hell.
We need to get him to the Med-Bay!
It was destroyed.
There's one on the ship.
Lill ol od for today.
Stitch him up and transfer him in
with the rest of Batch 89.
It's okay.
You're here with us now.
Hey! It's a new guy.
What kind of thing are you?
You've got, like, a mask on your face.
Mask, eyes, face, mouth...
Does it words?
It's okay, friend.
Don't let them scare you.
Hurts.
It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
A kill switch?
A device set to destruct
if anyone goes poking around inside him...
or even if we use the Med-Paks.
And why would Rocket have a kill switch?
Apparently, someone considers him
proprietary technology...
and sent that golden lunatic to get him.
So, he'll die if we operate on him?
And he'll die if we don't.
There has to be some way to bypass it.
It looks like there's a passkey
that could override the kill switch.
What do we know
about where Rocket came from?
He won't talk about it.
Much of the tech was developed
by a company called OrgoCorp.
And there's a code on all of it...
89P13.
He's got maybe 48 hours.
Where are you going?
OrgoCorp have to have records, right?
Maybe they'll have a way for us to
override the kill switch and save Rocket.
They won't just give us that information.
Well, that's why we're gonna break in.
We kill anyone who gets in our way!
- Not kill anyone.
- Kill a few people.
Kill no people.
Kill one guy,
one stupid guy who no one loves.
Now you're just making it sad.
Kraglin, Cosmo,
I need you to keep watch...
over Knowhere till we're back.
Couple of days, tops.
- Aye, Cap'n.
- Aye, comrade.
Take back what you said,
that I'm a bad dog.
Nope.
I know you don't really think
I am a bad dog.
Can you please take it back?
I will not.
I located the coordinates for OrgoCorp.
I think I have a contact near there.
Maybe they can help us get in.
Contact him.
Let's go save our friend.
No, no, no.
It's good to have friends.
Oh, my poor baby.
It hurts.
Do you have it?
He does not, sire.
I tried to warn you, High Evolutionary.
These Guardians are more powerful
than you think.
Or perhaps you simply overestimate
your own value, High Priestess.
No doubt a flaw of some type
in my own design.
I created you lot as merely
an aesthetic experiment.
Beautiful numbskulls.
But your egos have run wild.
Say, "ah"...
And this one
was meant to be the Warlock...
the apogee of their people.
You removed Adam from his cocoon early...
My liege.
He's still a child.
No, there's something wrong with him
even outside all that.
Yes, there's something wrong with me!
I was stabbed, you extraordinary phallus!
He doesn't know any better.
We shall do whatever you require, my liege.
You knew of 89P13's existence for years
without alerting me.
That's not what I require!
I'm sorry, my liege.
Find 89P13 and return it to me...
or I will destroy your entire civilization,
as is my right as your maker.
Do you understand?
Yes, sire.
Toodle-do.
How did 89P13 survive
after all these years, Theel?
It was always clever, sire.
- Yes, that's exactly why I want it now.
- Of course.
- Its brain.
- That is the only reason, sire.
But are you really trusting the Sovereign
to retrieve it?
They're merely a backup.
I believe I know where they're going.
It's bio-formed.
Instead of being built,
it's grown from living matter.
The structure is surrounded by three
impenetrable plasmic security shields.
It's not going to be easy
to break into this place, Star-Lord.
Doesn't have to be easy.
I was a professional thief, remember?
I'll jam the signals one at a time.
She calls me Star-Lord
when she's mad at me.
She's always mad...
at everyone.
It's because I was drunk.
She's right.
If I hadn't been drinking...
maybe Rocket... I'm sorry.
It's okay. He's your best friend.
Second best friend.
Everyone around me dies.
My mother, Yondu, Gamora.
Gamora isn't dead.
She is to us.
You want a Zarg-Nut?
Thank you.
First shield set.
Three, two...
one.
- Peter.
- What?
You had family on Earth...
and you never wanted
to go back to see them?
No, you're my sister.
That's all the family I want or need.
Besides, it was really just my grandpa, okay?
He was a pretty hard guy.
Still. Don't you think he...
What?
You were abducted by Ravagers
the same day he lost his daughter.
Oh, yeah, he was upset.
My mom died, he screamed in my face,
he pushed me out of the room!
He was probably
just trying to protect you.
- What are you talking about?
- What?
I'm talking about the people in my life
who died, and you're talking about this?
Second shield set.
Three, two...
one.
I'm only saying...
you've never even gone
to see if he's okay.
He could still be alive.
My grandpa, he'd be like
90-something years old.
So he could still be alive.
People on Earth die
when they're like 50.
They die when they're 50?
I don't know. Something like that.
What's even the point of being born?
Exactly!
Are you about to die?
I'm not 50!
The point is...
I wasn't talking about any of this.
Third shield set.
Three, two, one.
Well, not everything
is about what you are talking about.
And I'm only saying...
you are upset because so many of the people
you cared about have left you...
but you also left someone.
And maybe I wanted a Zarg-Nut!
It's too late. They're all gone.
Why didn't we go through?
We did. It's not the shield.
Oh, hell.
Ravagers.
Hey, guys...
you're about to be boarded
by the United Ravagers.
You can surrender and turn over
any stuff worth anything and live...
or you can die.
Totes up to you.
Drax, no, no, no, Drax!
Guys, it's me, Peter Quill,
I'm one of you, remember?
Hold on!
We have an appointment!
We have an appointment.
With who?
- With Gamora.
What?
You're early.
What are these?
OrgoCorp uniforms.
You're gonna have to wear these
to move through the Orgo...
without attracting attention.
This isn't my color.
What did you say?
It clashes with my eyes.
Put it on!
Nebula, why would you not tell me
that you've been in contact with Gamora?
Because I didn't want you
to get freaked out.
Freaked out how?
Like that.
Let me in there.
I don't wanna be trapped out here,
I can't...
Gamora, we are grateful for your help.
I'm not doing this
out of the kindness of my heart.
I'm doing this for the hundred thousand
units my sister promised.
So, you're a Ravager now?
Put on the uniform.
Never pictured you as the Ravager type.
Who are you again?
Oh, man.
OrgoCorp is in possession
of some of the most advanced...
cybergenetic IP in the galaxy...
so they're heavily guarded
by the deadly Orgosentries.
Now, I know you don't have
documentation to dock...
so you're gonna have to
get in there on your own.
Once in, Gamora is gonna
lead you to the records...
where maybe you can find the passkey...
to override the kill switch...
and help you save the hedgehog.
But if you get into trouble...
we will not be able to bail you out.
Yes.
Yes, of course. Brilliant.
His functioning has skyrocketed.
That's correct, P13.
Very good.
That's the new world.
Counter-Earth.
Where the experiments will go
once they're ready.
It blue.
That's the sky.
Sky.
Rocket.
Yes, it is.
What sounds?
That's music.
We like it?
We do.
This recording is over 5,000 years old.
Mo Ergastee Förn,
Mo Ergalone Förn Nort.
Which, translated, is...
Be not as you are,
but as you should be.
It's our sacred mission...
to take the cacophony of sounds
around us...
and turn it into a song.
To take an imperfect clump...
of biological matter such as you...
and transform it into something...
perfect.
And we're halfway there, aren't we?
Come with me, P13.
I'd like to show you something.
We have but a single quest...
to create the perfect species...
and the perfect society.
You, P13...
are part of Batch 89.
But here with Batch 90...
I've developed a process
by which I can guide...
any organism through millions of years...
of programmed evolutionary changes...
in a moment.
See, now, there's the rub.
For some reason...
these specimens are also over-producing...
loligo beta-microseminoprotein
in their systems...
causing them to be, well...
Violent. We don't like it.
A utopia can't have its denizens
murdering one another, can it?
It can'ts.
Can't.
Theel.
They're programmed to be peaceful.
Like you.
But for some reason, it's not catching.
Hyptonic filters.
What?
They's suppressaliting
the glycosylated saltses.
And then boop-boop-boop,
halfcystine residual be formin'...
and then, they make...
What do you say?
Loligo beta-microseminoproteins.
Yeah, thems.
And then, angry turtleses.
There.
That's the decompression chamber.
Lock in.
Go.
Activate gravity boots and gloves.
Nebula, go.
So, you really don't remember anything?
Like what?
'Bout your time with us.
No.
We were...
We weren't anything.
You and me...
That person was
some alternate future version of me.
It wasn't me.
We loved each other.
I don't think so.
I know you don't remember any of it.
You were everything to me.
And I miss you...
so much.
And, maybe...
maybe, if you open yourself up to it...
there's a possibility...
I don't think so, Quinn.
Quill.
I don't think so.
Well, what I'm trying to say...
Peter, you know
this is an open line, right?
What?
We're listening
to everything you're saying.
And it is painful.
And you're just telling me now?
We were hoping it would stop on its own.
But I switched it over to private!
What color button did you push?
Blue, for the blue suit!
Oh, no!
Blue is the open line for everyone.
- Orange is for blue.
- What?
Black is for orange...
yellow is for green, green is for red,
and red is for yellow.
No. Yellow is for yellow...
green is for red, red is for green.
- I don't think so.
- Try it then.
Hello!
You were right.
How the hell am I supposed to
know all of that?
Seems intuitive.
Can we get back to saving our friend?
Get that jammer
ready to change the shield.
Guys?
I mean, you wanna talk about a sweet ride?
The acceleration will crush your spine.
It's got that brand-new fusalix core.
You know what I'm talking about?
Yeah.
Really?
'Cause I just made that up.
I thought you said somethin' else.
Master Karja.
- No, you didn't.
- I did.
Master Karja, there appears to be
a physical breach...
in the white wing somewhere.
- Could it be a glitch?
- Maybe.
I'm accessing the eye.
I'll see if I can locate it.
There's some sort of anomaly
in the decompression chamber.
- Best you check it out, Master.
- On it.
Hurry.
Where do we put these?
Here! Hide them in this locker
until we leave.
Hurry!
What the hell was that, guys?
What, are you kidding me?
What?
A neutro-quark just hit the satellite.
It's burning a hole through the wall.
You geniuses...
you just throw the door open without
any proper precautionary procedure?
What procedure, bro?
You want us to read the manual
for you too, bro?
You could have killed everyone in the wing!
Exactly! You idiots!
I'm angry too!
Oh, no.
I mean, can't you see...
these authentic mechanic uniforms
that we're wearing on our bodies?
That blend in with some of our skin-tones
better than others?
Excuse my friend.
He is the boss' nephew.
He's a little...
Yeah. I got one of those too.
I mean, this one? This one I love.
I'm so proud.
You're doing great. So proud of you.
But this one, I just...
- Everything he does drives me crazy.
- Yeah.
- I thought you said something else.
- Shut up.
I swear I'm gonna throttle him.
I'm gonna go to jail for murder.
I am.
How'd you guys get here so fast?
I'll be honest with you,
we just happened in...
before it burned
all the way through, thankfully.
Good thing you were here.
All right, guys, wrap it up.
Looks like we're all clear here.
Our spacesuits!
You threw them in the contamination bin.
It expels stuff into space
the moment you shut the door.
That would have been helpful information
three minutes ago.
Damn it, Mantis,
why don't you ever think?
Are we pretending to be angry again?
Mantis, you asshole!
Guys, just focus for two seconds.
We'll find another way out of here.
Right now, we need to save Rocket's life.
Nebula, Quinn, and I will get to the records
and get the passkey.
Bug and Doofus, access the spaceport
through the elevator...
so Tree can land and get us out of here.
Apologies.
No problem.
Go.
Not my fault I don't know something...
if no one ever tells me.
I didn't even wanna come here.
I'm gonna need to see your...
You're hopelessly in love...
with him.
Oh, no.
Hey.
How you doin' today?
I'm all right.
What was your name again?
Drax the Destroyer.
That is such a lovely name.
I'll get the door for you.
- I'll be here when you come back out, okay?
- Sure.
Every single time.
My name is Bletelsnort.
Welcome to OrgoCorp headquarters.
For over 300 years...
OrgoCorp has been producing
cybernetic implants...
and genetic upgrades
across the universe...
under the watchful eye
of the High Evolutionary.
That warning we got today,
don't those two match the description?
Attention, all Orgosentries...
That manager should have access
to the records.
If the passkey is here,
she can get it for us.
All right. I'll handle this one.
How?
Pure Star-Lord charm.
I'm excited for you that you get to
see this again for the first time.
Hi, Yura.
Ura.
- Ura.
- Hi.
Hi, my name's Patrick Swayze.
I've been noticing you for quite a while...
and the way that you smile to yourself...
when you think nobody is looking...
it makes my every day a bit brighter.
We need your hand.
And it's your choice...
whether it's on your body or not.
- What are you doing?
- She was never gonna fall for that.
Dude, she was totally into me, man!
- I kind of thought you were a douchebag.
- Come on.
- We need a file.
- What file?
89P13. Could that be something?
- No.
- Then your use to us...
- is over.
- Wait, wait, wait!
It sounds like a species tag.
Show us!
All of our research supports the
High Evolutionary's altruistic objective...
of creating a utopian society.
That must be the spaceport.
What is all this?
Species patented over the years
using OrgoCorp tech.
Every species OrgoCorp has created
has its own individual file.
I'm so sorry about this.
Listen to me,
this is not the kind of thing we do.
Please, stop it with the subtle jabs!
Old you would have never done this.
You had a purpose higher than yourself.
- A calling to help people.
- Give me a break.
That's why you left Thanos
and formed the Guardians.
Except, I didn't form the Guardians.
And I barely left Thanos.
Whoever it was that you were in love with...
it wasn't me.
It sounds more like her.
- Her?
- What?
- That's ridiculous! Don't even...
- Do not bring me into this.
- Knock it off!
- What?
Don't look at me like a lost puppy
needing a soft place...
- to lie down.
- I didn't say anything!
I just never noticed
how black your eyes were.
They were replaced by my father...
as a method of torture.
He picked a pretty set.
There.
That's the file for 89P13.
Heads up, heads up!
Okay.
What?
Oh, no.
Walk!
Move it, move it!
Stand down!
Drax, we should make a run for it.
Or we could fight.
- Run.
- Fight.
- Run!
- Fight!
Take 'em!
What are we gonna do?
- I got a plan.
- What is it?
All of you, come with me...
Everybody, lower your weapons...
or I blow this woman's brains out!
That's the plan?
You're a kitty cat.
You feel like dancing.
Violent rage.
Lower your weapons!
Let's kill that one that looks like a carrot
to show we mean business.
God! Past Gamora's just mean!
She was always like that,
and yet, I was the bad guy.
We are not killing anyone!
Back off!
Groot, bring the Bowie to us.
Now.
I'm so sorry about this, Ura.
Oh, please.
We're here to save the life of our friend,
that is all.
We paid her to help us get in and get out.
You'd think that'd mean,
I'm gonna help you do it in a way...
that no one knows it's happening.
But no, what she means is,
I'm gonna shoot people.
- Threaten people's lives.
- Shut up!
And I know you're probably asking,
why would I trust her?
Well, that's a good question.
The answer is, we used to be in love.
Yeah. She was my girlfriend...
only she doesn't remember it,
because it wasn't her.
Because her dad threw her off a magic cliff
and she died...
and then I lost my temper
and nearly destroyed half the universe.
Then she came back, out of the past.
And there she is.
Everyone else who died in the past
stayed dead, not her.
Why? Was it the magic cliff?
I don't know.
I'm not some
fricking Infinity Stone scientist.
Just some dumbass Earth dude who met a girl,
fell in love...
that girl died...
and then came back a total dick.
He left out some important information...
but that is the gist of it.
Get to the security hub!
Okay!
Everybody, down on the floor,
or we blow your brains out!
Hey, hey, hey, we don't want any...
No! Oh, my God! Oh, my God! No!
Come on!
Would you please stop doing that?
Yeah!
Hey!
Run.
Drax!
Get on the ground
and show me your hands now.
Ura?
Please listen to me.
We need to get out of here with this...
to save my best friend's life.
If you could get us into
the system of those sentries out there...
they are good people, like you.
I'm certain of it.
And if I just had an opportunity
to speak to them...
They're corporate shills, you idiot.
They're not gonna listen to you.
They will listen
if I speak to them from my heart.
Ura.
Please.
Hey!
Come out now!
Damn it!
You are in.
Tell them your truth.
Yeah, I'm not that big of an idiot.
I just needed to get into the system.
Move it.
Told you she was into me.
I am Groot?
Yeah, that looked cool.
Is sky?
No.
That's not sky, that's a ceiling.
But sire's making a new world
for all of us...
and when we get there...
there will be sky...
and it will be beautiful and forever.
I have been thinking.
'Bout what?
Nothing in particular.
But I thought,
since you guys are my closest friends...
and my only friends...
you might be interested in knowing
that I have been thinking.
That's cool.
I've been thinking too...
about something more singular.
When sire moves us to the new world...
we're gonna need names.
I mean...
89Q12...
it's not really a name...
so I would like my name to be...
Lylla.
That's a pretty name, Lylla.
Thank you.
I think my name shall be Teefs...
because, although we all do have them...
mine are definitely the most prominent.
- Teefs.
- Lylla.
Me be called Floor,
because me is lying on floor.
You're lying on a floor,
so your name is Floor?
Yes!
- Floor.
What about you, friend?
Someday, I'm gonna make
great machines that fly...
and me and my friends
are gonna go flyin' together...
into the forever and beautiful sky.
Lylla, and Teefs...
and Floor, and me...
Rocket.
It really is good to have friends.
Yeah.
Start the incision here.
Keep calm.
- Hold it still.
- I can't!
It won't stop moving.
Why did he never tell us
about any of this?
This is worse
than what Thanos did to me.
Well, what about the passkey?
Is it there?
No. But a file was removed today.
Downloaded and deleted,
a million characters in length.
The biometrics say it was this man.
Recorder B2H6.
I saw this guy outside of records today.
Looks like one of
the High Evolutionary's recorders.
The High Evolutionary?
The founder of OrgoCorp?
OrgoCorp is just a way
to fund his experiments...
that lie outside intergalactic laws.
He's created whole societies.
Xeronians, the Ani-Men...
- The Sovereign.
- The Sovereign?
Corners of the universe consider him God.
I am Groot.
Yes.
Yes, what? That he's Groot?
He said maybe this man downloaded the passkey
into the computer on his head.
That could store the passkey.
We find him, we save Rocket.
The High Evolutionary's coordinates.
Put the coordinates in the nav.
Wait a minute.
Are you kidding me?
What he wants
is that gutted badger in the Med-Bay...
and you're gonna bring it straight to him?
It's almost certainly a trap.
Trap isn't a trap if you know the trap
is trying to trap you. It's a face-off.
A face-off is a trap if you're facing off...
against a guy a thousand times
more powerful than you.
Do you know who the High Evolutionary is?
Yeah, he's some dickhead
who dissected my best friend.
- Second best.
- The High Evolutionary...
isn't someone you wanna
think about messing with.
We won't think about it when we do it.
You know what? I don't care!
Just drop me off with the Ravagers...
and you go do
whatever it is that you wanna do.
We don't have time for this.
I'm not asking you.
Drop me off with my people now!
Your people?
The Ravagers aren't your people.
I'm a damn Ravager. You aren't.
Listen, I know you were always
looking for a family. Okay?
But my Gamora, the one I loved...
she didn't find it
with a group of criminals...
she found it with us.
People who care about you.
I know that's who you still are.
Somewhere inside of you...
What are you so afraid of in your self
that I need to be something for you?
I don't give a shit about your Gamora.
Life made me me!
I have a few upgrades courtesy of
that gutted badger in the Med-Bay...
and we are not risking his life
to make yours more convenient.
I'm family.
So is he.
Screw you.
Screw all of you.
Found him on the outskirts
of the first shield...
pirating supply ships.
I do appreciate this, good sir.
And I appreciate your generous contribution
to the Orgosentry retirement fund.
Your associate...
a Zehoberei named Gamora,
where is she now?
You ain't getting nothing from me.
Oh, we'll see about that,
won't we?
Adam.
Yes, Mother?
Show him we mean business.
I said show him we mean business,
not disintegrate him!
What more business
could we have shown him?
But now he's of no use to us!
Well, let's just question
the man's friend.
Friend?
You think that's a friend?
It's an animal!
He looks sad.
I really don't enjoy
how that's making me feel actually.
Your friend's a moron.
I got one of those too. I get it.
Outpost?
This is Gamora, you there?
Fitz-Gibbonok.
Come in.
Outpost, come in.
Yes, Gamora.
Salutations.
May I help?
Well, I need you guys to come pick me up.
I'm gonna upload the location-link
to the craft I'm on.
Oh, I think we can arrange that.
You need to say to him
exactly what I told you to say.
Why don't you just say it?
No one ever listens to me.
Quill...
Life is a pond...
and you've spent your entire life
leaping from woman to woman...
as if they're lily pads
upon this great pond.
Perhaps, what you need to do, Quill...
is learn to swim.
That actually made sense.
Yes, it made sense.
No, I mean, that's sort of an analogy.
And I didn't know that you were capable
of that type of thought.
I know lots of analogies, Quill.
Analogies, metaphors, et cetera.
For instance...
Gamora's head is like a lily pad
because it is green.
Analogy.
And also stupid-looking...
- and flappy.
- Flappy?
Because her skin is made of a leaf.
Metaphor.
Is it?
Yesterday, I made a poop
shaped like a fish.
Even my butt is capable of making an analogy.
What's happening?
The fluid is in his lungs.
P13?
P13.
Sire.
P13!
- My lord, might I suggest that we...
- Where is it? I passed it.
Must...
Sire was in the middle of his treatments
when we had a breakthrough with Batch 92.
Perhaps then we should resume tomorrow, yes?
We shall resume tomorrow, no!
P13!
There you are.
Hello.
How did you know...
about the microseminoproteins, P13?
What happened in there?
Why?
How did you know, P13?
It was too little filtration...
In the hypotonic, yes, we know,
we fixed that.
But how did you know?
I made you!
How did you know?
Because it worked.
It worked.
Their rage is gone.
We have the peaceful creatures
we always sought...
ready to inhabit the new world.
We're going to the new world?
We?
Look at you.
As if you were...
cobbled together by fat-fingered children.
How could you be part of a perfect species?
You're simply a medley of mistakes
we could learn from...
and apply to the creatures
that truly mattered.
Batch 89 was never meant
for the new world, P13.
You could figure out...
the complex workings
of cytoplasmic filtration systems...
but you couldn't figure out that?
But that brain.
That, I'd like to study further.
Prep it for surgery and removal
in the morning.
What about the rest of Batch 89, sire?
Incinerate them.
He's dying.
We need that passkey.
We don't have long.
We've arrived.
That looks just like...
home.
It's like a replica of Earth.
It makes no sense.
Atmosphere is habitable.
Gravity's Xandar minus one.
Hello.
We mean you no harm.
Listen to me, he was just trying
to throw her back her ball.
Hey!
Come on! There's no reason...
Hey, hey.
Groot, full Kaiju!
- Not full Kaiju!
- I am...
- Groot!
- Back up.
No, not Kaiju!
Groot, down!
There's no reason to be afraid.
Get down, Groot!
Everybody, it's okay.
It's okay.
Hey. Hey, hi.
We're not here to harm you.
Okay.
See? Here.
For your knee.
We just need to save our friend.
Filthy. It doesn't belong here.
I will train it
in the ways of the Sovereign.
I will train him not to do that.
It's an act of blasphemy
even having it here.
Kill it. Now.
I am the Warlock, Mum,
and I am done with being ordered around.
Gamora is here.
Which means the squirrel is also.
To save ourselves,
we must bring it to the High Evolutionary...
before his own people do.
Yeah, yeah, sit.
Let's sit. Okay.
I am Groot.
It's not rude.
It's what it's here for.
Drax, sit up!
Idiot.
Thank you.
Our friend...
He's dying.
We love our friend.
But he is dying.
That's not dying, that's already dead.
They'll think he's already dead.
They'll think we're here
on a quest for revenge.
Drax, sit up.
That's what it's here for!
Drax, it isn't.
It's made for people
to sit shoulder to shoulder...
right next to each other.
Get your boots off her pillows.
I find it hard to believe
it doesn't have multiple purposes!
I'm sorry. My friend...
is a dumbass.
That's the same as your dying.
Why do you criticize everything?
Well, why is it oblong then?
It was a totally different sound.
No, it wasn't. Dying. Dumbass. See?
It's the same.
All right, guys!
Can I proceed, please,
to try to save our friend?
Drax, I see you!
I understand that none of this
makes any sense to you right now.
We need your help...
in finding a man.
I'm gonna draw.
I'm gonna draw the man
that we're looking for.
Like this.
You see the thing on her head?
- He has a thing like this.
- That is delightful.
There you go.
Have you seen this man?
That's very good.
Can I have that later
to hang in my apartment, please?
Yeah.
Thank you.
His name is Mowtio?
Many mowtios. There?
At the pyramid.
Is that your car in the driveway?
Drax, stay here with Rocket.
Watch him.
That's who they're coming for.
- I wanna come.
- No.
Mantis, watch Drax.
Groot, you know what to do with these.
- Push down on it.
- What?
- Push it down.
- I am pushing down on it.
Push the button.
- It looks like you're pushing the keyhole.
- The what?
There's a button under the handle,
press that in.
Okay. Now what?
Open the fucking door.
That is a stupid design...
and your instructions were very unclear.
Let's get that passkey and save our friend.
I was eight years old
when I left Earth, okay?
Why would I know any more about
driving one of these things than you do?
Don't see you volunteering.
- You want me to drive?
- No.
- I'll drive.
- I don't want you to drive.
I got this.
You must be a really loyal pet...
if they're willing to do all this for you.
This is the perfect society?
Sire.
This one has been running for two hours...
without breaking a sweat.
- It's incredible...
- They can survive...
on thirty calories a day...
an hour's sleep a week,
they're always happy...
and they can rewire a carbenetrix core...
in under two minutes.
But will she be ready for the new colony?
Sire, they're here.
Here we go.
We're here to see...
The High Evolutionary is expecting you.
Which means it is a trap.
It's a face-off.
- She stays here.
- Why?
Policy against weaponry...
and your arm is a gun.
- He's clean.
- Let's go.
Hey.
It'll be okay.
Move it!
Are you okay, Rocket?
Me Rocket play now?
I can't right now, Floor.
What are you doing?
They ain't gonna set us free.
Yes, they are, Rocket.
We're going to the new world
any day now.
No, that can't be true.
It is.
They wanna kill us all in the morning.
What?
But I'm gonna fix it.
What is that?
It's a key.
I'm gonna use it
to get us all out of here.
I don't know if that's wise, Rocket.
Me Rocket leave!
Hooray time forever!
Just down that hall, there are ships.
I know.
And if we can get to one...
I can pilot it.
And then we'll all fly away together,
the four of us...
just like we always said, okay?
Okay?
Yippee! Rocket! Sky, sky, sky!
- You did it!
- Yes! Yes! Yes!
You did it!
You did it, you did it, you did it!
You did it.
It really is good to have...
Yes, I imagined you'd do something like this.
Back in the cage, P13.
Sky.
Rocket, Teefs, Floor go now.
- Q12 and P13 escaped from their pens.
- Rocket, Teefs, Floor go now.
- Q12 is neutralized...
- But P13 is still out...
- So I'll need assistance.
- Rocket, Teefs, Floor go now.
Rocket, Teefs, Floor go now.
Remember not to bruise its brain.
All right, P13!
You win the crying contest.
Now, back in the cage.
Rocket, Teefs, Floor go now.
- Rocket, let's go!
- Rocket, Teefs, Floor go now.
- Let's go! Rocket, please!
Rocket!
Down here. Hurry.
- Hey, there it is!
- Get him!
- Get back here!
- Get it!
What are you doing?
I got a bad feeling about this.
Peter just told you to stay here.
Yeah, well, that's his fault.
He should know by now that I never
do anything that anyone ever tells me.
We need to protect Rocket.
Yeah, that's right.
So, hop on and we'll ride back to the ship.
Just right over there?
Yeah.
Drax! Hey! Stop being a jerk!
You!
Hey, yeah, you!
I take it the passkey,
it's in that thing on your head.
I would advise against aggression.
Got time for me now?
Your friend once took advantage.
I learn my lessons.
I aim some small part
of my mental capacity...
back in my own direction...
and now,
gravity itself serves my whims.
War Pig.
Now.
You must find Counter-Earth familiar.
Counter-Earth?
I visited your planet many years ago.
Earth hasn't been my planet
in a long time.
Your people had...
wonderful spirit.
The art and music and literature
were some of the finest in the universe.
Earth would be a fabulous place,
were it not for the ignorance and bigotry.
- Okay.
- It inspired me to create Counter-Earth.
I don't care.
All of the good and none of the bad.
I don't need another speech
by some impotent whackjob...
whose mother didn't love him...
rationalizing why he needs
to conquer the universe.
I'm not trying to conquer the universe...
I'm perfecting it.
What the...
Hey!
Drop the badger.
- I just want the passkey.
- Then bring me 89P13.
I am Groot.
He says, suck my...
Why are you so angry?
Because I know what you did to our friend.
Anything I've done,
I've done for the betterment of the universe.
Newsflash, Einstein.
Better universes generally don't include
a bunch of octopuses selling meth...
to guys with cockroach heads.
They do not.
Which is why...
as I have done many times before...
I'm going to have to raze it all...
and start again.
What?
I got 89P13...
and I'm on my way.
We're in possession of the subject.
Oh, my God.
I am Groot?
Kill 'em all.
Stay.
I said stay.
What, did you want me to leave you back,
so that Mother could fillet you?
Stay.
What the hell?
- We're working for the same boss.
- Yes...
but I need the credit, chum...
to save my entire civilization.
So be a good creepy thing...
and back off.
No.
Mother.
Mother!
Mantis and Drax, come in.
Mantis? Drax?
Hey.
I need you to bring the ship here now!
Well, we can't do that exactly
because we're not at the ship.
Then where the hell are...
Nebula, come in.
Gamora! Take off now!
Get yourself and Rocket off the planet.
What kinda ship is this?
It's amusing really.
How stupid are you?
It was so obviously a trap.
It's not a trap. It's a face-off.
Now kill them all.
What do you have in your hand?
Grenade!
I am Groot!
No! Don't!
Don't! No, no, no! No, please!
Please, spare me!
Please, spare me, please.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank...
That'd be premature.
No, no, no...
Quite a novel escape plan,
jumping headfirst into an exploding planet.
You'll kill us both!
Not both.
Why are we doing this?
Quill and Groot are inside.
We have to get them out.
Groot.
Whoever's in the cockpit, activate the brake.
The steering mechanism is stuck.
Well, pull harder!
Let's go. Come on.
It's hard to breathe.
We're entering space.
Oh, piss off.
What kind of monster
slaughters a civilization?
Where are Mantis and Drax?
I don't know!
- Gimme.
- Here.
You're lucky I was able to...
- knock down that door...
- Rocket and Gamora are probably dead...
because of you!
- I didn't know.
- Oh, you didn't know?
When are you gonna
stop using the excuse of...
being some big dumb clown
for contributing nothing...
and the rest of us having to
carry your slack!
Don't push him!
You don't have the right to push him.
And you! You're no better.
The only thing we can count on you for...
is when someone shows weakness,
you'll be right there to support it.
Fine, I don't care.
I know you need to find fault in
everyone else to make yourself feel okay...
- so find it in me.
- Oh, go to hell, Mant!
But you don't have the right to push him!
It's not his fault he's stupid.
He's a liability.
He makes us laugh and he loves us.
How is that a liability?
All you care about is
intelligence and competence.
Not sure I appreciate this defense.
He has sadness...
but he's the only one of you
who doesn't hate himself.
So I don't care if he's stupid.
You think I'm stupid?
Yes.
Forget.
You're lucky I was able to knock down
that door with my incredible strength.
Quill?
Quill? Quill, are you there?
That language isn't in my translator.
Okay. Here we go.
Okay. All right, Rocket.
Go.
Lylla?
Friend.
Okay, okay.
Okay, here we go.
This isn't right.
Yeah, no, no, no, it's good.
It's gonna work. It's working.
It needs to be faster.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Rocket.
I let you down.
I got you killed.
I got everybody killed.
We were right.
The sky is beautiful, and it is forever.
And I've been flying with our friends.
Can I come?
Yes.
No, no, no!
No!
Come on.
- Come on!
- Quill.
No!
- No!
- Quill.
- I'm not gonna lose him.
He's gone.
I'm not letting him go!
Come on.
But not yet.
You still have a purpose here.
A purpose for what?
They made us for nothing.
Stupid experiments to be thrown away.
There are the hands that made us...
and then there are the hands
that guide the hands.
My beloved raccoon.
This story has been yours all along,
you just didn't know it.
I'm not a raccoon.
The passkey's going through!
Quill?
Where's Nebula?
She's...
Because her code is on the comm behind you.
What? Nebula?
- Where are you?
- Thank God!
We're here to get you out of here.
- Out of where?
- The High Evolutionary's ship.
No, I got off the ship.
- You what?
- Wait, where are you?
On the ship!
- On the ship?
- I didn't lie.
Why are you on the ship?
To save you obviously.
No, I told you to go back.
You gotta know by now I always figure out
an incredibly clever way to get out of a fix.
Tell him I said hi.
- Really?
- Tell him we're coming to save him.
Pay attention or play with the kids.
One or the other.
Play with the kids?
How did you get out?
That's not really important.
I am Groot.
Jumping a thousand feet to your death
without a parachute...
is a clever way...
of getting out of a fix?
You're all just makin' up
stuff that he's saying, right?
The important thing is...
we're all okay.
Rocket?
Yeah, he's here.
And he's okay.
Rocket, we love you very much,
and we're happy you're alive.
Well, that makes you the idiots then.
He's right about that.
Back in your cages!
Nebula?
Nebula, come in!
So, you'd like to joust, would you?
Go to hell...
you sick son of a bitch.
You killed all of those people.
As I will your friends.
I'm sending you the coordinates.
They will die unless you bring me...
what is mine!
Screw you,
you stretch-faced, RoboCop-looking...
Skeletor wannabe...
purple-nurple piece of...
He hung up.
You think?
1966.
The Soviet put me on a rocket...
knowing full well I'm never to return
and I will die...
in a fiery ball of death.
But one thing even mudak Soviets
never do...
is call me bad dog.
Oh, my God!
Could you just let it go?
Kraglin, please, just take it back.
This is killing us.
I can't take it back if she is
in fact...
a bad dog.
- Kraglin!
- It never stops hurting.
Kraglin.
Oh, hey, Pete.
We need to save Nebula, Mantis, and Drax,
and we need your help.
Me?
You're the one who lost it, you twit.
The Hellspawn had it, sire, but...
But, but, but!
But!
That rancid word.
I'm merely wondering
whether it might be wiser...
to go directly to the new colony
and not engage in unnecessary conflict.
They can rewire a carbenetrix core
in under two minutes...
but what is that, Vim?
Rote memorization.
Rote memorization!
In hundreds of years of our creations...
only one has known true invention.
One.
Putrid in every other way,
but 89P13 had that.
Yes, sire.
A populace unable to think
what hasn't yet been thought...
will die on the vine.
We need 89P13's brain...
so we can transfer that trait
into these creatures...
before we go to the new colony.
Nothing else matters.
How did they get down here?
Peter will be trying to get to the spaceport.
He doesn't know about the children.
You!
We need you to let all the other children
on board know...
to stay away from the starboard walls.
They know three frickin' words...
and two of them are "joob".
No! Listen to me!
You need to talk to the other children...
all of them here, and tell them...
to stay away from the freaking...
What the hell are you doing, Mantis?
Explaining it, dickhead!
You're scaring them.
Hello, dumb idiots.
I had a little girl like you.
You know what she used to like?
She liked when I made monkey noises.
How is that a monkey?
Beats me.
Yeah.
They're gonna tell the other kids
to stay away from the starboard wall.
Why didn't you tell us
you knew their language this whole time?
Why didn't you ask?
This could be futile, Quill.
He's too powerful.
Well, then I guess we'll die trying.
What is dying trying gonna accomplish?
Or we can just give him the badger?
Our thing is dying trying.
I am Groot.
I know who you are already!
Feel free to stay behind in the cargo area.
I'm not leaving my sister with that jackass.
This you?
Fell out of your bag.
Let's do this.
Wait.
Reading some old letters,
you smile...
You almost have to admire their pluck.
Sire.
Howdy there, you freakin' creep.
- Back up!
- Yes, sire.
You're on, Steemie.
First barrel.
Second barrel.
Third barrel.
Fourth barrel.
Hard starboard.
And fire!
They've breached the spaceport.
One of them holds subject 89P13.
Release the Hellspawn.
All of them.
Sire, the Hellspawn were created
solely to defend the new colony...
Do it now!
Get me 89P13...
and kill everyone
in the head of that dead god.
Spaceport wide open, Cap'n...
but that old missile's all we had.
Rocket, Groot, go, go!
Get inside that spaceport.
What the hell?
Aw, come on!
Kraglin, we have been infiltrated.
Open the pit.
Sire, our bargaining power will be gone.
Abilisks!
Good God!
This way!
One more step and this weird thing gets it!
Don't be rash.
What were you programming?
A self-destruction code.
What are you doing?
It's okay.
Mantis, stop!
They eat batteries...
not people.
Maybe they're just scared
of what we are gonna do to them.
We're not gonna hurt you.
Everything is going to be okay.
Use your heart, boy.
A dog!
Yeah.
She's a good dog.
I knew you believe I am good dog.
All right, all right, get off me, you idiot!
Sire, we must retreat.
The ship is going down.
The spaceport has intruders.
Go! See if one of them is 89P13.
Sire, you have an irrational obsession
with this animal.
You must stop, for God's sake!
There is no God!
That's why I stepped in!
Controller, I am taking command of the Arête.
Disengage all damaged sectors of the ship...
and retreat.
Attention...
all personnel.
Intruders have boarded the ship.
Head to the starboard spaceport.
Get me 89P13...
and kill the rest.
We go in there, we get Mantis...
Nebula, and Drax.
We move in, we get 'em, and we get out.
Did that look cool?
Okay, new game plan.
We get the hell out of here now.
There are thousands of creatures on the ship.
Many of them are children.
And we need to be good joob joob.
It means friends.
If we wanna live, we have to leave now.
This whole rig is gonna go down any second.
They will all die if we don't help them.
I'm done runnin'.
There's a big hole up in the deck.
If we can connect that to Knowhere,
we can lead the survivors to safety.
Nebs and me will pilot the ship.
You guys save all the higher life forms.
Hello, moron.
Come on!
Follow me, come on! Come on!
Go, go, go!
I am Groot!
This way to...
Thank you.
Yes, you're welcome.
I was screaming at...
something scary behind you, not you.
You look really cool.
Kill me if you want,
but then good luck gettin' out of here.
- Wait!
- Let him go, Flecktick...
it's our only chance.
I got a space big enough to get through.
I gotta find out if I can change it
to a permeable shield.
I can't fly this frickin' thing...
the flight controls are all screwed.
I'll do it.
Go help the others.
Wait, give me your comm.
Kraglin, I'll pilot from this side.
Kragula...
back in action!
Come on, come on, come on!
Go, go!
Go, go, go!
Wait, wait, wait!
Stop, stop!
Are those kids?
Okay, Cosmo, stitch it up!
It needs to be airtight
for the kids to make it across.
Locking up, Kapitan.
Go, now, go!
One by one, one by one!
Okay.
Locking in and headed down.
This way. This way.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
I tried to kill you.
I am Groot.
He says...
everyone deserves a second chance.
You are so strong.
Why are you so slow? Hurry!
Where's Rocket?
You!
You thought you could escape me!
No!
You think you have some worth
in and of yourself, without me?
No!
You are an abomination!
Nothing more than a step on my path...
you freakish little monster!
How dare you think you are more...
89P13?
The name's Rocket.
Rocket Raccoon.
His face came off!
It's a mask.
Look...
what you did to me.
For what?
All I wanted to do...
was to make things...
perfect.
You didn't wanna make things perfect.
You just hated things the way they are.
Kill him.
Why?
Because I'm a freaking
Guardian of the Galaxy.
We have to get outta here now.
We have to save them.
We've got all the kids on board.
No, Pete.
The rest of them.
Come on! Come on.
Move!
Move it, bird!
Come on!
Come on, come on, come on!
Thought we were limiting ourselves
to the higher life forms?
Yeah, well, me too.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Go, babies.
Go!
I cannot hold much...
Run!
Go! Go!
Quill!
Hurry!
Peter!
Did that...
look...
cool?
Come on.
Cosmo! I'm okay.
I am Groot.
Thanks.
Just tell them I'm gonna be right...
I am Groot.
Yeah.
It was good working with you too.
Hey, Gamora.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
You know, I'm still not
who you want me to be.
I know.
But who you are ain't so bad.
I bet we were fun.
Like you wouldn't believe.
Okay.
You okay?
I think I need to talk to everybody.
So, you're gonna leave?
My mother died in front of me
when I was eight years old...
and I have been running ever since.
I'm gonna need to take some time...
and learn how to swim.
I as well.
I love you all. I do.
But my whole life
I did whatever Ego wanted...
and then, I did
whatever the Guardians wanted.
I need to go out and discover what I want.
I'll come with you.
No, Drax. That's the whole point.
But you need someone to protect you.
- I don't.
- Not in a bad way.
Just because of your incredible weakness.
Oh, my gosh, you're so frustrating!
Drax.
I need you here.
We're building a new society.
I need all the support I can get
for those children out there.
Today, I saw who you are.
You weren't born to be a destroyer.
You were born to be a dad.
So, you'll lead the Guardians then?
No.
I'm gonna lead the city...
make it the type of home I never had.
So, that's it?
The group's over?
No.
Well, the Galaxy still needs its Guardians.
And you will make a better leader
than I ever was...
Cap'n.
I love you, guys.
For you.
Yeah!
Oh, yeah!
Welcome home.
I think I might be at the wrong...
I'm looking for Jason Quill.
Yes.
Come in.
Pete?
Pete.
Hi, Grandpa.
Yes! Yes! Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah!
Okay, how about your favorite musical act?
Phyla, you first.
Britney Spears and Korn.
Good choices.
I gotta go with the man.
Garth Brooks.
The Carpenters do not have a single bad song.
Adrian Belew.
Both solo and his work with King Crimson.
What about you, Captain?
This one's kind of special.
Guess they're here.
Well, I can handle this by my lonesome...
if y'all wanna chill.
Nah, nah.
It'll go faster if we all do it together.
Groot, wake up.
Do you ever feel a little sad for them?
Yeah, sure.
But these townsfolk can't protect themselves.
On your word, Kapitan.
Word.
I mean, if she needs help mowing her lawn,
I'll do it...
but I kinda feel like her son should help.
He's gonna sit on the porch
and watch me do it.
Like, he's a 45-year-old man...
able-bodied, and I'm mowing his lawn.
It just feels weird.
Don't get me started.
Oh, really?
Now I kind of want to know.