When you were here before
Couldn't look you in the eye
You're just like an angel
Your skin makes me cry
You float like a feather
In a beautiful world
And wish I was special
Come on, Drax. Dance.
Only idiots dance.
And I'm a creep
I'm a weirdo
What the hell am I doin' here?
I don't belong here
I want to have control
I want a perfect body
I want a perfect soul
I want you to notice
When I'm not around
You're so very special
I wish I was special
But I'm a creep
Hey! Uh-uh.
I told you a million times,
you keep your grimy
raccoon hands off my Zune.
I told you a million times,
I'm not a damn raccoon.
But I'm a creep
When I don't belong here
Whoa, whoa
Again?
Ah, she's runnin' out
She run, run, run, run
Whatever makes you happy
Whatever you want
I love you, Gamora.
You're so very special
I wish I was special
But I'm a creep
I'm a weirdo
What the hell am I doing here?
I don't belong here
So, what are you
gonna do about Quill?
Me? Why not you?
I got emotionalistical issues.
What am I gonna do?
Why are you on the ceiling?
I wanted to see if
these new gravity boots
worked on a slope.
Here we go.
Oh.
Sorry.
Bozhe moi, Kraglin.
You must know
you will never learn.
You think you could do better?
Da.
Davaj.
Telekinesis is cheating!
That's a stupid little pebble!
I could do that
with my dang finger!
You're a bad dog.
Do not say that to me.
You are. You're a bad dog.
Take that back.
Come on, that's not cool.
Nebula, did you hear?
He called me a bad dog,
and he refused to take it back.
I don't care, Cosmo.
- Is Peter okay?
- I don't know.
- What are you going to do?
- Me? He's your brother.
It doesn't matter,
he still doesn't listen to me.
Yeah, he has been pretty mopey
ever since Gamora died.
She's not dead.
She just doesn't
remember anything
from the past few years.
Nobody tells me nothing.
Mantis, why don't you
just touch him and,
- you know, make him happy?
- I am Groot?
- Dude!
- Gross!
No, not like that.
Touch him with her powers.
It is wrong to manipulate
the feelings of friends.
'Bout that time you made me
fall in love with my sock?
Well, that was funny.
I guess it's back to one of us
touching him the other way.
Maybe we should draw straws.
No one ever meant that, Drax.
If we still have time
We might still get by
Every time I think about it
I wanna cry
With bombs and the Devil
And the kids keep comin'
No way to breathe easy
No time to be young
But I tell myself
That I was doin' all right
There's nothin' left
To do at night
- What was that?
- What the hell?
- Oh, my God!
Is he okay?
Hey!
Where did you go, squirrel?
On the ground!
No, stop! Don't!
Stop, please! No!
STOP, please!
Please!
Who is that maniac?
Some super douche
with ray gun hands,
I don't frickin' know.
Who threw this thing at me?
Shut up.
Baby.
Pick on someone your own size.
Peter!
We need Med-Paks!
Nebula!
Piss off.
Ooh.
Rocket.
That hurts.
What a pity.
No!
All I did was
activate the Med-Paks!
Get them off! Now!
Oh, hell.
We need to get him
to the Med-Bay!
It was destroyed.
There's one on the ship.
Lill 0| od for today.
Stitch him up and transfer him
in with the rest of Batch 89.
It's okay.
You're here with us now.
Hey! It's a new guy.
What kind of thing are you?
You've got, like,
a mask on your face.
Mask, eyes, face, mouth,
does it words?
It's okay, friend.
Don't let them scare you.
Hurts.
It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
A kill switch?
A device set to destruct
if anyone goes
poking around inside him,
or even if we use the Med-Paks.
And why would Rocket
have a kill switch?
Apparently, someone considers
him proprietary technology
and sent that golden lunatic
to get him.
So, he'll die
if we operate on him?
And he'll die if We don't.
There has to be some way
to bypass it.
It looks like there's a passkey
that could override
the kill switch.
What do we know about
where Rocket came from?
He won't talk about it.
Much of the tech was developed
by a company called OrgoCorp.
And there's a code on all of it,
89P13.
He's got maybe 48 hours.
Where are you going?
OrgoCorp have to
have records, right?
Maybe they'll have a way for us
to override the kill switch
and save Rocket.
They won't just
give us that information.
Well, that's why
we're gonna break in.
We kill anyone
who gets in our way!
- Not kill anyone.
- Kill a few people.
Kill no people.
Kill one guy, one stupid guy
who no one loves.
Now you're just making it sad.
Kraglin, Cosmo,
I need you to keep watch
over Knowhere till we're back.
Couple of days, tops.
- Aye, Cap'n.
- Aye, comrade.
Take back what you said,
- that I'm a bad dog.
- Nope.
I know you don't really
think I am a bad dog.
Can you please take it back?
I will not.
I located the coordinates
for OrgoCorp.
I think I have
a contact near there.
Maybe they can help us get in.
Contact him.
Let's go save our friend.
I get the same old dreams
Same time every night
Fall to the ground And I wake up
So I get out of bed
Put on my shoes and in my head
Thoughts fly back
To the break-up
These four walls Are closing in
Look at the fix You've put me in
Since you been gone
No, no, no.
I'm out of my head Can't take it
Could I be wrong
But since you been gone
You cast the spell So break it
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
It's good to have friends.
Since you been gone
Oh, my poor baby.
N hurts.
- Do you have it?
- He does not, sire.
I tried to warn you,
High Evolutionary.
These Guardians are
more powerful than you think.
Or perhaps you simply
overestimate your own value,
High Priestess.
No doubt a flaw of some type
in my own design.
I created you lot as merely
an aesthetic experiment.
Beautiful numbskulls.
But your egos have run wild.
Say, "Ah."
- Ah.
- And this one
was meant to be the Warlock,
the apogee of their people.
You removed Adam
from his cocoon early,
my liege-
He's still a child.
No, there's something
wrong with him
even outside all that.
Yes, there's something
wrong with me!
I was stabbed,
you extraordinary phallus!
He doesn't know any better.
We shall do whatever
you require, my liege.
You knew of 89P13's existence
for years without alerting me.
That's not what I require!
I'm sorry, my liege.
Find 89P13 and return it to me,
or I will destroy
your entire civilization,
as is my right as your maker.
Do you understand?
Yes, sire.
Toodle-do.
How did 89P13 survive
after all these years, Theel?
It was always clever, sire.
Yes, that's exactly why
I want it now.
- Of course.
- |ts brain.
That is the only reason, sire.
But are you really trusting
the Sovereign to retrieve it?
They're merely a backup.
I believe I know
where they're going.
It's bio-formed.
Instead of being built,
it's grown from living matter.
The structure is surrounded
by three impenetrable
plasmic security shields.
It's not going to be easy
to break into this place,
Star-Lord.
Doesn't have to be easy.
I was a professional thief,
remember?
I'll jam the signals
one at a time.
She calls me Star-Lord
when she's mad at me.
She's always mad
at everyone.
It's because I was drunk.
She's right.
If I hadn't been drinking,
maybe Rocket... I'm sorry.
It's okay.
He's your best friend.
Second best friend.
Everyone around me dies.
My mother, Yondu, Gamora.
Gamora isn't dead.
She is to us.
You want a Zarg-Nut?
Thank you.
First shield set.
Three, two,
one.
- Peter.
- What?
You had family on Earth,
and you never wanted
to go back to see them?
No, you're my sister.
That's all the family
I want or need.
Besides, it was really
just my grandpa, okay?
He was a pretty hard guy.
Still. Don't you think he...
What?
You were abducted by Ravagers
the same day
he lost his daughter.
Oh, yeah, he was upset.
My morn died,
he screamed in my face,
he pushed me out of the room!
He was probably
just trying to protect you.
- What are you talking about?
- What?
I'm talking about the people
in my life who died,
and you're talking about this?
Second shield set.
Three, two, one.
I'm only saying,
you've never even
gone to see if he's okay.
He could still be alive.
My grandpa? He'd be, like,
90-something years old.
So he could still be alive.
People on Earth die
when they're, like, 50.
They die when they're 50?
I don't know.
Something like that.
What's even
the point of being born?
- Exactly!
- Are you about to die?
I'm not 50!
The point is,
I wasn't talking
about any of this.
Third shield set.
NEBULA". Three, two, one.
Well, not everything
is about
what you are talking about.
And I'm only saying
you are upset
because so many of the people
you cared about
have left you...
but you also left someone.
And maybe I wanted a Zarg-Nut!
It's too late.
They're all gone.
Why didn't we go through?
We did. It's not the shield.
Oh, hell.
Ravagers.
Hey, guys,
you're about to be boarded
by the United Ravagers.
You can surrender and turn over
any stuff
worth anything and live...
or you can die.
Totes up to you.
Drax, no, no, no, Drax!
- Mwah.
- Guys, it's me,
Peter Quill, I'm one of you,
remember?
Hold on!
We have an appointment!
- We have an appointment.
- With who?
- With Gamora.
- What?
- You're early.
What are these?
OrgoCorp uniforms.
You're gonna have to wear
these to move through the Orgo
without attracting attention.
This isn't my color.
What did you say?
It clashes with my eyes.
Put it on!
Nebula, why would you
not tell me
that you've been in contact
with Gamora?
Because I didn't want you
to get freaked out.
Freaked out how?
Like that.
Let me in there.
I don't wanna be trapped
out here, I can't...
Gamora, we are grateful
for your help.
Oh, I'm not doing this out
of the kindness of my heart.
I'm doing this
for the hundred thousand units
my sister promised.
So, you're a Ravager now?
Put on the uniform.
Never pictured you
as the Ravager type.
Who are you again?
Oh, man.
OrgoCorp is in possession
of some of the most advanced
cybergenetic IP in the galaxy,
so they're heavily guarded
by the deadly Or go sentries.
Now, I know you don't have
documentation to dock,
so you're gonna have to
get in there on your own.
Once in, Gamora is gonna
lead you to the records,
where maybe
you can find the passkey
to override the kill switch
and help you save the hedgehog.
But if you get into trouble,
we will not
be able to bail you out.
Yes.
Yes, of course. Brilliant.
His functioning has skyrocketed.
That's correct, P13.
Very good.
That's the new world.
Counter-Earth.
Where the experiments will go
once they're ready.
It blue.
That's the sky.
Sky.
Rocket.
Yes, it is.
What sounds?
That's music.
We like it?
We do.
This recording
is over 5,000 years old.
“Mo Ergastee Fbm, Mo Ergakane Fbm Non.“
Which, translated, is,
"Be not as you are,
but as you should be."
It's our sacred mission,
to take the cacophony
of sounds around us
and turn it into a song.
To take an imperfect clump
of biological matter such as you
and transform it into something
perfect.
And we're halfway there,
aren't we?
Come with me, P13.
I'd like to show you something.
We have but a single quest,
to create the perfect species
and the perfect society.
You, P13,
are part of Batch 89.
But here with Batch 90,
I've developed a process
by which I can guide
any organism
through millions of years
of programmed
evolutionary changes
in a moment.
({SCREECHES)
_
See, now, there's the rub.
For some reason,
these specimens
are also over-producing
loligo beta-micro semi no protein
in their systems,
causing them to be, well...
Violent. We don't like it.
A utopia can't have its denizens
murdering one another, can it?
It can'ts.
Can't.
TheeL
They're programmed
to be peaceful. Like you.
But for some reason,
it's not catching.
Hyptonic filters.
What?
They's suppressaliting
the glycosylated saltses.
And then boop-boop-boop,
halfcystine residual be formin',
and then, they make, urn...
What do you say?
Loligo
beta-micro semi no proteins.
Yeah, thems.
And then, angry turtleses.
Huh.
Woo ooh ooh ooh ooh Oooh ooooh
There. That's
the decompression chamber.
Lock in.
And in the end
We shall achieve in time
The thing they call divine
When all the stars
Will smile for me
Go.
When all is well
And well is all for all
And forever after
Well, maybe in the meantime
Wait and see
We love the all The all of you
Where lands are green
And skies are blue
When all in all
We're just like you
Activate gravity boots
and gloves.
And when I cry for me
I cry for you
Nebula, go.
For all the days
You've still to come
And did I ever say
I'd never play
Or fly toward the sun
Maybe in the meantime
Something's wrong
We love the all The all of you
Where lands are green
And skies are blue
So, you really don't
remember anything?
Like what?
'Bout your time with us.
No.
- Huh. We were...
- We weren't anything.
You and me...
That person was some alternate
future version of me.
It wasn't me.
We loved each other.
I don't think so.
I know you don't remember
any of it.
You were everything to me.
And I miss you...
so much.
And, maybe...
maybe, if you
open yourself up to it...
there's a possibility...
I don't think so, Quinn.
Quill.
I don't think so.
Well, what I'm trying to say...
Peter, you know this is
an open line, right?
What?
We're listening to everything
you're saying.
And it is painful.
And you're just telling me now?
We were hoping
it would stop on its own.
But I switched it over
to private!
What color button did you push?
- Blue, for the blue suit!
- Oh, no!
Blue is the open line
for everyone.
- Orange is for blue.
- What?
Black is for orange,
yellow is for green,
green is for red,
and red is for yellow.
DRAX". No. Yellow is for yellow,
green is for red,
red is for green.
- I don't think so.
- Try it then.
Hello!
You were right.
How the hell am I supposed
to know all of that?
Seems intuitive.
Can we get back
to saving our friend?
Get that jammer
ready to change the shield.
Guys?
I mean, you wanna talk
about a sweet ride?
The acceleration
will crush your spine.
It's got that brand-new
fusalix core.
You know what I'm talking about?
Oh, yeah.
Really? 'Cause I just
made that up.
Oh, I thought
you said somethin' else.
Master Karja.
- No, you didn't.
- |... I did.
Master Karja, there appears
to be a physical breach
in the white wing somewhere.
- Could it be a glitch?
- Maybe.
I'm accessing the eye.
I'll see if I can locate it.
There's some sort of anomaly
in the decompression chamber.
Best you check it out, Master.
On it.
Hurry.
Where do we put these?
Here! Hide them in this locker
until we leave.
Hurry!
What the hell was that, guys?
- What, are you kidding me?
- What?
A neutro-quark
just hit the satellite.
It's burning a hole
through the wall.
You geniuses,
you just throw the door open
without any proper
precautionary procedure?
What procedure, bro?
Oh! You want us to read
the manual for you too, bro?
You could have killed
everyone in the wing!
Exactly! You idiots!
I'm angry too!
On, no.
I mean, can't you see
these authentic
mechanic uniforms
that we're wearing
on our bodies?
That blend in with some of our
skin-tones better than others?
Excuse my friend.
He is the boss' nephew.
He's a little...
Oh. Oh.
Yeah. I...
I got one of those too.
I mean, this one?
This one I love.
I'm so proud.
You're doing great.
So proud of you.
But this one, I just...
Everything he does
drives me crazy.
Yeah.
I thought you said
something else.
Shut up.
I swear I'm gonna throttle him.
I'm gonna go to jail for murder.
I am.
How'd you guys get here so fast?
I'll be honest with you,
we just happened in
before it burned all the way
through, thankfully.
Ah. Good thing you were here.
All right, guys, wrap it up.
Looks like we're all clear here.
Our spacesuits!
You threw them
in the contamination bin.
It expels stuff into space
the moment you shut the door.
That would have been helpful
information three minutes ago.
Damn it, Mantis,
why don't you ever think?
Are we pretending
to be angry again?
Mantis, you asshole!
Guys, just focus
for two seconds.
We'll find another way
out of here.
Right now,
we need to save Rocket's life.
Nebula, Quinn, and I
will get to the records
and get the passkey.
Bug and Doofus,
access the spaceport
through the elevator
so Tree can land
and get us out of here.
Apologies.
No problem.
Go.
Not my fault
I don't know something
if no one ever tells me.
I didn't even wanna come here.
I'm gonna need to see your...
You're hopelessly in love
with him.
Oh, no.
Hey.
He'! -
How you doin' today?
I'm all right.
What was... What was
your name again?
- Drax the Destroyer.
- Oh.
That is such a lovely name.
Oh.
I'll get the door for you.
I'll be here when you
come back out, okay?
Sure.
Every single time.
My name is Bletelsnort.
HOST". Welcome
to OrgoCorp headquarters.
For over 300 years,
OrgoCorp has been producing
cybernetic implants
and genetic upgrades
across the universe
under the watchful eye
of the High Evolutionary.
That warning we got today,
don't those two
match the description?
Attention, all Or go sentries,
That manager should
have access to the records.
If the passkey is here,
she can get it for us.
All right.
I'll handle this one.
How?
Pure Star-Lord charm.
I'm excited for you
that you get to see this again
for the first time.
Hi, Yura.
Ura.
- Oh. Ura.
- Hi.
Hi, my name's Patrick Swayze.
I've been noticing you
for quite a while,
and the way
that you smile to yourself
when you think
nobody is looking,
it makes my every day
a bit brighter.
We need your hand.
And it's your choice
whether it's on your body
or not.
What are you doing?
She was never
gonna fall for that.
Dude, she was
totally into me, man!
I kind of thought
you were a douche bag.
- Oh, come on.
- We need a file.
- What file?
- 89P13.
- Could that be something?
- No.
Then your use to us
- is over.
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
It sounds like a species tag.
Show us!
All of our research supports
the High Evoiutionary's
altruistic objective
of creating a utopian society.
That must be the spaceport.
Whoa.
What is all this?
Species patented over
the years using OrgoCorp tech.
Every species
OrgoCorp has created
has its own individual file.
I'm so sorry about this.
Listen to me, this is not
the kind of thing we do.
Oh, please, stop it
with the subtle jabs!
Old you would have
never done this.
You had a purpose
higher than yourself.
- A calling to help people.
- Give me a break.
That's why you left Thanos
and formed the Guardians.
Except, I didn't
form the Guardians.
- Sheesh.
- And I barely left Thanos.
Whoever it was
that you were in love with,
it wasn't me.
It sounds more like her.
- Her?
- What?
- That's ridiculous!
- Do not bring me into this.
Don't even...
- Knock it off!
- What?
Don't look at me
like a lost puppy
needing a soft place
- to lie down.
- I didn't say anything!
I just never noticed
how black your eyes were.
They were replaced by my father
as a method of torture.
He... He picked a pretty set.
There.
That's the file for 89P13.
Heads up, heads up!
- Ugh.
- Okay.
What?
Oh, no.
Walk!
Move it, move it!
Stand down!
Drax, we should
make a run for it.
Or we could fight.
- Run.
- Fight.
-Run!
"Fight!
Take 'em!
What are we gonna do?
- I got a plan.
- What is it?
All of you, come with me...
Everybody, lower your weapons,
or I blow
this woman's brains out!
That's the plan?
- You're a kitty cat.
- Meow.
You feel like dancing.
Violent rage.
Lower your weapons!
Let's kill that one
that looks like a carrot
to show we mean business.
God! Past Gamora's just mean!
She was always like that,
and yet, I was the bad guy.
We are not killing anyone!
Back off!
Grout, bf log the Bowie
to us. Now.
I'm so sorry about this, Ura.
Oh, please.
We're here to save the life
of our friend, that is all.
We paid her to help us get in
and get out.
You'd think that'd mean,
"Oh, I'm gonna help you
"do it in a way that
no one knows it's happening."
But no, what she means is,
"|'m gonna shoot people.
- "Threaten people's lives."
- Shut up!
And I know
you're probably asking,
why would I trust her?
Well, that's a good question.
The answer is,
we used to be in love.
Yeah. She was my girlfriend,
only she doesn't remember it,
because it wasn't her.
Because her dad threw her off
a magic cliff and she died,
and then I lost my temper
and nearly destroyed
half the universe.
Then she came back,
out of the past.
And there she is.
Everyone else who died in
the past stayed dead, not her.
Why? Was it the magic cliff?
I don't know.
I'm not some fricking
Infinity Stone scientist.
Just some dumb-ass Earth dude
who met a girl, fell in love,
that girl died,
and then came back a total dick.
He left out
some important information,
but that is the gist of it.
Get to the security hub!
Okay!
Everybody, down on the floor,
or we blow your brains out!
Hey, hey, hey,
we don't want any...
No! Oh, my God
Oh, my God! No!
Come on! Would you please
stop doing that?
Now, I'm craving your body
Is this real
Temperature's rising
I don't want to feel
I'm in the wrong place
To be real
Yeah!
Hey!
And I'm longing to love you
Just for a night
Run.
Drax!
Get on the ground
and show me your hands now.
Ura?
Please listen to me.
We need to get out of here
with this
to save my best friend's life.
If you could get us
into the system
of those sentries out there,
they are good people,
like you. I'm certain of it.
And if I just had an opportunity
to speak to them...
They're corporate shills,
you idiot.
They're not gonna listen to you.
They will listen if I speak
to them from my heart.
Ura.
Please.
Hey!
Come out now!
Damn it!
You are in.
Tell them your truth.
Yeah, I'm not that big
of an idiot.
I just needed to get
into the system.
Move it.
Told you she was into me.
I am Groot?
Yeah, that looked cool.
Is sky?
No.
That's not sky,
that's a ceiling.
But sire's making a new world
for all of us,
and when we get there,
there will be sky,
and it will be beautiful
and forever.
Wow.
- Whoa.
I have been thinking.
'Bout what?
Oh, nothing in particular.
But I thought, since you guys
are my closest friends,
and my only friends,
you might
be interested in knowing
that I have been thinking.
That's cool.
I've been thinking, too,
about something more singular.
When sire moves us
to the new world,
we're gonna need names.
I mean,
89Q12,
it's not really a name,
so I would like my name to be...
Lylla.
That's a pretty name, Lylla.
Thank you.
I think my name shall be Teefs,
because, aHhough
we all do have them,
mine are definitely
the most prominent.
- Teefs.
- Lyl la.
Me be called Floor,
because me is lying on floor.
You're lying on a floor,
so your name is Floor?
FLOOR I Yes!
- Floor.
What about you, friend?
Someday, I'm gonna make
great machines that fly,
and me and my friends
are gonna go fl yin' together
into the forever
and beautiful sky.
Lylla, and Teefs,
and Floor, and me...
Rocket.
It really is good
to have friends.
Yeah.
Stan' the incision here.
RECORDER". Keep calm.
- H0/d if Sﬁ/l.
- / can "I!
/z' won '1' stop moving.
Why did he never tell us
about any of this?
This is worse
than what Thanos did to me.
Well, what about
the passkey? Is it there?
No. But a file
was removed today.
Downloaded and deleted,
a million characters in length.
The biometrics say it was
this man. Recorder B2H6.
I saw this guy
outside of records today.
Hmm.
Looks like one of the
High Evo|utionary's recorders.
The High Evolutionary?
The founder of OrgoCorp?
OrgoCorp is just a way
to fund his experiments
that lie outside
intergalactic laws.
He's created whole societies.
Xeronians, the Ani-Men,
- the Sovereign.
- The Sovereign?
Corners of the universe
consider him God.
I am Groot.
Yes.
Yes, what'? That he's Greet'?
He said maybe this man
downloaded the passkey
into the computer on his head.
Huh?
That could store the passkey.
We find him, we save Rocket.
The High Evo|utionary's
coordinates.
Put the coordinates in the nav.
Wait a minute.
Are you kidding me?
What he wants is that gutted
badger in the Med-Bay,
and you're gonna bring it
straight to him?
It's almost certainly a trap.
Trap isn't a trap
if you know the trap
is trying to trap you.
It's a face-off.
A face-off is a trap
if you're facing off
against a guy a thousand times
more powerful than you.
Do you know
who the High Evolutionary is?
Yeah, he's some dickhead
who dissected my best friend.
- Second best.
- The High Evolutionary
isn't someone you wanna
think about messing with.
We won't think about it
when we do it.
You know what? I don't care!
Just drop me off
with the Ravagers,
and you go do whatever it is
that you wanna do.
We don't have time for this.
I'm not asking you. Drop me
off with my people now!
"Your people"? The Ravagers
aren't your people.
I'm a damn Ravager.
You aren't.
Listen, I know you were always
looking for a family. Okay?
But my Gamora, the one I loved,
she didn't find it
with a group of criminals,
she found it with us.
People who care about you.
I know that's who you still are.
Somewhere inside of you...
What are you so afraid of
in your self
that I need to be
something for you?
I don't give a shit
about your Gamora.
Life made me me!
I have a few upgrades
courtesy of that gutted badger
in the Med-Bay,
and we are not risking his life
to make yours more convenient.
I'm family.
So is he.
Screw you.
Screw all of you.
Found him on the outskirts
of the first shield,
pirating supply Ships-
I do appreciate this, good sir.
And I appreciate
your generous contribution
to the Orgosentry
retirement fund.
Your associate,
a Zehoberei named Gamora,
where is she now?
You ain't getting
nothing from me.
Oh, we'll see about that,
won't we?
Adam.
Yes, Mother?
Show him we mean business.
I said show him
we mean business,
not disintegrate him!
What more business
could we have shown him?
But now he's of no use to us!
Well, let's just question
the man's friend.
Friend?
You think that's a friend?
It's an animal!
He looks sad.
I really don't enjoy
how that's
making me feel, actually.
Your friend's a moron.
I got one of those too.
I get it.
GAMORA". Outpost?
This is Gamora, you there?
Fitz-Gibbonok.
Come in.
GAMORA".
Outpost, come in.
Yes, Gamora.
Salutations.
May I help?
Well, I need you guys
to come pick me up.
I'm gonna upload
the location-link
to the craft I'm on.
Oh, I think we can arrange that.
Do you realize
That you have the most
Beautiful face?
Do you realize
We're floating in space?
You need to say to him exactly
what I told you to say.
Why don't you just say it?
No one ever listens to me.
Do you realize
That everyone...
Quill,
life is a pond,
and you've spent
your entire life
leaping from woman to woman
as if they're lily pads
upon this great pond.
Perhaps, what you need
to do, Quill,
is learn to swim.
- That actually made sense.
- Yes, it made sense.
No, I mean,
that's sort of an analogy.
And I didn't know
that you were capable
of that type of thought.
I know lots of analogies, Quill.
Analogies, metaphors, et cetera.
For instance,
Gamora's head is like a
lily pad because it is green.
Analogy-
And also stupid-looking
-and flappy-Happy?
Because her skin
is made of a leaf.
Metaphor.
Is it?
Yesterday, I made a poop
shaped like a fish.
Even my butt is capable
of making an analogy.
Oh.
What's happening?
The fluid is in his lungs.
P13?
P13.
Sire.
P13!
My lord,
might I suggest that we...
Must...
Ooh. Ooh.
Sire was in
the middle of his treatments
when we had a breakthrough
with Batch 92.
Perhaps then we should
resume tomorrow, yes?
"We shall resume tomorrow," no!
P13!
Oh. Ooh.
There you are.
Hello.
How did you know
about the micro semi no proteins,
P13?
What happened in there?
Why?
How did you know, P13?
Uh, it was
too little filtration...
In the hypotonic, yes,
we know, we fixed that.
But how did you know?
I made you!
How did you know?
Because it worked.
It... It worked.
Their rage is gone.
We have the peaceful creatures
we always sought,
ready to inhabit the new world.
We're going to the new world?
Oh.
We?
Look at you.
As if you were
cobbled together
by fat-fingered children.
How could you be part
of a perfect species?
You're simply a medley of
mistakes we could learn from
and apply to the creatures
that truly mattered.
Batch 89 was never meant
for the new world, P13.
You could figure out
the complex workings
of cytoplasmic
filtration systems,
but you couldn't
figure out that?
But that brain.
That, I'd like to study further.
Prep it for surgery
and removal in the morning.
What about the rest
of Batch 89, sire?
Incinerate them.
He's dying.
We need that passkey.
We don't have long.
MAN US".
We've arrived.
We care a lot
That looks just like...
home.
We care a lot
About disasters, fires
Floods and killer bees
It's like a replica of Earth.
It makes no sense.
Atmosphere is habitable.
Gravity's Xandar minus one.
We care a lot
About disease, baby, rock
Hudson, rock, yeah!
Oh, it's a dirty job
But someone's gotta do it
We care a lot
About the gamblers
And the pushers and the geeks
We care a lot
About the smack and crack
And whack that hits the streets
Hello.
We mean you no harm.
Listen to me, he was just trying
to throw her back her ball.
-0w!
- Hey!
- Ow, ow.
Come on! There's no reason...
Hey, hey.
Groot, full Kaiju!
- Not full Kaiju!
- I am
- Groot!
- Back up.
No, not Kaiju!
Groot, down!
There's no reason to be afraid.
Get down, Groot!
Everybody, it's okay.
It's okay.
Hey. Hey, hi.
We're not here to harm you.
Okay.
See? Here.
For your knee.
We just need to save our friend.
Filthy.
It doesn't belong here.
I will train it in the ways
of the Sovereign.
I will train him not to do that.
It's an act of blasphemy
even having it here.
Kill it. Now.
I am the Warlock, Mum,
and I am done
with being ordered around.
Gamora is here.
Which means
the squirrel is also.
To save ourselves,
we must bring it
to the High Evolutionary
before his own people do.
Yeah, yeah, sit.
Let's sit. Okay.
I am Groot.
It's not rude.
It's what it's here for.
Drax, sit up!
Idiot.
Thank you.
Our friend...
He's dying.
Uh...
We love our friend.
But he is dying.
That's not dying,
that's already dead.
They'll think he's already dead.
They'll think we're here
on a quest for revenge.
Drax, sit up.
That's what it's here for!
Drax, it isn't.
It's made for people
to sit shoulder to shoulder
right next to each other.
Get your boots off her pillows.
I find it hard to believe
it doesn't have
multiple purposes!
I'm sorry.
My friend is a dumb-ass.
That's the same as your dying.
Why do you criticize everything?
Well, why is it oblong then?
It was
a totally different sound.
No, it wasn't. Dying.
Dumbass.
- See? It's the same.
- All right, guys!
Can I proceed, please,
to try to save our friend?
Drax, I see you!
I understand that none of this
makes any sense
to you right now.
We need your help
in finding a man.
Uh, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna draw.
I'm gonna draw the man
that we're looking for.
Like this.
You see the thing on her head?
- He has a thing like this.
- That is delightful. Mm.
There you go.
Have you seen this man?
That's very good.
Can I have that later to hang
in my apartment, please?
Yeah. Thank you.
Mowtio.
His name...
His name is "ll/lowt/o"?
E0, e0. Uh...
Mowtios-ek Iolo.
- Many mowt/os.
- Oh.
- There?
- At the pyramid.
- Oh.
Is that your car
in the driveway?
- Oh.
- E0.
Drax, stay here with Rocket.
Watch him.
That's who they're coming for.
- I wanna come.
- No.
Mantis, watch Drax.
Groot, you know
what to do with these.
- Push down on it.
- What?
- Push it down.
- I am pushing down on it.
Push the button.
It looks like
you're pushing the keyhole.
- The what?
- There's a button
under the handle, press that in.
Okay. Now what?
Open the fucking door.
That is a stupid design,
and your instructions
were very unclear.
Let's get that passkey
and save our friend.
I was eight years old
when I left Earth, okay?
Why would I know any more
about driving one of
these things than you do?
- Don't see you volunteering.
- You want me to drive?
|'ll drive.
I don't want you to drive.
I got this.
Just a wild goose chase
And my dreams
Have all been denied
Why have I always Been a failure
What can the reason be
You must be a really loyal pet
if they're willing to do
all this for you.
Chasing rainbows
Watching clouds drifting by
My schemes are just like
All my dreams
Ending in the sky
Some fellows look
And find the sunshine
I always look And find the rain
And some fellows
Make a Winning sometime
I'm always chasing rainbows
This is the perfect society?
Sire.
This one has been running
for two hours
without breaking a sweat.
- It's incredible...
- They can survive
on 30 calories a day,
an hour's sleep a week,
they're always happy,
and they can rewire
a carbenetrix core
in under two minutes.
But will she be ready
for the new colony?
Sire, they're here.
Here we go.
We're here to see...
The High Evolutionary
is expecting you.
Which means it is a trap.
It's a face-off.
She stays here.
- Why?
- Policy against weaponry,
and your arm is a gun.
- He's clean.
- Let's go.
He'! -
It'll be okay.
Move it!
Are you okay, Rocket?
Me Rocket play now?
I can't right now, Floor.
What are you doing?
They ain't gonna set us free.
Yes, they are, Rocket.
We're going to the new world
any day now.
No, that can't be true.
It is.
They wanna kill us all
in the morning.
- What?
But I'm gonna fix it.
What is that?
It's a key.
I'm gonna use it
to get us all out of here.
I don't know
if that's wise, Rocket.
- Mm.
- Me Rocket leave!
Hooray time forever!
Just down that hall,
there are ships.
I know.
And if we can get to one,
I can pilot it.
And then we'll all fly away
together, the four of us,
just like we always said, okay?
Okay?
Whoo-hoo! Yippee!
Rocket! Sky, sky, Sky!
- You did it!
- FLOOR I Yes! Yes! Yes!
You did it!
You did it, you did it,
you did it!
You did it!
You did it.
It really is good to have...
Yes, I imagined
you'd do something like this.
Back in the cage, P13.
Sky.
Rocket, Teefs, Floor go now.
Q12 and P13
- escaped from their pens.
- Rocket, Teefs, Floor go now.
- Q12 is neutralized...
- But P13 is still out,
- so I'll need assistance.
- Rocket, Teefs, Floor go now.
Rocket, Teefs, Floor go now.
Remember not to bruise
its brain.
Rocket, Teefs, Floor go now.
All right, P13!
You win the crying contest.
Now, back in the cage.
- Rocket, Teefs, Floor go now.
- Rocket, let's go!
Let's go! Rocket, please!
Rocket! Rocket!
Down here. Hurry.
- Hey, there it is!
- Get him!
- Get back here!
- Get it!
He's getting away!
What are you doing?
I got a bad feeling about this.
Peter just told you
to stay here.
Yeah, well, that's his fault.
He should know by now
that I never do
anything that anyone
ever tells me.
We need to protect Rocket.
Yeah, that's right.
So, hop on and we'll ride
back to the ship.
Just right over there?
Yeah.
Drax! Hey! Stop being a jerk!
YOU!
Hey, yeah, you!
I take it the passkey,
it's in that thing on your head.
I would advise
against aggression.
Oh. Got time for me now?
Your friend once took advantage.
I learn my lessons.
I aim some small part
of my mental capacity
back in my own direction,
and now, gravity itself
serves my whims.
War Pig.
Now.
You must find
Counter-Earth familiar.
Counter-Earth?
I visited your planet
many years ago.
Earth hasn't been my planet
in a long time.
Your people had
- wonderful spirit.
- Mm.
The art and music and literature
were some of the finest
in the universe.
Earth would be a fabulous place,
were it not for
the ignorance and bigotry.
- Okay.
- It inspired me to create
- Counter-Earth.
- I don't care.
All of the good
and none of the bad.
I don't need another speech
by some impotent whack job
whose mother didn't love him
rationalizing why he needs
to conquer the universe.
I'm not trying
I'm perfecting it.
What the...
Hey!
Drop the badger.
- I just want the passkey.
- Then bring me 89P13.
I am Groot.
He says, "Suck my..."
Why are you so angry?
Because I know
what you did to our friend.
Anything I've done,
I've done for the betterment
of the universe.
Newsflash, Einstein.
Better universes
generally don't include
a bunch of octopuses
selling meth
to guys with cockroach heads.
They do not.
Which is why,
as I have done
many times before,
I'm going to have to raze it all
and start again.
What?
I got 89P13,
and I'm on my way.
We're in possession
of the subject.
Ow!
Oh, my God.
I am Groot?
Kill 'em all.
Stay.
Uh-uh. I said "stay."
What, did you want me
to leave you back,
so that Mother could fillet you?
Stay.
What the hell?
We're working for the same boss.
Yes, but I need
the credit, churn,
to save my entire civilization.
So be a good creepy... thing
and back off.
No.
Mother.
Mother!
Mantis and Drax, come in.
Mantis? Drax?
Uh, hey.
I need you to bring
the ship here now!
Well, we can't
do that exactly because...
we're not at the ship.
Then where the hell are...
Nebula, come in.
Gamora! Take off now!
Get yourself and Rocket
off the planet.
What kinda ship is this?
It's amusing, really.
How stupid are you, hmm?
It was so obviously a trap.
It's not a trap.
It's a face-off.
Now kill them all.
What do you have in your hand?
Grenade!
I am Groot!
No! Don't!
Don't! No, no, no! No, please!
Please, spare me!
Please, spare me, please.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank...
- That'd be premature.
- Huh?
No, no, no...
Quite a novel escape plan,
jumping headfirst
into an exploding planet.
You'll kill us both!
Not both.
Why are we doing this?
Quill and Groot are inside.
We have to get them out.
Groot.
Whoever's in the cockpit,
activate the brake.
The steering mechanism is stuck.
Well, pull harder!
Let's go. Come on.
It's hard to breathe.
We are entering space.
Joob joob?
Oh, piss off.
What kind of monster
slaughters a civilization?
- Where are Mantis and Drax?
- I don't know!
- Gimme.
- Here.
Ha! You're lucky I was able
- to knock down that door...
- Rocket and Gamora
are probably dead
because of you!
- I didn't know.
- Oh, you didn't know?
When are you gonna
stop using the excuse
of being some big dumb clown
for contributing nothing,
and the rest of us having
to carry your slack!
Don't push him!
You don't have the right
to push him.
And you! You're no better.
The only thing
we can count on you for
is when someone shows weakness,
you'll be right there
to support it.
Fine, I don't care.
I know you need to find fault
in everyone else
to make yourself feel okay,
- so find it in me.
- Oh, go to hell, Mant!
But you don't have the right
to push him!
It's not his fault he's stupid.
- He's a liability.
- He makes us laugh
and he loves us.
How is that a liability?
All you care about
is intelligence and...
and competence.
Not sure I appreciate
this defense.
He has sadness,
but he's the only one of you
who doesn't hate himself.
So I don't care if he's stupid.
You think I'm stupid?
Yes.
Forget.
Ha! You're lucky I was able
to knock down that door
with my incredible strength.
Quill?
Quill? Quill, are you there?
Joobjoob...
That language
isn't in my translator.
Okay. Here we go.
Okay. All right, Rocket.
Go.
Lylla?
Ff tend.
Okay, okay.
Okay, here we go.
This isn't right.
No, no, no, it's good.
It's gonna work. It's working.
It needs to be faster.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Rocket.
I let you down.
I got you killed.
I got everybody killed.
We were right.
The sky is beautiful,
and it is forever.
And I've been flying
with our friends.
Can I come?
Yes.
No, no, no!
No!
Come on.
- Come on!
- Quill.
No!
- No!
- Quill.
- I'm not gonna lose him.
He's gone.
I'm not letting him go!
Come on.
But not yet.
You still have a purpose here.
A purpose for what?
They made us for nothing.
Stupid experiments
to be thrown away.
There are the hands
that made us,
and then there are the hands
that guide the hands.
Mm.
My beloved raccoon.
This story
has been yours all along,
you just didn't know it.
|'m not a raccoon.
The passkey's going through!
Quill?
Where's Nebula?
Sh... She's, uh...
Because her code
is on the comm behind you.
What? Nebula?
- Where are you?
- Oh, thank God!
We're here
to get you out of here.
- Out of where?
- The High E vo/utionag/‘ls ship.
No, I got off the ship.
- You what?
- Wait, where are you?
On the ship!
- On the ship?
- / didn't/Ia.
Why are you on the ship?
To save you, obviously.
PETER". No, I told you to go back.
You gotta know by now
I always figure out
an incredibly clever way
to get out of a fix.
- Tell him I said hi.
- Really?
Tell him we're coming
to save him.
Pay attention
or play with the kids.
One or the other.
"Play with the kids"?
- How did you get out?
- That's not really important.
I am Groot.
Jumping a thousand feet to
your death without a parachute
is a clever way
of getting out of a fix?
You're all just makin' up
stuff that he's saying, right?
The important thing is
we're all okay.
Rocket?
Yeah, he's here.
And he's okay.
Rocket, we love you very much,
and we're happy you're alive.
Well, that makes you
the idiots then.
He is r/jght about that.
Back in your cages!
Nebula?
Nebula, come in!
So, you'd like to joust,
would you?
Go to hell,
you sick son of a bitch.
You killed all of those people.
As I will your friends.
I'm sending you the coordinates.
They will die
unless you bring me
what is mine!
Screw you, you stretch-faced,
RoboCop-looking,
Skeletor wannabe,
purple-nurple piece of...
He hung Up-
You think?
1966.
The Soviet put me on a rocket,
knowing full well I'm never
to return and I will die
in a fiery ball of death.
But one thing
even mudak Soviets never do
is call me bad dog.
Oh, my God!
Could you just let it go?
Kraglin, please,
just take it back.
This is killing us.
I can't take it back
if she is, in fact,
a bad dog.
Kraglin!
Oh, it never stops hurting.
Krag/in.
Oh, hey, Pete.
We need to save
Nebula, Mantis, and Drax,
and we need your help.
Me?
You're the one who lost it,
you twit.
The Hellspawn had it,
sire, but...
But, but, but! But!
That rancid word.
I'm merely wondering
whether it might be wiser
to go directly to the new colony
and not engage
in unnecessary conflict.
They can rewire a carbenetrix
core in under two minutes,
but what is that, Vim?
Rote memorization.
Rote memorization!
In hundreds of years
of our creations,
only one has known
true invention.
One.
Putrid in every other way,
but 89P13 had that.
Yes, sire.
A populace unable to think
what hasn't yet been thought
will die on the vine.
We need 89P13's brain,
so we can transfer that trait
into these creatures
before we go to the new colony.
Nothing else matters.
How did they get down here?
Joob joob.
Peter will be trying
to get to the spaceport.
He doesn't know
about the children.
You!
We need you to let all the
other children on board know
to stay away
from the starboard walls.
Joob joob?
They know three frickin' words
and two of them are "jbob."
- J00bj00b.
- No! Listen to me!
You need to talk
to the other children,
all of them here, and tell them
to stay away
from the freaking...
What the hell
are you doing, Mantis?
Explaining it, dickhead!
Joob joob e0!
You're scaring them.
Hello, dumb idiots.
I had a little girl like you.
You know what she used to like?
She liked when
I made monkey noises.
Beep.
Beep, beep. Beep-
How is that a monkey?
Beats me.
Boop.
E0, e0. Joobjoob.
- Joob joob.
- DRAX". Yeah.
Joobjoob.
Yeah. Joobjoob.
They're gonna tell
the other kids
to stay away
from the starboard wall.
Why didn't you tell us
you knew their language
this whole time?
Why didn't you ask?
This could be futile,
Quill. He's too powerful.
Well, then I guess
we'll die trying.
What is "dying trying"
gonna accomplish?
Or we can just give him
the badger?
Our thing is dying trying-
I am Groot.
I know who you are already!
Feel free to stay behind
in the cargo area.
I'm not leaving my sister
with that jackass.
This you?
Fell out of your bag.
Let's do this.
Well, you didn't wake up
This morning
'Cause you didn't go to bed
You were watching the whites
Of your eyes turn red
The calendar on your wall
Wait.
Reading some old letters
You smile...
You almost
have to admire their pluck.
Sire.
Across the clear blue sky
Howdy there, you freakin' creep.
Your life will surely change
- Back up!
- Yes, sire.
When things fall into place
You're on, Steemie.
First barrel.
This is the day
Your life will surely change
Second barrel.
Third barrel.
Fourth barrel.
When things fall into place
This is the day
Hard starboard.
Your life will surely change
And fire!
This is the day
They've breached the spaceport.
One of them holds subject 89P13.
Release the Hellspawn.
All of them.
Sire, the Hellspawn were created
solely to defend the new colony
Do it now!
Get me 89P13,
and kill everyone
in the head of that dead god.
Spaceport wide open, Cap'n,
but that old missile's
all we had.
Rocket, Groot, go, go!
Get inside that spaceport.
What the hell?
Aw, come on!
Kraglin,
we have been infiltrated.
Open the pit.
Sire, our bargaining power
will be gone.
Abilisks!
Good God!
This way!
(Mews) {CREATURE SQUEALS)
One more step
and this weird thing gets it!
Don't be rash.
What were you programming?
A self-destruction code.
What are you doing?
It's okay.
Mantis, stop!
They eat batteries,
not people.
Maybe they're just scared of
what we are gonna do to them.
We're not gonna hurt you.
Everything is going to be okay.
Use your heart, boy.
A dog!
Yeah.
She's a good dog.
I knew you believe
I am good dog.
All right, all right,
get off me, you idiot!
Sire, we must retreat.
The ship is going down.
The spaceport has intruders.
Go! See if one of them
is 89P13.
Sire, you have an irrational
obsession with this animal.
You must stop, for God's sake!
There is no God!
That's why I stepped in!
Controller, I am taking
command of the Aréte.
Disengage all damaged sectors
of the ship,
and retreat.
Attention,
all personnel.
Intruders have boarded the ship.
Head to the starboard spaceport.
Get me 89P13,
and kill the rest.
No sleep till
We go in there, we get Mantis,
Nebula, and Drax.
We move in, we get 'em,
and we get out.
Whoo!
Did that look cool?
Okay, new game plan.
We get the hell out of here now.
There are thousands
of creatures on the ship.
Many of them are children.
And we need to be good joobjoob.
- Huh?
- It means friends.
If we wanna live,
we have to leave now.
This whole rig is gonna
go down any second.
They will all die
if we don't help them.
I'm done runnin'.
Foot on the pedal
Never ever false metal
Engine running hotter
Than a boiling kettle
My job a/n '1' a job
ltis a damn good time
City to city
I'm running my rhymes
On location
Touring around the nation
Beastie Boys Always on vacation
Ain't no faking
Your money I'm taking
Going coast to coast
Watch all the girlies shaking
While you're at the job
Working nine-to-five
The Beastie Boys at the Garden
Cold kicking it live
No sleep till
Another plane, another train
Another bottle in the brain
Another girl, another fight
Another drive all night
No sleep till Brooklyn
Born and bred in Brooklyn, USA
They call me Adam Yauch
But I'm MCA
Like a lemon to a lime
A lime to a lemon
I sip the def ale
With all the fly women
Limos, arenas, and TV shows
Autographed pictures
And classy hoes
Step off, Holmes
Get out of my way!
Taxing little girlies
From here to LA
Waking up Before I get to sleep
'Cause I'll be rocking
This party eight days a week
No sleep till
No sleep till Brooklyn
Brooklyn
There's a big hole
up in the deck.
If we can connect that
to Knowhere,
we can lead
the survivors to safety.
Nebs and me will pilot the ship.
You guys save
all the higher life forms.
Hello, moron.
Come on!
Follow me, come on! Come on!
D0m0./
Come on!
Go, go, go!
Domo! Domo!
I am Groot!
Um, this way to, uh...
Thank you.
Yes, you're welcome.
I was screaming
at something scary behind you,
not you.
You look really cool.
Kill me if you want,
but then good luck
gettin' out of here.
- Wait!
- Let him go, Flecktick...
it's our only chance.
I got a space big enough
to get through.
I gotta find out
if I can change it
to a permeable shield.
I can't fly this frickin' thing,
the flight controls
are all screwed.
I'll do it.
Go help the others.
Wait, give me your comm.
Kraglin, I'll pilot
from this side.
Kragula,
back in action!
Come on, come on, come on!
Go, go!
Go, go, go!
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait!!
Stop, stop!
Are those kids?
Okay, Cosmo, stitch it up!
It needs to be airtight for
the kids to make it across.
Locking up, Kap/Ian.
Go, now, go!
One by one, one by one!
Okay.
Locking in and headed down.
This way. This way.
Why?
Why are you doing this?
I tried to kill you.
I am Groot.
He says,
"everyone deserves
a second chance."
You are so strong.
Why are you so slow? Hurry!
Where's Rocket?
Huh?
Domo. Domo.
You!
You thought you could escape me!
"No!
You think you have some worth
in and of yourself, without me?
No!
You are an abomination!
Nothing more than a step
on my path,
you freakish little monster!
How dare you think you are more,
89P13?
The name's Rocket.
Rocket Raccoon.
Hmm.
His face came off!
It's a mask.
Look what you did to me.
For what?
All I wanted to do
was to make things
perfect.
You didn't wanna
make things perfect.
You just hated things
the way they are.
Kill him.
Why?
Because I'm a freaking
Guardian of the Galaxy.
We have to get outta here now.
We have to save them.
We've got all the kids on board.
No, Pete.
The rest of them.
Come on!
Come on. Whoa!
Move!
Move it, bird!
- Whoa!
- Come on!
Come on!
Come on, come on, come on!
Thought we were
limiting ourselves
to the higher life forms?
Yeah, well, me too.
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Go, babies.
Go!
I cannot hold much...
Run!
GO! Go!
Quill! Hurry!
Peter!
Did that
look
cool?
Come on.
Cosmo! I'm okay.
I am Groot.
Thanks. Just tell them
I'm gonna be right...
I am Groot.
Yeah. It was good
working with you, too.
Hey, Gamma.
Are you ready'?
Yeah.
You know, I'm still not
who you want me to be.
I know.
But who you are ain't so bad.
I bet we were fun.
Like you wouldn't believe.
Okay.
You Okay?
I think I need to talk
to everybody.
So, you're gonna leave?
My mother died in front of me
when I was eight years old,
and I have been running
ever since.
I'm gonna need
to take some time...
and learn how to swim.
I as well.
I love you all. I do.
But my whole life
I did whatever Ego wanted,
and then, I did
whatever the Guardians wanted.
I need to go out
and discover what I want.
- |'|| come with you.
- No, Drax.
That's the whole point.
But you need someone
to protect you.
- I don't.
- Not in a bad way.
Just because of
your incredible weakness.
Oh, my gosh,
you're so frustrating!
Drax.
I need you here.
We're building a new society.
I need all the support I can get
for those children out there.
Today, I saw who you are.
You weren't born
to be a destroyer.
You were born to be a dad.
So, youW|ead the Guardians then?
No.
I'm gonna lead the city,
make it the type of home
lneverhad.
So, that's it?
The group's over?
No.
Well, the Galaxy
still needs its Guardians.
And you will make a better
leader than I ever was,
Cap'n.
I love you, guys-
For you.
Like a train on a track
Coming towards her
Stuck still, no turning back
She hid around corners
And she hid under beds
She killed it with kisses
And from it she fled
With every bubble
She sank with a drink
And washed it away down
The kitchen sink
The dog days are over
Hmm.
The horses are coming
So you better run
Run fast for your mother
Run fast for your father
Run for your children
For your sisters and brothers
And your longing behind
You can't carry it with you
If you want to survive
The dog days are over
Can you hear the horses
Yeah!
Oh, yeah!
The dog days are over
Welcome home.
The dog days are done
The horses are coming
So you better run
The dog days are over
The horses are coming
And I never wanted
Anything from you
Except everything...
I think I might be
at the wrong, uh...
I'm looking for Jason Quill.
Uh, yes.
Come in.
Happiness hit her
Like a bullet
In the back
Struck from a great height
Pete?
By someone who should know
Pete.
Hi, Grandpa.
Can you hear the horses?
'Cause here they come
Run fast for your father
For your sisters and brothers
Leave all your love
And your longing behind
Yes! Yes!
Yeah! Yeah!
The dog days are over
Yeah!
(Museums)
How young are you?
How old am I?
Let's count the rings
Around my eye
How smart are you?
How dumb am I?
Don't count any of my advice
Oh, meet me anyplace
Or anywhere or anytime
Now, I don't care
Meet me tonight
If you will dare, I might dare
Call me on Thursday
If you will...
Okay, how about
your favorite musical act?
Phyla, you first.
Urn... Britney Spears and Korn.
Good choices.
I gotta go with the man.
Garth Brooks.
The Carpenters do not
have a single bad song.
Adrian Belew.
Both solo and his work
with King Crimson.
What about you, Captain?
Uh, this one's kind of special.
Guess they're here.
Well, I can handle this
by my lonesome
if y'all wanna chill.
Nah, nah.
It'll go faster
if we all do it together.
Grout, wake up.
Nothin' the matter
With your head
Baby, find it
Come on and find it
Do you ever feel
a little sad for them?
Yeah, sure.
But these townsfolk
can't protect themselves.
COSMO". On your word, Kapitan.
Come and get your love
Word.
-Hail
What's the matter
With you feel right
Don't you feel right, baby
Hail, oh yeah
Get it from the main vine
All right
I said-a find it, find it
Go on and love it
If you like it, yeah
-Hail
It's your business
If you want some, take some
Get it together, baby
Come and get your love
Come and get your love, now
La, Ia, Ia, Ia, Ia
Come and get your love
La, Ia, Ia, Ia, woohoo
La, Ia, Ia, Ia, Ia
Come and get your love
La, na, na, na, na, na, da
Da, da, boom
Come and get your love
La, da boom, boom, boom, boom
Ta, daba, boom, boom
Come and get your love
La, Ia, Ia, Ia, Ia
La, Ia, Ia, Ia, woohoo
Come and get your love
La, Ia, Ia, Ia, Ia
La, Ia, Ia, Ia, woohoo
Come and get your love
La, Ia, Ia, Ia, Ia
La, da boom, boom, Ia, ta
Da boom, Ia, da boom
Come and get your love
La, da boom, boom, boom
Ta, daba, boom
Come and get your love
La, do boom
La, ta, da boom, boom, boom
Come and get your love
La, da boom, boom, boom
Ta, daba, boom, Ia, da boom
Come and get your love
Lights out tonight
Trouble in the heartland
Got a head-on collision
Smashin' in my guts, man
I'm caught in a crossfire
That I don't understand
But there's one thing
I know for sure, girl
I don't give a damn for
The same old played-out scenes
Baby, I don't give a damn
For just the in-betweens
Honey, I want the heart
I want the soul
I want control right now
You better listen to me, baby
Talk about a dream
Try to make it real
You wake up in the night
With a fear so real
You spend your life waiting
For a moment
That just don't come
Well, don't waste
Your time waiting
Badlands, you gotta
Live it every day
Let the broken hearts stand
As the price you've gotta pay
We'll keep pushin'
Till it's understood
And these badlands
Start treating us good
Workin' in the fields
Till you get your back burned
Workin' 'neath the wheel till
You get your facts learned
Baby, I got my facts
Learned real good right now
You better get it straight
Darling
Poor man wanna be rich
Rich man wanna be king
And a king ain't satisfied
Tiii he rules everything
I wanna go out tonight
I wanna find out what I got!
Well I believe in the love
That you gave me
I believe in the faith
That could save me
I believe in the hope
And I pray that some day
It may raise me above these
Badlands, you gotta
Live it every day
Let the broken hearts stand
As the price you've gotta pay
We'll keep pushin'
Till it's understood
And these badlands
Start treating us good
Whoa whoa whoa whoa
(sun AR sou»
Hmm, hm-hm-hm
Hmm, hm-hm-hm-hm
For the ones who had a notion
A notion deep inside
That it ain't no sin
To be glad you're alive
I wanna find one face
That ain't looking through me
I wanna find one place
I wanna spit
In the face of these
Badlands, you gotta
Live it every day
Let the broken hearts stand
As the price you've gotta pay
Keep movin' Till it's understood
And these badlands
Start treating us good
Whoa whoa whoa whoa
Badlands, whoa whoa whoa whoa
I mean, if she needs help
mowing her lawn, I'll do it,
but I kinda feel like
her son should help.
He's gonna sit on the porch
and watch me do it.
Like, he's a 45-year-old man,
able-bodied,
and I'm mowing his lawn.
- It just feels weird.
- Mm-hmm.
Don't get me started.
- Oh, really?
- Mm-hmm.
Now I kind of want to know.