[soft instrumental music plays]
[thunder crashes]
[rousing music plays]
[music fades out]
-[phone beeping]
-[soft thunder rumbles]
[man groans]
[gunshot]
[woman] There's a group of men
called The Firm.
[door rattling]
They've been running things
for a long, long time.
And when they need someone
to clean up their mess...
-[insistent banging at door]
-...they send me.
[ominous music]
[banging continues]
[stroke of a gong]
[rousing music plays]
[music fades out]
[woman on TV] Go get your helmet.
Let's go to the store.
-[character squeaks in protest]
-You look so cute, Nit.
[voices argue on TV]
[phone rings]
[Sam sighs]
-[man on speakerphone] Sam.
-Nathan.
-[Nathan] Where are you?
-At home. Sewing.
Meet me at the diner.
Why?
How much trouble am I in?
["You'll Never Know"
by Bobby Darin plays]
[service bell dings]
[song continues
over diner sound system]
An extra scoop
for my favourite client.
Thanks, Rose.
[ominous musical sting]
["Half a Photograph" by
Kay Starr plays in background]
I put in an extra scoop
for my favourite client.
-Thanks, Rose,
-I'm sure she won't be long.
You clearly don't know
my mother very well.
-[thunder rumbles]
-[slow suspenseful music]
Hey, stranger.
-Can I lighten your load?
-Not carrying today, Rose.
There's a first time
for everything. She's over there.
Thanks for keeping an eye
on her.
[rousing instrumental music]
-[music fades out]
-You said you'd be here in 30 minutes.
I'm a few minutes late.
Three hours.
You're bleeding.
[thunder rumbles]
Just another day at the office.
Did you bring it?
[Sam sighs]
Anna May sure can pick them.
-It's loaded.
-Good girl.
Listen, I, um...
have to disappear for a while.
-Then I'm coming with you.
-You can't. Not this time.
Nathan will be here soon.
He'll take care of you when I'm gone.
-I don't want to go with Nathan.
-I'm doing this for your own good.
I'll stay in the library
with Anna May and the others.
It's too dangerous.
What's going on?
[emotional music]
It's... it's complicated.
Tell me.
I'm not a kid any more.
No, you're not.
You haven't
touched your milkshake.
Didn't want to drink it
without you.
[climactic music]
[music fades out]
How long will you be gone?
I have to make
a quick phone call.
Stay here.
-[door crashes open]
-[suspenseful music]
[Rose] Evening, gentlemen.
Can I lighten your load?
-Get lost.
-Hey.
[suspenseful music plays]
[ominous music plays]
[in Russian accent]
Hello, little girl.
Mommy says I'm not allowed
to talk to strangers.
This "Mommy"
looks a lot like you.
Only bigger and more stabby.
Got my father's blood
all over her.
I don't like you.
[gasps mockingly]
Enough games.
Where is she?
[in Russian] Go kiss a pig.
[music intensifies]
[in English]
Tell me where she is.
[suspenseful music intensifies]
-[gun cocks]
-Close your eyes, baby girl.
-[gunshots]
-[glass smashing]
-[gunshots continue]
-[panicked grunts and shouts]
-[man exclaims in Russian]
-[gunshots continue]
[high-pitched ringing]
-[hurried steps]
-[door slams]
["Something On Your Mind"
by Karen Dalton plays]
Mom!
♪ Yesterday ♪
♪ Any way you made it
was just fine ♪
♪ So you turn your days
into nighttime ♪
♪ Didn't you know ♪
♪ You can't make it
Without ever even trying ♪
♪ And something's on your mind
Isn't it? ♪
♪ Let these times-- ♪
[music crescendos and fades]
[quiet music playing in diner]
Evening, darling.
-Can I lighten your load?
-I'm clean.
Regular clean or diner clean?
[chuckles ironically]
[sighs]
-Forgot about this one.
-Of course, sugar.
-Yeah.
[distant thunder rumbles]
[Nathan whispers] Boy.
Oh, these girls
are worse than the Stasi.
[sighs] You hurt?
Just another day at the office.
Wow, you sound
just like your mother.
I don't have a mother.
Well, you sure have her temper.
What the hell happened tonight?
Bad intel.
You said four or five idiots
with peashooters.
Yes. And?
[discordant tone]
[diner bell dings]
Oh, for Christ's sake, child.
This was supposed to be low-profile,
not a bloody massacre.
Next time,
I'll just let them shoot me.
just do what you're told.
Remember who you're working for.
As long as they're happy...
You called me here oh-so-urgently
just to remind me of that?
No.
Your talents are needed, pronto.
Somebody stole from us.
Who's crazy enough
to steal from The Firm?
Somebody who doesn't know
who we really are.
An accountant. From the
clean side of the business.
How much did he take?
Enough to earn
a visit from you.
We need that money back.
[whispers] Good girl.
I'll text you the address later.
Oh, and get rid of those
stone-age firearms you carry.
-I've had them for years.
-Find an open vendor.
And get yourself
some clean boomsticks.
We can't have you linked to that
war zone you left behind, can we?
[thunder rumbles]
[soft suspenseful music plays]
[man] Did you know about this little
endeavour my son had on the side?
[nephew] Sorry, Uncle.
I had no idea.
[exasperated sigh]
[grunts, exhales]
Where's the shoe?
What shoe?
The shoe that is not currently
covering my son's left foot.
The one that looks like
the right one.
That fucking shoe.
-I don't know.
-Well, find it.
[sidekick]
Found it, Mr. McAlester.
Nobody tells his mother
about this.
We'll tell her
he ran off with some girl.
I get it.
Now, bring me the heads
of the men who killed my boy.
-[music fades out]
-[church bells chiming]
[sighs]
[door slams heavily]
[church bells continue]
[librarian] Hmm.
[quiet chuckle]
[inhales deeply]
[sharp exhale]
Hello, dear.
What can I do for you?
I need to exchange
some... books.
Well, that's nice.
Not a lot of people your age
read nowadays.
-Do you have a card with us?
-No.
I'd like to open one.
Wonderful.
What kind of... books
are you interested in?
Mostly smaller ones.
A few heavies.
Well, you won't find them there.
Those are our
children's sections.
The Enchanted Forest...
and The Never-Ending Ocean.
They sound like fun.
[soft music plays]
Have we met before?
You seem so... familiar.
I'm embarrassed to say it's been
a while since I visited a library.
[quietly] Well, that's no way
to live, dear.
Let's get you into a good book.
Come.
[keys jangle]
[suspenseful music]
[key turns in lock]
[door creaks]
[music plays quietly
in background]
Anna May, this lovely young lady
wants to open an account with us.
Well,
Madeleine should have told you
that we don't accept new readers
without a reference.
Madeleine had a hunch.
Fudge your hunches,
if you pardon my French.
-Technically not French.
-Always literal.
-Yes, I'm literary. I'm a librarian.
-Be that as it may.
-Florence, dear.
-[music stops]
Would you join us?
[footsteps approach]
I'm afraid
we need a tie-breaker.
Madeleine thinks this girl
needs to do some reading.
I told you I had a hunch.
There's something
very familiar about her.
Hunch, smunch.
I, on the other hand, think
we should dispose of the body
and then have a long talk
about our onboarding protocols.
You know I can hear you, right?
Hush, girl.
Don't be rude.
Turn around, hon.
[annoyed sigh]
And take off your hat.
What did you say your name was?
She didn't.
[Florence] Hmm. That's odd.
[Anna May] Well, girl?
Cat got your tongue? Speak up.
It's Sam.
[soft dramatic music]
Scarlet's kid.
[Sam] Yeah.
I knew it.
Never forget those eyes.
We haven't seen you
since you were yea high.
How is your mother?
[Sam] Haven't seen her
in 15 years.
[Anna May sighs]
Well, that's something
we both have in common.
[Madeleine] My, my, my.
Little Sam.
We hear about you all the time.
You've made
quite a reputation for yourself.
Come here.
Give Auntie Madeleine a hug.
Why come back now?
I needed clean guns...
and I guess I needed an excuse.
[music stops]
[impressed whistle]
Nice collection.
And you take good care of them.
Let me guess.
You're the sentimental type.
Ro-man-tique.
Sentimental types
don't last long doing this.
So, no. I don't think
I'm the sentimental type.
Tommy Tomahawk.
I looked everywhere for him.
Yeah, sorry about that.
So...
you're an idealist.
Nope.
Maybe I don't have a type.
Everybody has a type.
-Everybody.
-Mm-hmm.
Maybe I'm the professional type?
Ah. Old school.
"No women, no children" type.
Women are fair game.
Gender equality.
Very progressive.
She's a feminist.
Fine.
You get to live.
We'll make these disappear
and get you into
some new, clean books.
[rousing music]
You'll need a Jane Austen.
[thuds]
A Charlotte Brontë.
And a Virginia Woolf.
[Madeleine] Oh,
and an Agatha Christie.
-For reading.
-[phone rings]
[dramatic music]
[up-tempo instrumental music]
[music fades out]
[door creaks quietly]
-[cookware clinking]
-[footsteps]
[water running]
[cheerful ringtone plays]
[suspenseful music]
[ringtone continues]
Please.
-[cheerful ringtone plays]
-I need to answer this.
[Sam] You need to walk away and
thank God I'm not in a killing mood.
[cheerful ringtone plays]
I got no choice.
-[man] No!
-[Sam] Enough!
[gunshot]
[Sam gasps]
-[cheerful ringtone plays]
-[grunting]
[exhales sharply]
[pained grunting]
[cheerful ringtone plays]
[ominous music]
[man on speaker]
Playing hard to get?
Not very smart, moron.
Not unless you want me to send
your little princess back in pieces.
You have exactly 60 minutes
to bring the money
to the Gutterball bowling alley.
A minute late,
and she'll be celebrating
her ninth birthday
with the worms.
60 minutes.
Please.
[man] It's my daughter.
[distorted]
♪ Yesterday ♪
♪ Any way you made it
was just fine ♪
[dramatic musical sting]
Fuck me.
[tense music]
[man grunting in pain]
[gust of wind blows]
[emotional music plays]
[elevator dings]
[music fades out]
["Try to Remember"
by Matt Monro plays]
♪ Try to remember ♪
♪ The kind of September ♪
[nurse] I'll get the doctor.
Guns go in the cookie jar.
-[ominous music]
-[man grunts]
-Hey. Haven't seen you in a while.
-Hmm.
And you brought a new friend.
-What the hell happened?
-I happened.
Just fix him.
I need him on his feet
in ten minutes.
-[man moans]
-[doctor] Ooh.
He's not going anywhere.
Not in ten minutes.
Maybe not ever.
-So what can we do?
-"We"?
Well, you can start
by not shooting people.
[man whispers]
Please. My Emily.
-There's no time.
-[doctor] Shh.
Just relax. Take it in deep.
Is that laughing gas?
Well, duh.
Just patch him up.
I'll be back soon.
He'd better be functional.
She's quite annoying,
isn't she?
[rousing music plays]
[laughs] Who am I talking to?
The guy that she shot
in the stomach?
-[music intensifies]
-[inhales deeply]
-[tires screech]
-[motor revving]
[car horn honking]
-[Nathan] Is it done?
-There's a change of plan.
What are you talking about?
What does that mean?
They kidnapped his little girl.
That's why he stole the money.
If I'm not at the Gutterball
in 15 minutes, they'll kill her.
Sam, you're not thinking straight.
Just bring the money back, now!
I just need half an hour. I'll
release her and bring the money.
Okay. Listen to me, Sam.
If you screw this one up,
they will give the kill order.
And I won't be able
to stop them.
She's just a little girl.
I can't leave her to die.
-I'm sorry.
-Don't you dare hang up on me.
-Don't you--
Fuck.
[sighs]
[exhales deeply]
[clears throat]
[soft dramatic music]
Go to the Gutterball.
Try to reason with her.
Bring back the money.
Wait.
Now, when I say,
"Reason with her,"
I mean no guns, no knives.
She comes back alive.
-Understood?
-[together] Yeah.
And for God's sake...
be careful.
Remember
who you're dealing with.
What are you waiting for? Go.
[tense music plays]
[whispers] One of the men Sam
killed was Jim McAlester's son.
[low] Are you sure
it was McAlester's kid?
[whispers] Yes.
The board is on its way.
Goddamn it, Sam.
[soft eerie music]
[cheerful ringtone plays]
[man] Who the fuck are you?
[Sam] Just someone
who has your money.
I want the girl.
[man] Where's Daddy?
He...
had an accident.
He sent me.
Do you want your money or not?
[ominous music]
[cheerful ringtone plays]
[man] The girl
got to this point alive.
But if you as much as sneeze
without my permission,
that could be easily rectified.
-Got it.
-Good.
Now, see the locker behind you?
[electronic buzzing]
Weapon and phone
go in the locker,
along with the clothes
you're wearing.
Slam the door shut,
and it'll lock.
Go to the Westfield Mall
across the street.
You, the suitcase,
the new clothes
and the little girl's phone.
Seriously?
Ten minutes.
[dramatic music intensifies]
Hello, Sam.
-[Sam sighs]
-[cheerful whistling plays]
[Sam] Bonehead.
-Hey, Sam.
-Sam.
[Sam laughs]
Boneheads.
-I really don't have time for this.
-Nathan's worried about you.
Doesn't want you to do
anything stupid.
So why don't you hand over
the suitcase,
and nobody gets hurt.
Counter-offer: Go back to Nathan, tell
him you tried, but I roughed you up.
[inhales sharply] Ooh.
You can beat each other up
for added realism.
-That's funny.
-[Sam] What?
No guns today?
Nathan doesn't want you hurt.
Not too badly, anyway.
Oh, that is so sweet.
I'll try not to kill you, too.
[rousing rock music plays]
[whistling mariachi music plays]
[neck cracking]
[electrical buzzing]
-[mariachi music continues]
-♪ We can fight ♪
♪ Fight, fight ♪
♪ Fight, fight, fight ♪
-[yelling]
-[blows]
[grunting]
[Dracula] Who the fuck is she?
♪ We can fight ♪
[music intensifies]
[grunting and yelling continues]
-[metallic blow]
-[shouting]
[laughs]
[man screams]
[music softens]
[musical intensifies]
-[blows]
-[grunting]
[taser buzzes]
-[bones crack]
-[thug screams]
-[loud crack]
-[man screams]
♪ We can fight ♪
[intense music continues]
-[music stops]
-[high-pitched ringing]
[music resumes]
♪ We can fight ♪
[music fades out]
[Sam panting]
[cheerful ringtone plays]
[breathes heavily]
[Dracula] Ground floor.
Video Beast.
[echoing silence]
[door creaking]
[door slams shut]
[suspenseful music]
Cutting it close.
I had a few hiccups.
We saw what you did with those hiccups.
How do we know you're not a cop?
Can a cop do what I just did?
I just want the girl.
Then we'll get along just fine.
There's a shopping cart
behind you.
Put the suitcase inside.
[Dracula] Push the shopping
cart towards us,
and we'll push the girl cart
towards you.
One.
[suspenseful music]
[Dracula] Two.
Three.
[soft, dreamy music]
-[suspenseful music]
-[men cackling]
It's okay. You're safe.
-[Emily whimpers]
-I'll be right back.
-[fast-paced music]
-[Emily screams]
[Dracula] We're all stinking rich,
you magnificent bastards.
[Frankenstein]
Stop the fucking car.
[Wolfman] Holy fuck!
-[tires screech]
-[smashing]
[explosion]
-[distant screaming]
-[glass smashing]
[cheerful music]
[screams]
[gunshots]
[Dracula] You greedy traitor!
[screams, grunts]
[rapid gunfire]
[gun clicks]
[music fades out]
No... no!
No, no, no!
[screaming]
[sighs]
[whispers] Fuck.
[paper rustles]
-[gunshot]
-[dramatic music resumes]
[gun clicking]
[gun clicks]
[strangled scream]
[music fades]
Anything broken?
-Are you bleeding?
-No.
Bleeding on the inside?
How can you tell?
It's inside.
You're probably fine. Let's go.
Try to keep up.
-[slow cheerful music]
-[thugs giggling]
[thugs snorting]
I see you morons
have found my stash.
[thug] This is some
good shit, Doc.
You should be very proud
of yourself.
This is not a toy.
It's for medicinal use only.
[quiet giggling]
So...
who fucked you up like this?
[inhales sharply, snorts]
-A girl.
-[thugs laugh hysterically]
A girl made you look like
you're from The Walking Dead?
I've never felt
pain like this before, Doc.
[leader] She got us good,
Doc. I...
I don't think
I'll ever walk again.
There must be an epidemic,
because I got a guy in the next
room who's got similar symptoms.
What do you mean?
I mean...
a girl fucked him up, too.
[cheerful music plays]
Keep talking, Doc.
-[Sam sighs]
-You're bleeding.
It's just a scratch.
It can get infected.
Worms will get in there and lay eggs.
Then they'll have to cut your arm off.
That's what they teach
in school these days?
Discovery Channel.
Thank God we're going straight
to the hospital.
Is my daddy there?
[emotional music]
Yeah.
Is that why he didn't come?
Is he sick?
He...
[Emily] It's okay.
You don't have to lie for him.
He never comes
when he says he will.
Here, just let me help you.
[seatbelt clicks]
Thank you.
Sure.
Are you sure it's her?
[leader] Yeah. She dropped off
some guy she shot.
Said she's going to come back
and pick him up later.
-[thugs laugh]
-And the money?
-She had it last time we saw her.
-[laughing]
Then get it back.
She's still getting
the VIP treatment?
[ominous music]
-Do whatever it takes.
-Alright, alright, alright.
Now that's what I call
a work benefit.
[elevator dings]
[Sam] Just, uh,
stay behind me, okay?
[ominous music]
Come on.
[gasps]
[slow delicate music]
[emotional music]
[sobs]
I'll get the doctor.
She's here.
Shot in the shoulder.
Maybe you should
take your break now.
So. My payment?
-Oh! [sharp inhale]
-Shh.
Transferred to your account.
Now...
What's the plan, Doc?
[hysterical laughter]
[together] Oh.
Once I stick her with this, she'll
start losing control of her arms.
[snickering]
After 60 seconds or so...
she's a sitting duck.
[suspenseful music]
-[door opens]
-[music intensifies]
What's wrong with you?
Let me do this right.
It's just a scratch.
Well, scratches get infected.
That's how you lose an arm.
Mm. Yeah, I heard.
[liquid sloshes]
What happened to him?
Someone shot him.
I hear that's pretty lethal.
Let's fix this.
Don't. I'm good.
Trust me, you'll need this.
[loudly] I said, I'm good.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean--
[medical gun clicks twice]
-You motherfu--
-[music crescendos]
-[Sam] Ah!
-60 seconds!
[doctor shouts] 60 seconds!
[breathes heavily]
[whispers] 60 seconds.
[through gritted teeth]
Oh, come on. Come on!
[breathes heavily]
Listen, I need your help.
Some bad men
are coming to hurt us.
Those who killed my dad?
I promise I'll explain, but
right now I need your help, okay?
-Okay.
-Good.
Grab the biggest knife.
Careful of the sharp end.
[metallic clink]
[whispers] Okay...
Now grab the tape.
Excellent. Tape it to my hand.
[whispers] 36...
[suspenseful music]
[whispers] 32...
Now tape the gun
to my other hand.
Careful. It's loaded.
[whispers] 15... 14...
[intense dramatic music]
Round two, bitch.
[thugs snickering outside]
Boneheads?
-Better get ready!
-[snickering]
Oh, thank God
it's just you three.
For a second there, I thought
it was someone dangerous.
The only reason you're still alive
is because Nathan wanted it that way.
[quietly] Now, take my finger
and put it on the trigger.
[leader] Well, it's over now.
I'm going
to tear you into little pieces.
And I'm going to love
every second of it.
Great. Hold that thought.
[Sam] I'll be right out.
[leader chuckling]
[rousing music]
You're being very brave, Emily.
I need you to do
one last thing for me,
and then go and hide, okay?
Okay.
[intense music escalates]
[cheerful mariachi music plays]
[men grunting]
[Sam grunts]
-[mariachi music continues]
-[cackles]
[grunts]
[screaming]
[gunshots]
[Sam gasps]
[gunshots continue]
[both growling]
[grunts with exertion]
-[Sam yells]
-[flesh tearing]
-[Sam grunting]
-[leader screams]
[roar]
[mariachi music continues]
[grunts]
[man screams and whimpers]
[Sam grunts]
[screams]
[flesh tearing]
-[vigorous roar]
-[Sam grunts]
[leader shouts]
[shotgun clicking]
[mariachi music intensifies]
[Sam grunts]
[shotgun clicks]
Hey, Bonehead.
[laughs]
-[resonant crash]
-[music stops abruptly]
-[Sam pants]
-[phone rings]
[grunts]
[groans]
[phone rings]
[panting continues]
Emily.
I need you
to come grab the phone.
[quiet ominous music]
[phone rings]
Come on. [pants]
It's okay. Just pick it up.
[phone rings]
[breathing heavily]
You are a goddamn rock star.
Put it on speaker.
[Nathan] Someone
better start talking.
That was a...
jerk move, sending
the Three Stooges after me.
You left us no choice, Sam.
There's always a choice.
[Nathan] Oh, well, then,
we can still figure this out.
Just bring the money back.
[Sam] It's gone. The suitcase
was blown to 1000 pieces.
[exhales incredulously]
Oh.
That's really unfortunate.
So now what?
[Nathan] Oh, you know
the drill, Sam.
You're no longer
under our protection.
[Nathan] In your little massacre
earlier tonight,
you killed the wrong people.
Including Jim McAlester's son.
But I was sent by you.
By The Firm.
It doesn't matter.
[tense emotional music plays]
This is business, Sam.
And you landed on the wrong side
of the balance sheet.
So...
It needs to be rectified.
How's this for business?
If I get out of this alive,
I'm coming for you.
All of you.
I would expect no less.
Goodbye, Sam.
[sniffs]
[tense emotional music fades]
[zippers closing]
[phone rings]
-[McAlester] Yes?
-Mr. McAlester, this is Nathan.
I'm the head of the HR department
here at The Firm.
What do you want?
To prevent an all-out war
between our two fine organizations,
we would like to offer you
the woman responsible for your loss.
So you had nothing
to do with this?
I can assure you, this is not how
The Firm conducts its business, sir.
It was an unsolicited action
by a very troubled individual.
Now, I'm sending you
her last location.
I hope
this is satisfactory, sir.
[McAlester] For now.
[phone beeps off]
Take everybody.
Don't come back
until it's done.
-[sighs]
-[soft dramatic music]
[clears throat]
[cocks gun]
[phone rings]
[soft dramatic music]
-It's a text message from Nathan.
-What's it say?
"I'm sorry, child.
I can no longer protect you."
"I left you a package to help
you survive the next few days."
"Take it, and disappear."
Then there's an address.
That's close by.
What if it's a trap?
[elevator dings]
[suspenseful music]
Can you press the button?
We're parked on minus two.
[elevator creaks]
[music intensifies]
[music stops abruptly]
[doctor panting]
Just remember, you were spared
thanks to
an eight-year-old girl.
[Emily] Eight
and three quarters.
Sorry.
Eight and three quarters.
[elevator dings]
Are you a serial killer?
What?
[defensively] No... Where did
you learn that expression?
-History Channel.
-Well...
I am not a serial killer.
But... you kill people?
Yes.
So that makes you a killer.
And you've killed
more than one.
That is serial.
It's...
It's more
complicated than that.
Serial killers are, uh,
you know, mentally unstable.
They kill people
out of a compulsive urge.
So, why do you kill them?
For money?
Again, it's, uh...
It's complicated.
[sighs]
Look, I'm going to need
your help for a little longer.
Because your arms
are still paralyzed?
Yes. After that,
I'll get you to your mother.
She left a long time ago.
-To your grandparents, then.
-They're dead.
Uncles? Anything?
[soft music plays]
We'll figure it out, okay?
Okay.
So, here's
an unrelated question.
Do you know how to drive?
[Sam] Let's go over it
one more time. Left.
[Sam] Right.
Yes, I've got it already.
"D" is for drive.
"R" is for reverse.
And you get to do the easy part,
stepping on the gas and brakes.
Don't be a smart-ass.
Turn the key.
[engine revs]
Put it in drive.
Let's go.
[suspenseful music]
That's it. Straighten up.
[laughs] I'm driving.
Yes, you are.
[tires screeching]
[engines revving]
-Don't worry about the bullets.
-[guns cocking]
Reverse. Now.
-[engine revs]
-Hard left!
-Put it in drive.
-Yeah.
[tires screeching]
-[Emily panting]
-That's it.
-Hard left.
-[tires screech]
-Go, go, go.
-[smashing]
[rapid gunfire]
[man] Damn it!
[Sam] Get ready. Hard left.
And another hard left.
[tires screech]
-[screeching of tires]
-Shh.
[ominous music]
[whispers] Okay.
Put it in reverse.
-Hard right!
-[engine revving]
[Sam] Put it in drive.
Hard left.
Put it in reverse.
[panting]
-[tense music plays]
-Okay, kill the lights!
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music continues]
[whispers] Okay, be quiet.
Duck down.
That's it. Get down.
[horn honks]
[men shouting]
[Sam whispers] Okay.
Put it in drive...
and close your eyes.
[rapid gunfire]
[both grunting]
Keep her straight.
[smashing]
Keep it straight.
[screaming]
[grunts]
Are your eyes still closed?
-Yes.
-Good girl.
Put it in reverse.
[Emily breathes shallowly]
[gasps]
[engine revving]
[grunts]
[car clanks and rattles]
-[engine revs]
-[tires screech]
[Emily] Can I turn on
the radio?
Go nuts.
["French Disko"
by Stereolab plays]
♪ Though this world's
essentially ♪
♪ An absurd place
to be living in ♪
♪ It doesn't call for
bubble withdrawal ♪
♪ I've been told
it's a fact of life ♪
[music fades out]
[song resumes on radio]
♪ Though this world's
essentially ♪
♪ An absurd place
to be living in ♪
♪ It doesn't call for
bubble withdrawal ♪
[phone rings]
[song ends abruptly]
[suspenseful music plays]
[Sam whispering]
Emily, doorbell.
[doorbell rings]
[music intensifies]
[music stops abruptly]
[woman] Didn't I teach you
to always guard your back?
[gasps]
[tremulously] Hi, Mom.
[whispers] Hi.
[soft emotional music]
[whispers] Is this, um...
Am I a grandmother?
God, no.
[sharp exhale]
Hi. I'm Emily.
-I'm her apprentice.
-What?
Emily.
Come.
[sighs, sniffs]
[on TV] ...the additional
burden of needing to care
for her
twelve-month-old daughter.
It will be at least a year...
[electrical zapping]
That is a hell of a story.
Mm. Hell of a night.
Um...
Try wiggling your fingers.
-Feeling should come back in no time.
-Yeah, it's already working.
Excellent.
You look really good.
Are you eating well?
Cut the crap, Ma.
Where have you been
for the last 15 years?
Around.
Watching you.
Making sure you're safe.
Great parenting.
Glad to see you taking
an interest in my career.
-I never wanted this life for you.
-How's that working out for you?
I wanted to stay with you
and your aunts, but I couldn't.
Why not?
Because I fucked up.
[quietly] I fucked up.
I was young when I had you.
[soft emotional music]
We left London, followed your
father here. When he died--
When he was murdered.
When he was murdered,
you were a baby. I had nothing.
No money, nowhere to go.
I knew Anna May
from your dad's work.
She and the other aunts
took us in.
The best years of my life.
Me too.
Fast-forward twelve years,
and I find out who shot your dad.
The Russians?
The Russians from the diner?
Once I knew, I couldn't let him
walk around enjoying life...
knowing what he did to us.
But he was in bed with The Firm,
so there was a price to pay.
Once I killed him,
there was a mark on my back.
[soft emotional music]
[voice breaks]
I couldn't take you with me.
I couldn't risk your life.
So I made Nathan promise
to keep you safe.
I guess that's over.
There isn't a day that goes by
I don't regret pulling that trigger.
But back then,
I couldn't help myself.
I'm sorry.
[music fades out]
Does the kid know
about you and her dad?
[Sam] No.
But she's smart.
She'll figure it out.
What happens when she does?
-[inaudible TV chatter]
-[soft emotional music]
I think
there's a bad man outside.
We have to get out of here.
-So, what's the plan?
-Can you press the lobby button?
-What plan?
-Come on, you always have a plan.
A secret escape route?
A warehouse filled with guns?
I called us an Uber.
-Are you kidding me?
-No.
An Uber. What the hell
are you talking about?
I know you. You make plans.
And then you make plans
to make other plans.
-You're frothing at the mouth.
-[rousing music]
-It's unbecoming.
-[Sam scoffs]
[elevator dings]
[dramatic music]
[whimpers]
[screams] Get them!
[men clamouring]
[music intensifies]
[mockingly] Don't feel bad.
Could happen to anyone.
My hand is still paralyzed.
Yeah, course it is.
-It is.
-I know.
[elevator dings]
[tense music]
[Scarlet] Right.
After you, ladies.
[Scarlet] Come on. Hurry up.
-[Sam] Where does it go?
-Fucking Narnia.
Go. In.
-In!
-[scoffs] Fine.
-[Sam] No plan, huh?
-[Scarlet] Now is not the time.
Out of my way.
[echoing boom]
-[Sam] Need help, Ma?
-No, thank you.
I'm quite capable...
of disposing of one...
[grunts]
...idiotic grate.
[hatch creaking]
[suspenseful music]
["Poupée de Cire, Poupée de Son"
by France Gall plays quietly]
[banging]
[clattering]
[breathless] That freezer is a mess.
It's completely unacceptable.
[dramatic music]
-Come on.
-Are you kidding me?
-We have to go.
-Go where?
Obviously your plan
was to end up here.
-That was a long time ago.
-Mom...
-I'm not going in there.
-Mom, listen.
We need weapons and a car.
We need a safe house!
I'm not sure they'd let me in!
Only one way to find out.
-[dramatic music]
-[church bells chiming]
Hey.
For the record, I still think
this is a shit idea.
[dramatic music plays]
[music fades out]
Madeleine?
-[Sam sighs]
-[gun cocking]
[Anna May] Girls,
I think I see a ghost.
-Hi, Madeleine.
-Hi, Scarlet.
[Scarlet] Florence.
-Hi, Anna May.
-No.
No, no. You don't get to talk.
Because you're a ghost,
and ghosts can't talk.
You know how I know that?
Can we do this later?
Because if ghosts could talk,
they would say something
before disappearing.
Or at least leave a note.
But they can't.
So, ipso facto,
you're a ghost.
-I'm sorry.
-[shouts] Fuck you.
Language, Anna May.
There's a child present.
Fine.
-Fudge you.
-Fudge you!
-[giggles]
-[ominous music]
-[Emily giggles]
And why is there a toddler
in our place of business?
The short version?
Please.
Her father was killed
and she has nowhere else to go.
I was downsized by The Firm,
and they fed me to McAlester's
endless supply of thugs.
And you decided to come here?
Shall we return
at a more convenient time?
Maybe you should.
[Anna May] It seems like
whenever you come here,
you bring a war with you.
Bring your problems--
We need to table this for now.
[loud bang at door]
Seconded.
Let's go down.
[multiple phones ringing]
[phones ringing]
[suspenseful music]
[loud, resonant bang]
Go and take Emily.
I'll buy us some time.
-I think I should stay.
-[banging]
No.
I screwed this up.
-I'll clean up my own mess.
-[banging]
We'll meet at the diner
once I've finished them off.
-Go.
-[banging at door]
Please.
[whispers] Come.
Are you sure?
I could use the target practice.
Mm-mm.
Anna May was right.
I shouldn't have
dragged you into this.
[dramatic music intensifies]
-[Emily] I'm staying with you.
-[sighs]
-No. No, you're not.
-[door bangs]
You're going to the basement,
where it's safe.
But you need me.
I'm your apprentice.
[whispers] Okay, listen, Emily.
The bad men are coming. I really
need you to go with my mom.
No! I want to stay with you.
-You can't.
-But why?
Because...
[swallows hard]
Because I killed your father.
You're lying.
You just want to get rid of me.
[soft emotional music]
Your dad, he, um...
He stole
from some very bad people.
And they hired me.
[door bangs]
And I shot him.
[Emily sobs quietly]
-[Emily sniffs]
-Come on. Let's go.
[door bangs]
I need weapons.
Try the self-help section.
[door bangs]
[door bangs loudly]
[cocks gun]
[suspenseful music]
-[Scarlet] I have to help her.
-You need my permission?
-I can't bail on her again.
-Why? You're good at it.
I'm sorry I couldn't give it up back
then and just stay here with you.
[sighs]
You're human.
You screwed up.
I can only imagine how painful
it was leaving her behind.
[banging intensifies]
[metal screeching]
Leaving us all behind.
But she grew up
to be a fine woman.
[door bangs]
I never wanted
this life for her.
Maybe it was meant to be.
Or maybe she wanted to be
just like her mother.
[metallic click]
[slow footsteps]
I missed you.
We kept these ladies for you.
[dramatic sting]
[Anna May] Just meet us
at the diner.
Come back in one piece, okay?
Both of you.
[tense music]
[grunts]
[rock music plays]
-[blows]
-[grunts]
[both grunting]
[metallic thud]
[both strenuously grunting]
[screams]
[strained grunting]
[grunts]
[Sam grunts]
Motherfucker!
[gun clicks]
[Sam screams]
-[kicking]
-[grunting]
[intense musical build-up]
[gunshots]
[music fades]
[soft music]
[Sam grunts]
Is anything broken?
-Are you bleeding?
-I'm fine.
Bleeding on the inside?
The rest of them are coming.
Would it kill you
to say thank you?
You can still go, Ma.
I'll cover you.
-And miss all the fun?
-[music fades out]
Women Who Run with the Wolves.
-Awakening the Giant Within.
-[grunts] Ammo?
How to Win Friends
and Influence People.
[quiet creaking]
[door shuts in far distance]
[grunts]
You should've stayed away
from this line of work.
Are you kidding, Ma?
You left.
Killing people was the only
thing I knew how to do.
Okay, maybe it wasn't the best
environment to raise a child in.
[sarcastic] You think?
It made you who you are.
At least we can agree on that.
[soft emotional music]
And you are a strong, smart,
incredibly impressive young woman.
There's not a single person on Earth
I'd rather kill people with.
Thanks, Ma.
[Madeleine] You're so strong!
You can't be 8 and three quarters.
[Emily] I am.
[Madeleine] You sure you're
not 28 and three quarters?
[van door slides shut]
[eerie music]
Anna May, Madeleine.
Come and see this.
[suspenseful music]
[whispers] Oh.
We're not leaving.
Scarlet's still a librarian,
no matter if she's an asshole.
-Language.
-Right.
-So these...
-Jerks.
...jerks up there
just made the biggest mistake
of their lives.
[Anna May] They stepped into our library
and threatened our own flesh and blood.
They're not going
to push us around.
They're not going to
scare us off. This ends now.
Madeleine,
finish getting the van ready.
Florence, you and I are going
up there to thin the herd.
We're going to bring the sky down
on their mother-fudging heads.
All in favour?
-Aye.
Aye.
[music intensifies]
Motion carried.
[soft dreamy music plays]
[inaudible]
[dreamy music fades out]
[rousing music]
[gunshots]
[rapid gunfire]
[intense musical build-up]
-[gunshots]
-[tense music]
You think
you have a chance here?
[nephew] I have an army.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I've got my mom.
[laughs]
[breathes heavily]
I wish we had more time, Ma.
It's quality, not quantity.
Chin up.
Why don't you come out, and I'll
put a bullet through your head?
Nice and quick.
-[gun clicks]
-Why don't you go fudge yourself?
[nephew] If you make me work for it,
I'll shoot you in the stomach.
Then we'll have
some real fun together.
[mouthing]
[tense music]
[Florence] Hey, dum-dums.
[gunshots]
[Anna May] Hey, idiots.
Catch these.
[metallic clang]
[coughing]
[birds and animals calling]
[nephew] Idiots to the left.
Morons to the right.
The rest of you knuckleheads
stay here and kill those two.
[chains rattle]
[hammers swoosh]
[tense music]
[birds calling]
[music intensifies]
Shh.
Put these on.
[quietly] I'm going
to make a little noise,
so play it loud.
[whispers]
Can you do that for me?
["Piece of My Heart"
by Janis Joplin plays]
♪ Oh come on, come on ♪
♪ Come on, come on ♪
♪ Didn't I make you feel ♪
[fight sounds]
♪ Like you were the only man ♪
♪ Yeah, didn't I give you
nearly everything ♪
♪ That a woman possibly can ♪
♪ Honey, you know I did ♪
♪ But each time
I tell myself that I ♪
♪ Well, I think I've had enough
But I'm going to show you, baby ♪
♪ That a woman can be tough ♪
♪ I want you to come on ♪
♪ Come on, come on ♪
♪ Come on and take it ♪
♪ Take another little piece
of my heart, now, baby ♪
♪ Break it ♪
♪ Break another little bit
of my heart, now, darling ♪
♪ Oh, have a ♪
♪ Have another little piece
of my heart, now, baby ♪
♪ You know you've got it ♪
♪ If it makes you feel good ♪
-[grunts and blows]
-[rock guitar solo]
[sharp blow]
[gunshot]
[Scarlet] Sam!
[Scarlet] Reload!
♪ I need you to come on ♪
♪ Come on, come on, come on ♪
♪ Now take it ♪
♪ Take another little piece
of my heart, now, baby ♪
♪ Oh, break it ♪
♪ Break another little bit
of my heart, now, darling ♪
♪ Yeah, come on now
Oh, have a ♪
♪ Have another little piece
of my heart, now, baby ♪
[song continues quietly
through headphones]
♪ You know you've got it ♪
♪ Take it ♪
♪ Take another little piece
of my heart, now, baby ♪
♪ Oh, take it ♪
♪ Take another little bit
of my heart ♪
♪ Have another little piece
[song stops abruptly]
[soft music]
[gun clicks]
[music intensifies]
[blows and grunting]
-[man roars]
-[Sam yells]
[gunshot]
[Scarlet grunts]
[screams]
[clanking]
[intense musical build-up]
[man screams in pain]
[yells]
[music intensifies]
[screams]
[chains clanking]
[grunts]
[metallic blow]
[gunshot]
[weapons clashing]
[roars]
-[roars]
-[dull metallic clang]
[distorted scream]
-[sharp blow]
-[man grunts]
[silence]
-[loud blow]
-[body thuds]
-[chains clank]
-[man groans]
[soft emotional music]
-[dull snapping]
-[man groans]
[Scarlet laughs]
You've got something
in your hair.
-[chains rattle]
-[body thuds]
It's a tooth.
Hey.
[soft moan]
[whispers] He...
He took Emily.
[quietly] I couldn't save her.
[whispers] It's okay.
We'll get her back.
[soft emotional music]
It was nice...
having a kid
in the library again.
Huh?
[emotional music]
[Anna May] "There is
little joy in life for me"
"And little terror
in the grave"
"I've lived
the parting hour to see"
"Of one
I would have died to save"
[cheerful ringtone plays]
[nephew] Well, that was exciting.
Been a long time since I killed someone.
Let me talk to Emily.
[nephew] It's a real tragedy
what happens to poor orphans
in our line of work, you know?
It's really quite sad.
What do you want?
[nephew] My uncle
insists on meeting you.
He says, skinning you alive
will let him
work through his, uh, grief.
That's not too much to ask,
is it?
If I come to you,
Emily goes free.
And everyone else
is off the table.
[nephew] Okay, we have a deal.
The diner.
[nephew] Can't wait.
I got to go.
You can't just hand yourself
over to those animals.
They can't bring guns
into the diner.
-It's Emily's best chance.
-It's a suicide mission.
Well, someone else got a plan?
Hmm?
I, uh... I don't right now, no.
[whispers] But it's you, Mom.
[whispers]
You always have a plan.
Sorry.
Then I guess this is goodbye.
[Sam sighs]
-[soft music]
-[birdsong]
[trees creak quietly]
[slow tense music plays]
They're waiting for you, honey.
[Sam] Thanks, Rose.
[eerie music]
Did they hurt you?
It's been a long day.
It's going to be over soon,
okay?
[whispers] Okay.
You're a special kid, Emily.
I wish I had more time
to get to know you.
[ominous music plays]
[music fades]
I'm Jim.
Samantha.
You know, Samantha...
I've always considered myself
a feminist.
When my first daughter was born,
I was over the moon.
Painted half the house pink.
It was all unicorns
and lollipops.
And my second daughter
was born.
And the third and the fourth.
Girls...
always whispering
at the dining table.
Always giggling
in dark corners.
I love my girls.
But I don't understand them.
Then my son was born.
It was different.
Simple.
We understood each other.
And I wasn't alone any more.
I know...
it was just a job to you,
and he was...
in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
[soft music]
None of that matters,
because you
took him away from me.
[suspenseful music]
I'm going to do terrible things
to you, Samantha.
You're going to suffer more
than you thought even possible.
Because you have made me
a stranger in my own home again.
For what it's worth...
[whispers] I am very sorry
about your son.
Thank you, Samantha.
Just let the girl go.
Not yet.
We had a deal.
And I'm a man of my word.
I will set the girl free,
unharmed.
But only after she's watched
what I do to you.
[whispers] Please.
Please, I...
I will do anything.
Don't start begging yet.
There's plenty of time for that.
-[waitress] Can I get you something?
-No, we're just fine.
[waitress] Maybe some more
coffee, or apple pie?
If I have to tell you no again,
there will be consequences.
[whistling
mariachi music plays]
[whispers] Hi, sweetheart.
[whispers] Hi, Mom.
Guess there was a plan,
after all.
[whispers] Guess so.
Why don't you
take Emily out of here?
It's no place for a kid.
Stay out of this, ladies.
It's not your fight.
There's no more
standing on the sidelines.
We all need to pick a side.
-Right, ladies.
-[guns cocking]
[dramatic mariachi music plays]
[mariachi music intensifies]
[gunshot resonates]
[silence]
["It's All Over Now, Baby Blue"
by The Animals plays]
♪ You must leave now ♪
♪ Take what you need
You think will last ♪
♪ But whatever it is
you think you need ♪
♪ You better grab it fast ♪
♪ Yonder stands your orphan
with his gun ♪
♪ Crying like a fire
in the sun ♪
♪ Look out
The saints are coming through ♪
♪ And it's all over now
Baby Blue ♪
♪ The highway is for gamblers
You'd better use your sense ♪
♪ Take whatever you've gathered up
From coincidence ♪
♪ The empty-handed painter
From your streets ♪
♪ Is drawing crazy patterns
On your sheets ♪
♪ The sky too now
is folding up on you ♪
♪ And it's all over now
Baby Blue ♪
♪ It's all over ♪
♪ Baby Blue ♪
♪ It's all over, baby ♪
[birdsong]
[ominous music]
Emily.
[gasping]
[water burbling quietly]
[Sam sighs]
[soft emotional music]
I am so sorry
I killed your father, Emily.
If I could take it back...
I know.
But you tried to save him.
Still.
And you saved me.
[laughs quietly]
[whispers] Thank you.
Besides... I know
you just pulled the trigger.
I know there was someone else
who told you what to do.
Who sent you to my father?
[suspenseful music]
There's a group of men
called The Firm.
[doorbell rings]
[thug] It's a...
It's a girl scout.
[Nathan] Get rid of her.
[Nathan] No, wait.
They've been running things
for a long, long time.
They make all the rules and...
change them
when it fits their needs.
[tense music]
[Sam] They think
they're untouchable.
They think they can get away
with anything.
But they won't, right?
No.
They won't.
Not any more.
[dramatic music intensifies]
Well, well, well.
What do we have here?
I'm selling cookies.
Oh, really? Uh, where are they?
-[tense music]
-[Nathan chuckles]
You're the little girl that I've
heard so much about, aren't you?
They think so little of me they
sent a child to do their dirty work?
I'm insulted, frankly.
"Look into your heart"?
[laughs]
[music quickens]
[groans]
Fuck me.
[cheerful ringtone]
[Sam] Can you hear me?
Loud and clear.
[Sam] We're both alive and well.
That's the way
it's going to stay.
[Nathan] Come on, Sam.
You know that's not up to me.
You get one chance
to end this now.
Years ago, my mom screwed up
and pulled the wrong trigger.
I'm not making the same mistake.
[Sam] That little girl in front
of you will have a future.
Go back to the partners and tell
them we know where they work,
where they live.
We can kill them 100 times over
without them ever seeing us coming.
Tell them
they were only spared
because of
an eight-year-old girl.
Eight and three quarters.
Sorry.
Got it?
Got it.
[Sam] Now, close your eyes
and count to ten.
Slow.
One...
two...
three...
four...
five...
six...
seven...
eight...
nine...
ten.
[chuckles incredulously]
[soft emotional music plays]
[seagulls squawk in distance]
Can I drive?
[together] No.
Can I turn on the radio, then?
Go nuts, baby girl.
[man on radio] Right folks,
time to hit the road.
Take care,
and see you on the other side.
["Goddess on a Hiway"
by Mercury Rev plays]
♪ Well I got us on a highway
I got us in a car ♪
♪ I got us going faster
Than we've ever gone before ♪
♪ I got us on a highway
I got us in a car ♪
♪ I got us going faster
Than we've ever gone before ♪
♪ And I know
It ain't going to last ♪
It ain't going to last
♪ When I see your eyes arrive ♪
♪ They explode
like two bugs on glass ♪
♪ Far above the ocean
Deep under the sea ♪
♪ There's a river running dry
Because of you and me ♪
♪ Far above the ocean
Deep under the sea ♪
♪ There's a river running dry
Because of you and me ♪
♪ And I know
It ain't going to last ♪
♪ It ain't going to last ♪
[dramatic music plays]
[dramatic music fades]
[instrumental music
plays through credits]
[music fades out]