>>>> TRAILER
You have left your elder son..
Mom…
like an orphan...they say.
What do you have to say about it?
My first emotion when I saw the boy..
Thrilled to see me?
Did your heart rate go up?
Did you feel like whistling?
The name is Ramana.
Nice to meet you, sir
Where is Pani, man?
Err…he’s waiting inside, sir.
It's his obligation.
Why wouldn't he wait?
Pani's daughter is incredible!
Stop pulling my leg, Ramu.
Goodness Gracious!
I'm beginning to blush, man.
Do you tear them before wearing
or simply wear them out?
Where to tear and how much to show!
It's completely distinct.
You should have offered her light.
I didn't because I had no matchstick.
Leave them.
They made a mistake.
As if he has done some Engineering.
Slap him so tight he should divulge
his mistress's name before his wife.
Your son is on a drinking spree, uncle!
That is Royal Satyam.
Simple like a black and white film!
This is Rowdy Ramana...
Cinemascope and 70mm.
Want to see my game?
"Spicy and pungent"
"Stinging curry chilli"
Hey!
He swallowed a mike.
"Iron bar, heavy hammer,
broken into pieces, by Ramana's blow"
He's a truck without brakes!
Who has the power to halt him?
Guntur chilli...
It appears fiery and red.
Once you taste it,
you can't help your tears.
My mother, who was supposed to
beat me when I was small,
now sends for me and slaps me
in all dignity.
Ramana, I say.
Your life is a miracle, bro.