Nandu!
Why are you standing in front
of the hospital and smoking?
Downloaded from
YTS.MX
My wife is sick. She is inside.
What happened to her?
The same women's illness.
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
Women's illness?
The expense...
- How much is the cigarette?
Ten rupees.
- Ten rupees?
And how many are in your pocket?
There's one more.
- You have money to die.
But not to save
your wife from death.
What are you saying?
Look at this. It says death on it.
And this sanitary pad is life.
Don't laugh.
With the price of two cigarettes.
You can save your wife from
such a dangerous disease.
Which can be caused by using dirty
clothes during periods.
And by not smoking cigarette.
You can protect yourself
from fatal diseases.
It means with instead of buying
death you can protect two lives.
Yours and your wife's.
Think it over and laugh.
Heroism doesn't like in smoking.
But in giving this.
Smoking causes cancer
and takes lives.
Consumption of liquor is injurious
to health.
HC-0382. Palani Swami, Head constable
from Kuppam police station.
You are here as a suspect.
Don't you feel ashamed
to be sitting here?
Palani, I don't have patience.
I need answers.
I need it too, ma'am.
You have arrested a man, who is
worshipped by all the villagers.
You will have to tell us where
Subramanium is. - What did you say?
Should I tell you?
You commit crimes.
Influence the law.
Erase the evidence.
And even stop the FIRs.
You earn money illegally
and claim to be a God.
He is not worth being called
a human.
Just the villagers call him God,
will he become a God?
Madam, shall I tell you something?
None of the villagers engaged
in farming are in any debts.
Those who migrated
to other villages for jobs,
are now living happily
in their own village.
This was all done by Subramanium,
but no one says this.
The ones who received help look
at him as God.
People like you who are skeptical
look for wrong in him.
If given a chance to speak,
even a demon like Ravan would claim
that he is a great person.
I don't want stories.
I want the truth.
Okay, madam.
So you want the truth.
If that is the case
then before telling you
the story of Subramanium's elevation
to the status of God
I will tell you about
the real demon of this village.
Listen.
Do you like this place more
than our village?
Then we will stay here.
Where are you from?
You may be
from the neighbouring village
but you can't intrude
into Tamma Reddy's territory.
Tamma Reddy's territory?
Who is Tamma Reddy?
Do you know who I am?
- Kumar from Kolar village.
I bought this place with my money.
Why would I listen to Tamma Reddy?
The land can be registered
under any name,
but the land belongs
to Tamma Reddy only.
This is not your Kolar,
where you can act as per your wish.
This is Kuppam.
The MLA of Kuppam is also my guy.
In front of my range
your Tamma Reddy won't last long.
Go and tell him.
Look! I swear by this sugarcane.
I am witnessing someone opposing
Tamma Reddy for the first time.
Good.
You too come along with your Tamma
Reddy, I will serve you mutton.
Dear, make curry for me.
Sure. So be it.
If this continues, will your son
become the MLA the next time?
What do I do? I am getting old.
He has to take the responsibility.
Anyhow, no one can oppose you
in this town, right?
Venkateshwar, not just here, you have
to give respect outside as well.
Only then will your life be safe.
Am I right?
How are you brother Tamma Reddy?
How come you are here?
Venkatesh, didn't you teach
your son wisdom and caution?
He publicly claims
to be the next MLA.
If your son becomes the MLA,
will my son work under him?
Sir,
I swear on my mother
I didn't know that your son
is entering into politics.
Please spare my son.
You will be doing a virtue.
I don't believe in virtue and sin.
Understood, MLA?
Keep your son within limits,
otherwise...
It won't happen, sir.
Why would anyone oppose
brother Sharad?
Leave!
Can you please taste this food?
Hey!
The chili is fine but
the spices are a tad bit strong.
Vishwa, you see.
He called me here in his ignorance.
When you had to kill him here,
why did you bring me here?
He boasted with attitude saying,
MLA was going to come.
He said it is his range.
That's why I wanted
to show him our range.
Moreover,
I need a woman to spend the night.
I thought why not sleep
with his wife.
First I will settle his score,
and then I will look after her.
Hey!
How many times should I teach you?
Blood won't ooze out properly if you
stab there. Stab a little up.
Get lost!
Now look how
his blood is oozing out.
Hey, burn it down.
No!
If Vishwas Reddy sees a woman
and the land Tamma Reddy steps on,
they take them by force.
In spite of owning the land,
these silent residents were beaten,
even on the festival day.
So they couldn't endure it.
The villagers were migrating out
of the village
when lives became unbearable.
Then one man came to stay
in that village.
He is Subramanium.
"Your power strengthens the weak."
"Your devotion strengthens
the meek."
"The end is near for the tyrants."
"Your devotees revere you."
"Hail Shiv Shambu!
You are merciless on the evil."
"You annihilate the enemies
and bring a new dawn."
"You are the auspicious God! O Gauri
Shankar, the enchanting one!"
"You are the ascetic.
You wipe the evil."
"You are the beginning and the end."
"O God, bless us with your grace."
"Be fearless! If you have
confidence, you will be invincible."
"May the torch
of truth always stay lit."
Hail Harom Hara! Hail Harom Hara!
All you do is pray.
Get me a cup of tea.
Why are you in such a hurry?
Neither Subramanium needs to go
to college nor you have a duty.
So why are you in such a hurry?
Ramanna, I am not fired.
I am only under suspension.
Once I become a police officer,
it won't be so easy to fire me.
You know,
I didn't do anything wrong.
I will get my job back
after the enquiry.
Yes, please take it.
- Understood?
Nobody respects a man without a job.
Did you see that, Subramanium?
"Hail Harom Hara!
This is your world."
Spread peace and prosperity."
"Hail Harom Hara!
Your arrival is auspicious."
Your wrath is fierce."
What's this? What if somebody sees?
So what?
You are a teacher and I am a lab
assistant. It won't look good.
So what? It's okay. Have it.
Okay, you leave.
Hello, Subramanium!
- Yes, dad. How are you?
Yes, I am fine.
But why didn't you come home?
Hey, get him into the vehicle.
Don't worry about that.
I will send you the money order.
Okay, son. I will hang up.
Brother, they publish everything
in the newspaper.
Why doesn't anybody report the
atrocities happening in our village?
Nothing was published
since I joined the duty.
How can you expect it now?
What happened?
You be quiet. This is normal here.
Make ginger tea.
- Yes.
Sit.
Why didn't you come by bus directly?
Do you have
any problem picking me up?
I didn't mean that.
But what if somebody sees us?
Being a girl, I am showing courage.
You are a man,
what are you scared of?
I am not scared.
Anyway, we don't have
to tell everything to you girls.
Look. Let me earn some money.
Once I save enough
then I will take you on
a drive in my car.
Here.
Okay. You leave,
I will get ready and come.
Brother. Brother, save me.
They are coming to kill me.
- What happened?
That guy chasing me
misbehaved with my sister.
I confronted him.
So he started beating me.
Hey, wait!
Listen. I will talk to the Principal
if you have any concerns.
What else will you do? Hit me?
What are you looking at?
Tell me. Come!
Brother, he is Sharad Reddy's guy.
Subramanium!
Despite kg who we are,
how dare you this!
Now get ready to face
the consequences.
Come on, let's go.
Brother Sharad.
What happened?
Somebody from the polytechnical
college dared to lay hands on us.
Hey! Start the car.
Hey, Sharad.
Listen. Wait outside.
Where are you going?
Didn't you hear it?
I will see who he is.
Are you out of your mind?
Will you get into their fights?
Are they working for you
or are you working for them?
Subramanium, don't you have a sense
of whom you are dealing with?
They can even close down this
college. Is this what you want?
Hello.
- Hey, I am Sharad speaking.
Sir, please forgive us.
It was a mistake.
How dare he! Who is he?
Don't you know what will happen
if I come there?
Sir, I promise this won't be
repeated. I beg your forgiveness.
He is not from this village. That's
why he doesn't know about you.
If he continues to work
at your college
I will make sure you no longer have
a college. Understood?
Okay, sir.
I knew this was coming.
While staying in this village,
I can't go against their word.
If you want to continue working
in this college,
you have to beg for
their forgiveness.
Or you should resign from your job.
Sir, I can't live like this.
I don't want a life where I have
to live on others' terms.
I will take your leave, sir.
Okay, leave. You don't need
this college, as per your range.
We can get a much better job
than this. I mean it.
Hey! Did you see it?
They are such rogues.
I hope somebody would
straighten them out.
Hey, Subramanium!
Subramanium, phone call for you.
Hello, Subramanium!
Yes, dad.
You haven't sent
the money this week.
Son, please try to send some money.
Are you there? Hello?
I will not send money order,
but come in person this time.
Okay then. Please come. Come fast.
I will take your leave.
- Okay.
My son is here, I am leaving.
- Okay. Take care.
Son, I thought you would come
in the evening.
Actually, I took a leave.
Okay.
Here's the key. Go home.
I have some urgent work.
I will come later.
Give me the money.
What's the hurry?
I have work.
Give it.
Don't lie there drunk.
Come home soon.
Don't make fun of me. Should
I bring chicken for you. - Yes.
The weather department
has forecast rain.
You don't pay my money.
Don't throw my stuff.
- Throw it outside.
Try to understand.
My son is here. Listen.
Brother, my son is inside.
When will you give me money?
Listen. Please leave.
- Won't you return our money?
Hey! - When will you repay us?
Return the money!
What is it?
Why are you troubling my father?
What happened?
Your father took loan. - If he can't
repay, why did he take a loan?
Listen. Please calm down
and tell me what happened.
Tell him he has borrowed money.
Are you scared?
Ask him where our money is.
Yes, tell us! Where is our money?
Answer us.
He has swindled our money. - Wait.
He is an educated guy.
He will talk sensibly.
Subramanium, your father has
borrowed money from all of us.
Even after many years
he hasn't even paid interest
or the principal amount.
When we demand money,
he keeps telling us that
you will pay off his loan.
But so far he hasn't given
a penny to any of us.
You solve our problem.
Okay, fine.
How much does he owe you?
He owes me 28,800 rupees.
Listen. Give me some time,
I will return all your money.
Should we trust us. Earlier
we gave time to your father,
now you want time.
It is not so, brother.
But I need some time
to gather this huge amount.
We can't give any more time. We have
waited for too long already.
Wait. Everyone, silent. Let me talk.
Look, Subramanium!
We should give you more time
but the villagers have lost faith
in your father.
We can give you 3 months' time.
Return our money within
three months.
I will repay your money within
this time. Okay?
How can we trust them? - How long
should we wait for our money?
You too say something.
Quiet! He has promised
to return within 3 months.
Let's leave for now.
- Let's go.
It's too much!
We have to leave empty-handed.
Hmm. Have it.
You may think I am talking
in intoxication.
Son, people respect only
those who have money.
You should not face this
in the future
that's why I am telling you
to earn a lot of money.
Because I am going through
an ordeal.
Only I know how I face
this humiliation.
You tell the same thing every
time you are drunk.
Continue!
Do not worry about
what happened today.
Anyhow,
I will manage to clear my debts.
How will you get the money?
There's no need.
I will manage something.
I forbid you.
We won't always live like this.
We will see good days too.
I will clear all my debts and get
you married to a good girl.
Will you be quiet?
You are talking about my wedding.
I didn't want to tell you
but you are forcing me.
I lost my job.
How will I get money the next month?
I am not refusing.
I said I will take care of it. Okay?
Please finish your dinner! Son!
Subramanium!
I will find peace only if
I share my feelings.
That's why I am sharing my pain
with you after you sleep.
Because I don't have anyone else
in this world to share with.
You never asked me anything, son.
Even today, you took the responsibility
of clearing my debts anyhow.
But you never asked me the reason.
You have always been
a good son to me.
But I was a useless father to you.
What sins have you done
to have me as your father
and what good deeds have
I done to have you as my son?
Only God knows the answer
and no one else.
Listen. I am not asleep yet.
- Huh?
Are you not asleep?
Sleep. Sleep. Sleep well.
I can't believe that you are so
upset because of losing his job.
Don't lose hope so soon.
Why are you looking at me like this?
What is going on in your mind?
Tell me the truth, Subramanium.
My father has taken huge debts
in my village.
I have been saving money
to start a business of my own
but even my entire savings isn't
enough to clear those debts.
How can you give up like others?
You are not like others.
You are unique.
Do not be dejected.
Don't wreck your brains over this.
Take this.
Why would you do that?
Don't you know why I did that?
You said you need money, right?
Either sell them or pawn them.
Your wish. Okay?
But you should not be sad.
I can't see you like this.
I don't want this.
I will find a way.
Listen to me!
- Keep it.
Subramanium! Hey, Subramanium!
It seems Palani is here.
Brother, what happened?
- My team member has passed away.
I need to attend his cremation.
Can you drop me?
Okay. I will get the key.
- Okay.
Palani has some work.
- Hmm.
You may leave.
Hey, Subramanium!
I will come back. You stay here.
- Okay.
It was terrible!
What will happen now?
- Yes, it is terrible.
He was a great man.
He always gave money
to the needy people
even when we didn't ask for it.
Thank you.
So, Palani!
When did you come?
Just now, sir.
- Okay.
I got some booze from the village.
Let's drink together.
I don't feel like drinking now, sir.
What is it? How can you reject
an offer of liquor!
No matter what,
he was your colleague.
I know you must be in pain.
Come and have a drink.
My friend is there.
I will send him and join you.
Okay, come there later.
- Sure.
Subramanium, keep this bag with you.
I will take it from you later.
Okay? You may leave.
Go quickly.
Where is the bag, Subramanium?
Nobody saw it, right?
No.
But why are you so tensed?
Didn't you see what's in it?
I saw.
You saw it, right?
If my department finds this out,
all hell will break loose.
This is the cause of my suspension.
I understand the gun,
what about the blueprint?
Four months ago...
All our problems will be solved
with it.
What if our sir finds out?
How will he find out if
we don't tell him?
Listen.
I have traced a party in a village.
I will get him to make
an exact replica of this.
We will replace
the replica over here.
Not only will we make profits
but also retain our duty.
What do you say?
- Okay.
Unfortunately,
there was an inspection that day.
The evidence went missing
and I was on duty that day.
So I was suspended.
Okay, fine.
But why do you keep it
with yourself?
Why don't you give it to that party?
How can I?
He has been arrested by
the police there.
Had I sold it to him,
I would have got 500 rupees.
What did you say?
500 rupees for this gun?
What else do you think?
If it takes 50 rupees for the metal
and 20 rupees for the making
still it should not cost more
than 100.
You are right. But who will make it?
People around
the world use gun for power.
But this gun has traveled
all around to get to me.
It's trying to tell me something.
The heart is sending a message.
Let's make a business out of this.
Huh? Are you being serious?
Why would I lie about this?
We both need money. You tell me.
Do you have a better idea than this?
Subramanium, look.
Only dangerous people get
into such business.
If we start this business, can we
survive while competing with them?
Brother,
we can manage to live somehow.
Even a lion gets caught by
the hunter if it gets scared.
It can be the king of the Jungle
only if it scares others.
Let's start with it.
We will deal with it later.
Look!
Even God gave a green signal to us.
They ring the bell every day
at this time in the temple.
How is that related to our business?
Look. Let's make a start.
We will stop if we feel it is wrong.
But if everything goes well,
we believe that
God is making us do it.
Tell me now!
Look.
I will come to you during
the business time,
but the liability falls entirely
on you.
I don't have any money to invest.
I am making this very clear to you.
What happened, Subramanium?
Why are you quiet?
Will you say something?
There is nothing to talk about.
Let's get into action.
Come on.
- Where are we going?
Let's find a good place
to start this business.
This place looks good,
Subramanium. Nobody stays here.
There's a school right beside it.
How can we do it here?
Look. How about this?
It will crumble with the sound
of the bullets.
I remembered a great place.
- Then show it to me.
Subramanium, stop here.
Brother.
How about we use this talkies?
Do you know who owns this talkies?
Let's go.
Why do we care who owns it?
It has been closed since the day
I came to this village.
It looks like no one comes here.
It's confirmed that
no one comes here.
The power supply is active,
but the bulb is not working.
They seem to be very poor.
Even the projector is not working.
Come on!
Hey, you! Will you act pompous?
Will you act pompous with me?
Beat him! Beat him!
Sharad Reddy is here.
We killed
your brother-in-law Kolar Kumar.
Do you think you are
a bigger Don than him?
I will teach you a lesson.
- Brother, please forgive me.
Come on!
They have left. Let's leave quickly.
Where, brother?
Where would we get
a better place than this?
We have electricity supply.
The sound doesn't go out.
Since Sharad Reddy visits the place,
no one else would come
to this place.
That's what I am saying.
He keeps coming to this place.
Let them have their petty fights.
Why should we care?
You are not scared despite
witnessing a murder.
You are definitely not a good man.
There's no such thing as good
or bad.
"Better you don't trigger,
before you butter him."
"Just dig your grave before,
you fight him."
"He got spring in the bones.
He is not a metaphor."
"Look at him right in the eye."
"Gun smith.
Gut is just like a loaded barrel."
Cutting deep into bloody bones."
"Gun smith."
"He is got a rusty face
and knitting hands."
"You will find him
like a moving gun."
Listen, Ramanna.
Subramanium seems to be having some
tension. Give 2 cups of tea.
Okay, brother.
It shoots in reverse.
And this?
Oh! You did it, kiddo.
I have seen only trash guns
throughout my service.
I haven't seen it as good as
this one so far.
Did you make
the bullets yourself too?
A gun should never be understood.
You should know its power only
after using it.
Mark my words. It will have
good demands in the market.
That's more like it. Now we shall
celebrate Diwali every day.
Listen,
come to Krishnagiri tomorrow.
You got me 60 kilometres away
from Kuppam
saying we have a good client
to do business.
But you are having
a liquor party instead.
Here.
If not him then someone
else will come.
If we have a product to offer,
the buyer will come to us.
Sharad! Why are you so late?
Any problem on the way here?
What do I say, Raj?
I got late because
of a girl's matter.
Leave it. Serve me a drink.
I don't have time. I will leave.
What's the hurry?
Is your step-brother causing
any trouble?
He has joined some other gang,
but there is no problem.
Okay. Let's finish one peg.
I will leave too.
Okay, brother.
I will take your leave.
Okay.
Guys, come on.
Look at what our boss is doing!
Look what he is doing
with boss over there.
Hey!
What's this?
Gun.
I can see that.
Why did you keep it here?
I thought you might need it.
Even the bullets are loaded.
Try it once.
You will get
a good feeling for sure.
I know what you are thinking now.
Take this with you.
Use it for some time.
If you like it talk to
your father and let me know,
how many you want and
where to deliver them.
What do you say?
- What should I say?
Daggers are enough these days.
What would I do with this gun?
Now, no one can save you.
This fight is between us.
You can show off your power
in your village.
How dare you!
Hey! Stop!
Hey! He has a gun!
That day the sound from
Subramanium's gun created an echo
in the ears of those gangs.
And it instilled fear in their eyes.
Sharad, shall I tell you something?
If you have a knife, only the one
you are about to stab will fear you.
But if you have a gun,
everyone around you will fear you.
"Where darkness spreads everywhere"
"he marches to annihilate the evil."
"There is only one slogan coming
from the Kailash."
"He is off to kill the demons."
"This is the time to end sin."
Hey!
Put extra spice in it.
Take this away.
Vishwas!
- Yes.
Sharad has brought something for us.
Instead of checking it out you
are busy with yourself.
We are not used to it.
We should stick with whatever
we are used to.
Yes. You are right.
Sharad, do you think we need this?
Do you think you and uncle are
in still young?
I am of marriageable age.
Tomorrow if I have to kill someone,
will I take a dagger?
But if we have a gun,
we can shoot him from a distance.
Hey! I can't do it.
- What?
I aimed here and it shot there.
Come on, uncle.
I too didn't know how to use dagger.
I learnt it gradually.
This gun too is similar to that.
You will learn to use it eventually.
It's right.
Now tell me,
how many guns do you want?
We can't just get one each
for the three of us.
No! Look around,
how they are staring at us.
Get one for each of them.
What are you doing here?
I will tell.
You said you smoke occasionally.
But now it seems you are
a chain smoker.
It is nothing! I am under a bit
of tension, that's why.
I threw it away.
Look. What are you doing? Stay away.
Oh really?
Don't get any ideas in your brain.
You can't do anything without
my permission. Understood?
Me? Nothing.
Tell me the truth.
What do you want to do?
Before you ask
I wanted to tell you long ago.
I am doing something wrong.
What's that?
I am making guns.
Say it again.
And keep it simple for me.
Guns. Pistols.
Do you want to see?
Here!
Does it go off?
If you load bullets into it,
it will kill too.
Is this the wrong thing
you mentioned about?
Yes.
How is this wrong?
What are you saying?
Isn't making guns wrong?
No. How can it be wrong?
All these years, have we ever got
more money that our basic needs?
No, right?
Anything that we do
for our survival is not wrong.
In these times, if we are nice,
society makes our lives miserable.
We have to be cunning
to lead a decent life.
Why are you talking like this?
What else did you expect then?
Oh God, we don't need all this.
It doesn't matter if
we don't have enough food.
We will manage in meager food.
Do you want me to say
such ridiculous things?
Drop me off at the college.
I am getting late.
Won't you drink it?
I don't drink while on business.
While I am drinking,
I don't talk about business.
He is like that only.
Come to the point.
My father has two wives.
His second wife has a son.
By joining hands with Mahendar,
he is getting too arrogant.
My gang is not secure enough,
at the moment.
My life is in danger too.
I need guns immediately.
Is that all?
I will give them.
When do you want them?
Do you know what kind
of a person he is?
It's not easy to get guns in
my area, escaping his watch.
If his gang finds out that
I have approached you for guns,
he will go to any extent to stop me
and show his power.
That's why I am warning you.
It will be difficult to come here
avoiding my step brother. - Look!
Rajmanikyam.
Rajmanik.
As I said, I do a lot of stuff.
If I commit to something,
I get it done by hook or crook.
You will receive your goods.
You just have a good time.
I will take care of the rest.
Hey! Search all the vehicles.
- Okay, sir.
Look there. Check that van.
They are checking because they have
received some information.
Rajamanikyam said that
someone has tipped them off.
Sir, we found nothing.
You may leave.
Police increased the surveillance.
I got a phone call.
I feared you would be caught.
By the way, where are the goods?
They are here
but first get those steel utensils.
Those utensils?
Rajamanikyam sent these.
This time our boss will be get
the election ticket.
No one can stop us.
Drive slowly.
Subramanium is sitting there.
Palani! Palani!
You started the story with the
promise of revealing the monster.
But you are telling me how
Subramanium turned into a monster.
I don't see Subramanium's virtues.
I see only his crimes.
Madam, I am telling you
the truth that you asked for.
If I had to tell only good things
about Subramanium,
I would have skipped half the story.
You would have found
the rest yourself.
We did business,
that's it. Not murders.
When
we felt everything was going well
Tamma Reddy and his men were causing
ruckus in the opposition.
Leave me!
We lost the case, Tamma Reddy.
Didn't I tell you that
I am going out
and get bathed before I come back?
I was feeling feverish.
Never mind.
Put on some powder at least.
You will look good.
Hey, Vishwas!
Yes, brother?
We lost the case.
Rajendra just informed me.
I will see that scoundrel lawyer.
Hey.
Singaru!
- Yes, sir!
Search that rascal. Where is he?
I want him with the lawyer
in the talkies by tonight.
Okay, sir.
Had you shown this brilliance
in the court,
you would have been alive today.
Drat!
The world is too small, madam.
An incident that happens afar
to a person,
affects some other person
who is not related to him.
But we were in the same village.
So how couldn't our matters
affect each other?
You fool!
Brother, leave me.
Do you think gun trading is easy?
I made a mistake!
You said it, didn't you?
Now go to hell.
Subramanium!
Things have heated up.
That Mahendra...
Rajamanikyam.
You are free to make
a gang against your brother,
that's your personal matter.
But I cannot accept that
you have brought guns
from someone else other than me.
Did you think I had not notice?
Or did you think I would be quiet
after find out?
Did you supply guns to me when
I needed them? So what do I do?
Have your tea and vacate the place.
Do you think you can do business
while going against me?
Don't you know I have whose support?
I don't care.
This is my village.
And I am the Don here.
That Mahendra has targeted us.
He may attack them any time.
What should we do now, kiddo?
The guns must reach our men
before Mahendra attacks.
Deliver them tonight.
Should I tell our men anything?
There's nothing to be said now.
Let's get into action.
Why are we sending all the guns?
Will they keep a count
when lives are lost there.
It's better if you could deliver
this personally.
After delivering goods once,
you are back here again.
Have you two lost your mind?
Aren't you scared?
If you have to continue
your business,
you must work under us and fear us.
My boss won't agree
to work under you.
Moreover,
he does not know what fear is.
Selva, did you see it?
Subramanium should fear us.
Get him into the vehicle.
If anything comes to us
after intimation, it's fear.
If it comes without our knowledge,
it's a danger.
If it all comes at once,
it's a bad time.
After that along
with Subramanium's life,
my life also took a drastic turn.
Hey, come in!
Come.
Come. Come.
How dare you go against boss!
Take this.
Come fast!
Hey, Singaru. Why did you take
so long to get this old man?
Hey! Be quiet. It was not
an easy task to bring him.
Hey, why are you talking
to the one we want to kill?
He has a son, boss.
Our men were searching for him.
I thought that
we would kill both at once.
We will kill him when he comes
for his cremation.
Kill him now.
Okay, boss.
See who is there.
- Okay, boss.
Boss, it was a peacock.
Kill it after you kill him.
I will have it for dinner
with liquor.
Son!
Hey! Go!
Hey! Call our men quickly. Come on!
Hey, boss. Kittappa.
Go.
Look, Mahendra.
Tell the ones over there that
there's a lion on this side.
His name is Subramanium Care
of Kuppam.
I have never questioned
any of your actions.
But yesterday your life was
in danger, so I have to ask.
What's the relationship between
a common man like you
and the goons of this area?
Son, I wanted to tell
this to you long back.
But I couldn't muster courage.
I used all my savings and
your mother's ornaments
to buy land in this village as
you too were working here.
Later I got to know that there
is someone called Tamma Reddy.
They threatened me
to give up that land.
They threatened me but
I was dumbfounded.
I got all the documents from the
seller and lodged a case in court.
The lawyer told me that the opposite
party is very powerful.
And we would require a lot
of money to win the case.
So I took a loan from everyone
in the village.
We won the case recently.
I was on my way to Kuppam
to inform you about this.
But in the meantime,
they started beating me up.
Why did they take me
to that talkies?
And what were you doing in
that talkies, at that time?
When I wonder about it,
it seems like God's miracle.
I don't understand why
they are like this.
I am sorry, but we don't have
anything better for offerings.
This temple is like this now
but once upon a time, this village
and temple were prosperous.
Since the arrival of Tamma Reddy,
this village has lost its happiness.
Most family members are found
as photo frames on the walls.
People do not even react to
their neighbours' beheading.
If they do,
they will lose their lives.
They don't have a son like yours,
who can go against them
to save his family.
When will he be cured?
The injuries will cure soon,
but I am not sure if
his fear will go away.
Don't take me wrong.
He will come out of the coma only
when he overcomes that fear.
How many men were there?
How many people attacked him?
He was alone, boss.
Who was he?
Subramanium.
Subramanium?
What the hell were you doing?
Brother, now I will go.
I will kill him in your presence or
else I will bring his head to you.
Hey, come along.
Brother. - Huh? - Do you have
a change for 50 rupees.
Did you hear the news?
- What is it?
Someone has thrashed Sharad
Reddy last night.
Is it true?
- Yes.
Did you hear? Someone thrashed
Reddy so badly last night,
that he almost died.
He deserves it.
Take the money!
Priest, did you hear this?
Someone has thrashed Reddy so bad
that he almost died. - Really?
Hail God! - All praise to powerful
Lord Murgan! Harom Hara!
Are you sure about this news?
- Yes, I am sure.
This is something to be celebrated.
Come on, everybody.
Today I will give peanuts for free.
Come and take it.
Take it, sister. - Did you hear that
Sharad Reddy has been thrashed?
Is it?
- Yes.
Durga,
Sharad Reddy has been thrashed.
Listen. Sharad Reddy has been
thrashed by someone.
Daughter, did you hear that Sharad
Reddy has been thrashed by someone?
Is it true?
- Yes, daughter.
Take it, sister.
Give it to me.
- Give me some.
I never thought
I would see this day.
I guess good times await us.
Where does he stay?
Where is that Subramanium
who thrashed my boy?
Trust me. I didn't know his name.
Now that I have heard the name,
I realise God has come to save us.
I wouldn't say anything even
if I knew his name.
Boss!
If I kill him,
the fear of watching him die would
make someone else speak out.
Kill him!
"The angel of death is here!"
"Lord Shankar."
You were asking about the whereabouts
of Subramanium, weren't you?
He is not just Subramanium,
but wrathful Subramanium!
If we kill him along with this man
we will get rid of the troubles.
- Have you forgotten who I am?
Come on! Kill him!
- Brother, get in.
I will kill you all and bury you.
- Listen to me. Get inside.
Get out of here!
Get inside.
- Go back! - Kill him!
I know about all the atrocities these
guys carried on in this village.
Henceforth nothing of that
sort will take place here.
I will get back all your lands
these people grabbed from you.
I will also get back all the money
they stole from the temple.
Call all those who have migrated
away from this village.
Now no father will have to look
forward to his son's arrival.
No daughter will cry for her mother.
No wife will live without her
husband.
The festival that stopped 30 years
ago will start again. I swear.
Henceforth if any troubles have
to reach you
Subramanium is standing before you,
it must first face me.
We have heard
about Tarakasur's story.
But today I am witnessing it.
He is not any ordinary Subramanium.
He is the manifestation
of Lord Murgan,
whom I prayed for all these years.
He is Lord Murgan.
All hail, Lord Murgan!
Harom Hara!
You don't have to live in
that village any more.
Don't worry about the money.
Let's go.
Yes.
- Thank you.
Brother, it is because of you
that we could meet again.
Now that all of you are back,
everything will be fine.
Okay, brother.
Bye.
(Chanting)
Brother, I have always seen rage
in your eyes
for the first time I see sadness.
A strong man should never display
his sadness to others.
My son lies in a hospital.
My younger brother was killed
in front of the village.
And I have exiled myself
from the village after losing.
I know who is responsible for it
still I can't do anything to him.
You have not lost until you give up,
Tamma Reddy.
Listen. Can't you see the water
dripping? Keep the umbrella out.
Keep it out, dear.
- Hmm.
Tell me. What do you want?
Father-in-law, give that.
We won the case in the court.
We have the order.
You need to sign these documents.
I got it.
Do some favours and I will get
your job done in 3 months.
Why are you silent?
Didn't you understand what favours
I am talking about?
We understood what it meant.
If you say 2 to 3 months,
my father-in-law and I would wait.
But my husband won't wait that long.
We can't consider his impatience.
He must wait.
Your husband is not a king that
things would happen at his pace.
Do you know Subramanium?
Why? Do I have to know him?
Can you please stand and look there?
I swear, I didn't know. Please sit.
Sit. Get some tea for them.
We don't require your hospitality.
Just get our job done.
Hey, look for that survey number.
Quick.
Hey, get it done fast.
Two minutes, brother.
Get the documents ready.
Yes. Give it.
Sir!
Your papers are ready, sir. I swear.
They have come
for the land documents.
The job is done.
Hey! Is your work done?
No. Not yet, brother.
They are refusing.
- It's not done.
There's no fault of mine.
I did it out of Tamma Reddy's fear.
Now...
The pace with which you got
my documents done
with the same pace,
their work must be done.
Okay?
I will do it, brother.
I will get it done in a month.
Grandpa, he is asking for a month.
Is it okay with you?
Son, we have been hearing the same
thing since the last 5 years.
Look, those times were different.
These times are different.
I will get it done quickly.
Brother, don't worry.
Brother,
they have ruined all my lands.
What should we do now?
My land is barren, brother.
I don't know what to do.
Even selling all my land will be
insufficient to clear my loans.
I will take care of everything.
- Okay.
Sir, take this. Please take this.
Come.
- Yes.
Brother, did you notice it?
Once upon a time,
my family was very small.
Now see how big it has become.
So have my responsibilities!
That means,
my income should also grow.
Brother Palani,
we have to lease this factory.
What? Are you going to increase
your income with bricks?
Why are you laughing,
kiddo? Say something.
There's nothing to say.
It's time for action.
"This life goes on unsteadily."
"But you have to run to win
the race."
"Those who wake up from slumber,
don't sleep again."
"It's true.
You can make your dream come true."
"You have to overcome difficulties."
Hey, kiddo.
We are finding it difficult to name
these models while taking orders.
Nobody is literate here.
So what? We need a name that
can be easily understood.
This is NTR Rao.
This is NR Rao.
This is Chiranjeevi.
And this is Krishna.
And what about this?
Amitabh Bachchan.
It'll be world famous.
"The heart beats fast.
Be careful, dear."
"There are hurdles on every path.
You can't rule here."
"There are no rules.
Only the brave ones win."
"You will have your day as well."
"The heart is yours.
I live for you."
"No matter how I am,
I will always be with you."
"Be it joy or grief,
I won't abandon you."
What, brother?
Why are you reading it?
You don't need it.
If you want to make progress,
you have to learn.
Your progress will stop
if you stop learning.
Kiddo.
They have come for money
to buy seeds.
Devi!
Enough, dear.
Eat it, father-in-law.
I have made your favourite dish.
Okay.
Dad, do only fathers know
their kids' likes and dislikes.
Children too know
their fathers' likes and dislikes.
Eat it.
- Eat it.
Kiddo, we have received this letter
from a Don of Mumbai.
Is he going on a war?
We can't build such a big weapon.
Are you planning to build it?
No, brother.
I was thinking once brother makes
it, what name should it be given.
What name have you thought of?
- Jyoti Lakshmi.
Jyoti Lakshmi?
- Yes.
Have a look at it.
- He says to name it Jyoti Lakshmi.
"Now our time will start.
Walk graciously."
"The destination is not far."
"Fulfill your dream with fortitude."
"Don't let anything stop you,
at any cost."
Take care.
Not of yourself,
take care of the gun.
Local made. - I have seen many
such bullets in Mumbai, madam.
Can't locally made goods
reach Bombay?
What should we do now, madam?
The man behind the trigger would
be apprehended somehow.
But I want the man
who made the trigger.
Tell me, Selva Manik.
What brings you here?
He taught me to shoot since
I have been in this business.
His name is Mahendra.
He reins even in big cities.
You have brought so many men,
then the job must be big enough.
What is it?
Look, brother.
Until yesterday,
my gang was unbeatable.
But today I have been betrayed by
my step-brother.
Many of
my gang members have been killed.
I won't spare him.
- He can't hide.
We have to break down his strength.
That means,
we need to kill Subramanium.
And I want your help to do that.
He was once our Sharad's friend
and has started a gang of his own.
Didn't you tell me that he has good
relationships with those people?
Then why do you need us?
But if we do this,
my boss's importance will dwindle.
That's why we have approached you.
Okay. Tell me,
what can I do for you?
Subramanium will recognize any
gangster from our three states.
Someone not related
to our field must approach him
and give him a big consignment order
and call him in our area.
Once he comes, he will not return.
He will be sent to hell!
So, instead of us, we should send
someone with political connection.
That's our plan.
Brother, MLA Venkateshwar is coming.
It's a very small matter,
Subramanium. You don't have to fear.
Do you see fear in my eyes?
Tell me.
Do you know Nataraj
from Krishnagiri?
Elections will be held there.
The opposition candidate
is expanding his gang.
We need guns for their safety,
that's why I have come to you.
That's fine.
But who told you that we sell guns?
Being in politics,
can't I find out this information?
Just let me know if you can do
the job or not.
There is nothing we can't do.
When do you want
the delivery and where?
Take a look.
The front one is NTR,
the one beside that is Chiranjeevi
and that one is Krishna.
Tell me what you want
and when you want.
Krishna. A tractor full.
You have
to deliver it to Krishnagiri.
Your job will be done.
Pay advance to my men.
If you go back on your promise,
you will lose your life.
My deal with me is like
a deal with God.
Your job will be done.
You may leave.
Where's the tractor?
I have counted the money, kiddo.
Subramanium,
you considered yourself a lion,
when this lion was missing.
My one hand is enough for you.
To kill you,
this lion will take you along.
"It's time to annihilate
the enemies."
Jyoti Lakshmi!
"It's time."
"It's time to annihilate
the enemies."
"Harom Hara."
"It's an extraordinary sight."
Oh no! What is that, brother?
It Subramanium's wrathful avatar.
"He has come as the angel of death."
"To punish you."
In a forest without lions,
even a wolf believes it's a lion.
Once your raise your head,
you will know who the lion is.
Do you know who I am?
Subramanium!
God of war.
Shall I tell you something?
I know that you are doing business
not just for our family
but for the people.
I felt like telling this
to you in front of God.
Son, the weapons that you create
I don't know if they
any good or bad.
But those weapons only shed blood.
If your weapons take innocent lives,
we will be burdened with those sins.
On the coming festival,
take a vow to quit this.
Will you listen to me, son?
Okay, dad.
Let's go.
Son, don't worry at all.
If you want to do something
for these people
find some another noble way,
which is in everyone's well-being.
There is a man named Subramanium
in Kuppam.
Did you come here to say this?
I also made a mistake
of underestimating him.
But he is more powerful
than a hundred of men.
We will see.
Idiot. We couldn't harm him
when he was out in the open.
He will blow us
to pieces in his area.
He thinks he is arms Lord by
manufacturing a few weapons.
Do you know what I will do now?
What?
Be it Kuppam or anywhere else,
he will die for sure.
But we have another problem.
Kiranmay.
Chidambaram, SHO.
He is our writer Shreenu!
Where's the evidence?
They are inside, madam
- Come.
This is from Madanapalli and
this is from Krishnagiri.
This is from Mullubangan and
this is from Kolar.
All of them have the same model
of guns and bullets.
So, manufacturers
and suppliers are the same?
But who is supplying so much, madam?
From our primary investigation
we have received information that
they are supplied
from the Kuppam borders.
But who can do this in Kuppam,
madam?
Chidambaram, there is
a small town called Bulandshaher,
in Uttar Pradesh.
Illegal guns were supplied
in India from there.
Just like you said,
if police too would have thought
who could do it from here
then that crime would have
never been exposed.
Condemnation without investigation
is the height of ignorance.
So, keep aside your intelligence
and search properly in Kuppam.
And secure all the borders
in the vicinity.
No vehicle should be allowed outside
without proper checking.
Yes, madam.
(Chanting)
Hail Lord Murgan!
- Harom Hara!
(Chanting)
Sir.
Brother Palani! Brother Palani!
Brother.
Hey! Why did you come here instead
of taking
the vehicle to the factory?
Brother, we have a huge problem.
On the way, the police stopped
and started checking the vehicle.
Did you check well?
They did, madam. They found nothing.
This is
a regular plying vehicle here.
Where are you coming from?
I am coming from
a neighbouring village, ma'am.
They found that the lorry belongs
to Subramanium. What do we do now?
Okay, go to the factory immediately.
I will take care of it. - Okay.
9mm bullet.
I didn't get it, madam.
Look, Chidambaram.
Kuppam has flower gardens,
so they can be transported.
There's is a quarry here,
so it can be exported.
But why are bricks getting exported?
They will get many from Karnataka
and Tamil Nadu.
Instead of getting from there,
why would they export
from this village?
Maybe their quality is good, madam.
Why would someone spend
such a big amount on quality?
It's bloody common sense, darn it!
Go in and get all the guns out.
- Okay.
Listen. Take different routes
and reach the desert.
It is from Bombay.
Since we are tracking trunk calls,
he is been doing
his business through letters.
Start the vehicle.
Madam. - We must not lose
Subramanium at any cost.
Send a team to search the factory.
- Okay, madam.
Mohan, reach the factory
for searching with your team.
(Chanting)
Chidambaram,
go inside and search the place.
Hey, search the whole house.
Don't miss any corner.
Son.
We didn't get anything
at the factory, madam.
Madam, we have found nothing.
Chidambaram,
frisk everyone present here.
You both go that side, you both
come here. Don't spare anyone.
Stand in line.
Subramanium, don't do anything.
Give me the cuffs.
Hey, you can't arrest our brother.
Hey!
Police are arresting Subramanium.
They are arresting our brother!
We have to stop them. Come on.
Son!
You can't come. Stay right there.
Hurry up!
Chidambaram, what's happening now?
Madam, I guess we can't move the
vehicle even an inch from here.
Ma'am, they won't listen unless
Subramanium asks them.
Subramanium, you would be
responsible for any bloodbath here.
Think about it.
Enough of theatrics. Get up now.
Look. You are my family.
What respect will I have if
my family is lying on the roads?
Listen to your Subramanium, get up.
Do not cause any ruckus. Do not stop
the festivities we started.
They can't do anything.
They are not arresting me. I am
going with them as per my will.
Subramanium should be released!
- Yes!
Yes! Release him!
If this continues like this,
how will we take him to court?
Hey! They have taken brother
Subramanium this way.
He is not inside.
Hey! Your hero is not here.
As per the court's warrant,
we have shifted him
to a different station.
Everyone leave from here.
Now,
for the festival to be celebrated
and the people's life to be saved
find out where Subramanium is.
So you think that I have relocated
your Subramanium from here.
But I believe that you have
influenced and taken him from here.
You know what happened
when we arrested him.
Protection warrant.
With your cooperation, we have
to take Subramanium to Chittoor.
You may have arrested him
but if someone has taken Subramanium
from your custody,
then it's a part of a very big plan.
Please, madam.
Please find our Subramanium
at any cost.
I beg of you.
Hello.
- Sir, what's happening here?
Did you intentionally make me
do all this?
If this is the case, the situation
is going to be chaotic.
Let it be, Kiranmay.
Things will go accordingly.
Give me the information now. Yeah.
Thanks, madam.
Rajamanikyam, it's me.
Listen to me carefully.
Yes. Tell me, brother.
Subramanium has been arrested.
Hello, Manju.
- What happened?
Get to work.
Brother, there is an emergency!
Arun, I am Palani speaking.
We found the location of the lion's
cage. It's time to hunt.
I will start.
Hello!
Sir, I am ASI Shekhar speaking.
Sir, as we thought, Subramanium
is not any petty criminal.
All the families
of the policemen who arrested him,
are in their control.
Gangsters from all the big states
are involved in this.
Even the home minister's family
has been abducted.
Hey, stop it!
Release him immediately.
- What happened, sir?
Take care of what more they want.
Hello.
- Sir, I am SP speaking.
I don't think you know well
about this Subramanium, sir.
What are you talking about?
Do what the minister has asked you
to do.
Break his limbs and
then hand him over to me.
Sir, if I disobey you,
the maximum I will lose is my job.
He has abducted families of all the
people involved in this operation.
Including the family of that
minister you are talking about.
Sir, I want to say something
for your own good.
Hide as soon as possible, sir.
Hey, what are you talking about?
I am asking you to live.
Singaru!
- Brother.
Ask everyone to get ready.
We won't spare him.
Okay, brother.
(Chanting)
The ritual has started
with Subramanium chants.
All hail, Lord Murgan! Harom Hara!
Hey!
This is...
Dad, I am here.
Let's go to the hospital.
My son...
- Dad.
I made a mistake.
I thought weapons are used
to kill the innocent people.
If I had a gun,
I could have saved many lives here.
- Yes, dad.
You are right.
- If the strong require a weapon
then it serves as strength
for the weak.
Son, you should not
stop your work.
Okay, dad.
Don't stop it.
I will do that, dad.
"Your blood challenges."
"Show them your rage."
Hey, Subramanium.
What are you doing?
Where are you planning to go alone?
You can't go alone.
I will come along with you.
I have lost enough lives.
Nobody should lose their life
for me in this village,.
I can't live with that.
Listen. Are you planning
to wage a war with this?
I won't say anything.
It's time for action.
Rajendra, he abducted Sharad
from the hospital and challenged us
to a war.
Hey!
Hey! Shoot him down.
Stop it. Stop it!
He is out of the range.
Hey! Move closer and shoot him down.
Hey, shoot him.
Lie down, everyone. Lie down!
Hey! You, go.
Boss,
he has buried something underneath.
Come.
Where is brother?
Your husband is there.
Devi! No!
Come here.
You will be okay.
Go from here.
"It's the start of destruction."
"It's time to end evil."
What harm did my father do to you?
What harm did
those people do to you?