RANI
Everyone looks at me in wonder
As I call out your name, day and night
My happiness knows no bounds
Sparks of desire fly everywhere
Fly everywhere
As our eyes meet
A fire comes alight
And in its flames
My poor heart melts
As our eyes meet
A fire comes alight
And in its flames
My poor heart melts
DINESH PANDIT
WRATH OF KASAULI
He is naughty yet a bit naive
The guy is so very naive
I too feel some sparks within me
Sparks light up within
My heart flutters when I see him
But I'm confused if he's hot or not
Hot or not
My heart leads me
Here and there
It knows not what it wants
Everything gleams and shines
The girl is nice
The guy is crooked
A bunch of lies
Oh, ho, ho
The guy is naive
The girl is sly
And therefore it's a
No, no, no
As our eyes meet
A fire comes alight
And in its flames
My poor heart melts
Who switched off the lights?
7 A.M.
TEA
UGVN LIMITED
ELECTRICITY DEPARTMENT - CHILA
Even though we are together
You feel so distant
As we can't express our feelings
We remain silent
Or bicker all the time
Words of love remain unspoken
Do I convince her
Or convince myself
How do I change our fate?
Now I leave
Everything to fate
Everything, I leave
To destiny
DINESH PANDIT
WRATH OF KASAULI
Oh
Days go by
And night begins
All night
I pace around my home
Pace around
Oh
I close my eyes
And hide my tears
How do I change our fate?
Now I leave
Everything to fate
Everything, I leave
To destiny
And abandon us
Now I leave
Everything to fate
Everything, I leave
To destiny
Now I leave
Everything to fate
Everything, I leave
To destiny
DINESH PANDIT
HORROR OF LUST
She has stolen my heart
From afar
I've been feeling this love
For some time now
To her I bestow
Every moment of my life
She's the reason for my being
She is my world
She is magical
My heart says to me
Slip away
My mind says to me
Drift away
My heart says to me
Slip away
Oh, I don't know what is right
Or wrong
This fever of love
Surges within me
Oh, I don't know who is friend
Or foe
This wave of joy
Has saved me
As I dive
Into the depths
She comes closer
Closer to me
Longing to touch her
Waiting for that moment
She is my reason
She is my refuge
She is everywhere
My heart says to me
Slip away
My mind says to me
My heart says to me
Slip away
My mind says to me
Drift away
Slip away
RANI
Stop!
OFFICE OF JWALAPUR INSPECTOR GENERAL
JWALAPUR TO DELHI
All that happened, is in the past
These new moments
Let us cherish them
Slowly
With you
My days are happy again
These precious dreams of mine
I give to you
Come and see them
Our lives
Have come together
And everything is bright again
You've come to me
Like we've never been apart
Love has blossomed
Like things were never amiss
You are mine
May the fragrance of your love
Now be mine
Your eyes speak a thousand words
Your heart beats
Together with mine
I feel alive
My destiny
Lies in your hands
We will never be apart
Let me give you
Many new reasons
To smile
You've come to me
Like we've never been apart
Love has blossomed
Like things were never amiss
You are mine
- Wrath of Kasauli.
RANI
SIGNATURE
OFFICE OF JWALAPUR INSPECTOR GENERAL
DINESH PANDIT
WRATH OF KASAULI
Your tears are the reason for my sorrows
Your happiness, I owe to you
Every inch of my being
Says that
We write our own story
We are our destiny
We only have each other
Sorrows are gone
Happiness is ours
We've made it together at last
You've come to me
Like we've never been apart
Love has blossomed
Like things were never amiss
You are mine
DINESH PANDIT
WRATH OF KASAULI
RANI
DINESH PANDIT
WRATH OF KASAULI