-I’m waiting for instructions.
-I have a clear shot.
-What the fuck are you doing?
-There are fucking snipers!
-On your knees!
-They’re aiming.
-Give me the go.
-They’re going to execute them.
They’re going to shoot.
Put the gun down!
They’re going to kill them.
Open fire.
-Condor three, open fire.
-Behind you!
SATURDAY
06:00 P.M.
Good! Good, Mr Torres. Good. Very good.
But now let’s change the series, okay?
Let’s change the letter, all right?
Another country. Don’t complain. Come on.
Helsinki! Get downstairs! Hurry!
-What do we have?
-He’s seriously injured. Hurry up!
You killed her, motherfuckers!
Hurry up.
Water, please.
-Water, please.
-Water.
Thanks. Arturo, hold on tight. Rio!
Alcohol.
I need you to take his hand off...
Raquel.
Ex-employees of the Royal Mint
have revealed the identity
of the man wounded by the police.
It’s Arturo Roman,
the general manager of the Royal Mint,
who was just injured
by the police forces
while on the roof with the robbers.
These events took place
32 hours into the heist.
HOUR 32 OF THE HEIST
I need to talk to my wife, please.
I need to talk to my wife.
They say that when we’re at Death’s door,
we’re finally able
to see our life clearly.
And Arturo Roman, losing blood on a table,
was waiting for that: Death's wisdom...
to find out once and for all
who the love of his life had been.
Laura, the woman he had shared
14 years of holy matrimony with?
Or Monica, his secretary and lover,
who made him feel young?
Unfortunately, the only certainty
Arturo had at that moment
was that,
if they didn’t getthe bullet out,
he’d croak before solving the enigma.
And, frankly, our first aid courses
weren’t guaranteed to save anyone.
Inferior vena cava.
Right renal vein.
Left.
Mesenteric.
Right pulmonary vein. Left.
This is the heart.
The cava.
Subclavian, right and left.
Brachial.
Humeral.
Internal jugular.
External jugular.
And the main arteries in red.
Hey, stop.
Let’s see.
You want us to learn medical science
with two markers?
If anyone is shot,
he can't go to a hospital.
You have to manage inside.
-It’ll be suicide.
-Shut the fuck up.
It's one thing to lock ourselves
in that death trap.
-It's another to kill each other.
-Denver.
We’re asking you to learn
how to take out a bullet.
-Don’t be dramatic.
-It’s not that hard.
Use the tweezers
without fucking anything else up.
The shot already fucked it up.
If they shoot me, take me to the hospital.
The answer is no.
Well, I prefer being crippled and free
over being healthy in prison.
Nobody leaves.
Each of you is a clue that can be used.
If somebody wants out, now is the time.
You'll stay here until the heist is over.
Is this lesson long?
My dick's shrinking like Helsinki’s.
Hey! What did you say about my dick?
-Enough.
-Do you want to see it?
Please.
Come on, get dressed.
Give someone else a turn.
-Mr. Dick.
-Come on.
-No?
-Well, there we go.
-Well...
-Come on, Nairobi.
-It’s all right.
-Come on, Nairobi!
So sexy!
Go on. Let’s see what you've learned.
This is the carotid...
And so, while playing doctor,
I found out Nairobi was
more interesting than she seemed.
The heart.
The aorta...
Nobody knew anythingabout anyone...
Abdominal aorta.
...but I never suspected
Nairobi had a son...
or a daughter...
as it seemed by her C-section scar.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
-What are you looking at?
-Calm down.
I'm gonna shove that down her throat.
She’s a lesbian. I don’t know
what the fuck she’s looking at.
You’re the lesbian. Your bean
was as hard as a sugar cube.
Sugar cube? I’m going to...
Stop it!
And that’s where our friendship started.
Raquel, the Ministry's on the phone.
What should I tell them?
-Raquel! What should I say?
-Pardon?
They’re asking who gave the order.
I gave the order.
Tell them... the wounded man is a hostage.
-And hang up the fucking phone!
-He looked like a robber.
I asked for the green light. I insisted.
Inspector, I take responsibility too.
Inspector, the ambulance is ready.
Let’s talk to the robber.
Preparing to contact the robber.
We had to make a decision.
It seemed like they’d execute them.
Silence, please!
Professor?
You shot at the hostages.
One is near death.
I guess that’s why you’re calling.
I have an ambulance for the injured man.
Nobody’s leaving here.
-That man is bleeding out.
-From the bullet you shot.
You're going to let him die?
Let me get a medical team in there.
Professor, listen.
I know it was my mistake,
but if a hostage dies, it’ll be
as awful for you as it'll be for me.
Believe me. In less than five minutes,
the public will know
that man died because you didn’t
let us come in and save his life.
Two surgeons and a nurse
with surgical equipment.
-Let me know when they arrive.
-Thanks.
I also have something to ask you.
-The man wants to talk to his wife.
-Of course.
Jesus.
Find Mr. Roman’s wife.
How soon can a medical team get here?
By helicopter from La Paz,
in ten to 15 minutes.
-Bring them here. Now!
-Okay.
Excuse me.
Can you drive?
-Yes.
-I need to go for a ride.
-Thanks.
Hey, Raquel.
What’s up?
I have to think.
Drive.
Don’t look at me like that.
I’m not leaving you alone.
Where the fuck is she?
That bitch escaped!
Let’s see...
I’m coming.
There we go.
What's going on?
Are you able to come over tonight?
-I don’t know, Mom.
-Why? Did something happen?
Mom, it’s...
I’m...
I madea huge mistake at work.
Honey, your job is really difficult.
Tell me about it.
Things don't seem so serious
after you talk about them.
I was drinking wine with...
That's nice. With who? Do I know him?
No, Mom. I don’t know him either.
The thing is...
When I went back to the tent,
there was a very serious situation,
a risky one,
on the roof of the Royal Mint and...
I thought one of the hostages
was in danger, so I gave...
the order to shoot.
And an innocent man was shot.
-Yes. I saw it on TV, honey.
-Now I don’t know what to do.
I don’t know whether to call his wife,
give a press conference, resign...
I don’t know what to do, Mom.
Well, first of all, relax
and don’t blame yourself.
They all have masks and guns,
confined, all mixed together.
You only wanted
to protect the hostages, right?
Honey, what if you saved somebody’s life?
You wouldn’t be calling me, would you?
Well...
and then...
I wouldn’t know you like to meet
and have drinks with strangers.
God! I don’t meet strangers.
Honey, we have
so little time in this life...
Okay, Mom,
but that’s not the issue now.
The issue is
I’m in a critical situation at work.
Honey, screw that job.
Why don’t you tell them
you want to stamp passports?
Maybe you'll have some fun. Heavens!
Or do you think you’ll end up
holding hands with the robber
in a retirement home?
You won’t, honey.
But maybe with that stranger...
Don’t laugh.
I knowwhat I’m talking about.
I’ve been a widow for 20 years and...
Time doesn’t stop, honey.
It doesn’t go backwards either, you know?
Entering the perimeter.
I’ll think about it, Mom.
Don't wait up for me, all right?
Fine.
Listen, you go to bedwith someone too.
RAQUEL LIKES A STRANGER
-What the fuck do you want?
-I don’t know. I saw that earlier and...
And it got my attention.
I didn’t know what it was.
Sorry.
Okay, I forgive you.
Okay, see you later.
What are you doing?
Beat it. I don’t want to chitchat.
How old is he?
Your son.
Seven.
He’s seven.
Where's he?
With his father?
No, he’s never been around.
We don’t know anything about his father.
What’s his name?
Axel.
His name’s Axel.
It means axe.
-Axe.
-Yes.
And he’s an ace.
Just like his mother.
That kid's a survivor, you know?
He's survived everything.
He’s like a cork in the middle of the sea.
He doesn’t sink.
That’s the way he is.
When he was three...
I had to take him from my mother’s house
because her husband...
gave him anisette when I wasn’t there,
because his crying bothered him.
So I left with him.
Just the two of us.
We didn't need a family.
Me and him.
And we were fucking great.
But I screwed it up.
One day...
I had to go get pills to sell.
And...
And I left him alone.
For five minutes.
It was just five minutes.
And he caused a scene
as fucking Spider-Man. Damn Spider-Man!
Because he wanted to be a superhero.
He climbed everywhere.
He climbed very well.
He went out the window
and got on the balcony.
He took a chair and got up on it
and shouted, "Mommy!"
He was three and a half.
Sure enough, five minutes later,
we had the police, firemen...
everyone.
They caught me with the pills,
with a record,
without a job.
I went to jail.
So my child started moving
from one foster family to the next.
And I got nothing.
Nothing, huh?
I wasn’t allowed
a single visit, a single call...
Nothing.
Then I was released...
and nothing happened.
They didn’t give him back to me.
-Have you seen him since?
-They won’t let me.
But...
I know where he is.
-Really?
-He’s in the Canary islands.
He’s with a family who owns a hotel.
He’s fine.
Are you going to go and get him?
I’m taking him...
and that’s it.
To the other side of the world.
I'll tell you something.
In this heist,
nobody’s going to screw up,
not me or anyone else.
If somebody screws up,
I’ll destroy their life.
Out of all the plans everyone has,
yours...
is the best.
And let me tell you something else.
Do you like tequila?
It’s 4:03 am.
We have class very early.
Plastic explosives.
Sorry.
It’d be great
if you were well rested for class.
-We couldn’t sleep.
-Go to bed.
-The three of us together?
-In our own beds.
Those pajamas look
really good on you, Professor.
Now.
And you... And you with the lights.
That guy really turns me on. Really.
-He really turns me on!
-Really? I can’t tell at all.
You can't tell?
-A lot.
-Let him notice.
What a headache, man!
Jesus...
Monica. Hey...
-What are you doing here? Are you crazy?
-I wasn’t feeling well.
I think the medication made me sick.
Medication?
That'll do it. Yes, child. That’ll do it.
Oh, my, you’re burning up.
She has to get the hell out of here.
-I’ll help you.
-Wait.
-Could I be alone for a minute?
-Yes.
Please.
What do you think?
She’s not feeling very well.
She looks bad.
If we don’t take that bullet out,
she’s fucked.
Dad, calm down, all right?
She’ll be fine.
Why did you fucking shoot her?
Because Berlin was going to kill her.
I had no other choice.
Son of a bitch.
If he wants to kill someone,
he should pull the trigger, not you.
We came for a robbery.
Not to kill people or save lives.
We’re fucking idiots.
-Of all the people--
-Dad, calm down.
Calm down.
Monica, are you finished yet?
Yes.
-Let’s go.
-Raquel, wait a second.
I want to talk to you.
I want to go in with the medical team.
No. Somebody’s going in, but not you.
Sure. There’s always
someone better than me for everything.
Raquel, I’m a firearms expert.
I can go in and know, at a glance,
how many, what type, and if they’re fake.
We could figure out who the robbers are.
You’re right.
You’ll go with the doctors and cover them.
Now let me tell you what we’re doing.
I heard a shot earlier.
The police. They shot a hostage.
-A hostage?
-Yes.
Who?
Who did they shoot?
The manager.
Arturo?
Did the police kill Arturo?
No. They didn’t kill him.
-Is he okay?
-Yes.
Is he alive?
-Is Arturo okay?
-He’s fine. Yes.
-Are you sure?
-Sure.
-Is he okay?
-A surgeon is coming in with his team.
They'll operate and save him.
-They're going to operate?
-Yes.
You have to tell him I’m alive.
You have to tell Arturo.
-Do you hear me?
-Nobody is saying anything.
Because you’ll be fine
and he will too, okay?
Let’s have a look at the wound.
Calm down.
He is going to blame himself.
He asked me to get the phone,
and he'll think I'm dead because of him.
You have tell him I’m alive, okay?
And his son too.
You're pregnant?
Very well.
Congratulations.
-Give me a pen, please.
-Okay.
When?
Thanks.
Angel!
I’ve decided we should go in.
I'll use the medical team to do it.
I cherish these decisions you make
on ambulance rides.
I'm only here
to fulfill the wishes of the government.
and avoid a violent outcome.
Wow!
The CNI officer
has suddenly become a pacifist.
Weren’t you the one
who wanted to bring in tanks?
I wanted to surprise them.
Finish this quickly.
But now the priority is
to have zero victims.
So I advise you to negotiate and wait.
It must suck being here all day
thinking you’re the best,
yet unable to make any decisions.
Like being on a hostage crisis talk show.
Inspector, I’m not going to fall for that,
because I understand that,
at a certain age, hormones take over.
-I know because of my mother.
-Where are you going?
You know, I have to report
all this, right?
Of course.
So far, the robbers
have always been ahead of us.
Everything was planned. Except this shot.
It’s the first thing not in the plan.
And we must take advantage.
The only way to get in
without being detected by their cameras
is to move along this underground tube
that leads straight to the basement.
It’s the ventilation pipe.
It was added seven months ago
to release heat from the presses.
It’s a work in progress.
They probably don’t know it’s there.
I need two of your men
to go through there.
Officer Garcia Lobo, here,
and I’ll go with him.
Fine.
Deputy Inspector Rubio
will go with the two surgeons as a nurse.
It's 6:09 p.m.
Let's synchronize our watches.
At 06:15 p.m.,
the medical team will go in.
The surgery
shouldn’t take more than 30 minutes.
But they can keep going
until exactly 7:00 p.m.
When the doctors leave,
a lot of the robbers will be watching.
That’s when Suarez and Lobo
enter through the underground pipe.
They’ll arrive in the basement
dressed in red jumpsuits and Dalí masks.
They’ll become hostages.
This will only be successful
if done like clockwork.
Inspector?
Arturo Roman’s wife is here.
One moment, please.
Suarez, get moving.
Take care of the doctors. And be careful.
Get the operation ready!
What happened? Is my husband okay?
He's conscious and stable.
He was shot by mistake.
-Shot? What do you mean?
-He’s injured, but alive.
Calm down.
The robbers are letting
a surgical team go in
and they'll help him right away.
Sorry, but...
I wasn’t even listening. Sorry.
Calm down.
Everything’s gonna be all right.
-Sit down, please.
-Thanks.
-You can talk to him right now.
-Yes.
Take this.
Almansa, record!
We have to take that bullet out right now.
You do it, Dad.
You’re less nervous.
Where’s the surgical kit
the Professor gave us?
-There’s a scalpel in there.
-Berlin has it.
Fuck.
It’s not a good idea to ask him for it.
The surgeons!
Go and get one from them. Hurry.
Okay.
Wait!
Give him the note, please.
I’ll clean the wound now, okay?
Relax. You’re going to be fine, okay?
-Hello?
-Professor, Arturo Roman’s wife is here.
Arturo.
What’s your wife’s name?
Laura.
A beautiful name. You can talk to Laura.
Wives are good for moments like these.
They’re comforting.
Nobody remembers their wife
when they're at a club
in the middle of a bender,
If you have a problem, an accident,
or... you’re simply scared,...
things change.
Are you thinking
about your secretary right now?
Yeah?
No.
Who has time to think about a lover
who is about to abort your baby?
-Or just nothing?
-Spare me the speech.
Listen to me.
If you say anything, I’ll finish you
and your wife will hear it live.
Imagine that.
Inspector.
They’re turning on a phone.
We have to tap that phone.
I want to see the selfie and main cameras.
There.
Hello, darling.
Arturo, darling, how are you?
Fine. I’m fine.
"It was a clean shot...
-There’s no image.
No selfie or main cameras.
They covered them.
They’re letting some surgeons in.
I know.
Look, I’ve...
I’ve been thinking about you and...
and everything we did wrong.
Don’t think about it, darling. Not now.
Not now.
Besides, it’s my fault.
I know we’re not fine.
We haven’t been fine for some time.
I neglected you and our children.
I’ve been selfish.
I promise that’s all going to change.
I promise that’s going to change.
You’ve beensaying for ten years
you want to see your sister in Australia.
That it could be
a chance for the kids to learn English
and see kangaroos.
That’s the first thing
we’ll do when I get out.
I owe you that.
I’ll do it for you.
Because I love you so much.
All these years wasted, chasing...
thinking all that mattered
was money and status and...
But all that matters is you.
It’s always been you.
Since the day I met you.
I swear there are times when...
I try to remember that day...
and I wonder
what the hell you saw in me, Monica.
Laura.
Just concentrate on getting out.
Just think about that.
I love you.
I love you, honey.
Laura, are you okay?
Calm down.
You’re a real expert, Arturo.
Your secretary... with the belly...
Laurita waiting for you
in the 4x4 with the children.
You're surrounded by money.
You're a legend.
Berlin. The doctors are outside.
You must excuse me.
Does everyone know what to do?
They do. Of course they do.
Are you ready?
Okay, they’re ready.
Mercedes!
Are you ready?
Yes, sir.
I want her out of here.
Rio, take her to an office.
Nairobi.
Put on your masks!
Come with me! Rock and roll!
Come in.
Leave everything on the floor.
Close the doors.
Move forward.
Hands on your head and legs apart.
We’re going to frisk you.
Get him out of here, please.
Listen carefully.
One of the nurses is an undercover cop.
-Which one?
-The one with glasses.
You know what to do.
-Perfectly. Let’s get to it.
-Berlin!
It has to be fucking precise work.
I know.
Guys, the man with glasses is the cop.
They’ll go in.
Maybe during an attack
or an emergency...
It could be a Red Cross guy
or the pizza guy,
but they will surely
try to infiltrate someone.
And that will be our chance
to try and sneak in a Trojan horse.
Do you know what that is?
-I don’t, but it reminds me of something.
-No!
-The Trojan horse...
-Condoms!
Shut up and focus. Jesus!
Sorry.
I’m sorry.
The Greeks were at war with the Trojans.
One day the Trojans found,
in front of their city,
a wooden horse, a huge wooden horse.
And, arrogantly, they thought it was
from the Greeks to say they surrender.
So they opened the gates...
and they brought it in.
But they didn’t know
that horse was hollow...
and full of Greek warriors.
That night, the Trojans lost the war.
And that’s exactly what we're going to do.
When they try to enter...
thinking they’re winning the battle...
Leave all your metallic objects
on that tray.
Glasses.
Watches.
If you have weapons,
microphones,
I also advise you leave them there.
We’re going to track
any type of radio frequency.
Take off your shoes too, please.
And now lie down.
On the ground.
That's it.
Like cockroaches.
Stand up.
Put on your shoes.
Take only the glasses.
You’re going to need them.
Now, yes...
Welcome.
Take your things and come with me.
Thanks.