View47.com - Watch Free Movies Online
You think you know
the truth about him?
You know nothing.
His father was Zeus. The Zeus.
King of the gods.
His mother,
alcmene, a mortal woman.
Together, they had a boy.
Half human,
half God.
But Zeus' queen, hera,
saw this bastard
child as an insult,
a living reminder of
her husband's infidelity.
Alcmene named
the boy Hercules,
which means "glory of hera,"
but this failed to
appease the goddess.
She wanted him dead.
Luckily,
he took after his father.
Once he reached manhood,
the gods commanded him
to perform twelve labors,
twelve dangerous missions.
If he completed
them all and survived,
hera agreed to finally
let him live in peace.
He fought the lernean hydra!
He battled
the erymanthean boar!
But his greatest labor
was the nemean lion.
This was no ordinary beast.
It had a hide so tough,
no weapon could penetrate it.
But even this
monster was no match
for the son of Zeus.
What a load of crap!
Every word is true.
You know what I think?
This friend of yours
doesn't even exist.
Laugh all you want.
He's coming.
And be warned, gryza,
he despises pirates.
Macedonia has been good to us.
Plenty of villages
ripe for pillaging.
We are here to stay.
Finish him.
The more you struggle,
the faster you drop.
Indeed, your fleet is strong.
I...
Yet, as I was about to explain
before I was so
rudely interrupted,
the nemean lion
was strong, too.
Yet, he still destroyed it.
And not with a sword
or a spear or arrows. No!
I did it with my bare hands!
Or so they say.
Hercules.
Is this all the men you have?
There's 40 of us. One of you.
The king of this land
has offered me gold
to dispose of you.
So leave, or die.
I get paid either way.
Make him bleed.
Five men with a single blow.
Still think you can destroy
the son of Zeus?
Bring me his head!
Seems they need
more convincing, autolycus.
That's why we're here.
Atalanta.
Amphiaraus.
May Zeus forgive you.
Tydeus?
Die, Hercules!
Ah, good man.
Hurry!
Hurry! Uncle!
Uncle, hurry!
Hurry! Hurry!
Any longer, Uncle...
And the girls
would finally be safe
from your attentions.
The rest of you may go.
But not you.
Thirteen,
14, 15, 16,
- 17, 18, 19, 20.
- That was fun.
Twenty pirates
at two gold pieces a head,
minus the headless ones.
Let's see.
Not a bad night.
You see how the pirates ran?
My story
softened their resolve.
Their resolve must
be broken, iolaus.
When you spread
the legend of Hercules,
make it bigger, scarier.
The more they believe
Hercules is truly
the son of Zeus,
the less likely
they are to fight.
Oh!
Aye.
- Amphiaraus?
- Mmm?
Care to join us here on earth?
A lion and a crow in strange
alliance, fighting across
a sea of corpses.
If you're going
to use those herbs,
amphiaraus, at least share.
Huh?
Hold it!
Hold it! Hold it! Hold it!
Fight it!
Keep practicing, boys!
So who's next? You? You?
Ah!
That's a pretty sight.
One more payday, autolycus,
that's all we need.
Then we get to live like
the kings we've served.
Or live simply.
You still dreaming
of barbarian lands?
Beyond the aegean.
At the shores
of the black sea.
That is where I will live out
the rest of my
days in solitude.
Boring, if you ask me.
Maybe so, autolycus.
But I'll never find peace
unless I move as far
away as possible.
What of tydeus?
Without you to
temper his rage,
I fear what he may become.
Tydeus will go with me.
Civilization has become
too civilized for us.
Uncle!
Join us.
The girls are
eager to welcome you.
See?
I told you I knew Hercules.
Are you his servant?
I'm his nephew.
Are you, really?
I tell of
Hercules' twelve labors,
like the nemean lion,
the apples of the hesperides,
the belt of hippolyta
with its buxom naked Amazons
and exciting bondage.
-I immortalize him...
-He talks,
while the rest of us fight.
It is a wonder
you share the same
blood as Hercules.
Have fun.
- Ladies.
- Oh...
What do you
want with Hercules?
My words are for him, not you.
Atalanta, it's all right.
You certainly are
a hard man to find.
Maybe I don't want
anyone to find me.
I'm not just anyone.
My name is ergenia,
daughter to lord cotys.
Your father is most fortunate
to have such a beautiful heir.
My father is most unfortunate.
He battles a warlord, rhesus.
Our land is torn by civil war.
Every day, villages are
destroyed, crops ruined,
innocents slaughtered.
We all have problems.
Well, perhaps I can
convince you to make
our problems your own.
Unfortunately, my lady,
Hercules is fully committed
till the feast of dionysus.
We could, however,
advance you to
the front of the line,
for the right price.
Hmm.
I thought heroes
fight for glory.
But mercenaries
fight for gold.
Lord cotys is a rich man.
I like him already.
If you agree to aid him,
he will pay your
weight in gold.
Eat up.
"A lion and crow in
strange alliance."
Told you.
Where are we going?
It is good to see
you safe, my lady.
This war claims
more victims every day.
We were concerned, my lady.
Thank you, general sitacles.
I was well protected.
Ah.
The mighty Hercules. An honor.
Though not quite
as big an honor
as I expected.
General, go tell my father
Hercules is here.
Uncle? Hera. Impressive.
It's meant to be.
It took five years
and a thousand men
to build her temple.
Hera is the patron
goddess of thrace.
Everyone knows the legend,
how hera seeks to
destroy Hercules.
Perhaps the right cause
might finally reconcile you.
Mother!
Arius.
- You're Hercules.
- That's right.
My name is arius.
I know all your
labors by heart.
You killed the giant geryon
with a single blow,
cleaned the augean stables
in one night.
Hercules is probably tired.
And the labor of the hide,
and the labor of the mares.
- That's enough, arius.
Come along.
Stay away from him.
Men who deal in violence
attract violence.
But he's Hercules.
He's no mere mortal.
He's the greatest!
Lord cotys will see you now.
Have you ever met royalty,
Hercules?
Once or twice.
- Father!
- Ah!
Megara.
Welcome home, my love.
Hercules!
Whenever I'm here,
I imagine this is what
elysium must look like.
Well, men like us
have the means
to create our own
paradise on earth.
Look.
Magnificent, aren't they?
Well, do not keep us
in suspense. Are we safe
from the monster hydra?
The hydra's heads,
your majesty.
The masks of serpents.
No wonder men thought
they were monsters.
You've done your sovereign
a great service. Come.
Let the people
have their hero.
All hail king eurystheus.
And the mighty
protector of Athens,
Hercules!
Hercules! Hercules! Hercules!
A man faced with such
adoration might be tempted
to think himself a God.
I only want to be
a husband and a father.
Lord cotys awaits.
Hercules.
Welcome.
An honor to
host such a legend.
Lord cotys.
But in legend, you fight alone.
My reputation would not exist
without my comrades.
Autolycus of sparta.
Tydeus of thebes.
Atalanta of scythia.
Iolaus of Athens.
And amphiaraus of argos.
Amphiaraus?
The famed seer of argos.
It is said you have glimpsed
your own death,
so you fight each battle
knowing that it is not yet
your time to die.
What else can you
tell of the future?
Only what the gods
see fit to reveal.
A shame.
It would have been
a great gift to know
the outcome of this war.
The gods can be
frustrating sometimes,
lord cotys.
With respect, I fear tha
t the task ahead might not be
suitable for a woman,
even if she is
an Amazon warrior.
I stand corrected.
When the kings of yesteryear
built this citadel,
it was intended as
the high seat of all thrace.
But now thrace is divided.
This war has
depleted our forces.
We're left with nothing
but farmers and merchants
to replenish our army.
It takes every one of us
to resist rhesus.
People think that
he cannot be killed
by an ordinary mortal.
Only by a God.
Rhesus is a sorcerer.
His magic words confuse men,
bend them to his will.
He leads an army of monsters,
half horse, half human.
Centaurs?
- You've actually seen them?
- They have been seen.
Come, Hercules.
Let me show you what misery
rhesus has brought us.
Every week,
more refugees arrive
seeking my protection,
most of them covered
in blood, crippled or
burnt by rhesus' men.
I feared nothing could ever
be good again,
till you arrived.
I'm just
a mercenary fighting for gold.
How we view ourselves
is of little consequence.
How others
perceive us is important.
And your name, like it or not,
is a rallying cry.
I have seen too much reality
to trust in legends,
and I am not alone.
Nobody has any faith anymore.
The people need a hero.
They need
someone to look up to.
My son believes in you.
Bring us peace,
and I will
believe in you, too.
I'm convinced
these are good people.
I see.
And who's more convincing,
cotys or his daughter?
All the gold on earth is not
as convincing as
a pair of breasts.
Maybe, but gold never ages.
Which is why
I got them to
double our price.
Double your weight in gold?
Well done.
Amphiaraus?
If it be the will of Zeus.
Which title
sounds more terrifying
to our enemies?
Savior of thrace"
A legend is born"?
Both sound
terrifyingly boring.
What are we supposed to do
with an army of farmers?
Train them.
Oh, shit.
In war, there is one thing
more important than killing.
Surviving.
My companions
and I will show you
how to stay alive,
so that you may return home
to your farms someday.
Autolycus.
Shield wall! Form!
Corpses!
Every last one of you!
Because your
shield wall was weak.
Dead.
Very dead.
Soldier,
many lives depend on you.
When attacked,
lock your feet in the ground.
You understand?
Yes, sir.
When a shield wall is strong,
nothing can ever defeat it!
You must learn
to work together,
react together.
When you do, each individual
will become a link in a chain
that will be
stronger than iron.
I hope the enemy
has a sense of humor.
Right. Today's lesson,
how not to stab yourselves!
It is imperative that
we strike now, my lord,
given this opportunity.
Ah! There you are!
Hercules,
my scouts have brought news.
Rhesus is on the move.
Archers who shoot lightning
from their bows.
And infantry 4,000-strong,
their minds bewitched.
Demons march with them.
So now we're fighting demons.
No stranger than the monsters
I hear you faced, Hercules.
My lord, rhesus is preparing
to attack bessi lands.
He will be on
them within six days.
If the bessi fall, we're next.
Unless we intercept him.
Your men need weeks,
if not months, of training
before they're ready.
The bessi are a fierce
but primitive tribe.
If we do not protect them,
then there will
be a bloodbath.
Face rhesus with
an untrained army
and you risk losing
far more than a single battle.
My lord, rhesus is coming.
I vouch my life on it.
The longer rhesus lives,
the more villages will
be burnt and the more
innocents will be killed.
Assemble your men.
We march tomorrow.
Hercules,
the gods have
offered us a gift.
We must not squander it.
Are your gods going to
be fighting with us?
No.
The son of Zeus will.
I've seen how you
watch over Hercules.
Tell me,
how did a woman,
beautiful woman,
fall in with
these hardened men?
Killers?
Son of Zeus need
a woman's protection?
I don't protect him.
I protect you from him.
Hmm.
General, from now on,
maybe you should favor
the company of your men.
He pulled a knife?
It was only a small prick.
Ah!
Your mother told
you to stay away.
You should listen.
What's wrong with him?
Tydeus is my
most loyal warrior.
He was born in war.
When I found him,
he was more animal than human.
He never speaks
of what he saw.
He never speaks at all.
But he relives it every night.
Come.
Let's find your mother.
When I grow up,
I want to be
a great hero like you.
Like me?
- No hero is
greater than Hercules.
I know all your labors.
Like the cretan bull,
you wrestled it for seven days
and seven nights.
Uh, that's a bit exaggerated.
-And struck it 49
times with your club.
-Maybe not quite that many.
Until it fell dead
and crete was saved.
It's my favorite labor.
Also queen hippolyta's belt,
with its buxom Amazons
and exciting bondage.
-Do you even know
what that means?
-No.
- Mother.
- Arius.
You're supposed to be in bed.
Why are you in the hospice?
My mother saves
people's lives.
Many of our physicians
were killed during battle.
So, out of necessity,
I taught myself
the art of healing.
If I could be like you,
I would protect all of thrace
and no one
would ever get hurt.
Here.
I was going to give this
to someone else,
but I never got the chance.
Only a hero may wear this.
But to become a hero,
you must grow strong.
Is this
the nemean lion's tooth?
- It is.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Good night.
Good night, Hercules.
Have no fear.
If you fall in
the service of a just cause,
your souls will go to elysium,
where they will dwell forever
among the shades of heroes,
like theseus.
Odysseus!
And the great achilles.
Or if you're lucky,
you'll go to Hades,
where all the fun people are.
Iolaus.
Your place is
beside lord cotys,
where it's safe.
I've been giving it a lot
of thought, and I really feel
I'm ready to fight.
You're a storyteller,
not a warrior.
We share the same blood.
And I will not see it shed.
Chariot.
Now.
Thracians,
the shield wall is your home.
Your shelter.
When you sleep,
the wall is your blanket.
When you fight,
the wall is your armor.
The shield wall will
never break formation
as long as there is
breath in your body.
Remember these words,
and you will taste victory.
- Move the army out!
- Move out!
Halt!
- Halt!
We are too late.
Rhesus has already been here.
Leave the chariots.
We'll go down on foot.
The lion and crow
cross a field of corpses.
I hate being
right all the time.
Halt.
- Halt!
This head is rotting.
A week old, at least.
Yet some of these
bodies are fresh.
Uncle!
And we've walked into a trap.
Shield wall! Form a single
square! Protect lord cotys!
Iolaus, go!
Shield wall!
We're here to help them.
Why are they attacking?
This is rhesus' doing.
They say his spells have
the power to cloud minds.
Turn comrades
against each other.
King's guards,
around lord cotys!
Amphiaraus,
do we die in this battle?
My time's not come yet.
Not sure about yours.
That's comforting.
I think he wants a challenge.
Hercules' fists
have been dipped
in the blood of the hydra!
Lethal to anyone but him!
Watch!
Did you see that?
The gods fight on our side!
Hercules! Hercules! Hercules!
Hercules! Hercules!
Battle position!
Lady Artemis, if I am to fall,
let me be judged...
Stand fast!
Hold your position!
Do not yield!
No retreat! Stay in the wall!
Hold the lines!
Do not yield!
Defend lord cotys!
The wall has been breached!
Seal up the shield wall!
Defend lord cotys!
Whip!
Hercules!
Bring the chariots!
Defend your lord!
No!
Advance!
Make way!
Where is rhesus?
Lord cotys.
We came here to
save this village,
but, no, they killed
half my army.
Rhesus.
This is all his doing.
And yours.
I warned you.
Your men are brave,
but untrained,
unprepared for battle.
Give me time to make warriors.
Very well.
Cover up,
before your loyal army
sees you bleed like a mortal.
Phineas.
You plead your life.
And I gladly offer it.
I failed to see this trap.
The fault is mine!
Spare the other scouts.
General sitacles.
I think we've lost enough men
for the day, don't you?
But just to avoid
future misunderstandings,
I'll be taking charge
of your scouts from now on.
Is that clear?
Thank you.
Another mistake,
I'll end you myself.
I'm applying a salve of mint,
chamomile and Clay
to seal the wound.
This is extract of
lithops for the pain,
a powerful sedative.
It should rest you after
consuming it. It may have
certain side effects.
I don't need it.
Ah, forgive me, I forgot.
No mortal can harm Hercules.
And, uh, your lion's hide
is indestructible?
Drink, son of Zeus.
Arius' father was the same,
he distrusted medicines.
Where is he now?
Taken by the gods
before my son was born.
I'm sorry.
I never knew my father.
Well, he must have been
very, very strong.
Tell me about arius.
Oh. He's a good boy.
And someday,
he will make a fine king.
Do you have any children?
Do they live in Athens?
Thank you for your care.
The sedative
will help you rest.
How could you do
such a terrible thing?
By law, I should execute you,
but I believe
a more fitting punishment
would be to let you live.
So you can walk
the earth in torment,
haunted by the knowledge
that you alone are responsible
for the death of
your loved ones.
The great Hercules.
Hands forever stained
with innocent blood.
Get out, you monster.
Get out!
No!
It happened
again, didn't it, hmm?
Another vision of Cerberus,
the three-headed
beast of Hades?
The gods show you things
they don't share with others.
There's a word for that.
Madness.
When we were
driven from Athens,
I consulted
the oracle of delphi
on your behalf.
Do you remember her prophecy?
"Hercules must
finish the labor
that remains unfinished."
And what is that, Hercules?
Confront
the beast that haunts you.
Only then will you find peace.
I speak from experience.
No matter how far you run,
no matter how fast you go,
the beast will follow.
Man cannot escape his fate.
Room for one more
in your company?
It'd be a pleasure having
female companionship
for a change.
Atalanta doesn't quite count.
No offense.
If only your manhood
was as long as your tongue.
Both can satisfy
in different ways.
You're a famed
storyteller, iolaus.
Grace me with a story.
Any particular subject,
my lady?
Murder, of a woman
and her three children.
Is it true? Did Hercules
slaughter his own family?
- Who said so?
- Oh, soldiers talk.
They say if Hercules
ever returns to Athens,
king eurystheus
will have him executed.
Hercules had
completed his labors
and returned home. But hera...
No myths. I want the truth.
No one knows the truth.
Not for sure.
We found Hercules alone.
His wife, megara and
the children, dead.
He remembers nothing.
Do you believe he is innocent?
We grew up together, both
orphans, trying to survive in
the streets of Athens.
We found a home in the army.
Looked out for each other.
Hercules'
strength set him apart.
Kings of Athens started to
send him on all the most
dangerous missions.
The twelve labors.
And he took me with him.
To fight by his side.
And with each mission,
our numbers grew.
Scythia, the Amazon kingdom
where the royal family
had been assassinated.
My family was gone.
Everyone was gone.
Hercules helped me
avenge their murder.
He became my brother-in-arms.
Thebes, the city of corpses,
where we found a single child,
still alive.
Hercules took tydeus in when
everyone else saw
nothing but a wild animal.
You know how a rumor spreads.
How a legend grows.
Hercules' deeds
were so incredible,
they could not possibly
have been
performed by a mere mortal.
So we played along.
We encourage people to think
Hercules was the son of Zeus.
It's good.
Scares the enemy.
Iolaus helps.
He talks nice.
You're very loyal friends.
You're avoiding my question.
Hercules is a warrior.
And there is something
that haunts warriors.
It can cloud their minds.
We call it the blood rage.
This rage afflicted Hercules.
He made me vow to keep
the world away from him.
To make sure that he would
never harm innocents again.
And that,
my lady, is the truth.
The truth,
Whatever the truth,
the death of his loved ones
haunts Hercules.
Only the gods can help him,
if he listens.
Come! Gather around,
soldiers of thrace,
and behold,
when Hercules gives an order,
even the gods listen.
Zeus' master ironsmith,
using the forges
of your own citadel,
has crafted
these divine weapons
that will make you invincible.
As steel is hewn into shields,
so, too, will you be
hewn into warriors.
You shall carry
the shield of Hercules!
It's lighter.
Infused with the souls
of stymphalian birds
from Hercules' sixth labor!
Spirits of birds?
How does that work, exactly?
Well, much as
birds take flight,
so, too, are these shields
lighter than air.
It's in the fibers. Here.
Try on the helmet of Hercules.
It covers my whole face.
Forged after Hercules' very
own helmet, when he
defeated the demon geryon.
You sure it wasn't your
horseshit that frightened
geryon to death?
Mmm?
General sitacles,
perhaps you
would care to inspect
the armor of Hercules?
Leather armor?
Mmm?
We will be skewered like pigs.
Linothorax.
Hewn from the skin of
the erymanthean boar.
It's indestructible.
Wait. If it's indestructible,
how did Hercules
cut it off the boar?
He used
an indestructible blade.
One, two.
Get up.
Next!
Again!
Both eyes open.
Keep practicing.
Firmer grip.
Elbow up.
Good.
Shield wall! Form!
Stand tall.
Excellent.
Careful you don't
cut yourself, boy.
Again!
Rhesus is here.
Close enough to stick
a blade between his ribs.
What did you see?
Centaurs.
Half man, half horse.
Hundreds of them.
He saw shadows in the night.
My lord, I will go ahead
into the rhesus camp.
I will bring
word of his plans.
If we let them get
past mount asticus,
thrace will fall.
You want to stop rhesus?
We'll go through the forest
and they'll
never see us coming.
It'll slow down our chariots.
A gamble.
I have a plan.
The scouts have returned.
Rhesus has made his camp
in mount asticus,
72 leagues away.
Once these men
are ready, we march.
So, have you seen
if we win or lose?
The gods have been
annoyingly silent
on that matter.
What they have told me is that
I'm soon to discover
there truly is
a heaven or a hell.
When will you die?
Within a week in a place
that looks
an awful lot like hell.
As always,
the gods are
generous with hints,
but cheap on specifics.
Cheer up, Hercules.
I've lived, not always well,
but long enough.
I'm ready for what's next.
Thracians, halt!
Shield wall! Form!
Battle positions!
Tydeus?
There is no enemy camp.
This is the right place.
Centaurs!
They're real.
It seems that we're expected.
Centaurs?
Rhesus!
You have come
looking for a fight,
and we are happy to oblige.
Hercules. The son of Zeus.
Your legend ends here.
Look at me.
Do I look afraid?
Phineas.
Traitor!
Hades will have you!
After it has you, my lord.
It is over, cotys.
Mount asticus on your front.
The woods at your back.
And my troops
outman you three to one.
Surrender now,
and we shall
consider being merciful.
Men die who speak to my lord
in such a manner.
You've made your choice.
Go!
In this moment, on this day,
become the man
you were born to be!
You have it within yourselves
to write your own legends!
Let it be to death or victory!
Charge!
Shield wall!
Flanks out!
Maybe today.
Now!
Watch as the Amazon
uses the arrows of Artemis...
Silence, boy!
Spears forward!
Archers, ready!
Loose!
Advance!
Set them aflame!
Take cover!
Defend lord cotys!
Maybe not.
Shield wall! Attack!
Push forward!
To kill a snake,
cut off its head.
Victory is yours, lord cotys!
It is not over yet!
Fucking centaurs.
Hail, lord cotys!
Halt!
Get up.
- Up.
- Enough!
You helped
a tyrant enslave a nation.
All I did was stop you
from burning more villages.
I burned no villages.
Then who did?
Ask yourself,
if cotys is beloved,
why did he need
to hire mercenaries
to do his dirty work?
Keep moving, dog.
You've been
fighting on the wrong side.
Where are you going?
I'm taking some
water to the prisoner.
Sit down.
It's time.
Thrace is finally united.
One land,
one king,
one thrace.
One land!
One king! One thrace!
Thrace is not a man,
a king, or a God!
Thrace is her people!
Who cares what rhesus claims?
Our work is done.
Let's collect our
fee and be gone.
Don't do anything foolish.
Where are you going?
I saw pity in
your eyes for rhesus.
Why?
Look at me.
Cotys is responsible
for this war, isn't he?
You lie very well. Clearly,
your father's daughter.
I didn't do it for my father.
I did it for my son.
If I disobeyed cotys or
resisted in any way,
arius would be executed.
I did what any mother would.
I protected my child.
My husband was king.
And cotys poisoned him
to take his place.
Rhesus fought back.
Civil war broke out.
Arius is the legitimate king.
My father is old.
He will not live forever,
and once he is gone,
my son will be a good king.
And he will heal this land.
That's a dream.
And you can help.
Please, when you leave thrace,
take arius with you.
Please keep him safe.
Find another savior.
Hercules?
The king
commands your presence.
My lady.
Ah, champion of thrace!
Something tells me
we're not gonna get paid.
- You could be right.
- Oh, shit.
You wanted conquerors,
not heroes.
You betrayed me, cotys.
Betrayed?
A mercenary who has long since
sold his conscience for gold
can hardly presume to
judge his employers.
Let's not
quibble about details.
We all know your legend,
Hercules.
But here is mine.
When I was a general
in the army of thrace,
I had dreams of
ruling this kingdom.
But thanks to you,
my dreams have grown.
I now crave an empire.
My thousands will
train more thousands,
and they even more.
The lessons of
Hercules will spread.
What you began here
can never be stopped.
And if you fear
what such an army may do,
then lead it.
You want me to serve you?
Spare me the moral outrage.
Child killer.
Getting us all killed,
bad idea.
Well,
I must take this as a "no."
In that case,
your services are
no longer required.
You will be paid in full.
Bring them the gold.
If we hurry,
we can be spending
our fortunes in Macedonia.
Take mine, too.
What do you
think you're doing?
Let's go.
There will be no
more innocent blood
on my hands.
I can't leave
without setting this right.
Oh, I see.
And who's gonna be paying us
for this suicidal endeavor?
Thrace needs our help.
To hell with thrace.
We have gold.
You remember the black sea.
That beach you spoke
of is within reach.
Leave now, be free.
I would never be free.
In this fight, you're alone.
Never saw that one coming.
- How can you just walk away?
- You can't just leave.
- Why not?
- It's all right.
You've sacrificed
your lives for me.
Now you can finally be free.
Whatever debt you feel
you owe me is paid.
Debt?
You think we follow you
because we owe you?
Look around, Hercules.
We're family.
All we have is each other.
We will fight for you.
And if it's our time,
we will die for you.
Because you would die for us.
Take that, too.
I have no need of it.
This is madness.
You want madness?
Tonight, a spear of flame
will Pierce my heart.
Is that not
the most insane death
you've ever heard of?
Crazy. The lot of you.
Autolycus.
Iolaus. Go with autolycus.
I think I'll stay.
Nephew.
Uncle, all I've ever done is
tell stories of great deeds
performed by others.
It's time I stopped
telling their stories.
Started living my own.
Well, you may have all
completely lost
your minds, but not me.
Not me.
Autolycus?
Live like a king, my friend.
What about cotys?
He paid us to save thrace.
Let's not disappoint him.
Lay down your arms.
Lay down your arms!
Or your nephew dies first.
I invite you to join me.
You refuse.
I order you to leave.
You return.
Get
your hands off me.
I overheard her
conspiring with Hercules.
They were planning to remove
the young prince
from your protection.
No.
Let go of him!
Don't touch him!
Arius! No!
No! You're hurting him! No!
Hercules, no!
Help me! Stop!
- Help! No!
- Arius. No.
Arius! No!
Magnificent, aren't they?
An extraordinary species.
Incredibly loyal.
As long as they're fed.
- Remember them?
- Eurystheus.
They remember you.
Confused, Hercules?
Kingdoms are won with armies,
but empires are
made by alliances.
King eurystheus and I
will now rule all of Greece.
Cerberus only
exists in my mind.
Speak a little louder,
Hercules.
I didn't quite catch that.
The wolves.
They were there that night.
The wolves were there.
You drugged me.
The wolves were there
the night my
family was murdered.
My men told me
how your children screamed
as my wolves
gnawed on their bones.
As their fangs
despoiled your daughter's
pure flesh.
When the people
called out your name
louder than mine,
you see,
when they saw you as a God,
how long before
they saw you as their king?
I wanted nothing!
Precisely! Your sin, Hercules,
was that you had no ambition!
I can deal with
an ambitious man!
He can be bought!
But a man who wants nothing
has no price!
Killing you would have
turned Athens against me.
I had to ruin your name.
My wife!
My children!
Well, you have our permission
to join them in death.
All of you!
Starting with my
faithless daughter!
No! Get off me!
No! No! No!
Unhand me! No!
She's your own
flesh and blood!
I will raise arius to be
my worthy successor!
You stay away from my boy!
You monster, you bastard!
-You are a monster!
You are a monster!
-No!
You are not a man!
You're a demon!
Who are you?
Are you a murderer?
Damn you! I curse you!
Are you a mercenary
who turns his
back on the innocent?
Stay away from my son!
Are you only the legend?
Or are you
the truth behind the legend?
No! Father,
please, please, please.
We believe in you.
We have faith in you.
Have faith in yourself.
Save me!
Remember the man
that you are.
Father,
the gods will punish you!
You cannot escape this time!
Remember the deeds
you have performed,
the labors you
have accomplished!
No! No!
- Stop it!
- Leave her alone!
Now, tell me!
Please!
Who are you?
I am Hercules!
Unleash the wolves!
Get away!
Ahh!
Three wolves should be
more than enough for one lion.
Ahh!
Hurry!
- Hurry!
No!
Ahh!
The gods have
revealed your innocence.
The final labor is complete.
But I'm just getting started.
Doesn't take a vision to know
what's waiting
for us up there.
My time.
Excuse me.
That was my moment, my fate.
You're welcome.
I'm going after eurystheus!
Hercules, listen to me.
None of this is my fault.
You see,
cotys poisoned my mind.
Turned me against you.
I like you.
No, stop.
I command you to stop!
I'm your king!
You took an oath to obey me!
You swore to Zeus!
Wait, wait, wait.
You fight for gold.
I have plenty of gold.
Name your price.
Find it in your
heart to forgive.
You want forgiveness?
Ask my family for forgiveness.
I've never
killed a God before.
I really think I'm
ready to fight now.
Well done, warrior.
- Eurystheus?
- Dead.
- We need to find arius.
- Follow me.
Soldiers of thrace!
You followed me in battle.
Follow me now.
Don't be fools!
Hercules is mortal! Not a God!
Anyone who sides
with him will die!
And I will show you.
Bring him.
- Arius!
- Mama!
No! He's your grandson!
You failed to save
your children, Hercules.
But you may yet save him.
Please, father! No!
Admit defeat!
Bow to me!
You have until
the count of three!
One!
Two!
Don't just stand there!
Kill someone!
Protect lord cotys!
Arius, run!
Mother!
Get the boy!
Ahh!
Tydeus!
Attack!
Hold them back!
Spears!
Go through the fire!
Here! Here! Help! Come on!
Easy, tydeus.
Hercules.
Lock shields!
March!
Find peace, my brother.
As you said, Hercules,
there is no way to
defeat a shield wall!
There is no way out!
Come out and face me!
You're no hero! You're no God!
You're nothing
but a mercenary!
Your wife and
children deserved to die!
What're you doing?
Get back up there!
Hercules must die!
Come on!
Kill that filthy bastard!
Hercules! Hercules!
Hercules! Hercules! Hercules!
You want to know
the truth about Hercules?
There it is.
To be honest,
I prefer it to the legend.
The world needs a hero
they can believe in.
Is he actually
the son of Zeus?
I don't think it
really matters.
You don't need to be
a demigod to be a hero.
You just need to
believe you're a hero.
It's what worked for him.
But then again,
what the hell do I know?
I'm supposed to
be dead by now.