[THUNDER RUMBLING]
IOLAUS:  You think you know
the truth about him?
[LIGHTNING CRASHING]
His father was Zeus.
The Zeus.
King of the gods.
His mother, Alcmene,
a mortal woman.
Together, they had a boy.
But Zeus' queen, Hera,
saw this bastard child
as an insult,
a living reminder
of her husband's infidelity.
Alcmene named
the boy Hercules,
which means
"glory of Hera,"
but this failed
to appease the goddess.
She wanted him dead.
[HISSING]
[CRUSHING]
[GASPS]
Luckily,
he took after his father.
Once he reached manhood,
the gods commanded him
to perform Twelve Labors,
twelve dangerous missions.
If he completed them all
and survived,
Hera agreed to finally
let him live in peace.
[ROARING]
He fought the Lernean Hydra!
[PANTING]
He battled
the Erymanthian Boar!
But his greatest Labor
was the Nemean Lion.
[LION GROWLING]
This was no ordinary beast.
[ROARS]
It had a hide so tough, no
weapon could penetrate it.
[ROARING LOUDLY]
But even this monster was no
match for the son of Zeus.
What a load of crap!
Every word is true.
[MEN LAUGHING]
[IOLAUS WHIMPERS]
GRYZA:
You know what I think?
This friend of yours
doesn't even exist.
[MEN CONTINUE LAUGHING]
Laugh all you want.
He's coming.
And be warned, Gryza,
he despises pirates.
Macedonia has been
good to us.
Plenty of villages
ripe for pillaging.
We are here to stay.
Finish him.
[GASPING]
The more you struggle,
the faster you drop.
[GRYZA CHUCKLES]
Indeed, your fleet
is strong. I...
Yet, as I was
about to explain
before I was
so rudely interrupted,
the Nemean Lion
was strong, too.
Yet, he still destroyed it.
And not with a sword
or a spear or arrows. No!
I did it with my bare hands!
Or so they say.
Hercules.
Is this all the men
you have?
There's forty of us.
One of you.
The king of this land
has offered me gold
to dispose of you.
So leave or die.
I get paid either way.
Make him bleed.
[MEN YELLING]
Five men with a single blow.
Still think you can destroy
the son of Zeus?
Bring me his head!
[MEN YELLING]
Seems they need more
convincing, Autolycus.
That's why we're here.
[MEN SCREAM]
Atalanta.
[GROANS]
Amphiaraus.
May Zeus forgive you.
Tydeus? [YELLING]
[ALL GRUNTING]
[MEN SCREAMING]
Die, Hercules!
[SCREAMING STOPS]
Ah, good man.
[CHUCKLES]
[PANTING]
[ROPE SNAPPING]
Hurry!
Hurry! Uncle!
[YELPING]
Uncle, hurry!
Hurry! Hurry!
[SCREAMS]
Any longer, Uncle...
And the girls would finally
be safe from your attentions.
The rest of you may go.
But not you.
AUTOLYCUS: Thirteen,
fourteen, fifteen, sixteen,
seventeen... That was fun.
...eighteen,
nineteen, twenty.
Twenty pirates
at two gold pieces a head,
minus the headless ones.
Let's see.
Not a bad night.
You see how the pirates ran?
My story
softened their resolve.
Their resolve
must be broken, Iolaus.
When you spread
the legend of Hercules,
make it bigger, scarier.
The more they believe Hercules
is truly the son of Zeus,
the less likely
they are to fight.
Oh!
Aye.
Amphiaraus? Mmm?
Care to join us
here on Earth?
A lion and a crow
in strange alliance,
fighting across
a sea of corpses.
If you're going to use
those herbs, Amphiaraus,
at least share.
Huh?
[ALL CHUCKLING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Hold it!
Hold it! Hold it!
Keep practicing, boys!
So, who's next?
You? You?
[SNIFFING]
Ah!
That's a pretty sight.
One more payday, Autolycus,
that's all we need.
Then we get to live
like the kings we've served.
Or live simply.
You still dreaming
of barbarian lands?
Beyond the Aegean.
At the shores
of the Black Sea.
That is where
I will live out
the rest of my days
in solitude.
Boring, if you ask me.
Maybe so, Autolycus.
But I'll never find peace
unless I move
as far away as possible.
What of Tydeus?
Without you
to temper his rage,
I fear what he may become.
Tydeus will go with me.
Civilization has become
too civilized for us.
Uncle!
Join us. The girls
are eager to welcome you.
See? I told you
I knew Hercules.
Are you his servant?
I'm his nephew.
Are you really?
I tell of Hercules'
Twelve Labors,
like the Nemean Lion,
the Apples of Hesperides,
the Belt of Hippolyta
with its buxom naked Amazons
and exciting bondage.
I immortalize...
He talks,
while the rest of us fight.
It is a wonder you share
the same blood as Hercules.
[WOMEN LAUGHING]
Have fun.
Ladies. BOTH: Oh...
What do you want
with Hercules?
My words are for him,
not you.
HERCULES:
Atalanta, it's all right.
You certainly
are a hard man to find.
Maybe I don't want
anyone to find me.
I'm not just anyone.
My name is Ergenia,
daughter to Lord Cotys.
Your father is most fortunate to
have such a beautiful heir.
My father
is most unfortunate.
He battles a warlord.
Rhesus.
Our land is torn
by civil war.
Every day villages
are destroyed,
crops ruined,
innocents slaughtered.
We all have problems.
Well, perhaps
I can convince you
to make our problems
your own.
Unfortunately, my lady,
Hercules is fully committed
till the Feast of Dionysus.
We could, however, advance
you to the front of the line,
for the right price.
Hmm.
I thought heroes
fight for glory.
But mercenaries
fight for gold.
Lord Cotys is a rich man.
I like him already.
If you agree to aid him,
he will pay
your weight in gold.
Eat up.
"A lion and crow
in strange alliance."
Told you.
Where are we going?
It is good to see you safe,
my lady.
This war claims
more victims every day.
We were concerned, my lady.
Thank you, General Sitacles.
I was well protected.
Ah.
The mighty Hercules.
An honor.
But not quite as big an
honor as I expected.
Uncle? Hera. Impressive.
It's meant to be.
It took five years
and a thousand men
to build her temple.
Hera is the patron
goddess of Thrace.
Everyone knows the legend.
How Hera seeks
to destroy Hercules.
Perhaps the right cause
might finally reconcile you.
Mother!
Arius.
You're Hercules.
That's right.
My name is Arius. I know
all your Labors by heart.
You killed the giant Geryon
with a single blow,
cleaned the Augean
stables in one night.
Hercules is probably tired.
And the Labor of the Hide,
and the Labor of the Mares.
That's enough, Arius.
Come along. [CHUCKLES]
[WHISPERS]
Stay away from him.
Men who deal in violence
attract violence.
But he's Hercules. He's no mere
mortal. He's the greatest!
Lord Cotys will see you now.
Have you ever met royalty,
Hercules?
Once or twice.
BOTH: Father! Ah! [CHUCKLES]
[APPLAUSE]
Megara.
Welcome home, my love.
[ALL CHEERING]
Hercules!
Whenever I'm here,
I imagine this is what
Elysium must look like.
[CHUCKLES] Well,
men like us
have the means
to create our own paradise
on Earth. Look.
Magnificent, aren't they?
Well, do not keep us
in suspense.
Are we safe
from the monster Hydra?
The Hydra's heads,
Your Majesty.
The masks of serpents.
No wonder men thought
they were monsters.
You've done your sovereign
a great service. Come.
Let the people
have their hero.
MALE SERVANT:
All hail King Eurystheus.
And the mighty
protector of Athens,
Hercules![CROWD CHEERING]
CROWD: [CHANTING]
Hercules! Hercules!
Hercules!
A man faced
with such adoration
might be tempted
to think himself a god.
I only want to be
a husband and a father.
[BOTH SCREAMING]
Lord Cotys awaits.
Hercules.
Welcome.
An honor to host
such a legend.
But in legend,
you fight alone.
My reputation would not
exist without my comrades.
Autolycus of Sparta.
Tydeus of Thebes.
Atalanta of Scythia.
Iolaus of Athens.
And Amphiaraus of Argos.
Amphiaraus?
The famed seer of Argos.
It is said that you have
glimpsed your own death,
so you fight each battle
knowing that it is not yet
your time to die.
What else can you tell
of the future?
Only what the gods
see fit to reveal.
A shame. It would have been
a great gift
to know the outcome
of this war.
The gods can be frustrating
sometimes, Lord Cotys.
[CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS]
With respect,
I fear that the task ahead
might not be suitable
for a woman,
even if she is
an Amazon warrior.
I stand corrected.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
COTYS: When the kings
of yesteryear built
this citadel,
it was intended
as the high seat
of all Thrace.
But now Thrace is divided.
This war has depleted
our forces.
We're left with nothing
but farmers and merchants
to replenish our army.
It takes every one of us
to resist Rhesus.
People think he cannot be
killed by an ordinary mortal.
Only by a god.
Rhesus is a sorcerer.
His magic words confuse men,
bend them to his will.
He leads an army
of monsters,
half horse, half human.
Centaurs?
You've actually seen them?
They have been seen.
COTYS: Come, Hercules.
Let me show you what misery
Rhesus has brought us.
Every week, more refugees
arrive seeking my protection,
most of them
covered in blood,
crippled or burnt
by Rhesus' men.
I feared nothing could ever be
good again, till you arrived.
I'm just a mercenary
fighting for gold.
How we view ourselves
is of little consequence.
How others perceive us
is important.
And your name,
like it or not,
is a rallying cry.
I have seen too much reality
to trust in legends,
and I am not alone.
Nobody has any faith anymore.
The people need a hero.
They need someone
to look up to.
My son believes in you.
Bring us peace and
I will believe in you, too.
I'm convinced
these are good people.
I see. And who's
more convincing,
Cotys or his daughter?
All the gold on Earth
is not as convincing
as a pair of breasts.
Maybe, but gold never ages.
Which is why I got them
to double our price.
Double your weight in gold?
[LAUGHS] Well done.
Amphiaraus?
If it be the will of Zeus.
Which title sounds more
terrifying to our enemies?
"Hercules,
savior of Thrace"
or "Hercules,
a legend is born"?
Both sound
terrifyingly boring.
[CHUCKLES]
What are we supposed to do
with an army of farmers?
Train them.
Oh, shit. [CHUCKLES]
In war, there is one thing
more important than killing.
Surviving.
My companions and I will
show you how to stay alive,
so that you may return home
to your farms someday.
Autolycus.
Shield wall! Form!
[YELLING]
[MEN GROANING]
[PANTING]
Corpses!
Every last one of you!
Because your shield wall
was weak.
Dead.
Very dead.
Soldier,
many lives depend on you.
When attacked, lock your
feet in the ground.
Understand?
Yes, sir.
When a shield wall
is strong,
nothing can ever
defeat it!
You must learn
to work together.
React together.
When you do, each individual
will become a link in a chain
that will be stronger
than iron.
I hope the enemy
has a sense of humor.
Right. Today's lesson,
how not to stab yourselves!
It is imperative that
we strike now, My Lord,
given this opportunity.
COTYS: Ah! There you are!
Hercules, my scouts
have brought news.
Rhesus is on the move.
Archers who shoot
lightning from their bows.
An infantry, 4,000 strong,
their minds bewitched.
Demons march with them.
So now
we're fighting demons.
No stranger than the monsters
I hear you faced, Hercules.
My Lord, Rhesus is preparing
to attack Bessi lands.
He will be on them
within six days.
If the Bessi fall, we're next.
Unless we intercept him.
Your men need weeks, if
not months of training
before they're ready.
The Bessi are a fierce
but primitive tribe.
If we do not protect them,
then there will be
a bloodbath.
Face Rhesus with
an untrained army,
and you risk losing far
more than a single battle.
My Lord, Rhesus is coming.
I vouch my life on it.
The longer Rhesus lives,
the more villages
will be burnt
and the more innocents
will be killed.
Assemble your men.
We march tomorrow.
Hercules, the gods
have offered us a gift.
We must not squander it.
Are your gods going to be
fighting with us?
No.
The son of Zeus will.
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
[FAINT GROWLING]
[WHIMPERING]
[SNARLING]
Ah! [SCREAMING]
[PANTING]
Your mother told you to stay
away. You should listen.
What's wrong with him?
Tydeus is
my most loyal warrior.
He was born in war.
When I found him, he was
more animal than human.
He never speaks of
what he saw.
He never speaks at all.
Come.
Let's find your mother.
When I grow up, I want to
be a great hero like you.
Like me?
No hero is
greater than Hercules.
I know all your Labors.
Like the Cretan Bull.
You wrestled it for seven
days and seven nights.
Uh, that's a bit
exaggerated.
And struck it 49 times
with your club.
Maybe not quite that many.
Until it fell dead
and Crete was saved.
It's my favorite Labor.
Also Queen Hippolyta's Belt,
with its buxom Amazons
and exciting bondage.
Do you even know
what that means?
No.
[LAUGHS]
[MAN COUGHS]
Mother.
Arius. You're supposed
to be in bed.
Why are you in the hospice?
My mother
saves people's lives.
Many of our physicians
were killed during battle,
so out of necessity I taught
myself the art of healing.
If I could be like you,
I would protect all of Thrace
and no one
would ever get hurt.
[CHUCKLES]
Here.
I was going to give this
to someone else,
but I never got the chance.
Only a hero may wear this.
But to become a hero,
you must grow strong.
Is this
the Nemean Lion's tooth?
It is. ARIUS: Thank you.
Thank you.
Good night.
Good night, Hercules.
AMPHIARAUS: Have no fear.
If you fall in the service
of a just cause,
your souls
will go to Elysium,
where they will dwell forever
among the shades of heroes
like Theseus.
Odysseus!
And the great Achilles.
Or if you're lucky,
you'll go to Hades,
where all the fun people are.
Iolaus.
Your place is beside Lord
Cotys, where it's safe.
I've been giving it
a lot of thought,
and I really feel
I'm ready to fight.
You're a storyteller,
not a warrior.
We share the same blood.
And I will not
see it shed. Chariot.
Now. [SCOFFS]
Thracians,
the shield wall is your
home. Your shelter.
When you sleep,
the wall is your blanket.
When you fight,
the wall is your armor.
The shield wall
will never break formation
as long as there is
breath in your body.
Remember these words
and you will taste victory.
Move the army out! SOLDIER 1: Move out!
SOLDIER 2: Move out!
[HORSES NEIGHING]
Halt!
SOLDIER 1: Halt!
SOLDIER 2: Halt!
SOLDIER 4: Stop marching!
SOLDIER 5: Stand easy!
We are too late.
Rhesus has already
been here.
Leave the chariots.
We'll go down on foot.
The lion and the crow
cross a field of corpses.
I hate being right
all the time.
Halt. SOLDIER 1: Halt!
SOLDIER 2: Halt!
SOLDIER 3: Halt!
[SOLDIERS SHOUTING
INDISTINCTLY]
HERCULES:
This head is rotting.
A week old, at least.
Yet some of these
bodies are fresh.
[YELLS]
[YELPING]
IOLAUS: Uncle! [BOTH GRUNTING]
[SHRIEKS]
And we've walked into a trap.
Shield wall!
Form a single square!
Protect Lord Cotys!
Iolaus, go.
Shield wall!
We're here to help them.
Why are they attacking?
This is Rhesus' doing.
They say his spells have
the power to cloud minds.
Turn comrades
against each other.
King's guards,
around Lord Cotys!
Amphiaraus, do we die
in this battle?
My time has not come yet.
Not sure about yours.
That's comforting.
[YELLING]
I think he wants a challenge.
[ALL CHEERING]
Hercules' fists
have been dipped
in the blood of the Hydra!
Lethal to anyone but him!
Watch!
[YELLING]
[CHEERING STOPS]
Did you see that?
The gods fight on our side!
[ALL CHEERING]
Hercules!
Hercules! Hercules!
ALL: [CHANTING] Hercules!
[YELLING]
[ALL YELLING]
Battle position!
Lady Artemis, if I am to fall,
let me be judged not to be...
[YELLING CONTINUES]
[ALL GRUNTING]
Stand fast!
SITACLES:
Hold your positions!
Do not yield!
No retreat!
Stay in the wall!
Hold the lines!
Do not yield!
Defend Lord Cotys!
[SCREAMS]
SITACLES: The wall
has been breached!
Seal up the shield wall!
Defend Lord Cotys!
Whip!
Hercules!
Bring the chariots!
SITACLES:
Defend your Lord!
No!
[URGES HORSES]
[LAUGHS]
[YELLING]
[GRUNTS]
Advance!
SOLDIER: Advance!
[GROANS]
[SOLDIERS CHEERING]
SOLDIER: Make way!
Where is Rhesus?
[INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS]
Lord Cotys.
We came here
to save this village,
but, no,
they killed half my army.
Rhesus.
This is all his doing.
And yours.
I warned you.
Your men are brave,
but untrained,
unprepared for battle.
Give me time
to make warriors.
Very well.
Cover up,
before your loyal army
sees you bleed like a mortal.
I'm applying a salve of mint,
chamomile and clay
to seal the wound.
This is extract of lithops
for the pain.
A powerful sedative.
You should rest here
after consuming it.
It may have
certain side effects.
I don't need it.
Ah, forgive me, I forgot.
No mortal can harm Hercules.
And, uh,
your lion's hide
is indestructible?
Drink, son of Zeus.
Arius' father was the same,
he distrusted medicines.
Where is he now?
Taken by the gods
before my son was born.
I'm sorry.
I never knew my father.
Well, he must have been
very, very strong. [LAUGHS]
Tell me about Arius.
Oh. He's a good boy.
And someday,
he will make a fine king.
Do you have any children?
Thank you for your care.
The sedative
will help you rest.
[MEGARA SCREAMS]
[PANTING]
[CHILDREN LAUGHING]
[LAUGHING CONTINUES]
[GROWLING]
No!
[SNARLING]
[YELLING]
[PANTING]
AMPHIARAUS: It happened
again, didn't it, hmm?
Another vision of Cerberus,
the three-headed
beast of Hades?
The gods show you things
they don't share with others.
There's a word for that.
Madness.
When we were driven
from Athens,
I consulted the Oracle
of Delphi on your behalf.
Do you remember
her prophecy?
"Hercules must
finish the Labor
"that remains unfinished."
And what is that, Hercules?
Confront the beast
that haunts you.
Only then will you
find peace.
I speak from experience.
No matter how far you run,
no matter how fast you go,
the beast will follow.
Man cannot escape his fate.
Room for one more
in your company?
It'd be a pleasure having female
companionship for a change.
Atalanta doesn't quite
count. No offense.
If only your manhood was
as long as your tongue.
Oh, both can satisfy
in different ways.
You're a famed
storyteller, Iolaus.
Grace me with a story.
Any particular subject,
My Lady?
Murder of a woman
and her three children.
Is it true? Did Hercules
slaughter his own family?
Who said so?Oh, soldiers talk.
They say if Hercules
ever returns to Athens,
King Eurystheus
will have him executed.
Hercules had
completed his Labors
and returned home,
but Hera...
No myths. I want the truth.
No one knows the truth.
Not for sure.
We found Hercules alone.
His wife, Megara,
the children, dead.
He remembers nothing.
Do you believe
he is innocent?
We grew up together,
both orphans,
trying to survive
in the streets of Athens.
We found a home in the army.
Looked out for each other.
Hercules' strength
set him apart.
The Kings of Athens
would send him on all the
most dangerous missions.
The Twelve Labors.
And he took me with him.
Fight by his side.
And with each mission,
our numbers grew.
Scythia, the Amazon kingdom
where the royal family
had been assassinated.
My family was gone.
Everyone was gone.
Hercules helped me
avenge their murder.
He became
my brother-in-arms.
Thebes, the city of corpses,
where we found
a single child
still alive.
Hercules took Tydeus in
when everyone else saw
nothing but a wild animal.
You know how
a rumor spreads.
How a legend grows.
Hercules' deeds
were so incredible
they could not possibly have
been performed by a mere mortal.
So we played along.
We encourage people to think
Hercules was the son of Zeus.
It's good.
Scares the enemy.
Iolaus helps.
He talks nice.
And that, My Lady,
is the truth.
The truth.
[SCOFFS]
Whatever the truth,
the death of his loved ones
haunts Hercules.
Only the gods can help him,
if he listens.
Come! Gather around, soldiers
of Thrace, and behold.
When Hercules gives an
order, even the gods listen.
Zeus' master ironsmith
using the forges
of your own citadel
has crafted
these divine weapons
that will make you
invincible.
As steel is
hewn into shields,
so, too, will you be hewn
into warriors.
You shall carry
the shield of Hercules!
It's lighter.
Infused with the souls
of the Stymphalian birds
from Hercules' sixth Labor!
Spirits of birds?
How does that work, exactly?
Well, much as
birds take flight,
so, too, are these shields
lighter than air.
It's in the fibers.
Here.
Try on the helmet
of Hercules.
It covers my whole face.
Forged after Hercules'
very own helmet,
when he defeated
the demon Geryon.
You sure it wasn't your
horseshit that frightened
Geryon to death?
Mmm?
IOLAUS: General Sitacles,
perhaps you would care to
inspect the armor of Hercules?
[CHUCKLES]
Leather armor?
Mmm?
We will be
skewered like pigs.
[SITACLES GRUNTS] [SOLDIERS GASP]
Linothorax.
Hewn from the skin of
the Erymanthian Boar.
It's indestructible.
Now, wait,
if it's indestructible,
how did Hercules
cut it off the boar?
He used an indestructible
blade. [SCOFFS]
[SOLDIERS MURMURING]
SOLDIERS:
One, two... [GRUNTS]
[GRUNTS]
Get up.
Next!
[SOLDIERS GRUNTING]
Again!
Both eyes open.
Keep practicing.
[GROANS]
Firmer grip.
Elbow up.
Good.
Shield wall! Form!
ATALANTA: Stand tall. [SOLDIER GRUNTS]
Excellent.
HERCULES: All right.[SOLDIERS APPLAUDING]
[ALL GRUNTING]
Spread out.
[IOLAUS GRUNTING]
Careful you don't
cut yourself, boy.
AUTOLYCUS: Again!
[SOLDIERS GRUNTING]
Rhesus is here.
Close enough to stick a
blade between his ribs.
What did you see? Centaurs.
Half man, half horse.
Hundreds of them.
He saw shadows in the night.
My Lord, I will go ahead
into the Rhesus camp.
I will bring word
of his plans.
If we let them get past Mount
Asticus, Thrace will fall.
You want to stop Rhesus?
We'll go through the forest and
they'll never see us coming.
It'll slow down
our chariots. A gamble.
I have a plan.
The scouts have returned.
Rhesus has made
his camp in Mount Asticus,
72 leagues away.
Once these men are ready,
we march.
So, have you seen
if we win or lose?
The gods have been annoyingly
silent on that matter.
What they have told me is
that I'm soon to discover
if there truly is
a heaven or a hell.
When will you die?
Within a week in a place that
looks an awful lot like hell.
As always, the gods
are generous with hints,
but cheap on specifics.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, cheer up, Hercules.
I've lived, not always
well, but long enough.
I'm ready for what's next.
Thracians, halt!
[SOLDIERS GRUNT]
Shield wall! Form!
Battle positions!
Tydeus?
[YELLING]
[SOLDIERS GRUNT]
There is no enemy camp.
This is the right place.
SOLDIER 1: Halt!
SOLDIER 2: Halt!
Centaurs!
They're real.
[BLOWING HORN]
[CENTAURS SHOUTING]
It seems that we're expected.
Centaurs?
[EXHALES]
Rhesus!
You have come
looking for a fight,
and we are happy to oblige.
Hercules. The son of Zeus.
Your legend ends here.
HERCULES: Look at me.
Do I look afraid?
It is over, Cotys.
Mount Asticus on your front.
The woods at your back.
And my troops outman you
three to one.
Surrender now and we shall
consider being merciful.
Men die who speak to
My Lord in such a manner.
You've made your choice.
Go!
In this moment,
on this day,
become the man
you were born to be!
You have it within yourselves
to write your own legends!
Let it be to death
or victory!
[SOLDIERS CHEERING]
Charge!
HERCULES: Shield wall!
[SOLDIERS GRUNT]
Flanks out!
Maybe today.
Now!
[SOLDIERS GROANING]
Watch as the Amazon uses
the arrows of Artemis...
Silence, boy!
Spears forward!
[SOLDIERS GRUNT]
[URGES HORSES]
Archers, ready!
Loose!
[BOTH SCREAM]
Advance!
Set them aflame!
Take cover!
SITACLES:
Defend Lord Cotys!
Maybe not.
Shield wall! Attack!
Push forward!
To kill a snake,
cut off its head.
[URGING HORSE]
[SOLDIERS CHEERING]
Victory is yours,
Lord Cotys!
It is not over yet!
Yeah!
[HORSE NEIGHING]
[PANTING]
Fucking centaurs.
[ALL CHEERING]
ALL: [CHANTING]
Hail, Lord Cotys!
[SOLDIERS BOOING]
SITACLES: Halt!
[SOLDIERS LAUGH]
Get up.
Up. Enough!
You helped a tyrant
enslave a nation.
All I did was stop you
from burning more villages.
I burned no villages.
HERCULES: Then who did?
Ask yourself.
If Cotys is beloved,
why did he need to hire
mercenaries to do his
dirty work?
Keep moving, dog.
You've been fighting
on the wrong side.
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[MEN LAUGHING]
Where are you going?
I'm taking some water
to the prisoner.
Sit down.
It's time.
[MUSIC STOPS]
Thrace is finally united.
One land.
One King.
One Thrace.
ALL: One land!
One King! One Thrace!
Thrace is not a man,
a king, or a god!
Thrace is her people!
[GROANS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
Who cares
what Rhesus claims?
Our work is done. Let's
collect our fee and be gone.
Don't do anything foolish.
Where are you going?
[GASPS]
I saw pity in your eyes
for Rhesus.
Why?
Look at me.
Cotys is responsible
for this war, isn't he?
You lie very well. Clearly,
your father's daughter.
I didn't do it
for my father.
I did it for my son.
If I disobeyed Cotys
or resisted in any way,
Arius would be executed.
I did what any mother would.
I protected my child.
My husband was king.
And Cotys poisoned him
to take his place.
Rhesus fought back.
Civil war broke out.
Arius is
the legitimate king.
My father is old.
He will not live forever
and once he is gone,
my son will be a good king.
And he will heal this land.
That's a dream.
And you can help.
Please, when you leave
Thrace, take Arius with you.
Please keep him safe.
Find another savior.
SITACLES: Hercules?
The King commands
your presence.
My Lady.
Ah, champion of Thrace!
Something tells me
we're not gonna get paid.
You could be right. Oh, shit.
You wanted conquerors,
not heroes.
You betrayed me, Cotys.
Betrayed?
A mercenary who has long since
sold his conscience for gold
can hardly presume
to judge his employers.
Let's not quibble
about details.
We all know your legend,
Hercules. But here is mine.
When I was a general
in the army of Thrace,
I had dreams
of ruling this kingdom.
But thanks to you,
my dreams have grown.
I now crave an empire.
My thousands
will train more thousands,
and they even more.
The lessons of Hercules
will spread.
What you began here
can never be stopped.
And if you fear
what such an army may do,
then lead it.
You want me to serve you?
Oh, spare me
the moral outrage.
Child killer.
[ALL GASP]
Getting us all killed,
bad idea.
Well, I must take this
as a "no."
In that case,
your services
are no longer required.
You will be paid in full.
Bring them the gold.
If we hurry,
we could be spending
our fortunes in Macedonia.
Take mine, too.
What do you think
you're doing? Let's go.
There will be no more
innocent blood on my hands.
I can't leave without
setting this right.
Oh, I see.
And who's gonna be paying us
for this suicidal endeavor?
Thrace needs our help.
To hell with Thrace.
We have gold.
You remember
the Black Sea.
That beach you spoke of
is within reach.
Leave now, be free.
I would never be free.
In this fight, you're alone.
Never saw that one coming.
How can you just walk away?
You can't just leave.
Why not? It's all right.
You've sacrificed
your lives for me.
Now you can finally be free.
Whatever debt you feel
you owe me is paid.
Debt?
You think we follow you
because we owe you?
Look around, Hercules.
We're family.
All we have is each other.
We will fight for you.
And if it's our time,
we will die for you.
Because you
would die for us.
Take that, too.
I have no need of it.
This is madness.
AMPHIARAUS:
You want madness?
Tonight, a spear of flame
will pierce my heart.
Is that not the most insane
death you've ever heard of?
Crazy. The lot of you.
Autolycus.
Iolaus. Go with Autolycus.
I think I'll stay.
Nephew.
Uncle, all I've ever done
is tell stories of great
deeds performed by others.
It's time I stopped
telling their stories.
Started living my own.
Well, you may have all
completely lost your minds,
but not me.
Not me.
Autolycus?
Live like a king,
my friend.
[URGES HORSES] [HORSES NEIGHING]
What about Cotys?
He paid us to save Thrace.
Let's not disappoint him.
[CREAKING]
SITACLES:
Lay down your arms.
Lay down your arms!
I invite you to join me.
You refuse.
I order you to leave.
You return.
[GRUNTS]
Get your hands off me.
I overheard her
conspiring with Hercules.
They were planning
to remove
the young Prince
from your protection.
No. No! [ARIUS SCREAMING]
Let go of him!
Don't touch him!
[SHOUTS]
Arius! No!
[SCREAMING]
No, you're hurting him! No!
ARIUS: Hercules, no!
Help me! Stop!
ERGENIA: No. Arius.
[CRYING] No.
Arius! No![GROANING]
[PANTING]
[GROWLING]
[SNARLING]
MAN: Magnificent, aren't they?
An extraordinary species.
Incredibly loyal.
As long as they're fed.
Remember them?
Eurystheus.
They remember you.
Confused, Hercules?
Kingdoms are won
with armies,
but empires are made
by alliances.
King Eurystheus
and I will now rule
all of Greece.
[SNARLING]
Cerberus only exists
in my mind.
Speak a little
louder, Hercules.
I didn't quite catch that.
The wolves.
They were there that night.
The wolves were there.
You drugged me.
[MEGARA SCREAMING]
The wolves were there the
night my family was murdered.
My men told me how
your children screamed
as my wolves gnawed
on their bones.
[GASPS]
As their fangs despoiled
your daughter's
pure flesh.
When the people called out
your name louder than mine,
you see, when they
saw you as a god,
how long before
they saw you as their king?
I wanted nothing!
Precisely! Your sin, Hercules,
was that you had no ambition!
I can deal with
an ambitious man!
He can be bought! But a
man who wants nothing
has no price!
Killing you would have
turned Athens against me.
I had to ruin your name.
My wife!
My children!
Well, you have our permission
to join them in death.
All of you! Starting with
my faithless daughter!
ERGENIA: Let go of me!
[GRUNTS] No! No! No!
Unhand me!
No!
She's your own
flesh and blood!
I will raise Arius to be
my worthy successor!
You stay away from my boy!
You monster, you bastard!
You are a monster!
No! [GRUNTS]
ERGENIA:
You are not a man!
You're a demon!
AMPHIARAUS: Who are you?
ERGENIA: No, no, no!
Are you a murderer?
Damn you! I curse you!
Are you a mercenary who turns
his back on the innocent?
Stay away from my son!
AMPHIARAUS: Are you
only the legend?
Or are you the truth
behind the legend?
Father, please.
Please, please...
We believe in you. [ERGENIA SOBBING]
We have faith in you.
Have faith in yourself.
[GRUNTS]
Remember the man
that you are.
The gods will punish you!
You cannot escape it!
AMPHIARAUS:
Remember the deeds
you have performed,
the Labors you have
accomplished!
No. No!
Stop it! Leave her alone!
AMPHIARAUS: Now, tell me!
[SCREAMING]
Who are you?
I am Hercules!
[GASPS]
Unleash the wolves!
[WOLVES SNARLING]
HERCULES: Get away!
Ahh!
Three wolves should be more
than enough for one lion.
[WOLF WHINES] Ahh!
Hurry!
[GRUNTING]
Hurry!Hurry!
No!
[GRUNTING]
[JAW CRACKING]
Ahh!
[WOLF WHINES]
The gods have
revealed the truth.
The final Labor
is complete.
But I'm just
getting started.
Doesn't take a vision to know
what's waiting
for us up there.
[ALL GRUNTING]
[SOLDIER SCREAMS]
My time.
Excuse me. That was my
moment, my fate.
You're welcome.
[SCREAMS]
I'm going after Eurystheus!
[GRUNTING]
Hercules, listen to me.
None of this is my fault.
You see, Cotys
poisoned my mind.
Turned me against you.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
I like you.
Now stop.
I command you to stop!
I'm your King!
You took an oath
to obey me!
You swore to Zeus!
Wait, wait.
You fight for gold.
I have plenty of gold.
Name your price.
Find it in your heart
to forgive.
You want forgiveness?
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
Ask my family
for forgiveness.
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
I've never killed
a god before.
[GROANS]
I really think
I'm ready to fight now.
Well done, warrior.
[MEN SHOUTING]
Eurystheus? Dead.
We need to find Arius.
HERCULES: Follow me.
HERCULES: Soldiers of Thrace!
You followed me in battle.
Follow me now.
Don't be fools!
Hercules is mortal!
Not a god!
And I will show you.
Bring him.
Arius!Mama!
No!
He's your grandson!
You failed to save
your children, Hercules.
But you may yet save him.
[WHIMPERS]
Please, Father, no!
Admit defeat!
Bow to me!
You have until
the count of three!
One!
Two!
[GROANS] [SOLDIERS MURMURING]
Don't just stand there!
Kill someone!
SOLDIER: Protect Lord Cotys.
Arius, run!
Mother!
Get the boy!
[SCREAMING]
[TYDEUS YELLING]
[GROANS]
[CONTINUES YELLING]
Ahh!
Tydeus!
Attack! [SOLDIERS YELLING]
HERCULES: Hold them back!
COTYS: Spears!
[BOTH GROANING]
Go through the fire!
[SOLDIERS YELLING]
Here! Help me!
Easy, Tydeus.
[ALL YELLING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[SOLDIERS SCREAMING]
H...
Hercules.
[LAUGHS]
[TYDEUS CHOKING]
Lock shields!
March!
Find peace, my brother.
As you said, Hercules,
there is no way
to defeat a shield wall!
There is no way out!
Come out and face me!
[GRUNTING]
You're no hero!
You're no god!
You're nothing
but a mercenary!
Your wife and children
deserved to die!
[YELLING]
[GASPS]
[CONTINUES YELLING]
COTYS: What's he doing?
Get back up there!
Hercules must die!
Come on!
Kill the filthy bastard!
[WHIMPERS]
[COTYS SCREAMING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
ALL: [CHANTING]
Hercules! Hercules!
Hercules! Hercules! Hercules!
AMPHIARAUS:  You want to know
the truth about Hercules?
There it is.
To be honest,
I prefer it to the legend.
The world needs a hero
they can believe in.
Is he actually
the son of Zeus?
I don't think
it really matters.
You don't need to be
a demigod to be a hero.
You just need to believe
you're a hero.
It's what worked for him.
But then again,
what the hell do I know?
I'm supposed to be
dead by now.
[LIGHTNING CRASHES]