Subtitles by demonseye
There's simply no way to shield
against every weaponized agent.
Instead, I can make
super-immune systems
by strengthening
the human cellular response.
Banner, I know
where you're going.
But manipulating the immune system
is dangerous and stupid.
The president's science advisors
made it absolutely clear...
no human subjects.
David, I have wonderful news.
I'm gonna have a baby.
What's it gonna be?  Whoa, look at that,
Bruce. Huh?  Want a dinosaur?
Come on,
let's have another fight. Come on.
You don't scare me.
That's a delicious eyeball.  Ooh, you're big
and green and scary.  I'm gonna run away.
Really, speaking of Cheryl,
guess... what...
Bruce, you're hurt!
Jack hit 'im with the stick,
but... Bruce wouldn't hit 'im back.
He just stood there, shaking.
It's okay.
Yeah, strange
he didn't make a peep.
Any other kid
would've wailed his head off.
That's Bruce. He's like that.
He's just so... bottled up.
The samples we found in your lab...
they were human blood.
You've ignored protocol.
You had no right
snooping around in my lab.
That's my business.
Wrong, Banner. It's government business,
and you're off the project.
Attention, to all personnel.
Fail-safe has been initiated.
Gamma decontamination
will occur in 30 minutes!
Evacuate immediately!
I repeat...
- Edith?
- David, what's going on?
- I gotta talk to you, Edith.
- Bruce, stay here.
What are you doing?
David, please, stop it!
No!
- David, no!
David! No!
Bruce.
Bruce, wake up, son.
Bruce. Bruce.
Another nightmare?
I don't know.
I don't remember.
Hi, mom.
Already off to college.
Gonna miss you terribly.
I'll miss you too.
Please. Come here.
Look at you.
Soon to be a great scientist.
I guess.
- I mean, who knows?
- I do.
There's something inside you...
so special.
Some kind of greatness.
I'm sure,
someday you're gonna...
share it with
the whole world.
But, as far as I'm concerned,
security oughta be...
Good morning, dr. Krenzler.
Security oughta be beefed up a lot more.
In a place like this, you can't be too careful...
Bruce!  Big day.
- Did you sleep?  I didn't sleep.
- I slept okay.
- Is Betty here?
- She's around.
I really gotta say, seeing you
in that stylin' head wear...
You're implying something
about my helmet?
You look like a massive nerd,
even around other scientists.
Can I just ask... were you wearing
the helmet while she dumped you?
See, it protects
my very important brain, Harper.
Go prep the samples.
- Hey. I found you.
- Betty, hey.
I hate them.
- Wait, I just got here. Who do we hate?
- The review board.
We have to make
a presentation on Tuesday.
And you're gonna
make it with me.
- You think I should?
- Yeah, you're great with that stuff.
You start talkin' about microbes and
nanomeds, you sound almost... passionate.
I'm sorry.
That was rude.
Look, nobody expects this
to be easy,
us working together
after being... so close.
We were close?
Look, if I could be more...
whatever, you know, I'm...
- just...
- Don't.
It's not your fault, really.
You're just a by-product
of my... inexplicable obsession
with emotionally distant men.
I'll get over us.
Good for you.
Anyway, I'm just really stressed
about this review.
If we don't get
impressive results today,
we're gonna have
a really hard sell come Tuesday.
Well, then,
let's go be impressive.
Harper?
- Ready when you are.
- Let's hit it.
- We passing inspection?
- Safeties all going green.
Countdown... started.
Nanomeds released.
Four seconds.
Okay.
Nanomeds fully dispersed.
Okay. Let's hit Freddie
with the gamma radiation.
Gamma exposure.
Nanomeds now active.
Nanomeds replicating
cells on border.
It's working...
Cell copy to disassemble ratio
holding within one percent.
Imbalanced nanomed activity.
You wanna go to the review board
on Monday and tell 'em
we've developed a brand-new
method for exploding frogs?
Yeah. I think maybe
there's a market for it.
And what if there's a plague?
What have you had, Betty,
like, one beer?
I'm just sa...
I'm just saying, you know,
frogs start falling from the sky,
who do they come to?
We'd be world-renowned.
Make any parent proud.
I bet they would be.
They actually did want me
to be a scientist.
I mean, your birth parents.
Guess we'll never know.
I don't understand why
you don't wanna find out about them.
They're dead. They died before
I can remember anything. And it...
Why do you always
come back to this?
Don't know.
Guess I figure there's
more to you than you like to show.
I guess
there couldn't be any less.
Right. So now we come
full circle back to that.
Nice work, Betty.
Betty!
- Glen!
- Hey.
Hi.
What happened
to your uniform?
Oh, I, uh... I switched over.
I'm still working
with your father, but...
Well, you know, the military's subcontracting out
all the most interesting work, and...
can't argue with a paycheck.
I basically run
all the labs on the base now.
Oh.
Hey, you...
You're looking good.
You're the genetics expert.
Ah, the good old college days.
So, how's business?
What do you want?
All right, I'll cut to the chase.
I've been hearing interesting things
about what you guys are doing here.
Your little molecular machines
have some incredible implications.
How would you like
to come work for Atheon?
Get paid 10 times as much
as you earn now...
and own a piece of the patents.
- You just have to say the word.
- Two words. The door.
General?
Come in.
Talbot wanted you to see this, sir.
It's about a lab Atheon is targeting for
acquisition and removal to desert base.
Why isn't it
going through NSC?
It, uh, concerns
your daughter, sir.
Hi. Sorry.
Hey, what happened to Benny?
Is he not working
the night shift anymore?
Benny's dead.
I'm the new guy.
Oh.
- Good to meet you.
- Same.
- Let's try another.
- Mm, no. Stay here.
- I look tired anyway.
- Yeah, but you look great.
What's the matter?
It's these dreams, doctor.
I keep having 'em,
and they're terrible.
Tell me about your dream.
Well, it starts...
It starts with a memory...
I think it's my first memory.
It's this... image I have...
from when I was
maybe two years old.
Do you think
it's just a dream?
No, I think it's something
that happened when...
I was living at a desert base
with my father.
Anyhow...
the dream goes on, and...
suddenly I'm alone.
That's terrible.
You know I'd never hurt you.
Hey, there.
What's your name, darlin'?
Eh? What's your name?
Okay. It's okay.
I gotta talk to you, Edith.
Bruce, stay here!
"C... T... G...
A... G."
Bruce.
My Bruce.
Good morning.
Glen dropped by.
- What's he doing here?
- You know, dr. Krenzler,
you and I have never had the chance
to get to know each other properly.
Well, that's because I don't wanna get
to know you, properly or improperly.
So, leave.
Hey, no worries.
Yeah, let me give you
a little heads-up.
There is a hairsbreadth
between friendly offer...
and hostile takeover.
I've done my homework.
The work you're doing here is dynamite.
Think. GI's embedded with
technology
that makes them instantly
repairable on the battlefield,
in our sole possession.
That's a hell of a business.
Well, it's not what we're doing here.
We're doing the basic science for everyone.
You know, someday
I'm gonna write a book...
and I'm gonna call it "When Stupid Ideals
Happen To Smart, Penniless Scientists".
In the meantime, Bruce,
you will be hearing from me.
- About Glen, I, um...
- There's nothing to talk about.
Okay.
I just wanted to say, don't worry
about 'im... I'll handle it.
How?
I'm gonna call my father,
ask him to exert some pressure.
Last I heard, you and your father
weren't speaking.
Hm.
Well...
I guess now I have something
to talk with him about.
I think this circuit's kinda fried.
I-I don't know.  Maybe you
wanna come take a look at it.
Okay, I'll be right there.
The gamma's too high!
Bruce, I can't stop it!
Harper, get out!
Get out!
- How's Harper?
- He's all right.
You saved him.
I don't think he's coming back
to the lab for a while, though.
I don't understand
how this is possible.
You should be dead.
They worked... the nanomeds.
I mean, I feel great.
I feel like... I don't know.
They must have, like, fixed me.
Bruce, they've killed everything else
that they've come into contact with.
- Are you sure the doctor checked?
- The doctor gave me the full workup.
He wants to know where
he can get what I'm taking.
I'm a hundred percent.
More.
- What do you mean?
- Remember my bad knee?
Well, now it's my good knee.
Bruce, this isn't funny.
I was watching you.
You were gonna die,
and I was gonna have to watch you die.
Betty...
I'm sorry.
Really.
- Hey, I'm not gonna explode, okay?
- Yeah.
You should get some rest.
And I'm fine, really.
I've never felt better.
Your name is not Krenzler.
It's Banner.
- What?
- Your name...
it's Banner. Bruce Banner.
Bruce.
- How did you get in here?
- I work here now.
In the labs.
The late shift.
It keeps me close to you.
You always work so late yourself
with your friend, Miss Ross.
No, no. Please. Please.
Let me.
You're not well.
You've had
a terrible accident.
You're wondering
why you're still alive.
You're thinking
there's something... inside.
Something different...
inexplicable.
I can help you understand...
if you'll let me.
If you'll...
forgive me.
Look, mister, I'm sure I have
nothing to forgive you for.
So, perhaps you should leave now.
I'll be fine.
You must know.
You may not want to believe it,
but I can see it... in your eyes.
So much like your mother's.
Of course,
you're my flesh and blood.
But then,
you're somethin' else too, aren't you?
My physical son,
but the child of my mind, too.
No. You're lying.
My parents died
when I was a small boy.
No, no, no, that's not true. That's not true.
That's what they wanted you to believe.
The experiments, the accident...
all top secret.
They put me away for 30 years.
Thirty years!
Away from you.
Away from our work.
But they couldn't keep me forever.
After all, I'm sane.
They had to admit it.
You see,
everything...
your extraordinary mind
has been seeking all these years...
it's been inside you.
Now, we will understand it.
We will harness it.
No, don't answer it.
It's Miss Ross again.
There's something you need to know
about her, Bruce. Something troublesome.
Let me protect you from 'er.
No. Get out.
- Bruce...
- Get out!
Sit!
We're gonna have to watch
that... temper of yours.
- You sure you're okay?
- Yeah, just glad to be out of bed.
Got a message from my father.
He's coming to see me.
- Your father?
- Mm.
- When?
- Lands in about an hour.
The funny thing is...
he called me.
- Hi, dad.
- Hello, Betty.
- Here, ma'am.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome. Sir?
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Look, I'm gonna...
get right to it.
It's about Glen, isn't it?
He's been snooping
around my lab.
Glen noticed some things.
Asked me to make some inquiries.
- Are you here to... question me?
- No.
We've turned up
some surprising things.
This Krenzler you work with...
you know who he really is?
How much do you
actually know about 'im?
I think the question is,
what is it
that you know about him?
- Well, right now, I'm not at liberty...
- Not at liberty to disclose it to me, right.
Right.
You know...
I think I was hoping that...
maybe this time you just...
honestly wanted to see me again.
- You've got this all wrong, Betty.
- Do I?
Yes. I do wanna see you.
I really wish that
I could believe you.
Everything...
your extraordinary mind
has been seeking...
all these years,
it's been inside you.
Hi, you've called dr. Krenzler.
Please leave a message
and I'll call you right back.
Bruce. Hey. Are you there?
Look, um,
I think I screwed up.
My father... It's... it's like he suspects
you of something. I don't know.
I was so impatient,
like always, and
I didn't hear him out.
I don't know, I...
I just think that they're planning
something with the lab.
So, um, uh...
Call me. Okay?
Bye.
Betty!
Dispatch! Dispatch!
We have a 4-15 at the lab!
Send Berkeley P.D. now!
Send 'em now!
Watch out!
- Edith?
- David, what is going on?
- I gotta talk to you, Edith.
- Bruce, stay here.
My big Bruce.
Bruce?
There was some sort
of explosion.
They wouldn't let us
into the building.
I was worried about you.
Well... I'm okay.
What happened
to you last night?
I had the most vivid dream.
It was like being born.
Coming up for air.
Light hitting my face.
Screaming...
My heartbeat...
it was, like, boom...
boom...
- Were you at the lab?
- No.
But something...
And there was that man.
The one with the dogs.
Who?
That new janitor.
He said he was my father.
I'll get it.
My father.
My, my...
So, this is
the young Bruce Ban...
Krenzler.
I think you left something
in your lab last night.
Mitchell!
Escort my daughter outside.
I'll join her shortly.
- I'd rather stay here.
- Now! Betty...
It's okay. I'll be fine.
Keep 'im under observation.
I'll be back.
- What?
- Your friend in there.
There's a good chance he's caught up
in some... very bad business.
Unfinished business.
And I promise you, I'm gonna
get to the bottom of it.
You have my word
I'll make sure he's cared for.
But as of right now,
he is incommunicado.
And for the next
few days, at least,
you're gonna stay away
from here. For your own good.
Okay, and that's for the new guy
on the night shift, right?
Great. Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Dr. Ross...
How unexpected.
Please, come in.
I'm sorry to just... show up
at your house... like this.
Uh...
I came to... ask you
something that...
I really have
no business asking.
- He told you.
- He said you talked to 'im.
Oh.
Please, sit down.
Bruce was at the lab last night.
He said that you were there too.
But he can't remember
much about it.
I need to find out
what happened.
So, you wanna know, uh,
what's wrong with him...
so you can fix 'im?
Cure him, change him.
My father's with the military.
He seems to think he's involved
in some kind of threat to national security.
Mm.
Your father. Ross.
You brought your father down
upon his head?
How little you understand,
Miss Ross,
and how dangerous
your ignorance has become.
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be sorry.
My son is...
unique.
That's why you can't relate to 'im.
And because he is unique, the world
will not tolerate his existence, will they?
But... you...
you try... don't you?
Yes.
And a very beautiful woman
like you,
your attentions...
can't be completely unwanted.
Can they?
No.
Not with... eyes like yours,
watching... expectantly,
lovingly.
But I'm afraid
we're both too late to help 'im.
There's nothing
I can do for him...
or for you.
Besides,
he's made it clear
he wants nothing to do with me.
His choice.
Now, if you'll excuse me, Miss Ross,
I have some work to do.
And don't worry about the... dogs.
You'll be fine.
Just don't look 'em in the eyes.
Goodbye.
He gets released, and a month later
your lab is destroyed.
What a coincidence.
So, you're just not gonna tell me
where he is, are ya?
How many times do I have to tell you?
I'd like to help you, but I just don't know.
You know who I am.
Right, Banner?
Your Betty's father.
You're a high-ranking general.
Let's cut the crap.
I'm the guy who had your father
tossed away, and a lot more like 'im,
and I'll do the same with you
if I feel so disposed. You understand?
If you had 'im tossed away,
then why are you asking me?
I don't remember. I was
always told my father was dead.
Don't play with me!
You were four years old
when you saw it.
When I saw what?
You were right there.
How could anyone forget a thing like that?
What?
Oh, some more repressed memories.
Just tell me.
I'm sorry, son.
You're an even more screwed-up mess
than I thought you'd be.
Until we get
to the bottom of this,
your lab has been declared
a top-secret military site
and you're not gonna get
a security clearance to get back into it...
or any other lab that's doin'
anything more interesting than...
tryin' to figure out
the next generation of herbal hair gel.
One more thing.
If you ever...
come within a thousand yards
of my daughter again,
I'll put you away for the rest
o' your natural life.
Dogs!
Go! Go get 'er!
And let nothing
stand in your way!
Go!
Hello?
Bruce?
So, they think they can just
throw you away as they did me.
What's wrong with me?
What did you do to me?
I got a visit today.
A very unwelcome visit.
I'm afraid
my hand is being forced.
What did you do to me?
You so much wanna know,
don't you?
But I think no explanation
will serve you half as well...
as experience.
In any case, I still don't
quite understand it myself.
If they'd only
let me work in peace...
Of course, my betters
would have none of that.
So, you experimented
on yourself, didn't you?
And passed on to me.
What?
An alteration. Genetic.
A deformity.
I guess you could call it that.
But an amazing strength, too.
And now, finally unleashed,
I can harvest it.
No.
You'll do no such thing.
I will isolate it
and treat it myself.
I'll remove it and I'll kill it
before it does any real harm.
Oh, I'll bet you and your Betty
would love to destroy it.
But would you really
destroy part of yourself?
I don't think so.
And as for Betty...
I'm sending her a surprise visit
from some four-legged
friends of mine.
You see, I've managed to culture
some of your very own DNA, Bruce,
and the results are tremendous.
They're unstable,
but very powerful.
What about my DNA?
Let's just wait and see
what Betty makes of the results, huh?
No. You're crazy.
I won't let you.
Get your hands off of me.
Talbot, what's this...
Inside, asshole.
I wanna talk to you.
Listen to me,
my father's going after Betty.
What makes you think you can go behind my back
and get Ross to cut me out, huh?
Listen to me!
Betty's in trouble!
You pathetic freak.
Betty's in danger.
I swear to you, she'll be killed.
I can state the obvious.
Something tells me
you aren't in much of a position
to be making
stupid threats to anyone.
- Talbot.
- Yeah?
- You're making me angry.
- Oh, am I?
I got him! Open fire!
Bruce?
He sent these dogs,
didn't he?
But I killed them!
My God.
That must be the nanomeds.
It must be the gamma exposure.
But we've never seen
any effect like this before.
No. Deeper.
The gamma just unleashed
what was already there.
Unleashed what?
Me.
It.
It's okay.
Shh. It's okay.
What were those animals?
My father sent them.
He is my father.
He wanted me to change.
He wanted me to change
into that mindless... hulk.
Why would he want that?
Can you remember anything?
Is there anything
from when you were changed?
It was like a dream.
About what?
Rage.
Power.
And freedom.
Hello? Sir.
- Hello.
- Dad?
Betty! Are you all right?
I'm scared.
I need your help.
Where are you?
- How are you?
- Okay... I guess.
I think that somehow...
your anger is triggering
the nanomeds.
How could it?  We designed them
to respond to physical damage.
Emotional damage
can manifest physically.
Like what?
Serious trauma.
Repressed memories...?
Your father grilled me about... something
that happened to me from early childhood
that I'm supposed to remember.
He did?
It sounded bad,
but... I honestly don't remember.
The thing that worries me...
is...
a physical wound is finite,
but with emotions,
what's to say that
it won't just go on and on...
and start a chain reaction?
You know
what scares me the most?
Is that, when it happens,
when it comes over me...
and I totally lose control...
I like it.
It's okay. I got you.
I'm sorry.
You'll be okay.
It's just to make you sleep.
Target down.
Target secure.
I'm gonna take you
someplace safe.
Okay? Bruce?
Bruce?
All right. Clear!
- Attention on deck.
- Carry on.
We're buried out here
in the middle of nowhere.
How long are you gonna
keep him sedated?
For the rest of his natural life,
if I have to.
- You said I could trust you.
- I'm your father.
You can trust me to do what I think is right,
not what you think you want.
- He is a human being.
- Well, he is also something else.
Suppose he gets out,
has one of his little mood swings
in a populated area.
Yes, I'm aware of the potential danger.
I'm also aware that he saved my life.
Yeah, from a mutant
French poodle.
I'm indebted to 'im for that.
He also put three men in a hospital,
and Talbot's barely walkin'!
- I mean, what do you want me to do?
- I want you to help him!
- Why is he such a threat to you?
- Because I know what he comes from.
He is his father's son,
every last molecule of 'im.
He says
he doesn't know his father,
but he's workin' in the same
exact goddamn field his father did.
So, either he's lyin'...
or it's somethin' worse, and he's...
What?
Predestined to follow
in his father's footsteps?
I was gonna say "damned".
Of course you were.
But I'm a scientist.
As a scientist, I believe we can
figure this out and he can be helped.
I know you do.
Whether you know... or care,
I've got a lot o' pride
in what you've done.
But this is too big for you.
Look. I know the government thinks
they have a weapon on their hands.
Otherwise, he'd be dead by now.
They can probe and
prod all they want.
In the meanwhile,
just let me try to help him.
Nobody knows 'im
better than I do.
What did David Banner
do to him?
Cover left!
Clear left.
Cover right!
What's happening here?
My hand.
You see, the strength
of my son's DNA,
combined with...
nanomed reconstruction...
You see, I can partake
with the essences of all things.
Gonna have to ask you to...
put your hands up, pal, okay?
Nice an' easy.
Do you really believe
that I am separate from you?
Where am I?
You're home.
It's hard to believe
we used to live here.
I must have seen you...
or known you.
If only I could remember...
This is my old house, isn't it?
Let's go.
Please try.
- What is it?
- Nothing.
Really?
Damn it.
Okay, Betty...
what do you wanna know?
What was in that room?
What are you afraid
that I'll see?
See? There's nothing.
It's empty.
What do you mean
I don't have access to him?
NSA has decided to turn over study
of the, uh, the threat... to Atheon.
But you're head of the base.
I thought you were in charge.
But I don't set policy,
and I still take orders.
I can't believe Talbot
would go around me like this!
Oh, there's a lot o' powerful people
that want in on this.
And money to be made.
Lots of it!
You know the worst part
about all this?
When I had David Banner locked up
and sent that kid away,
I didn't give that boy a second thought.
He was just collateral damage.
Well, he isn't anymore, is 'e?
What can I do?
You can go home now.
I'd tell you to go and... say goodbye,
but I've already been informed
that... for now all further contact
is out of the question.
Right.
Hiya, Bruce. How you feelin'?
Grub okay in here for you?
- What do you want?
- That's a good question.
See, I need your cells to trigger
some chemical distress signals.
You know, so you can turn
a little green for me again...
and I can carve off
a piece of the real you...
analyze it, patent it,
make a fortune.
- Do you mind?
- I'll never let you.
I'm not sure
you got much of a choice.
Come on, Bruce.
Aren't you feelin' a little angry?
After all, you've only
got me to play with
now that Betty's dumped you
and gone back to Berkeley.
You're lying.
You know, for me
this is a win-win situation.
You turn green, and all these guys
come in and kill you
and I perform the autopsy.
You don't...
and I'd mop the floor with you,
and maybe by accident
go too far and break your neck.
Bad science, maybe...
but personally gratifying.
Come on, Bruce!
Let's see what you got.
Never.
You know, consciously
you may control it,
but, subconsciously,
I bet that's another story.
All right, let's jump-start
those brain waves.
Bruce.
My dear Miss Ross.
Welcome back.
There are two guards
right outside.
You don't have to worry.
I'm not angry with you. Not anymore.
What do you want?
It's over for me now.
I know that.
And soon it'll be over for Bruce.
That's why I've come to you,
to ask you... if
you could persuade your father,
as a man,
as a father himself,
that if I turn myself in,
now, peacefully,
and before
he puts me away forever,
that he would let me
see my son ... for one last time.
Could you do that for me?
It's out of
my father's hands now.
I understand.
He's a puppet now.
- I don't blame him.
- You shouldn't.
You should blame yourself
for what you've done to your son.
And what have I done
to my son, Miss Ross?
Nothing. I tried to improve
on the limits in myself.
Myself! Not him!
Can you understand?
To improve on nature.
My nature!
Knowledge of oneself!
It's the only path to the truth,
that give men the power
to go beyond God's boundaries!
You know what's beyond
your boundaries? Other people.
All you've given Bruce is fear.
Fear of life.
Fear?
Perhaps, Miss Ross.
And loneliness, too.
Yes... I feel them both.
But I have lived... completely once.
I was so much in love,
and she so much wanted a baby.
My baby.
I could tell
from the moment she conceived
that it wasn't a son
I had given her,
but something else.
A monster, maybe.
I should have put a stop
to it right then,
but I was curious
and that was my downfall.
And as I watched
this tiny life unfold,
I began to imagine
the horror of it,
and my curiosity was replaced...
with compassion.
But they took away
my chance to cure him.
Your father threw me out.
What are you doing?
I remember that day so well...
Every moment, every sensation,
walking into the house,
the feeling of the handle
of the knife in my hand.
I knew I was doing a father's work,
fulfilling a father's mercy.
David, please stop it! No!
David, no!
Talk to me! Listen!
But then she surprised me.
No! No!
David, no!
It was as if...
she... and the knife...
merged.
No!
You cannot imagine
the unbearable finality of it.
And in that one moment,
I took everything
that was dear to me
and transformed it into
nothing more than a memory.
Bingo! That must be some
jumbo nightmare he just had.
Okay, do it now.
Start the enzyme extraction.
Sir, negative on drill penetration.
Damn it, drill 'im harder!
Give 'im full RPMs!
Come on, Holeman!
Come on!
Should I neutralize?
No, I can't do anything
with goop. Come on!
All right,
put 'im to sleep.
It's not stopping 'im!
Ready room, send in
our containment team.
Non-lethals only.
I repeat, non-lethals only.
I must have a sample of 'im.
Sir!
- Jesus!
- Hit 'im with the foam.
Deploy containment foam.
Talbot, talk to me.
Under control, general.
I'll let you know if we need you.
Unacceptable.  Unseat your
asses down here immediately.
I want a full-court evacuation now.
I'm shutting you down.
Lockdown.
- Didn't you hear what the general said?
- I said "lockdown"!
Clear!
I need a sample of 'im!
Take it easy there, buddy.
This might give you
a bit of a sting here, Bruce.
- Fall back! Fall back!
- Clear your weapon! Clear it!
Gimme the M2.
So long, big boy.
Clear!
Lockdown the entire
facility immediately.
Target's still moving...
towards blue level.
Evacuate the main hall.
Send in backup, heavy weapons.
Issue general quarters.
Set firing lines left and right!
Heavy weapons, go, go, go!
Contamination, sir.
System readings are redline.
Data's on
backup power supply.
Incoming!
- Shut down all power to the main hall.
- Sir?
Show 'im the way out.
We'll fight 'im outside.
Driver, stop.
Gunner, traverse left!
Traverse left!
Clear back! Clear back!
Mr. President,
I have some bad news, sir.
Well, let's have it, general.
I've briefed the President on Angry Man.
I assume that's what this is about.
It is, ma'am. I'm requesting
a National Command Authority override.
Angry Man is unsecure.
I need everything we have at my disposal
in order to stop his movement.
You're expecting
civilian casualties, general?
Not if I can help it, ma'am.
Consider it done.
Keep us posted.
Contact Goodman Control.
Patch data to the assets.
Contact H.Q.
Have them initiate
an immediate evacuation
in vicinity of grid coordinates
653-216.
Confirm that the area
has been cleared.
Confirm area cleared.
H.Q. confirms area cleared.
Assets on-line, sir.
Gentlemen,
it's time to dig in.
I want this target
stopped in his tracks.
Jesus.
Mayday! Mayday!
Ah, shit!
Tango Four is down. Have C-SAR
respond to our 20 ASAP.
We're okay, but, damn it, get 'im
off us before he tears us apart!
I've got no shot.
Do you have a clear line of fire?
Watch it, Tango Flight.
Break left! Break left!
Tango Three, pull back and
set up for a Hellfire shot.
Hold your fire
till we draw 'im off.
Tango One is hot.
Gun wazzed.
Roger. Going hot.
Guns ready.
Engage at will.
Tango One, pull back!
Clear my line!
Tango Flight, clear back.
I got him painted for Hellfire.
Roger that.
Tango One, clear.
Take the shot.
Tango One, Tango Three.
I have contact.
Holy shit!
He's got my missile!
Mayday! Mayday!
We're hit! We're going down!
Give me a head count.
Tango Three,
give me a sit rep.
Our kite's busted up...
but we're okay.
Tango Flight, do you have
eyes on the target?
Tango One,
I have 'im in the rocks.
Salvo all. Turn it
into a parking lot.
T-Bolt, your parking lot
is ready.
We're bingo for fuel
and ammo. R.T.B.
T-Bolt,
this is Goodman Control.
Be advised, target not destroyed.
He's on the move again.
Damn!
I've got it.
It appears
he's heading home.
Launch fast movers.
Have them intercept and engage.
Hello?
Betty... Bruce got out.
He's headed your way,
probably right for you.
How far from
the base are you?
I'm already here.
They're taking his father in now.
That's all good news.
Stay there, Betty.
Legend One rolling in hot.
Legend Two, breaking off left.
I think I can come back around
for a gun attack.
Acquire a clear target.
Fire at will.
Increase altitude.
Civilian aircraft in vicinity.
Pull up! Pull up!
You're headed for the bridge!
I can't pull up!
Okay, you've got him now. Take 'im
on a ride to the top of the world.
Let's see what the thin air
will do for 'im.
Initiating afterburner.
I'm passing flight level 600.
This is out of my envelope.
Hang in there, Legend.
I can't maintain.
He's all over my aerodynamics.
He'll lose consciousness
before you.
Nine-fifty. I can't hold it.
I'm pullin' back!
Puny human.
Contact. He's in the water.
All units, weapons hot.
Let's not take any chances.
You are cleared to fire
on target, Legend.
- Dad?
- Betty?
We don't have a choice.
I have to destroy 'im.
But you can't.
You will only fuel his rage,
and you will make him stronger.
It's you he's coming for.
You know that.
Then let me go to him.
Please.
Just give him
a chance to calm down.
To all aircraft.
Vicinity of San Francisco.
This is DEVO armed guard.
This area has been declared
restricted airspace.
All aircraft are ordered
to clear the airspace immediately.
Echo, One-Niner.
Weapons are hot.
Target acquired.
Waiting your orders to engage.
Repeat, waiting
your orders to engage.
Command code yellow.
Hold for authorization.
All units, hold your fire.
This is T-Bolt to all assets. You have
direct orders to hold your fire.
I repeat, hold your fire.
Echo One-Niner.
Roger that.
Go go, go, go, go, go!
Engine 24 to command.
We are in position now.
You found me.
You weren't
that hard to find.
Yes, I was.
Let's take a walk.
That's the deal, gentlemen.
He stays on this base
until we get the final word from C-3
on how to dispose of 'im.
In the meantime, if he does
anything but sit there in that chair,
we're gonna turn on the juice
and he'll be incinerated immediately.
We've established
a 200-yard perimeter, sir.
If we deploy the electromagnetic array,
there should be no collateral damage.
Here they come!
I'm doin' this for you, Betty.
But one way or another, we're gonna
have to prepare for the worst.
I should have killed you.
And I should have killed you.
I wish you had.
I saw her last night.
Saw her face.
Brown hair...
Brown eyes...
She smiled at me.
She reached down
and kissed my cheek.
I can almost remember
a smell.
Almost like desert flowers.
Her favorite perfume.
It's my mother,
and I don't even know her name.
It's all right, son.
You go ahead and cry.
Go ahead and cry.
Cry. Crying will do you good.
Don't touch me!
Maybe once
you were my father,
but you're not now
and you never will be.
Oh, is that so?
Well, I got news for you.
I didn't come here to see you.
I came here to see my son.
My real son.
The one inside of you.
You're nothing
but a... superficial shell,
a husk of
flimsy consciousness,
ready to be torn off
at a moment's notice.
You can think what you like.
I don't care. Just go!
No, son. Listen to me.
I found a cure.
For me.
My cells can transform too,
absorb enormous amounts of energy.
But, unlike you, they're unstable.
Son... I need your strength.
I gave you life.
Now you must give it back to me!
Only a million times
more radiant, more powerful!
- Stop it.
- Stop? Stop what?
Stop... what?!
Think about all those men
out there in their uniforms,
barking and swallowing orders,
inflicting their petty rule
over the entire globe!
Think of all the harm
they've done!
To you! To me!
To humanity!
And know this...
that we can make them...
and their flags and their anthems
and their governments
disappear in a flash!
You in me!
I'd rather die.
Oh, that's your answer?
Then indeed you shall die...
and be reborn
a hero... of the kind
that walked the earth
long before the pale religions
of civilization
infected humanity's soul!
Go!!!
Stop your bawling,
you weak little speck
of human trash.
All right... I'll go!
- You just watch me go!
- Hit it.
Hit it again!
We can't, sir. There's no power.
Some kind of counter-electromagnetic field.
Move in and
assault the target. Move in!
Move, move, move!
Sir, I've located them on radar.
Pear Lake.
Call up the task force.
Yes!
That's right. Keep fighting.
The more you fight,
the more of you I take.
Strange. We're reading a phenomenal drop
in temperatures there.
But simultaneous radiological activity.
They're absorbing
all the ambient energy.
Sleep now, Bruce,
and forget forever.
Struggle no more...
and give me all of your power.
You think
you can live with it? Take it!
Take it all!!!
Oh, yes! Yes!
Take it back!
It's not stopping!
Gentlemen... release.
Gamma charge away.
- Mwah!
- Sweet dreams.
- Hello?
- Betty, is that you?
- Hi, dad.
- I'm glad I caught you.
- I'm glad you called.
- Thanks.
Look, Betty... you and I...
well, we both know that Bruce
couldn't have survived that blast.
But... well, you know...
- What is it?
- Well, you know.
The usual loonies.
Seein' things.
Only now everything's green.
Right.
Look, uh...
if by some chance
he... did survive...
and he should try to contact you,
try to get in touch,
you'd tell me, wouldn't you?
No... I wouldn't.
But... you know as well as I do,
I wouldn't have to.
I mean, my... phones are bugged,
my computer's tapped.
I'm under surveillance.
I'll tell you, though,
that... if he were alive,
I'm... the last person
I would want him to come to
because... as much as I miss 'im,
I... I... loved him. I, uh...
Yeah.
I'm sorry, Betty.
I am so sorry.
I know you are.
Si.
Let's take a walk.