- There’s simply no way
to shield against every weaponized agent.
Instead, I can make super immune systems
by strengthening the human cellular response.
- Banner, I know where you’re going,
but manipulating the immune system
is dangerous and stupid.
The president’s science advisors made it absolutely clear.
No human subjects.
- David, I have wonderful news.
I’m gonna have a baby.
( straining )
Aah!
- ( cries )
- Oh, what’s this here? Oh, lookee there.
Bruce? Huh? Want the dinosaur?
Come on, let’s have a little fight.
Come on. Rrawr. You don’t scare me.
Mmm, hey, delicious. Oh, you’re big and brave.
You’re scary. I’m gonna run away.
- ( gasps ) Bruce, you’re hurt!
- Jack hit him with the stick,
but Bruce wouldn’t hit him back.
He just stood there shaking.
- Kind of strange he didn’t make a peep.
Any other kid would have wailed his head off.
- That’s Bruce. He’s like that.
He’s just so bottled up.
- The samples we found in your lab,
they were human blood.
You’ve ignored protocol.
- You had no right snooping around in my lab.
That’s my business.
- Wrong, Banner!
It’s government business and you’re off the project.
- Attention, all personnel.
Fail-safe has been initiated.
Gamma decontamination will occur in 30 minutes.
Evacuate immediately.
I repeat, evacuate immediately.
( alarm sounds )
- Edith?
- David, what’s going on?
- I gotta talk to you, Edith.
- Bruce, stay here!
What are you doing?
- Rarrwr! Aah! Rarrwr! Grr!
( roaring )
( arguing )
- David, please stop! No!
David, no!
( arguing and shouting )
- ( screaming )
- Bruce. Bruce, wake up, son.
Bruce. Bruce.
Another nightmare?
- I don’t know.
I don’t remember.
Hi, Mom.
- Already off to college.
I’m gonna miss you terribly.
- I’ll miss you, too.
- Please come here.
Look at you.
Soon to be a great scientist.
- I guess. I mean, who knows?
- I do. There’s something inside you.
So special.
Some kind of greatness, I’m sure,
and someday you’re gonna share it with the whole world.
- As far as I’m concerned, security ought to be--
- Good morning, Dr. Krenzler.
- Security ought to be beefed up a lot more.
In a place like this, you can’t be too careful.
- Bruce? Big day.
Did you sleep? I didn’t sleep.
- I slept okay. Is Betty here?
- She’s around.
I really gotta say, seeing you in that styling headwear...
- You implying something about my helmet?
- You look like a massive nerd even around other scientists.
Can I just ask?
Were you wearing the helmet while she dumped you?
- See, it protects my very important brain, Harper.
Go prep the samples.
- Hey, I found you.
- Betty, hey.
- I hate them.
- Wait. I just got here. Who do we hate?
- The review board.
We have to make a presentation on Tuesday.
- Oh.
- And you’re gonna make it with me.
- You think I should?
- Yeah, you’re great with that stuff.
Start talking about microbes and nanomeds,
you sound almost passionate.
Sorry. That was rude.
- Look, nobody expects this to be easy,
us working together after being so close.
- We were close?
- Look, if I could be more whatever, you know, I just--
- Don’t.
It’s not your fault, really.
You’re just a by-product of my inexplicable obsession
with emotionally distant men.
I’ll get over us.
- Good for you.
- Anyway, I’m just really stressed about this review.
If we don’t get impressive results today,
we’re gonna have a really hard sell come Tuesday.
- Well, then let’s go be impressive.
Harper?
- Ready when you are.
- Let’s hit it.
We passing inspection?
- Safeties all going green. Countdown started.
- Nanomeds released.
- Four seconds.
- Okay. Nanomeds fully dispersed.
- Okay.
Let’s hit Freddie with the gamma radiation.
- Gamma exposure.
- Nanomeds now active.
- Nanomeds replicating cells on border.
- It’s working.
- Cell copy to disassemble ratio holding within 1%.
Imbalanced nanomed activity.
- ( sighs )
- You wanna go to the review board on Monday
and tell them we’ve developed
a brand-new method for exploding frogs?
- Yeah. I think maybe there’s a market for it.
I mean, what if there’s a plague?
- What have you had, Betty, like one beer?
- ( slurring ) I’m just saying, you know,
frogs start falling from the sky,
who do they come to?
We’d be world-renowned.
- Make any parent proud.
- I bet they would be.
- They actually did want me to be a scientist.
- I mean your birth parents.
- Guess we’ll never know.
- ( sighs )
I don’t understand why you don't wanna find out about them.
- They’re dead.
They died before I could remember anything.
Why do you always come back to this?
- Don’t know. Guess I figure
there’s more to you than you like to show.
I guess there couldn’t be any less.
- Right. So now we come full circle back to that.
Nice work, Betty.
- Betty?
- Glenn. - Hi.
- Hi.
- What happened to your uniform?
- Oh, I switched over.
I’m still working with your father,
but, well, you know, the military’s
subcontracting all the most interesting work.
( chuckles )
I can’t argue with the paycheck.
I basically run all the labs on the base now.
Hey, you’re looking good.
Ah, the good old college days.
So how’s business?
- What do you want?
- ( sighs )
All right, I’ll cut to the chase.
I’ve been hearing interesting things
about what you guys are doing here.
Your little molecular machines
have some incredible implications.
How’d you like to come work for Atheon?
Get paid 10 times as much as you are now
and own a piece of the patents.
You just have to say the word.
- Two words. The door.
- General?
- Come in.
- Talbot wanted you to see this, sir.
It’s about a lab Atheon is targeting
for acquisition and removal to Desert Base.
- Why isn’t he going through NSC?
- It concerns your daughter, sir.
- Hey, what happened to Benny?
Is he not working the night shift anymore?
- Benny’s dead. I’m the new guy.
- Oh.
Good to meet you. - Same.
( click )
- Let’s try another. - No, stay here.
I look tired anyway.
- Yeah, but you look great.
What’s the matter?
- It’s these dreams, Doctor.
I keep having them and they’re terrible.
- Tell me about your dream.
- Well, it starts with a memory.
I think it’s my first memory.
It’s this image I have
from when I was maybe two years old.
- Do you think it’s just a dream?
- No. I think it’s something that happened
when I was living out at Desert Base with my father.
Anyhow, the dream goes on
and suddenly I’m alone.
- That’s terrible.
You know I’d never hurt you.
- ( sighs )
- Hey there.
What’s your name, darling?
Hmm? What’s your name?
( barks and growls )
Okay. It’s okay.
- I gotta talk to you, Edith.
- Bruce, stay there.
- Aah!
- ( gasps )
( dog whimpers )
- C, T, G, A, G.
Bruce.
My Bruce.
- Morning. Glenn dropped by.
- What’s he doing here?
- You know, Dr. Krenzler,
you and I have never had the chance
to get to know each other properly.
- Well, that’s because I don’t want
to get to know you properly or improperly.
( pager beeps )
So leave.
- Hey, no worries.
You know, let me give you a little heads up.
There is a hair’s breadth
between a friendly offer and a hostile takeover.
I’ve done my homework.
The work you’re doing here is dynamite.
Think. GIs embedded with technology
that makes them instantly repairable on the battlefield
in our sole possession.
That’s a hell of a business.
- Well, that’s not what we’re doing here.
We’re doing the basic science for everyone.
- You know, someday I’m gonna write a book,
and I’m gonna call it "When Stupid Ideals
Happen to Smart, Penniless Scientists."
In the meantime, Bruce, you will be hearing from me.
- About Glenn, I, uh...
- There’s nothing to talk about.
- Okay.
I just wanted to say don’t worry about him.
I’ll handle it.
- How?
- I’m gonna call my father,
ask him to exert some pressure.
- The last I heard,
you and your father weren’t speaking.
- Hmm. Well, I guess now I have something
to talk with him about.
- I think the circuit’s kind of fried.
I don’t know. Maybe you wanna come take a look at it.
- Okay, I’ll be right there.
- Oh!
- The gamma’s too high!
Bruce, I can’t stop it!
- Harper, get out!
- Get out!
- How’s Harper?
- He’s all right. You saved him.
I don’t think he's coming back to the lab for a while, though.
I don’t understand how this is possible.
You should be dead.
- They worked, the nanomeds.
I feel great. I feel like, I don’t know.
They must have, like, fixed me.
- Bruce, they’ve killed everything else
that they’ve come into contact with.
Are you sure the doctor checked--
- The doctor gave me the full workup.
He wants to know where he can get what I’m taking.
I’m 100%. More.
- What do you mean?
- Remember my bad knee?
Well, now it’s my good knee.
- Bruce, this isn’t funny.
I was watching you.
You were gonna die,
and I was gonna have to watch you die.
- Hey, I’m sorry.
Really.
Hey, I’m not gonna explode, okay?
- Yeah. ( crying )
- You should get some rest.
I’m fine, really.
I’ve never felt better.
( dog whimpers )
- Your name is not Krenzler.
It’s Banner.
- What?
- Your name. It’s Banner,
Bruce Banner. Bruce.
- How’d you get in here?
- I work here now in the labs, the late shift.
It keeps me close to you.
You always work so late yourself with your friend Ms. Ross.
No, no, no, please, please. Let me.
You’re not well.
You’ve had a terrible accident.
You’re wondering why you’re still alive.
You’re thinking there’s something inside,
something different...
inexplicable.
I can help you understand if you let me.
If you’ll...forgive me.
- Look, mister,
I’m sure I have nothing to forgive you for,
so perhaps you should leave now.
I’ll be fine.
- You must know.
You may not want to believe it,
but I can see it in your eyes.
So much like your mother’s.
Of course, you’re my flesh and blood.
But then you’re something else, too, aren’t you?
My physical son,
but the child of my mind, too.
- No. You’re lying.
My parents died when I was a small boy.
- No, no, no, it’s not true, it’s not true.
That’s what they wanted you to believe.
The experiments, the accident, all top secret.
They put me away for 30 years.
30 years.
Away from you, away from our work.
But they couldn’t keep me forever.
After all, I’m sane. They had to admit it.
You see, everything your extraordinary mind
has been seeking all these years,
it’s been inside you.
Now you will understand it.
We will harness it.
( telephone rings )
No, don’t answer. It’s Ms. Ross again.
There’s something you need to know about her, Bruce.
Something troublesome.
Let me protect you from her.
- No. Get out.
- Bruce? - Get out!
( dogs snarl ) - Sit!
We’re gonna have to watch that temper of yours.
( dogs whimper )
( snarling )
- You sure you’re okay?
- Yeah. Just glad to be out of bed.
- I got a message from my father.
He’s coming to see me.
- Your father? When?
- Lands in about an hour.
The funny thing is, he called me.
Hi, Dad.
- Hello, Betty.
- Oh, thanks.
- You’re welcome. Sir. - Thank you.
- You’re welcome.
- Look, I’m gonna get right to it.
- It’s about Glenn, isn't it?
He’s been snooping around my lab.
- Glenn noticed some things.
Asked me to make some inquiries.
- Are you here to question me?
- No.
We’ve turned up some surprising things.
This Krenzler you work with, you know who he really is?
How much do you actually know about him?
- I think the question is
what is it that you know about him?
- Well, right now I’m not at liberty to--
- Not at liberty to disclose it to me. Right, right.
You know, I think I was hoping
that maybe this time
you just honestly wanted to see me again.
- You’ve got this all wrong, Betty.
- Do I? - Yes.
I do want to see you.
- I really wish that I could believe you.
- Father: Everything your extraordinary mind
has been seeking all these years,
it’s been inside you.
( telephone rings )
( ring )
- Answering machine: Hi. You’ve called Dr. Krenzler.
Please leave a message and I’ll call you right back.
( beep )
- Betty: Bruce, hey. Are you there?
Look, I think I screwed-up.
My father, it’s like he suspects you of something.
I don’t know. I was so impatient like always
and I didn’t hear him out.
I don’t know.
I just think that they’re planning something with the lab.
So call me, okay?
Bye.
( hangs up )
- Betty?
( growls )
( grunts )
Aah!
- Dispatch! Dispatch!
We have a 415 at the lab.
Send the Berkeley PD now. Send ’em now.
( siren )
- Edith?
- David, what’s going on?
- I gotta talk to you, Edith.
- ( growls )
- Oh!
( roars )
- Bruce.
My Bruce.
( crying )
( knock on door )
( knock knock knock )
- Bruce?
There was some sort of explosion.
They wouldn’t let us into the building.
I was worried about you.
- Well, I’m okay.
- What happened to you last night?
- I had the most vivid dream.
I was like being born, coming up for air.
Light hitting my face, screaming.
My heart beat like boom...
boom...
boom.
- Were you at the lab?
- No, but something...
But there was that man,
the one with the dogs.
- Who?
- That new janitor.
He said he was my father.
( pounding on door )
- I’ll get it.
- My, my.
So this is the young Bruce Bann--
Krenzler.
I think you left something in your lab last night.
Mitchell, escort my daughter outside.
I’ll join her shortly.
- I’d rather stay here.
- Now, Betty.
- It’s okay.
I’ll be fine.
- Keep him under observation. I’ll be back.
- What?
- Your friend in there, there’s a good chance
he’s caught up in some very bad business,
unfinished business.
I promise you, I’m gonna get to the bottom of it.
You have my word, I’ll make sure he’s cared for.
But as of right now, he’s incommunicado.
For the next few days at least,
you’re gonna stay away from here
for your own good.
- Okay, and that’s for the new guy on the night shift, right?
Great. Thank you. I appreciate it.
- Dr. Ross.
I wasn’t expecting you,
but come in.
- I’m sorry to just show up at your house like this.
- Aw.
- I came to ask you something
that I really have no business asking.
- He told you.
- He said you talked to him.
- Sit down.
- Bruce was at the lab last night.
He said that you were there, too.
He can’t remember much about it.
I need to find out what happened.
- So you wanna know what’s wrong with him
so you can fix him.
Cure him. Change him.
- My father’s with the military.
He seems to think he’s involved
in some kind of threat to national security.
- Mm-hmm, your father... Ross.
You brought your father down upon his head.
How little you understand, Ms. Ross,
and how dangerous your ignorance has become.
- I’m sorry?
- Don’t be sorry.
My son is...unique.
That’s why you can’t relate to him.
And because he is unique,
the world will not tolerate his existence, will they?
But you...
You try, don’t you?
And a very beautiful woman like you,
your attentions
can’t be completely unwanted, can they?
No, not with eyes like yours
watching expectantly, lovingly.
But I’m afraid we're both too late to help him.
There’s nothing I can do for him or for you.
Besides, he’s made it clear
he wants nothing to do with me.
His choice.
Now if you’ll excuse me, Ms. Ross,
I have some work to do.
And don’t worry about the dogs.
You’ll be fine.
Just don’t look 'em in the eyes.
Goodbye.
- Ross: He gets released
and a month later your lab is destroyed.
What a coincidence.
So you’re just not gonna tell me where he is, are you?
- How many times do I have to tell you?
I’d like to help you, but I just don’t know.
- You know who I am, right, Banner?
- You’re Betty's father. You’re a high-ranking general.
- Let’s cut the crap.
I’m the guy who had your father tossed away
and a lot more like him,
and I’ll do the same with you if I feel so disposed.
You understand?
- If you had him tossed away,
then why are you asking me? I don’t remember.
I was always told my father was dead.
- Don’t play with me!
You were four years old when you saw it.
- When I saw what?
- You were right there.
How could anyone forget a thing like that?
- What?
- Oh, some more repressed memories.
- Just tell me.
- I’m sorry, son.
You’re an even more screwed up mess than I thought you’d be.
Until we get to the bottom of this,
your lab has been declared a top secret military site.
And you’re not gonna get a security clearance
to get back into it
or any other lab that’s doing anything more interesting
than trying to figure out
the next generation of herbal hair gel.
One more thing.
If you ever come within 1,000 yards of my daughter again,
I’ll put you away for the rest of your natural life.
( dogs snarling )
- Dogs.
( barking )
Go! Go get her!
And let nothing stand in your way!
( cell phone rings )
( ring )
- Hello?
- Father: Bruce?
So they think they can just throw you away
as they did me.
- What’s wrong with me?
What did you do to me?
- I got a visit today, a very unwelcome visit.
I’m afraid my hand is being forced.
- What did you do to me?
- You so much want to know, don’t you?
But I think no explanation
will serve you half as well as experience.
In any case, I still don’t quite understand it myself.
If they’d only let me work in peace.
Of course, my betters would have none of that.
- So you experimented on yourself, didn’t you?
And passed on to me what?
- An alteration, genetic, a deformity.
I guess you could call it that,
but an amazing strength, too.
And now finally unleashed, I can harvest it.
- No. You’ll do no such thing.
I will isolate it and treat it myself.
I’ll remove it and I’ll kill it
before it does any real harm.
- Well, I bet you and your Betty would love to destroy it,
but would you really destroy part of yourself?
I don’t think so.
And as for Betty, I’m sending her a surprise visit
from some four-legged friends of mine.
You see, I managed to culture
some of your very own DNA, Bruce,
and the results are tremendous.
They’re unstable, but very powerful.
- What about my DNA?
- Let’s just wait and see
what Betty makes of the results.
- No, you’re crazy. I won’t let you.
- Get your hands off of me.
- Inside, asshole. - I wanna talk to you.
Listen to me. My father’s going after Betty.
- What makes you think you can go behind my back
and get Ross to cut me out, huh?
- Oh!
Listen to me. Betty’s in trouble.
- You pathetic freak. - Betty’s in trouble.
I swear to you she’ll be killed.
- If I can state the obvious, something tells me
you aren’t in much of a position
to be making stupid threats to anyone.
- Talbot. - Yeah?
- You’re making me angry.
- Oh, am I?
- ( growls )
( snarls )
( roars )
- Lay down fire! Open fire!
( car alarm beeps )
( crash )
- ( gasps )
( twigs snap )
( dogs snarling )
( growling and barking )
- ( growls )
Aah!
Huh?
Oh!
( roars )
He sent his dogs, didn’t he?
But I killed them.
( grunts )
- Aah!
Oh, God, it must be the nanomeds.
It must be the gamma explosion,
but we’ve never seen any effect like this before.
- No, deeper.
The gamma just unleashed what was already there.
- Unleashed what?
- Me.
It.
- It’s okay.
It’s okay.
What were those animals?
- My father sent them.
He is my father.
He wanted me to change.
He wanted me to change into that mindless hulk.
Why would he want that?
- Can you remember anything?
Is there anything from when you were changed?
- It was like a dream.
- About what?
- Rage...
power...
and freedom.
( cell phone rings )
- Hello? Sir.
- Hello? - Dad.
- Betty, are you all right?
- I’m scared.
I need your help.
- Where are you?
- How are you?
- Okay, I guess.
- I think that somehow
your anger is triggering the nanomeds.
- How could it?
We designed them to respond to physical damage.
- Emotional damage can manifest physically.
- Like what?
- Serious trauma.
Repressed memories.
- Your father grilled me about something
that happened to me from early childhood.
I’m supposed to remember.
- He did?
- It sounded bad,
but I honestly don’t remember.
- The thing that worries me
is a physical wound is finite,
but with emotions, what’s to say
that it won’t just go on and on
and start a chain reaction?
- You know what scares me the most?
Is that when it happens,
when it comes over me and I totally lose control...
I like it.
( gasps )
- It’s all right. I got you.
I’m sorry.
You’ll be okay. It’s just to make you sleep.
- Target down. - Target secure.
- I’m going to take you someplace safe, okay?
Bruce?
- Attention on deck. - Carry on.
- We’re buried out here in the middle of nowhere.
How long are you gonna keep him sedated?
- For the rest of his natural life if I have to.
- You said I could trust you.
- I’m your father.
You can trust me to do what I think is right,
not what you think you want.
- He is a human being.
- Well, he is also something else.
Suppose he gets out,
has one of his little mood swings in a populated area?
- Yes, I’m aware of the potential danger.
I’m also aware that he saved my life.
- Yeah, from a mutant French poodle.
I’m indebted to him for that.
He also put three men in a hospital,
and Talbot’s barely walking.
I mean, what do you want me to do?
- I want you to help him.
Why is he such a threat to you?
- Because I know what he comes from.
He is his father’s son, every last molecule of him.
He says he doesn’t know his father,
but he’s working in the same exact goddamned field
his father did.
So either he’s lying
or it’s something worse and he’s...
- What?
Predestined to follow in his father’s footsteps?
- I was gonna say damned.
- Of course you were.
But I’m a scientist.
As a scientist, I believe we can figure this out
and he can be helped.
- I know you do.
But whether you know or care,
I’ve got a lot of pride in what you’ve done.
But this is too big for you.
- Look, I know the government
thinks they have a weapon on their hands.
Otherwise, he’d be dead by now.
They can probe and prod all they want.
In the meanwhile, just let me try to help him.
Nobody knows him better than I do.
What did David Banner do to him?
- Cover left. - Cover left.
- Cover right!
- Aah!
( squeaking and clanking )
- What’s happening here?
- My hand.
You see the strength of my son’s DNA
combined with nanomed reconstruction?
You see, I can partake with the essences of all things.
- I’ll have to ask you to put your hands up, pal, okay?
Nice and easy.
- ( laughs )
Do you really believe
that I am separate from you?
( laughs )
- Where am I?
- You’re home.
It’s hard to believe we used to live here.
- I must have seen you or known you.
If only I could remember.
This is my old house, isn’t it?
Let’s go.
- Please try.
What is it?
- Nothing.
- Really?
- Damn it.
Okay, Betty, what do you want to know?
- What was in that room?
What are you afraid that I’ll see?
- See? There’s nothing.
It’s empty.
- What do you mean, I don’t have access to him?
- NSA has decided
to turn over study of the threat to Atheon.
- But you’re head of the base.
I thought you were in charge.
- Well, I don’t set policy,
and I still take orders.
Aah!
I can’t believe Talbot would go around me like this.
Oh, there’s a lot of powerful people that want in on this.
Money to be made, lots of it.
You know the worst part about all of this?
When I had David Banner locked up
and sent that kid away,
I didn’t give that boy a second thought.
He was just collateral damage.
Well, he isn’t anymore, is he?
- What can I do?
- You can go home now.
I’d tell you to go and say goodbye,
but I’ve already been informed that for now
all further contact is out of the question.
- Right.
- Hi, Bruce. How you feeling?
Grub okay in here for you?
- What do you want?
- That’s a good question.
See, I need your cells
to trigger some chemical distress signals.
You know, so you can turn a little green for me again
and I can carve off a piece of the real you,
analyze it, patent it, and make a fortune.
Do you mind?
- I’ll never let you.
- I’m not sure you've got much of a choice.
- Ow!
- Come on. Aren’t you feeling a little angry?
After all, you’ve only got me to play with
now that Betty’s dumped you and gone back to Berkeley.
- Ow! You’re lying.
- You know, for me, this is a win-win situation.
You turn green and all these guys come in and kill you
and I perform the autopsy.
You don’t-- - Ow!
And I mop the floor with you
and, maybe by accident, go too far and break your neck.
Bad science, maybe.
But personally gratifying.
- Ow!
- Come on, Bruce.
Let’s see what you got.
- Never.
- You know, consciously you may control it,
but subconsciously, I bet that’s another story.
All right, let’s jump-start those brain waves.
- My dear Ms. Ross. - ( gasps )
- Welcome back.
- There are two guards right outside.
- You don’t have to worry.
I’m not angry with you, not anymore.
- What do you want?
- It’s over for me now. I know that.
And soon it’ll be over for Bruce.
That’s why I've come to you.
To ask you if you could persuade your father,
as a man, as a father himself,
that if I turn myself in now peacefully
and before he puts me away forever,
that he would let me see my son
for one last time.
Would you do that for me?
- It’s out of my father’s hands now.
- I understand.
He’s a puppet now.
I don’t blame him.
- You shouldn’t. You should blame yourself
for what you’ve done to your son.
- And what have I done to my son, Ms. Ross?
Nothing. I tried to improve on the limits in myself.
Myself, not him.
Can you understand?
To improve on nature, my nature.
Knowledge of one’s self.
It’s the only path to the truth
that give men the power to go beyond God’s boundaries.
- You know what’s beyond your boundaries?
Other people.
All you’ve given Bruce is fear.
Fear of life.
- Fear.
Perhaps, Ms. Ross.
And loneliness, too, yes.
I feel them both...
but I have lived completely once.
I was so much in love,
and she so much wanted a baby, my baby.
I could tell from the moment she conceived
that it wasn’t the son I had given her,
but something else, a monster maybe.
I should have put a stop to it right then,
but I was curious
and that was my downfall.
And as I watched this tiny little life unfold,
I began to imagine the horror of it,
and the curiosity was replaced with compassion.
But they took away my chance to cure him.
Your father threw me out.
I remember the day so well,
every moment, every sensation.
Walking into the house,
the feeling of the handle of the knife in my hand.
I knew I was doing a father’s work,
fulfilling a father’s mercy.
- Edith: David, please stop it. No!
( shouting )
- But then she surprised me.
- Aah!
- No! No! David, no!
- It was as if she and the knife merged.
- No!
- You can’t imagine the unbearable finality of it.
And in that one moment,
I took everything that was dear to me
and transformed it into nothing more than a memory.
- Bingo. That must be some jumbo nightmare he just had.
Okay, do it now. Start the enzyme extraction.
- Sir, negative on drill penetration.
- Damn it, drill him harder.
Give me full RPMs. Come on, Holman, come on.
- Should I neutralize?
- No! I can’t do anything with goop. Come on!
- ( roars )
- All right, put him to sleep.
- Ah...ah...ah-choo!
- It’s not stopping him.
- Ready Room, send in our containment team.
Nonlethals only. I repeat, nonlethals only.
I must have a sample of him.
- Sir!
- Jesus.
- Hit him with the foam.
- Deploy containment foam team.
- Talbot, talk to me.
- Under control, General.
I’ll let you know if we need you.
- Unacceptable.
Unseat your asses down there immediately.
I want a full-court evacuation now.
I’m shutting you down. - Lock down.
- Didn’t you hear what the general said?
- I said lock down!
Clear! I need a sample of him.
All right, take it easy there, buddy.
This might give you a bit of a sting here, Bruce.
- ( growls )
- Fall back! Fall back!
- Clear your weapons! Clear!
- Give me the M-2! So long, big boy.
- Clear!
- Aah!
- Lock down the entire facility immediately.
- The target’s still moving towards Blue Level.
- Evacuate the main hall.
- ( roars )
- Send in backup. Heavy weapons.
Issue general quarters.
- Contamination, sir. System readings are redline.
- Data’s on backup power supply.
- Incoming!
- Shut down all power to the main hall.
- Sir? - Show him the way out.
We’ll fight him outside.
- Driver, stop. Driver, stop.
- Gunner, traverse left. Traverse left.
Aah!
- Whoa!
- Mr. President, I have some bad news, sir.
- Let’s have it, General.
- I have briefed the president on Angry Man.
I assume that’s what this is about.
- It is, ma’am.
I’m requesting a National Command Authority override.
Angry Man is unsecure.
I need everything we have at my disposal
in order to stop his movement.
- You’re expecting civilian casualties, General?
- Not if I can help it, ma’am.
- Consider it done. Keep us posted.
- Contact Goodman control.
Patch data to the assets.
Contact H.Q.
Have them initiate an immediate evacuation
in vicinity of grid coordinates 653-216.
Confirm that the area’s been cleared.
- Confirm area cleared.
- H.Q. confirms area clear.
Assets online, sir.
- Gentlemen, it’s time to dig in.
I want this target stopped in his tracks.
- Jesus.
- Mayday! Mayday!
Aw, shit!
- Tango Four is down!
Have C-SAR respond to our 20 ASAP!
- We’re okay, but get him off of us
before he tears us apart!
- I’ve got no shot.
Do you have a clear line of fire?
- Watch it, Tango flight.
- Break left! Break left!
- Tango Three, pull back
and set up for a hellfire shot.
- Hold your fire till we draw him off.
- Tango One is hot. Gun wazzed.
- Roger. Going out, gun ready.
- Engage at will.
- ( growls )
- Tango One, pull back. Clear my line.
- Tango flight, clear back.
I’ve got him painted for hellfire.
- Tango One, clear. Take your shot.
- Tango One, Tango Three, I have contact.
Holy shit! He’s got my missile!
- ( spits )
Mayday! Mayday! We’re going down!
- Give me a head count.
- Tango Three, give me a sit rep.
- Our kite’s busted up, but we’re okay.
- Tango flight, do you have eyes on the target?
- Tango One, I have him in the rocks.
- Salvo all. Turn it into a parking lot.
- T-Bolt, your parking lot is ready.
We’re bingo for fuel and ammo. RTB.
- T-Bolt, this is Goodman control.
Be advised target not destroyed.
He’s on the move again.
- Damn!
I’ve got it.
It appears he’s heading home.
Launch fast movers.
Have them intercept and engage.
( cell phone rings )
- Hello? - Betty, Bruce got out.
He’s headed your way probably right for you.
How far from the base are you?
- I’m already here.
They’re taking his father in now.
- That’s all good news.
Stay there, Betty.
- Legend One rolling in hot.
Legend Two breaking off left.
- I think I can come back around for a gun attack.
- Acquire a clear target and fire at will.
He’s out of it. Civilian aircraft.
- Aah!
- Pull up! Pull up!
You’re headed for the bridge!
- Aah!
I can’t pull up! I can’t pull up!
- Okay, you’ve got him now.
Take him on a ride to the top of the world.
Let’s see what the thin air will do for him.
- Initiating afterburner.
I’m passing flight level 600.
This is out of my envelope.
- Hang in there, Legend. - I can’t maintain.
He’s all over my aerodynamics.
- He’ll lose consciousness before you.
- 950. I can’t hold it.
I’m pulling back!
Aah!
- Puny human.
- Contact. In the water.
All units, weapons hot.
- Let’s not take any chances.
You are cleared to fire on target, Legend.
- Dad? - Betty.
I don’t have a choice.
I have to destroy him.
- But you can’t. You’ll only fuel his rage
and you will make him stronger.
- It’s you he's coming for. You know that.
- Then let me go to him. Please.
Just give him a chance to calm down.
( screaming )
- All aircraft, vicinity San Francisco.
This is T-Bolt on guard.
This area has been declared restricted airspace.
All aircraft are ordered to clear the airspace immediately.
- ( roars )
- Echo 1-9er. Weapons are hot, target acquired.
Awaiting your orders to engage.
Repeat. Awaiting your orders to engage.
- Command code yellow. Hold for authorization.
- All units, hold your fire.
- All assets, hold your fire.
I repeat, hold your fire.
( sirens )
- You found me.
- You weren’t that hard to find.
- Yes, I was.
- ( crying )
- Come on, let’s take a walk.
- That’s the deal, gentlemen.
He stays on this base
until we get the final word from C-3
on how to dispose of him.
In the meantime,
if he does anything but sit there in that chair,
I’m gonna turn on the juice
and he’ll be incinerated immediately.
- We’ve established a 200-yard perimeter, sir.
If we deploy the electromagnetic array,
there should be no collateral damage.
- I’m doing this for you, Betty.
One way or another,
we’re gonna have to prepare for the worst.
- I should have killed you.
- And I should have killed you.
- I wish you had.
I saw her last night.
Saw her face.
Brown hair.
Brown eyes.
She smiled at me.
She reached down and kissed my cheek.
I can almost remember her smell.
It was like desert flowers.
- Her favorite perfume.
- It’s my mother.
I don’t even know her name.
( crying )
- Sorry, son.
Go ahead and cry.
Cry, all right?
- Don’t touch me!
Maybe once you were my father,
but you’re not now and you never will be.
- Oh, is that so?
Well, I got news for you.
I didn’t come here to see you.
I came here to see my son,
my real son,
the one inside of you.
You’re nothing but a superficial shell,
a husk of flimsy consciousness
ready to be torn off at a moment’s notice.
- You can think what you like.
I don’t care. Just go!
- No, son, listen to me.
I found a cure for me.
My cells can transform, too.
Absorb enormous amounts of energy.
But unlike you, they’re unstable.
Son, I need your strength.
I gave you life.
Now you must give it back to me,
only a million times more radiant, more powerful.
- Stop!
- Stop what? Stop what?
Think about all those men out there in their uniforms
barking and swallowing orders,
inflicting their petty rule over the entire globe.
Think of all the harm they’ve done to you,
to me, to humanity.
And know this.
That we can make them and their flags
and their anthems and governments
disappear in a flash.
You and me.
- I’d rather die.
- Oh, that’s your answer.
And indeed you shall die and be reborn a hero
of the kind that walked the Earth
long before the pale religions of civilization
infected humanity’s soul.
- Go!
- Whaa whaa whaa.
Stop your bawling,
you weak little speck of human trash.
I’ll go.
You just watch me go!
- Hit it.
- Aah!
- ( roars )
- Hit it again. - We can’t, sir.
There’s no power.
Some kind of counterelectromagnetic field.
- Move in and assault the target. Move in!
- Sir, I’ve located them on radar. Pear Lake.
- Call up the task force.
- Yes.
- ( roars )
- That’s right. Keep fighting.
The more you fight, the more of you I take.
- Strange.
We’re reading a phenomenal drop in temperatures there.
Simultaneous radiological activity.
- They’re absorbing all the ambient energy.
- Relax.
- Sleep now, Bruce, and forget forever.
Struggle no more
and give me all of your power.
- Do you think you can live with it?
Take it.
Take it all!
- Yes.
Yes.
- ( roars )
Oh, yes!
Take it back.
It’s not stopping.
Take it back!
( screaming and groaning )
- Gentlemen, release.
- Gamma charge away.
- Sweet dreams.
( telephone rings )
( ring )
- Hello?
- Betty? That you?
- Dad?
- I’m glad I caught you.
- I’m glad you called.
- Thanks.
Look, Betty, you and I have...
Well, we both know
that Bruce couldn’t have survived that blast.
But, well, you know...
- What is it?
- Aw, you know, the usual loonies seeing things,
only now everything’s green.
- ( laughs ) Right.
- Look, if by some chance he did survive,
he should try to contact you, try to get in touch,
you’d tell me, wouldn’t you?
- No, I wouldn’t.
But you know as well as I do I wouldn’t have to.
I mean, my phones are bugged.
My computer’s tapped. I’m under surveillance.
I’ll tell you, though, that if he were alive,
I’m the last person I would want him to come to.
Because as much as I miss him,
I...I loved him, but I...
- Yeah.
I’m sorry, Betty.
I am so sorry.
- I know you are.
- ( speaking Spanish )
- Sí.
( roars )
( rock music plays )
♪ You operate and motivate on synthetic fuel ♪
♪ You’re Mother Nature and an atom bomb ♪
♪ As long as you’re kept full of pretty bodies ♪
♪ Your little secret will be safe with me ♪
♪ Around again
♪ Insane again
♪ It comes again
♪ And sets me free
♪ So set me free, set me free ♪
♪ ’Cause I think you need my soul ♪
♪ Set me free, set me free
♪ You’re kept alive and polarized ♪
♪ With one thing in mind
♪ Metabolizing everything that you see ♪
♪ But now and then or a little later ♪
♪ Now I’m gonna take you down with me ♪
♪ Around again
♪ Insane again
♪ She comes again
♪ And sets me free
♪ So set me free, set me free ♪
♪ ’Cause I think you need my soul ♪
♪ Set me free, set me free
♪ So set me free, set me free ♪
♪ ’Cause I think you need my soul ♪
♪ Set me free, set me free
♪ So take me down
♪ Take me down, down, down, down ♪
♪ Take me down, take me down ♪
♪ So take me down
♪ Take me down, down, down, down ♪
♪ Take me down, take me down ♪
♪ So set me free, set me free ♪
♪ ’Cause I think you need my soul ♪
♪ Set me free, set me free
♪ So set me free, set me free ♪
♪ ’Cause I think you need my soul ♪
♪ Set me free, set me free
♪ So set me free, set me free ♪
♪ ’Cause I think you need my soul ♪
♪ Set me free, set me free
♪ So set me free, set me free ♪
♪ ’Cause I think you need my soul ♪
♪ Set me free, set me free
♪ So set me free, set me free ♪
♪ ’Cause I think you need my soul ♪
♪ Set me free, set me free
♪ My freedom
♪ My freedom.