jmg subs
There's simply no way to shield
against every weaponized agent.
But I can make
super-immune systems...
by strengthening
the human cellular response.
Banner, I know where you're going.
But manipulating the immune system
is dangerous and stupid.
The President's science advisors
made it absolutely clear.
No human subjects.
David, I have wonderful news.
I'm gonna have a baby.
What's it gonna be? Look at that.
Want the dinosaur? Come on,
let's have a little fight. Come on.
You don't scare me.
That's a delicious eyeball.
You're big and green and scary.
I'll run away.
Bruce, you're hurt.
Jack hit him with the stick,
but Bruce wouldn't hit him back.
He just stood there, shaking.
It's okay.
Strange he didn't make a peep.
Any other kid
would've wailed his head off.
That's Bruce. He's like that.
He's just so bottled up.
The samples we found in your lab,
they were human blood.
You've ignored protocol.
You had no right
snooping around in my lab.
- That's my business.
- Wrong, Banner.
It's government business
and you're off the project.
Attention, all personnel!
Fail-safe has been initiated.
Gamma decontamination
will occur in 30 minutes.
Evacuate immediately. I repeat...
evacuate immediately!
Edith.
- David, what's going on?
- I gotta talk to you, Edith.
Bruce, stay here.
What are you doing?
David, please stop it! No!
Bruce, wake up, son.
Bruce. Bruce.
Another nightmare?
I don't know. I don't remember.
Hi, Mom.
Already off to college.
- I'm gonna Miss you terribly.
- I'll Miss you, too.
Please, come here.
Look at you.
Soon to be a great scientist.
- L guess. I mean, who knows?
- L do.
There's something inside you
so special.
Some kind of greatness, I'm sure.
Someday you're gonna...
share it with the whole world.
Berkeley Nuclear
Biotechnology institute.
As far as I'm concerned,
security ought to be...
Good morning, Dr. Krenzler.
Security ought to be beefed up
a lot more.
In a place like this,
you can't be too careful.
Bruce.
Big day. Did you sleep?
I didn't sleep.
- I slept okay. Ls Betty here?
- She's around.
I really got to say, seeing you
in that styling headwear...
You implying something
about my helmet?
You look like a massive nerd,
even around other scientists.
Can I just ask?
Were you wearing the helmet
while she dumped you?
See, it protects
my very important brain, Harper.
Go prep the samples.
Hey, I found you.
Betty, hey!
- I hate them.
- I just got here. Who do we hate?
The review board. We have to make
a presentation on Tuesday.
And you're gonna make it with me.
- You think I should?
- Yeah, you're great with that stuff.
You start talking about
microbes and nanomeds...
you sound almost passionate.
Sorry. That was rude.
Look, nobody expects this
to be easy...
us working together
after being so close.
We were close?
If I could be more...
whatever, you know. I'm just...
Don't. It's not your fault, really.
You're just a byproduct
of my inexplicable obsession...
with emotionally distant men.
I'll get over us.
Good for you.
Anyway, I'm just really stressed
about this review.
If we don't get impressive results,
we'll have a hard sell on Tuesday.
Then let's go be impressive.
Harper.
- Ready when you are.
- Let's hit it.
Are we passing inspection?
Safeties all going green.
Countdown started.
Nanomeds released.
Four seconds.
Okay. Nanomeds fully dispersed.
Okay. Let's hit Freddie
with the gamma radiation.
Gamma exposure.
Nanomeds now active.
Nanomeds replicating cells
on border.
It's working.
Cell copy-to-disassemble ratio
holding within 1%.
Imbalanced nanomed activity.
You want to tell the review board
that we've developed...
a brand-new method
for exploding frogs?
Yeah. I think maybe
there's a market for it.
What if there's a plague?
What have you had, Betty,
like one beer?
I'm just saying, you know,
frogs start falling from the sky...
who do they come to?
- We'd be world-renowned.
- Make any parent proud.
I bet they would be.
They actually did want me
to be a scientist.
I mean your birth parents.
L guess we'll never know.
I don't understand why you don't
want to find out about them.
They're dead. They died before
I could remember anything, any...
Why do you always come back to this?
I don't know.
I guess I figure there's more to you
than you like to show.
I guess there couldn't be any less.
Right. So now we come full circle
back to that.
Nice work, Betty.
Betty.
Glenn.
- Hi.
- What happened to your uniform?
- I switched over.
I'm still working
with your father...
but the military's subcontracting
the most interesting work...
and I can't argue with the paycheck.
I basically run all the labs
on the base now.
You're looking good.
...you're the genetics expert.
The good old college days.
So, how's business?
What do you want?
All right, I'll cut to the Chase.
I've heard interesting things
about what you guys are doing.
Your little molecular machines
have some incredible implications.
How'd you like to
come work for Atheon...
get paid 10 times
as much as you are now...
and own a piece of the patents?
- You just have to say the word.
- Two words: The door.
- General?
- Come in.
Talbot wanted you to see this, Sir.
It's about a lab Atheon is targeting
to acquire and move to Desert Base.
Why isn't he going through NSC?
It concerns your daughter, Sir.
What happened to Benny?
He's not working the night shift?
Benny's dead. I'm the new guy.
- Good to meet you.
- Same.
- Let's try another.
- No, stay here.
- I look tired anyway.
- Yeah, but you look great.
What's the matter?
It's these dreams, Doctor. I keep
having them and they're terrible.
Tell me about your dream.
It starts...
with a memory.
I think it's my first memory.
It's this image I have...
from when I was maybe two years old.
Do you think it's just a dream?
No, I think it's something
that happened...
when I was living at a desert base
with my father.
Anyhow, the dream goes on...
and suddenly I'm alone.
That's terrible.
You know I'd never hurt you.
Hey there.
What's your name, darling?
Okay. It's okay.
- I gotta talk to you, Edith.
- Bruce, stay here.
C, T, G, A...
G.
Bruce.
My Bruce.
Morning. Glenn dropped by.
- What's he doing here?
- You know, Dr. Krenzler...
we've never had the chance
to get to know each other properly.
It's because I don't want to get to
know you, properly or improperly.
So leave.
Hey, no worries.
You know,
let me give you a little heads up.
There is a hair's breadth between
friendly offer and hostile takeover.
I've done my homework. The work
you're doing here is dynamite.
Gl's embedded
with technology...
that makes them instantly repairable
on the battlefield...
in our sole possession.
- That's a hell of a business.
- It's not what we're doing here.
We're doing the basic science
for everyone.
You know, someday I'm gonna
write a book and I'm gonna call it.
'When Stupid ideals Happen
to Smart Penniless Scientists.
In the meantime, Bruce,
you will be hearing from me.
- About Glenn.
- There's nothing to talk about.
I just wanted to say,
don't worry about him.
I'll handle it.
How?
I'm gonna call my father.
Ask him to exert some pressure.
Last I heard, you and your father
weren't speaking.
I guess now I have something
to talk with him about.
I think this circuit's fried.
I don't know.
Maybe you want to
come take a look at it.
Okay, I'll be right there.
The gamma's too high!
Bruce, I can't stop it!
Harper, get out!
Get out!
- How's Harper?
- He's all right.
You saved him.
I don't think he's coming back
to the lab for a while, though.
I don't understand
how this is possible.
You should be dead.
They worked.
The nanomeds.
I feel great. I feel like...
I don't know,
they must have fixed me.
They've killed everything else
that they've come in contact with.
Are you sure the doctor checked.
The doctor gave me the full workup.
He wants to know
where he can get what I'm taking.
I'm 100%.
More.
- What do you mean?
- Remember my bad knee?
Now it's my good knee.
Bruce, this isn't funny.
I was watching you.
You were gonna die and I was gonna
have to watch you die.
I'm sorry.
Really.
I am not gonna explode, okay?
Yeah.
You should get some rest.
I'm fine, really.
I've Never Felt Better.
Your name is not Krenzler.
It's Banner.
- What?
- Your name. It's Banner.
Bruce Banner.
- How did you get in here?
- L work here now.
In the labs. The late shift.
It keeps me close to you.
You always work so late yourself
with your friend, Miss Ross.
No, please. Let me.
You're not well.
You've had a terrible accident.
You're wondering why
you're still alive.
You're thinking
there's something inside.
Something different.
Inexplicable.
I can help you understand,
if you let me.
If you'll...
forgive me.
Look, mister...
I'm sure I have nothing
to forgive you for...
so perhaps you should leave now.
I'll be fine.
You must know.
You may not want to believe it,
but I can see it...
in your eyes.
So much like your Mother's.
Of course you're my flesh
and blood...
but then you're something else, too,
aren't you?
My physical son...
but the child of my mind, too.
No. You're lying.
My parents died
when I was a small boy.
No, that's not true.
That's what
they wanted you to believe.
The experiments, the accident,
all top-secret.
They put me away for 30 years.
30 years.
Away from you. Away from our work.
But they couldn't keep me forever.
I'm sane. They had to admit it.
You see...
everything your
extraordinary mind...
has been seeking all these years...
it's been inside you.
Now we will understand it.
We will harness it.
Don't answer. It's Miss Ross again.
There's something
you need to know about her, Bruce...
something troublesome.
Let me protect you from her.
No. Get out.
Get out!
Sit!
We're gonna have to watch
that temper of yours.
- Sure you're okay?
- Yeah, just glad to be out of bed.
I got a message from my father.
He's coming to see me.
Your father? When?
He lands in about an hour.
The funny thing is, he called me.
- Hi, Dad.
- Hello, Betty.
- Here, ma'am.
- Thanks.
You're welcome. Sir.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Look, I'm gonna get right to it.
- It's about Glenn, isn't it?
He's been snooping around my lab.
Glenn noticed some things.
He asked me to make some inquiries.
- Are you here to question me?
- No.
We've turned up
some surprising things.
This Krenzler you work with...
do you know who he really is?
How much do you actually know
about him?
I think the question is...
what is it that you know about him?
I'm not at Liberty to.
Not at Liberty
to disclose it to me. Right.
You know, I think I was hoping...
that maybe this time you just
honestly wanted to see me again.
You've got this all wrong, Betty.
- Do I?
- Yes.
I do want to see you.
I really wish
that I could believe you.
Everything your extraordinary mind...
has been seeking all these years...
it's been inside you.
This is Dr. Krenzler.
Please leave a message
and I'll call you right back.
Bruce, hey. Are you there?
Look, I think I screwed up.
My father, it's like
he suspects you of something.
I was so impatient, like always...
I didn't hear him out. I don't know.
I just think they're planning
something with the lab.
So call me, okay? Bye.
Betty!
Dispatch! We have a 4-15 at the lab!
Send the Berkeley P.D. now!
What's going on?
- L gotta talk to you.
- Bruce, stay here.
My Bruce.
Bruce?
There was some sort of explosion.
They wouldn't let us
into the building.
I was worried about you.
I'm okay.
What happened to you last night?
I had the most vivid dream.
It was like being born.
Coming up for air.
Light hitting my face. Screaming.
My heartbeat was like...
boom...
boom.
Were you at the lab?
No.
But something...
And there was that man.
The one with the dogs.
Who?
That new janitor.
He said he was my father.
I'll get it.
My father.
My, my.
So this is the young Bruce Banner.
Krenzler.
I think you left something
in your lab last night.
Mitchell.
Escort my daughter outside.
I'll join her shortly.
- I'd rather stay here.
- Now, Betty.
It's okay. I'll be fine.
Keep him under observation.
I'll be back.
- What?
- Your friend in there...
there's a good chance
he's caught up in some bad business.
Unfinished business.
I promise you, I'm going to
get to the bottom of it.
You have my word
I'll make sure he's cared for.
But as of right now,
he's incommunicado.
For the next few days at least...
you're going to stay away from here,
for your own good.
And that's for the new guy
on the night shift?
Great. Thank you. I appreciate it.
How unexpected. Please, come in.
I'm sorry to show up
at your house like this.
I came to ask you something...
that I really have
no business asking.
He told you?
He said you talked to him.
Please, sit down.
Bruce was at the lab last night.
He said that you were there, too,
but he can't remember much about it.
I need to find out what happened.
So you want to know
what's wrong with him.
So you can fix him.
Cure him. Change him.
My father's with the military.
He thinks he's involved in some
kind of threat to national security.
Your father, Ross.
You brought your father
down upon his head.
How little you understand,
Miss Ross.
And how dangerous
your ignorance has become.
- I'm sorry?
- Don't be sorry.
My son is... unique.
That's why you can't relate to him.
And because he is unique...
the world will not tolerate
his existence, will they?
But you...
you try, don't you?
And a very beautiful woman
like you...
your attentions...
can't be completely unwanted...
can they?
No.
Not with eyes like yours...
watching expectantly, lovingly.
But I'm afraid
we're both too late to help him.
There's nothing I can do for him,
or for you.
Besides...
he's made it clear
he wants nothing to do with me.
His choice.
Now if you'll excuse me, Miss Ross,
I have some work to do.
And don't worry about the dogs.
You'll be fine.
Just don't look them in the eyes.
Goodbye.
He gets released, and a month later
your lab is destroyed.
What a coincidence.
So, you're just not gonna tell me
where he is, are you?
How many times must I tell you...
I want to help you,
but I don't know.
You know who I am, right, Banner?
You're Betty's father,
a high-ranking general.
Let's cut the crap.
I'm the guy
who had your father tossed away.
I'll do the same with you if I feel
so disposed, you understand?
If you had him tossed away,
why ask me? I don't remember.
I was always told
my father was dead.
Don't play with me!
You were four years old
when you saw it!
When I saw what?
You were right there!
Who could forget a thing like that?
What?
Some more repressed memories.
Just tell me.
I'm sorry, son.
You're an even more screwed-up mess
than I thought you'd be.
Till we get to the bottom of this...
your lab has been declared
a top-secret military site...
and you won't get security clearance
to get back into it...
or any other lab that's doing
anything more interesting than...
trying to figure out the next
generation of herbal hair gel.
And one more thing
if you ever come
within a thousand yards...
of my daughter again...
I'll put you away
for the rest of your natural life.
Dogs?
Go!
Go get her!
And let nothing stand in your way!
- Hello?
- Bruce?
So, they think they can just
throw you away, as they did me.
What's wrong with me?
What did you do to me?
I had a visit today.
A very unwelcome visit.
I'm afraid my hand is being forced.
What did you do to me?
You so much want to know,
don't you?
But no explanation will serve you
half as well as experience.
In any case, I still don't
quite understand it myself.
If they'd only let me work in peace.
But, of course, my betters
would have none of that.
So you experimented on yourself,
didn't you?
And passed on to me, what?
An alteration. Genetic.
A deformity,
I guess you could call it that.
But an amazing strength, too.
And now, finally unleashed,
I can harvest it.
No.
You'll do no such thing.
I'll isolate it and treat myself.
I'll remove it and kill it
before it does any real harm.
I bet you and your Betty
would love to destroy it.
But would you really destroy
part of yourself?
I don't think so.
And as for Betty...
I'm sending her a surprise visit
from my four-legged friends.
You see, I've managed to culture
some of your very own DNA, Bruce...
and the results are tremendous.
They're unstable, but very powerful.
What about my DNA?
Let's just wait and see
what Betty makes of the result.
No. You're crazy. I won't let you.
Get your hands off me!
Inside, asshole!
I want to talk to you.
My father's going after Betty.
Do you think you can go
behind my back...
and get Ross to cut me out?
Listen to me! Betty's in trouble!
You pathetic freak.
Betty's in danger, I swear to you.
If I can state the obvious,
something tells me...
you aren't in much of a position to
be making stupid threats to anyone.
- Talbot.
- Yeah?
- You're making me angry.
- Am I?
Open fire!
BRUCE?
He sent his dogs, didn't he?
But I killed them.
Oh, my God.
It must be the nanomeds.
It must be the gamma exposure.
But we've never seen any effect
like this before.
No. Deeper.
The gamma just unleashed
what was already there.
Unleashed what?
Me.
Lt.
it's okay.
What were those animals?
My father sent them.
He is my father.
He wanted me to change.
He wanted me to change
into that mindless hulk.
And why would he want that?
Can you remember anything?
Is there anything
from when you were changed?
It was like a dream.
About what?
Rage.
Power.
And freedom.
Hello.
Sir.
- Dad?
- Betty, are you all right?
I'm scared.
- I need your help.
- Where are you?
How are you?
Okay, I guess.
I think that somehow your anger
is triggering the nanomeds.
How could it? We designed them
to respond to physical damage.
Emotional damage
can manifest physically.
Like what?
Serious trauma.
Repressed memories.
Your father grilled me
about something...
that happened to me
from early childhood...
that I'm supposed to remember.
- He did?
- Lt sounded bad...
but I honestly don't remember.
The thing that worries me...
is a physical wound is finite.
But with emotions, what's to say
that it won't just go on and on...
and start a chain reaction?
You know what scares me the most?
Ls that when it happens...
when it comes over me
and I totally lose control...
I like it.
it's okay, I've got you. I'm sorry.
You'll be okay.
It's just to make you sleep.
- Target down.
- Target secure.
I'm gonna take you
someplace safe, okay?
Bruce. Bruce.
- Attention on deck.
- Carry on.
We're buried out here
in the middle of nowhere.
How long are you gonna
keep him sedated?
For the rest of his natural life,
if I have to.
- You said I could trust you.
- I'm your father.
Trust me to do
what I think is right...
not what you think you want.
- He is a human being.
- He is also something else.
Suppose he gets out...
and has one of his little
mood swings in a populated area?
Yes, I'm aware
of the potential danger.
I'm also aware
that he saved my life.
Yeah, from a mutant French poodle.
I'm indebted to him for that.
He also put three men in a hospital,
and Talbot's barely walking.
- I mean, what do you want me to do?
- I want you to help him!
Why is he such a threat to you?
Because I know what he comes from.
He is his father's son,
every last molecule of him.
He says he doesn't know his father.
But he's working in the same,
exact goddamn field his father did.
So either he's lying,
or it's something worse...
- And he's...
- What?
Predestined to follow
in his father's footsteps?
I was going to say 'damned.
Of course you were.
But I'm a scientist,
and as a scientist...
I believe we can figure this out
and he can be helped.
I know you do.
Look, whether you know or care...
I've got a lot of pride
in what you've done.
But this is too big for you.
Look, I know the government thinks
they have a weapon on their hands...
otherwise, he'd be dead by now.
They can probe and prod
all they want.
Meanwhile, let me try to help him.
Nobody knows him better than I do.
What did David Banner do to him?
Cover left! Cover right!
What's happening here?
My hand.
You see,
the strength of my son's DNA...
combined with
nanomed reconstruction...
You see, I can partake
with the essences of all things.
I'm gonna have to ask you
to put your hands up, pal, okay?
Nice and easy.
Do you really believe
that I am separate from you?
Where am I?
You're home.
It's hard to believe
we used to live here.
I must have seen you or known you.
If only I could remember.
This is my old house, isn't it?
Let's go.
Please try.
- What is it?
- Nothing.
Really?
Damn it.
Okay, Betty.
What do you want to know?
What was in that room?
What are you afraid that I'll see?
See? There's nothing.
It's empty.
What do you mean
I don't have access to him?
NSA has decided to turn over
study of the threat...
to Atheon.
But you're head of the base.
I thought you were in charge.
I don't set policy.
And I still take orders.
I can't believe
Talbot would go around me like this!
There's a lot of powerful people
who want in on this...
and money to be made, lots of it.
Know the worst part about all this?
When I had David Banner locked up
and sent that kid away...
I didn't give the boy
a second thought.
He was just collateral damage.
He isn't anymore, is he?
What can I do?
You can go home now.
I'd tell you to go and say goodbye,
but I've already been informed...
that for now all further contact
is out of the question.
Right.
Hi, Bruce. How you feeling?
The grub okay here for you?
- What do you want?
- That's a good question.
I need your cells to trigger
some chemical distress signals...
so you can turn
a little green for me again...
and I can carve off a piece
of the real you...
analyze it, patent it
and make a fortune.
You mind?
I'll never let you.
I'm not sure
you've got much of a choice.
Come on,
aren't you feeling a little angry?
After all,
you've only got me to play with...
now that Betty's dumped you
and gone back to Berkeley.
You're lying.
You know, for me,
this is a win-win situation.
You turn green, all these guys
come in and kill you...
and I perform the autopsy.
You don't...
and I mop the floor with you...
and maybe by accident
go too far and break your neck.
It's bad science, maybe...
but personally gratifying.
Come on, Bruce.
Let's see what you got.
Never.
You know, consciously,
you may control it...
but subconsciously,
I bet that's another story.
All right,
let's jump-start those brain waves.
My dear Miss Ross, welcome back.
There are two guards right outside.
You don't have to worry.
I'm not angry with you, not anymore.
What do you want?
It's over for me now, I know that.
And soon it will be over for Bruce.
That's why I've come to you,
to ask you...
if you could persuade your father...
as a man, as a father himself...
that if I turn myself in now,
peacefully...
and before he
puts me away forever...
that he would let me see my son...
for one last time.
Could you do that for me?
It's out of my father's hands now.
I understand. He's a puppet now.
- I don't blame him.
- You shouldn't.
You should blame yourself
for what you've done to your son.
And what have I done to my son,
Miss Ross? Nothing.
I tried to improve
on the limits in myself.
Myself, not him.
Can you understand?
To improve on nature. My nature.
Knowledge of oneself.
It's the only path to the truth...
that gives men the power
to go beyond God's boundaries.
You know what's beyond
your boundaries? Other people.
All you've given Bruce is fear.
A fear of life.
Fear?
Perhaps, Miss Ross.
And loneliness, too.
Yes.
I feel them both.
But I have lived...
completely once.
I was so much in love.
And she so much wanted a baby...
my baby.
I could tell from the moment
she conceived...
that it wasn't a son
I had given her...
but something else.
A monster, maybe.
I should have put a stop to it
right then...
but I was curious...
and that was my downfall.
And as I watched
this tiny life unfold...
I began to imagine
the horror of it...
and my curiosity was replaced...
with compassion.
But they took away
my chance to cure him.
Your father threw me out.
I remember that day so well...
every moment, every sensation.
Walking into the house...
the feeling of the handle
of the knife in my hand.
I knew I was doing
a father's work...
fulfilling a father's Mercy.
David, please stop it! No!
David, talk to me!
But then she surprised me.
It was as if...
she and the knife...
merged.
Go!
You cannot imagine...
the unbearable finality of it.
And in that one moment...
I took everything
that was dear to me...
and transformed it...
into nothing more than a memory.
Bingo! That must be some
jumbo nightmare he just had.
Do it now.
Start the enzyme extraction.
Sir, negative on drill penetration.
Damn it, drill him harder.
Give me full RPMs. Come on.
- Should I neutralize?
- No!
I can't do anything with goop.
Come on!
All right, put him to sleep.
It's not stopping him!
Ready room, send in our
containment team, non-lethals only.
I repeat, non-lethals only.
I must have a sample of him.
Sir!
Jesus.
- Use the foam.
- Deploy containment foam.
Talbot, talk to me.
Cease fire!
Under control, General.
I'll let you know if we need you.
Unacceptable. Unseat your asses
down there immediately.
I want a full evacuation now.
I'm shutting you down.
Lock down.
- Didn't you hear the General?
- I said lock down!
Clear! I need a sample of him!
All right,
take it easy there, buddy.
This might give you
a bit of a sting here, Bruce.
Fall back!
Clear your weapon!
Give me the M2.
So long, big boy.
Clear!
Lock down
the entire facility immediately.
Target still moving
towards blue level.
Evacuate the main hall.
Send in backup, heavy weapons.
Issue general quarters.
Contamination, Sir.
System readings are redline.
Stand by
for backup power supply.
Incoming!
- Shut down power to the main hall.
- Sir?
Show him the way out.
We'll fight him outside.
Driver, stop.
Gunner! Traverse right!
Mr. President,
I have some bad news, Sir.
Let's have it, General.
I've briefed the President
on Angry Man.
I assume that's what this is about.
Lt is, ma'am.
I'm requesting a National
Command Authority override.
Angry Man is unsecure.
I need everything we have
at my disposal to stop his movement.
You're expecting
civilian casualties, General?
Not if I can help it, ma'am.
Consider it done. Keep us posted.
Contact Goodman Control.
Patch data to the assets.
Contact HQ.
Have them initiate
an immediate evacuation...
in the vicinity
of grid coordinates 6-5...
Confirm that the area
has been cleared.
Confirm area cleared.
HQ confirms area cleared.
Assets on-line, Sir.
Gentlemen, it's time to dig in.
I want this target
stopped in his tracks.
Jesus.
Mayday!
Shit!
Tango-4 is down.
Have C-SAR respond to our 20 now.
Get him off us
before he tears us apart!
I've got no shot!
You have a line of fire?
- Watch it, Tango.
- Break left!
Tango-3, pull back
and set up for a Hellfire shot.
Hold your fire
until we draw him off.
Tango-1 is hot.
Roger. Going hot. Guns ready.
Engage at will.
Tango-1, pull back! Clear my line!
Tango-flight, clear.
I have him painted for Hellfire.
Tango-1 clear. Take the shot.
Tango-1, Tango-3, I have contact.
Holy shit! He's got my missile!
Mayday!
Mayday! We're hit! We're going down!
- Give me a head count.
- Tango-3.
Our kite's busted up,
but we're okay.
Tango-flight,
you have eyes on the target?
Tango-1, I have him in the rocks.
Salvo all.
Turn it into a parking lot.
T-bolt, your parking lot is ready.
We're bingo for fuel and ammo. RTB.
T-bolt.
Be advised, target not destroyed.
He's on the move again.
Damn!
I've got it.
It appears he's heading home.
Launch fast movers.
Have them intercept and engage.
- Hello?
- Betty, Bruce got out.
He's headed your way,
probably right for you.
How far from the base are you?
I'm already here.
They're taking his father in now.
That's all good news.
Stay there, Betty.
Legend-1 rolling in hot.
Legend-2 breaking left.
I think I can come
back around for a gun attack.
Acquire a clear target.
Fire at will.
Increase altitude.
Civilian aircraft in vicinity.
Pull up!
You're headed for the bridge!
I can't pull up!
You got him. Take him
on a ride to the top of the world.
Let's see what the thin air
will do for him.
Initiating afterburn.
I'm passing Flight Level 600.
This is out of my envelope.
Hang in there, Legend.
I can't maintain.
He's all over my aerodynamics.
He'll lose consciousness before you.
950.
I can't hold it. I'm pulling back.
Puny human.
Contact. He's in the water.
All units, weapons hot.
Let's not take any chances.
You are cleared
to fire on target, Legend.
- Dad?
- Betty?
We don't have a choice.
I have to destroy him.
But you can't.
You'll only fuel his rage
and make him stronger.
It's you he's coming for,
you know that.
Then let me go to him.
Please.
Just give him a chance to calm down.
All aircraft
vicinity San Francisco...
this is T-bolt on guard.
This area has been declared
restricted airspace.
All aircraft are ordered
to clear the airspace immediately.
Echo-19, weapons are hot.
Target acquired.
Waiting your orders to engage.
Command code yellow.
Hold for authorization.
All units, hold your fire.
T-bolt to all assets.
You have direct orders to hold your fire.
I repeat. Hold your fire.
Move now!
Everybody down! Down!
You found me.
You weren't that hard to find.
Yes, I was.
That's the deal, gentlemen.
He stays on this base until
we get the final word from C-3...
on how to dispose of him.
In the meantime, if he does
anything but sit in that chair...
we'll turn on the juice and
he'll be incinerated immediately.
We've established
a 200-yard perimeter, Sir.
If we deploy
the electromagnetic array...
there should be
no collateral damage.
I'm doing this for you, Betty.
But one way or another, we're gonna
have to prepare for the worst.
L should have killed you.
As I should have killed you.
I wish you had.
I saw her last night.
Saw her face.
Brown hair...
brown eyes.
She smiled at me.
She reached down
and kissed my cheek.
I can almost remember a smell.
It was like desert flowers.
Her favorite perfume.
It's my Mother...
and I don't even know her name.
It's all right, son.
Go ahead and cry.
- Cry. Crying will do you good.
- Don't touch me!
Maybe once you were my father.
But you're not now
and you never will be.
Ls that so?
Well, I got news for you.
I didn't come here to see you.
I came here to see my son.
My real son.
The one inside of you.
You're nothing
but a superficial shell...
a husk of flimsy consciousness...
ready to be torn off
at a moment's notice.
You can think what you like.
I don't care. Just go.
No, son, listen to me.
I found a cure.
For me.
My cells can transform, too...
absorb enormous amounts of energy.
But, unlike you, they're unstable.
Son...
I need your strength.
I gave you life.
Now you must give it back to me...
only a million times more radiant...
more powerful.
- Stop!
- Stop what?
Stop what?
Think of all those men out there
in their uniforms...
barking and swallowing orders!
Inflicting their petty rule
over the entire globe!
Think of all the harm they've done!
To you! To me!
To humanity!
And know this,
that we can make them...
and their flags, their anthems
and their governments...
disappear in a flash!
You in me.
I'd rather die.
That's your answer?
Then indeed you shall die...
and be reborn a hero...
of the kind that walked the Earth...
long before the pale religions
of civilization...
infected humanity's soul!
Go!
Stop your bawling...
you weak little speck
of human trash.
I'll go.
You just watch me go!
Hit it!
- Hit it again.
- We can't, Sir.
There's no power. Some kind of
counter electromagnetic field.
Move in and assault the target.
Move in!
Sir, I've located them on radar.
Pear Lake.
Call up the task force.
Yes.
That's right. Keep fighting.
The more you fight,
the more of you I take.
Strange.
We're reading a phenomenal drop
in temperatures there...
with simultaneous
radiological activity.
They're absorbing
all the ambient energy.
Relax.
Sleep now, Bruce,
and forget forever.
Struggle no more...
and give me all of your power.
You think you can live with it?
Take it!
Take it all!
Yes.
Take it back.
It's not stopping!
Take it back!
Gentlemen, release.
Gamma charge away.
Sweet dreams.
ONE YEAR LATER...
- Hello?
- Betty? Is that you?
Hi, Dad.
I'm glad I caught you.
- I'm glad you called.
- Thanks.
Look, Betty...
you and I...
We both know that Bruce...
couldn't have survived that blast.
But... Well, you know...
What is it?
You know, the usual loonies...
seeing things,
only now everything's green.
Right.
Look...
if by some chance he did survive...
and he should try to contact you,
and try to get in touch...
you'd tell me, wouldn't you?
No. I wouldn't.
But you know as well as I do
I wouldn't have to.
I mean, my phones are bugged...
my computer is tapped,
I'm under surveillance.
I'll tell you, though...
that if he were alive...
I'm the last person
I would want him to come to...
because, as much as I Miss him...
I loved him.
I'm sorry, Betty.
I am so sorry.
I know you are.
Listen to your father
and take your medicine, okay?
Take all the medicine.
Quiet!
Sit down!
Shut up!
We need these medicines
for the people who live here.
Who are you to decide
what the people need?
These people are helping
our enemies.
And maybe you are too.
Take all this.
It is the property
of the government.
You're making me angry.
You wouldn't like me when I'm angry.