Attack!
- Go! Come on! Get out there!
- To the ladders!
Get out!
Heinrich, come on, move! Let's go!
To the ladders!
On my command!
- Charge!
- Hans?
Attack! Get out there!
Go! Charge!
- Hans?
- Go, Heinrich! Get out there!
Attack!
Keep going!
Faster! Go! Faster!
Take cover!
Heinrich!
ALL QUIET ON THE WESTERN FRONT
NORTHERN GERMANY
SPRING 1917
THIRD YEAR OF WAR
- Paul!
Paul. Hey.
Well?
- So, what now?
- Don't know.
- Does he know we're all going?
- Of course.
You're staying home?
My God, staying tied
to your mummy's apron-strings?
Here, I'll sign it for you.
- His parents have to do that.
- But they didn't. Give it here.
- It won't work. They'll find out.
- How?
How? Are they pen pals with his father?
- Give me your pen.
- I don't have one.
Ludwig.
You'll be in trouble.
You'll get a thrashing.
Got a better idea?
I won't be the only one left behind.
Yeah!
Congratulations, Private Béumer.
You're going to the front.
I'm a dead man.
You're standing here
on the threshold of existence.
Remember this moment.
It's an important moment.
In years to come, you will be judged
on what you dared to become today.
The Iron Youth of Germany.
My friends,
you are fortunate
to be living in great times.
Your deeds will be the water
that will nourish a strong and noble root.
Stand still and listen, Leinemann!
The Kaiser needs soldiers, not children.
I am sure that I will see most of you
here at home again soon,
your sword returned
to its scabbard with honour.
With an Iron Cross
pinned to your proud chest.
But don't be fooled.
During the darkest hours out there
as you await an attack,
you may start to harbour doubts.
But this is no time for weakness of mind!
Any wavering, any hesitation
is a betrayal of the Fatherland!
Modern warfare is like a game of chess.
It's never about the individual.
It's always about the whole.
You will prove yourselves
worthy of your uniforms
and break through
the enemy front in Flanders.
And then, in just a few weeks,
you will finally march on Paris!
'Yes!
Our future,
the future of Germany,
lies in the hands
of its greatest generation.
My friends, that's you!
Yes!
So, off to battle!
For Kaiser, God and Fatherland!
Yes!
- Bravo!
- Yes!
Next.
Béumer, Paul. 53 Wiesengrund.
Born 18th November '99.
- Correct?
- Yes, sir.
Next.
Paul?
Here. Your father can be proud of you.
- Yes.
- Next.
Everything all right?
- Yes, I just want to get going at last.
- Next.
Off you go.
Next.
Excuse me.
This belongs to someone.
Next.
Yes. It was probably too small
for the fellow. Happens all the time.
Here. Take care.
Thank you.
Blimey, as if they were tailor-made!
Well, Ludwig,
are you going to get all the girls now?
Yeah.
As long as you don't shoot us.
Girl, I do love you
But I can't marry you just yet
Wait another year
Then it will...
She won't wait, Franz.
She won't wait.
You lady killer, you.
Drink a cup of tea, sugar and coffee
And a glass of wine
Girl, I do love you
But I can't marry you just yet
Wait another year
Then it will come true
Then it will come true...
LA MALMAISON, NORTHERN FRANCE
25 KM TO THE WESTERN FRONT
What's your name, soldier?
Kropp. Albert Kropp, sir.
Do you like dirty girls, Kropp?
Do you like dirty girls?
No, sir.
Why did you sleep with one then?
Report for guard duty at 3 a.m.
Gentlemen, you'll be fighting
in an absolute shithole.
And you'd better do it with a clean G98.
You'll pamper it.
You'll love it.
And damn it, you'll keep it as spotless
as the Holy Virgin's thighs.
- Do we understand each other?
- Yes, sir!
Welcome
to the 78th Infantry Reserve Regiment.
We're on the Western Front now.
Welcome to Paris!
Yes!
Damn it, what happened?
I have to deliver the company
to the front by 6 p.m.
You can, but on foot.
We need the trucks, Lieutenant.
- With all due respect, my orders...
- You can stick your orders up your arse!
I've got 40 men here dying in the mud.
Get out right now!
Everyone out!
Come on. Make it snappy.
You heard the staff surgeon.
Faster, soldiers! Don't fall asleep here!
Come on!
- Franz Mijller, right?
- Yes.
The commander-in-chief expects you
to survive at least six weeks.
- Do you want to be alive in six weeks?
- Yes, sir.
Then stop dragging your feet
and get a move on!
- Did you hear me?
- Yes.
Hurry UP!
We're not at a tea dance!
Gas!
'Gas!
Gas masks on!
That, gentlemen, was a fat pig.
If the French could aim better,
they'd be scraping us off the road now
with a spoon and burying us in a mess tin.
But one thing is as sure as eggs is eggs.
Fat pigs don't carry gas.
Eyes front!
- Have you got cloth ears?
- No, sir.
I was just trying to put on my mask.
You, Paul Béumer,
will almost certainly be dead by dawn.
You should eat something, damn it.
Attention! Gas masks off!
Gas masks off!
Not you. You keep yours on
until guard duty tonight.
With that bonehead there.
Line up! March!
Stick together and get moving!
Come on, hurry up!
Paul! Paul, come on.
Give me your backpack.
You can carry mine next time.
Congratulations, soldiers.
This is your new home.
Helmets off!
I see the men have been enjoying
my absence, Steinberger.
There was gunfire all night.
Their nerves are shot.
Dry boots are a good remedy for that.
Do you want us all to drown?
Everyone pitches in! Bail out the trench.
What are you waiting for, Béumer?
Why are you still standing around?
Throw a dog a bone,
it will always snap it up.
Give a man power...
Man is a beast.
Drink.
Katczinsky, come over here. Lend a hand.
We'll get hit hard tonight.
Sorry.
Forget about it.
This isn't how I imagined it.
Shut up, Ludwig.
My hands. I can't feel my hands any more.
Stick them down your trousers.
That's what I always do.
You think that will make it shoot better?
- Did you hear that?
- What?
That sound. Listen.
There's nothing there.
Our first Frenchmen.
Calm down, Paulie.
I hear it now too.
Who's there?
Hey.
Show yourself!
No!
| Qot hit!
- No, Paul. No.
- What's going on there?
Oh, no.
What is it?
They shot at me from over there.
They saw your muzzle flash.
Keep your heads down.
Unless you want to catch the next bullet
with your teeth, move ten metres.
Shoot, then move.
Shoot, then move. Understood?
Yes.
Come on.
Take cover!
In here!
Béumer, Kropp! You two, in here. Quick!
In the bunker!
Get in!
"Watch what you eat."
That's what my mother said.
- We'll stick together, Paul.
- Yeah.
- We'll stick together.
I can't do this, Paul.
I can't do this. I want to go home.
I want to go home.
Creeping barrage.
What?
Every few minutes,
the artillery barrage moves forward,
and directly behind it,
the infantry advances.
What does that mean?
They're coming.
- Where are you going?
- I'll be right back.
The barrage is nearly over.
- No. Let me go.
- Calm down.
- Let me out. I want to get out of here.
- Calm down!
Calm down.
No!
Get out!
Move! Get out!
Get out of here!
Everyone, get out!
Paul. That's Paul.
Albert!
Albert, we've found Paul!
We have to move that beam.
Paul.
Are you okay?
Are you okay, Paul?
Come on. Paul, come on. I'll help you.
Come on. Up you come. Sit down.
- Are you injured?
- Keep going.
Paul, are you injured?
- Can you hear me?
- Albert Kropp, we need help!
- See you later, Paul.
Katczinsky, get on with it!
And you? Are you injured?
No.
Then start collecting.
Oh, man!
Hard work pays off.
Come on! Keep moving now!
We haven't got all day.
Albrecht, Karl. Diepholz.
18 MONTHS LATER
14th September 1898.
Blumenthal, Samuel.
Dresden, 6th November 1900.
It was his birthday yesterday.
Von Gallwitz, Gustav.
Osnabrijck, 20th June '99.
Gétz Lijttwitz...
That's enough.
GERMAN HIGH COMMAND
7 NOVEMBER 1918
Mr. Erzberger.
May God be with us.
Again more than 40,000 dead
in the last weeks alone.
That should convince the general staff.
I think the gentlemen know it's over.
We all know.
The Field Marshal.
CHAMPAGNE, FRANCE
OCCUPIED TERRITORY
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
If we keep up this pace, Paul,
we'll have conquered France in 180 years.
I worked it out.
Don't get caught, Kat.
Never.
Listen.
What do you think, Paul?
Is it worth dying for?
It is when you're hungry.
Kat?
Run!
Hey! Dirty Kraut!
Men, you're heroes.
Shut the door,
or the others will smell it.
- Password.
- I don't know. I've forgotten everything.
- Use your Prussian brain.
- Here. Eyes wide, long fingers.
- Exactly.
- Mouth open, goose in.
A piece of goose from the goose.
From Franz to Franz.
I'll have a wing.
Do I have to share? I'll have the rest.
Well, in with it!
Come here, you blind hen.
Wide-mouthed frog.
- May we rest in peace under the barrage.
- Oh, God.
Oh, God.
Hey, boys, I'll never forget this.
Does it taste good?
Yes.
- And you?
- Yes, good.
Good, Paul?
Good, Kat.
Life is short.
Where's Emil when you need him?
Emil, bring over the coffee and caviar!
Yes, and run a foot bath.
I need a foot bath.
Kat?
What is it?
You stole the goose Give it back
Give it back
- Or the hunter will get you...
- The farmer!
The farmer! Yes!
Or the farmer will get you
With his rifle...
Tjaden sits very quietly and says,
"A|| I ever hear about is crosses."
"My father was Captain of Nazareth."
"Captain of Nazareth?" asks the teacher.
"Never heard of it.
Tjaden, go home and ask again, okay?"
The next morning,
Tjaden rushes into the classroom and says,
"|'m so sorry,
my father wasn't Captain of Nazareth."
"My father had the clap in a |azaret."
Tjaden didn't even go to school.
Look!
Hey! Hello!
Come here!
Fresh baguette!
For you!
Lebervvurst, love!
Lots of love!
Hey, Franz, where are you going?
- Take me with you!
- Come on then!
Look!
Now he's making a fool of himself.
Ooh la la! You're very beautiful, my love.
Franz!
The skinny dark-haired one is mine!
Where's he going now?
Franz?
Goodbye!
Goodbye, my friends!
Damn.
If it was all over now,
you know what I'd do?
There's no peace. It's not over.
But if it was.
- Bloody hell, there'd be girls again.
- Yes, indeed.
I wouldn't wear any trousers for a week.
I should smack your arses
for bringing that up.
What about you, Paul?
- No idea. Can't think of anything.
- |'d stay with the Prussians.
You're crazy, Tjaden.
Have you ever dug peat?
Try it one day.
Can't be worse than digging trenches.
Takes longer than digging trenches.
And you can't slack off either.
In the army during peacetime,
you have no worries.
Food's there every morning,
or you raise a stink.
Then you've got your nice bed,
fresh sheets every week.
And then...
Then you make NCO.
Imagine that. I'll be a police ranger.
A cognac here, a pint there.
Everyone wants to be friends
with a ranger. Everyone.
There's just one catch, Tjaden.
What's that?
You'll never make NCO.
You always ask such nonsense questions.
It won't change anything.
- Kat! Kat!
- Here!
- Kat!
IIMy.
"You asked for a food parcel."
"Four helpings of wurst
and lard are on their way...
a few cakes,
sauerkraut and bockwurst,
and...
Hing...
Hingfong essence with sugar cubes,
some eggs and a jar of plum jam."
"Make it last because I don't want
to have to send more too soon."
"Better not share it with your comrades."
"My dear dumpling,
I have another question for you."
"How much money have you saved so far?"
"Can you maybe send some home?"
"They say that the war will be over soon,
so it would be good
to have some left over."
"Now you'll think,
listen to the old lady, how cheeky!"
"But no of fence."
"You know me, I can't get enough."
"Give me an inch and I'll take a mile."
"So don't keel over on the home stretch."
"Karl Lemmer is already
in a field hospital in the East."
"Something to do with his stomach.
He was hardly out there three weeks."
"Can't you get off too,
with your rheumatism?"
"You've done your bit."
If only she could see you now,
sitting here with your cigar!
"On Sunday, I'm visiting..."
"On Sunday,
I'm visiting our little boy's grave."
"|'m going to read to him.
He always liked that so much."
"Next year, we'll go together
and celebrate his tenth birthday."
"Well, that's all I had to say."
"Kisses from your wife."
"Goodbye."
I didn't know.
Oh, Paul.
What's going to happen?
Going home someday...
Going back to our old lives.
And all they'll want to know is
if we fought in close combat.
We'll walk around like travellers
in a landscape from the past.
I ask myself...
if I wouldn't just rather
sit around a campfire with you
and Tfladen and Krupp
and MUller...
and eat fried potatoes.
With the skin on.
Yeah...
I'm bored.
How long until we get going again?
Franz?
Yeah?
We have to leave at six tomorrow.
To look for some kids.
What happened?
They should have arrived today.
An entire company.
How was it?
- Nice.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
Here.
Smell.
What's her name?
Eloise.
Her skin was as white as milk.
And her breasts...
Hey.
I want a turn.
Albert.
- Kropp. Let me have it.
- Here.
- Oh, my!
- Tjaden.
A girl like that never has
dirty fingernails.
- No.
- At most, a bit of sand from the beach.
Tjaden.
- Come on, give it to me.
- |'m sure she has a bath twice a day.
Tjaden.
Please. It's mine.
- Tjaden!
- No, it's mine now.
That was one hell of a blast.
Trench mortar.
It blasted him right out of his uniform.
Is he one of those we're looking for?
No, they've only been missing
since yesterday.
He's been up there a while.
Not funny.
Don't start getting soft, men.
- How many are we looking for?
- Sixty young recruits.
Turnip bread for breakfast.
Turnip bread for lunch.
Turnip bread all the time.
I've had enough.
Tell me when you've found them.
I'm not taking another step.
Gas.
There was gas here.
Yes.
Hello, madam.
I'm KrOPP-
And you?
Do you want to...
Do you want to come with me?
Not a problem.
Kat.
Kat!
Shit.
- Bloody kids.
- Yeah.
They took their masks off too soon.
Soon, Germany will be empty.
COMPIEGNE, FRANCE
a NOVEMBER 191a
Sir.
Well, Brixdorf, what's the latest?
The French are putting the pressure on.
Early this morning,
our scouts intercepted orders
summoning entire divisions to Latierre.
A fleet of tanks
is still stuck in Fernancourt.
We need to prepare for an attack.
The Social Democrats will be
the end of mankind, Brixdorf.
Sir?
I just put the German delegation
on the train to Compiegne
to negotiate a ceasefire.
These people, Brixdorf,
are selling off our fatherland.
My order is war.
And as long as that's the case,
I'll fight tooth and nail.
We have to hold firm
and wait for fresh troops.
New recruits are due in a few months.
The French are trying
to force their shitty terms on us.
I will not surrender.
We have to strike now with all our might.
Sir.
For our part,
I have to insist...
we have to insist...
For God's sake!
Shit.
Sir!
Soldiers, pack your bags,
roll up your bedding
and wash your mess kits.
The entire regiment
is being sent to the front line.
We're taking anyone
who can stand on two legs.
Line up, damn it!
You think the French will wait
for you to comb your pubes?
Here we go again.
- Move it!
- Where to?
Where to?
Into battle.
Monsieur le Maréchal is expecting you.
I'll be back soon.
Jealous?
I stand before you
in the hope that you will take
our presence as an opportunity
to suspend all hostilities.
In the name of humanity,
I ask you to agree
to an immediate ceasefire
for the duration of our negotiations
in order to spare our nations
any unnecessary losses.
Matthias Erzberger,
head of the German delegation.
Marshal Foch asks
what brings us gentlemen to him.
We look forward to your suggestions
for bringing about a permanent ceasefire
at sea, on land and in the air.
I don't have any suggestions for you.
What does he mean?
I think he might not like
how you phrased it.
Yes.
Okay, then...
Monsieur le Maréchal,
if you please,
we would like to know the conditions...
He wants you to formally ask for it.
Monsieur le Maréchal,
I'm asking you for an armistice.
We're asking for an armistice.
You have 72 hours to accept
our conditions. They are non-negotiable.
- 72 hours?
- The war will continue until you sign.
Monsieur le Maréchal,
in the name of God,
don't let 72 hours go by.
People are dying out there.
Sign then.
Understood.
Soldiers, march.
March, soldiers.
Let's go. Out of here!
March.
Soldiers, march.
March, soldiers. Out of here!
Charge!
- Faster!
- Hooray!
Onwards, men!
Charge!
Hooray!
Keep ranks!
Keep going!
Go, go, go!
Let's go, Paul. Come on. Paul!
Get out!
Open fire!
Get down!
Take cover!
Get out of here! Get out!
Stay where you are and close ranks!
Hand grenades!
Aim for the tracks when they're above us.
Let's go, men! Go! Franz!
Franz!
Follow me!
Come on! Follow me!
Franz!
Go! Come on!
Paul!
Charge!
Paul.
Paul!
Open fire!
Retreat!
No, don't shoot! No!
No!
Don't! Don't shoot!
Albert.
- Albert.
- Come on!
Come on!
Keep going!
Where's Franz?
I've lost Franz!
Katczinsky!
Secure the machine gun and retreat!
We'll regroup in Eguisac,
two kilometres northeast of here.
I am missing my comrades, Sergeant!
And I miss my mother, damn it!
Grenades! Ammunition! Let's go!
Paul, come on!
This isn't a negotiation.
This is a diktat.
Maybe we should return to Spa
to consult with the general staff.
And what good will that do?
Even if we end up losing,
we won't be any worse off
than with this surrender.
Besides a few hundred thousand
more deaths.
Alsace-Lorraine, occupation of the Rhine,
artillery, locomotives, trains.
This is total capitulation!
250,000 Americans are landing
in Europe every month.
Marne, Cantigny, Cambrai, all lost.
The only thing separating us
from a ceasefire is false pride.
It's time to deal with the mess
you and your generals have left us.
But if you'd rather leave now, go ahead.
We're staying here.
It's winter.
Without trains and provisions,
the Bolsheviks will overrun us.
The men will starve on the way home,
instead of dying with honour
on the battlefield.
Honour?
My son was killed in this war.
Where's his honour?
Von Helldorf.
Get a few copies of the Allied demands
and telegraph them to headquarters.
Inform the government.
We have 72 hours, gentlemen,
and every minute we waste talking here,
another soldier dies.
Let's find mercy where we can,
but for God's sake,
let's end this war.
Retreat!
They're retreating! Barrage!
Barrage!
Be quiet!
Shut up.
Shut up!
No!
Comrade.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
House...
Your wife...
I promise.
I pro...
When were you born, Brixdorf?
1877, in June.
A summer child.
Yes.
What does your father do?
My family owns a manufactory in Holstein.
What kind?
Riding saddles, sir.
Riding saddles.
They'll always sell.
Your future is safe.
I'm very lucky.
Well?
Looking forward to going home?
- When we're not needed here any more?
- Yes.
There's a job waiting for me
after the war.
I'll take over the business.
Congratulations.
What about you?
I'm a soldier.
My father was an officer in this regiment.
He fought in three wars under Bismarck.
He won all three.
In 1871, he marched on Paris.
He came home a hero.
I was born too late, Brixdorf.
Half a century without war.
What is a soldier without war?
Were you close to your father?
As a child, perhaps.
A man is born alone,
he lives alone,
and he dies alone.
THE KAISER HAS ABDICATED
Come in.
Von Helldorf, what is it?
Hindenburg.
Open it then.
He urges us to sign.
It's over!
"the sin of the world,
have mercy on us."
"Lamb of God,
you take away the sin of the world..."
Knock on the monastery door,
and you'll find only
thieves and scoundrels.
It's over. The fat pigs have realised.
They're negotiating at last.
We're going home soon, soldier!
Where's the infirmary?
- No!
- Just chloroform the man!
Béumer.
- Tjaden.
- Béumer.
What happened? Where did you get hit?
Above the knee.
I think.
I can't feel anything.
How far above the knee was I shot?
I can't lift my head.
Ten centimetres at least.
- You're going home, Tjaden.
- You think so?
Yes, of course.
How can I be a ranger like this?
For Christ's sake!
You still can.
You'll see.
I won't let them amputate.
I won't live as a cripple.
You won't have to.
They've patched up much worse here.
Oh, Paul.
I'm supposed to give you something.
Is he dead?
You have to be brave now.
You're alive.
You have to be grateful for that.
For us.
For those who didn't make it.
Be quiet.
Listen, you can't say that. Not you.
That would really suit you.
Not until everyone's here...
They're in the infirmary or mass graves.
- Dish it up. We can smell it's done.
- I can't.
Why not, you vagrant?
I've cooked for 150.
I can't serve 80 men food for 150!
Are you thick as pig shit?
You've received provisions
for the second company.
- We're the second company!
- Yes!
So dish it out, full stop!
Kat!
- Kat!
- Paul!
Kat!
Paul!
- Paul!
- Kat, you're alive!
You're alive!
Paul!
Tjaden got hit.
He's in the church.
He'll get a double helping from us.
- Yes.
- Come on.
Careful.
And one here too.
Bloody hell, I thought you were dead.
We'll all die at some point.
But not on the home stretch.
If you die before me, I'll kill you.
Tjaden.
Kat?
Kat.
We brought you some soup.
Did you bring some cutlery?
Yes, we brought some cutlery too.
Enjoy it.
No! Tjaden, stop! Stop it, Tjaden!
Tjaden, no!
We need help here!
Why did you do that?
Why?
It's over, boys, it's over.
He's bleeding out!
Quiet.
Tjaden.
What is it?
I've lost something.
Kat, can you speak French?
My mother wanted me to learn French.
And piano.
She didn't want me to go to war.
"It's not for you," she always said.
"You'll be dead in no time."
I wanted to show them I could do it.
How does that help us now?
"|n a few weeks, we'll be in Paris."
I can't discard two years
of hand grenades like a pair of socks.
- Paul...
- We'll never get rid of the stench.
- Enough.
- Ludwig's dead, Franz, Albert...
What's it to us now?
At least they're at peace. We're alive.
All of this is like a fever.
No one actually wants it,
but suddenly it's here.
We didn't want it,
the others didn't want it.
And yet, here we are.
And yet, half the world is here.
And God watches on
as we slaughter each other.
Well...
But what do I know?
I know nothing.
I'm a pair of boots with a rifle.
Get some sleep. We got lucky.
Yes.
Kat?
What did your son die of?
Smallpox.
I'm afraid of what's to come.
Don't be.
Henfl.
Taste it.
Are they fresh?
I'm sorry, sir, but I don't think so.
Monsieur le Maréchal.
I'm listening.
The Kaiser has abdicated.
Soldiers are refusing to obey orders.
Deserters are roaming the countryside.
The new government will do its utmost
to fulfil the duties imposed on it,
but the population,
through no fault of its own,
risks descending into famine and anarchy.
This is a disease of the defeated,
not of the victorious.
I don't fear it. I reject any compromise.
Monsieur le Maréchal, please.
Be fair to your enemy,
otherwise he will hate this peace.
Fair?
You speak of fairness?
Sign it.
Let the minutes record
that the armistice
will take effect in six hours
at the 11th hour
on the 11th day of the 11th month.
Very good.
The war is over.
What will you do now?
What do you see here, Brixdorf?
The plains of Latierre, sir.
Eguisac.
I see them too.
And German soldiers
running away like rabbits.
The French are farting
into our posts in Latierre,
and out there is a train
full of horse fuckers,
selling off our homeland.
Withdraw the recruits from all posts.
Have them assemble in the courtyard.
We're going to sort out this shitty mess!
Any communication with the enemy
remains prohibited.
Firstly, hostilities
on the entire front will cease today,
11th November,
at 11 o'clock in the morning.
Secondly, troops will not cross the lines
held on this day, at this hour.
The lines will be accurately marked...
What time is it?
- Why aren't you sleeping?
- Listen.
It's so quiet here.
I think I've gone deaf.
They've signed, Paul.
The war's over.
It's over.
Are you hungfi'?
I'm huHQTY-
Where are you going?
Come on, before the bastard wakes up.
- What are you doing for Christmas, Paul?
- I don't know.
I'm roasting a goose.
With red cabbage, potatoes.
Then I'll light all the candles
and kiss my wife.
My God, Paul. My wife, she's beautiful.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- What does she look like?
- Well...
Long, dark, curly hair.
And she's round and strong.
Yeah?
Christmas.
It's all so far away.
But it isn't. It's very soon.
We want another child. Children, Paul.
Because what's Christmas without children?
It's nothing.
You know, once...
Once we're back home, then...
- Yeah?
- We'll do something big.
The two of us together, okay?
Well...
What?
I'm a cobbler, Paul. I repair shoes.
Yeah? You can read, write.
You have your school diplomas.
Didn't do me any good.
What are we going to do?
Nail soles on shoes together?
Are you trying to insult me?
I can't even read a letter from my wife.
Go to college, Paul.
Or I'll shoot you right here.
My trousers are falling down.
My trousers are loose.
You'll just have to eat a little.
Soon we'll be home,
then we can eat what we want.
Whatever we want.
It's your turn.
If the farmer catches me again,
he'll shoot me.
Watch out for the damn dog.
Yeah.
Look.
It's really good.
Want some?
Shit.
Hey!
Stop!
Kat! Run!
Bastard!
Damn.
Oh, crap.
Look at this.
What is it?
- I got lucky.
- He hit the eggs?
- Press on it.
- Okay.
Come on, get it all in there.
All of it.
We can fry them.
Nonsense. We'll eat them right now.
Like this is fine too.
Doesn't get better than that.
I'll be right back.
Kat?
Kat!
What happened?
Let's go.
- Who fired the shot?
- The little shit from the farm.
The farmer's boy.
Kat!
What a mess.
HOW big?
Little finger. I'll get the bullet out.
No, just give me a cigarette.
Leave that to the medic.
They stuck me
in a class of seven-year-olds.
I had already started shaving.
Find a word...
that rhymes with trifle.
Nothing rhymes with trifle. Nothing.
For Christ's sake!
Did it have to happen now, of all times?
- We have to keep going.
- Yeah.
Keep going.
Okay? Kat?
Rifle.
Rifle rhymes with trifle.
When we get home, you're going
to make me a new pair of boots.
I'm walking my feet bloody.
Stop!
Medic!
You could've saved yourself the trouble.
He's dead.
It's... It's just a small bullet wound.
Yes, black blood. Straight into the liver.
His organs are poisoned.
Unconscious.
He's dead.
I know more about these things.
That... That's impossible. I was...
I was just talking to him.
He's unconscious.
You see?
He was just unlucky.
So close to the end.
Drink a cup of tea, sugar and coffee
And a glass of wine
Girl, I do love you...
Come along, soldier!
The General's sending us home!
We're going home!
Go on, keep going!
Step it up a notch!
Attention!
Soldiers,
we stand here as brothers
in a world of enemies, forced to watch
as German social democrats render
our beloved people defenceless
by accepting a perfidious armistice.
Comrades,
you will be going home soon
to parents, wives and children.
The war is over.
After years of sacrifice and suffering,
you can now look forward to your reward.
The reward of admiration
for everything you've achieved here.
But, comrades,
do you want to be welcomed
as soldiers and heroes,
or as cowards
who chickened out
when it really came down to it?
Soldiers,
we're going to strike now
with all our rig our and might.
Latierre belongs in German hands.
We will seize the plains before 11 a.m.
and end this war with a victory!
Onwards with God who will be with us,
as He was with our fathers.
I'm not going back into battle. Not me!
Shut up!
Take aim!
- No!
- Fire!
Company, halt!
Order arms!
Fix bayonets!
What time?
Fifteen minutes to go.
Belonged to Lefévre.
Poor bastard. He saved it for the end.
- He won't need it any more.
- Thank you, sir.
Here's to you and to Lefévre.
Well, it's good.
The nightmare is over.
Enemy attack!
- In position!
Fire!
Grenades!
Charge!
No, no! Please!
No! Don't! No!
Cease fire!
It's eleven o'clock!
Are you all right, soldier?
Yes.
Well, then...
Start collecting, please.
SHORTLY AFTER THE BEGINNING OF THE WAR
IN OCTOBER 1914,
THE WESTERN FRONT BECAME BOGGED DOWN
IN TRENCH WARFARE.
AT THE END OF THE WAR IN NOVEMBER 1918,
THE FRONT LINE HAD BARELY MOVED.
MORE THAN THREE MILLION SOLDIERS
DIED HERE,
OFTEN WHILE FIGHTING TO GAIN
ONLY A FEW HUNDRED METRES OF GROUND.
DURING THE FIRST WORLD WAR,
ALMOST 17 MILLION PEOPLE LOST THEIR LIVES.
ALL QUIET ON THE WESTERN FRONT
Subtitle translation by:
Diana Renker, Calum Short