How does one come
to know the unknowable?
What faculties must a man possess?
Since it was discovered that whale oil
could light our cities
in ways never achieved before,
it created global demand.
It has pushed man to venture
further and further
into the deep blue unknown.
We know not its depths,
nor the host of creatures that live there.
Monsters.
Are they real?
Or do the stories exist only to make us
respect the sea's dark secrets?
The question both vexes and excites me
and is the reason I have written you
a second time, to request a meeting.
A conversation with you, sir,
I believe will serve me well
for the novel I intend to write,
currently entitled...
Moby Dick.
I hope you will reconsider my offer.
The unknown.
That is where my imagination
yearns to venture.
And so the question plagues me still.
How does a man come to know
the unknowable?
Sincerely,
Herman Melville.
We are closed.
No boarders after 8 o'clock.
You came.
Someone here for you, my love.
Tom Nickerson?
Herman Melville.
We received your letter.
You are either a desperate man,
or a fool to come
all the way to Nantucket.
Well,
my offer still stands.
Three months' lodgings
for a single night's talk.
All I have in the world.
But I prefer to think of it as an investment.
I want you to tell me what happened...
to the Essex.
What do you think happened?
There are rumblings.
Rumors that the Essex was...
What do you want?
What story do you expect to hear?
That of the whale.
The Essex ran aground.
There was a full inquiry.
I believe the inquiry was less than truthful.
Get out.
You are the last survivor of the Essex sir.
If you won't talk, who will?
Did you not hear me?
Leave.
Now.
No. You must not go. Please.
He is in no mind to talk.
And I have not come all this way
to be humiliated and waste my time.
Please, Mr. Melville.
He won't talk about the Essex to me.
To anyone. Never has. Never.
There is an agony about him.
His soul is...
in torment,
and in need of confession.
Please, just let me talk to him.
Please.
Love.
I believe it would do you good
to talk to the man.
No.
You listen well.
Who holds this place together
while you drink yourself to death?
You will talk with this man
as much as is necessary,
to keep the money.
You know our circumstances Thomas.
Only as much as is necessary.
I will get whiskey.
I neglected to mention it in my letter but...
I was a whaler once.
One trip, I mean.
Green hand.
So, you have seen it all.
My wife read your books.
She...
enjoyed them.
I am happy to hear it.
I have had good sales.
And I think this story...
could surpass the success
of even my first novel,
which did quite well.
Another of your...
seafaring yarns?
Have you read Hawthorne, Mr. Melville?
Now there is a writer.
Great writer.
He is.
But he is not here.
And I am.
For my own particular reasons.
I will tell you of the Essex.
I believe you will be disappointed.
But every word I say will be true.
Story of the Essex,
is the story of two men.
Captain George Pollard,
and his first mate,
Owen Chase.
Owen.
You don't wanna be late.
I will be there.
Besides, can't have our daughter
sleeping under a leaky roof, can we?
What makes you so sure it's a girl?
Well, it has to be.
So she can remind me
why I still love you
when you are being stubborn.
Well, if it's to be a daughter,
she will be a version of you, not me.
Blond locks and determined
to conquer the world.
I suppose after today, you will be
trading in that tunic for a uniform.
That's right.
Finally out of this patch of dirt,
into a captain's house like you deserve.
I don't need one of those houses
in town with stuffy neighbors.
There is plenty of room here
for the three of us.
You know, sometimes your kind heart
and good nature
is just unbearable.
Go get your captaincy.
What's your bid?
I will have 1.90.
I have got 1,000 gallons at 2 dollars!
I will take 40 shares!
Seller! Seller! Over here!
Criterion's back with a fine haul.
1,600 barrels.
A new record.
50 Pound sterling for head matter
on the London market.
Congratulations.
Good morning Mr. Chase.
Mr. Mason.
Come in please.
My partner Benjamin Fuller.
Good morning sir.
Do sit down.
Mr. Chase.
I do hope you realize how satisfied we are
with the work you have done for us
over the years.
Thank you sir.
Now one of our ships,
the Essex
has just been refitted at great expense,
and is to go to sea.
Now having made
such an investment in her,
we want to be sure
she is in the best possible hands.
So,
it gives us great pleasure
to offer you a position aboard her.
As first mate.
As first mate?
Mr. Mason, you-you promised me
command of a ship after my last voyage
when I brought you back 1500 barrels.
Do you remember?
You gave me your word.
That promise must now be deferred.
Like everyone else,
we have had a lean time recently.
No never on my watch.
Nantucket now dominates
the world market.
That must not change.
This is no time for experimentation.
The Essex will be captained
by George Pollard,
scion of a great whaling family.
His father also happens to be our patron.
Blood Mr. Chase.
You can have all the voyages
under your belt you want
but blood will always win out.
Yes well blood is not gonna fill
a ship with oil Mr. Mason.
To successfully command
a captain needs respect.
Now what if the men don't respect him?
You will make sure that they do.
Good day gentlemen.
I understand your disappointment
So...
a one fifteenth lay.
That's more than
I have ever paid any first officer.
And if you bring back
2000 barrels of oil
I give you my word...
next time you will have your captaincy.
You have given me
your word before Mr. Mason.
No this time I will take it in writing.
Captain Pollard.
We have just had a most
agreeable conversation with Mr. Chase.
He will be honored to serve under you.
I am glad to hear it.
Now I am to babysit a greenhorn.
Some chinless Nantucketer born
with a damn silver spoon in his mouth.
You know I should have thrown
the offer back in their faces.
Why?
You now have
the offer of command in writing.
Yes well a liar's word is worthless
even on paper.
You know I would love you just as much
if you were a merchant captain.
And you would not be gone for 2 years.
I won't be gone 2 years.
A Bedford whaler came back
last week who was gone 3.
She lost two men,
and still with her hull half empty.
Yeah well they were from Bedford
and they didn't have me on board.
Son of a bitch!
I will captain my own ship!
A whaling ship.
Up to them all we would ever have
is this patch of dirt
and that's not gonna happen Peggy.
Those are your father's words not yours.
What's wrong with his words?
He wanted things
for his family for himself.
He was a dreamer Owen.
Yes he was.
Dreamed of the sea and never got
to sail it because of men like them.
At least he got to see his children born.
It's all I know.
I am sorry.
I married a whaleman.
Hey.
I will come back as quick
as a summer's night I swear.
Just come back.
Promise me.
I already swore to you.
Now you want me to promise too?
I promise.
Son, a word with you.
To be a captain, you cannot be a friend.
You are their superior.
Never forget that.
Never let them forget that.
Thank you sir.
Your great grandfather
and a few others,
created this industry.
Without us, without you,
the world plunges into darkness.
I hope to bring honor
to the Pollard family name sir.
Thou didst, O Lord,
create the mighty whale.
That wondrous monster of a mighty length,
beyond conception,
his unmeasured strength.
But everlasting God, thou dost ordain
That we,
poor feeble mortals,
should engage.
Ourselves our wives
and children to maintain
This dreadful monster,
with a martial rage.
O Father,
grant that your glorious light,
shine on these men.
Ensure them a prosperous voyage
that they may return safely
and with a full ship
so that the white flames
of Nantucket whale oil
may continue to keep light in our homes
city streets safe from sin in the night
and to fuel the machines of industry
that drive our great nation forward
as our noble species evolves.
In your name we pray.
So,
what month was this?
Late in the year.
We were one of the last ships to go out
which is why my friend
Barzillai and I got a berth.
You know...
I was 14.
14.
Nickerson, you are standing
around boy. Move!
First time to sea.
Scared but more scared to show it.
Barzillai was 17.
Orphans. Grew up on the wharf.
Both in a hurry to be called men.
Grubs.
What are those pins they are wearing?
They are whale pins Thomas.
How do I get one of them?
Well you got to thrust the killing lance
into the largest beast that
ever breathed on this Earth.
Nickerson get the green stuff
to Mr. Bond there.
Make it quick damn it.
I shall have 12 of those one day.
Windlass is ready
and sails are loose sir.
Mr. Joy this is only half my order!
Put them over the ground tier casks.
Well, well, you being on board
means only one thing.
Yeah. at least there is one person on this
ship who knows the truth about Owen Chase.
No that all the other ships
have already crewed up.
Now, now.
I am a reformed man Owen.
Question is are you?
Don't tell me Matthew Joy's
put down the bottle.
Dry as sand.
Has Owen Chase put down his temper?
Serene as the church.
I will believe that when I see it.
And given our captain
I will give your serenity about...
48 hours?
Good luck.
Pollard. George Pollard.
Owen Chase.
Chase.
That's an off island name isn't it?
Yes it is.
And very shortly we will be
off island for some time
and I will be very much at home.
Must say I was surprised.
Normally a captain gets
to choose his first mate.
An experienced captain, yes.
Of course you can understand
from the owners' point of view
they want to feel their investment's
in the hands of men.
Indeed.
They probably want a little
extra reassurance that's all.
Well do keep an eye on me and let me
know if I am doing anything wrong.
Oh, I know no other way Captain.
Mr. Chase haul short the anchor.
Yank to the wind! There is top men aloft.
Aye!
Mr. Lawrence take the helm.
Aye sir.
Mr. Joy make sail.
Mr. Cole! Mr. Chappel!
Stand by the spanker.
Set your fore stay sail
and your fore and main topsails.
Come on look lively you lads.
Come on Nickerson! While we are young!
Let fall clews and bunts and sheet ho!
Set topsails and topgallants.
Heave away on the windlass.
Set topgallants.
Let go clew lines and sheet ho!
There is a snarl in the gasket sir.
Mr. Chappel take the helm.
It won't clear Mr. Chase!
Come on!
Why are not those braces laid out?
Mr. Ray where are my headsails?
Aye sir!
Crank away on the windlass!
Crank away on the windlass sir!
Nickerson pull!
Make sail God damn it!
God and all of Nantucket is watching men.
Anchor's trim!
Captain! Head down!
Mind your head Captain.
What's the matter Mr. Sheppard?
Gasket has fouled the sheet sir.
It won't clear Mr. Chase!
Topgallant sheet is jammed!
The gasket still won't clear!
We don't have enough sail on yet.
Still won't clear!
Watch your step!
It's the gasket Owen!
Stand clear.
Bloody hell!
Let fall your course!
Heave!
Make fast!
Nice piece of work Mr. Chase.
If we make Cape Verdes
in the next 2 weeks
we will have a decent chance
of reaching the Pacific on schedule.
Corn Mr. Chase?
Oh no thank you sir.
Never did have much of a taste for it.
That's odd.
Told your father grew corn on Cape Cod.
That's right. He did.
As you can imagine I certainly
grew tired of eating it every day.
Corn.
Okra. Beans I believe?
Before he went to jail.
Are you familiar with this story Mr. Joy?
Sir?
Were you aware that...
Mr. Chase was effectively orphaned,
due to his father's incarceration?
Well we all have...
we all have our own paths to sea.
As a rule we tend
not to ask too many questions.
Can't have been easy though.
Yet
you had Nantucket's great seafaring family
to adopt you.
This is far from the first time I have been
called a landsman...
or an offislander by some
Nantucketer reminding me how I am not,
a part of that family.
Now if the Captain will excuse me there
are whaleboats and watches to assign.
No sir. Not for me.
Not a drop?
No sir.
Like I said...
sometimes the fewer questions,
one asks the better.
Serve that food up.
Getting this slop on the first day?
Cheap bastards. Where is the meat?
That's a gorgeous girl Mr. Chappel.
A vision of beauty that.
Carved on a varnished whale bone.
Let me have a touch.
Don't touch.
I thought you were married anyway.
I am and there she is.
Well...
that's her nose anyway.
Congratulations ladies.
That was a fine job trimming sails today.
A sorrier pack of deck wallopers
I don't think I have ever seen.
Mr. Chappel.
Sir!
You are Captain's harpooner.
Mr. Lawrence,
you will be mine.
Aye sir.
And Mr. Peterson.
Second mate's harpooner.
Aye sir.
There will be 6 men to a boat.
First drills are tomorrow.
6 bells sharp.
We are not even east of Halifax, sir.
What's your name?
Coffin.
Henry Coffin.
He is the Captain's cousin sir.
Well, well, Mr. Coffin.
You think a whale knows
if it's east of Halifax?
I don't know who all of you are,
or how you got here.
Some of you probably have felonies
to hide and you are on the run.
That's fine.
I don't give a damn.
But in return you exist for one thing,
and one thing only.
And that is whale oil.
I intend to fill our 2000 barrels,
and be home as quickly as possible.
And even when the weather is fine
and there are no whales Mr. Coffin
we will lower the boats
and practice all maneuvers
necessary in the capture of a whale.
And any man who is idle
will find himself swimming home.
Is that understood?
Aye sir.
Sir.
Greenhorn.
On deck.
On you go.
Aye, aye, landsman.
Thomas Nickerson right?
Aye sir.
You know some feel sick at first.
Please, pull me back up!
Best way to square it
with King Neptune boy!
Please bring me up!
Better now?
Shit.
Sir I am so sorry.
Well,
now you got something
to write home to your mother about.
My mother is buried up in Smith's Hill.
There is a stone for my father too, he was...
He was lost at sea before I was born.
Here give me that.
Well this is your family now boy.
For better or for worse.
Worse mostly.
Swab the deck kid.
Dogwatch!
You are gonna learn
what it takes to be whalers today mates.
Aye sir!
You led that line wrong Nickerson.
Aye sir.
We will stay at this
till sundown if we have to.
Aye Mr. Joy sir!
Main topsail leech lines!
Harpooner make ready to boat!
Aye sir!
Aye Mr. Joy!
Go main topsail leech lines.
Too slow you damn coofs!
The bailing piggins.
You will learn every inch of this ship
before you return to your bunks.
Aye sir!
Sweat that line Barz.
You need to move quicker Mr. Ray.
Aye Mr. Chase.
Ain't no greenhorns no more Mr. Chase.
You are a sailor now!
Not bad Mr. Ray. Well done.
Forecourse bunts!
Aye sir.
Get used to it lads.
You are gonna work like horses.
Mr. Chase?
Sir.
Set stunsails.
Is that wise sir?
We are nearing the Gulf Stream.
Best keep it 5 knots
till we can see the weather.
We are 2 days behind.
We need to make up the time
if we are to catch the easterlies.
Set stunsails.
Aye Mr. Chase!
Come on, move.
Belay that! Set stunsails!
Get aloft Mr. Coffin.
The captain wants speed.
Aye sir.
Look for braces lads.
Trim for speed.
Aye sir.
Set fore the main topsail
and topgallant stunsails men.
Move it.
Make fast your stunsail halyard.
Make fast stunsail halyard sir.
Stunsail boom ready sir!
Bracing fore topsail sir.
Hey!
The captain's got us moving now!
We are finally getting somewhere!
She may be old
but she can still roll boys!
Sir a squall on the starboard bow.
We must shorten sail immediately.
Not just yet Mr. Chase.
Sir we are headed into a squall
at more than 8 knots
and it's moving faster than that.
Let it come.
The men are soft from months on land.
They need a good baptism.
Let them know our work has begun.
If we don't shorten sail and bear off
it will catch us on the beam.
Mr. Chase...
we will stand on.
Mr. Lawrence?
Hold our course.
Holding course sir.
We will lose half a day running
like that.
We will skirt the edge of it.
If the men can't handle a gust like this
then God help us all.
Best secure for heavy weather.
Rough weather coming up boys.
Get this deck secure.
Double gripes on the boats!
Best prepare for weather Mr. Bond.
We are headed into a squall.
Secure the main hatch!
She is moving fast!
We must fall off and run with it.
We will stand on Mr. Chase.
Mr. Lawrence!
Hold your course!
Holding course, sir.
Sea is coming aboard!
Hold on!
Shorten sail Mr. Chase!
Climb to weather and grab the shrouds!
Climb to weather!
Get to windward and hold on!
We need to get those sails down!
Go now!
Nickerson hold fast!
Hold steady lines!
Hold fast!
Turn the ship!
Turn to leeward!
No! The damage is done!
Strike topgallants. Let fly sheets!
No turn the ship!
Veer off Mr. Lawrence.
It's too late! It's too goddamn late!
We will be broadsided!
Turn this ship!
Hold on!
Turn!
Strike those damn topgallants!
Hold on!
Look out!
Mr. Joy!
We have to cut away the topgallants!
Topgallants away!
We have to get her upright!
You wish to see me sir?
At 6 bells tomorrow
you will assemble the crew.
Inform them that we will be returning
to Nantucket for repairs.
You will then apologize to them
for interfering with a captain's order
which nearly cost the lives
of every man on this ship today.
What?
I will accept your resignation
upon our return to port.
That will be all.
It was your order to set stunsails sir.
That decision was sound.
The men needed testing.
So you send them into a storm?
That...
was unlucky.
No it was bad seamanship.
And blaming misfortune
is just plain weakness.
Damn your impertinence!
Do you know who you are speaking to?
My name is Captain George Pollard.
Pollard!
And you Mr. Chase
no matter how many whale pins
you may have on your lapel,
are nothing more than
the son of a farmer,
who is managed to bully his way
into an officer's tunic.
Now get out.
To return to port without a single
barrel of oil would be a mistake sir.
And not behoove a man
whose name is Pollard.
Or Chase for that matter.
And the best thing for both of us
would be to work all hours God sends us
fill this ship with oil
and be home inside a year
and rid of one another
as quickly as possible.
Trust me I am every bit
as desirous of that as you.
Of course that is a captain's decision.
They were like an ill married couple.
An ill married couple
will tolerate each other Mr. Melville.
But an ill married couple
can also bring down a ship.
Are you married Mr. Melville?
I am.
God have mercy on you.
First child on the way too.
So does your good wife
know that you have brought
all you have in the world here tonight
and given it to a stranger?
No sir.
You are full of surprises are not you?
So...
The Essex did not return to...
to port.
She did not.
She continued out to sea.
Yes she did.
And before long,
we heard that...
call that all whalemen pray for.
Blows.
Blows!
To windward!
There she blows!
Right or sperm Mr. Ramsdell?
Sperm whales they are!
There go the flukes!
Mr. Chase!
Hoist and swing boats.
All hands! All hands on deck!
All hands on deck!
Away the boats.
Lower away!
Straight!
Crack them backbones.
Aye sir!
Give way all.
Spring those oars till your arms fall off.
There they breach!
Thataway boys!
Full pressure!
Aye sir!
Come on!
Put your back into it.
Pull!
Pull like a vengeance!
There she blows!
That's a calf.
That's the calf?
That's the cow.
And that's our boy!
That's the money.
Nickerson push!
Sorry sir.
40barreler?
50.
Oh he is a buster!
Bite the oars lads.
Blister your goddamn lungs!
Full pressure!
Smartly lads! Smartly!
Mind your oars!
Mr. Ramsdell prepare the line.
Aye sir.
Mr. Lawrence the first one is mine.
Take me to the pretty spot.
Pull!
Come on. Stay on him.
You are on your first
Nantucket sleigh ride boy.
Oh my God!
Look at him!
The most fearsome creature
ever to live on this Earth.
He sounds.
My hands!
We need to wet the line Nickerson.
Give way lads. Give way.
Got 140 fathoms of line left Mr. Chase.
80 fathoms of line left sir!
He is gonna pull us under!
Matthew I need your line!
Keep going!
Peterson give me the line.
Aye sir.
Give me that line Mr. Peterson.
We are down to 60 fathoms of line left sir!
20 fathoms Mr. Chase.
Tie it off!
Safe!
Go!
Peterson lay out.
Aye sir.
How many fathoms can he go?
70 fathoms left sir.
No, no, no, wait.
Owen!
No, no! Not yet!
Don't touch that line!
Down to 50 fathoms sir.
Owen God damn it!
I said don't touch it!
30 fathoms left Mr. Joy.
10 fathoms left sir!
Backwater!
Push!
Chimney was afire!
Afire!
Hurry it along lads.
God! Get out you bastards.
Blubber in the oil.
Smell that boys!
That's us making money!
Get out of there you sons of bitches.
There you got it?
There is not a chance.
How is it looking?
It's not good.
That's it.
Mr. Chase sir.
Yeah?
That's all of it sir.
We can't get any more out.
That's the gold in there boys.
Come on keep digging.
We are too big to wriggle down there.
Then find someone who can.
Nickerson! Come here boy.
Hey!
I said come here.
Climb on into him.
Come on Thomas.
What's in there is worth a hell of a lot
more than what they are boiling down.
Sir!
I can't I am...
I am sorry. I can't.
You get down there
or I will have you sleep down there.
You best put that between your teeth boy.
Stinks worse than
the devil's asshole down there.
Thanks.
Sorry.
Here Nickerson, take my pillow with you.
Down you go.
A man gets to know himself down there.
They ever send you into a whale's head?
No.
I was spared.
Well,
that's where the treasure is.
I will never forget that first bull.
47 barrels.
Of course, the happiness was short lived.
The waters there had all been fished out?
That they had.
So,
we headed further out.
Yeah.
Took us a month to round the Horn.
Left the South Atlantic behind
with a sliver of hope
that things could change for the better.
But making the Pacific
didn't improve our lot.
Whale sightings were too damn scarce.
After nearly a year at sea...
the temperaments of our captain
and first mate grew more strained.
Captain Pollard spent most
days and nights in his cabin
afraid to look his crew in the eye.
Our hold was almost empty.
And to gaze upon our paltry efforts
only served as a reminder,
that we were a long way from going home.
I don't talk that talk.
Speak English.
Offer me more.
Here sir.
This Nantucket whale oil.
Ain't no skinny hog worth more than that.
More!
Capitan.
Excuse me.
The locals told me your voyage
was waylaid sir.
Captain George Pollard. The Essex.
Capitan Clemente Pelaez,
the Santa Maria.
Would you buy a colleague a drink?
No, no.
Bad luck?
How far out?
Far enough for only a fool to go.
How far would that be?
A thousand leagues along the equator.
The Offshore Grounds.
Were there whales there?
More than you have ever dreamed.
Hundreds.
Fields of flukes far as the eye can see.
Could have filled up 3000 barrels
in the space of a day.
What do you mean could have?
If it were not for that...
demon.
A whale.
White as alabaster.
Hundred feet long.
Sent 6 of my crew to their graves.
And the rest of us
something...
to remember him by.
Now this white whale did he dance
a jig and pick your pocket as well?
Gracias.
You believe that?
If we set sail now,
catch the south easterlies
at their best time
and fill our belly
we could be home in six months.
What say you Mr. Chase?
No need to endure our predicament
for a moment longer than necessary.
Amen to that.
Amen.
Greed took hold
of our captain and first mate.
So we headed out.
A thousand leagues along the equator.
Where knowledge ended,
speculation began.
That's where the whales had gone to hide.
As far from man as they could possibly go.
But we hunted them down.
Centuries before,
sailors feared sailing
off the edge of the Earth.
But we were headed for the edge of sanity.
Trust gave way to doubt.
Hope to blind superstition.
Captain,
the men are talking.
That's what men do.
They are not happy with your decision
to sail out this far.
Well did you correct them?
Did you remind them of our purpose
to fill this ship with whale oil
and if the whales are 1000 leagues out
that that is where we will go?
Cousin...
please.
This is madness.
You have let yourself
be influenced by that man.
You must turn this ship back.
I suggest...
you go back down
reassure the men...
be...
a leader
and don't ever...
ever abuse the privilege
of family with me again.
Mr. Coffin.
What is it?
Listen.
Mr. Chase?
I see some white water.
Where?
Portside!
We are away!
Portside Captain!
Where are they?
You see anything?
Lower away!
The devil take the Mexican grounds!
Peak oars!
Give it to him, Mr. Chappel!
Stick him man! Stick him!
Dead ahead Peterson!
Don't let him chew your oars boys.
Back to it.
The whale?
Yes.
So it's true?
Too much is true.
Get it up!
Full pressure!
Mr. Bond!
Back the foreyard lower the tackle!
Aye sir!
Here she comes Peterson. Now! Now!
Mr. Lawrence,
take us leeward
head us straight for the school.
Aye sir.
Hot tar sir.
We will find him.
We are boat to black skin.
Beach us on her!
She is ours men!
What was that Mr. Lawrence?
Mr. Chase!
God damn it.
Find Mr...
Mr. Easton!
Get Mr. Lawrence to man the pumps!
Where is he?
Port bow!
Get me the biggest irons we have.
He wants a fight?
Never seen a whale do that.
Mr. Lawrence take the wheel.
Mr. Ramsdell,
secure the other end of the line
to the foremast.
Aye sir.
As I live and breathe,
he is mine.
Cut the line!
Look out!
Captain!
What?
The Essex!
She is listing.
Turn this boat around!
Help me!
Nickerson!
Mr. Joy!
Here!
Give me your hand!
Help!
Nickerson!
Mr. Chase!
A whale sir.
It stove the ship.
What?
We lost Easton and Sanborn.
The pumps are useless sir.
Prepare to abandon ship.
We can't row our way home.
We will have to strip her of her sails
and jimmyrig something.
Aye sir.
Gather as much food
and water as you can carry.
We are gonna need
all the fresh water you can find.
Nickerson you grab as much as you can.
Barz come with me.
Sweet Lord!
First the sails, then the provisions.
Get as much food as you can carry lad.
Make haste boys!
Nickerson there are
more casks in steerage.
Got it?
Hardtack is dry.
Move sprightly gentlemen.
Lower away!
Take those tack lines.
Up aloft!
Lower away! Bring it down!
Mr. Cole get that yard down.
Bring it down. Keep it coming!
Hold off!
Come on Nickerson!
Get those sails!
There you go.
Get that yard down!
We need the sails.
Not enough water.
Get the barrels now!
Strip that rigging!
More fresh water!
More hardtack! Come on!
I can see more casks in the steerage!
Benjamin! Quick! Come on!
Give me your hand!
Get him up.
I got you.
Hardtack!
Come on! Move it!
Step lively Mr. Nickerson!
Gotta get away from the oil!
She is going down! She is listing!
Where is Owen?
Nickerson where is Mr. Chase?
He was just here sir.
Come on hurry up!
Owen!
Mr. Chase!
We got to shove off!
Come on now boys!
Oil on deck!
Captain!
Mr. Chase!
Mr. Chase sir!
Owen!
Where is the first mate?
Mr. Chase sir!
Owen!
She is gonna blow!
We got to move!
No wait! Wait!
Mr. Chase sir!
Mr. Chase!
There he is!
There he is! There he is!
Over here!
Mr. Chase!
Move that!
Mr. Chase, sir.
Here!
Get a hold now.
We got you.
Sir.
You are alright now Mr. Chase.
Going fishing are we?
Clean and load it Mr. Joy.
Back away,
or she will take us down with her.
Captain.
What about our provisions?
2 ounces of hardtack a day per man.
And half a cup of water.
Hey man we can't live on that.
Not for more than a few days.
It's he.
Yeah it's him alright.
You don't fool me Mr. Chase.
Mr. Coffin?
That right?
You put us here.
You know you put us here.
Hey! Put it down!
Mr. Coffin put the pistol down.
Say you are scared!
Mr. Coffin!
Put the pistol down.
You know what happens
when the food and water runs out?
Do as the captain says Coffin!
I just wanna see the landsman scared.
Mr. Coffin put the pistol down.
That's an order!
Do as the captain says! Now!
Say it!
Henry.
Henry!
Put the pistol down.
Put it down.
So east it was.
Back in the direction we had come.
Though only the sun
and compass told us so.
All directions looked the same.
Our hope was to catch
the Westerlies to Easter Island.
A journey of 3000 miles.
In 12 days we have drifted south.
6 degrees latitude.
We are not one mile closer
to Easter Island.
We stayed in the same place.
We are cursed.
We will make up for it
when we catch the variables.
We will catch them.
Chappel!
You have got him Captain!
Mr. Joy the halyard's jammed!
Mr. Joy!
You alright Mr. Joy?
Grab the tiller!
Grab it!
Matthew!
Get that sail down!
Matthew.
Hey what happened?
What happened?
Owen.
What are you doing here?
Let me take a look.
No, no, no.
Lay still. Let me take a look.
No!
Owen I am fine.
Alright. Just relax.
Relax.
Let me take a look.
I am fine!
I know. I know.
I just wanna take a look.
I banged my head.
Just a scratch alright?
Just a scratch.
Give him some water.
I don't need any water!
Give him some goddamn water!
No, no, no. I don't need water.
I am fine.
Yeah.
Take that. Take it.
Hey. I got you. I got you.
You are alright.
Hey! What are you all looking at?
I am fine.
Captain Pollard.
Fit as a fiddle.
Fit as a goddamned fiddle.
You hear me?
Owen.
Yeah.
I am fine.
Alright? I am fine!
You are a tough son of a bitch.
Thank you. I am fine.
Get out of here.
He is good.
Let's go.
Why waste water on a dead man?
Them two men have known each other,
sailed together since childhood.
Now tell me,
could you sit there
and watch your own brother die?
Simply a matter of numbers Mr. Chappel.
There is not enough for all of us.
Why waste water on a dead man?
Why waste water on...
Why waste water?
Why waste?
Why waste water on a dead man?
Mr. Nickerson?
Why waste water...
You alright sir?
I cannot.
Cannot what?
No you-you...
You have enough. You hav...
More than enough.
But sir we have come so far.
We have come to an end.
We have an agreement sir.
Take the money and leave!
The devil's bargain.
No sir.
The devil loves unspoken secrets.
Especially those that
fester in a man's soul.
What's yours?
I am not a great writer.
I am not Hawthorne.
But from my first hearing of it this...
this tale has haunted me.
It consumes me.
I fear if I do not write it
then I should never write again.
What else?
I fear if I do write it...
that it will not be
as good as it should be.
Continue the story sir.
For the both of us.
Pass that down.
Thank you sir.
We thank you Lord for this is our food.
I am sorry.
For life and health
and every good.
Let all manner to...
Land.
Land!
Land! Land!
Oars!
Give way! Give way!
Oars now! Give way!
Row!
I saw it Mr. Chase.
That you did boy.
Hold fast. Hold fast! Hold fast!
Mr. Chase sir. What is it?
Mr. Chase!
What the devil is it?
Why have you stopped?
He is been following us!
What?
What is he talking about?
There is nothing out there Mr. Chase!
There ain't nothing out there sir!
Sir what are you doing?
Brace! Brace! Brace!
No!
Where is he?
This could be Ducie Island.
Without a map compass or quadrant
there is no way to be certain.
We will keep fires going night and day.
Hope a passing ship,
catches sight of our smoke.
This is what I wanted you to see.
They ave been here a long time no doubt.
Waiting for a ship.
But no ship came.
No ship is going to come.
If we stay we die.
How long do you think
it will take the tropic birds
to stop coming here once
they see their eggs eaten?
It's a privilege to know
the moment of one is death in advance
be able to prepare for it.
Curse to be so far from home,
without a chance to say goodbyes
without a chance to make peace,
without a chance to settle the scores.
Then let us at least settle
those between us...
Captain.
Captain of what?
The Essex was lost
through no fault of yours.
I was as much to blame for...
You are not the captain.
But you were born to do this job.
I was just born into it.
What do we do do you think George?
And what offense...
did we give God
to upset him so?
The only creature to have
offended God here is the whale.
Not us?
In our arrogance, our greed,
look where we find ourselves.
We are supreme creatures
made in God's own likeness.
Earthly kings...
whose business it is to circumnavigate,
the planet bestowed to us.
To bend nature to our will.
You really feel like an earthly king
after everything that
we have been through?
We are nothing. We are...
We are specks.
And dust.
We sail into the sun at dawn.
If we are to die...
then with God's grace...
let us die as men.
Are we ready Mr. Weeks?
Aye sir.
Mr. Chappel?
Mr. Wright?
I can't do it sir.
Me Wrights and Weeks,
we are staying.
You ready to go Matthew?
I will give you a hand.
Here you got to get up.
No, there is no point.
You hear me?
No we are going home.
We are going home.
There is no point.
Just go.
God damn it Matthew.
It's alright.
Well I will send a boat for you
the minute we get back.
Then we will play cards
back in Nantucket alright?
Yeah.
It's a deal.
Good.
You want me to open that for you?
I think I will manage.
If it comes to that.
God be with you brother.
Yeah and you.
Brother Peterson?
You all coming with us?
Mr. Peterson.
Why don't you come in our boat
with Mr. Bond here?
Where... Where is he?
Pollard?
Mr. Lawrence.
Mr. Lawrence wake up.
Where is the other boat gone?
Pollard!
Captain Pollard!
Pollard.
Captain Pollard sir!
Captain!
Captain Pollard!
Pollard!
What's the matter?
Ben-Benjamin. What are you doing?
He is dead.
Putting him overboard sir.
Look at me.
Look at me Benjamin.
No right minded sailor discards
what might yet save him.
Listen to me boy. Listen to me.
He can help us.
My God.
My heavenly king.
Sweetness is the power of his grace.
With longing eyes thy creatures
await on thee for daily food.
My soul is dead.
So it was decided.
We prepared the body.
We removed the organs.
Separated his limbs from his body,
and cut all the flesh from the bones.
After which...
we closed the body
and we sewed it up
as decently as we could
and committed it to the sea.
We ate the heart first.
You judge me.
No.
There.
It is done.
It is out.
And you have never told anyone?
No.
Not even your wife?
Do you think she could ever love me
if she knew the abominations,
I had committed?
Yes.
She would.
And if you had told me
the story when we met...
I would still wear your ring today.
The strength of that boy,
still lives in you.
I see that.
Even if you don't.
You can finish your story now my love.
Hey sit up.
Listen
put your head back.
Look we still got
a few drops of water left.
Don't you quit on me.
We are going home.
Do you have a family...
back home, Mr. Chase?
Yeah I have a wife.
Yes and a son or a daughter.
Very well.
Captain.
We will draw again.
We will do no such thing.
Mr. Ramsdell,
you will assume command of this vessel.
Cousin will you?
You are our...
You are our captain.
The men need you.
The men will be fine.
Please.
Please. Please.
Henry.
Let us draw again.
It is an order.
If you cannot do it,
pass the pistol to another man.
Henry, no, no, no!
You got to help me kid.
You got to help me.
We were weeks in the doldrums.
That part of the Pacific
is more desert than ocean.
The sun beating down.
My fear.
All I could think about
was that everyone would die
and I would be the last left alive.
And as best Mr. Chase could tell
we were still 800 miles from land.
Mr. Chase.
Captain Pollard.
I am happy to see you.
Been very little happiness in our survival.
Or in ours sir.
Barzillai?
The third boat?
They ave...
They ave been gone for days.
I am afraid they are lost sir.
Mr. Chase, you have the best position.
It's just a whale.
He is there! Throw the lance!
Throw it!
Throw it! Throw the lance!
Come on.
Throw it!
Kill it! He is there!
Throw the lance!
Why didn't you kill it?
You are a damn fool.
Currents drew us apart
and that was the last we would see
of Captain Pollard's whale boat.
A boat!
Broad on the port bow!
May God have mercy.
Mr. Chase.
Fath...
Father!
Don't lea...
Don't leave me Father!
Mr. Chase.
Sir.
Look. Look sir.
Mr. Chase.
Look.
Wake up Mr. Chase!
Here wake up!
Please, wake up sir there is land.
Mr. Chase look.
We were rescued there,
off the island of Mas Afuera, Chile
90 days after the sinking of the Essex.
They gave us some old clothes.
Fed us too.
It was hard to eat at first.
Strange.
They looked after us as best they could
till we found a ship
that would carry us home.
That voyage took another three months.
It looked like the whole island
turned out to see us return.
But there were no cheers.
Only silence.
They looked at us like we were...
apparitions,
phantoms.
We did said nothing of the details
of our survival to anyone
but I wondered if they somehow
knew of our privations.
Maybe they were just curious.
Oh my God!
I promised didn't I?
Oh God.
Hi.
Hey sweetie. Who is this?
Phoebe Ann.
Phoebe Ann Chase
This is Daddy.
Hey sweetie.
It's your daddy.
Oh my God.
Of course they could not leave him alone.
Mr. Chase and his wife had
scarcely walked a block towards home
when he was stopped and
made to return to the Maritime office.
There were business matters
still in question.
So to the matter.
Due to the significant loss of life
and property on our voyage,
it seems there will be an inquiry.
And as captain and first mate
we will be expected to give...
an account of what happened.
Yes, of course.
And having discussed this
with the ship owners and...
my father...
it is clear that full disclosure,
will have ramifications.
Terrible ramifications
for the whole industry.
That a whale brought down the Essex.
But it's the truth.
If the insurance houses and investors
were to start worrying about...
sea monsters sinking ships
sailors drawing lots to survive...
We are in the oil business.
All of us.
And as in any business
the probability of success must
always be greater than the risk incurred.
So what are you suggesting George?
That you say the ship ran aground.
That's a lie.
And that the men that died drowned.
And that's another lie.
Think on it. They will make you captain.
Well that pledge I already have
in writing.
Only on the condition
you bring home a ship full of oil.
This way it's guaranteed.
You would be a wealthy man.
The name Chase need
no longer be a landsman's name
but an established name that...
belongs among the great families
of Nantucket.
You want me to whitewash
what happened for profit?
We are asking you to be pragmatic.
The Essex was stove by a white whale.
And those of us that survived
in ill equipped whaleboats
had to commit abominations,
in order to survive.
And on our return
we are expected to spread barefaced lies
so that you the ship owners of Nantucket
might line your pockets
and sleep well at night?
Well I will not embroider the truth.
Nor should you George.
That last time I saw him...
Mr. Chase sir!
I could not find the right words
to say what I wanted to.
Thomas.
Perhaps there are no words.
I am gonna be on my way to Falmouth,
and...
It's...
It's been an honor sir...
to sail with you.
The honor is been mine Mr. Nickerson.
Here.
Good luck out there Thomas.
And you sir.
Next day George Pollard was called
before the inquiry.
Gentlemen Captain George Pollard.
And all the important men
in Nantucket were there.
It was a formality.
Good day to you Captain.
Please sit down.
For the record then...
The Essex was stove by a white whale,
1200 leagues west of Ecuador.
It was as if Owen Chase himself
had spoken.
Told them the truth.
Captain Pollard's conscience was clear.
But the inquiry was a sham.
Pollard went out again
looking for the white whale.
He never found it.
He ran a second ship aground off Hawaii.
Twice cursed.
Never sailed again.
And Owen Chase?
He was a man of his word.
First he sent a boat back
to Ducie Island.
Mr. Joy had passed.
But the other 3 were...
incredibly still alive.
And then?
And then he packed up his family,
and moved to New Bedford.
Started over.
Became a merchant captain
sailing on his own terms.
Well you certainly got your
money's worth Mr. Melville.
These February nights
are the longest of the year.
Well, you can both rest now.
Believe me.
I shall not be resting for some time.
Why?
You got your story.
You know your plot.
It's all there.
Maybe it was not...
a plot.
I was after.
No.
What then?
Something else you have given me tonight.
And what's that?
The courage to go where...
one does not want to go.
Mr. Melville...
what you have heard,
what I have told you,
will it all...
be of service to your book?
It will be a work of fiction,
Mr. Nickerson
inspired by truth.
But I, don't believe
I will feel the need to use all of it.
Thank you.
Here.
Take that with you.
No.
The money is for you. I insist.
I insist you keep it.
And I insist,
one person in this conversation is sober.
So it's back to...
Pittsfield Massachusetts.
Well...
good luck.
Thank you.
You know...
I heard a man from Pennsylvania
drilled a hole in the ground recently,
and found oil.
That can't be true.
I heard it too.
Oil from the ground.
Fancy that.
By LESAIGNEUR
Sync & corrections August 2022