OLD WOMAN:
Well, my dad was a farmer.
Um... Like everybody else
back then.
Of course,
he didn't start that way.
MAN ON RADIO: Computer
says you're too tight.
Nah, I got this.
Crossing the Straits.
Shutting it down, Cooper.Whoa!
[POWERING DOWN]
Shutting it all down.
No, I need power up!
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE: Eject![COOPER SCREAMING]
YOUNG MURPH: Dad?
Sorry, Murph.
Go back to bed, babe.
I thought you were the ghost.
No.
There are no such things
as ghosts, babe.
Grandpa says
you can get ghosts.
Yeah, maybe that's 'cause
Grandpa's a little too close
to being one himself.
Back to bed.
Were you dreaming
about the crash?
Get your butt back in bed,
Murph. [LAUGHS]
OLD MURPH: The wheat had died.
The blight came
and we had to burn it.
And we still had corn.
We had acres of corn.
But, uh, mostly we had dust.
OLD WOMAN 1:
I guess I can't describe it.
It was just constant.
Just that steady blow
of dirt.
OLD WOMAN 2: We wore
little strips of sheet
sometimes over
our nose and mouth
so that we wouldn't breathe
so much of it.
OLD MAN: Well,
when we set the table,
we always set the plate
upside-down.
Glasses or cups,
whatever it was,
upside-down.
Shake a leg!
Murph, get a move on!
COOPER: Tom, 4:00 today,
you and me in the barn,
Herbicide Resistance 101.
Check?Yes, sir.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER ON RADIO][DONALD HUMMING]
Not at the table, Murph.
Dad, can you fix this?
COOPER: What the heck
did you do to my lander?
Wasn't me.
Let me guess.
It was your ghost?
It knocked it off my shelf.
It keeps on
knocking books off.
TOM: No such thing as ghosts,
dumb-ass.
Hey.I looked it up.
It's called a poltergeist.
Dad, tell her.
Well, it's not
very scientific, Murph.
You said science was about
admitting what we don't know.
She's got you there.COOPER: Hey.
Start looking after our stuff.
Coop.
All right, Murph,
you want to talk science?
Don't just tell me that
you're afraid of some ghost.
No, you got to go further.
You got to record
the facts, analyze,
get to the how and the why,
then present your conclusions.
Deal?
Deal.All right.
Y'all have
a good day at school.
DONALD: Hold up.
Parent-teacher conferences.
Parent.
Not grandparent.
[HONKING HORN]
Slow down, turbo!
That's not a dust storm.
Nelson's torching
his whole crop.
Blight?
They're saying it's
the last harvest for okra.
Ever.
He should've planted corn
like the rest of us.
Now, you be nice
to that Ms. Hanley.
She's single.
What's that supposed to mean?
Repopulating the Earth.
Start pulling your weight,
young man.
Well, why don't you start
minding your own business,
old man.
All right, Murph,
give me second.
Uh-huh.
Third.
[GEARS GRINDING]
Find a gear, dumb-ass.Grind it!
Shut it, Tom!
[TIRE HISSING]
What'd you do, Murph?
Aw, she didn't do nothin'.
Blew a tire is all.
Murphy's Law.
Shut up!
Grab the spare, Tom.
That is the spare.
COOPER: Get the patch kit!
TOM: How am I supposed
to patch it out here?
COOPER:
You got to figure it out.
I'm not always gonna be here
to help you.
What's going on, Murph?
Why did you and Mom name me
after something that's bad?
Well, we didn't.
Murphy's Law?
Murphy's Law doesn't mean that
something bad will happen.
What it means is whatever
can happen will happen.
And that sounded
just fine with us.
Whoa!
Get in.
Get in, let's go.
What about the flat tire?
[ENGINE STARTING]
Yeah.
It's an Indian
Air Force drone.
Solar cells could power
an entire farm.
Take the wheel, Tom.
Go, go, go!
Keep that aimed right at it.
Faster, Tom. I'm losing it.
Right at it.
Stay on it.
Here we go. Here we go.
Whoa!
Nice one, Tom.
Dad?
I almost got it.
Don't stop. Don't stop!
Dad!
Tom!
Why? You told me
to keep driving.
Well, I guess that
answers the old,
"If I asked you to
drive off a cliff" scenario.
We lost it.
No, we didn't.
Want to give it a whirl?
This...
Go.
Let's lay her down
right there at the edge
of the reservoir.
Nicely done.
TOM: How long you think
it's been up there?
Delhi Mission Control
went down, same as ours,
10 years ago.Oh!
So for 10 years?
Why did it come down so low?
I don't know.
Maybe the sun
cooked its brain
or it was looking
for something.
What?
Give me a large flatblade.
Maybe some kind of signal?
I don't know.
What are you gonna do with it?
I'm gonna give it something
socially responsible to do,
[PANTING]
like drive a combine.
Can't we just let it go?
It wasn't hurting anybody.
This thing needs to learn
how to adapt, Murph,
like the rest of us.
COOPER: So how's this work?
You guys come with?
TOM: I've got class.
This one needs to wait.
What did you do?
They'll tell you about it
when you get in there.
Am I gonna be mad?
Not with me.
Just please try not to.
Hey, relax.
I got this.
Little late, Coop.
Yeah, we had a flat.
And I guess
you had to stop off
at the Asian
fighter plane store.
No, actually, sir, that's a...
That's a surveillance drone.
With outstanding solar cells.
It's Indian.
Take a seat.
So, uh...
We got Tom's scores back.
He's going to make
an excellent farmer.
Yeah, he's got
a knack for it.
What about college?
Well, the university
only takes a handful.
They don't really have
the resources to...
I still pay my taxes.
Where's that money go?
There's no more armies.
Well, it doesn't go
to the university.
Look, Coop,
you have to be realistic.
You're ruling my son out
for college now?
The kid's 15.
Tom's score simply
isn't high enough.
What's your waistline?
About 32?
About a 33 inseam?
I'm not sure I see
what you're getting at.
You're telling me
it takes two numbers
to measure your own ass,
but only one to measure
my son's future?
[SIGHS] Come on.
You're a well-educated man,
Coop.
And a trained pilot.And an engineer.
Okay, well, right now
we don't need
more engineers.
We didn't run out of
television screens
and planes.
We ran out of food.
The world needs farmers.
Good farmers, like you.
And Tom.
Uneducated farmers.
We're a caretaker
generation, Coop.
And things
are getting better.
Maybe your grandkids
will get to be engineers...
Are we done here, sir?
No.
Ms. Hanley's here
to talk about Murph.
MS. HANLEY: Murph is a great
kid. She's really bright.
But she's been having
a little trouble lately.
She brought this in
to show the other students.
The section
on the lunar landings.
Yeah, it's one
of my old textbooks.
She always loved
the pictures.
It's an old federal textbook.
We've replaced them
with the corrected versions.
Corrected?
Explaining how
the Apollomissions
were faked
to bankrupt the Soviet Union.
You don't believe
we went to the moon?
I believe it was a brilliant
piece of propaganda.
That the Soviets bankrupted
themselves pouring resources
into rockets
and other useless machines.
"Useless machines."
And if we don't want
a repeat of the excess
and wastefulness
of the 20th century, then
we need to teach our kids
about this planet,
not tales of leaving it.
You know, one of those
useless machines
they used to make
was called an MRI.
And if we had
any of those left,
the doctors would've
been able to find
the cyst in my wife's brain
before she died
instead of afterwards.
And then she'd have been
the one sitting here,
listening to this
instead of me,
which would have
been a good thing,
'cause she was always
the calmer one.
I'm sorry about your wife,
Mr. Cooper.
But Murph
got into a fistfight
with several of
her classmates over this
Apollononsense.
So we thought
it would be best
to bring you in
and see what ideas
you might have for
dealing with her behavior
on the homefront.
All right. [INHALES]
Yeah, you know what? Um...
There's a game tomorrow night.
She's going through
a bit of a baseball phase.
Her favorite team is playing,
and there's gonna be candy
and soda...
I think I'll take her to that.
[WHISTLING]
How'd it go?
I got you suspended.
What?BOOTS ON RADIO: Cooper.
This is Cooper, go.
Coop, those combines
you rebuilt went haywire.
Uh, just reset
the controllers.
I did that.
You should
come take a look.
BOOTS: One by one they've been
peeling off the fields
and heading over.
Something's interfering
with the compass.
Magnetism or some such.
[CLATTERING]
YOUNG MURPH: Nothing special
about which book.
I've been working on it,
like you said.
I counted the spaces.
Why?
In case the ghost
is trying to communicate.
I'm trying Morse.
Morse?
Yeah.
Dots and dashes, used...
I know what
Morse code is, Murph.
I just don't think
your bookshelf's
trying to talk to you.
COOPER: Had to reset every
compass clock and GPS
to offset for the anomaly.
DONALD: Which is?
I don't know.
If the house was built
on magnetic ore,
we'd have seen this
the first time
we switched on the tractor.
I hear your meeting at
the school didn't go so well.
[SCOFFS] You heard?
It's like we've forgotten
who we are, Donald.
Explorers, pioneers,
not caretakers.
When I was a kid,
it felt like they made
something new every day.
Some gadget or idea.
Like every day
was Christmas.
But six billion people...
Just try to imagine that.
And every last one of them
trying to have it all.
[SIGHS]
This world isn't so bad.
And Tom will do just fine.
You're the one
who doesn't belong.
Born 40 years too late,
or 40 years too early.
My daughter knew it,
God bless her.
And your kids know it.
Especially Murph.
Well, we used to look up
in the sky and wonder
at our place in the stars.
Now we just look down
and worry about
our place in the dirt.
Cooper,
you were good at something
and you never got a chance
to do anything with it.
I'm sorry.
You didn't expect this dirt
that was giving you this food
to turn on you like that
and destroy you.
In April, I believe I'm right,
15th of April, I think.
'Cause this happened
about 1:30, when that thing
came off the top
of that canyon.
[CROWD CHEERING]
In my day,
we had real ballplayers.
Who are these bums?
COOPER: Well, in my day,
people were too busy
fighting over food
to even play baseball.
Popcorn at a ballgame
is unnatural.
I want a hot dog.
School says you're gonna
follow in my footsteps.
I think that's great.[SCOFFS]
You think that's great?
You hate farming, Dad.
Grandpa said.
Grandpa said, huh?
Listen, all that matters is
how you feel about it.
I like what you do.
I like our farm.
You're gonna
be great at it.
[CROWD CHEERING]
[SIREN BLARING]
Let's get out of here.
COOPER:
All right, it's a doozy.
Uh, gang, let's mask up.
Tom? Murph? Check?CHILDREN: Yep.
Murph, Tom,
you guys shut your windows?
Murph!
YOUNG MURPH: The ghost.
Grab your pillow.
You're sleeping in with Tom.
It's not a ghost.
[WHISPERING] It's gravity.
DONALD: I'm dropping Tom,
then heading to town.
You want to clean that up
when you're finished
praying to it?
It's not Morse, Murph.
It's binary.
Thick is one, thin is zero.
Coordinates.
Nope.
Mmm-mmm.
Here we go.
Thirty-three.
That's it.
I can't miss this![SIGHS]
Grandpa will be back
in a couple hours, Murph.
But you don't know
what you're gonna find.
And that
is why I can't take you.
Murph?
Grandpa will be home
in a while.
Tell him I'll call him
on the radio.
[YELPS]Jeez!
What are you doing?
[LAUGHING]
Oh, you think
this is funny? Huh?
You wouldn't be here
if it wasn't for me.
Make yourself useful.
[CONTINUES LAUGHING]
[SOFTLY] Hey, Murph?
Murph!
I think this is
the end of the road.
Didn't you bring
the bolt cutters?
That's my girl.
MALE GUARD: Step away
from the fence!No, no, no.
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
I'm not armed.
My daughter's in the car.
[TASING]
[MECHANICAL FOOTSTEPS
APPROACHING]
MALE GUARD: Don't be afraid.[SCREAMS]
TARS: How did you
find this place?
Where's my daughter?
TARS: You had
the coordinates
for this facility
marked on your map.
Where did you get
those coordinates?
[SHOUTING]
Where's my daughter?
Don't make me
take you down again.
Sit down!
Oh, you still think
you're a Marine, pal?
Marines don't exist anymore.
And I got grunts like you
mowing my grass.
Where did you find
those coordinates?
But you don't look
much like a lawnmower.
Think I'll turn you into an
overqualified vacuum cleaner.
WOMAN: No, you won't.
TARS, back down, please.
You know, you're taking a risk
using ex-military as security.
They're old,
and their control units
are unpredictable.
It's what the government
could spare.
[PANTING]
Who are you?
Dr. Brand.
I knew a Dr. Brand once.
He was a professor.
What makes you think
I'm not?
Oh, wasn't near
as cute, either.
Please, Dr. Brand.
I don't have
any idea what this is.
Now I'm scared for
my daughter and
I want her by my side.
You give me that,
I'll tell you anything
you want to know.
Get the principals
and the girl in
the conference room, please.
Your daughter is fine.
Bright kid.
Must have a very smart mother.
It's pretty clear
you don't want any visitors.
So why don't you
just let us back up
from your fence
and we'll be on our way? Huh?
It's not that simple.
Well, sure, it is.
I don't know
anything about you.
anything about this place.
Yes, you do.
Dad!
Hello, Cooper.
Professor Brand.
WILLIAMS: Explain to me
how you found this facility.
Kind of an accident.
We stumbled upon it.
We were on a salvage run...
You're sitting in the
best-kept secret in the world.
Nobody stumbles in here.
Nobody stumbles out.
PROFESSOR BRAND:
Cooper... Please.
Cooperate with these people.
Look.
It's kind of hard to explain.
We learned these coordinates
from an anomaly.
What sort of anomaly?
I hesitate to
term it supernatural,
[CHUCKLES] but it definitely
wasn't scientific.
You're going to have to be
specific, Mr. Cooper.
Right now.
It was gravity.
DOYLE: Um...
What sort of
gravitational anomaly?
Where was this?COOPER: Hey.
Now I'm real happy
'cause you're excited
about gravity, bud,
but you're not getting
any answers from us
until I get assurances.
Assurances?Yeah.
Like that we're
getting out of here.
And I don't mean
in the trunk of some car.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Don't you know
who we are, Coop?
No, Professor, I don't.
BRAND: You know my father,
Professor Brand.
We're NASA.
NASA?
PROFESSOR BRAND: NASA.
The same NASA you flew for.
COOPER: I heard
they shut you down, sir,
for refusing to drop bombs
from the stratosphere
onto starving people.
When they realized that
killing other people was
not a long-term solution,
then they needed us back.
In secret.Why secret?
Because public opinion
wouldn't allow
spending on
space exploration.
Not when you're struggling
to put food on the table.
Blight.
Wheat seven years ago.
Okra this year.
Now there's just corn.
And we're growing
more than we ever have.
But like the potatoes
in Ireland
and the wheat
in the Dust Bowl,
the corn will die.
Soon.
We'll find a way, Professor.
We always have.
Driven by the unshakeable
faith the Earth is ours.
Well, not just ours, no.
But it is our home.
Earth's atmosphere
is 80% nitrogen.
We don't even
breathe nitrogen.
Blight does.
And as it thrives,
our air gets
less and less oxygen.
The last people to starve
will be the first
to suffocate.
And your
daughter's generation
will be the last
to survive on Earth.
BRAND: Murph is feeling
a little tired.
I was wondering if she could
take a nap in my office.
Yeah. Thank you.
Okay.
Now you need to tell me
what your plan is
to save the world.
We're not meant
We're meant to leave it.
COOPER: Rangers.
PROFESSOR BRAND:
The last components
of our one versatile ship
in orbit, the Endurance.
Our final expedition.
You sent people out there
looking for a new home?
The Lazarus missions.
Oh, that sounds cheerful.
Lazarus came back
from the dead.
Sure, but he had to die
in the first place.
There's not a planet
in our solar system
that could sustain life
and the nearest star's
over 1,000 years away.
And that doesn't even
qualify as futile.
Where'd you send 'em?
Cooper,
I can't tell you any more
unless you agree
to pilot this craft.
You're the best pilot
we ever had.
I barely left
the stratosphere.
This team never
left the simulator.
We need a pilot,
and this is the mission
that you were trained for.
Without even knowing it?
An hour ago, you didn't even
know I was alive.
You were going anyway.
We had no choice.
But something sent you here.
They chose you.
Who's "they"?
How long would I be gone?
Hard to know.
Years?
I've got kids, Professor.
Get out there and save them.
Who's "they"?
We started detecting
gravitational anomalies
almost 50 years ago.
Mostly small distortions
to our instruments
in the upper atmosphere.
In fact, I believe
you encountered one yourself.
Yeah, over the Straits.
My crash.
Something tripped
my fly-by-wire.
Exactly.
But of all these anomalies,
the most significant is this.
Out near Saturn,
a disturbance of spacetime.
Is that a wormhole?
It appeared 48 years ago.
And it leads where?
Another galaxy.
A wormhole's not a naturally
occurring phenomenon.
Someone placed it there.
"They"?Mmm-hmm.
And whoever they are,
they appear to be
looking out for us.
That wormhole
lets us travel
to other stars.
It came along
right as we needed it.
They've put potentially
habitable worlds
right within our reach.
Twelve, in fact,
from our initial probes.
You sent probes into that?Mmm-hmm.
We sent people into it.
Ten years ago.
The Lazarus missions.
PROFESSOR BRAND:
Twelve possible worlds,
12 Ranger launches
carrying
the bravest humans
ever to live,
led by the remarkable
Dr. Mann.
Each person's landing pod
had enough life support
for two years.
But they could
use hibernation
to stretch that,
making observations
on organics
over a decade or more.
Their mission was
to assess their world,
and if it showed potential,
then they could
send out a signal,
bed down for the long nap,
wait to be rescued.
And what if the world
didn't show promise?
Hence the bravery.
You don't have the resources
to visit all 12.
No.
Data transmission back through
the wormhole is rudimentary.
Simple binary pings
on an annual basis
give us some clue as to
which worlds have potential.
And one system shows promise.
One. That's a bit of
a long shot, isn't it?
One system with
three potential worlds?
[CHUCKLES]
No long shot.
Okay.
So if we find a home,
then what?
That's the long shot.
There's a Plan A and a Plan B.
Did you notice
anything strange
about the launch chamber?
COOPER: This entire facility's
a centrifuge.
Some kind of vehicle.
A space station?
PROFESSOR BRAND:
Both. Plan A.
How do you get it
off the ground?
The first gravitational
anomalies changed everything.
Suddenly we knew that
harnessing gravity was real.
So I started
working on a theory
and we started
building this station.
But you haven't
solved it yet.
That's why
there's Plan B.
The problem is gravity.
How to get a viable amount of
human life off the planet.
This is one way.
Plan B: a population bomb.
Over 5,000 fertilized eggs
weighing in at
just under 900 kilos.
Well, how would you raise 'em?
With equipment on board,
we incubate the first 10.
After that,
with surrogacy,
the growth
becomes exponential.
Within 30 years,
we could have
a colony of hundreds.
The real difficulty
with colonization
is genetic diversity.
This takes care of that.
But what about
the people here?
You just...
You give up on 'em?
My kids?
That's why Plan A
is a lot more fun.
How far have you got?
Almost there.
You're asking me
to hang everything
on an almost.
I'm asking you to trust me.
[SIGHS]
Find us a new home.
And by the time you return,
I will have solved
the problem of gravity.
I give you my word.
YOUNG MURPH: Go away!
[SIGHING]
Murph.
Go! If you're leaving,
just go.
DONALD: This world was never
enough for you, was it, Coop?
What, because
heading out there
is what I feel like
I was born to do?
And it excites me?
No, that does not
make it wrong.
DONALD: It might.
Don't trust the right thing
done for the wrong reason.
The why of the thing,
that's the foundation.
And the foundation's solid.
We farmers,
we sit here every year
when the rains fail
and we say,
"Next year."
Well, next year
ain't gonna save us,
nor the one after that.
This world's
a treasure, Donald,
but it's been telling us
to leave for a while now.
Mankind was born on Earth,
it was never meant
to die here.
Tom will be all right,
but you got to
make things right
with Murph.
I will.
Without making promises
you don't know you can keep.
You have to talk to me, Murph.
I need to fix this
before I go.
Then I'll keep it broken
so you have to stay.
After you kids came along,
your mom,
she said something to me
I never quite understood.
She said, "Now,
"we're just here to be
memories for our kids."
And I think now I understand
what she meant.
Once you're a parent,
you're the ghost
of your children's future.
[SNIFFLES] You said
ghosts didn't exist.
That's right, Murph.
Murph, look at me.
I can't be
your ghost right now.
I need to exist.
They chose me.
Murph, they chose me.
You saw. You're the one
who led me to 'em.
That's exactly
why you can't go.
I figured out the message.
One word. Know what it is?
"Stay."
It says, "Stay," Dad.
[WHISPERS] Murph.
You don't believe me.
Look at the books!
Look at this. It says, "Stay."
Why... You're not listening!
It says, "Stay!"
No, I'm coming back.
When?
[SNIFFLES]
[KISSES]
One for you, one for me.
When I'm up there
in hypersleep, or...
[SNIFFLES]
Or traveling
near the speed of light,
or near a black hole,
time's gonna change for me.
It's gonna run more slowly.
When we get back,
we're gonna compare.
YOUNG MURPH: Time will
run differently for us?
[WHISPERS] Yeah.
By the time I get back,
we might even be
the same age, you and me.
"What?" Imagine that!
Aw, Murph...
You have no idea
when you're coming back.
No idea at all![CLATTERS]
Murphy...[SOBBING]
Murph, don't make me
leave like this.
Come on, Murph!
Don't make me leave
like this, Murph!
[YOUNG MURPH
CONTINUES SOBBING]
Hey...
I love you.
Forever. You hear me?
I love you forever.
And I'm coming back.
I'm coming back.
How'd it go?
COOPER: It went fine.
Just fine.
I love you, Tom.
Travel safe, yeah?Yeah.
You look after our place
for me, all right?
All right?Uh-huh.
Hey, can I use your truck
while you're gone?
You mean your truck?
I'll make sure
they bring it back.
[ENGINE STARTS]
Look after my kids, Donald!
TARS: Go for
main engine start.
T minus 10...
Dad!
...nine...
...eight,
seven...
Dad!
...six,
five, main engine start, four,
three,
two,
one. Booster ignition and...
Lift off.
All engines look good.
Beginning roll program.
Prepare for
stage one separation.
Stage one.
There is Mach 1.
Everybody good?
Plenty of slaves
for my robot colony?
They gave him a humor setting,
so he'd fit in better
with his unit.
He thinks it relaxes us.
A giant sarcastic robot.
What a great idea!
TARS: I have a cue light
I can use
when I'm joking
if you like.
That'd probably help.
Yeah, you can use it to find
your way back into the ship
after I blow you
out the airlock.
What's your
humor setting, TARS?
That's 100%.
Let's bring it on down
to 75, please.
TARS: Stage two separation.
COOPER:
All feeds going manual.
DOYLE: Going manual.
Deactivate probe heater
one, two and three.
DOYLE: Check.
Taking control.
TARS: This is handover to you.
DOYLE: ADF check.
COOPER: Over.
Pull thrusters back.
Fuel cells one,
two, three.
DOYLE: 100%.
COOPER: Ex-mites.
It's hard leaving
everything.
My kids. Your father.
We're going to be spending
a lot of time together.
We should learn to talk.
And when not to.
Just being honest.
I don't think
you need to be that honest.
Hey, TARS, what's
your honesty parameter?
90%.
90%?
Absolute honesty isn't
always the most diplomatic,
nor the safest form
of communication
with emotional beings.
Okay.
90% it is, Dr. Brand.
We are coming up
on the Endurance.
Twelve minutes out.
Okay. Taking control.
Approaching module port,
500 meters.
It's all you, Doyle.
Nice and easy, Doyle.
Nice and easy.
I'm feeling good.
Take us home.
Lock?
Target locked.DOYLE: Target locked.
COOPER: Well done.Okay, helmets on.
Good job.
Door's not charging.
Never mind.
Cooper,
you should have control.
Control here.
Communication with
ring module active.
[WHISPERS] Oh, wow.
TARS: That's initiate.
[BRAND SIGHS]
COOPER: Are we ready to spin?
BRAND: Just a sec.
TARS: Hello, CASE.
Hello, TARS.
All right, we're all set.
Let's do it.
[CHUCKLES]
COOPER: 30% of spin.
One G.
How's gravity
treating you back there?
Well.
Romilly? Hey, you okay?
Yeah. Mmm.You all right?
Yeah,
I just need a minute.
BRAND: Okay, I think
we have some Dramamine
in the hab pod.
I'm just gonna go get that.
Might be in
the cryo-beds.
I'll just be a sec.
Hey, Brand?
Yeah?
Bring a lot.[LAUGHS]
Amelia... Be safe.
Give my regards
to Dr. Mann.
I will, Dad.
It looks good
for your trajectory.
We've calculated
two years to Saturn.
That's a lot of Dramamine.
Look after my family,
will you, please, sir?
We'll be waiting for you
when you get back.
A little older,
a little wiser,
but happy to see you.
"Do not go gentle
into that good night
"Old age should burn and rave
at close of day
"Rage, rage against
the dying of the light
"Though wise men at their end
know dark is right
"Because their words had
forked no lightning they
"Do not go gentle
into that good night
"Rage, rage against
the dying of the light"
DOYLE: [WHISPERS] You good?ROMILLY: Yeah.
Okay.Thank you, sir.
Here. Pills.
So alone.
We have each other.
Dr. Mann had it worse.
No, I mean them.
Hmm?
COOPER: It's a perfect planet,
and we're not gonna
find another one like her.
No, it's not like
looking for a new condo.
The human race
is going to be
adrift,
desperate for a rock
it can cling to
while it catches
its breath.
We need to find that rock.
And our three prospects
are at the edge of what
might sustain human life.
Laura Miller's planet
is first.
Laura started
our biology program.
COOPER: Mmm-hmm.
BRAND: Uh,
Wolf Edmunds is here.
Tell me about Edmunds.
Oh, uh...
Wolf's a particle physicist.
None of them
had families, huh?
No. No attachments.
My father insisted.
They all knew
the odds against
ever seeing
another human being again.
I'm hoping we can surprise
at least three of them.
How about Mann?Dr. Mann?
Well, he's remarkable.
He's the best of us.
He inspired 11 people
to follow him
on the loneliest journey
in human history.
Scientists, explorers.
That's what I love.
You know, out there
we face great odds.
Death, but...
Not evil.
You don't think
nature can be evil?
No. Formidable.
Frightening. But...
No, not evil.
Well, is a lion evil because
it rips a gazelle to shreds?
Just what we take
with us, is that it?
Yeah.
This crew represents
the best of humanity.
Even me, huh?
You know what?
We agreed, 90%.
There you go.
Don't stay up.
I'll be there in a minute.
Just remember, Coop,
you are literally
wasting your breath.
COOPER: Hey, TARS?
Let's go over that trajectory
one more time.
TARS: Eight months to Mars.
Counter-orbital
slingshot around.
Fourteen months to Saturn.
Nothing's changed on that.
Just let me
ask you something.
[WHISPERING]
Dr. Brand and Edmunds...
TARS: Why are you whispering?
They can't hear you.
[NORMAL VOICE]
Dr. Brand and Edmunds.
They close?
I wouldn't know.
Is that 90% "wouldn't know"
or 10% "wouldn't know"?
I also have
a discretion setting, Cooper.
Oh.
But not a poker face, Slick.
Hey, guys.
Dad's about to go down
for the long nap.
So I wanted to
give you an update.
Uh...
The Earth looks
amazing from here.
Um...
You can't see
any of the dust.
[CHUCKLES]
I really hope
you guys are doing great.
I know you're gonna
get this message.
Professor Brand's assured me
that he's gonna get it to you.
Know that I love you.
Is it him?
DONALD:
I don't think so, Murph.
You must be Donald.
Hello, Murph.
Why are you
in my dad's truck?
He wanted me
to bring it for your brother.
He sent you a message.
She's pretty upset
with him for leaving.
If you record any messages,
I can get them
to transmit it to Cooper.
Murph is a bright spark.
Maybe I should fan the flame.
She's already making fools
of her teachers.
So maybe she should come
and make a fool out of you.
So where are they?
Heading for Mars.
The next time
you hear from Cooper,
they'll be coming up
on Saturn.
YOUNG TOM: ...school goes,
the administration wants me
to repeat plant pathology.
Which sucks.
But they said I could start
advanced agriculture
a year early.
All right, I got to go, Dad.
Hope you're safe up there.
DONALD: I'm sorry, Coop.
I asked Murph to say hi,
but she's as stubborn
as her old man.
I'll try again next time.
COOPER: You all right, Rom?
This gets to me, Cooper.
This. This.
Millimeters of aluminum,
that's it, and then nothing
out there
for millions of miles
won't kill us in seconds.
You know that
some of the finest
solo yachtsmen in the world
don't know how to swim?
They don't know how.
And if they go overboard,
they're done.
We're explorers, Rom.
This is our boat.
Here.
[DEVICE BEEPS][CRICKETS CHIRPING]
[RAIN FALLING]
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
COOPER: This is
from the relay probe?
It was in orbit
around the wormhole.
This is the wormhole,
and every time
we'd come around,
we would receive images
from the other side
of the foreign galaxy.
Oh, yeah. Like swinging
a periscope around.
Exactly.
So we got a pretty good idea
what we're gonna find
on the other side, huh?
Navigationally.
BRAND ON INTERCOM:
Guys? Looks like we'll be
approaching the wormhole
in about three hours.
Hey, Coop?
Can we stop the spinning?
Why?Um...
Because we're close enough
to see it now?
All right.
[WHISPERS] Thanks.
There, that's it!
That's the wormhole!
Say it,
don't spray it, Rom.
It's a sphere.
Of course it is. You thought
it would just be a hole?
No, it's just that
all the illustrations
I've ever seen, they...
ROMILLY: The illustrations
are trying to show you
how it works.
So they say you want to
go from here to there.
But it's too far, right?
Mmm-hmm.
So a wormhole
bends space like this,
so you can take
a shortcut through
a higher dimension.
Okay, so,
to show that,
they've turned
three-dimensional space
into two dimensions,
which turns a wormhole into
two dimensions... A circle.
What's a circle
in three dimensions?
A sphere.Exactly.
A spherical hole.
But who put it there?
Who do we have to thank?
I'm not thanking anybody
until we get out of here
in one piece, Rom.
Any trick to this, Doyle?
No one knows.
[SIGHING]
The others made it, right?
At least some of them.
COOPER: Oh...
Everybody ready to say
good-bye to our solar system?
To our galaxy.
Here we go.
[RATTLING]
[BEEPING]
Your controls won't work here.
We're passing
through the bulk.
It's space beyond
our three dimensions.
All you can do
is record and observe.
[BREATH TREMBLING]
What is that?
I think it's them.
Distorting spacetime.
Don't! Don't!
[ALARM BLARING]
[ALARM CONTINUES BLARING]
[ALARM STOPS]
What was that?
The first handshake.
We're...
We're here.
So the lost communications
came through.
BRAND: How?
The relay on this side
cached them.
So years of basic data.
No real surprises.
Miller's site has kept
pinging thumbs up,
as has Dr. Mann's.
Edmunds' went down
three years ago.
Transmitter failure?
Maybe. He was sending
the thumbs up
right until it went dark.
But Miller's still looks good,
though, right?
Because she's
coming up fast.
Mmm-hmm.
With one complication.
The planet is much closer to
Gargantua than we thought.
COOPER: Gargantua?
It's what we're calling
the black hole.
Miller's and Dr. Mann's
planets both orbit it.
And Miller's
is on the horizon?
ROMILLY: As a basketball
around a hoop.
Landing there takes us
dangerously close.
And a black hole that big
has a huge gravitational pull.
Look, I could swing around
that neutron star
to decelerate.
No, no, no, it's not that.
It's time.
The gravity on that planet
will slow our clock
compared to Earth's
drastically.
How bad?
Every hour we spend
on that planet will be
seven years back on Earth.
[WHISPERS] Jesus!
Well, that's relativity,
folks.
Well, we can't just
drop down there without...
Cooper, we have a mission.
Yeah, Doyle,
we have a mission,
and our mission Plan A is
to find a planet that
can habitate the people
that are living
on the Earth right now.
You can't just think
about your family.
Now, you have to think
bigger than that, all right?
I am thinking about my family
and millions of
other families, okay?
Plan A does not work
if the people on Earth
are dead by the time
we pull it off.
No. It doesn't.
That's why there's a Plan B.
Okay. Cooper's right.
We need to think about time
as a resource,
just like oxygen and food.
Going down there
is gonna cost us.
All right, look.
Dr. Mann's data
is promising, right,
but it's going to take us
months to get there.
And Edmunds',
it's even further.
Now Miller hasn't sent much,
but what she has sent
is very promising.
It's water,
it's organics...
You don't find that every day.
No, you don't.
And just think
about the resources,
including time,
that would be spent
trying to get back here.
Romilly?Yeah.
How far off from Miller's
planet do we have to be
to stay out of
the time shift?
Just back from the cusp.
Which is here,
just outside of
Miller's planet.
ROMILLY: Right.Okay.
Here's Gargantua.
Here's Miller's planet.
Instead of taking
the Endurance
into orbit
around Miller's planet,
which would conserve fuel,
but we would lose
a lot of time,
what if we take a wider orbit
around Gargantua,
parallel with
Miller's planet,
outside of this time shift,
to here?
Then we take the Ranger down,
we get Miller,
we get her samples.
We come back,
we analyze, we debrief.
We're in, we're out.
We lose a little fuel,
but we save a lot of time.
That'll work.That's good.
There's not gonna be time
for monkey business
or chit-chat down there.
So, TARS, you should
definitely stay here.
CASE, you're with me.
Anyone else can stay.
If we're talking
about a couple years,
I could use the time
to research gravity.
Observations from
the wormhole,
that's gold
to Professor Brand.
TARS, factor an orbit
of Gargantua.
Conserve fuel,
minimize thrusting,
but make sure we stay
in range of Miller's planet.
You got it?
TARS: I wouldn't
leave you behind,
Dr. Brand.
COOPER: You ready, CASE?Yup.
You don't say much, do you?
TARS talks plenty
for both of us.
[BEEPING]
Detach.
[RATTLING]Romilly, are you reading
these forces?
ROMILLY: It's unbelievable.
A literal heart of darkness.
If we could just see
the collapsed star inside
the singularity,
yeah, we'd solve gravity.
And we can't
get anything from it?
ROMILLY: Nothing
escapes that horizon.
Not even light.
Oh, the answer's there,
just no way to see it.
There's Miller's planet.
Good-bye, Ranger.
CASE: This is fast
for atmospheric entry.
Should we use
the thrusters to slow?
No.
No, I'm gonna use
the Ranger's aerodynamics
to save some fuel.
CASE: Air brake?
We want to get down fast,
don't we?
Actually, we want to
get there in one piece.
Hang on.
CASE: Brand, Doyle, get ready.
[PANTING]
[BEEPING]
CASE: We should ease!
COOPER: Hands where I can
see 'em, CASE.
The only time
I ever went down
was when a machine was
easing at the wrong time.
CASE: A little caution...Can get you killed,
just like reckless driving.
DOYLE: Cooper,
it's too damn fast!
I got this.
CASE: Should I disable
the feedback?
No. No,
I need to feel the air.
Here we go.
DOYLE: It's just water!
[PANTING]
The stuff of life.
CASE: 1,200 meters.
Do we have a fix
on the beacon?
CASE: Got it!
Can you maneuver?
I'm gonna need to
shave some speed.
I'm gonna spiral down
on top of it.
Everybody hang on!
CASE: 700.
On my cue, CASE. On my cue.
CASE: 500 meters.
[BRAND PANTING]
Fire!
Very graceful.
No.
But very... Efficient.
What are you waiting for?
Let's go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Seven years per hour here.
Let's make it count!
[BRAND PANTING]
CASE: This way.
About 200 meters.
The gravity's punishing.
Been floating through space
too long?
CASE: 130% Earth gravity.
Come on.
[BRAND GRUNTING ON RADIO]Come on, come on.
There's nothing here.
CASE: Should be right here.
If the signal's coming
from here...
Her beacon.
DOYLE: Wreckage.
Where's the rest?
BRAND: Towards the mountains!
Those aren't mountains.
They're waves.
What? What?
Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
COOPER: That one's
moving away from us.
BRAND: We need the recorder.
Brand, Doyle,
back to the Ranger now!
BRAND: We're not leaving
without her data.
COOPER: Get back here now!
We do not have time!
A second wave is coming!
We're in
the middle of a swell.
BRAND: No, I got it.
Get your ass
back to the Ranger, now!
[BRAND GRUNTING]
Brand, get back here, now!
[GASPS]
BRAND: No, Cooper, go.
Cooper, go. I can't make it.
Go!
CASE, go get her.
Get up! Get up, Brand!
DOYLE: Go, go! Go!
I'm not gonna make it!
Yes, you are. Yes, you are!
[GRUNTING]
Come on, CASE has her!
Get back here, Doyle!
[BRAND CONTINUES GRUNTING]
Come on, Brand!
Get to the hatch!
[PANTING]
Go, go! Go!
[BEEPING]
COOPER: Shit.
Manually overriding
inside hatch!
Cooper! Wait!
Cooper, wait! Wait! Stop it!
COOPER: The engines
are flooded!
I'm gonna have to
shut her down.
[BRAND SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS]
[BRAND GASPS]
[GASPING]
Holy shit.
Hang on![CONTINUES GASPING]
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS]
[BOTH PANTING]
CASE, what's the problem?
CASE: Too waterlogged.
Let it drain.
God damn it!
I told you to leave me!And I told you...
Why didn't you leave me?...to get your ass back here!
The difference is one of us
was thinking
about the mission, Brand!
You were thinking about
getting home.
I was trying to do
the right thing!
Can you tell that to Doyle?
[GASPING]
COOPER: CASE, how much time?
45 to an hour.
[GASPS]
COOPER:
The stuff of life, huh?
What's this gonna
cost us, Brand?
A lot. Decades.
[GROANS]
What happened to Miller?
Judging by the wreckage,
she was broken up by a wave
soon after impact.
How's the wreckage
stayed together
after all these years, huh?
Because of the time slippage.
On this planet's time,
she just landed hours ago.
She probably just died
minutes ago.
CASE: The data Doyle received
was just the initial status,
echoing endlessly.
Oh, we are not
prepared for this.
You eggheads have the survival
skills of a Boy Scout troop.
Well, we got this far
on our brains,
farther than any human
in history.
Well, not far enough!
And now we're stuck here
till there won't be anyone
left on Earth to save.
I'm counting every minute,
same as you, Cooper.
Is there any possibility...
I don't know...
Some kind of way we can maybe
all jump in a black hole?
Gain back the years?
[SCOFFS]
Don't shake your head at me.
Time is relative, okay?
It can stretch
and it can squeeze, but
it can't run backwards.
It just can't.
The only thing that can move
across dimensions, like time,
is gravity.
Okay.
The beings that led us here,
they communicate
through gravity, right?[WHISPERS] Yes.
Could they be talking to us
from the future?
Maybe.
Okay. If they can...
"They" are beings
of five dimensions.
To them, time might be
another physical dimension.
To them,
the past might be a canyon
that they can climb into
and the future,
a mountain they can climb up.
But to us, it's not, okay?
Look, Cooper, I screwed up.
I'm sorry.
But you knew about relativity.
Oh...
Brand...
[INHALES DEEPLY]
My daughter was 10 years old.
I couldn't teach her
Einstein's theories
before I left.
Couldn't you have told her you
were going to save the world?
No.
When you become a parent,
one thing becomes
really clear.
And that is that
you want to make sure
your children feel safe.
And it rules out
telling a 10-year-old
that the world is ending.
CASE: Cooper?
[RUMBLING FROM OUTSIDE]
How long
for the engines, CASE?
A minute or two.
COOPER: Well,
we don't have it.
Helmets on!
Brand, co-pilot, you're up.
CASE, blow the cabin oxygen
through the main thrusters!
We're gonna spark it.Roger that.
Locked.Depressurizing.
Engines up![ENGINES POWERING UP]
Hello, Rom.
I've waited years.
How many...
How many years?
ROMILLY: By now it must be...
TARS: 23 years,
four months, eight days.
Doyle?
I thought I was prepared.
I knew the theory.
[WHISPERS]
Reality's different.
ROMILLY: And Miller?
There's nothing here for us.
[SOFTLY]
Why didn't you sleep?
Oh, I had
a couple of stretches.
But I stopped believing
you were coming back.
And something seemed wrong
about dreaming my life away.
I learned what I could
from the black hole,
but I couldn't send anything
to your father.
We've been receiving,
but nothing gets out.
BRAND: Is he alive?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah.
ROMILLY: We've got years
of messages stored.
Cooper.
MALE AUTOMATED VOICE:
Messages span 23 years.
Play it from the beginning.
YOUNG TOM: Hey, Dad.
Checking in. Saying hi.
Um...
Finished second in school.
Miss Kurling's
still giving me C's though.
Pulled me down,
but second's not bad.
Grandpa attended the ceremony.
Um...
Oh.
I met another girl, Dad.
I, uh...
I really think
this is the one.
Name's Lois.
That's her right there.
[COOPER SOBBING]
Murphy stole Grandpa's car.
She crashed it.
She's okay, though.
Hey, Dad.
Look at this!
You're a grandpa.
His name's Jesse.
I wanted to call him Coop,
but Lois says, uh,
maybe next time.
Donald says he's already
earned the "great" part,
so we just leave it at that.
Just hold him.
[JESSE GURGLING]
LOIS: Oh, dear.
Say "Bye-bye, Grandpa."
Bye-bye, Grandpa. It's okay.[JESSE FUSSING]
Sorry it's been a while.
It's, uh...
[SOFTLY] Just...
What with Jesse and all.
Uh...
Grandpa died last week.
We buried him out in the
back forty next to Mom and...
...Jesse.
Which is where we would have
buried you if you'd ever
come back.
Murph was there
at the funeral.
We don't see her that much,
but she came for that.
You aren't listening to this,
I know that.
All these messages
are just, like,
drifting out there
in the darkness.
Lois says that, uh,
I have to let you go.
And, uh...
So...
I guess I'm letting you go.
I don't know
where you are, Dad,
but I hope
that you're at peace and...
Good-bye.
Hey, Dad.
[WHISPERS] Hey, Murph.
You son of a bitch.
I never made one of these
when you were still responding
because I was so mad at you
for leaving.
And then when you went quiet,
it seemed like I should
live with that decision.
And I have.
But today's my birthday.
And it's a special one,
because you told me...
[SIGHS]
You once told me that
when you came back,
we might be the same age.
And today I'm the age
you were when you left.
[SOBBING]
So it would be a real good
time for you to come back.
[SWITCHES CAMERA OFF]
[SNIFFLES]
I didn't mean to intrude.
It's just that I've never
seen you in here before.
I've never been
in here before.
PROFESSOR BRAND:
I talk to Amelia all the time.
It helps.
I'm glad you've started.
MURPH: I haven't.
I just had something
I needed to get out.
PROFESSOR BRAND: I know
they're still out there.
MURPH: I know.
There are so many reasons
their communications
might not be
getting through.
I know, Professor.
I'm not sure
what I'm more afraid of.
Them never coming back,
or coming back
to find we've failed.
Then let's succeed.
So...
Back to the fourth iteration.
Let's run it through
some new fields.
With respect, Professor,
we've tried that
hundreds of times.
It only has to
work once, Murph.
Every rivet that
they strike could
have been a bullet.
We've done well
for the world here,
whether or not
we crack the equation
before I kick the bucket.
Don't be morbid, Professor.
I'm not afraid of death.
I'm an old physicist.
I'm afraid of time.
MURPH: Time.
You're afraid of time.
For years, we've been
trying to solve the equation
without changing
the underlying assumption
about time.
And?And that means
each iteration is an attempt
to prove its own proof.
It's recursive.
It's nonsensical.
Are you calling
my life's work
nonsense, Murph?
No, I'm saying
you've been trying to
finish it with one arm...
No, with both arms
tied behind your back.
And I don't understand why.
I'm an old man, Murph.
Can we take this point up
at another time?
I want to talk
to my daughter.
PROFESSOR BRAND: Stepping out
into the universe,
we must confront the reality
of interstellar travel.
We must reach far beyond
our own lifespans.
We must think not as
individuals but as a species.
"Do not go gentle
into that good night."
COOPER: TARS
kept the Endurance
right where we needed her.
But the trip took years longer
than we anticipated.
We no longer have the fuel
to visit both prospects, so...
We have to choose.
But how?
They're both promising.
Edmunds' data is better,
but Dr. Mann is the one
still transmitting.
We've no reason to suspect
Edmunds' data
would have soured.
His world has key elements
to sustain human life.
As does Dr. Mann's.
Cooper, this is my field.
And...
I really believe Edmunds'
is the better prospect.
Why?
Gargantua, that's why.
Look at Miller's planet.
Hydrocarbons, organics, yes.
But no life. Sterile.
We'll find the same thing
on Mann's.
Because of the black hole?
BRAND: Murphy's Law.
Whatever can happen
will happen.
Accident is the first
building block of evolution.
But when you're orbiting
a black hole,
not enough can happen.
It sucks in asteroids
and comets,
other events which would
otherwise reach you.
We need to
go further afield.
You once said that Dr. Mann
was the best of us.
He's remarkable.
We're only here
because of him.
And yet here he is.
He's on the ground,
and he's sending a very
unambiguous message,
telling us to
come to his planet.
Granted, but Edmunds' data
is more promising.
We should vote.
Well, if we're going to vote,
there's something
you should know.
Brand?
He has a right to know.
That has nothing
to do with it.
What does?
She's in love
with Wolf Edmunds.
ROMILLY: Is that true?
Yes.
And that makes me
want to follow my heart.
But maybe we've spent too long
trying to figure all this out
with theory.
You're a scientist, Brand.
So listen to me
when I say that love isn't
something we invented.
It's [SIGHS]
observable, powerful.
It has to mean something.
Love has meaning, yes.
Social utility,
social bonding,
child rearing...
We love people who have died.
Where's the social utility
in that?
None.
Maybe it means something more,
something we can't
yet understand.
Maybe it's some evidence,
some...
...artifact
of a higher dimension
that we can't
consciously perceive.
I'm drawn across the universe
to someone I haven't seen
in a decade,
who I know is probably dead.
Love is the one thing
we're capable of perceiving
that transcends dimensions
of time and space.
Maybe we should trust that,
even if we can't
understand it yet.
All right, Cooper...
Yes,
the tiniest possibility of
seeing Wolf again excites me.
That doesn't mean
I'm wrong.
Honestly, Amelia,
it might.
[SOBS]
TARS, chart a course
for Dr. Mann's.
We'll lose about a third
again. But next year...
[CLICKS TONGUE]
Next year I'm gonna work
Nelson's farm
and I'll make it up.
What happened to Nelson?
LOIS: Murph,
have you eaten enough?
Would you like
some more souffle?
No, no. I'm full, thanks.
It was delicious.
Coop, finish your fritter,
please.
Will you spend the night?
Your room is exactly
as you left it. It's ready.
I need to get back.
[SNIFFLES]
LOIS: My sewing machine
is in there,
but there's plenty of...
I need to...
Too many memories.
TOM: Well...
We might have
something for that.
Hey, Coop.
[COOP COUGHING]
The dust.
Lois, I have a friend who...
[COOP COUGHING]
...could look at his lungs.
COOPER: Amelia, I'm sorry.
You were just
being objective.
Unless you're punishing me
for screwing up
on Miller's planet.
No, this wasn't
a personal decision.
If you're wrong,
you will have a very personal
decision to make.
Your fuel calculations are
based on a return journey.
Strike out on Mann's planet,
and we'll have to decide
whether to return home
or push on to Edmunds'
with Plan B.
Starting a colony
could save us
from extinction.
You might have to
decide between
seeing your children again
and the future
of the human race.
I trust you'll be
as objective then.
He's been asking for you
since he came to.
We were trying
to reach you.
MURPH: [WHISPERS]
Hey.
Murph.
Hi. I'm here, Professor.
[WEAKLY] I let them all down.
No, you got us so far!
Real close.
I'll finish what you started.
Good, good, Murph.
You had faith
all those...
All those years.
I...
I asked you to have faith.
I wanted you to believe
that your father...
...would come back.
I do, Professor.
Forgive me, Murph.
There's nothing to forgive.
I...
I lied, Murph.
I lied to you.
There was no need for him
to come back.
There is no...
No way to help us.
But Plan A...
All this.
All these people.
And the equation.
Did my father know?
Did he leave me?
Do
not
go
gentle...
No.
No!
You can't leave.
You... No.
MURPH: Dr. Brand,
I'm sorry to tell
that your father died today.
He had no pain.
He was at peace.
I'm very sorry for your loss.
[SNIFFLES]
Brand, did you know?
He told you, right?
[BITTER LAUGH]
You knew.
This was all a sham.
You left us here.
To suffocate.
To starve.
[BEEPING]
COOPER: Frozen cloud.
[UNLOCKING]
[COUGHS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SOBBING]
It's okay.
Pray you never learn
just how good it can be
to see another face.
I hadn't a lot of hope
to begin with, but...
After so long, I had none.
My supplies were
completely exhausted.
The last time I went to sleep,
I didn't even set
a waking date.
You have literally
raised me from the dead.
Lazarus.Hmm.
What about the others?
I'm afraid you're it, sir.
So far, surely.
No, our present situation
is that there's very little
chance of rescuing any others.
BRAND: Dr. Mann. Dr. Mann?
Tell us about your world.
[SNIFFLES]
Our world, we hope.
Our world, uh, is cold,
stark,
but undeniably beautiful.
The days are 67 hours long,
cold.
The nights are
67 far colder hours.
The gravity is a very, very
pleasant 80% of the Earth's.
Now, up here where I landed,
the water is alkali,
and the air has too much
ammonia in it to breathe
for more than
just a few minutes,
but down at the surface...
And there is a surface.
...the chlorine dissipates.
The ammonia gives way
to crystalline hydrocarbons
and breathable air.
To organics.
Possibly, even to life.
We might be
sharing this world.
These readings
are from the surface?
Over the years,
I've dropped various probes.
COOPER: How far
have you explored?
I've mounted
several major expeditions.
But with oxygen
in limited supply,
KIPP there really did
most of the legwork.
TARS: What went wrong
with him, sir?
DR. MANN: Degeneration.
He misidentified
the first organics we found
as ammonia crystals.
He struggled on for a time,
but ultimately
I decommissioned him
and used his power source
to keep the mission going.
I thought I was alone
before I shut him down!
TARS: Would you like me
to look at him?
No. No.
He needs a human touch.
TARS: Dr. Brand, CASE is
relaying a message for you
from the comm station.
Okay. Be right there.
Excuse me.
Dr. Brand,
I'm sorry to tell you
that your father died today.
He had no pain.
He was at peace.
I'm sorry for your loss.
BRAND: Is that Murph?
She's... She's grown.
MURPH: Brand, did you know?
He told you, right?
[BITTER LAUGH]
You knew.
This was all a sham.
You left us here.
To suffocate.
To starve.
Did my father know, too?
[SOBBING] Dad?
I just want to know
if you left me here to die.
I just have to know.
[CONTINUES SOBBING]
Cooper, my...
My father dedicated
his whole life to Plan A.
I have no idea
what she's talking about.
DR. MANN: I do.
He never even hoped to
get the people off the Earth?
No.
But he's been
trying to solve
the gravity equation
for 40 years.
Amelia, your father
solved his equation
before I even left.
Then why wouldn't
he use it?
The equation couldn't
reconcile relativity
with quantum mechanics.
You need more.
More? More what?
DR. MANN: More data.
You need to see
into a black hole.
The laws of nature prohibit
a naked singularity.
Romilly, is that true?
If a black hole is an oyster,
then the singularity's
the pearl inside.
The gravity's so strong,
it's always hidden
in darkness
behind the horizon.
That's why we call it
a black hole.
Okay, but
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
if we see
beyond the horizon...
We can't, Coop.
DR. MANN:
There are some things
that aren't meant
to be known.
Your father had to
find another way
to save the human race
from extinction.
Plan B. A colony.
Why not tell people?
Why keep building
those damn stations?
Because he knew
how hard it would be
to get people to work together
to save the species
instead of themselves.
Or their children.
Bullshit.
You never would've come here
unless you believed
you were gonna save them.
Evolution has yet
to transcend
that simple barrier.
We can care deeply,
selflessly
about those we know,
but that empathy
rarely extends
beyond our line of sight.
But the lie.
That monstrous lie?
Unforgivable.
And he knew that.
He was prepared to
destroy his own humanity
in order to save the species.
He made
an incredible sacrifice.
No.
No, an incredible sacrifice
is being made
by the people on Earth
who are gonna die!
Because in his arrogance
he declared
their case hopeless.
I'm sorry, Cooper,
their case is hopeless.
No. No.
We are the future.
Cooper, what can I do?
Let me go home.
GETTY: You're
absolutely positive?
His solution was correct.
He'd had it for years.
It's worthless?
It's half the answer.
Okay. How do you find
the other half?
Out there? A black hole.
But stuck down here
on Earth?
Yeah?
I'm not sure you can.
GETTY: God,
they just pack up and leave.
What are they
hoping to find?
Survival.
Damn it.
Murph.
Don't... [SIGHS]
Don't people have
a right to know?
Well, panic won't help.
We just have to keep working,
same as ever.
Yeah. But isn't that exactly
what Professor Brand was
manipulating us to do?
Brand gave up on us.
I'm still trying
to solve this.
So...
Do you have an idea?
A feeling.
I told you about my ghost.
My dad thought
I called it a ghost
because I was scared of it.
But I was never scared of it.
I called it a ghost
because it felt...
It felt like a person.
It was trying to
tell me something.
If there's an answer
here on Earth, it's back there
somehow, in that room.
So I have to find it.
[ENGINE STARTING]
We're running out of time.
CASE: What about auxiliary
oxygen scrubbers?
COOPER: No,
they can stay, CASE.
I'll be sleeping
most of the way, anyway.
Hey, Coop.Yeah.
I have a suggestion
for your return journey.
Yeah, what's that?
Have one last crack
at the black hole.
I'm going home, Rom.
Yeah, I know.
This isn't going to
cost you any time.
There's a chance
for the people on Earth.
Talk to me.
Gargantua's an older
spinning black hole.
It's what we call
a gentle singularity.
Gentle?
They're hardly gentle.
But the tidal gravity
is so quick that
something crossing the horizon
fast might survive.
A probe, say.
What happens after it crosses?
After the horizon
is a complete mystery.
So, what's to say there
isn't some way that the probe
can glimpse the singularity
and relay the quantum data?
If he's equipped to transmit
every form of energy
that can pulse.
TARS: Just when did this probe
become a "he," Professor?
TARS is the obvious candidate.
I've already told him
what to look for.
TARS: I need the old optical
transmitter off KIPP, Cooper.
You'd do this for us?
TARS: Before
you get all teary,
try to remember that
as a robot
I have to do anything you say.
Your cue light's broken.
TARS: I'm not joking.
I'm gonna need TARS
to remove and adapt
some components from KIPP.
Well, I don't want to disturb
his archival functions.
ROMILLY: Oh, I'll supervise.
All right.
Dr. Mann, we need to find
three secure sites.
One for Brand's lab,
two for habitat.
Once those modules
have landed, you don't
want to move 'em.
Well, I can take you
to the probe sites,
but I don't think this...
These conditions
are gonna hold.
I think we should wait.
COOPER: CASE is
headed back down
with the rest
of the distillery equipment.
I'd really like to secure
those sites by nightfall.
Well, these squalls
do usually blow over.
Okay then.
But you're gonna need
a long-range transmitter.Got it.
Are you charged?Yeah.
Follow me.
TARS, 72 hours, yeah?
TARS: Roger that, Cooper.
DR. MANN: Brand told me why
you feel you have to go back.
But I'd be remiss if I didn't
at least mention that
a mission such as ours
could certainly use
an extra engineer.
[BEEPING]
You better slow down, turbo.
Safety first, CASE, remember.
CASE ON RADIO:
Safety first, Cooper.
COOPER: I have to
tell you, Dr. Mann,
I'm honored to be
a part of this.
But once we set up base camp
and secure those modules,
my work's done here.
I'm going home.
You have attachments.
But even without
a family, I can
promise you that,
that yearning
to be with other
people is powerful.
That emotion
is at the foundation
of what makes us human.
It's not to be taken lightly.
[LOIS COUGHING]
How long have you
had that cough?
LOIS: A while.
COOP: Mom lets me
play in here.
I don't touch your stuff.
Just take this gently.
DR. MANN: You know why we
couldn't just send machines
on these missions,
don't you, Cooper?
[PANTING] A machine
doesn't improvise well
because you can't program
a fear of death.
Our survival instinct
is our single greatest
source of inspiration.
Take you, for example.
A father
with a survival instinct
that extends to your kids.
What does research tell us
is the last thing
you're going to see
before you die?
Your children. Their faces.
At the moment of death,
your mind's gonna push
a little bit harder
to survive.
For them.
Deep breath.[COOP COUGHING]
Uh, hey, I bet you're Coop.
Why don't you have
a seat here for me?
It's bad.
They cannot stay here.
Okay?Yeah.
ROMILLY: TARS,
what's taking so long?
TARS: Professor,
I am having trouble
completing the boot up.
I don't understand.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
It's funny.
When I left Earth,
I thought I was
prepared to die.
The truth is,
I never really considered
the possibility
that my planet
wasn't the one.
Nothing worked out the way
it was supposed to.
COOPER: Let's go.
[BEEPING]
You... [SCREAMING]
[DR. MANN GRUNTS]
All right, hey, buddy,
why don't you give me
a big deep breath?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[COOP BREATHES DEEPLY]
What is this?
What are you doing?
DR. MANN: I'm sorry! I can't
let you leave with that ship.
We're gonna need it
to complete the mission
once the others realize
what this place isn't.
We cannot survive here.
I'm sorry!
[GRUNTING]
DR. MANN: No!
[SCREAMING]
MURPH: They can't stay
here anymore.
You have to leave right now.
Okay. Let me make something
abundantly clear.
You have a responsibility...Tom!
GETTY: Oh, Jesus.TOM: Coop, get her stuff.
She's going home.
Dad didn't raise you
to be this dumb, Tom!
TOM: Dad didn't raise me,
Grandpa did.
And he's buried out back
with Mom and Jesse.
[PANTING]
You faked all the data?
DR. MANN: Yeah.
[BOTH PANTING]
There's no surface?
No.
I tried to do
my duty, Cooper,
but I knew the day
that I arrived here
that this place had nothing.
And I resisted
the temptation for years,
but I knew that
if I just pressed
that button, then
somebody would come
and save me.
You fucking coward.
DR. MANN: Yes.
Yes.
[GRUNTS]
Listen, if you're not going
to go, let your family go.
Just, like, save your family.
And we go live underground
with you?
Pray that Daddy
comes to save us?
Dad's not coming back.
He never was coming back.
It's up to me.
You're gonna save everybody?
'Cause Dad couldn't do it.
Dad didn't even try!
Dad just abandoned us!
He left us here to die.
Nobody's going with you.
You gonna wait
for your next kid to die?
[WHISPERING] Get out.
And don't come back.
MURPH: You can keep my stuff.
[YELLING]
Stop it!
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]No. No!
Dr. Mann,
there's a 50/50 chance
you're gonna kill yourself!
Those are the best odds
I've had in years.
[SCREAMS][AIR ESCAPING]
[COOPER COUGHING]
[GASPING]
[GRUNTS]
[WHIMPERING]
Don't judge me, Cooper.
You were never tested
like I was.
Few men have been.
You tried your best, Murph.
[COOPER CHOKING]
You're feeling it, aren't you?
The survival instinct.
That's what drove me.
That's what drives all of us.
And it's what's gonna save us.
'Cause I want to save
all of us. For you, Cooper.
I'm sorry, I can't watch you
go through this, I'm sorry.
I thought I could,
but I can't.
I'm here. I'm here for you.
DR. MANN ON RADIO: Just listen
to my voice, Cooper.
I'm right here.
[CHOKING]
You're not alone.
[PANTING]
Do you see your children?
It's okay.
They're right there with you.
Did Professor Brand tell you
that poem before you left?
Do you remember?
"Do not go gentle
into that good night
"Old age should burn and rave
"At close of day
"Rage, rage against
the dying of the light"
[COOPER CHOKING]
[GASPING]
[CONTINUES GASPING]
Brand! Help!
Help! Help!Cooper?
[PANTING]
BRAND: CASE!
No air.
Ammonia.
BRAND: Cooper! Cooper,
we're coming! CASE!
CASE: I have a fix.BRAND: Go! Go, go, go!
CASE: And away!
Cooper, we're coming,
hang in there. Don't talk.
Try to breathe as little as
possible. We're almost there.
TARS: There's
a security lockout, sir.
It requires a person
to access function.
It's all yours, sir.Thank you.
BRAND: [PANTING]
Try not to breathe.
We're coming.
We're coming right now.
CASE, come on!
Move, move, move!
We got to go faster, CASE!
Faster, faster, faster!
Hang in there. Come on.[COOPER WHIMPERS]
I see him, I see him!
CASE, bank! Bank right!
[BRAND GRUNTS]
Cooper! Cooper!
I'm here!
[COOPER WHEEZING]
[INHALING]
Joe, get the water truck!
This data makes no sense.
[BRAND GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
I'm sorry.
What?
Mann was lying!
BRAND: Cooper.
Go. Go.
Romilly.
BRAND: Romilly!
Romilly! Do you read me,
Romilly? Romilly!
TARS: Step back, Professor!
Step back!
[PANTING]
COOPER: Romilly...
BRAND: Romilly,
do you read me?
Keep watch!
Lois?
COOPER: What happened
to caution, CASE?
CASE: Safety first, Cooper.
BRAND: Romilly.
Romilly, do you read me?
This is Brand.
Romilly?
CASE: Dr. Brand? Cooper?
There's been an explosion.
Dr. Mann's compound.
TARS! TARS, ten o'clock!
Let me know
when TARS is aboard.
TARS: Romilly did not survive.
I could not save him.
CASE: TARS is in.I'll take it from here.
Do we have a fix
on the Ranger?
CASE: He's pushing into orbit!
Ah, if he takes control
of that ship, we're dead.
He'd maroon us?
Oh, he is marooning us.
I'll meet you guys downstairs.
You can wait by the car.
Come on. Give me your bag.
Get in the back seat.
Get in the back seat now!
COOPER: Dr. Mann,
please respond.
Dr. Mann, please respond!
CASE: He doesn't know
the Endurance
docking procedure.
The autopilot does.
Not since TARS disabled it.
Nice.
What's your trust
setting, TARS?
Lower than yours apparently.
COOPER:
Do not attempt docking.
I repeat,
do not attempt docking.
Please res...
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Auto-docking sequence
withheld.
Override. Unauthorized.
Override.
Unauthorized.
Do not attempt docking.
I repeat,
do not attempt docking.
Please res...
[GRUNTING]
Moving slowly
toward the Endurance.
[ALARM BLARING]
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Imperfect contact.
Override. Hatch lockout.
Is he
locked on yet?
CASE: Imperfectly.
Dr. Mann, do not...
[ALARM CONTINUES BLARING]
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Hatch lockout disengaged.
Dr. Mann, do not, I repeat,
do not open the hatch.
I repeat,
If you open the hatch,
the airlock will depressurize.
[BEEPING]
What happens
if he blows the airlock?
CASE: Nothing good.
COOPER: Okay, pull back.
Pull back.
Retro thrusters,
everything we've got, CASE!
CASE: Retros at full!Back!
CASE, relay my transmission
to the onboard computer
and have it rebroadcast
as emergency PA.
Dr. Mann...
I repeat, do not open
the inner hatch. I repeat...
Brand?
I don't know
what he said to you,
but I am taking command
of the Endurance.
Then we can talk about
completing the mission.
Dr. Mann, listen to me.
This is not about my life.[ALARM BLARING]
Or Cooper's life.
This is about all mankind.
[ALARM STOPS]
There is a moment...
It is not sa...
Oh, my God.
[SWITCHES CLICKING]
[GEARS ENGAGING]
CASE: Cooper, there's no point
using your fuel to chase...
Analyze the Endurance'sspin.
Cooper, what are you doing?
Docking.
CASE: Endurancerotation
is 67... 68 RPM.
Get ready to match our spin
with the retro thrusters.
CASE: It's not possible.COOPER: No...
It's necessary.
CASE: Endurance
is hitting stratosphere!
BRAND: She's got
no heat shield.
CASE, you ready?Ready.
Cooper! This is no time
for caution.
CASE, if I black out,
you take the stick.
TARS, get ready to engage
the docking mechanism.
CASE: Endurance
is starting to heat.
20 feet out.
TARS: I need 3 degrees
starboard, Cooper.
10 feet out.
TARS: Cooper, we are lined up.
Initiating spin!
[BRAND MUMBLING AND GROANING]
[GRUNTING]
[GASPING]
Come on, TARS.
Come on, TARS!
TARS: We are locked, Cooper.
Locked. Easing up!
Easy.
COOPER: Retro thrusters!
Main engines on.
Pushing out of orbit.
Come on, baby.
Killing main engines!
Okay, we're out of orbit.
[LAUGHING]
Okay. And for our next trick!
[CONTINUES LAUGHING]
CASE: It'll have to be good.
We're heading
into Gargantua's pull.
COOPER: Oh, shit.
CASE, take the stick.Roger that.
[PANTING]
[BRAND GRUNTING AND PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
[BEEPING][COOPER GRUNTING]
[GRUNTING]
CASE: Cooper, we're slipping
towards Gargantua.
Shall I use main engines?
COOPER: No.
We got to let her slide
as far as we can.
[BRAND PANTING]
COOPER: Give it to me.
TARS: There's good news
and there's bad news, Cooper.
Yeah, I've heard
that one, TARS.
Give it to me straight.
The backup generator
kicked in,
so the system's stable.
They're all good.
Good.
Okay. The navigational hub
has been completely destroyed.
We don't have
enough life support
to make it
back to Earth, but
I think we can scratch our way
to Edmunds' planet.
What about fuel?
Not enough.
But I have a plan.
We let Gargantua pull us down
close to her horizon.
Then a powered
slingshot around,
launching us towards
Edmunds' planet.
BRAND: Manually?
That's what I'm here for.
I'm gonna take us just inside
the critical orbit.
BRAND: What about
the time slippage?
COOPER: Neither one of us
has time to worry
about relativity right now,
Dr. Brand.
I'm sorry, Cooper.
COOPER: Once we've gathered
enough speed
around Gargantua,
we use Lander 1
and Ranger 2
as rocket boosters to
push us out
of the black hole's gravity.
The Lander's linkages
have been destroyed,
so we'll have to
control manually.
Once Lander 1 is spent,
TARS will detach...
TARS: ...and get sucked
right into that black hole.
Why does TARS have to detach?
COOPER: Oh, we have to
shed the weight
to escape the gravity.
TARS: Newton's third law.
The only way humans
have ever figured out
of getting somewhere
is to leave something behind.
Cooper, you can't ask TARS
to do this for us.
He's a robot.
So you don't have to
ask him to do anything.
BRAND: Cooper, you asshole!
Sorry, you broke up
a little bit there.
TARS: It's what we intended,
Dr. Brand.
It's our only chance
to save people on Earth.
If I can find a way
to transmit
the quantum data
I'll find in there,
they might still make it.
Let's just hope there's still
someone there to save.
[HULL CREAKING]
CASE: Maximum velocity
achieved.
Prepare to fire
escape thrusters.
Ready?
Ready.
TARS: Ready.
CASE: Main engine ignition
in three,
two,
one...
Mark.[GASPING]
Come on, baby.
[GRUNTING]
CASE: Lander 1 engines,
on my mark.
Three,
two,
one. Mark.
[LAUGHS]
Ranger 2 engines,
on my mark.
Three, two, one...
Mark.Fire!
[GASPING]
Well, this little maneuver's
gonna cost us 51 years!
You don't sound so bad
for pushing 120!
[BOTH WHOOPING]
[SIGHS]
CASE: Lander 1, prepare
to detach on my mark.
Three, two,
one. Mark.
TARS: Detach!
BRAND: Good-bye, TARS.
Good-bye, Dr. Brand.
See you
on the other side, Coop.
See you there, Slick!
[BEEPING]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
Okay, CASE,
nice reckless flying!
CASE: Learned from the master.
Ranger 2, prepare to detach.
What?
No! No! Cooper!
CASE: Three...Cooper, what are you doing?
Newton's third law. You got to
leave something behind.
You told me we had enough
resources for both of us.
We agreed, Amelia,
90%.CASE: Mark.
Don't.
Detach.
[SOBBING]
COOPER:
Okay... I am nosing down.
Approaching the event horizon.
[EXHALES]
Portside,
dipping down beneath it
to go through it.
Heading towards... Blackness.
I have a visual of the event.
It's all black.
TARS, do you read me?
It's all blackness.
TARS! Do you read me? Over.
Okay.
Screens
getting interference.
[GRUNTS]
Losing control of the stick.
I got flashes.
Flashes of lightness
and blackness.
[STRAINING] The turbulence
in the gravity is increasing.
Uh...
The computers are going down.
[GRUNTS]
[GROANING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Gravitational pull. I'm losing
control of the stick.
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMING]
MAN 1: Come on and join me!
Cut it, before it jumps.
We need more.
MAN 2: On the next row!
GETTY: Murph? Murph, come on!
FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE:
Eject. Eject.
Eject.
[PANTING]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GASPING]
[GRUNTING]
[COUGHS]
[GASPING]
Ahhh!
[PANTING]
[GRUNTING]
[GASPING]
Murph.
Murph! Murph! Murph!
Murph!
No, no, no!
No! No!
[PANTING]
[SOBBING]
[SCREAMING]
[PANTING]
If you're leaving, just go.
COOPER: No, no. No.
No, don't go.
Don't go, you idiot.
Don't go!
Morse. Morse.
Morse.
Dot.
S.
T.
A.
Dash!
Dash! Dash!
Murph, we don't have time
for this! Come on!
Y.
[GRUNTS]
"Stay!"
[PANTING]
Come on, Murph.
Murph, come on!
What's it say?
What's it say, babe?
"Stay."
Tell him, Murph.
Make him stay.
Make him stay, Murph.
Don't let me leave, Murph!
[SOBBING]
No! No! No!
[CONTINUES SOBBING]
It was you.
You were my ghost.
[RADIO STATIC]
[SOBBING]
TARS: Cooper. Cooper.
Come in, Cooper.
TARS?
Roger that.
You survived.
Somewhere
in their fifth dimension.
They saved us.
Yeah? Who the hell is "they"?
And just why would
they want to help us, huh?
I don't know,
but they constructed
this three-dimensional space
inside their
five-dimensional reality
to allow you to understand it.
Well, that ain't working.
Yes, it is.
You've seen that time
is represented here
as a physical dimension.
You have worked out
that you can exert
a force across spacetime.
Gravity... To send a message.
Affirmative.
Gravity
can cross the dimensions,
including time.
Apparently.
Do you have the quantum data?
Roger. I have it.
I am transmitting it
on all wavelengths,
but nothing is getting out,
Cooper.
I can do this. I can do this.
But such complicated data
to a child?
Not just any child.
What else?
Oh, come on, Dad.
Murph, the fire's out!
Come on!
Even if you
communicate it here,
she won't understand
its significance for years.
I get that, TARS. All right?
But we've got to
figure something out
or the people on Earth
are gonna die.
Think, think, think!
Cooper,
they didn't bring us here
to change the past.
Say that again.
They didn't bring us here
to change the past.
No, they didn't bring us
here at all.
We brought ourselves.
COOPER: TARS, give me
the coordinates for NASA
in binary.
TARS: In binary. Roger.
Feeding data.
"It's not a ghost."
"It's gravity."
COOPER: [PANTING]
Don't you get it yet, TARS?
I brought myself here!
We're here to communicate with
a three-dimensional world.
We're the bridge!
I thought they chose me.
But they didn't choose me,
they chose her.
TARS: For what, Cooper?[LAUGHS]
To save the world.
All of this
is one little girl's bedroom.
Every moment.
It's infinitely complex.
They have access
to infinite time and space,
but they're not
bound by anything!
They can't find
a specific place in time.
They can't communicate.
That's why I'm here. I'm gonna
find a way to tell Murph,
just like I found this moment.
TARS: How, Cooper?
Love, TARS, love.
It's just like Brand said.
My connection with Murph,
it is quantifiable.
It's the key!
TARS: What are we here to do?
Find how to tell her.
The watch.
That's it.
We code the data into the
movement of the second hand.
TARS, translate the data
into Morse and feed it to me.
TARS: Translating data
into Morse.
Cooper, what if she
never came back for it?
She will. She will.
GETTY: Murph,
I can see his car!
He's coming, Murph!
Okay. I'm coming down.
TARS: How do you know?
Because I gave it to her.
TARS: Roger.
Morse is dot-dot-dash-dot.
COOPER: Dot-dot-
dash-dot.
TARS: Dot-dash-dot-dot.
COOPER: Dot-dash-dot-dot.
TARS: Dash-dash-dash.
COOPER: Dash-dash-dash.
[GASPS]
MURPH: He came back!
It was him all this time!
I didn't know. It was him!
Dad's gonna save us.
Eureka!
It's traditional.
[LAUGHING] Eureka!
Did it work?
TARS: I think it might have.
How do you know?
TARS: Because the bulk beings
are closing the tesseract.
Don't you get it yet, TARS?
They're not "beings."
They're us.
What I've been doing for
Murph, they're doing for me.
For all of us.
TARS: Cooper,
people couldn't build this.
COOPER: No. No, not yet.
But one day.
Not you and me. But a people.
A civilization that's evolved
past the four dimensions
we know.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
COOPER: What happens now?
DOCTOR: Mr. Cooper.
Let's take it slow, sir.
Nice and easy, Mr. Cooper.
Remember, you're
no spring chicken anymore.
Actually,
you are 124 years old.
[PEOPLE PLAYING BASEBALL
OUTSIDE]
Take it slow, sir.
You were extremely lucky.
The Rangers found you
with only minutes left
in your oxygen supply.
[GLASS SHATTERING]
[CHEERING AND LAUGHING]
Where am I?
DOCTOR: Cooper Station.
Currently orbiting Saturn.
Cooper Station.
Nice of you
to name it after me.
[LAUGHS]
What?
The station
isn't named after you, sir.
It's named
after your daughter.
Although she's
always maintained
just how important
you were.
Is she still alive?
She'll be here
in a couple weeks.
She is far too old
to be transferring
from another station,
but when she heard
that you'd been found...
Well, this is...
This is Murphy Cooper
we're talking about.
Yes, it is.
DOCTOR: We'll have you checked
out of here in a couple days.
I'm sure you'll be excited
to see what's in store.
I actually did a paper on you
in high school.
I know all about your life
back on Earth.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
If you'll follow me,
we've got a really
good situation for you.
So, um, when I made
my suggestion to Ms. Cooper,
I was delighted to hear that
she thought it was perfect.
OLD WOMAN 1:
It was just constant.
Just that steady blow of dirt.
Of course, I didn't
speak to her personally.
We always
set the plate upside-down.
Glasses or cups,
whatever it was, upside-down.
My dad was a farmer.
Like everybody else
back then.
There just
wasn't enough food.
OLD WOMAN 2: We wore
little things, little strips
of sheet, put it sometimes
over our nose and mouth,
so we wouldn't
breathe so much of it.
Well, it was pretty exciting
for me because it was hope.
OLD MAN: I don't care
who describes it,
there is no way for it to be
exaggerated. It was that bad.
ADMINISTRATOR:
She did confirm
just how much
you loved farming.
Oh, she did, did she?Yeah.
Here we are.
Home sweet home.
Everything replaced
and put back where it...
Hey, is this...
Oh, yeah.
The machine we found
out near Saturn
when we found you, yes.
Its power source was shot,
but we could get you
another one if you want it.
Yes. Please.
TARS: Settings.
General settings.
Security settings.
Honesty, new setting,
95%.
TARS: Confirmed.
Additional customization?
Humor,
75%.
TARS: Confirmed.
Auto self-destruct
T minus 10, nine...
Let's make that 60%.
TARS: 60% confirmed.
Knock-knock.
You want 55?
TARS: Is this really
what it was like?
It was never this clean,
Slick. [CHUCKLES]
I don't care much for this
pretending we're back
where we started.
I want to know where we are.
Where we're going.
Mr. Cooper.
The family's all in there.
Family?
Yeah, they all came out
to see her.
She's been in cryo-sleep
for almost two years.
[SOBBING]
You told 'em I like farming.
[LAUGHING]
It was me, Murph.
I was your ghost.
I know.
People didn't believe me.
They thought that
I was doing it all myself.
But...
I knew who it was.
Nobody believed me.
But I knew you'd come back.
How?
Because my dad promised me.
Well, I'm here now, Murph.
I'm here.
No.
No parent should have to
watch their own child die.
I have my kids here
for me now.
You go.
Where?
Brand.
She's out there,
setting up camp.
Alone
in a strange galaxy.
Maybe right now she's
settling in for the long nap
by the light of our new sun
in our new home.