Well my dad was a farmer.
Like everybody else back then.
Of course he didn't start that way.
Computer says you are too tight.
No I got this.
Crossing the Straights.
Shutting it down Cooper.
No!
Shutting it all down.
No I need power up!
Dad?
Sorry Murph.
Go back to bed babe.
I thought you were the ghost.
No.
There are no such things as ghosts babe.
Grandpa says you can get ghosts.
Well maybe that's because Grandpa
is a little too close to being one himself.
Back to bed.
Were you dreaming about the crash?
Get your butt back in bed Murph.
The wheat had died.
The blight came and we had to burn it.
And we still had corn.
We had acres of corn.
But...
mostly we had dust.
I guess I can't describe it.
It was just constant.
Just that steady blow of dirt.
We wore...
little strips of sheet,
but sometimes over our nose and mouth,
so that we would not breathe
so much of it.
Well when we set the table
we always set the plate upside-down.
Glasses or cups
whatever it was upside-down.
Shake a leg!
Murph get a move on!
Tom 4 o'clock today you and me
in the barn Herbicide Resistance 101.
Check?
Yes sir.
Not at the table Murph.
Dad can you fix this?
What the heck did you do to my lander?
Was not me.
Let me guess. It was your ghost?
It knocked it off my shelf.
It keeps knocking books off.
No such things as ghosts dumb-ass.
Hey.
I looked it up.
It's called a poltergeist.
Dad tell her.
Well it's not very scientific Murph.
You said science was about admitting
what we don't know.
She has got you there.
Hey.
Start looking after our stuff.
Coop.
Alright Murph you wanna talk science?
Don't just tell me that you are afraid
of some ghost.
No you got to go further.
You got to record the facts analyze
get to the how and why...
and present your conclusions.
Deal?
Deal.
Alright.
Have a good day at school.
Hold up.
Parent-teacher conferences. Parent.
Not grandparent.
Slow down Turbo.
That's not a dust storm.
Nelson is torching his whole crop.
Blight?
They are saying
it's the last harvest for okra.
Ever.
He should have planted corn
like the rest of us.
Now you be nice to that Miss Hanley.
She is single.
What's that supposed to mean?
Repopulating the earth start
pulling your weight young man.
Why don't you start minding
your own business...
old man?
Alright Murph give me second.
Third.
Find a gear dumb-ass.
Grind it!
Shut it Tom!
What did you do Murph?
She didn't do nothing.
Blew a tire is all.
Murphy's Law.
Shut up!
Grab the spare Tom.
That is the spare.
Get the patch kit!
How am I supposed to patch it out here?
You got to figure it out.
I am not always gonna be here to help you.
What's going on Murph?
Why did you and Mom name me
after something that's bad?
No we didn't.
Murphy's Law?
Murphy's Law doesn't mean
that something bad...
will happen. What it means
is whatever can happen...
will happen.
And that sounded just fine with us.
Get in.
Get in, let's go.
What about the flat tire?
Yeah.
It's an Indian Air Force drone.
Solar cells could power an entire farm.
Take the wheel Tom.
Go, go, go!
Keep that aimed right at it.
Faster Tom. I am losing it.
Right at it.
Stay on it.
Here we go.
Nice one Tom.
Dad?
I almost got it. Don't stop. Don't stop!
Dad!
Tom!
You told me to keep driving.
Well I guess that answers the old
if I asked you to drive off a cliff scenario.
We lost it.
No we didn't.
Want to give it a whirl?
This way.
Go.
Let's lay her down right there
at the edge of the reservoir.
Nicely done.
How long you think it's been up there?
Delhi Mission Control went down
same as ours
ten years ago.
So for ten years?
Why did it come down so low?
I don't know.
Maybe the sun cooked its brain
or it was looking for something.
What?
Give me a large flat blade.
Maybe some kind of signal?
I don't know.
What are you gonna do with it?
I am gonna give it something
socially responsible to do...
like drive a combine.
Can't we just let it go?
It was not hurting anybody.
This thing needs to learn
how to adapt Murph...
like the rest of us.
So How does this work?
You guys come with?
I have got class.
This one...
needs to wait.
What did you do?
They will tell you about it
when you get in there.
Am I not gonna be mad?
Not with me.
Just please try not to.
Hey.
Relax.
I got this.
Little late Coop.
Yeah we had a flat.
And I guess you had to stop
off at the Asian fighter plane store.
No actually sir that's a...
That's a surveillance drone.
With outstanding solar cells.
It's Indian.
Take a seat.
So...
we got Tom's scores back.
He is going to make an excellent farmer.
Yeah he has got a knack for it.
What about college?
Well the... university only takes a handful.
They don't really have the resources to...
I still pay my taxes.
Where is that money go?
There is no more armies.
Well it doesn't go to the university.
Look Coop you have to be realistic.
You are ruling my son out for college now?
The kid is 15.
Tom's score simply isn't high enough.
What's your waistline?
About what 32?
About a 33 inseam?
I am not sure I see
what you are getting at.
You are telling me it takes two numbers
to measure your own ass
but only one to measure my son's future?
Come on.
You are a well-educated man, Coop.
And a trained pilot.
And an engineer.
Ok well right now,
we don't need more engineers.
We didn't run out of television screens
and planes.
We ran out of food.
The world needs farmers.
Good farmers like you.
And Tom.
Uneducated farmers.
We are a caretaker generation Coop.
And things are getting better.
Maybe your grandkids will get to be engin...
We done here sir?
No.
Miss Hanley is here to talk about Murph.
Murph is a great kid.
She is really bright.
But she has been having
a little trouble lately.
She...
brought this in to show the students.
The section on the lunar landings.
Yeah it's one of my old textbooks.
She always loved the pictures.
It's an old federal textbook.
We have replaced them
with the corrected versions.
Corrected?
Explaining how the Apollo missions were
faked to bankrupt the Soviet Union.
You don't believe we went to the moon?
I believe it was a brilliant piece
of propaganda.
That the Soviets bankrupted themselves,
pouring resources into rockets
and other useless machines.
Useless machines.
And if we don't want a repeat of the excess
and wastefulness of the 20th century then...
we need to teach our kids
about this planet,
not tales of leaving it.
You know one of those useless machines
they used to make was called an MRI.
And if we had any of those left,
the doctors would have been able to find
the cyst in my wife's brain,
before she died instead of afterwards.
Then she would have been the one
sitting here listening to this,
instead of me which would have been
a good thing because she was always...
the calmer one.
I am sorry about your wife Mr. Cooper.
But...
Murph got into a fistfight with several
of her classmates over this...
Apollo nonsense.
So we thought it would be best to bring you
in and see what ideas you might have
for dealing with her
behavior on the home front.
Yeah you know what...
There is a game, tomorrow night.
She is going through a bit
of a baseball phase.
Her favorite team is playing.
There is gonna be candy and soda and...
I think I will take her to that.
How did it go?
I got you suspended.
What?
Cooper.
This is Cooper. Go.
Coop those combines
you rebuilt went haywire.
Just reset the controllers.
I did that.
Now you should come take a look.
One by one they ave been peeling
off the fields and heading over.
Something is interfering with the compass.
Magnetism or some such.
Nothing special about which book.
I have been working on it, like you said.
I counted the spaces.
Why?
In case the ghost
is trying to communicate.
I am trying Morse.
Morse?
Yeah.
Dots and dashes used...
I know what Morse code is, Murph.
I just don't think your bookshelf
is trying to talk to you.
Had to reset every compass clock
and GPS to offset for the anomaly.
Which is?
I don't know.
Maybe the house was built
on magnetic ore,
we would have seen this the first time
we switched on the tractor.
I hear your meeting at the school
didn't go so well.
You heard?
It's like we have forgotten
who we are Donald.
Explorers, pioneers, not caretakers.
When I was a kid...
it felt like they made something
new every day.
Some...
gadget or idea.
Like every day was Christmas.
But six...
billion people...
just try to imagine that.
And every last one of them
trying to have it all.
This world isn't so bad.
And Tom will do just fine.
You are the one who doesn't belong.
Born 40 years too late
or 40 years too early.
My daughter knew it, God bless her.
And your kids know it.
Especially Murph.
Well we used to look
up in the sky and wonder...
at our place in the stars.
Now we just look down...
and worry about our place in the dirt.
Cooper,
you were good at something...
and you never got a chance
to do anything with it.
I am sorry.
You didn't expect this dirt,
that was giving you this food...
to turn on you like that and destroy you.
In April I believe I am right...
Fifteenth of April I think.
This happened about 1:30
when that thing
came off the top of that canyon.
In my day we had real ballplayers.
Who are these bums?
Well in my day people were too busy
fighting over food to even play baseball.
Popcorn at a ballgame is unnatural.
I want a hot dog.
School says you are gonna
follow in my footsteps.
I think that's great.
You think that's great?
You hate farming Dad.
Grandpa said.
Grandpa said?
Listen all that matters
is how you feel about it.
I like what you do.
I like our farm.
You are gonna be great at it.
Let's get out of here.
Alright it's a doozy.
Alright gang let's mask up.
Tom? Murph?
Yeah.
Check?
Murph, Tom, you guys,
shut your windows?
Murph?
The ghost.
Grab your pillow.
You sleep in with Tom.
It's not a ghost.
It's gravity.
I am dropping Tom then heading to town.
You want to clean that up,
when you have finished praying to it?
It's not Morse Murph. It's binary.
Thick is one, thin is zero.
Coordinates.
Nope.
Here we go.
Thirty-three.
That's it.
I can't miss this!
Grandpa will be back
in a couple hours Murph.
But you don't know what you are gonna find.
And that...
is why I can't take you.
Murph?
Grandpa will be home in a while.
Tell him I will call him on the radio.
Jesus.
What are you doing?
Oh you think this is funny?
You would not be here,
if it was not for me.
Make yourself useful.
Murph?
Murph!
I think this is the end of the road.
Didn't you bring the bolt cutters?
That's my girl.
Step away from the fence!
No! No! No!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
I am not armed.
My daughter is in the car.
Don't be afraid.
How did you find this place?
Where is my daughter?
You had the coordinates for this facility
marked on your map.
Where did you get those coordinates?
Where is my daughter?
Don't make me take you down again.
Sit down!
Oh you still think you are a Marine pal?
Marines don't exist anymore.
And I got grunts like you mowing my grass.
Where did you find those coordinates?
But you don't look much like a lawnmower.
Think I will turn you into
an overqualified vacuum cleaner.
No you won't.
TARS,
back down please.
You know you are taking a risk,
using ex-military security.
They are old and their control units are...
unpredictable.
It's what the government could spare.
Who are you?
Dr. Brand.
I knew a Dr. Brand once.
He was a professor.
What makes you think I am not?
Was not near as cute either.
Please Dr. Brand.
I don't have any idea what this is.
Now I am scared for my daughter
and want her by my side.
You give me that I will tell you
anything you want to know.
Get the principals and the girl
in the conference room please.
Your daughter is fine.
Bright kid.
Must have a very smart mother.
It's pretty clear you
don't want any visitors.
So why don't you just let us back up
from your fence
and we will be on our way?
It's not that simple.
Well...
sure it is.
I don't know anything about you.
I don't know anything about this place.
Yes you do.
Dad!
Hello Cooper.
Professor Brand.
Explain to me how you found this facility.
Kind of an accident.
We sort of stumbled upon it.
We were on a salvage run...
You are sitting in the best-kept
secret in the world.
Nobody stumbles in here.
Nobody stumbles out.
Cooper,
please.
Cooperate with these people.
Look.
It's kind of hard to explain.
Now we learned these...
coordinates,
from an anomaly.
What sort of anomaly?
I hesitate to term it supernatural,
but it definitely was not scientific.
You are going to have to be specific
Mr. Cooper.
Right now.
It was gravity.
What sort of gravitational anomaly?
Where was this?
Now I am real happy that you are
excited about gravity bud but..
You are not getting any answers
from us until I get assurances.
Assurances?
Yeah.
Like that we are getting out of here.
And I don't mean in the trunk of some car.
Don't you know who we are Coop?
No professor, I don't.
You know my father Professor Brand.
We are NASA.
NASA?
NASA.
The same NASA, you flew for.
I heard they shut you down sir.
For refusing to drop bombs,
from the stratosphere onto starving people.
When they realized that killing other
people was not a long-term solution
then they needed us back.
In secret.
Why secret?
Because public opinion would not
allow spending on space exploration.
Not while you are struggling
to put food on the table.
Blight.
Wheat,
seven years ago.
Okra, this year.
Now there is just corn.
And we are growing more
than we ever have.
But like the potatoes in Ireland
and the wheat in the Dust Bowl...
the corn...
will die.
Soon.
We will find a way professor.
We always have.
Driven by the unshakable faith,
the Earth is ours.
Not just ours, no.
But it is our home.
Earth's atmosphere,
is 80 percent...
nitrogen. We don't even breathe nitrogen.
Blight does.
And as it thrives,
our air gets less and less oxygen.
The last people to starve
will be the first to suffocate.
And your daughter's generation...
will be the last to survive on Earth.
Murph is feeling a little tired.
I was wondering
if she could take a nap in my office.
Yeah. Thank you.
Ok...
now you need to tell me,
what your plan is to save the world.
We are not meant, to save the world.
We are meant to leave it.
Rangers.
The last components of our
one versatile ship,
in orbit the Endurance.
Our final expedition.
You sent...
people out there
looking for a new home?
The Lazarus missions.
Oh that sounds cheerful.
Lazarus came back from the dead.
Sure but he had to die in the first place.
There is not a planet in our solar system
that could sustain life,
and the nearest star
is over a thousand years away
and that doesn't even qualify as futile.
Where did you send them?
Cooper...
I can't tell you anymore,
unless you agree to pilot this craft.
You are the best pilot we ever had.
I barely left the stratosphere.
This team never left the simulator.
We need a pilot,
and this is the mission
that you were trained for.
Without even knowing it?
An hour ago,
you didn't even know I was alive.
I mean, you-you-you were going anyway.
We had no choice.
But something sent you here.
They chose you.
Who is they?
How long...
would I be gone?
Hard to know.
Years?
I have got kids professor.
Get out there and save them.
Who is they?
We started detecting gravitational
anomalies almost 50 years ago.
Mostly small distortions to our instruments
in the upper atmosphere.
In fact, I believe you
encountered one yourself.
Yeah over the Straights.
My crash. Something...
tripped my fly-by-wire.
Exactly.
But of all these anomalies,
the most significant, is this.
Out near Saturn...
a disturbance of space-time.
Is that a wormhole?
It appeared 48 years ago.
And it leads where?
Another galaxy.
A wormhole is not a naturally
occurring phenomenon.
Someone placed it there.
They?
And whoever they are...
they appear to be looking out for us.
That wormhole,
lets us travel to other stars.
It came along right as we needed it.
They ave put potentially habitable
worlds right within our reach.
Twelve in fact from our initial probes.
You sent probes into that?
We sent people into it.
Ten years ago.
The Lazarus missions.
Twelve possible worlds...
twelve Ranger launches.
Carrying...
the bravest humans,
ever to live.
Led by the remarkable Dr. Mann.
Each person's landing pod had
enough life support for two years.
But they could use hibernation
to stretch that making...
observations on organics
over a decade or more.
Their mission was to assess their world
and if it showed potential...
then they could send out a signal bed
down for the long nap,
wait to be rescued.
And what if the world didn't show promise?
Hence the bravery.
You don't have the resources
to visit all 12.
No.
Data transmission back
through the wormhole is rudimentary.
Simple binary pings on an annual basis
give us some clue as to which worlds
have potential.
And one system shows promise.
And one, that's a bit of a long shot, isn't it?
One system with three potential worlds?
A long shot?
Ok.
So if we find a home...
then what?
That's the long shot.
There is a Plan A,
and a Plan B.
Did you notice anything strange
about the launch chamber?
This entire facility is a centrifuge.
Some kind of vehicle.
A space station?
Both.
Plan A.
How do you get it off the ground?
The first gravitational,
anomalies changed everything.
Suddenly we knew,
that harnessing gravity,
was real.
So, I started working on a theory and...
we started building this station.
But you have not solved it yet.
That's why there is Plan B.
The problem is gravity.
How to get a viable amount
of human life off the planet.
This is one way.
Plan B.
A population bomb.
Over 5000 fertilized eggs,
weighing in at just under 900 kilos.
Well how would you raise them?
With equipment on board
we incubate the first 10.
After that, with surrogacy,
the growth becomes exponential.
Within 30 years we could have
a colony of hundreds.
The real difficulty with colonization
is genetic diversity.
This takes care of that.
But what about the people here?
You just...
you give up on them?
My kids?
That's why Plan A.
Is a lot more fun.
How far have you got?
Almost there.
You are asking me to hang everything...
on an almost?
I am asking you, to trust me.
Find us a new home.
And by the time you return...
I will have solved the problem,
of gravity.
I give you my word.
Go away!
Murph.
Go!
If you are leaving just go.
This world was never enough for you,
was it Coop?
What, because heading out there
is what I feel like I was born to do?
And it excites me?
No that does not make it wrong.
It might.
Don't trust the right thing
done for the wrong reason.
The why of the thing
that's the foundation.
And the foundation is solid.
We farmers we sit here every year
when the rains fail and we say.
Next year.
Well next year ain't gonna
save us nor the one after that.
This world is a treasure Donald but
it's been telling us to leave for a while now.
Mankind was born on Earth
it was never meant to die here.
Tom will be alright but you got
to make things right with Murph.
I will.
Without making promises you
don't know you can keep.
You have to talk to me Murph.
I need to fix this before I go.
Then I will keep it
broken so you have to stay.
After you kids came along your mom she said
something to me I never quite understood.
She said now...
We are just here...
to be memories for our kids.
And I think that now
I understand what she meant.
Once you are a parent you are
the ghost of your children's future.
You said ghosts didn't exist.
That's right Murph.
Murph look at me.
I can't be your ghost right now.
I need to exist.
They chose me.
Murph they chose me.
You saw.
You are the one who led me to them.
That's exactly why you can't go.
I figured out the message.
One word.
Know what it is?
Murph.
Stay.
It says...
Stay Dad.
Murph.
You don't believe me.
Look at the books!
Look at this. It says, Stay.
Why you are not listening!
It says, Stay!
No, I am coming back.
When?
One for you,
one for me.
When I am up there in hypersleep,
or...
or traveling near the speed of light
near a black hole...
time is gonna to change for me.
And it's going to run more slowly.
Now...
when I get back...
we are going to compare.
Time will run differently for us?
Yeah.
By the time I get back we might
even be the same age,
you and me.
What?
Imagine that!
Murph...
You have no idea when you are coming back.
No idea at all!
Murph don't.
Don't make me leave like this.
Come on Murph!
Don't make me leave like this Murph!
Hey...
I love you.
Forever. You hear me?
I love you forever,
and I am coming back.
I am coming back.
How did it go?
Fine.
Just fine.
I love you Tom.
Travel safe?
Yeah.
You look after our place for me alright?
Alright?
Hey can I use your truck
while you are gone?
You mean your truck?
I will make sure they bring it back.
Look after my kids Donald!
Go for main engine start. T-minus 10...
Dad!
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Dad!
Six.
Five.
Main engine start.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Booster ignition and...
All engines look good.
Beginning roll program.
Prepare for stage one separation.
Stage one.
There is Mach 1.
Everybody good?
Plenty of slaves for my robot colony?
They gave him a humor setting
so he would fit in better with his unit.
He thinks it relaxes us.
A giant sarcastic robot.
What a great idea!
I have a cue light I can use
when I am joking if you like.
That had probably help.
Yeah you can use it to find
your way back to the ship,
after I blow you out the airlock.
What's your humor setting TARS?
That's 100 percent.
Let's bring it on down to 75 please.
Stage two separation.
All feeds going manual.
Going manual.
Deactivate probe heater,
one, two and three.
Check.
Taking control.
This is handover to you.
A.D.F. check.
Over.
Pull thrusters back.
Fuel cells, one, two, three.
One hundred percent.
Ex-mites.
It's hard leaving everything.
My kids.
Your father.
We are going to be spending
a lot of time together.
We should learn to talk.
And when not to.
Just being honest.
I don't think you need to be that honest.
Hey TARS, what's your honesty parameter?
Ninety percent.
Ninety percent?
Absolute honesty isn't always
the most diplomatic
nor the safest form of communication
with emotional beings.
Ok.
Ninety percent it is Dr. Brand.
We are coming up on the Endurance.
Twelve minutes out.
Ok. Taking control.
Approaching module port, 500 meters.
It's all you Doyle.
Nice and easy Doyle.
Nice and easy.
I feel good.
Take us home.
Lock.
Target locked?
Target locked.
Well done.
Ok, helmets on.
Good job.
Door is not charging.
Never mind.
Cooper you should have control.
Control here.
Communication with ring module active.
That's initiate.
Are we ready to spin?
Just a sec.
Hello CASE.
Hello TARS.
Alright, we are all set.
Alright, let's do it.
Thirty percent of spin.
One G.
How is gravity treating you back there?
Well.
Romilly? Hey, you ok?
Yeah.
You alright?
Yeah, I just need a minute.
Ok, I think we have some Dramamine
in the hab pod I am just gonna get that
or maybe in the cryo-beds.
I will just be a sec.
Hey Brand?
Yeah?
Bring a lot.
Amelia,
be safe.
Give my regards to Dr. Mann.
I will Dad.
It looks good for your trajectory.
We have calculated two years,
to Saturn.
That's a lot of Dramamine.
Look after my family will you please sir?
We will be waiting for you
when you get back.
A little older, a little wiser,
but happy to see you.
Do not go gentle
into that good night,
Old age should burn
and rave at close of day:
Rage,
rage
against the dying of the light.
Though wise men at their end
know dark is right,
Because their words
had forked no lightning they.
Do not
go gentle into that good night.
Rage,
rage
against the dying of the light.
You good?
Yeah.
Ok, thank you.
Here. Pills.
So alone.
We have each other.
Dr. Mann had it worse.
No, I mean them.
It's a perfect planet and we are not
gonna find another one like her.
No, it's not like...
looking for a new condo.
The human race is going to be...
adrift...
desperate for a rock it can cling
to while it catches its breath.
We need to find that rock.
And our three prospects are at the edge
of what might sustain human life.
Laura Miller's planet,
is first.
Laura started our biology program and...
Wolf Edmunds is here.
Tell me about Edmunds.
Wolf is a particle physicist.
None of them had families?
No. No attachments.
My father insisted.
They all knew the odds against ever
seeing another human being again.
I am hoping we can surprise
at least three of them.
How about Mann?
Dr. Mann?
He is remarkable. He is the best of us.
He inspired 11 people to follow him
on the loneliest journey in human history.
Scientists, explorers.
That's what I love.
You know out there we face great odds.
Death but...
not evil.
You don't think nature can be evil?
No.
Formidable. Frightening. But...
no, not evil.
Is a lion,
evil because it rips a gazelle to shreds?
Just what we take with us then.
Yeah.
This crew represents the best of humanity.
Even me?
You know what? We agreed 90 percent.
There you go.
Don't stay up.
I will be there in a minute.
Hold on, just remember Coop,
you are literally wasting your breath.
Hey TARS?
Let's go over that trajectory one more time.
Eight months to Mars.
Counter-orbital slingshot around.
Fourteen months to Saturn.
Nothing is changed on that.
Just let me ask you something.
Dr. Brand and Edmunds...
Why are you whispering?
They can't hear you.
Dr. Brand and Edmunds.
They close?
I would not know.
Is that 90 percent would not know
or 10 percent would not know?
I also have a discretion setting Cooper.
But not a poker face Slick.
Hey guys.
Dad is about to go down for the long nap.
So I wanted to give you an update.
The Earth looks amazing from here.
You can't see any of the dust.
I really hope you guys are doing great.
I know you will get this message.
Professor Brand,
assured me that he will get it to you.
Know that I love you.
Is it him?
I don't think so Murph.
You must be Donald.
Hello Murph.
Why are you in my dad's truck?
He wanted me to bring it for your brother.
He sent you a message.
She is pretty upset with him for leaving.
If you record any messages I can
get them to transmit it to Cooper.
Murph,
is a bright spark.
Maybe,
I should fan the flame.
She is already making
fools of her teachers.
So maybe she should come
and make a fool out of you.
So where are they?
Heading for Mars.
The next time you hear from Cooper,
they will be coming up on Saturn.
As far as school goes
the administration wants me to repeat
Plant Pathology. Which sucks.
But,
they said I could start
Advanced Agriculture a year early.
Alright, I got to go Dad.
Hope you are safe up there.
Sorry Coop.
I asked Murph to say hi...
but she is as stubborn as her old man.
I will try again next time.
You alright Rom?
This gets to me Cooper.
This. This.
Millimeters of aluminum
that's it and then nothing...
out there for millions of miles,
won't kill us in seconds.
You know that some of the finest
solo yachtsmen in the world
don't know how to swim?
They don't know how.
And if they go overboard
psst they are done.
We are explorers Rom.
This is our boat.
Here.
This is from the relay probe?
It was in orbit around the wormhole.
This is the wormhole,
and every time we come around...
we would receive images from the other
side of the foreign galaxy.
Oh yeah.
Like swinging a periscope around.
Exactly.
So we got a pretty good idea
what we are gonna find on the other side?
Navigationally.
Guys? Looks like we will be approaching
the wormhole in about three hours.
Hey Coop?
Can we stop the spinning?
Why?
Because we are close enough to see it now?
Alright.
Thanks.
There that's... That's it!
That's the wormhole!
Say it don't spray it Rom.
It's a sphere.
Of course it is. What you...
You thought it would just be a hole?
No it's just that all the illustrations
I have ever seen they...
The illustrations they are
trying to show you how it works.
So they say you want to go from here...
to there.
But it's too far right?
So a wormhole bends space like this,
so you can take a shortcut through...
a higher dimension.
Ok so...
to show that they ave turned
three-dimensional space
into two dimensions which turns
a wormhole into two dimensions...
a circle.
What's a circle in three dimensions?
A sphere.
Exactly.
A spherical hole.
But who put it there?
Who do we have to thank?
I am not thanking anybody until we get
out of here in one piece Rom.
Any trick to this Doyle?
No one knows.
The others made it right?
At least some of them.
Everybody ready to say goodbye
to our solar system?
To our galaxy.
Here we go.
The controls won't work here.
We are passing through the bulk.
It's space beyond our three dimensions.
All you can do is record and observe.
What is that?
I think it's them.
Distorting space-time.
Don't! Don't!
What was that?
The first handshake.
We are...
We are here.
So the lost communications came through.
How?
The relay on this side cached them.
So years of basic data. No real surprises.
Miller's site has kept pinging
thumbs up as has Dr. Mann's.
Edmunds' went down three years ago.
Transmitter failure?
Maybe.
He was sending the thumbs
up right until it went dark.
But Miller is still looks good though right?
Because she is coming up fast.
With one complication.
The planet is much closer
to Gargantua than we thought.
Gargantua?
It's what we are calling the black hole.
Miller's and Dr. Mann's planets
both orbit it.
And Miller's is on the horizon?
As a basketball around a hoop.
Landing there takes us dangerously close.
And a black hole that big has
a huge gravitational pull.
Look I could swing around that neutron
star to decelerate.
No it's not that. It's time.
The gravity on that planet will slow
our clock compared to Earth...
is drastically.
How bad?
Every hour we spend
on that planet will be...
seven years back on Earth.
Jesus.
Well that's relativity folks.
Well we can't just drop
down there without...
Cooper, we have a mission.
Yeah Doyle we have a mission
and our mission Plan A is...
to find a planet that can habitate the
people that are living on Earth right now.
You can't just think about your family.
Now you have to think bigger than that alright?
I am thinking about my family
and millions of other families ok?
Plan A does not work,
if the people on Earth
are dead by the time we pull it off.
No. It doesn't.
That's why there is a Plan B.
Ok.
Cooper is right.
We need to think about time as a resource
just like oxygen and food.
Going down there is going to cost us.
Alright look.
Dr. Mann's data is promising.
Right? But it's going
to take us months to get there.
And Edmunds' it's even further.
Now Miller has not sent much
but what she has is very promising.
It's water it's organics...
You don't find that every day.
No you don't.
And just think about the resources
including time that would be
spent trying to get back here.
Romilly.
Yeah?
How far off from Miller's planet do we have
to be,
to stay out of the time shift?
Well just back from the cusp.
Alright which is here,
just outside of Miller's planet.
Right.
Ok.
Here is Gargantua.
Here is Miller's planet.
Instead of taking the Endurance
into orbit around Miller's planet
which would conserve fuel
but we would lose a lot of time...
what if we...
take a wider
orbit around Gargantua
parallel with Miller's planet outside
of this time shift to here?
Then we take the Ranger down
we get Miller,
we get her samples.
We come back we analyze
we debrief. We are in we are out.
We lose a little fuel
but we save a whole lot of time.
That will work.
That's good.
There is not gonna be time for monkey
business or chit-chat down there.
TARS you should definitely stay here.
CASE, you are with me.
Anyone else can stay.
If we are talking about a couple of years,
I could use the time to research gravity.
Observations from the wormhole
that's gold to Professor Brand.
TARS factor an orbit of Gargantua.
Conserve fuel, minimize thrusting,
but make sure we stay
in range of Miller's planet.
You got it?
I would not leave you behind...
Dr. Brand.
You ready CASE?
Yup.
You don't say much do you?
TARS talks plenty for both of us.
Detach.
Romilly are you reading these forces?
It's unbelievable.
A literal heart of darkness.
If we could just see
the collapsed star inside...
the singularity,
yeah we would solve gravity.
And we can't get anything from it?
Nothing escapes that horizon.
Not even light.
The answer is there, just no way to see it.
There is Miller's planet.
Goodbye Ranger.
This is fast for atmospheric entry.
Should we use the thrusters to slow?
No.
I am gonna use the Ranger's aerodynamics
to save some fuel.
Air brake?
We want to get down fast, don't we?
Actually we want to get
there in one piece.
Hang on.
Brand, Doyle, get ready.
We should ease!
Hands where I can see them CASE.
It's the only time I ever went down was when
a machine was easing at the wrong time.
A little caution...
Can get you killed just like reckless driving.
Cooper it's too damn fast!
I got this.
Should I disable the feedback?
No.
I need to feel the air.
Here we go.
It's just water!
The stuff of life.
Twelve hundred meters.
Do we have a fix on the beacon?
Got it!
Can you maneuver?
I will need to shave some speed.
I am gonna spiral down on top of it.
Everybody hang on!
Seven hundred.
On my cue CASE. On my cue.
Five hundred meters.
Fire!
Very graceful.
No.
But very...
efficient.
What are you waiting for?
Let's go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Seven years per hour here.
Let's make it count!
This way.
About 200 meters.
The gravity is punishing.
Been floating through space too long?
One hundred and thirty percent
Earth gravity.
Come on. Come on.
There is nothing here.
Should be right here.
If the...
signal is coming from here, then...
Her beacon.
Wreckage.
Where is the rest?
Towards the mountains!
Those are not mountains.
They are waves.
Oh shit. Oh shit.
Shit.
Now that one is moving away from us.
We need the recorder.
Brand, Doyle, back to the Ranger now!
We are not leaving without her data.
Get back here now!
We do not have time!
The second wave is coming!
We are in the middle of a swell.
No I got it.
Get your ass back to the Ranger now!
Brand get back here now!
No Cooper go. Cooper go.
I can't make it.
Go!
CASE go get her.
Get up. Get up Brand!
Go, go! Go!
I am not gonna make it!
Yes you are. Yes you are!
Come on CASE has her. CASE has her!
Get back here Doyle!
Come on!
Get to the hatch!
Go, go! Go!
Shit.
Manually overriding inside hatch!
Cooper! Wait!
The engines are flooded!
I am gonna have to shut her down.
Holy shit.
Hang on!
CASE what's the problem?
Too waterlogged. Let it drain.
Goddamn it!
I told you to leave me!
And I told you
Why didn't you leave me?
To get your ass back here!
The difference is one of us
was thinking about the mission!
Cooper you were
thinking about getting home.
I was trying to do the right thing!
Can you tell that to Doyle?
CASE how much time?
Forty-five to an hour.
The stuff of life?
What's this gonna cost us Brand?
A lot.
Decades.
What happened to Miller?
Judging by...
the wreckage she was,
broken up by a wave soon after impact.
How is the wreckage stayed together
after all these years?
Because of the time slippage.
On this planet's time she...
just landed hours ago, she...
She probably just died minutes ago.
The data Doyle received was just
the initial status, echoing endlessly.
Oh we are not prepared for this.
You eggheads have the survival
skills of a Boy Scout troop.
Well we got this far on our brains.
Farther than any human in history.
Well not far enough!
And now we are stuck here,
untill there won't be
anyone left on Earth to save.
I am counting every minute
same as you Cooper.
Is there any possibility,
I don't know some...
some kind of a way we can maybe
all jump...
in a black hole.
Gain back the years?
Don't shake your head at me.
Time is relative, ok?
It can stretch and it can squeeze but...
it can't run backwards.
It just can't.
The only thing that can move,
across dimensions like time,
is gravity.
Ok.
The beings that led us here,
they communicate...
through gravity right?
Yes.
Could they be talking
to us from the future?
Maybe.
Ok. If they can...
They...
are beings of five dimensions.
To them time might be
another physical dimension.
To them...
the past might be a canyon that they can
climb into and the future...
a mountain they can climb up.
But to us...
it's not ok?
Look Cooper I screwed up.
I am sorry.
But you knew about relativity.
Brand...
My daughter was 10 years old.
I could not teach her
Einstein's theories before I left.
Could not you have told her you
were going to save the world?
No.
When you become a parent,
one thing becomes really clear.
And that is that you want to make
sure your children feel safe.
And it rules out telling a 10-year-old,
that the world is ended.
Cooper?
How long for the engines CASE?
A minute or two.
But we don't have it.
Helmets on!
Brand co-pilot you are up.
CASE blow the cabin oxygen
through the main thrusters!
We are gonna spark it.
Roger that.
Locked.
Depressurizing.
Engines up!
Hello Rom.
I have waited years.
How? How many years?
By now it must be...
Twenty-three years...
four months eight days.
Doyle?
I thought I was prepared.
I knew the theory.
Reality is different.
And Miller?
There is nothing here for us.
Why didn't you sleep?
Oh I had a couple of stretches.
But I stopped believing
you were coming back.
And something seemed wrong
about dreaming my life away.
I learned what I could
from the black hole...
but I could not send
anything to your father.
We have been receiving
but nothing gets out.
Is he alive?
Oh yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah.
We have got years of messages stored.
Cooper.
Messages span 23 years.
Play it from the beginning.
Hey Dad.
Checking in. Saying hi.
Finished second in school.
Miss Kurling is still giving me C's though.
Pulled me down but second is not bad.
Grandpa attended the ceremony.
I met another girl Dad.
I...
I really think this is the one.
Name is Lois.
That's her right there.
Murphy stole Grandpa's car.
She crashed it.
She is ok though.
Hey Dad.
Look at this!
You are a grandpa.
His name is Jesse.
I kind of wanted to call him Coop
but Lois says...
maybe next time.
Donald says he is already
earned the great part so...
we just leave it at that.
Oh dear. Oh dear.
Say Bye-bye Grandpa.
Bye-bye Grandpa. Ok.
Sorry it's been a while.
Just...
what with Jesse and all.
Grandpa died last week.
We buried him out in the back
forty next to Mom and...
Jesse.
Which is where we would have
buried you if you would ever...
come back.
Murph was there at the funeral.
We don't see her that much
but she came for that.
You are not listening to this I know that.
All these messages are just like...
drifting...
out there in the darkness.
Lois says that...
I have to...
let you go.
And...
so...
I guess...
I am letting you go.
I don't know wherever you are Dad but...
I hope that you are at peace and...
Goodbye.
Hey Dad.
Hey Murph.
You son of a bitch.
I never made one of these when
you were still responding...
because I was so mad at you for leaving.
And then when you went quiet it...
seemed like I should live
with that decision. And I have.
But today is my birthday.
And it's a special one
because you told me...
You once told me that when you came
back we might be the same age.
And today I am the age
you were when you left.
So it would be a real good
time for you to come back.
I didn't mean to intrude.
It's just that I have never
seen you in here before.
I have never been in here before.
I talk to Amelia,
all the time.
It helps.
I am glad you have started.
I have not.
I...
just had something I needed to get out.
I know they are still out there.
I know.
There are so many reasons
their communications,
might not be getting through.
I know professor.
I am not sure,
what I am more afraid of.
Them never coming back or...
coming back...
to find we have failed.
Then let's succeed.
So...
back, to the fourth iteration.
Let's run it through some new fields.
With respect professor,
we have tried that hundreds of times.
It only has to work once...
Murph.
Every rivet, that they strike,
could have been a bullet.
We have done well for the world here
whether or not, we crack the equation,
before I kick the bucket.
Don't be morbid professor.
I am not afraid of death.
I am an old physicist.
I am afraid of time.
Time.
You are afraid of time.
Figures we have been trying
to solve the equation
without changing the underlying
assumption about time.
And?
And that means...
each iteration is an attempt to...
prove its own proof.
It's...
recursive it's nonsensical.
Are you calling my life's work,
nonsense Murph?
No I am saying
that you have been trying to...
finish it with one arm, no with...
both arms tied behind your back.
And I don't understand why.
I am an old man Murph.
Can we take this point up at another time?
I want to talk to my daughter.
Stepping out into the universe...
we must confront the reality
of interstellar travel.
We must reach,
far beyond our own lifespans.
We must think not,
as individuals,
but as a species.
Do not go gentle into that good night.
TARS kept the Endurance,
right where we needed her.
But the trip took years
longer than we anticipated.
We no longer have the fuel
to visit both prospects so...
we have to choose.
But how?
They are both promising.
Edmunds' data is better but Dr. Mann
is the one still transmitting so...
We have no reason to suspect
Edmunds' data would have soured.
His world has key elements
to sustain human life.
As does Dr. Mann's.
Cooper this is my field.
And...
I really believe Edmunds'
is the better prospect.
Why?
Gargantua, that's why.
Look at Miller's planet.
Hydrocarbons organics yes...
but no life.
Sterile.
We will find the same thing on Mann's.
Because of the black hole?
Murphy's Law.
Whatever can happen will happen.
Accident is the first
building block of evolution.
But when you are orbiting a black
hole not enough can happen.
It sucks in asteroids and comets,
other events which would
otherwise reach you.
We need to go further afield.
You once said that Dr. Mann...
was the best of us.
He is remarkable.
We are only here because of him.
And yet yet here he is.
He is on the ground,
and he is sending a very unambiguous
message telling us...
to come to his planet.
Granted but...
Edmunds' data,
is more promising.
We should vote.
Well if we are going to vote
there is something you should know.
Brand?
He has a right to know.
That has nothing to do with it.
What does?
She is in love with Wolf Edmunds.
Is that true?
Yes.
And that makes me want to follow my heart.
But maybe we have spent too long trying
to figure all this out with theory.
You are a scientist Brand.
So listen to me...
when I say that...
love isn't something we invented. It's...
observable powerful.
It has to mean something.
Love has meaning yes.
Social utility, social bonding,
child rearing.
We love people who have died.
Where is the social utility in that?
None.
Maybe it means something
more something we can't...
yet...
understand.
Maybe it's...
some evidence, some...
artifact of,
a higher dimension that
we can't consciously perceive.
I am...
drawn across the universe to someone
I have not seen in a decade...
who I know...
is probably dead.
Love, is the one thing we are
capable of perceiving,
that transcends dimensions
of time and space.
Maybe we should trust that
even if we can't understand it yet.
Alright Cooper...
yes...
the tiniest possibility of seeing
Wolf again excites me.
That doesn't mean I am wrong.
Honestly Amelia...
it might.
TARS chart a course for Dr. Mann's.
We will lose about a third again.
But next year...
Next year I am gonna work
Nelson's farm and we will make it up.
What happened to Nelson?
Murph have you eaten enough
or would you like some more soufflé?
Oh no.
I am full thanks.
It was delicious.
Coop finish your fritter please.
Will you spend the night?
Your room is exactly as you left it.
It's ready.
I need to get back.
My sewing machine
is in there but there is plenty...
I need to...
Too many memories.
We might have something for that.
Hey Coop.
The dust.
Lois, I have a friend who...
could look at his lungs.
Amelia I am sorry.
You were just being objective.
Unless you are punishing me,
for screwing up on Miller's planet.
No this was not a personal decision.
Well.
If you are wrong you will have
a very personal decision to make.
Your fuel calculations
are based on a return journey.
Strike out on Mann's planet and we will have
to decide whether to return home...
or push on to Edmunds' with Plan B.
Starting a colony,
could save us from extinction.
You might have to decide
between seeing your children again...
and the future of the human race.
I trust you will be as objective then.
He has been asking
for you since he came to.
We were trying to reach you.
Murph.
I am here professor.
I let you all down.
No you got us so far.
Real close.
I will finish what you started.
Good, good Murph.
You had faith...
all those...
all those years.
I...
I asked you to have faith.
I wanted you to believe...
that your father...
would come back.
I do professor.
Forgive me Murph.
There is nothing to forgive.
I...
I lied Murph.
I lied to you.
There was no need for him...
To come back.
There is...
no way to help us.
But Plan A...
All this.
All these people.
And the equation.
Did my father know?
Did he leave me?
Do...
not...
go...
gentle...
No.
No!
You can't leave.
You... No.
Dr. Brand I am sorry to tell you
that your father died today.
He had no pain.
He was at peace.
I am very sorry for your loss.
Brand did you know?
He told you right?
You knew.
This was all a sham.
You left us here.
To suffocate.
To starve.
Frozen cloud.
It's ok.
Pray you never learn...
just how good it can be,
to see another face.
I had not a lot of hope to begin with but...
after so long I had none.
My supplies were completely exhausted.
The last time I went to sleep
I didn't even set a waking date.
You have literally
raised me from the dead.
Lazarus.
What about the others?
I am afraid you are it sir.
So far...
surely.
No our present situation,
is that there is very little chance
of rescuing any others.
Dr. Mann.
Dr. Mann?
Tell us about your world.
Our world we hope.
Our world...
is cold...
stark...
but undeniably beautiful.
The days are 67 hours long, cold.
The nights are...
67 far colder hours.
The gravity is a very,
very pleasant 80 percent of the Earth's.
Now up here where I landed
the water is...
alkali...
and the air has too much ammonia in it
to breathe for more
than just a few minutes but...
down at the surface,
and there is a surface...
the chlorine dissipates.
The ammonia gives way to crystalline
hydrocarbons,
and breathable air.
To organics.
Possibly even to life.
We might be sharing this world.
These readings are from the surface?
Over the years,
I have dropped various probes.
How far have you explored?
I have mounted several major expeditions.
But with oxygen in limited supply KIPP
there really did most of the legwork.
What went wrong with him sir?
Degeneration.
He misidentified the first organics
we found as ammonia crystals.
We struggled on for a time but...
ultimately I decommissioned him and...
used his power source
to keep the mission going.
I thought I was alone
before I shut him down.
Would you like me to look at him?
No. No. He needs a human touch.
Dr. Brand, CASE is relaying a message
for you from the comm station.
Ok. Be right there. Excuse me.
Dr. Brand I am sorry to tell you
that your father died today.
He had no pain.
He was at peace.
I am sorry for your loss.
Is that Murph?
She is...
She is grown.
Brand did you know?
He told you right?
You knew.
This was all a sham.
You left us here.
To suffocate.
To starve.
Did my father know too?
Dad?
I just want to know...
if you left me here to die.
I just have to know.
Cooper my...
My father dedicated...
his whole life,
to Plan A. I have...
no idea what she is talking about.
I do.
He never even hoped to get
the people off the Earth?
No.
But...
But he has been trying to solve
the gravity equation for 40 years.
Amelia your father solved
his equation before I even left.
Then why would not he use it?
The equation could not reconcile relativity
with quantum mechanics.
You need more.
More?
More what?
More data.
You need to see into a black hole.
The laws of nature prohibit
a naked singularity.
Romilly is that true?
If a black hole is an oyster then
the singularity is the pearl inside.
The gravity is so strong, it's always
hidden in darkness behind the horizon.
That's why we call it a black hole.
Ok but...
if we see beyond the horizon.
We can't Coop.
There are some things
that are not meant to be known.
Your father had to find another way,
to save the human race from extinction.
Plan B. A colony.
Why not tell people?
Why keep building those stations?
Because he knew how hard it would be
to get people to work together,
to save the species instead of themselves.
Or their children.
Bullshit.
You never would have come here unless
you believed you were gonna save them.
Evolution has yet to transcend
that simple barrier.
We can care deeply, selflessly
about those we know...
but that empathy rarely extends
beyond our line of sight.
But the lie.
That monstrous lie?
Unforgivable.
And he knew that.
He was prepared to destroy
his own humanity,
in order to save the species.
He made an incredible sacrifice.
No.
An incredible sacrifice is being made,
by the people on Earth,
who are gonna die!
Because in his fucking arrogance...
he declared their case hopeless.
I am sorry Cooper...
their case is hopeless.
No.
We are the future.
Cooper what can I do?
Let me go home.
You are absolutely positive?
His solution was correct.
He would had it for years.
It's worthless?
It's half the answer.
Ok.
How do you find the other half?
Out there? A black hole.
But stuck down here on Earth?
Yeah?
I am not sure you can.
God they just pack up and leave.
What are they hoping to find?
Survival.
Damn it.
Murph...
don't...
Don't people have a right to know?
Panic won't help.
We just have to keep
working same as ever.
Yeah but...
isn't that exactly what Professor Brand
was manipulating us to do?
Brand gave up on us.
I am still trying to solve this.
So...
do you have an idea?
A feeling.
I told you about my ghost.
My dad thought I called it a ghost...
because I was scared of it.
But I was never scared of it.
I called it a ghost because it felt...
It felt like a person.
It was trying to tell me something.
If there is an answer here on Earth,
it's back there...
somehow in that room.
So I have to find it.
We are running out of time.
What about auxiliary oxygen scrubbers?
No they can stay CASE.
I will be sleeping most of the way anyway.
Hey Coop?
Yeah?
I have a suggestion
for your return journey.
Yeah what's that?
Have one last crack at the black hole.
I am going home Rom.
Yeah I know.
This isn't going to cost you any time.
There is a chance for the people on Earth.
Talk to me.
Gargantua is an older spinning black hole.
It's what we call a...
a gentle singularity.
Gentle?
They are hardly gentle.
But the tidal gravity is so quick that...
something crossing the horizon fast,
might survive.
A probe say.
What happens after it crosses?
After the horizon is a complete mystery.
So...
what's to say there isn't
some way that the probe
can glimpse the singularity
and relay the quantum data?
If he is equipped to transmit
every form of energy that can pulse.
Just when did this probe
become a he professor?
TARS is the obvious candidate.
I have already told him what to look for.
I will need the old optical
transmitter off KIPP Cooper.
You would do this for us?
Before you get all teary try to remember
that as a robot,
I have to do anything you say.
Your cue light is broken.
I am not joking.
I will need TARS to remove and adapt
some components from KIPP.
I don't want to disturb
his archival functions.
I will supervise.
Alright.
Dr. Mann we need to find
three secure sites.
One for Brand's lab, two for habitat.
Once those modules have landed
you don't want to move them.
Well I can take you to the probe sites
but I don't think this...
these conditions are gonna hold.
I think we should wait.
CASE is headed back down with the rest
of the distillery equipment.
I would really like to secure
those sites by nightfall.
Well...
these squalls do usually blow over.
Ok then.
But you are gonna need a long range transmitter.
Got it.
Are you charged?
Yeah.
Follow me.
TARS.
72 hours yeah?
Roger that Cooper.
Brand told me why you feel
you have to go back.
But I would be remiss if I didn't
at least mention that...
a mission such as ours could certainly use...
an extra engineer.
You better slow down Turbo.
Safety first CASE remember.
Safety first Cooper.
I have to tell you Dr. Mann
I am honored to be a part of this.
But once we set up base camp,
and secure those modules,
my work is done here.
I am going home.
You have attachments.
But even without a family I can...
promise you that...
that yearning to be with other people...
is powerful.
That emotion is...
at the foundation...
of what makes us human.
It's not to be taken lightly.
How long have you had that cough?
A while.
Mom lets me play in here.
I don't touch your stuff.
Just take this gently.
You know why we could not just send machines
on these missions don't you Cooper?
A machine doesn't improvise well,
because you can't program a fear of death.
Our survival instinct is our single greatest...
source of inspiration.
Take you for example.
A father...
with a survival instinct,
that extends to your kids.
What does research tell us,
is the last thing you are going
to see before you die?
Your children.
Their faces.
At the moment of death
your mind is gonna push
a little bit harder to survive.
For them.
Deep breath.
Hey. I bet you are Coop.
Why don't you have a seat here for me?
It's bad. They cannot stay here.
Ok?
Yeah.
TARS what's taking so long?
Professor I am having
trouble completing the boot up.
I don't understand.
It's funny.
When I left Earth...
I thought I was prepared to die.
The truth is...
I never really...
considered the possibility
that my planet was not the one.
Nothing worked out the way
it was supposed to.
Let's go.
Alright hey buddy why don't you
give me a big deep breath.
What is this?
What are you doing?
I am sorry!
I can't let you leave with that ship.
We are gonna need it
to complete the mission...
once the others,
realize what this place isn't.
We cannot survive here.
I am sorry!
They can't stay here anymore.
You have to leave right now.
Ok let me let me make something
abundantly clear.
You have a responsibility...
Oh! Jesus!
Coop get her stuff. She is going home.
Dad didn't raise you to be this dumb Tom!
Dad didn't raise me, Grandpa did.
And he is buried out back
with Mom and Jesse.
You faked, all the data?
Yes.
There is no surface?
No.
I tried to do my duty Cooper...
but I knew...
the day that I arrived here that...
this place had nothing.
And I resisted,
the temptation for years...
but...
I knew that...
if I just pressed that...
button then...
somebody would come and save me.
You fucking coward.
Yes.
Listen if you are not going to go
let your family go.
Just let save your family.
And go live underground...
with you?
Pray that Daddy comes to save us?
Dad's not coming back.
He never was coming back.
It's up to me.
You are gonna save everybody?
Because Dad could not do it.
Dad didn't even try!
Dad just abandoned us!
He left us here to die.
Nobody is going with you.
You gonna wait for your next kid to die?
Get out.
And don't come back.
You can keep my stuff.
Stop it!
No. No!
Dr. Mann there is a 50-50 chance
you are gonna kill yourself!
Those are the best odds I have had in years.
Don't judge me Cooper.
You were never tested like I was.
Few men have been.
You tried your best Murph.
You are feeling it are not you?
The survival instinct.
That's what drove me.
It's what drives all of us.
And it's what's gonna save us.
Because I want to save all of us.
For you Cooper.
I am sorry I can't...
I can't watch you go through this.
I am sorry.
I thought I could,
but I can't.
I am here. I am here for you.
Just listen to my voice Cooper.
I am right here.
You are not alone.
Do you see your children?
It's ok.
They are right there with you.
Did Professor Brand tell you
that poem before you left?
Do you remember?
Do not go gentle...
into that good night,
Old age
should burn
and rave at close of day;
Rage,
rage against the dying of the light.
Brand! Help!
Help! Help! Help..
Cooper?
CASE!
No air.
Ammonia.
Cooper. Cooper we are coming!
CASE!
I have a fix.
Go! Go go go!
And away!
Cooper we are coming.
Hang in there. Don't talk.
Try to breathe as little as possible.
We are almost there.
There is a security lockout sir.
It requires a person to access function.
It's all yours sir.
Try not to breathe.
We are coming. We are coming...
coming right now.
CASE come on!
We got to go faster! We got to go faster!
Faster! Faster! Faster!
Cooper.
Hang in there. Come on.
I see him. I see him. I see him!
CASE bank! Bank right!
Cooper! Cooper!
I am here!
This data makes no sense.
I am sorry.
What?
Mann was lying!
Go. Go.
Romilly.
Romilly!
Romilly! Do you read me Romilly?
Step back professor! Step back!
Romilly...
Romilly, do you read me?
Keep watch!
Lois?
What happened to caution CASE?
Safety first Cooper.
Romilly? Romilly do you read me?
This is Brand.
Romilly?
Dr. Brand.
Cooper.
There is been an explosion.
Dr. Mann's compound.
TARS. TARS 10 o'clock!
Let me know when TARS is aboard.
Romilly did not survive.
I could not save him.
TARS is in.
I will take her from here.
Do we have a fix on the Ranger?
He is pushing into orbit!
If he takes control of that ship we are dead.
He did maroon us?
No he is marooning us.
I will meet you guys downstairs.
Go wait by the car.
Come on! Give me your bag.
Get in the backseat.
Get in the backseat now!
Dr. Mann, please respond.
Dr. Mann, please respond!
He doesn't know
the Endurance docking procedure.
The autopilot does.
Not since TARS disabled it.
Nice.
What's your trust setting TARS?
Lower than yours apparently.
Do not attempt docking.
I repeat. Do not attempt docking.
Please res...
Auto-docking sequence withheld.
Override.
Unauthorized.
Do not attempt docking.
I repeat do not attempt docking.
Please resp...
Damm.
Moving slowly toward the Endurance.
Imperfect contact.
Override.
Hatch lockout.
Is he locked on yet?
Imperfectly.
Dr. Mann. Do not...
Hatch lockout disengaged.
Dr. Mann do not...
I repeat. Do not open the hatch.
If you open the hatch
the airlock will depressurize.
What happens if he blows the airlock?
Nothing good.
Ok pull back pull back! Retro thrusters
everything we have got CASE!
Thrusters are full!
Back!
CASE relay my transmission
to the on board computer
and have it rebroadcast as emergency P.A.
Dr. Mann...
I repeat. Do not open the inner hatch.
I repeat. Do not open...
Brand?
I don't know what he said to you.
But I am taking command of the Endurance.
And then we can talk
about completing the mission.
Dr. Mann.
I is ten to me.
This is not about my life.
Or Cooper's life.
This is about all mankind.
There is a moment...
It is not...
Oh my God.
Cooper, there is no point using your fuel to chase...
Analyze the Endurance's spin.
Cooper what are you doing?
Docking.
Endurance rotation is 6768 RPM.
Ok get ready to match our spin
with the retro thrusters.
It's not possible.
No...
it's necessary.
Endurance is hitting stratosphere!
She is got no heat shield.
CASE you ready?
Ready.
Cooper!
This is no time for caution.
CASE if I black out you take the stick.
TARS get ready to engage
the docking mechanism.
Endurance is starting to heat.
Twenty feet out.
I need three degrees starboard Cooper.
Ten feet out.
Cooper we are lined up.
Lined up.
Initiating spin!
Come on TARS.
Come on TARS!
We are locked Cooper.
Locked. Easing up!
Easy.
Retro thrusters!
Main engines on.
Pushing out of orbit.
Come on baby.
Killing main engines!
Ok we are out of orbit.
Ok.
And for our next trick!
It will have to be good.
We are heading into Gargantua's pull.
Oh shit.
CASE take the stick.
Roger that.
Cooper,
we are slipping towards Gargantua.
Shall I use main engines?
No.
We got to let her slide as far as we can.
Give it to me.
There is good news
there is bad news Cooper.
Yeah I have heard that one TARS.
Give it to me straight.
The backup generator kicked in so
the system is stable.
They are all good.
Good.
Ok.
The navigational hub has
been completely destroyed.
We don't have enough life support
to make it back to Earth but...
I think we can scratch our way
to Edmunds' planet.
What about fuel?
Not enough.
But I have a plan.
We let... Gargantua...
pull us down close to her horizon.
Then a powered slingshot around
launching us towards Edmunds' planet.
Manually?
That's what I am here for.
I am gonna take us just
inside the critical orbit.
What about the time slippage?
Neither one of us has time to worry
about relativity right now Dr. Brand.
I am sorry Cooper.
Once we have gathered
enough speed around Gargantua...
we use Lander 1...
and Ranger 2 as rocket boosters to...
push us out of the black hole's gravity.
The Lander's linkages
have been destroyed...
so we will have to control manually.
Once Lander 1 is spent TARS will detach...
And get sucked right into that black hole.
Why does TARS have to detach?
Well we have to shed the weight
to escape the gravity.
Newton's third law.
The only way humans have ever
figured out of getting somewhere
is to leave something behind.
Cooper,
you can't ask TARS to do this for us.
He is a robot.
So you don't have
to ask him to do anything.
Cooper you asshole!
Sorry you broke up a little bit there.
It's what we intended Dr. Brand.
It's our only chance
to save people on Earth.
If I can find a way to transmit
the quantum data I will find in there
they might still make it.
Let's just hope there is still
someone there to save.
Maximum velocity achieved.
Prepare to fire escape thrusters.
Ready?
Ready.
Main engine ignition in Three.
Two.
One.
Mark.
Come on baby.
Lander 1 engines on my mark.
Three.
Two.
One.
Mark.
Ranger 2 engines on my mark.
Three.
Two.
One.
Mark.
Fire!
This little maneuver
is gonna cost us 51 years!
You don't sound so bad for pushing 120!
Lander 1.
Prepare to detach.
On my mark.
Three.
Two.
One.
Mark.
Detach!
Goodbye TARS.
Goodbye Dr. Brand.
See you on the other side Coop.
See you there Slick!
Ok CASE.
Nice reckless flying!
Learned from the master.
Ranger 2.
Prepare to detach.
What?
No! No!
Cooper! What are you doing?
Newton's third law.
You got to leave something behind.
You told me we had
enough resources for both of us.
We agreed Amelia...
90 percent.
Don't.
Detach.
Ok.
I am nosing down.
Approaching the event horizon.
Portside dipping down beneath it...
to go through it.
Heading towards,
blackness.
I have a visual of the event.
It's all black.
TARS do you read me?
It's all blackness.
TARS! Do you read me? Over.
Ok.
Screen is...
getting interference.
Losing control of the stick.
I got flashes.
Flashes of lightness and blackness.
The turbulence in the gravity,
is increasing.
The computers are going down.
Gravitational pull.
I am losing control of the stick.
Murph? Murph come on!
Eject. Eject.
Eject.
Murph.
Murph! Murph! Murph!
Murph!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
No! No!
If you are leaving just go.
No no. No.
No don't go. Don't go you idiot.
Don't go!
Morse.
Dot. Dot.
S.
T.
A.
Dash!
Murph!
We don't have time for this!
Come on!
Y.
Stay!
Come on. Come on Murph.
Murph! Murph. Come on.
What's it say?
Stay.
Tell him Murph.
Make him stay.
Make him stay Murph.
Don't let me leave Murph!
Don't...
No!
It was you.
You were my ghost.
Cooper.
Come in Cooper.
TARS?
Roger that.
You survived.
Somewhere...
in their fifth dimension.
They saved us.
Yeah?
Who the hell is they?
And just why would they want to help us?
I don't know, but they constructed
this three-dimensional space...
inside their five-dimensional reality
to allow you to understand it.
Yeah that ain't working.
Yes it is.
You have seen that time is represented
here as a physical dimension.
You have worked out that you can
exert a force across space-time.
Gravity,
to send a message.
Affirmative.
Gravity
can cross the dimensions...
including time.
Apparently.
Do you have the quantum data?
Roger. I have it.
I am transmitting it on all wavelengths
but nothing is getting out Cooper.
I can do this. I can do this.
But such complicated data to a child?
Not just any child.
What else?
Oh, come on Dad.
Murph the fire is out! Come on!
Even if you communicate it here,
she won't understand its significance for years.
I get that TARS.
Alright but we we have got
to figure something out or...
the people on Earth are gonna die.
Think, think, think!
Cooper...
they didn't bring us
here to change the past.
Say that again.
They didn't bring us
here to change the past.
No they didn't bring us here at all.
We brought ourselves.
TARS.
Give me the coordinates
for NASA...
in binary.
In binary. Roger.
Feeding data.
It's not a ghost.
It's gravity.
Don't you get it yet TARS?
I brought myself here!
We are here to communicate,
with the three-dimensional world.
We are the bridge!
I thought they chose me.
But they didn't choose me they chose her.
For what Cooper?
To save the world.
All of this,
to one little girl's bedroom.
Every moment.
It's infinitely complex.
They have access,
to infinite time and space
but they are not bound,
by anything!
They can't find a specific place
in time.
They can't communicate.
That's why I am here.
I am gonna find a way to tell Murph,
just like I found this moment.
How Cooper?
Love TARS love.
It's just like Brand said.
My connection with Murph,
it is quantifiable.
It's the key!
What are we here to do?
Find how to tell her.
The watch.
That's it.
We code the data into the movement
of the second hand.
TARS,
translate the data
into Morse and feed it to me.
Translating data to Morse.
Cooper what if she never came back for it?
She will.
Murph I can see his car!
He is coming Murph!
Ok.
I am coming down.
How do you know?
Because I gave it to her.
Roger. Morse is dot-dot-dash-dot.
Dot-dot...
dash-dot.
Dot-dash-dot-dot.
Dash-dash-dash.
Dash. Dash. Dash..
He came back!
It was him...
all the time! I didn't...
I didn't know. It was him!
Dad is gonna save us.
Eureka!
It's traditional.
Did it work?
I think it might have.
How do you know?
Because...
the bulk beings
are closing the tesseract.
Don't you get it yet TARS?
They are not beings.
They are us.
What I have been doing for Murph,
they done for me.
For all of us.
Cooper people could not build this.
No. No.
No, not yet.
But one day.
Not you and me.
But people.
A civilization,
that's evolved past
the four dimensions we know.
What happens now?
Mr. Cooper.
Let's take it slow sir.
Nice and easy Mr. Cooper.
Remember you are no spring chicken anymore.
Actually you are 124 years old.
Take it slow sir.
You were... extremely lucky.
The Rangers found you with only minutes
left in your oxygen supply.
Where am I?
Cooper Station.
Currently orbiting Saturn.
Nice of you to name it after me.
What?
Well the station isn't named after you sir.
It's... it's named after your daughter.
Although she's always maintained,
just how important you were.
Is she still alive?
She will be here in a couple weeks.
She is far too old to be
transferring from another station...
but when she heard
that you had been found...
well this is...
this is Murphy
Cooper we are talking about.
Yes it is.
We will have you checked
out of here in a couple days.
I am sure you will be excited
to see what's in store.
I actually...
did a paper on you,
in high school.
I know all about your life back on Earth.
Oh yeah.
Brand.
If... If you will follow me we have got
a really good situation...
for you.
So...
when I made my suggestion to Miss Cooper...
I was delighted to hear
that she thought it was perfect.
It was just constant.
Just that steady blow of dirt.
Of course I...
I didn't speak to her personally.
Set the plates upside-down.
Glasses or cups whatever
it was upside-down.
Well my dad was a farmer.
Like everybody else back then.
There just was not enough... food.
We wore little things little strips...
of sheet over our nose and mouth
so we would not breathe so much of it.
Well it was pretty exciting
for me because it was hope.
I don't care who describes it there is no
way for it to be exaggerated. It was that bad.
She did,
confirm just how much you loved farming.
Oh she did, did she?
Yeah.
Come here.
Home sweet home.
Everything replaced and...
put back where it...
Hey is this...
Oh yeah the...
The machine we found out near Saturn
when we found you. Yes.
Its power source was shot
but we could get you another one if you wanted.
Yes.
Please.
Settings.
General settings.
Security settings.
Honesty new setting:
95 percent.
Confirmed.
Additional customization?
Humor.
75 percent.
Confirmed.
Auto self-destruct T-minus 10...
9...
Let's make that 60 percent.
60 percent confirmed.
Knock-knock.
You want 55?
Is this really what it was like?
It was never this clean Slick.
I don't care much for this...
pretending we are back where we started.
I want to know where we are.
Where we are going.
Mr. Cooper.
The family is all in there.
Family?
Yeah they all came out to see her.
She is been in cryo-sleep
for almost two years.
You told them I like farming.
It was me Murph.
I was your ghost.
I know.
People didn't believe me.
They thought that I was doing it all myself.
But...
I knew who it was.
Nobody believed me.
But I knew you would come back.
How?
Because my dad promised me.
Well I am here now Murph.
I am here.
No.
No parent should have
to watch their own child die.
I have my kids here for me now.
You go.
Where?
Brand.
She is out there...
setting up camp.
Alone...
in a strange galaxy.
Maybe right now she is...
settling in for the long nap...
by the light of our new sun...
in our new home.
By LESAIGNEUR
Sync & corrections August 2022