[man] It's been a while
since I was in front of you.
Maybe I'll do us all a favor
and just stick to the cards.
There's been speculation
that I was involved in
the events that occurred
on the freeway and rooftop...
[woman] Sorry, Mr. Stark,
do you honestly expect us
to believe that that
was a bodyguard in a suit
that conveniently appeared,
despite the fact
that you historically
despise bodyguards?
- [Tony] Yes.
- [woman] And this
mysterious bodyguard
was somehow equipped
with an undisclosed
Stark high-tech-powered
- battle...
- [Tony] I know
that it's confusing.
It is one thing to question
the official story,
and another thing entirely
to make wild accusations
or insinuate
that I'm a superhero.
- I mean, let's face it.
I'm not the heroic type.
- [man speaking Russian]
A laundry list of character
defects, all the mistakes
I've made, largely public.
The truth is...
- ...I am Iron Man.
- [reporters clamoring]
[man speaking Russian]
[man continues speaking Russian]
[man coughs]
[woman speaking
Russian on TV]
[speaking Russian]
[old man wheezes]
[coughing]
[yelling]
[fizzling]
[air hissing]
[electrical whirring]
[laughing]
[man on radio] Two-seven-zero at 30 knots. Holding steady at 15,000 feet.
You are clear for exfiltration over the drop zone.
[♪ AD/DC: Shoot To Thrill]
[man continues indistinct]
♪ All you women who want a man of the street ♪
♪ Don't know which way
you wanna turn ♪
♪ Just keep coming
and put your hand out to me ♪
♪ Cos I'm the one
who's gonna make you burn ♪
♪ I'm gonna take you down
♪ Down, down, down
♪ So don't you fool around
♪ I'm gonna pull it, pull it
Pull the trigger ♪
♪ Shoot to thrill
Play to kill ♪
- ♪ Too many women
Too many pills, yeah ♪
-[cheering]
♪ Shoot to thrill
Play to kill ♪
♪ I got my gun at the ready
Gonna fire at will ♪
♪ Shoot you
Shoot you ♪
Shoot you down ♪
♪ Shoot you
Shoot you ♪
♪ Shoot you down
[cheering]
♪ I'm gonna shoot to thrill
♪ Shoot to
♪ Thrill ♪
[applause, cheering]
[horns blaring]
Oh, it's good to be back!
- You missed me.
- [man] Blow something up!
I missed a few...
Blow something up?
I already did that.
I'm not saying that
the world is enjoying
its longest period
of uninterrupted peace
in years because of me.
[cheering]
I'm not saying
that from the
ashes of captivity,
never has a greater phoenix
metaphor been personified
in human history.
[cheering]
I'm not saying
that Uncle Sam can kick back
on a lawn chair,
sipping on an iced tea,
because I haven't come across
anyone who's man enough
to go toe-to-toe
with me on my best day!
- [cheering]
- [chanting] Tony! Tony!
- [woman] I love you, Tony!
- Please. It's not about me.
- [chanting continues]
- It's not about you.
It's not even about us.
It's about legacy,
about what we choose to leave
behind for future generations.
That's why for the next year,
and for the
first time since 1974,
the best and brightest men
and women of nations and
corporations the world over
will pool their resources,
share their collective vision
- to leave behind
a brighter future...
- [cheering]
...that's not about us.
Therefore, what I am saying,
if I'm saying anything,
is welcome back
to the Stark Expo.
[cheering]
And now, making
a special guest appearance
from the great beyond
to tell you what it's all about,
please welcome
- my father, Howard.
- [orchestral music plays]
Everything is achievable
through technology.
Better living. Robust health.
And for the first time in human history, the possibility of world peace.
So from all of us here
at Stark Industries,
I would like to
personally introduce you
to the City of the Future.
Technology holds infinite
possibilities for mankind,
and will one day rid society
of all its ills.
Soon, technology
will affect the way you
live your life every day.
No more tedious work,
leaving more time
for leisure activities
and enjoying the sweet life.
The Stark Expo. Welcome.
[cheering]
We are coming to you live
from the kick-off
of the Stark Expo,
where Tony Stark
has just walked offstage.
Don't worry if you can't
make it here tonight, because
this Expo goes on all year.
I'm gonna be here checking out all the attractions and the pavilions and the inventions
from all around the world.
It's a zoo out there.
Watch out. Open up. Let's go.
- [cheering]
- [Tony] Hey! Nice to see you.
- All right. Thank you.
I remember you.
- Tony.
- Tony...
- Oh, hey...
- Call me.
- Hey, come on.
- [Tony] Hello, dear friends.
- Can you sign this?
It would be a pleasure.
See you, buddy.
- This is Larry.
- [Tony] The oracle of Oracle.
- What a pleasure.
Nice to see you.
- Call me.
- Larry King.
- Larry!
Oh, yes, my people, my people.
- Come on, Tony.
- There we go.
That was very mellow.
- That wasn't so bad.
- It was perfect.
Look what we got here.
The new model.
- Does she come with the car?
- I hope so.
- Hi. And you are?
- Hi.
- Marshal. Pleased to meet you.
- Irish. I like it.
[Tony] I'm on the wheel.
You mind? Where you from?
- Bedford.
- What're you doing here?
- Looking for you.
- Yeah? You found me.
[clears throat]
What're you up to later?
Serving subpoenas.
Yikes.
- He doesn't like
to be handed things.
- I have a peeve.
- I got it.
- You are hereby ordered
to appear before the Senate
Armed Services Committee
- tomorrow morning at 9am.
- Can I see a badge?
- You wanna see the badge?
- He likes the badge.
- You still like it?
- Yep.
- [engine starts]
- How far are we from D.C.?
D.C.? Two hundred
and fifty miles.
- [tires squeal]
- [gavel banging]
[man] Mr. Stark, can we pick up
where we left off? Mr. Stark!
- Please.
- Yes, dear?
- Could I have your attention?
- Absolutely.
Do you or do you not possess
a specialized weapon?
- I do not.
- [senator] You do not?
I do not. Well, it depends
on how you define "weapon."
- The Iron Man weapon.
- My device does not
fit that description.
- How would you describe it?
- By defining it as what it is.
- As?
- It's a...
It's a high-tech prosthesis.
- [laughter]
- That's actually the most apt
description I could make.
- It's a weapon, Mr. Stark.
- If your priority
was actually...
My priority is to get
the Iron Man weapon
turned over to the people
of the United States.
Well, you can forget it.
I am Iron Man.
The suit and I are one.
To turn over the suit
would be to turn over myself,
which is tantamount
to indentured servitude,
or prostitution, depending
on what state you're in.
- [laughter]
- You can't have it.
Look, I'm no expert.
In prostitution? Of course not.
You're a senator! Come on!
- [laughter]
- [senator] I'm no
expert in weapons.
We have somebody here who
is an expert on weapons.
I'd like to call Justin Hammer,
our current primary
weapons contractor.
Let the record reflect
that I observed
Mr. Hammer entering the chamber
and I am wondering
if and when any actual expert
will also be in attendance.
- [crowd murmuring]
- [banging gavel]
[laughs] Absolutely.
I'm no expert.
I defer to you, Anthony.
You're the wonder boy.
Senator, if I may.
I may well not be an expert,
but you know who
was the expert? Your dad!
Howard Stark.
Really a father
to us all, and to the
military-industrial age.
But let's be clear. He was no
flower child. He was a lion.
We all know why we're here.
In the last six months,
Anthony Stark has created a
sword with untold possibilities.
And yet he insists
it's a shield.
He asks us to trust him
as we cower behind it.
I wish I were comforted,
Anthony. I really do.
I'd love to leave my
door unlocked when I leave the
house. But this ain't Canada.
We live in a world
of grave threats,
threats Mr. Stark will not
always be able to foresee.
Thank you.
God bless Iron Man.
God bless America.
- [scattered applause]
- That is well said, Mr. Hammer.
The committee would
now like to invite
Lieutenant Colonel
James Rhodes to the chamber.
- Rhodey? What?
- [murmuring]
Hey, buddy. I didn't
expect to see you here.
It's me. I'm here.
Deal with it. Let's move on.
- I just...
- Drop it.
- I'll drop it.
- [Stern] I have
before me a complete report
on the Iron Man Weapon,
compiled by Colonel Rhodes.
Colonel, for the record,
can you read page 57,
paragraph four?
You're requesting
I read specific selections
from my report?
- Yes, sir.
- It was my understanding
I was going to testify
- in a more comprehensive...
- I understand.
A lot of things have changed.
You do understand that reading
a single paragraph out of
context does not reflect...
Just read it, colonel.
I do. Thank you.
Very well.
"As he does not operate
within any definable
branch of government,
Iron Man presents a potential
threat to the security
of both the nation
and to her interests."
I did, however, go on to
summarize that the benefits
of Iron Man far
outweigh the liabilities,
- and it would be
in our interest...
- That's enough!
- ...to fold Mr. Stark
into the chain of command.
- That's enough!
I'm not a joiner,
but I'll consider Secretary
of Defense if you ask nice.
- [laughter]
- If we can amend
the hours a little.
I'd like to show, if I may,
the imagery that's
connected to your report.
I believe it is
somewhat premature to reveal
- these images
to the general public.
- [Stern] With all due respect,
colonel, I understand.
If you could just narrate those
for us, we'd be very grateful.
Let's have the images.
Intelligence suggests the
devices seen in these photos
are in fact attempts
at making manned copies
of Mr. Stark's suit.
This has been corroborated
by our allies and local
intelligence on the ground,
indicating these suits
are quite possibly,
at this moment, operational.
[Tony] Hold on one second.
Let me see.
There's something here.
Oh! Boy, I'm good.
I commandeered your screens.
I need them.
It's time for
a little transparency.
- Let's see what's
really going on.
- What is he doing?
If you'll direct your
attention to said screens,
I believe that's North Korea.
[man speaking
foreign language on screen]
[people screaming on screen]
Can you turn that off?
Take it off.
- Iran.
- [speaking foreign language]
No grave, immediate threat here.
Is that Justin Hammer?
- How did Hammer
get in the game?
- Where's the plug?
[Tony] Justin, you're on TV.
[Justin] OK. Left twist.
- Good. Turn to the right.
- [screaming]
- [Justin] Where's the outlet?
- [Justin on TV]
Oh, shit. Oh, shit!
- [Tony] Wow.
- [crowd murmuring]
Yeah, I'd say most countries,
five, ten years away.
Hammer Industries, 20.
I'd like to point out
that test pilot survived.
[Stern] We're done
is the point he's making.
I don't think
there's any reason...
- Point is you're welcome.
- [Stern] For what?
Because I'm your
nuclear deterrent.
It's working. We're safe.
America is secure.
You want my property?
You can't have it!
But I did you a big favor.
I've successfully
privatized world peace.
[applause]
What more do you want?
For now!
I try to play ball
with these ass-clowns!
[bleep] ...you, Mr. Stark.
[bleep] ...you, buddy.
[Stern] We're
adjourned for the day.
- OK.
- You've been a delight.
[man speaking Russian on TV]
My bond is with the people.
And I will serve
this great nation
at the pleasure of... myself.
And if there's one thing
I've proven,
it's you can count on me
to pleasure myself.
- [electronic whirring]
- [fizzling]
[machinery whirring]
[♪ The Clash:
Should I Stay Or Should I Go]
- Wake up. Daddy's home. - [computer] Welcome home, sir.
Congratulations on
the opening ceremonies.
They were such a success.
As was your Senate hearing.
And may I say how refreshing it is to finally see you
in a video
with your clothing on, sir.
[chuckles]
You!
I swear to God
I'll dismantle you,
I'll soak your motherboard,
I'll turn you into a wine rack.
How many ounces a day
of this gobbledygook
am I supposed to drink?
[computer] We are up
to 80 ounces a day to
counteract the symptoms, sir.
Check palladium levels.
[computer] Blood toxicity:
24 percent.
It appears that the continued
use of the Iron Man suit is
accelerating your condition.
Another core has been depleted.
God, they're running out quick.
[computer] I have run
simulations on every
known element,
and none can serve as
a viable replacement
for the palladium core.
You are running out of
both time and options.
[sighs]
Unfortunately, the device that's keeping you alive is also killing you.
Miss Potts is approaching.
I recommend informing her...
- Mute.
- [computer silences]
[door beeps]
- Uh-uh.
- Is this a joke?
- What are you thinking?!
- What?
- What are you thinking?
- Hey! I'm thinking I'm busy
and you're angry
about something.
Do you have the sniffles?
I don't wanna get sick.
- Did you just donate
our entire...
- Keep your distance.
...modern art
collection to... to the...
- Boy Scouts of America.
- Boy Scouts of America?
It is a worthwhile organization.
I didn't physically check the
crates, but basically, yes.
And it's not our collection,
it's my collection.
No offense.
No. You know what?
I think I'm entitled
to say "our collection,"
considering the time
that I put in,
over ten years, curating it.
- It's a tax write-off.
I needed that.
- You know, there's only
about 8,011 things I really
need to talk to you about.
Dummy! Hey! Stop spacing out.
The Bridgeport's already
machining that part.
The Expo is a
gigantic waste of time.
- I need you to wear a surgical
mask until you're better. OK?
- That's rude.
There's nothing more important
to me than the Expo. It's my
primary point of concern.
The Expo is your
ego gone crazy.
Wow. Look at that.
That's modern art.
That's going up.
- You've got to be kidding.
- I'm putting this up now.
Stark is in
complete disarray.
- You understand?
- Our stocks have
never been higher.
- Yes, from
a managerial standpoint.
- Then let's double back.
- Move onto another...
- Oh, no, no, no!
You are not taking down
the Barnett Newman
and hanging that up!
I'm not taking it down.
I'm replacing it with this.
Let's see what I...
OK. Fine. My point is,
we have already awarded
contracts to the
wind farm people...
Don't say "wind farm."
I already feel gassy.
...and the plastic plantation
tree, which was your idea.
- Those people are on payroll.
- Everything was my idea.
I don't care about
the liberal agenda anymore.
It's boring! I'm giving you
a boring alert. You do it.
- I do what?!
- Excellent idea.
I just figured this out.
You run the company.
Yeah. I'm trying
to run the company.
Stop trying and do it.
I'm not asking you to try,
I'm asking you to physically
do it. I need you to do it.
- I am trying to do it.
- You're not listening!
I'm trying to make you CEO!
Why won't you let me?
Have you been drinking?
Uh, chlorophyll.
I hereby irrevocably
appoint you
chairman and CEO
of Stark Industries,
effective immediately.
Yeah. Done deal. OK?
I've actually given
this a fair amount of thought,
believe it or not.
Doing a bit of headhunting,
so to speak.
Trying to figure out
who a worthy successor would be.
And then I realized...
...it's you.
It's always been you.
I thought there'd
be a legal issue,
but actually
I'm capable of
appointing my successor,
my successor being you.
Congratulations.
- Take it. Just take it.
- I don't know what to think.
Don't think. Drink.
[laughs]
[speaking Russian]
[♪ The Clash:
The Magnificent Seven]
- [Tony] Come on, bring it in.
- The notary's here!
Can you please come sign
the transfer paperwork?
[Tony] I'm on Happy time!
[grunts]
- Sorry.
- What the hell was that?
It's called mixed martial arts.
Been around for three weeks.
It's called dirty boxing.
Nothing new about it.
- Put 'em up. Come on.
- [Happy grunts]
I promise you this is the
only time I will ask you
to sign over your company.
♪ The magnificent
I need you to
initial each box.
Lesson one.
Never take your eye off...
- [grunts]
- [bell rings]
- I'm done.
- What's your name, lady?
- Rushman. Natalie Rushman.
- Front and center.
- Come into the church.
- You're seriously not gonna...
- If it pleases the court,
which it does.
- It's no problem.
I'm sorry.
He's very eccentric.
[exhales] What?
- Can you give her a lesson?
- No problem.
- What?
- Who is she?
She is from Legal
and she is potentially
a very expensive
sexual harassment lawsuit,
- if you keep ogling her.
- I need a new assistant.
I've got three excellent
potential candidates
lined up to meet you.
I don't have time.
I need someone now.
I feel like it's her.
- No, it's not.
- You ever box before?
- I have.
- Like Tae Bo? Booty Boot Camp?
- Crunch? Something like that?
- [clears throat]
- How do I spell
your name, Natalie?
- R-U-S-H-M-A-N.
- [Pepper] You're gonna
Google her now?
- [Tony] Hmm?
I thought I was ogling her.
Oh, wow. Very
impressive individual.
- You are so predictable.
- Fluent in French,
Italian, Russian, Latin.
Who speaks Latin?
- No one speaks Latin.
It's a dead language.
- No one?
- You can read or write it,
not speak it.
- Did you model in Tokyo?
'Cause she modeled in Tokyo.
She's got everything I need.
Rule number one: never take
your eye off your opponent.
- Whoa!
- Oh, my God!
- [grunts]
- [Pepper] Happy!
- [Tony] That's what
I'm talking about.
- I just slipped.
- You did?
- Yeah.
- [bell rings]
- Looks like a TKO to me.
I just...
I need your impression.
You have a quiet reserve.
You're an old soul.
- I meant your fingerprint.
- Right.
- [Tony clears throat]
- So how are we doing?
Great. Just wrapping up. Hey.
You're the boss.
Will that be all,
Mr. Stark?
- No.
- Yes. That will be all,
Miss Rushman.
Thank you very much.
- I want one.
- No.
[man speaking French]
[crowd cheering]
It's Europe. Whatever happens
in the next 20 minutes,
just go with it.
- Go with it? Go with what?
- [Natalie] Mr. Stark?
- Hello. How was your flight?
- Excellent.
- Boy, it's nice to see you.
- We have one photographer
from the ACM, if you don't mind.
- OK.
- Mm-hmm.
- When did this happen?
- You made me do it.
- I made you do what?
- Smile. Look there.
- [both chuckle]
- Stop acting constipated.
- You are so predictable.
- Don't flare your nostrils.
- This way.
- Thanks. You look fantastic.
- Thank you.
- But that's unprofessional.
- What's on the docket?
- You have a 9:30 dinner.
- I'll be there at 11:00.
Is this us?
- Absolutely. It can be.
- Great. Make it us.
- OK.
- Mr. Musk. How are you?
- Hi, Pepper.
- Congratulations
on the promotion.
- Thank you.
Elon, those Merlin
engines are fantastic.
Thank you. I have an
idea for an electric jet.
You do?
Then we'll make it work.
- You want a massage?
- Oh, God. No.
I'll have Natalie
make an appointment.
I don't want Natalie
to do anything.
- I didn't mean to
spring this on you.
- Thank you.
- Green is not your best color.
- Please!
- Anthony! Is that you?
- My least favorite person
on Earth, Justin Hammer.
You're not the only rich guy
here with a fancy car.
Do you know Christine
Everhart from Vanity Fair?
- You know each other.
- Hi.
- Yes.
- Yes, roughly.
BTW, big story. The new
CEO of Stark Industries.
Congratulations.
I know. My editor will kill me
if I don't grab a quote
for our powerful women issue.
- Oh. Sure.
- Can I...?
She's actually doing a big
spread on me for Vanity Fair.
- Thought I'd throw
her a bone. Right?
- Yes.
She did quite a spread
on Tony last year.
- And she wrote a story as well.
- It was very impressive.
- That was good.
- Very well done.
- Thank you.
- I'm gonna go wash.
- Don't leave me.
- Hey, buddy. How you doing?
- I'm all right.
- You're looking gorgeous.
Can I ask, is this the first
time that you guys have...
- Say brie.
- Oh, God, it's so awful.
- [laughter]
- The first time you've seen
each other since the Senate?
- Since he got his
contract revoked?
- Actually, it's on hold.
Not what I heard. What's the
difference between "hold"
and "canceled?" The truth?
No. The truth is...
Why don't we put that away?
The truth is I'm hoping to
present something at your Expo.
Well, if you invent something
that works, I'll make sure
I get you a slot.
- Mr. Stark?
- Yes.
- Your corner table is ready.
- I actually have
- a slot this year.
- Hammer needs a slot,
Christine!
We kid. [laughs]
We kid. We're kidders.
Got any other bad ideas?
[crowd clamoring]
[engines revving]
Tony and I... I love Tony Stark.
Tony loves me.
We're not competitors.
Him being out of the picture
created tremendous opportunity
for Hammer Industries.
Everything Tony and I do
is a healthy...
But what's the use of having and owning a race car...
- [man speaking French]
- ...if you don't drive it?
- [crowd cheering]
- Is he driving?
[man speaking French on TV]
Natalie. Natalie!
- Yes, Miss Potts?
- Did you know about this?
This is the first
I've known of it.
- [Pepper] This cannot happen.
- [Natalie] I understand.
How can I help you?
- Where's Happy?
- Outside.
- Get him. I need Happy.
- Right away.
Tony's just... you know...
We're not competitive.
You know what I mean?
You know what? Can you
excuse me just one second?
- Can you just read me
what you wrote?
- I will.
- Read it back to me.
- I have to make
one quick phone call.
- Where you going?
There's caviar coming.
- This is great stuff.
I'll be right back!
[engine revving]
[crowd cheering]
[man speaking indistinctly
over PA]
[man speaking French on TV]
[man shouting on TV]
[electrical whirring]
[man shouting in French]
[all gasping]
Go, go!
Hang on.
- [speaking French]
- [shouting]
[electrical fizzling]
[car engines approaching]
[all shouting, gasping]
- Give me the case.
- Here. Take it.
- Where's the key!
- In my pocket.
Car!
- [crowd screaming]
- [man speaking over PA]
[fizzling]
[Pepper] Oh, my God.
- [horn honking]
- [brakes squealing]
- [Happy] Are you OK?
- Yeah.
- Were you heading
for me or him?
- I was trying to scare him.
- 'Cause I can't tell!
- Are you out of your mind?!
- Better security.
- Get in the car!
- I was attacked!
You're the CEO! Better security
measures! It's embarrassing.
First vacation in two years.
- [all screaming]
- Whoa!
[Pepper] Oh, my God!
- I got him!
- [Tony] Hit him again!
- Give me the football.
- OK.
- I got him!
- Take the case!
- [Happy] Give him the case!
- [Pepper] Stop banging the car!
[Pepper screaming]
[screaming] Oh, God!
[Tony] Give me the case!
Please!
Come on!
[all screaming]
[grunting]
[electric fizzling]
[crowd cheering]
[laughs] You lose!
[man laughing]
[laughing] You lose!
You lose, Stark!
- [laughing]
- [siren approaching]
[sirens wailing]
[speaking French]
Pretty decent tech. Cycles
per second were a little low.
You could have doubled up
your rotations.
You focused the repulsor
energy through ionized plasma
channels. It's effective.
Not very efficient.
But it's a
passable knock-off.
I don't get it. A little
fine-tuning, you could have
made a solid paycheck.
Sold it to
North Korea, China.
Iran. Or gone right
to the black market.
You look like you
got friends in low places.
You come from
a family of...
...thieves and butchers.
And now, like
all guilty men,
you try to rewrite
your own history.
And you forget all the lives
the Stark family has destroyed.
Speaking of thieves,
where'd you get this design?
My father. Anton Vanko.
I've never heard of him.
My father is the
reason you're alive.
The reason I'm alive
is 'cause you had a shot,
you took it, you missed.
Did I?
If you can make God bleed,
then people will cease
to believe in him.
And there will
be blood in the water.
And the sharks will come.
The truth, all I have
to do is sit here and watch
as the world
will consume you.
Where will you watch the world
consume me from? That's right.
A prison cell.
I'll send you a bar of soap.
Hey, Tony. Before you go.
Palladium in the chest,
painful way to die.
[knocking on door]
[speaking French]
- [door shuts]
- [chuckles]
It's unbelievable. It proves the genie is out of the bottle,
and this man has no idea
what he's doing.
He thinks of the Iron Man
weapon as a toy.
I was at a hearing
where Mr. Stark, in fact,
was adamant that these suits
can't exist anywhere else,
don't exist anywhere else,
never will exist
anywhere else,
for five to ten years, and here we are in Monaco realizing,
- uh-oh, these suits exist now.- [Tony] Mute.
He should be giving me
a medal. That's the truth.
What is that?
This is your...
in-flight meal.
Did you just make that?
Yeah. Where do you think
I've been for three hours?
Tony?
What are you not telling me?
I don't want to go home...
...at all.
Let's cancel my
birthday party and, uh...
We're in Europe. Let's
go to Venice, Cipriani.
- [sighs]
- Remember?
- Oh, yes.
- It's a great place to... to...
- ...be healthy.
- I don't think this
is the right time.
We're in kind of a mess.
But maybe that's why
it's the best time.
Well, I think as the CEO,
I need to show up.
As CEO, you are
entitled to a... leave.
- A leave?
- A company retreat.
A retreat?
During a time like this?
We need to recharge
our batteries and
figure it all out.
Not everybody
runs on batteries, Tony.
[man shouting in distance]
[grunting]
[speaking French]
- [alarm blaring]
- [men shouting]
[classical music playing]
[Justin] Hey, there he is!
There he is.
What an absolute pleasure.
Welcome.
Oh, goodness gracious.
Can we get the handcuffs
off my friend here?
Forgive me, I'm sorry.
I'm such a huge fan of yours.
I didn't want to make
a first impression like
this. He's not an animal.
Come on. He's a human being.
Thank you.
- [speaking French]
- We're fine.
My name's Justin Hammer.
I'd like to do some business
with you. Please, sit.
Dig in. What do
we have today, Jack?
- We have some
salmon carpaccio, sir.
- Salmon carpaccio?
Mm-mmm! Anything you want here,
we got it.
I like my dessert first.
I had this flown in
from San Francisco.
It's Italian, though.
Organic ice cream.
I got a sweet tooth.
Apparently you do, too,
for Tony Stark.
What I saw you do
to Tony Stark on that track,
how you stepped up to him
in front of God and everybody,
that was... Wow!
You spoke to me with
what you did. I know
you knew I'd be listening.
This is why I couldn't bear to
have you shipped off to God
knows where. A waste of talent.
But if I might make
a suggestion. You don't just
go and try and kill the guy.
I think, if I may,
you go after his legacy.
That's what you kill.
You and me, we're a lot alike
in a lot of ways.
The only difference between you
and I is that I have resources.
I think, if I may,
you need my resources.
Someone behind you.
A benefactor.
I'd like to be that guy.
[laughs, sighs]
[speaking Russian]
OK. Do you speak English?
Because I can get a translator.
Have you been understanding
everything I'm saying?
- Very good man.
- Very good, man.
- [both laugh]
Hey! Huh?
- Hey.
- Yes?
I want my bird.
A bird? You want a bird?
- I want my bird.
- I can get you ten birds.
- Well, OK.
Nothing's impossible.
I could...
Are we talking about...
Is this a bird
back in Russia?
Yes, but the fundamentals
of the company are
still very, very strong,
despite the events in Monaco.
- The AP wants a quote.
- Fax them this press release.
- Where is he?
- He doesn't want
to be disturbed.
- He's downstairs.
- But his continuing
erratic behavior
may lead many people
to ask themselves,
"Can this man
still protect us?"
[Pepper] Iron Man never
stopped protecting us.
The events in Monaco
proved that.
[computer] Query complete, sir.
Anton Vanko was
a Soviet physicist
who defected to the
United States in 1963.
However, he was accused of espionage and deported in 1967.
His son, Ivan,
who is also a physicist,
was convicted of selling
Soviet-era weapons-grade
plutonium to Pakistan
and served 15 years
in Kopeisk Prison.
No further records exist.
Tony, you got to get
upstairs and get on top
of this situation right now.
Listen, I've been on the phone
with the National Guard all day
trying to talk them out
of rolling tanks up to PCH,
knocking down your front door
and taking these.
They're gonna take your suits.
They're sick of the games.
You said nobody would possess
this technology for 20 years.
Well, guess what?
Somebody else had it yesterday.
It's not theoretical anymore.
Are you listening to me?
Are you OK?
Let's go.
[grunts]
Hey, hey...
- Are you all right?
- I should get to my desk.
- See that cigar box?
- Yeah.
It's palladium.
Is that supposed
to be smoking?
If you must know,
it's neutron damage.
It's from the reactor wall.
You had this in your body?
How about the high-tech
crossword puzzle on your neck?
Road rash.
Thank you.
- What are you looking at?
- I'm looking at you.
You want to do this whole
lone gunslinger act,
and it's unnecessary.
- You don't have
to do this alone.
- I wish I could believe that.
I really do.
But you got to trust me.
Contrary to popular belief,
I know exactly what I'm doing.
[Justin] This is where we do it.
My humble abode.
You can work in absolute peace.
Must be kind of fun to be dead,
right? No pressure?
Here they are! I'm excited.
They're combat ready.
I may have done a few
miscalculations and rushed
the prototype into production.
Sue me. I'm enthusiastic.
Go ahead, take a look around.
Oh, you don't
want to do that.
You'll be able to access that
as soon as we generate
some encrypted pass codes.
Can we generate
some encrypted pass codes?
Get some of those
encrypted pass codes, Jack.
Never mind. I...
Wow. OK. Good stuff.
[speaking Russian]
- Sorry?
- Software shit.
Uh-huh. Well...
[Justin laughs]
You're good.
You really blasted in past
the firewall there. Uh...
Let me show you where you're
gonna be working primarily.
Go ahead, take a look.
Get a good look at that.
That's something, isn't it?
Those are really just
for show and tell.
They're $125.7
million a pop, so...
Wait! Oh, gosh.
Um...
[whispers] Jesus Christ,
get somebody up here to help.
Um, that's where
the pilot goes.
I'm having a tough time
finding volunteers.
I'll take care of that.
Just leave it.
What you want them do?
Well, long term, I want them
to put me in the Pentagon
for the next 25 years.
I want to make Iron Man
look like an antique.
I want to go to the Stark Expo
and take a dump
in Tony's front yard.
- Know what I'm talking about?
- [laughs] I can do that.
No problem.
Hey! Fabulous! I love it.
This is our guy. Didn't I
tell you? I had a feeling.
Do you know which watch you'd
like to wear tonight, Mr. Stark?
I'll give them a look.
- I should cancel
the party, huh?
- Probably.
- Yeah. 'Cause it's, um...
- Ill-timed.
- Right. Sends
the wrong message.
- Inappropriate.
Is that dirty enough for you?
Uh, gold face, brown band.
The Jaeger.
I'll give that a look.
Bring them over here.
I'll take that.
Why don't you...?
I gotta say, it's hard to get a
read on you. Where are you from?
Legal.
Can I ask you a question,
hypothetically? A bit odd.
If this was your last birthday
party you were gonna have,
how would you celebrate it?
I'd do whatever I wanted
to do, with whoever
I wanted to do it with.
[sighs]
[scratching record]
[♪ 2Pac featuring Dr. Dre
&amp; Roger Troutman: California
Love [Single Version]]
[crowd cheering]
Yes, sir, I understand.
No, no, sir, that will not be
necessary. I'll handle it.
Sir, I personally guarantee
that within 24 hours,
Iron Man will be back on watch.
[music continues]
Hey, Pepper.
- I'm gonna go get some air.
- What's wrong?
- [glass shatters]
- I don't know what to do.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- Oh!
- [crashing]
- [crowd yelling, laughing]
- That's it. I'm making...
- No, no! Don't call anyone.
- This is ridiculous. I stuck
my neck out for this guy.
- I know. I know. I get it.
- I'll handle it, OK?
- Handle it.
Or I'm gonna have to.
The question I'm asked most
often is, "How do you go
to the bathroom in the suit?"
- Just like that.
- [cheering]
[Tony laughing]
Does this guy know
how to throw a party or what?
[cheering]
- I love you.
- Aw! Unbelievable.
Thank you so much, Tony,
we all thank you so much
for such a... wonderful night.
We're gonna say
good night now.
- Thank you all for coming.
- [crowd groans]
No, we can't, wait.
We didn't have the cake,
- and we didn't
blow out the candles.
- You're out of control.
- I'm out of control?
- Trust me on this one.
- You're out of control
gorgeous.
- Time to go to bed.
- It's time.
- Give me a smooch.
- You're not gonna be happy.
- You know you want to.
- You just peed in the suit.
- It has a filtration system.
- It's not sexy.
- You could drink that water.
Just send everybody home,
OK? It's time to...
- If you say so.
- OK.
I'll take this.
You take that.
- Pepper Potts.
- [applause]
She's right.
The party's over.
Then again, the party was over
for me an hour and a half ago.
The after-party starts
in 15 minutes!
[cheering]
And if anybody, Pepper,
doesn't like it,
- there's the door.
- [crowd gasps]
[cheering]
[yelling]
[Tony] Pull!
- Pull!
- [screeching]
Pull!
Yah!
Do me, do me!
I think she wants the Gallagher!
- [yells]
- You got it!
[James] I'm only
gonna say this once.
Get out.
You don't deserve to wear
one of these. Shut it down.
- Goldstein.
- Yes, Mr. Stark?
[laughing] Give me a fat beat
to beat my buddy's ass to.
[♪ Queen: Another One
Bites The Dust]
I told you to shut it down.
Now, put that thing back
where you found it
before someone gets hurt.
- Really?
- ♪ Ain't no sound but
the sound of his feet ♪
♪ Machine gun's ready to go
♪ Are you ready? Hey, are you ready for this? ♪
♪ Are you hanging
on the edge of your seat? ♪
[Tony] Sorry, pal, but Iron Man
doesn't have a sidekick.
Side... kick... this!
[♪ Rob Base and DJ E-Z Rock:
It Takes Two]
Had enough?
- Natalie!
- Ms. Potts.
Oh, don't you "Ms. Potts" me.
I'm onto you.
You know what?
Ever since you came here... Oh!
[Happy] Pepper!
[Happy] Get out of here!
Get out of here!
[crowd exclaiming]
[Tony] You want it? Take it!
[metal clanging]
- [yelling]
- [crowd screaming]
[James] Put your hand down.
[Tony] You think
you got what it takes
- to wear that suit?
- We don't have to do this.
You want to be the war machine,
take your shot.
- Put it down!
- You gonna take a shot?
- No!
- Drop it, Tony!
- Take it!
[lights fizzling]
[beeps, whirring]
[James] Edwards Tower,
this is Lieutenant
Colonel James Rhodes,
inbound from three miles east
at 5,000 feet.
Requesting permission
to land at hangar 22.
[rumbling]
[man] Colonel.
Major.
Wow.
Yeah.
Let's take it inside.
[man] Clear the area!
[♪ Beastie Boys: Groove Holmes]
Sir! I'm going to have
to ask you to exit the doughnut!
I told you I don't want to join
your super-secret boy band.
[laughs] No, no. I remember,
you do everything yourself.
- How's that working out?
- It's, it's, it's, it's...
I'm sorry. I don't wanna
get off on the wrong foot.
Do I look at the patch
or the eye?
Honestly, I'm a bit hung over.
I'm not sure if you're real...
I am very real.
I am the realest person
you're ever gonna meet.
- Just my luck.
Where's the staff...?
- That's not looking so good.
I've been worse.
[Natalie] We've
secured the perimeter,
but I don't think we should
hold it for too much longer.
Huh.
- You're fired.
- That's not up to you.
Tony, I want you
to meet Agent Romanoff.
- Hi.
- I'm S.H.I.E.L.D. shadow.
Once we knew you were ill,
- I was tasked to
you by Director Fury.
- I suggest you apologize.
You've been very busy,
made your girl your CEO,
you're giving
away all your stuff.
You let your friend
fly away with your suit!
- If I didn't know better...
- You don't know better.
I didn't give it to him.
- He took it.
- Whoa, whoa. What? He took it?
You're Iron Man
and he just took it?!
The little brother
walked in there, kicked your
ass and took your suit.
- Is that possible?
- According to Mr. Stark's
database security guidelines,
there are redundancies to
prevent unauthorized usage.
- What do you want from me?
- What do we want? Nuh-uh-uh.
What do you want from me?
You have become a problem,
a problem I have to deal with.
Contrary to your belief, you are
not the center of my universe.
- I get it.
- I have bigger problems
than you
in the southwest region
to deal with! Hit him.
- [hisses]
- Ah! Oh, God!
Are you gonna
steal my kidney and sell it?
Could you please not do anything
awful for five seconds?
- What'd she just do to me?
- What did we just do for you?
That's lithium dioxide. It's
gonna take the edge off. We're
trying to get you back to work.
Give me a couple of boxes,
I'll be right as rain.
It's not a cure.
Just abates the symptoms.
Doesn't look like
it's gonna be an easy fix.
Trust me, I know.
I'm good at this stuff.
I've been looking for a suitable
replacement for palladium.
I've tried every combination,
every permutation
of every known element.
Well, I'm here to tell you
you haven't tried them all.
Hey, hey, hey!
Special delivery!
Candygram!
I brought you something.
Oh, yeah!
- [bird squawks]
- [laughs]
- We got you the bird, pal!
- This is not my bird.
What do you mean? That's the
bird. This is the bird! Yeah!
Pulled a lot of strings
to get this bird.
- This is a great bird!
- It's a beautiful bird.
We got this all the way
from Russia!
Hey, man, this not my bird.
Well, even if it's not the bird,
this is a gorgeous bird.
I mean, you know,
don't get so attached to things.
Learn to let go.
Wait a minute.
Jack, what is that?
Is that...? That's not a helmet.
What is that?
Um, Ivan?
What's this? Jack?
Is that a helmet? It doesn't
look like a helmet to me.
How do you get a head
in there? Jack, could
you put your head in there?
- No.
- Try to put your head
in there. Go ahead.
Try to put your head
in there.
See, Ivan, he can't
put his head in there.
That's not a helmet,
it's a head.
I need to put a guy in there.
I need to fit a person
in that suit. You understand?
- Drone better.
- What? Drone better?
Why is drone better?
- Why is drone better?
- People make problem.
- Trust me. Drone better.
- Ivan, you know, I like you.
I got you the bird.
You said no problem.
That's what you said to me,
you said, "No problem."
Now, I need suits.
The government wants suits.
Like Iron Man! You understand?
That's what the people want!
That's what's gonna make
them happy.
Hey, man,
don't get too attached
to things.
Learn to let go.
[bird squawks]
These drones better
steal the show, Ivan.
You understand?
They better rock my world, Ivan!
Unbelievable.
This ought to get
the Senate off my ass.
- It's functional?
- Fully mission capable.
Good. Get Hammer
down here to weaponize it.
- Sir?
- Justin Hammer's making
a weapons presentation
at the Expo. We'd
like this to introduce it.
- Sir, I don't believe
the Expo...
- Colonel,
the world needs to see
this fast. We've got
to make this happen.
- Yes, general, but...
- It's also an order.
- Yes, sir.
- Good work, colonel.
You've made
your country proud.
Thank you, sir.
That thing in your chest
is based on
unfinished technology.
No, it was finished.
It's never been particularly
effective until I miniaturized
it and put it in my...
No. Howard said the arc
reactor was a stepping
stone to something greater.
He was about to kick off
an energy race that
was gonna dwarf the arms race.
He was onto something big.
Something so big that it was
gonna make the nuclear reactor
look like a triple-A battery.
Just him?
Or was Anton Vanko in on it?
Anton Vanko is the
other side of that coin.
Anton saw it as a way
to get rich. When your father
found out, he had him deported.
When the Russians found out
he couldn't deliver,
they shipped his ass off to
Siberia and he spent the next
20 years in a vodka-fueled rage.
Not quite the environment
you wanna raise a kid in.
The son you had the misfortune
of crossing paths with
in Monaco.
You told me I hadn't
tried everything.
What haven't I tried?
He said you were the only person
with the means and knowledge
- to finish what he started.
- He said that?
Mm-hmm.
Are you that guy? Hmm? Are you?
'Cause if you are,
then you can solve
the riddle of your heart.
I don't know where you're
getting your information,
but he wasn't my biggest fan.
What do you remember
about your dad, huh?
He was cold, calculating.
He never told me he loved me,
or even that he liked me.
So it's a little
tough for me to digest
when you're telling me
he said the future was riding
on me and he's passing it down.
I don't get that.
We're talking about a guy whose
happiest day was when he shipped
me off to boarding school.
- That's not true.
- Then clearly you know my dad
better than I did.
As a matter of fact, I did.
He was one of the founding
members of S.H.I.E.L.D.
- What?
- I got a 2:00.
Wait, wait, wait. What's this?
- You're good, right?
- No, I'm not.
- You got this, right?
- Got what?
I don't know what
I'm supposed to get.
Natasha will remain
a floater
at Stark with
her cover intact.
And you remember
Agent Coulson, right?
- Yeah.
- Oh, and Tony.
Remember, I got my eye on you.
We've disabled all
communications. No contact with
the outside world. Good luck.
Please. First,
I need a little body work.
I'll put a little
time in at the lab.
If we could send one
of your goon squad down
to the Coffee Bean
for a Starbucks run or
something, that'd be nice.
I'm not here for that.
I've been authorized
by Director Fury to use any
means to keep you on premises.
If you attempt to leave
or play any games,
I will Tase you and watch Supernanny
while you
drool into the carpet.
- OK?
- I think I got it, yeah.
Enjoy your evening's
entertainment.
Think this is
their power source?
Major, this is not
a scientific exercise.
Let's just focus
on arming it, all right?
Yes, sir.
[Justin] Oh, yes!
Oh, yes, yes, yes!
Is it my birthday?
You got it. What did you do?
What did you do?
Oh!
- Is this what I think it is?
- Yes, it is. Hammer.
I want to know what
you're gonna do for us.
What am I gonna do for you?
Well, first thing I'm gonna
do for you is I'm gonna
upgrade your software. Then...
That's not what I'm
talking about. Hammer!
I'm talking about
firepower.
You're talking
to the right guy.
Claridge Hi-Tec,
semi-automatic 9mm pistol.
Too downtown? I agree.
M-24 shotgun, pump action.
Five round magazine. Know what?
You're not a hunter.
What am I talking about?
I'm getting rid of it.
This is the FN-2000
from Belgium.
They do make something
better than waffles.
It's beautiful.
But I can tell this isn't
disco enough for you.
I'm gonna put it right here.
We're looking at a Milkor
40-millimeter grenade launcher.
Tear gas, smoke.
Hippie control.
You're tough.
Let me tell you something.
Size does matter. Don't let
anyone tell you different.
This is an M134, 7.62 minigun.
Six individual barrels.
The torso taker,
powder maker.
Our boys in uniform
call it Uncle Gazpacho
or Puff the Magic Dragon.
OK.
These are the Cubans, baby.
These are the Cohibas,
the Montecristos.
This is a kinetic-kill
Sidewinder vehicle
with a secondary
cyclotrimethylenetrinitramine
RDX burst.
It's capable of busting
a bunker under the bunker
you just busted.
If it were any smarter,
it'd write a book.
A book that would make Ulysses
look like it was
written in crayon.
And it would
read it to you.
This is my Eiffel Tower,
my Rachmaninoff's Third.
My Pietà.
It's completely elegant,
it's bafflingly beautiful
and it's capable of reducing
the population of any
standing structure to zero.
I call it the Ex-Wife.
That's the best I got.
Are we gonna do this?
Give me something.
You're like a sphinx.
I can't read you.
- I think I'll take it.
- Which one?
All of it.
Everything is achievable
through technology.
Better living. Robust health.
And for the first time
in human history,
the possibility
of world peace.
I'm Howard Stark. Everything
you'll need for the future
can be found right here.
City of the Future?
City of Tomorrow? Hang on.
I'm Howard Stark. Everything
you'll need in the future
can be found right here.
So from all of us
at Stark Industries,
I would like to personally...
Tony, what are you doing
back there? What is that?
Put that back. Put it back
where you got it from!
Where's your mother? Maria!
Go on. Go, go, go.
All right,
I think we got the, uh...
I'll come in and, uh...
Are you waiting on me?
So from all of us
at Stark Industries,
I'd like to show you...
...my ass. I'd like to...
This is... I can't.
We have this, don't we?
This is a ridiculous way
to make a living.
Everything...
...is achievable...
...through technology.
Tony. You're too young to
understand this right now,
so I thought I'd put it
on film for you.
I built this for you.
And someday you'll realize it represents a whole lot more than just people's inventions.
It represents my life's work.
This is the key to the future.
I'm limited by the
technology of my time.
But one day
you'll figure this out.
And when you do...
...you will change the world.
What is and always will be
my greatest creation...
...is you.
[film slapping reel]
- Hello, sir.
- [speaks Spanish]
- Seisdollars. Six.
- I don't have any dough. Here.
- No, sir, that's too much.
- It's fine. Take that.
- That's... No, señor.
- Take it.
I don't like people
handing me things,
so just drop it there.
- Are you Iron Man?
- Sometimes.
We believe in you!
It was an illegal seizure
of trademarked property.
- Ms. Potts?
- [Tony] Relax.
- [woman] Mr. Stark is...
He refuses...
- He's here.
- I don't. It's fine.
I'll just be a second.
- It's our position
that Stark has
and continues to maintain
proprietary ownership
- of the Mark II platform.
- [TV] When Mr. Stark announced he was indeed Iron Man,
- he made a promise...
- No, the suit belongs to us.
...he would look out for us.
He obviously did not.
And now we learn that his
secretary, a woman named
Virginia "Pepper" Potts
has been appointed as CEO
of Stark Industries.
What are her qualifications?
- No.
- Miss Potts is doing nothing...
- [Tony] Mute.
- [Pepper] No.
Bert, Bert, listen to me.
Don't tell me that
we have the best patent
lawyers in the country,
and then not
let me pursue this.
- I'll get this out of here.
- Tell the president
to sign an order.
We'll talk about it
at the Expo.
Hammer's giving some
presentation tomorrow evening.
- Will Tony Stark be there?
- Will I?
- No, he will not. Bye.
- I'd like to be.
- Got a minute?
- No.
You just got off the phone.
Thirty seconds.
- Twenty-nine, 28...
- OK, I, um...
I was driving over here,
and I thought I was coming
to apologize, but I'm not.
- You didn't come to apologize?
- That goes without saying.
I'm working on that.
But I haven't been
entirely upfront with you,
and I want to try
to make good.
Can I move this?
- This is crazy. It's like
a Ferris wheel, going...
- No.
[clears throat]
Do you know how short life is?
And if I never
got to express...
And by the way, this is
somewhat revelatory to me.
I don't care... I mean,
I care. It would be nice.
I'm not expecting you to...
Here's what I'm trying to say.
I'll just say it.
Let me stop you here.
Because if you say "I"
one more time,
I'm gonna hurl something
at your head, I think.
I am trying to run a company.
Do you have any idea
what that entails?
- Yes.
- People are relying
on you to be Iron Man
and you disappeared. All
I'm doing is putting out your
fires and taking heat for it.
I am trying to do the job
that you are meant to do.
Did you bring me
strawberries?
Did you know there's
only one thing on Earth
I'm allergic to?
Allergic to.
Strawberries. Mm-hmm.
This is progress.
I knew there was
a correlation
between you and this.
- I need you...
- I need you, too.
...to leave... now.
- [door opens]
- Ms. Potts?
Hi. Come on in.
- Wheels up in 25 minutes.
- Thank you.
- [Happy] Anything else, boss?
- [Tony] I'm good, Hap.
I'll be just...
another minute.
I lost both the kids
in the divorce.
[laughs] That's...
No.
[clears throat]
Are you blending in well
here, Natalie?
Here at Stark...
Enterprises.
Your name is Natalie,
isn't it?
I thought you two
didn't get along.
- That's not so.
- It's just me
you don't care for.
- No? Nothing.
- Actually, while you're here,
you and Natalie can discuss
the matter of the
personal belongings.
Absolutely.
I'm surprised you can
keep your mouth shut.
Boy, you're good. You are
mind-blowingly duplicitous.
You're a triple imposter. I've
never seen anything like it.
Is there anything real about
you? Do you even speak Latin?
[speaks Latin]
Which means? Wait, what?
What did you just say?
It means you can either
drive yourself home
or I'll have you collected.
You're good!
Jarvis, could you kindly
vacuform a digital wireframe?
I need a manipulatable
projection.
[Jarvis] 1974 Stark Expo
model scan complete, sir.
Uh, how many buildings
are there?
[Jarvis] Am I to include
the Belgian waffle stands?
That was rhetorical.
Just show me.
Uh-huh.
Um...
What does that
look like to you, Jarvis?
Not unlike an atom.
In which case, the nucleus...
would be here.
Highlight the unisphere.
Lose the footpaths.
Get rid of them.
[Jarvis] What is it you're
trying to achieve, sir?
I'm discovering...
Correction:
I'm rediscovering...
...a new element.
Lose the landscaping,
shrubbery, trees,
parking lots,
exits, entrances.
Structure the protons
and neutrons
using the pavilions
as a framework.
Dead for almost 20 years,
still taking me to school.
[Jarvis] The proposed element
should serve as a viable
replacement for palladium.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Unfortunately, it is
impossible to synthesize.
Uh-huh.
Get ready for a major remodel,
fellas. We're back
in hardware mode.
[grunting]
[socket wrench cranking]
I hear you broke
the perimeter.
Yeah. That was like three
years ago. Where you been?
- I was doing some stuff.
- [Tony] Yeah? Well, me, too.
And it worked.
Hey. I'm playing for the home
team, for you and your
Fabulous Furry Freak Brothers.
You gonna let me work
or break my balls?
What's this doing here?
That's it.
- Bring it to me.
- You know what this is?
Exactly what I need
to make this work.
Lift the coil. Go!
Put your knees into it.
There you go.
And... drop it. Drop it.
Perfectly level.
- I'm busy. What do you want?
- Nothing. Goodbye.
I've been reassigned.
Director Fury wants me
in New Mexico.
- Fantastic.
Land of Enchantment.
- So I'm told.
- Secret stuff.
- Something like that.
- [laughs]
- Good luck.
- Bye. Thanks.
- We need you.
- Yeah. More than you know.
- Not that much.
[machinery whirring]
[Jarvis] Initializing
prismatic accelerator.
Approaching maximum power.
[machinery whirring faster]
Whoops.
[high-pitched whirring]
[rattling]
That was easy.
[Jarvis] Congratulations, sir.
You have created
a new element.
Sir, the reactor has
accepted the modified core.
I will begin
running diagnostics.
[phone rings]
Hey, Ivan.
I got Senator Stern here.
I thought we'd swing over and look at the drone designs.
The drone is not
going to be ready.
- Not... What do you mean?
- I can make presentation,
- not demonstration.
- [laughs] What the hell
is the difference?
Presentation.
No flying. No shooting.
Wait, wait, wait.
What can you make them do?
This is a weapons demonstration.
- I can make salute.
- You can make salute?
What do you mean,
make salute?
What the hell
does that mean, Ivan?
This is not what we agreed to.
You promised me suits, then you promised me drones...
- Hey, man,
everything will be OK.
- This is not what I wanted.
[door beeps, lock buzzes]
Hey, there he is.
It's the birdman!
Oh, now you like the bird.
Is that right?
Is that your bird?
I'm confused.
You said it wasn't,
but now you're best of pals.
You love that bird,
don't you?
You know what? Take the bird.
- [bird squawks]
- Hey!
Take his pillows, too.
Both of them.
And his shoes.
Take his shoes.
I took your stuff.
How does that make you feel?
You feel bad?
Good.
'Cause that's how I feel!
We had a contract!
I saved your life,
and you give me suits.
That was our deal.
And you did not deliver.
I don't know if you're
a genius or a fraud.
I don't know what you are!
Something really,
really great fell into my lap.
If it hadn't, I'd be
at your mercy tonight.
Now, I have a piece
of Stark tech that
I pimped out myself.
Your overpriced paperweights
will look like a backdrop
to my demonstration.
You dig
what I'm getting at?
[speaks Russian]
I don't know if you know this,
but I don't speak Russian!
I'm gonna leave now,
and go to the Expo.
Maybe I'll even get laid.
See these guys?
They're your babysitters.
They are not to be
trifled with.
When I get back,
we're gonna renegotiate
the terms of our agreement.
And you're gonna make good
on our arrangement.
Because if you don't,
you will be exactly what
you were when I found you:
A dead man. You got that?
Maybe you can watch me on TV.
[door opens]
[chuckles]
[Tony] Dummy. You.
Can we clean up this mess?
- You're killing me.
- [Jarvis] Incoming call
with a blocked number, sir.
My phone privileges
are reinstated. Lovely.
Coulson, how's the
Land of Enchantment?
[Ivan] Hey, Tony,
how you doing? [laughs]
- I double cycle.
- What?
You told me double cycles,
more power.
- Good advice.
- You sound pretty
sprightly for a dead guy.
You, too. [laughs]
- Trace him.
- [Jarvis] Sir.
Now, the true history of
Stark name will be written.
Jarvis, where is he?
[Jarvis] Accessing
the Oracle grid.
Eastern seaboard.
What your father did
to my family over 40 years,
I will do to you
in 40 minutes.
Sounds good. Let's get
together and hash it out.
[Jarvis] Tri-state area.
Manhattan and
outlying boroughs.
I hope you're ready.
[dial tone]
[Jarvis] Call trace incomplete.
- [Jarvis] Sir!
- You want to run
some tests, run them.
And assemble the suit
while you're at it.
- We are unclear
as to the effects...
-I don't want to hear it!
[exhales, coughs]
Ah! That tastes like coconut...
...and metal.
Oh, wow, yeah!
- I'll keep the car down here.
- Thank you, Happy.
[PA] Justin Hammer's
presentation will begin
shortly in the main pavilion.
[applause]
[♪ Average White Band:
Pick Up The Pieces]
Yeah!
That's what I'm talking about.
Thanks for coming.
Ladies and gentlemen,
for far too long,
this country has had
to place its brave men
and women in harm's way.
But then
the Iron Man arrived,
and we thought
the days of losing lives
were behind us.
Sadly, that technology
was kept out of reach. That's
not fair. That's not right.
- And it's just too bad.
- Oh, Lord.
Regardless, it was
an impressive innovation,
one that grabbed
headlines the world over.
Well, today, my friends,
the press is faced with
quite a different problem.
They are about
to run out of ink.
[scattered applause]
Get that out of here.
Ladies and gentlemen,
today I present to you
the new face of the
United States military!
The Hammer drone!
- [The Caisson Go
Rolling Alongplaying]
- [applause]
[Justin] Army!
[applause]
- Navy!
- [Anchors Aweighplaying]
- Air Force!
- [The U.S. Air Forceplaying]
- Marines!
- [The Marine Hymnplaying]
[Justin] Yeah! Yeah!
Whoo!
That's a hell of a lot
better than some cheerleaders.
Let me tell you.
But as revolutionary
as this technology is,
there will always be a need
for man to be present
in the theater of war.
Ladies and gentlemen, today
I am proud to present to you
the very first prototype in
the Variable Threat
Response Battlesuit
and its pilot,
Air Force Lieutenant
Colonel James Rhodes!
- [applause]
- What?
For America and its allies,
Hammer Industries
is reporting for...
[rumbling]
[applause, cheering]
[Tony] We've got trouble.
[James] Tony, there are
civilians present.
I'm here on orders.
- Let's not do this right now.
- Give them a wave.
- [Justin] Hey, all right! Yeah!
- [Tony] These people
are in danger.
You got to get them
out of here. Trust me
for the next five minutes.
I tried that. I got
tossed around your house.
- I think he's working
with Vanko.
- Vanko's alive?
- [Justin] Huh? Yeah!
- [Tony] Where is he?
- What?
- Where's Vanko?
- Who?
- Tell me.
What are you
doing here, man?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Is that you?
- [James] I'm not doing that.
That's not me. I can't move.
I'm locked up! I'm locked up!
Get out of here! Go!
The system's compromised!
- [crowd screaming]
- [Tony] Let's take it outside.
[screaming]
No. No!
- Jarvis, break in.
I need to own him.
- [Jarvis] Yes, sir.
Tony, I'm locked on.
I have target lock.
- On what?
- On you!
[James] Tony, on your six!
- What's going on?
- The software's
been overridden.
What? What do you mean
it's been overridden?
- He slaved the drones.
- That's impossible.
- Call the guards.
- The phones are down.
- Then call their cells.
- Cell phones
not working, either.
- He locked us out
of the mainframe.
- Who locked you out?
Please, please. Go away.
I've got this handled.
- Have you now?
- Yes, I do!
In fact, if your guy
hadn't showed up,
this wouldn't be happening.
So please go away! Thank you.
We gotta get
these bitches out of here.
- Ah!
- [Pepper yelps]
Tell me who's behind this.
Who's behind this?!
Ivan. Ivan.
Ivan. Ivan Vanko.
- Where is he?
- He's at my facility.
- I need NYPD, please.
Command Central.
- No, no, no!
- No, no, honey.
Don't call the authorities!
- Right away.
Step aside! Step aside.
Tell me everything
you know. Go.
- How we doing, Jarvis?
- Remote reboot unsuccessful.
[screaming]
Nobody's answering the phone!
What's going on?
Get in the car. Take me
to Hammer Industries.
- I'm not taking you anywhere.
- You want me to drive?
No, I'm driving.
Get in the car!
[screaming]
Nice work, kid.
[James] You got multiples
coming in on you.
Let's get this
away from the Expo.
When we arrive, I need you
to watch the perimeter.
I'm gonna enter the facility
and take down the target.
- [horn honking]
- [tires screeching]
- Watch the road.
- I got it.
[car alarm blaring]
[multiple car alarms blaring]
Listen, listen.
A pack just peeled off,
headed back to the Expo.
Got it.
I'm closing on you! Ordinance
coming in hot, Tony! Watch it!
- Stay in the car.
- I'm not staying in the car.
- I said, stay in the car.
- What are you wearing?
I'm not letting you
go in there alone.
- [door beeps]
- You want to help?
- Keep the car running.
- OK.
[alarm blaring]
Hey, you can't come in here!
[guard] Hold on! Hey!
[guard yelling]
[grunting]
Each set of drones
is communicating
in its own unique language.
Well, choose one
and focus on that.
Have you tried Russian?
Try Russian.
[grunting]
[indistinct radio chatter]
Ah!
[screaming]
I got him!
- You still locked on?
- Yeah.
Drop your socks and
grab your Crocs. We're about
to get wet on this ride.
Wait, wait, wait!
[Romanoff] He's gone!
Sorry, buddy.
Had to thin out the herd.
What's your 20?
- What are you doing?
- I'm rebooting Rhodey's suit.
Tony!
Reboot complete.
You got your best friend back.
Thank you very much,
Agent Romanoff.
Well done with
the new chest piece.
I'm reading higher output and
your vitals all look promising.
Yes, for the moment,
I'm not dying. Thank you.
What do you mean?
Did you say you're dying?
[Tony] That you?
Uh, no, I'm not. Not anymore.
- What's going on?
- I was going to tell you...
- You really were dying?!
- You didn't let me.
- Why didn't you tell me?!
- I was gonna make you
an omelet and tell you!
Hey, hey, save it for the
honeymoon. You got incoming.
The fight's coming to you.
- Great. Pepper?
- [Pepper] Are you OK now?
- I'm fine. Don't be mad.
I will formally apologize...
- I am mad.
...when I'm not fending
off a Hammeroid attack!
- Fine. - We could have been in Venice.
Oh, please.
Snap out of it, buddy.
I need you.
They're coming.
Let's go. Get up.
Oh, man,
you can have your suit back.
- You OK?
- Yeah, thanks.
- Tony, look, I'm sorry. OK?
- Don't be.
- No, I should have trusted you.
- I put you in this position.
Forget it.
No, it's your fault,
I just wanted to say I'm sorry.
Thank you. That's all
I wanted to hear.
Partner.
They're coming in hot.
Any second.
What's the play?
We wanna take the high ground.
Let's put the biggest gun
up on that ridge.
Gotcha.
- Where do you wanna be?
- Where you going?
What are you talking about?
You have a big gun.
- You are not the big gun.
- Tony, don't be jealous.
- The bells and whistles.
- It's called being a badass.
Fine.
All right, you go up top.
I'll draw them in.
Don't stay down here.
This is the worst place to be.
- OK, you got a spot...
- It's the kill box, Tony.
- This is where you go to die.
- [explosion]
[beeping]
- See that?
- Yeah, nice.
[Tony] Rhodey?
Get down!
Wow. I think you should
lead with that next time.
Yeah, sorry, boss.
I can only use it once.
It's a one-off.
I told you that
five minutes ago.
- That's your guy here.
- Excuse me?
- We're gonna place
you under arrest.
- Are you kidding.
- Hands behind your back.
- I'm trying to help here.
[laughs] I get it.
I see what you're doing.
You're trying
to pin this on me, huh?
That's good. That's good.
You're starting to think
like a CEO. Taking out
the competition.
I like that. Think you're
making a problem for me?
I'm gonna make a problem
for you. I'll see you
again real soon.
When they get here,
station them at the southeast
and both west exits.
We shut down the 7 train
in and out of Willets Point.
Have city buses there
to ferry people
to operating lines.
- Yeah. Coming with us?
- No, I'm gonna stay
till the park is clear.
OK.
[Romanoff] Heads up, you got
one more drone incoming.
This one looks different.
Repulsor signature's
significantly higher.
[engine roaring]
Good to be back.
[James] This ain't
gonna be good.
I got something special
for this guy.
I'm gonna bust his bunker
with the Ex-Wife.
With the what?
[beeping]
- Hammer Tech?
- [James] Yeah.
I got this.
[grunting]
[Tony yelling]
[grunts]
Ah!
[Tony] Rhodes!
I got an idea.
- Wanna be a hero?
- What?
[Tony] I could really
use a sidekick!
- Put your hand up!
- This is your idea?
- Yep.
- I'm ready! Go, go, go!
Finish him!
You lose.
[beeping]
[rapid beeping]
All these drones
are rigged to blow.
- We gotta get
out of here, man!
- Pepper?
[beeping]
Oh!
[Pepper screams]
[grunting]
Oh, my God! I can't
take this anymore!
- [Tony] You can't?
- I can't take this.
- Look at me!
- My body literally
cannot handle the stress.
I never know if you're gonna
kill yourself or wreck
the whole company!
I think I did OK!
I quit. I'm resigning.
- That's it.
- What did you just say?
You're done?
Surprising.
No, it's not surprising.
I get it. You don't have
to make any excuses.
I'm... I'm not
making excuses.
- You actually were
just making excuses.
- I wasn't.
- I'm actually very justified.
- You deserve better.
- Well...
- You've taken
such good care of me.
Been in a tough spot.
You got me through it.
- So... right?
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Thank you for understanding.
Yeah, let's talk clean up.
- I'll handle the transition...
- What about the press?
You only had the job
for a week.
- With you,
it's like dog years.
- I know.
It's like the president...
Weird.
- No, it's not weird.
- It's OK?
- Yeah.
- OK. Try it again.
[James]
I think it was weird.
You guys look like two seals
fighting over a grape.
- I had just quit.
- Yes. We're not...
You don't have to do that.
I heard the whole thing.
- You should get lost.
- I was here first.
Get a roof.
- [chuckles] I thought
you were out of one-liners.
- That was the last one.
- You kicked ass back there.
- [James] Thank you. You, too.
Listen, my car got taken out
in the explosions.
So I'm gonna have to hang on
to your suit for a minute, OK?
Not OK. Not OK with that.
It wasn't a question.
How you gonna resign?
- I don't understand.
- [laughs]
I don't think I want you
looking at that.
I'm not sure it
pertains to you anymore.
Now, this,
on the other hand,
is Agent Romanoff's
assessment of you.
Read it.
Uh...
"Personality review.
Mr. Stark displays
compulsive behavior."
In my own defense,
that was last week.
"Prone to self-destructive
tendencies." I was dying.
I mean, please.
And aren't we all?
"Textbook narcissism."
Agreed.
OK, here it is. Uh...
"Recruitment assessment
for Avenger Initiative.
Iron Man, yes."
I gotta think about it.
Read on.
"Tony Stark not...
not recommended?"
That didn't make any sense.
How can you approve me,
but not approve me?
I got a new ticker,
I'm trying to do right
by, uh, Pepper.
I'm in a stable-ish
relationship.
Which leads us to believe
at this juncture,
we'd only like to use you
as a consultant.
You can't afford me.
Then again, I will waive
my customary retainer
in exchange for...
a small favor.
Rhodey and I are being
honored in Washington,
and we need a presenter.
I'll see what I can do.
It is my honor
to be here today
to present these distinguished
awards to Lieutenant Colonel
James Rhodes
and Mr. Tony Stark,
who is, of course,
a national treasure.
[♪ AC/DC: Highway To Hell]
Thank you, lieutenant colonel,
for such an exceptionally
distinguished performance.
- You deserve this.
- Thank you, sir.
Mr. Stark, thank you
for such an exceptionally
distinguished performance.
- You deserve this.
- Ow!
Oh, sorry.
Funny how annoying
a little prick can be, isn't it?
Let's get a photo.
♪ Living easy, living free
♪ Season ticket
on a one-way ride ♪
♪ Asking nothing
Leave me be ♪
♪ Taking everything
in my stride ♪
♪ Don't need reason
Don't need rhyme ♪
♪ Ain't nothing
I would rather do ♪
♪ Going down
Party time ♪
♪ My friends
are gonna be there too ♪
♪ I'm on the highway to hell
♪ On the highway to hell
♪ Highway to hell
♪ I'm on the highway to hell
♪ No stop signs
Speed limit ♪
♪ Nobody's gonna slow me down
♪ Like a wheel
Gonna spin it ♪
♪ Nobody's gonna
mess me around ♪
♪ Hey, Satan
Paid my dues ♪
♪ Playing in
a rocking band ♪
♪ Hey, Mama
Look at me ♪
♪ I'm on my way
to the promised land ♪
♪ I'm on the highway to hell
♪ Highway to hell
♪ Don't stop me
♪ Hey, hey
♪ I'm on the highway to hell
♪ Highway to hell
♪ And I'm going down
♪ All the way
♪ Whoa
♪ On the highway to hell ♪
[♪ Make Way
for Tomorrow Today ]
♪ Oh, a bright
new morning is dawning ♪
♪ Make way for tomorrow today
♪ Yes, a new tomorrow's
a-borning ♪
♪ To light up a brave new day
♪ Oh, the future is
brimming with promise ♪
♪ And that promise
is heading our way ♪
♪ So keep your eyes
on that shining horizon ♪
♪ Make way for tomorrow today
♪ Daring new devices
will help us to succeed ♪
♪ Better tools for living
will meet our every need ♪
♪ Incredible inventions
through new technology ♪
♪ Extending life's dimensions
for all humanity ♪
♪ Oh, the marvels
rising around us ♪
♪ Bringing progress
and dazzling display ♪
♪ So keep your eyes
on that shining horizon ♪
♪ Make way
for tomorrow today ♪
♪ Make way for tomorrow
♪ Today ♪
Sir, we found it.
[thunder cracks]