Please, Jackie?
I need it for school.
Mm-mmm.
Nobody believes me
about the talismans,
but if I show them some
super-rabbit speed...
A talisman
is not a toy, Jade.
Come on, Jackie.
You were a kid once.
Didn't you ever want to be
the big chan on campus?
Yes, I did.
And this is the scar
I have to show for it.
I don't want you
getting hurt, too.
So no showing off.
But as long
as I don't show off,
I can still
borrow it, right?
See you
after school. Bye!
Jackie'll never even
notice it's--
Jackie: Jade? Jade!
Whah!
Jade, did you just
- intercept my chronoton beam?
Me, kepler?
No.
Can't have you disrupting
the time continuum.
Heh heh.
Baah!
- There you are.
You forgot your lunch.
Heh! Thanks.
Whew! And she's safe.
Ah! I wish
we hadn't lost
that speed talisman.
I wish chan
was never born.
I wish one of them
talismans
would come to us
for a change.
¶ Boom chicka-chicka
boom-boom chicka-chicka ¶
¶ boom uhh ¶
I wish I had
a million bucks.
¶ Boom chicka-chicka ¶
¶ boom-boom
chicka-chicka boom ¶
(gasps)
I'm late!
(All grumble)
Sparks? Since when
are there...
Whoa.
Aaaaaaaah!
Uhh!
Ok...
That was weird.
Hey, miss hartman,
sorry I'm--
ha ha ha ha ha!
What are you
wearing?
Ahem.
Are you in the right
classroom, young lady?
Miss hartman,
it's me.
Jade chan. Nice do.
Chan. Of course.
Class, Jade
is the new student
we've been expecting.
I am?
Now, let's start
with current events.
Who watched
president Carter's
speech on TV--
new student?
Bell-bottoms?
President who?
What is going--
(Gasps)
1976?
I'm not late for class.
I'm early. Way early.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I'm your new student,
Jackie chan.
No way.
Another chan?
Are you two related?
B-b-b-bathroom.
What did you do?
You're the speed talisman,
not the talisman-
that-sends-you-back-
in-time talisman.
The beam.
Kepler said I was messing
with the time something-uum.
Well, whatever you did,
I'm gonna reverse it, fast.
Hmm?
Rrrrr!
Come oooooon!
Pet rocks,
mood rings.
Get 'em while
they're now, baby.
Ohh...I'm stuck
in the seventies.
So, she speeds off,
and then, zappo--
she's gone.
It was freaky, big v,
left behind some kind
of energy hole.
Energy hole? Zappo?
A crude description,
valmont.
But I indeed sense
a wrinkle in time.
The child has used
the speed talisman
to forge a tunnel
to the past.
And if shendu's rabbit
dug a hole,
all you idiots
have to do to secure
the talisman
is go through that hole.
But tunnels through time
flow only in one direction.
If you wish them
to return,
they will require this.
So, uh, just
how far back does this
tunnel thingy go?
We talking
dinosaurs?
I don't care if it
leads to the big bang,
you buffoons!
Just bring me
that talisman.
(Telephone rings)
Hello?
Jackie, you are
a terrible guardian!
Uncle?
Jade's teacher phoned.
She is skipping
school.
One more thing:
These kinds of things
never happened
when I was raising you!
They certainly didn't.
Kepler, have you
seen Jade--aah!
Same beam
almost fried Jade.
Maybe I should
move the emitter.
Uhh! Maybe?
This is a safety hazard!
My chronoton beam
is not a hazard.
If anyone
were to be exposed,
this scanner
would reveal...
A trail
of particles...
Leading out
of the lab.
And straight to Jade.
Bell-bottoms. Uck!
That's so nineties!
I got to find
a way home, fast!
Can not!
Can so!
Can not. Nobody
can jump this fence.
It's too tall.
I can. Watch.
Hyuh...Aah--
- gotcha!
Whoa! Ohh!
Where did you
come from?
Ha ha!
Evel knievel
wannabe.
Both: Ha ha ha ha ha!
You ok?
Didn't hurt
yourself, did you?
I'm just
very embarrassed.
My scar...
What scar?
Exactly.
I really will
be able to jump
that fence someday.
Oh, I believe you.
I'm learning kung fu.
My parents sent me
to America
so I can train
with my uncle.
Uncle! Why didn't
I think of that?
Whoa!
- Come on!
I don't know
about this.
Enter.
No way! There could be
raptors or t-rexes.
I'm not your
Guinea piiiii--
if there are dinosaurs,
they will be busy
eating Finn.
Whoa!
(All shout)
Ow! Oof!
Finn: Get down.
Get funky.
It's the seventies.
The talisman is near.
(Gasps)
How did you know
where I live?
Whoa! What are these?
8-track tapes.
But where
are the antiques?
While I wish to trade
in ancient treasures,
8-track is the wave
of the future.
How did you know
about antiques?
Because I'm Jade chan,
your niece,
and I need your expert
magic advice!
Magic?
Oh...Guess you don't
study with chi master fong
for another few years.
The talisman.
Shouldn't
you guys be, like,
9 years old?
Jackie, go to your room.
Whoa. It's chan,
but bite-size.
And if we off him
when he's little...
He'll never
get big.
Destroy him.
(Gasps)
Bad day.
All: Rrrah!
Hyuh!
Ahh...Hyuh!
Hyoo-wuh!
Huhh!
Whoa. Jackie gets it
all from uncle.
Of course I do.
He trains me.
Hyah-ha! Whoa.
Run!
Wah...Haa!
You will pay for that!
All: Ow! Oh! Ow! Ooh! Hey!
What's that?
My lucky rabbit's foot.
The talisman.
Sorry.
We'll bring them back.
Thank you!
What are you
doing--aah!
Jackie: Bwaaah!
(All sigh)
What are we
gonna do?
If we go back
empty-handed,
valmont's
gonna freak.
Ooh! Valmont!
He'd know what to do.
Let's find him
and ask him.
Earth to ratso.
It's 1976.
Valmont is a kid,
a British kid.
He's not gonna be
in San Francisco.
Bingo.
What do  you buffoons want?
Wow. That's him,
all right.
What are you doing
in America?
(Scoffs)
I'm an exchange
student,
and I won't
be harassed
by American
salesmen.
Who sent you people?
Uh, you did.
See, it's like this,
little v.
We're not salesmen.
We're from the future.
Impossible.
My particles couldn't
make a wormhole
unless Jade was moving
at unthinkable speed.
But this
is definitely a bridge
in the time continuum.
Jade's either
in the future,
or she's...
In the past!
My scar! Oh, Jade's
changing the past,
my past!
Careful. One-way trip.
But if Jade's
in the past,
the future could be
in big trouble.
Slow down!
Please, slow down!
Think we ditched 'em.
Ditched who?
Why are those men after me?
What's that rabbit thing?
How can you run so fast?
What's going on?
Ok. Here's the deal.
I'm from the future.
You're my uncle.
The talisman's magic.
The dark hand
is after it.
And now they want
to get rid of you
so they won't
have to fight you
when you grow up.
Get it?
That's crazy, Jade.
You're crazy.
Do I really grow up
to be a criminal
mastermind?
Uh-huh.
Well, then, I say
we kidnap the old man
and use a ransom note
to lure this chan
into an ambush.
Uh, that's the plan
you used the first time
we met chan.
And it didn't
work then.
Then might I suggest
you leave him...
To me.
Sir! Come quickly!
Your nephew needs help!
Jackie?
Where is he?
Uhh...Ohh...
My first act
of mega-villainy.
This is exhilarating.
Coast is clear.
Come on.
Uncle's probably
worried sick.
Jackie: Hello?
Uncle? Hello?
(Gasps)
The dark hand's
got uncle!
We have
to rescue him.
I have to rescue him.
If they get
their hands on you,
it'll mess up the future.
And if uncle is harmed,
it will mess up my future.
Jade! Jade?
Oh! The dark hand's
got uncle!
What are they doing here?
Mmm...Mmm...Mmm...
Mmm...
So, uh, what if
your host parents
come home,
little big v?
I will simply
assure them
this is all
part of some
sort of
social studies
project
for school.
Hey!
Ooh!
Hwuh! Uhh!
Argh!
Gah!
- Eeg!
Unh! Uhh!
Raarrr!
Mmm-mmm!
Whoa!
Bah-hah!
Whew!
What's with
the crystal ball?
I'm coming, uncle!
Jade: Jackie!
Ohh!
Ready to rewrite
history, little chan?
Noooooooo....
(Blubbers)
Help! Help!
Jackie hasn't learned
how to swim yet?
Hang on, Jack--
the talisman.
Unh! Let go!
(Chokes, sputters)
(Pants)
Oh! Oh...
Bad day.
(Chokes)
(Choking)
Oh! Let me go! Uhh!
Hand over
the talisman.
Fetch!
Jackie! Say something!
(Coughs)
(Gasps)
That'll do.
How come no one
invited me...
To the pool party?
How 'bout
we just go home
with the talisman?
Valmont:
You can't leave me!
I'm your boss!
You got to be
kidding me.
The talisman.
It's magic.
Uh-huh. Give me
a hand, Jackie.
Coming.
- Coming.
Aah!
- Aah!
Bah!
- Bah!
Are you...
You are!
I have to break up
the lovefest,
but the bad guys said
they're going home!
Which means
they can go home.
Must be that
crystal ball thing.
You mean this?
I took it from the man
who grabbed me.
I'm telling you,
I didn't lose it!
Lose what, you buffoons?
Jade: This.
Rrrrrr!
Ooh-hoo!
Ooh.
(Kids chatter)
Give me that!
Hyah-gaah!
Everybody
- is kung fu fighting.
Hyuh!
Hyuh! Uhh! Uhh!
(Kids cheer)
¶ I got
the boogie fever ¶
¶ uh, uh ¶
¶ I got the fever ¶
¶ I, uh, got the fever ¶
(kids cheer)
Where'd tohru go
with the--
(gasps)
Jackie!
I can see the future.
Huh?
Wet willies!
Ooh!
Big me, catch!
Tohru: Chan!
Get off me!
The crystal, or you'll have
an unhappy childhood.
Let him go,
or he will, too!
Do as he says.
Please.
Hold it.
Chan wouldn't hurt a kid,
not even mini-valmont.
Ohh...
Jackie
wouldn't...
But I would!
Do it,
and no one leaves.
No!
(Gasps)
Wait!
Uh-oh.
We'll be stranded!
(Kids cheer)
But I don't want
to go back! I don't
want to go back!
You may have won
today, chan.
But we will
meet again, and--
hyah!
Aah!
Jackie, it looks
like you'll have
a very interesting
future.
With a very
odd niece.
One more thing:
Did she say
anything else
about my future
in antiques?
Uhh! Unh! Grr-grr!
Uh-oh.
The old days.
Time continuum's
good as new.
But I still can't
figure out
how you made
a wormhole
without going
supersonic.
I did go supersonic.
See, the rabbit talisman
has magic powers, and--
(chuckles)
Magic powers.
I'll prove it!
Hey, Jackie,
can I borrow the--
heh. Never mind.
What is taking them
so long?
(Old man's voice)
Yo, big v.
We, uh, took
the long way home.
So, uh,
you can change us
back, right?
Interviewer:
Hey, Jackie...
Were you cool
when you were a kid?
All the kids
in the school--
they didn't like me.
I remember we testing,
uh, the skill
in the school.
One by one,
you'd do a somersault,
do different tricks
to pass the test.
They all push me.
They go first.
I'm the last one.
What I'm gonna do?
Everybody
do somersault--shoo!
Shoo! Shoo!
I go out, I do one
somersault like this.
That low. My nose
just touch the ground.
Then the teacher,
"oh, good."
So, I think, "I'm cool."