(Gasps) Ah!
Is it Halloween
already?
You forgot, didn't you?
Tonight's the school play.
I'm Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde!
It's my big debut!
Oh, I am sorry, Jade,
bu the university
asked uncle and me
to explore
the subterranean city
underneath the streets.
Uh-huh.
No, it's true.
A recent tremor
has opened a passageway
to parts of San Francisco
which have been buried
since the 1906 earthquake.
Another tremor may
collapse the passageway
at any moment,
so there's not much time.
But...My play.
Oh, I am sorry.
I would rather
see your play,
but I have to
do this now.
And I cannot be
in 2 places
at the same time.
Uh, that's ok.
I understand.
Your work
is pretty important.
Huh?
Why do I need
the tiger talisman?
2 jackies can be
in 2 places at once.
(Stretching) Ahh!
All right!
The tiger is free.
Free to be me!
Ahh!
You know how lame it is
being trapped
in the same body with him?
Oh, no!
This is a big mistake!
We should not be
2 jackies.
See what I mean?
Outta my way--pussycat!
I am very disappointed
in you, Jade.
You know that playing
with magic is a no-no.
Ha! A no-no?
Oh, no!
Say it ain't so!
We should turn ourselves
back into one Jackie
right away.
Not gonna happen.
Uncle: Jackie,
open the door!
This bag is heavy!
Uncle! He will
agree with me.
No! He'll see you guys!
Open up!
Uncle is not
in a mood for games!
(Doorknob rattles)
Uncle: Jackie!
Where is Jackie?
I thought I heard him.
Um...He's packing.
So, uncle, did you
pick up my cape
from the klean-o-Max?
Cape? What cape?
Tch! The school play!
If I don't have a cape,
my big debut
will be ruined!
I'll be ruined!
Everything
will be ruined!
Ok, ok! You are
making my brain hurt.
Tell Jackie to be ready
for our journey
when I return.
Deal.
Nice save, jadester.
Our journey?
Uncle's going
underground, too?
Isn't anyone
gonna come see me be
Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde?
I would love to!
Oh, the theater,
the theater!
Uh-oh. No way I'm
showing up at school
with him.
I know exactly
how you feel.
Good! Come on!
Huh? But what about me?
Uncle: Jackie!
You are still
not ready?
We are going
to go now!
And why did you
not tell me
that you already
picked up Jade's
cape?
I have no idea what
you are talking about.
(Gasp)
A city
suspended in time.
"The bizzaritorium"?
I have read about
this place.
It is a museum
of strange things
from around the world.
Oof. Excuse me--
I'm free...
To be me!
Amazing.
Simply amazing!
Uncle!
What was that?!
"Spring-heel Jack."
Throughout history,
there have been many tales
of a ravenous troll
who could leap
great distances.
The founder of this museum,
Simon magus,
must have used magic
to capture the creature.
And now he is loose!
I'm so sorry, uncle!
I will put
the Jack back,
right away!
Wha-ha!
Yoo-hoo!
Mr. spring-heel Jack!
Excuse me!
I must ask you
to return to the museum.
Simon magus
tried to stop me.
He gave me quite a run.
But I shall dine
on his descendants
one by one by...One.
Aah!
(Sniffing)
Are you helping magus?
A relative, perhaps?
(Sniff sniff)
No. I guess the two of you
are just a pair of saps.
Uncle,
are you all right?
Do not worry
about me.
Worry about
the magus family.
They are
in grave danger.
And so...
Dr. Jekyll believed
that he could separate
the good from the evil
in man.
(Softly)
Nice read, Simone.
With this potion,
I will prove
my scientific theories
to the world!
But what if I'm wrong?
Heavens! The results
could be disastrous!
Come on, doc!
Pick up the pace!
Turn into Mr. Hyde
and terrorize
the town already!
(Softly)
You think you could
do better?
Don't mind if I do.
(Coughs and gags)
This tastes terrible.
(Gagging)
I shouldn't have
brought the tiger.
Spring-heel Jack:
Ha ha ha ha ha!
(Sniffing)
Magus, magus,
wherever you are,
spring-heel Jack
will not be far.
Ah hah hah hah hah!
Do not worry!
He's just, uh...
My dog!
Well, that's
one ugly dog.
(Sniff sniff sniff)
Jackie,
do something!
Foolish mortals.
You won't capture me...
Which is more than can
be said for either of thee!
Spring-heel Jack
needs a time-out.
(Audience laughing)
Simone: Um, uh...Dr. Jekyll
wanted to be good,
but he soon lost
control of himself
to his evil side,
uh, Mr. Hyde!
This potion is wonderful!
Evil Hyde is much cooler
than old goody-goody
Jekyll! Ha ha ha!
(Audience laughs)
Uh, Jade, isn't that
your uncle?
Uh...Maybe.
(Cell phone rings)
Jade, I accidentally
released an evil troll
named spring-heel Jack.
Cool!
And he attacked
uncle and me
and trapped us
in a phone booth!
Not cool.
Spring-heel Jack
is planning to destroy
innocent people.
We must stop him!
Don't worry.
I'll get the tiger.
Psst! Tiger!
Uncle and the, uh,
pussycat need your help.
Sorry. I'm busy
with my big debut.
(Singsong) Ok...
But you're gonna miss out
on some butt-kicking action
all over an evil troll.
Hmm. Evil troll?
Big debut...
Evil troll...
(Muttering in audience)
I'm on my way,
brother.
Stay here.
Simone...
(Whispering)
Due to some, uh,
technical difficulties,
we'll be taking
a short intermission.
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you!
Yuck!
2 jackies?
How long did you plan
to keep this secret?
I was not born
yesterday!
Listen, unc.
We don't have time
for long-winded lectures.
Where's the evil troll?
Crowd: Oh! Aah! Oh, look!
He went that way.
2 jackies equals
one big headache!
Aah!
Oh, no!
(Whimpering)
(Sniffing)
Stop your whining.
No need to bawl.
You're not a magus
after all.
Hee-uhh!
Your head,
it must be very thick
if you think I'll fall
from just one kick.
Catchy.
(Crack, crack)
Excuse me,
Mr. spring-heel
Jack?
Why don't we
sit down and talk
about this
like gentlemen?
Back so soon?
How can it be?
Your clothes
aren't even watery.
Oh!
Aah!
Do you enjoy
being a meanie?
I'll confess...Yes!
Miss me?
There are 2 of you?
This could be trouble.
Perhaps I'm only
seeing double!
(Groans)
Sorry!
Jade: Need a hand?
I thought you were
at the play.
Emergency intermission.
I couldn't miss a chance
to see  the tiger
àin action!
Ok.
Not ok!
Jade!
Oh! Uncle!
It's all my fault!
I snuck into section 13!
I took the tiger talisman.
I hid the halves
in a potted plant. I--
save the acting
for your play.
Deal. So what's the plan?
Help me find a net.
Spring-heel Jack
will be the winner
when I have the maguses
for dinner!
(Sniffs) Almost there.
No--wait!
Correction--(Sniff sniff)
A pure-blooded magus
in this direction!
Wait. Wait...
Now!
No nets or chains
or heavy locks
will put this Jack
back in its box!
Imprisoned for a century,
but now I'm free,
free to be me!
Buddy,
I know exactly
how you feel.
You do, do you?
Can this be true?
Magus sounds like
a real party pooper
just like
some people I know.
I was trapped, too,
but now that I'm free,
I want to stay free
to be  me!
Hmm...You're just
like me.
And it would seem
that you and I
should be a team!
What's in it for me?
Fame, fortune, fun!
Done!
This is terrible!
My dark side
has gone over to...
The dark side!
Spring-heel:
I smell a magus
to the east.
It won't be long
before we feast!
Enough is enough!
We need to reunite
the jackies.
I will return
with the tiger talisman.
(Panting)
Brother!
This is not right!
You should not
be helping
spring-heel Jack!
Dude just wants
to be free--like me!
But he's a really bad,
um, Jack-thing,
and you're--
cool?
Not anymore.
Me, not cool?
Cool people
don't help creeps.
At least that's what
all the cool people
think.
Then that's what
I think, too!
Hel-lo!
(Sniff sniff)
The magus soon
will be in sight,
and we'll consume them
bite by bite.
Forget the  we, Jack.
You're on your own!
Now, now.
What's this
you're telling me?
You'd rather
be my enemy?
Whatever.
That was cool!
Unsuccessful,
but cool.
Ok, bro.
Let's show this troll
what 2 jackies can do.
Follow those jackies!
Stay calm.
Just makin' a movie.
Oh!
Driver: Oof!
Aah!
Number one
and number 2,
I've had enough
of both of you.
There's only one
direction to go
to catch
this jumping Jack.
Which way is that?
Up.
Go, jackies!
Roll the troll!
Oopsie.
End of the line.
Aah!
(Commotion, screams)
(Sniffing)
At last,
- a magus is in sight,
and I shall quench
my appetite.
Aah!
Spring-heel Jack?
My mama told me about you,
but I thought
it was just a story.
A story, yes,
but it's all true.
I'm real,
and I've come
for you!
Aah!
Spring-heel Jack
is after Simone?
(Gasps)
Simone magus!
Big giant duh!
Fiddle-Dee-Dee.
The girl belongs
to me!
Finders keepers.
Losers weepers.
You're the ones
who will be weeping.
I'm the one who'll
do the keeping!
Uncle!
Fee, fi, fo, fum.
Can you two
really be this dumb?
Jackies! Catch!
All is fine.
The magus is mine.
That's not all
that's yours.
Huh?
Uh-oh.
I hope we didn't
frighten you
by acting so ferocious.
Please forgive
my other self.
His manners
are atrocious!
This child must be
made to pay
for what magus did
that fateful day.
Your sweet revenge
has just been soured.
I will not let her
be devoured.
No, no, no!
You cannot go!
(Clunk)
Jackies, help!
You! The nice one.
Tell us how to stop
your darker side.
Bind his legs
so he will halt.
Then hit him
with a pinch of salt.
Ah! Salt I have.
Boy, talk about
convenient.
Simone, hide in here!
Brother, help!
It's up to you!
No, we must be one,
not 2.
I can assist with that.
A curse upon
my lighter side.
He told the secret
I would hide!
Without him,
you'd have never known
that salt will turn me
back to--
stone.
Tiger, we must
reunite.
For once,
I think you may be right.
I am me again!
I am back!
And, ohh...
My aching back.
Jade: Jack is back!
Don't forget, Jackie.
You promised
to come see me
in the final performance
of  Jekyll and Hyde
àtomorrow.
Oh, Jade! I'm so sorry.
But I will be very busy
writing up my research
on the underground city,
and I cannot be
in 2 places at--
I will be there.
Hey, Jackie,
what kind of movies
do you like to see?
When I'm young,
I like only
one kind of movie--action.
But now I become familiar.
I like drama.
I like American film,
Indian film,
Iran, Iraq film,
uh, Germany film.
I have to look every film.
What is the bad things,
what is the good things--
I have to know.
There's so many...
Good director around
the world
we just not introduced.
If you like movie,
you should watch
every film--
cheap film,
expensive film,
any kind of film.