Jackie: If the Hana fuda
cards are correct,
then the next  oni mask...
Has gotta be...There!
Where is card indicating
mask removal ingredient?
Right here, unc.
Whoop--
aiyaa!
(All gasp)
Whew!
Snatched from the jaws
of defeat.
Whoa!
Well, at least you guys
got a good look
at the ingredient
on the card...Right?
Heh heh.
No removal ingredient?
No problem.
We just make mega-sure
no one wears the mask
this time. Right?
(Gasp)
Dark magic
resides here.
Quickly, we must
find mask before--
hey, wait a sec.
I've seen this place...
On TV!
We're in miss Kimber's
psychic shack.
Miss who's
psychic what?
Miss Kimber,
from the psychic hot line.
Duh.
Pfft!
No one can see future.
All psychics are--
phonies?
Ha ha ha ha ha.
I knew you was gonna
say that.
Whoa!
She's good!
A cheap trick.
Fortune teller
saw us approach.
Hmm. But she's
very skilled
dollmaker.
You are here
for the mask, hmm?
(Gasp) How do you
know this?
The boy's not too quick
on the uptake, huh?
I'm psychic, hon.
Ho ho ho.
Then I guess you knew
we'd be taking it.
Thank you.
Hmm.
The stars don't say
you take it, sugar.
He does.
Jackie, Jade: Hak foo?
(Scoffs)
Stars do not talk.
Hak foo:
So  that is the mask...
Destined for my face.
Jackie, take mask!
I knew he was going
to say that, too.
Whoa!
Whoo! Aah! Oh!
Oh, sorry. Aah!
Jade: Faster, Jackie,
he's gaining!
Jade! This is...
Dangerous?
Hey, I must be psychic.
And what do you think
you're whipping up, sugar?
If you can truly
see future,
you would know
uncle is devising
removal spell
in case mask is worn
by hak foo.
Only...Uncle
must learn
of missing
key ingredient.
(Gasp) You hear that?
The stars are talking.
And they say you can have
the answer you seek
revealed by yours truly
for only 9.95 a minute.
(Gasp)
You are fraud...
And money grubber!
Unh!
Whoa!
All hands on deck!
Hyah!
Unh! Unh!
Whoa!
Uhh!
Hyah!
Aah! Ooh!
Uh, not too much
off the top, please.
Let him go!
Uh, Jade,
who is steering?
Uh-oh.
And here is prediction
for you:
I see piece of uncle
in your future!
Whenever you're done, hon,
you're gonna want to scooch
a tad to the left.
(Boat approaching)
Whoa!
Aah!
Unh!
Oh!
Whoa! Unh!
Mud slide!
(Groaning)
Jade, where is
the mask?
At last!
Uh...Found it.
And now, chans,
prepare to meet
the fiercest tribe
of shadowkhan yet--
mine.
Demon summons
ninja army!
(Both gasp)
They--they are--
they are so...
Cute!
(Growling)
Demon compensates
for inferior ninja army!
Unh! Ooh!
Uhh! Uh!
No!
Aah!
Jackie, grab on!
Jackie!
I will not see you later,
alligator.
(Grumbling)
...little shrimps!
Jackie?
(Gasping for air)
Ah, Jackie,
you are trying
to find card
with mask removal
ingredient?
No, uncle.
I am trying
not to become
alligator bait!
Well, you must learn
to multi-task.
Now come.
We must research
mask removal ingre--
ah...Teeny tiny
shadowkhan.
Mmm...Milk and--
uncle: Tohru! Research!
Crumbs.
Oh...I hope
you do not mind
if we roll out
the futons.
Jade: Good night.
This is monumental.
Never before
have we captured
a shadowkhan.
It is...So cute!
Do not be deceived
by appearances.
Uncle will bring
Japanese reference book
so you can get busy.
Who knows what close study
of our captive may uncover.
(Sighs) Yes,  sensei.
(Glass jar rattles)
Cookie-eating
shadowkhan.
Huh?
My shadow!
Ohh...
Sensei.
One more thing.
Keep blowfish handy.
Cannot be
too careful with--
(thud)
(Gasp) Ooh.
(Tohru snoring)
(Glass jar clinks)
(Gasp)
(Growling)
Aiyaaa!
(Snarling)
(Gasp)
Aah!
Uncle!
(Growling)
Jackie, fire blowfish!
Uncle is waiting!
Jade: I got it!
Fish fry!
Ooh!
Tohru is in
very deep sleep.
Shadows contain our yin--
one half of our chi.
Clearly this
shadowkhan tribe
grows stronger
by feeding
upon human shadows.
And without this part
of our life force,
we are doomed
to a state of limbo.
Well, how can we get
tohru's shadow back?
We must end
hak foo's control
over his shadowkhan,
but we cannot
remove mask from him
without spell ingredient.
Hmph! Stupid gator!
And without tohru
to translate Japanese,
learning spell ingredient
will be difficult.
Well, until you do,
that shadow eater
is out there.
We must find it
before it harms
anyone else.
Ninja hunt.
Do not be foolish.
Your own shadows
are at risk.
T'ch.
If the li'l freaks
are hungry,
they can eat this!
Hyah!
Jade: Oops.
Aaah!
The way to keep
shadow eaters
from eating shadow
is to not cast one.
Now, exhale and...
Attack!
Hak foo:
- Fight like warriors!
Eye of the tiger!
How charming.
Grr! Show master tarakudo
your war faces!
Ooh. If I
had a spine,
it would
be tingling.
Grr!
Hak foo,
all shadowkhan
are deadly.
You just need
to be aware
of their strengths.
You call these strong?
I see a demonstration
is in order.
Chow: Aah!
Hello!
Kinda in the middle
of something here!
Ho ho ho.
Where'd you get
the mini-'Khan?
Grrrrr!
Uh-uh-uh-uh-uh.
Wait for it.
(Whistles)
Tarakudo: Uh, fellas?
Chow: Ha! Hey, hak,
are these guys
on loan from Santa?
Ha ha ha!
Huh?
Hey, how--
what are you--
(gasp)
Ohh. Uhh.
Growing boys need
their nutrients.
And an entire city
of shadows
awaits my army!
Uncle: Ninja-suction unit?
Check.
Chi-powered
night-vision goggles?
Check.
Hand-held
dark chi detector?
Check.
And, in case back-up
is needed...
Check!
Base potion,
in the event
uncle discovers
missing ingredient
for removal spell.
(Sigh)
Uncle will remain here
armed with
Japanese-to-Chinese
dictionary.
Let's bring tohru
back from dreamland.
(Crackling)
We found tohru's
shadow eater.
More like a new batch
of shadow eaters.
Run!
(Gasp)
Huh?
(Crackles)
Ooh! Ooh!
Bwaaa!
Whoa. Ninja swarm.
don't worry, Jackie.
No shadow, no lunch.
Uhh!
Aah! Ohh!
You've been hosed.
(Sigh)
Thank you, Jade.
"Substitute mask removal
ingredient is often
shoelace of giraffe."
Aiyaaa!
Giraffes do not wear shoes!
Jade chan, pest control.
Huh!
Huh?
My bag is full.
I'm betting
this little guy
will lead us
to the big one
who munched
tohru's shadow.
Oh!
Jade?
Uh...
Found our boy.
And he has been snacking
between meals.
Ohh!
(Growling)
I thought you were
gator food, chan.
Time to hand over
tohru's shadow.
Huh?
Jackie, he's too big!
Jade, run!
Run after tiny, right!
And stay out
of the light!
Uh, Jackie...
That may be
a problem.
Good morning, chan...
And good night.
Bear feeds on honey!
Uhh!
Uhh! Whaa!
Where is that
removal spell, uncle?
(Sighs)
Japanese translation is
not going well, tohru.
Unless ingredient
we seek is
"lobster wearing
corduroy pants."
(Softly)
Aiyaaa.
Hmm?
(Gasp)
You!
Looks like you in need
of some good fortune, sugar.
Who says uncle
needs fortune?!
Hmm?
Phone me now,
and we can fix whatever
is ailing you...
Together.
Pfft! If uncle
wanted quack,
he would phone take-out
for Peking duck!
Only  I have the answers
you seek.
Ohhh!
Oh!
Ooh!
Imagine, chan,
an army
of these creatures,
obeying my every command!
Huh! Aah!
Come on out, tiny.
don't you want to
party with your pals?
Whoa!
Unh!
Grrrr!
(Click click)
There's more than one way
to skin a ninja!
Gone fishin'.
(Blows)
(Sigh)
For you, my apprentice.
(Ring)
Welcome to miss Kimber's
psychic hotline,
where I reveal
what the stars tell.
Uncle needs helps finding
mask-removal ingredient
and for you to never speak
of this to anyone!
Yes. Yes. I see.
And it's high time
you pursued
your true passion.
(Gasp)
Oil painting?!
That's right.
'Cause the stars say
uncle needs to take
time out for  uncle.
(Gasp)
It is like you have
window into uncle's soul.
Here, tiny!
(Kissy sounds)
Here, boy. Come on.
Where are you?
(Rumbling)
Oh, boy.
You may have survived
a gator, chan,
but how about
a land shark?!
(Sniffing)
Grrr! Enough
with the shadow puppets!
Rrrr!
Oh!
It's chow time.
(Distant pounding
and shaking)
Huh! Uh!
Jackie, I think tiny
had a big breakfast.
(Roar)
Now  that's what
I call a warrior!
(Cell phone rings)
Uncle?
Jackie, if psychic
speaks truth,
there is good chance
uncle will be taking
unexpected trip.
Oh, the mask-removal
ingredient is fish.
Oh! Uncle, we are about
to be swallowed
by a whale!
Where are we supposed
to find a fish
in the middle
of downtown?!
Duh!
Hit it, unc!
Uncle, on phone:
Dokeru kimen yaaku.
Uhh!
(Struggling)
Whoa!
Aah!
Oof!
Ohhh!
Jade:
Think one of those
belongs to tohru?
Jackie,
all is right again.
(Groan)
Sensei?
Aiyaaa!
Who told you
to move, tohru?
What...What  is that?
Oil painting.
Uncle must learn
to take time out for uncle.
If you could have
a superpower,
what would it be?
If I have superpower,
I can stop everything,
like, "freeze!"
Then, after I fix
everything, "continue."
Yeah, like tornado
coming, I can, "freeze."
Tell people, "run away."
"Ok, keep coming."
And, yes, I'd really like
to have this kind of power.