Jade: Help!
Jackie, can't hang on!
Need...Food.
You are not starving
to death, Jade.
You could have
some of uncle's
mung beans.
I'll never be  that hungry.
Unh! Tohru went to get
dinner forever ago.
What, did he get attacked
by ninjas or something?
(Chanting)
(Gasps)
(Tohru roars)
Ayah!
Tohru, no! He is
a holy man!
(Whimpers)
Heh. Welcome
to uncle's rare finds.
Kindly forgive the brutish
behavior of my apprentice.
He offers you his meal
as an apology.
(Slurping)
Ooh, we would never
eat  his food.
You do not like mushu?
We monks
of the Ben shui order
have followed signs
and omens
to this place in search
of the chosen one.
Haven't seen him.
You?
Wha...
- Hey!
Accept this offering,
o chosen one.
But he can't be
your leader.
He's our tohru.
The chosen one has lived
a thousand lifetimes.
When one life
has run its course,
the chosen one's
life energy--his chi--
returns in a new vessel.
That's why tohru's
so big.
All that extra chi.
Why did you not tell me you
were a leader of holy men?
I did not know.
No doubt it is due
to my good influence.
Come.
We must journey
to our temple
in Bhutan,
where
the high mystic
will awaken
your chi.
You're leaving now?
The chosen one's chi
is vulnerable
while it sleeps.
If the dark forces were
to destroy him now--
destroy?
Let 'em try.
Big t can take care
of himself.
(All gasp)
Oh, no, no, no.
The chosen one
is a being of peace,
not of war.
It is foretold
that a champion
will come forward
to defend him.
Huh?
Uh, so, uh,
what sort of dark forces
are we talking about?
The Ben shui have located
the chosen one.
I, tao LAN wong,
cannot allow
his chi to be awakened,
for evil must prevail.
Dark chi must reign!
Gon! Chui! Ran!
Seek out the chosen one
and annihilate him!
All: Ohh!
The chosen one
is a river
of enlightenment,
not a beast
of burden.
Ahh.
The champion
will serve.
Huh? Unh! Uhh! Oof!
Behold, chosen one...
- But--
your sacred garments.
Silk. Very chic.
I am losing
my assistant
shopkeeper.
Jackie will just
have to help more
around the shop.
Come, you will
both serve
- the chosen one well.
Uh, serve?
Really, this is
not necessary.
Ohh! The chosen
one's glory
must be celebrated,
not concealed.
Tch! So those dark forces
can find him?
Unh! Ohh! Argh!
Rise, champion.
Our temple is still
many miles away.
(Yawns)
Ohh! The chosen one
requires rest.
We will stop
for the night.
Grr.
Uncle is too old
for this.
Tch! I'm too old
Let's just try to make
the best of--oh!
When the chosen one
sleeps well,
everyone is rested.
(All grumbling)
(Snoring and wheezing)
Ohh.
Ooh...Tohru,
uncle has the willies.
Willies?
Dark chi must be near.
How near?
Ohh!
Whoa! Freaky eyes.
A dark chi warrior!
Chi master fung warned me
of such dark entities.
Uh-uh-uh!
The chosen one is
a being of peace.
Ohh.
Pillow fight--unh!
You are too young
to wage battle
with the forces
of darkness!
Aww!
One more thing...
Both warrior and weapon
share the same dark chi.
They function as one.
How nice for them.
Gone! Jackie,
you smoked him!
This was
but a test.
And Jackie
aced it, right?
Hmm, let us say
more extreme
challenges lie ahead.
Tohru:
Not anymore.
We are
going home.
I do not
want anyone
to be hurt
on my behalf.
Ohh! Such selflessness
in the face of danger!
There can be no doubt.
He  is the chosen one!
Auughh.
Jade: Are we there yet?
Are we there yet?
Patience.
Before the chosen one
reaches our temple,
he must greet
his worshippers.
Worshippers?
Man: It's
the chosen one!
Woman: Look,
it's him!
(All calling out)
W-what do they want?
To bask in your glory.
Villagers, chanting:
Chosen one!
Ohh! Where did he go?
Ohh! The chosen one
has vanished!
Tohru!
Ow!
You are
a lousy champion!
You let the chosen one
out of your sight!
We must find him.
Who knows
- what the dark forces
intend to do?
Tohru? Tohruuu!
Big t, where are you?
Dark forces, huh?
Ahem!
(Imitating monk)
The chosen one is
a cleanser of souls,
not a washer
of dishes.
(Sighs) But I do not  want
to be the chosen one.
Tch! Why not?
You have your own
personal champion
and servants
who wait on you
hand and foot.
I am not accustomed
to such treatment, Jade.
I enjoy serving people,
especially those I like.
Well, maybe
washing dishes
isn't the only way
to help.
Did you see
how happy you made
those villagers?
The chosen one
serves, too,
in a...Different
kind of way.
Ohh, perhaps you are right.
Good, 'cause you
missed a spot.
You are  so fired.
Jackie? Uncle?
I've found--
trouble.
Dark chi guy brought
some freaky-eyed friends.
Let's take 'em.
But the chosen one is
not allowed to fight.
Eh! Nobody's lookin'.
Ohh!
Wah!
Bah!
Hyah!
You are still
too young!
Ohh...
Chopped salad.
You're fixing a snack?
How can uncle
cast a chi spell
without
the ingredients?
Ooh, you better
get cooking!
Huh!
Daaaah!
Huh?
(Both chanting)
Ohh.
We really smoked 'em
this time. Right, uncle?
My disappearing spell
is only temporary.
Our temple is near.
The chosen one
will be safe
once the high mystic
awakens his chi.
So, a champion is not
enough for the chosen one.
He brings his own
chi wizard as well.
Then it will take
a chi wizard
to beat a chi wizard.
Do not worry,
champion.
Good chi protects
our temple.
The dark entities
cannot enter from outside.
Greetings, friend.
Are you prepared
to accept your destiny?
(Chanting)
Chosen one. Chosen one.
I am.
Then let us begin
the awakening ceremony.
Ah...Mmm...
When you awaken
from this trance,
your chi will
awaken as well.
You will remember
your thousand lifetimes
and lead us once again.
(Chanting)
(All chanting)
Ooh, the willies.
(Gasps)
The dark warriors!
But I thought
the dark entities
could not enter
from outside.
A dark chi trick.
They were summoned
from  within the temple.
If the dark ones
destroy the vessel,
the chosen one's chi
will be lost forever!
(Gasps) And we'll
lose tohru forever.
Destroy the chosen one!
Unh! Ha! Unh! Ha!
Step aside, wizard!
Your tepid spells
cannot stop me.
Be warned.
I was a student
of chi master fung.
And I am tao LAN wong,
the dark master
who defeated fung.
(Gasps)
You will pay for that!
(Chants)
Hyah! Nyuh! Uhh!
Mine!
Yours.
(All chant)
Ooh...
How did you do that?
Master fung
taught me well.
How long is this ritual?!
This walking stick belonged
to the previous chosen one,
the yak Shepherd chop yep.
It will help you.
How?
It is full
of his good chi.
Use your chi
to control it.
How?!
Heh. I have a stick.
Doh! Uhh! Oh! Ooh!
A very good stick.
If it works for them...
Yes!
No! Ohh!
(Gasps)
Stop!
Whoa.
Waah! Hyah!
Cool.
There goes my chi.
No! Leave him alone!
(Chanting)
Huh?
No.
(Grunts)
The awakening is complete,
great leader.
Your memories
have been restored.
They have?
You do not remember
your thousand lifetimes?
Mm-mmm.
Not even your once trusty
walking stick
or your most favorite yak?
Mmm...I am sorry.
No.
He is not the chosen one.
I am not?
I am not!
Guess what that means?
(Tohru growls)
Rahhrrrr!
When the true
chosen one is found,
I shall return.
That is what you think!
Ow!
Yaaah!
Go, uncle.
Now your temple is safe.
Tao long
and his dark warriors
may not enter again.
Duh! Grr...
Gyuh...Gyuh!
I insist.
Um, my apologies
about the mix-up.
The chosen one
will be found
when the time is right.
Go in peace, friend.
Could it be that you
found the right place,
but the wrong vessel?
Did you see
how the girl child
wielded the chosen one's
walking stick?
It is as if her chi
and his were one.
Perhaps we should see
if she remembers the yak.
Hey, Jackie.
Yes?
Are the characters
in the show
based on people
you know?
I think, yes.
When I look at the uncle,
the way he speak,
"ooh, ooh, ooh."
Half like my father,
half like my manager.
Jade, yes. So many young
girls like the niece.
Of course, not the bad guy.
The shadowkhan.
He's got--that's--
that's--you make somebody.
Tohru?
One of my stunt guys.
The character of myself,
sometimes very comedy,
sometimes very serious.
That's me.