Ew!
"One more thing.
Go through archway,
then go 30 more paces."
Ah! The sorcerer's eye!
Just where uncle
said it would be.
And the inscriptions
are intact.
The museum will be
very pleased to--huh?!
Oh!
Aah! Bad day! Bad day!
Bad day.
Aah!
Who are you?!
The new owner
of that necklace. Give!
No! This artifact
belongs in a museum.
Heh, sorry.
Oh, you will be.
Aah!
Ooh!
Whew. Aah!
Are we
having fun yet?
No, we are not.
Why are you doing this?
You seem like
such a nice lady.
Been called
a lot of things,
relic hunter,
mercenary, thief,
but Vanessa barone,
nice lady?
Ha ha! That is
a new one.
The necklace.
No. It belongs in a museum.
Ooh!
- Aah!
Oh! My leg!
Oh no. I better
call a doctor.
For you!
Return to pontello.
But I--you...
Gotta admit it, sal.
Venice is a nice change.
No street crime,
no weirdos, no--
heh heh.
Guide book was wrong.
No subway in venice.
Gondola rides!
All your favorite canals!
The divatello,
the monteleone,
the pontello...
Pontello!
It is a canal.
That's a-right.
So, how many
tickets you want?
¶ La la la ¶
know what I'm
holding here,  paisan?
A key to all
- the riches in the world.
Uh, no speak English.
Ha ha ha!
(Gasps)
You?!
This belongs
in a museum.
Whoa!
Mama Mia!
(Cell phone rings)
Hello?
I suppose
you're having fun
without me, Jackie.
Fun? No, not really, Jade.
What is it you need?
I need to be
where the action is.
How come you didn't
take me with?
I told you! School
is too important, and--
ha! You missed!
Missed what?
Nothing!
Can we talk later?
Fine. Just
hurry back.
Uncle won't let me
do anything fun.
Believe me, Jade.
There is nothing
I would like more
than to return
to uncle's shop.
Hopefully, in one--wha?!
No!
"Uncle's shop."
(Gasps)
Jackie! How'd you
get here so soon?
You were in a taxi
when I called.
Yes, a water taxi. In Italy.
Come again?
Jackie! Did not
expect you
until tonight!
You and I both, uncle.
I believe this necklace
has magical powers.
Cool! Can
I check it out?
No, Jade. This necklace
could be very dangerous.
Everything
is very dangerous.
Traveling to venice,
digging for artifacts,
wearing jewelry.
Perhaps the inscriptions
from the mural
will help explain.
Uncle will look into it.
Meanwhile,
you fix your niece!
What do
you mean? Ow!
Open eyes! Jade turning
into a couch potato.
Watches TV all day, all night.
Young girl needs a hobby.
Hmm. I see
what you mean.
(Door opens)
Greetings, campers!
I'm a buttercup scout,
and my troop
is trying to raise money
by selling these
delicious boxes of--
cookies!
What kind
would you like, mister?
We have vanilla cream,
chocolate mint,
oatmeal raisin--
oh, may I...
Have them all?
You sure may!
Will that be check or--
cool!
I try to get out,
but they just keep
pulling me back in.
Hey! It was just
getting good!
I think I found you
a hobby, Jade.
Buttercup scouts.
This is a joke, right?
It's adventurous,
but not dangerous.
Oh, you look so cute!
(Muffled whispers)
Oh, I mean cool.
I look like an elf.
I have heard that
scouting builds character.
I have also heard
that scouts receive
a discount on cookies.
Jackie, I don't wanna be
a buttercup scout!
It's gonna be totally boring.
Please, Jade.
Just give it a chance.
You never know
until you try.
Wanna bet?
Uncle: Jackie! Come see!
Necklace has name.
The eye of Aurora.
Ah, Aurora was
an ancient Egyptian
Princess said to--
getting to that!
Aurora was ancient
Egyptian Princess.
Necklace given
to her by sorcerer.
Possesses magical powers
of teleportation.
Travel anywhere
in the blink of an eye.
But why would
Princess Aurora--
getting to that!
Princess was greedy.
Used necklace to travel world
and steal
treasure from rivals.
Ah, no wonder
Vanessa barone
is so eager to
get her hands on it.
Getting to--who?
A nice lady
I met in venice.
Where to, lady?
Chinatown.
(Door handle being turned)
Who is there?
Warning you!
Uncle may be thin,
but he is scrappy!
Aah!
Evil demons.
Must be the necklace.
It has released
a curse upon us.
Jackie!
(Snoring)
You must learn to use
a napkin, tohru.
Aah! Go away!
Demons, shoo! Shoo! Shoo!
Hiya!
Wha?
Chill, uncle,
it's just us...
Buttercup scouts.
We were gonna
build bird feeders,
but Jade talked us
into making masks.
Don't they
look scary?
Scary, no.
Uncle's heart
always pounds
like jackhammer!
(Sighs)
Just trying to whip up
a little excitement.
Why are you all here?
Don't you have
a camping trip today?
Uh-huh. Oh, gee!
Didn't I tell you, Jackie?
You're today's buttercup mom.
Me?! I can not
be a buttercup mom.
I'm not even a mom.
Actually, the rule book's
pretty gray on that subject.
A buttercup troop leader
can be a mom, dad,
uncle, whatever.
They even have a uniform
in your size.
Come on, uncle Jackie.
Just give it a chance.
You never know until you try.
How about it, Jackie?
You and me turn in
our buttercup
badges right now,
leave this whole
dopey idea behind,
head for the nearest
pyramid or--
no, Jade.
This camping trip
is a chance
for you and I
to have fun together.
Without bad guys.
I try to get out,
but they keep
pulling me back in.
And without any TV.
Ok, buttercup scouts!
All aboard!
Hmm...
Maybe there's
a way to spice up
this trip after all.
(Door handle turning)
(Door opens and closes)
No more buttercup scouts!
Too late, bus left!
Oh, I'm not interested
in transportation.
I'm looking for
the eye of Aurora.
(Gasps) Never heard of it.
Thank you, come again.
You never
heard of it, huh?
Where's the necklace,
old timer?
Uh, necklace gone.
Jackie took it, uh, to museum.
How long before
Jackie returns from
summit hill, sensei?
Summit hill, eh?
Thanks for the tip, tiny.
Grr.
What?
And that is how
you tie a bowline knot.
Who wants to try?
Scouts: Me! Pick me!
I wanna try!
All right,
- Tara and Dana first.
Isn't this fun?
Scouts: Yeah!
Gathering wood,
chasing butterflies,
and tying knots.
Oh, yeah. A real party.
Jade, the first
rule of scouting is
always be prepared.
You never know
when knot-tying
might come in handy.
I'll remember that
when I join the Navy.
Maybe I should give you
a special assignment.
Really? Cool!
What is it?
Canteens need refilling.
You want me to fetch water?
Yes, please.
There's a stream
behind those trees.
And please,
don't wander off!
(Scoffs) We're a mile
from a mall.
What's he think?
I'm gonna make a prison break,
hop in a getaway car
and return to Siberia--huh?
Whoa! Weird!
Siberia! This thing's awesome.
Doggies! Oh, they're so cute!
And hungry.
And  so not dogs.
Wolves! Help!
Jackie! Answer phone!
(Cell phone rings)
Hello?
Jackie, you are in danger.
Bad lady coming your way.
Jackie is not here.
Huh? Who this?!
What are you doing
with Jackie's cell phone?
Um, speaking
with you, sensei.
Ah! Must go
to summit hill!
Warn Jackie!
Quickly! Find map of city!
How'd we do?
Very nice job.
Very thorough, too.
Scouts: (Gasping)
What is it? A Bear?
Oh, it is probably
just Jade playing a prank.
Aah!
(Gasps)
Vanessa barone!
Now that's a face
only a mummy could love.
The necklace, chan.
I don't have it.
Uh, scout's honor.
If you're lying, you're going
to need a lot more bandages.
A buttercup scout
never lies!
Charming.
Well, hop to it,
buttercup scouts.
I'm not leaving till you
find my eye of Aurora.
Honolulu! Miami!
Moose world!
Come on
and work all ready!
Whoa! Oof!
Oh.
Come on! Fly!
Activate! Power up!
Heh. N-nice wolfies.
I'd love to hang out
and play fetch,
but, see,
I--I really
gotta catch a cab
and return
to uncle's shop
before it gets too--
I found one!
A map?
A box of cookies.
I am still
- searching for a map.
Hurry! Jackie
is in big--aah!
Hey! It worked!
(Gasps) Where is Jackie?!
At the campsite.
I figured out
the necklace.
You just say
the word return to,
and whatever
you say next
is where you go.
Like this:
Return to uncle's side.
Wha! Do not
do that again!
Wait!
Do that again!
Must go
warn Jackie!
Bad lady
headed his way!
No prob.
Return to summit hill!
(Sighs) I did not
have a chance to ask her
for more cookies.
Ugh!
What?
Ah, express delivery.
How thoughtful.
Well, chan,
love to stay and rap,
but by the looks of it,
you're all wrapped up.
So ta-ta!
Kia!
Thank you for the lesson
in bandage removal,
miss barone.
See, girls?
Quick and painless.
Wha?!
Buttercup scouts!
Too violent!
Do not watch!
(Scoffs) As if!
Sayonara, all.
It's been a kick.
Return to Peru!
I travel solo, chan.
So, step off.
Both: Aah!
Return to Everest!
Both: Ooh!
M-m-mount Everest!
B-bad idea!
I wanted a soft landing.
Next time
pick a warm place.
Like...Sahara desert!
Uh, oh! Return
to Sahara desert!
Brilliant! You must have been
a real a-plus student, chan!
A-minus in school.
A-plus at the dojo.
Well, you're a complete
washout as a scout leader,
chan.
Leaving those sweet,
defenseless girls
all alone in the woods.
(Gasps)
You're right! Wha?!
Ha! Return
to aculp--
no, return to summit hill!
Jackie!
You're back!
Yes, but so is she.
And I have the necklace.
Return to venice!
Correction. You have
half the necklace.
Come on, Jackie.
Now's our chance
to get her.
Please, Jade.
Stay with the others.
I have a plan.
Ok, I give up!
No more fighting!
That's his plan?!
What's the catch?
No catch. As you said,
I am responsible
for the safety
of these girls.
If you promise to leave,
I will give you
the other half
of the necklace
and tell you
where to find
an amazing treasure.
I'm listening.
A small island
off the coast of Chile.
Very remote.
Uh, demolition island.
Uh, devotion island?
Desolation island.
Nice try, chan.
Thought you could
trick me into traveling
to one of the most
remote spots on earth.
No, really. I--
I'd wager you were
planning to alert
the authorities
to fly in and pick me up
the moment I got there.
(Sighs) Actually,
I was going to touch
the 2 necklace halves
together, then pull
my half back
so you would
be teleported,
then stranded.
But you were
too clever to say,
"back to
desolation island."
Oh, return to
desolation island.
(Gasps)
Get her!
Jade. The buttercups.
Jackie! Where are--
can't talk, uncle.
Must go to desolation island.
Desolation island?
Jackie!
Ooh! Where are
the others?
With little miss
globetrotter crook.
Scouts: Yeah!
We're saved!
Ah, you used
the first aid skills
I taught you.
Actually, a little something
I picked up watching TV.
Robinson crusoe
goes Hawaiian.
So how we gonna get home,
buttercup mom Jackie?
No way that'll hold us all.
Tohru?
I was hoping to purchase
some more cookies.
Once we are home,
I will buy you
all you can eat!
Hey, Jackie?
Do you cook?
My father is a big cook.
My father's a chef
but his son's the worst.
I even don't know
how to cook the rice.
The people tell me
it's the rice machine.
You put some rice in...
I broke the machine.
Somebody give me a rice,
already cook,
then I can put some oil,
with a pepper...
Only that one.
Jackie chan fried rice.