Uncle:
We will find next oni-mask
in pacific northwest,
near base of cascade
mountains.
Why did I let you
talk me into this?
You said it yourself,
Jackie, you're too fat.
I said I am too heavy
to climb the totem pole
without risk of
damaging it, Jade.
Heavy, fat--same diff.
Hey! He looks
just like his mug shot.
He will fit snugly...
Upon my face!
Flying squirrel
cracks acorn!
Unh!
Whoa!
Jade!
Aah!
Aaah!
Jade!
(Grunts)
Hang on!
(Growls)
You there! Chop chop!
Fetch the mask...
While I destroy chan.
Hyah!
Yaah!
Unh!
Hunh!
Flying dragon corkscrew!
(Grunting)
Make it easy on
yourself, kiddo.
We just want the mask.
Then come and get it.
(Echoing)
Tohru, is mask removal
potion ready?
Uh, almost, sensei.
So, what's the deal with
these oni-masks anyway?
You worry about driving.
Let uncle worry about masks.
Uh, sorry, dude.
Uh, rocks
crush paper.
Ohh!
Unh! (Growls)
Hunh!
Wait a minute!
Paper covers rock.
(Grunts)
End of the line, chans.
(Trees falling)
Aiyaa!
It...Jostled.
(Gasps) Ingredient
for mask removal spell
was very rare!
Ow!
Who told you to
drive like hot shot?
With no potion,
we must ensure that
no one wears mask.
Will do.
Hunh!
Hyah!
Oof!
Look out!
Captain black!
I said look  out,
not up.
(Groaning)
Tiger snatches mask
before it sticks!
Guess again, kitty cat.
Huh?
(Grunting)
Captain black's
got game.
Huh!
- Hey!
Unh!
Exit's that way.
(Yelling)
Happy trails.
Captain black,
are you...All right?
Never better.
(Coughing and sputtering)
Finn: Tarakudo's gonna
be one unhappy camper.
Well, it ain't my fault.
I was paper.
Ahem.
What is not your fault?
We never had a chance,
big head honcho, sir.
That oni mask,
it's defective.
Yeah, captain black's
wearing it,
but he didn't
go all dark side.
The captain black?
All: Uh-huh.
Then we now have
a man on the inside.
Whoa!
Captain black.
Your face...
Relax.
It's only a mask.
Does it come off?
Why would I want it to?
(Grunting)
Whoa.
Jade:
He's...Peppy.
But he does not
seem evil.
Because captain black's
inherent goodness
is keeping
the dark forces
within him at bay...
For the moment.
But we must remove
the mask before
it corrupts his chi.
And to accomplish that,
we must acquire more
spell ingredient.
Apologies, sensei.
One more thing!
While tohru and I
are away,
it is essential
that captain black
not learn the full extent
of the mask's magic.
He must not summon
his shadowkhan.
So what are we
supposed to do,
distract captain hornhead
with videos and board games?
(Alarm sounds)
Code blue.
3 dozen tourists have been
abducted on Alcatraz.
All right,
let's go!
Roger that!
Take 5, boys.
I'll handle
this one solo.
Uh, maybe that is not
such a good idea.
What's wrong, Jackie?
don't think
ol' black magic
is up to it?
(Grunting)
Help! Help us!
Help us!
Jade!
You watch
captain black's back,
I watch yours.
Help us!
Help us! Help!
Oh, captain black!
We've never been
formally introduced.
I am tarakudo,
king of all shadowkhan.
You may bow.
The only king
I bow to is Elvis,
and I don't
see you wearing
blue suede shoes.
And I don't see you
wearing your mask
at full throttle,
and I can help you unleash
its true potential.
No sale, helium head.
(Sighs)
Oh, well. Plan b.
Ha! You'd better
cook up plan c.
I already ate your goons
for breakfast.
He's being
straight, t.K.
We can't beat him.
Wait for it...
(Grunting)
Now watch
as the good captain
gets in touch
with his dark side.
(Grunts) This is black!
I need backup! Now!
Shadowkhan.
Big ones.
(Gasps)
I thought these guys
were supposed to be
on our side.
Eee-tai!
Aah!
Aaah!
Black here.
Cancel that backup.
Whoa! Captain black
has new recruits.
Ahh, things are going
exactly as I envisioned.
This is the plan?!
You have the right
to remain busted!
Jackie, why didn't you
tell me I could summon
these shadow guys?
They're gnarly.
Heh heh. Must have
slipped my mind.
(Gasping)
Ohh...
These midday swims
are getting to be
quite the habit with you,
aren't they, hak foo?
Uhh...Black has
beaten us...Again!
Calm down. By summoning
his shadowkhan,
black has sealed
his promotion from captain
to demon general.
Where did
all the agents go?
Black: Mandatory
leave of absence.
Meet the next generation
of law enforcement, Jackie.
Captain black,
they are ninjas.
My ninjas...Obeying
my every command.
Loyal, efficient, tireless.
Even as we speak,
they're out there,
cleansing
the streets of scum.
He-hey!
We got another one!
But I didn't
do anything!
I'm telling you,
I'm innocent!
Yeah, yeah,
save the drama
for your mama.
Good work, men!
Uh, what did
all these people do?
It's what
they  didn't do, Jackie.
I'm sorry?
(Softly)
They're not one of us.
- How can you be sure?
(Whispers)
The mask tells me.
It knows who's
naughty and nice.
It tells me
who to punish.
Where is uncle?
(Grunting)
Here is where we will
find more rare seaweed
for removal spell, tohru.
Oh, I hate fish.
(Thump)
Aiyaa!
If the oni-mask keeps
"talking" to captain black,
who knows what
it will tell him next?
If we keep him inside
section 13 until
uncle gets back,
what's the worst
that could happen?
(Gasps)
The other oni masks!
We have to snag
those face-huggers
before captain black
remembers they're
in the vault!
Jackie:
Easier said than done.
Section 13 is crawling
with his shadowkhan police.
We must act like
nothing is wrong.
Bad move, Jackie.
Gaah!
Where you off to,  buddy?
Ha ha! Captain black!
Just out for a stroll.
Hmm. Like to...
The vault?
Uh, no.
Jackie, Jackie, Jackie.
I thought
I could trust you.
we were friends.
We are friends.
That is why
you must listen to me.
The mask is turning
you into one of
tarakudo's generals!
You must resist it!
Nonsense.
The mask lets me
see things clearly.
Like the fact that
you want to betray me.
And since you're not
one of us, Jackie,
you can join the others.
Please! Listen to me!
Not to the mask!
(Electronic beeps)
Hmm?
Come on, come on! Unh!
(Grunts)
Oh, Jade! don't go
and make captain black mad!
"Black." A fine name.
The color of darkness.
(Grunts) Denied!
(Growls) No!
Duh, Jade, they're shadows.
You weren't planning
on stealing my masks,
now, were you, Jade?
You're getting kind
of greedy, aren't you,
captain black?
You only have one face.
But 3 partners in darkness,
itching for a makeover.
The captain black I know
would never do that!
The captain black you know
is on permanent vacation.
Well, he's about to catch
the next flight back!
Unh!
Ohh. Haven't been
feeling quite myself.
Your other self isn't
quite yourself, either.
Whoa, Nelly!
So you've gone and yanked
my yin from my Yang.
Feels like
a burden's been lifted.
Now what?
Hello?!
(Crash)
Hey! The power of
an ox in my pinkie!
Jackie's behind bars
and uncle's m.I.A.,
so it's up to us!
Let's go kick my butt!
What's the matter,
chan?
don't you
like your room?
Heh heh heh heh.
Maybe you should
complain to the management.
Boys, I come
bearing gifts.
No! Unh! Uhh! Uhh!
Put on a happy face.
Huh?
- Huh?
Rahr!
You've been jacked...
By the rabbit.
Catch her!
If you can!
Huh?
Uhh!
Rrr...
Facial!
Rrr...Rrr...
Tiger talisman?
Brought out
the best in me.
Ohh.
They keys!
(Grunting)
Rrr!
The bigger they are...
The slower they are.
Hyuh! Uhh!
Uhh!
(Gulps)
Rrr...Uhh!
Ha ha ha!
I'm as strong
as any one of you bruisers.
Ooh!
Uhh!
Evil captain black:
Oh, captain black...
I don't think
section 13 is big enough
for the both of us.
Then I'm afraid
I'll have to ask you
to leave.
Hurry, uncle.
Quickly, tohru!
(Grunting)
Eee!
Tohru: Aah!
- Uncle: Aiyaa!
Uhh!
Warning--
I may look small,
but I'm a giant
can of butt whoop
just waiting
to be opened.
Weakling.
(Pow)
Ohh...
I'm embarrassed
that we're even related.
Ah, my masks.
Psst!
Jackie!
I told you--do not
allow captain black
to summon
shadowkhan!
Captain black doesn't
live here anymore,  old man.
Guess again,
sparky.
Give up yet?
Uhh!
Thought so.
Look, I know we've been
at each other's throats,
but...Friends?
No agents.
Security here stinks.
Heh heh heh heh.
Jade, you may
want to add this
to your collection.
It's good to have you
back, captain black.
It's good to be good.
Uncle: One more thing!
We must find phone booth
removal potion!
Hey, Jackie, have you ever had
a disagreement with a
good friend?
There's so many,
- so many times that happened.
Either one,
you have to call,
"hey, are you
angry about me?"
If I do something wrong,
I say, "sorry."
Because very hard
to make a friend,
a good friend.
When you have a good friend,
I would never let go.
Besides, parents important,
friends also important.
All those years,
I travelled so many places,
the friends helped me.
So friendship, friendship
is very, very important.