According to our GPS unit,
we are directly in the heart
of the Sahara desert.
Heh. Wyoming is
not in Africa, is it?
Hmph! Technology!
Carrot will tell us
when we are near.
So where in yellowstone park
would a talisman-powered
rabbit hide?
It's gotta be
in one of these
giganto rabbit holes.
Jade!
Yeah, yeah, I know.
(As Jackie)
You are supposed to be
on the tour.
No, Jade!
Those are not rabbit holes!
"Danger! Geysers"?
(Rumbling)
Uh-oh.
(Grunting)
Jackie, I'm stuck!
Grab on!
Whoa-oa-oa-oa!
(Gasps)
Jackie, dark warriors ho!
Finn: D-master wong wants
the power of superspeed,
chan.
So hand over
the bunny pronto!
But we haven't even
found it yet.
Be that way.
(Gasp)
Aah!
Whoa! Timber!
Jade!
Uh, ratso?
Aah!
Nice catch.
Oh, thanks.
That was close.
Hey!
Come on!
So the dark warrior
wants a piece of unc--aah!.
(Chuckles)
A geezer in a geyser.
Jackie!
Stay in here.
Oh!
Hmm.
Unh!
I'll teach you
to mess with Finn 2.0.
Whoa!
(Chanting)
And I will teach you
to mess with
uncle original recipe.
Heh. Occupied.
Oh!
So that's where you're hiding
Peter cottontail.
You caught me,
Sherlock.
Ooh.
Short ears.
Uh...
Yours?
(Snarling)
Aah!
Yup. That'll leave a mark.
(Rumbling)
Aah!
Sayonara, chan.
Huh?
Finn: Gah!
You mean, "cowabunga."
Come on, uncle.
Something tells me
we are close to finding
our rabbit, uncle.
Aah! What manner
demonic creatures
are these?!
Midget deer.
Uncle, they are
rabbits. Ow!
Rabbits
do not have antlers!
He's right, you know.
Howdy, folks, and welcome
to Douglas, Wyoming,
home of the jackalope.
Whatever it is,
it's not packin'
talisman heat.
(Gasp)
It destroyed
the locator!
Uh, sir, I am hoping
you can help us.
It is very important
that we locate
a particular rabbit.
Heh heh, well,
you're barkin' up
the wrong tree, partner.
I said this was
jackalope country.
Look, we both know
jackalopes are rabbits
who wear fake antlers
for the tourists.
(Chuckles) No sirree.
I assure you
that Douglas jackalopes
are the real deal.
Now, that was
an ugly thing to do.
Jade, you know
the dark warriors
could return at any time.
Uncle and I must search
for the rabbit alone.
But, Jackie,
I'm an essential member
of clan chan!
Which is why I am giving you
an essential mission.
Go to the nice library
down the block,
and do your homework.
Ooh. Highly classified.
When is Jackie gonna realize
I'm his secret weapon?!
Tch! His loss
if he can't figure out
I have a nose
for sniffing out magic.
Whoa!
I got it, coach!
Psyche!
Good arm.
Thanks for making me
look bad, kid.
Coach: Hey, chip!
Ready for me, coach?
How about some h-2-0
for the troops?
Oh, right away,
coach.
Nice work, chip.
Now, let's get all
that equipment stacked
nice and neat.
Then can I get in
some practice
for the big game
tonight?
We'll talk.
Now hustle!
Hey, sorry I goofed on you
back there, chip.
Whatever.
It's tough enough
getting coach to
take me seriously.
I don't need
your help in
that department.
Tch! Listen, chip.
If there's one rule
Jade chan lives by,
it's this.
If coach won't
give you a shot,
you have to put yourself
in the game.
You're just
a little girl.
What do you know
about football?
Let's just say my coach
doesn't always
put me in the game,
but I know you can't
make the big plays
from the sidelines.
Totally.
I mean, I'm as good
as any of
the other players.
Well, I could be
faster.
Faster shmaster.
I can see you've got
what it takes.
You can?
Sure thing.
So are you gonna
just stand there
and look pretty
or are you gonna
belt this pigskin
to the moon?
Go jackalopes!
Coach: Hey, chip!
Huh?
You need me coach?
Yeah. Did you
feed lucky?
Ohh.
Right away, coach.
Lucky?
Our mascot.
Yeah, we never lost
a game he's been at.
The other schools
try to steal him
just to jinx us.
Lucky wouldn't
happen to be
a rabbit, would he?
Jackalope.
Chip: Mmm.
There you go, luckster.
Hmm, can a rabbit
wear silly antlers
and still be noble?
Let's find out.
Shoo.
Vamoose!
Come on, super-speed,
and you're off.
Activate already!
Oopsy.
(Pants)
Jackie, I found
our bunny.
You--wha--
you did what?
(Sighs)
Jade, what was the bunny
doing at the library?
Uh--crrrrrr.
Uh, you're
breaking up.
Meet me at
the town square--
crrrr--and make it
snappy.
Chip!
You need me coach?
You wanna explain that?
Locator carrots also
make good rabbit bait.
Jade:
Here comes turbo-hare.
Jackie: Got you!
Aaahhh!
Aah! Ugh!
Nooo--oof!
Aah--oop!
Oof!
Ohh.
Whoa!
Jackie, you are terrible
rabbit catcher.
You have to go about
this the right way,
Jack-rabbit.
Speed catches speed.
Jade: Go get 'em.
Come to Jackie!
Eeeyaaah.
Bad day, bad day,
bad day!
Jackie: Yes!
Come to Jackie!
Jackie: Huh?
Daolon wong.
Daolon: Ah, super-speed.
Chip: I know I shut
the cage door.
I bet that Jade girl
took lucky.
She's gotta be a ringer
for the other team.
Oh, if coach
ever finds out
I led her
to our mascot,
I'll be benched forever.
Whoa.
Lucky.
Whoa--agh!
(Chants)
Sir, you are
in possession of
Warren oates
memorial high
football team
property.
Haaa!
Whoa!
What school
are you from?
I will not
bring it back later!
Thank you!
How many schools
are trying to nab him?
Because of you,
I have lost
the rabbit.
(Gulp)
Um, it's a jackalope.
Mondo blading, Jackie.
Listen carefully...
Aah! Shoo!
(Blows air)
For you will bring
the rabbit to me
tonight at
the town square.
Tch! In your dreams,
creepopotamus.
If you do not,
this child's fate
shall haunt
your dreams.
(Jade gasps)
Chip!
Jade: Jackie.
It's all my fault.
We have to
rescue chip.
Of course,
and we will--ow!
We cannot hand
over the rabbit
to forces
of darkness.
Of course,
and we won't.
Jackie?
I just had a light bulb.
Come on, jackalopes.
We don't need lucky
to win.
Announcer:
Touchdown, bears.
That chip better find
lucky soon.
Chip: Please
let me go, mister.
The game already started,
and it's homecoming,
and this could be my--
silence!
If I must hear about
your cursed big chance
once more--
Jackie: Daolon wong.
Hand over the boy.
Not until you deliver
the power of the--
that is not the rabbit.
Uh, yes, it is.
Then why does it
not move?
Um, it is napping?
(Chants quietly)
Wake up!
See? It moved.
If this is indeed
the rabbit,
why does my scepter
not glow bright red?
Um.
Because it is really
a jackalope.
Aiyaah!
Whoa!
Bwaa!
(Chants rapidly)
Huh?
Jackie, what's
taking you?
Jade? You are supposed
to be at the motel,
guarding the--
rabbit.
Daolon: Hoo!
No sweat, Jackie.
As long as I have
the rabbit,
old rigor mortis
can't catch me.
don't worry, chip.
You're in
good hands.
So you did kidnap lucky.
It was me or the forces
of darkness.
Duh.
Yaah!
Lucky's more than lucky.
He's magic.
Jade:
I'm greased lightning.
Jade!
Whoop!
Ooh!
Jade.
Give me that.
Chip: Hand-off.
Time to put myself
in the game.
No, wait!
Ball hog.
Grrr!
Both my running backs
are out of the game?
Ready for me now, coach?
What do I have to lose?
Only one way we can
win this one, lucky.
Announcer:
Touchdown, jackalopes.
He's fast.
I knew it.
There's chip.
Jackie, you must
retrieve the rabbit.
How can I get near him?
Oh, wardrobe.
Announcer:
Unbelievable!
Another touchdown,
jackalopes!
Yeah, chip!
That's my boy.
You know, he's like
a son to me.
Show 'em what you got,
chan-man.
Gan! Ren! Chui!
Hey, football.
Bonding time,
eh, big "d"?
We knew you were
one of us.
Ugh!
The rabbit.
Let's win one
for the wongster.
Go dark warriors.
Grrr.
I will destroy you.
Uncle, singsong:
Hey, ugly!
(Daolon and uncle chant)
Hey!
Chip, please give me
the rabbit.
No way. I'm on
a major streak here.
Listen, you are in
grave danger.
Hike.
Time-out.
Baaahhh!
He's going the wrong way.
Who is that guy?
(Chants)
Uh-oh, uncle
needs an assist.
Hey, girls,
wanna learn
a new cheer?
(Pants)
Huh?
Whoa-oh.
Chip!
Jackie: Buh!
Dah! Egh!
Yaah!
Sorry.
That's not how
I drew up the play.
Uh, I don't have
the ball, guys.
But you do have
Mr. floppy ears.
Chip: Baaah!
Oh ho ho.
Ohh.
Lucky?
Fumble!
Catch!
Uh-oh.
Please do not run,
little bunny rabbit.
Come to Jackie.
It's ok.
Good bunny.
Give me a "d"!
"D"!
Give me a  zho!
Zho!
À  zho!
Put that together,
and what do
you have?
(Cheering in Chinese)
Erggghhh.
Urggghhh.
Gaah!
Go, jackalopes.
Jade, where's lucky?
There's only 10 seconds
left in the game.
Lucky's taking 5, chip,
but that's all right
because you don't need
no stinkin' rabbit.
You can win it
on your own.
You think?
I know.
Now go out there,
show us what you're made of,
and win one
for the jadester.
Hey, buddy,
that's our mascot.
Uh, you must be
mistaken.
No antlers.
Quarterback: Hike.
(Slow motion)
He's gonna make it!
Crowd: Chip! Chip! Chip!
Chip! Chip! Chip!
Player: You the man!
Who knew you had it
in you, son?
Let's try starting you
in the next game.
Aw, keep
your rabbit.
That kid's
my good luck charm.
Yep, he's a chip off
the old block.
Hey, Jackie,
how many push-ups
do you do a day?
There's a lot of things
to train.
Push-ups, lift-ups,
kicking, punch,
30 each for 6 times.
It's not like I can do
1000 push-ups,
then what?
After you do
1000 push-ups,
you can't.
You cannot do anything.