This is the entrance
to the temple of Shiva?
Ah! Oh!
Dead end.
The temple.
(Gasps)
Hak foo?
The bands of Shiva.
With these,
I will be unstoppable.
Stop!
Uh, do not take that
which does not belong
to you, uh, mortal!
Shiva speaks?
With a familiar voice.
Unh!
Shiva runs, too.
Angry crow
takes flight!
Aah!
Rabid hamster
climbs wheel!
Whoa!
I will get you, chan!
Hak foo really
rolls with the punches.
Ok, disappearing spell,
what shall we make
vanish into thin air?
Homework?
(Scoffs) I wish.
Ming vase?
Uh, kinda priceless.
Bingo!
Xia xu, xia xu,
xia xu sandwich!
I am da bomb!
Hak foo seemed
very interested
in having these relics.
And uncle
is very interested
in having his lunch.
Aiyaa!
Tohru!
Did you eat my
mung bean sandwich?
No, sensei.
I have been here,
baking cookies.
Jade?!
Who needs
a sandwich
anyway
when you can
have cookies,
huh, uncle?
He who partakes
in dessert before lunch
disturbs good chi
with bad cholesterol.
Uh, perhaps
we should chew on
why hak foo
may have wanted
shiny new
wristbands?
Yours is
not to ask.
But to fork
over! Arr!
You break it,
you buy it!
Sensei?
Aah!
Oh...
Tohru! I cannot
feel my legs!
Give me the bands,
chan.
Xia xu, xia xu,
xia xu, hak foo!
What?
(Gasps)
Jackie, no!
W-what happened?
Where am--we?
Geography later.
The bands now!
Shoe!
No one shoos me--aah!
Jade, echoing:
Uncle! Come quickly!
Uncle, echoing: Aiyaa!
Bad dream. Bad dream.
Bad dream!
Tohru sat on me,
and my shop is a shambles!
Uncle, I used
a disappearing spell
on hak foo.
You are not supposed
to use magic!
Jackie! Your niece
needs a talking to!
Jackie can't
hear you
'cause I disappeared
him, too.
(Gasps) What?!
I can hear you!
Jade! Uncle!
I'm not disappeared!
I'm...Shrunken?
Aah!
Surely,
there must exist
a counterspell.
Most likely.
Which spell did you use?
The yeoh cheung archive,
book 3, page 95.
And which limbo-like
void did you choose
as the destination?
Uh, none.
Aiyaa! You must
always choose
a destination
when casting
a disappearing
spell.
Jackie could
be anywhere!
I sure hope
it's somewhere with a phone.
Jade! You're a genius!
(Ring)
Uncle's rare finds.
May I help you?
Hello?
Small or large,
I will take the bands.
Who is it?
Is it Jackie?
Crank call!
Come,
we must find
counterspell!
Tohru, I will need
eye of wombat.
It's in
the refrigerator beside
the chopped liver.
Bear fishing
for salmon!
Aah!
Ugh! Augh!
Pee-yuuu!
Hmm. Sensei
did not have lunch.
(Very high-pitched)
Tohru!
Tohru! It's me! Jackie!
Jackie!
(Hums to himself)
Monkey climbs vine!
Oh, visual aid.
Tohru! Over here!
(Hums to himself)
Arr!
Aah!
Ah-ah-choo!
Kangaroo hop!
Ugh! Gah!
(Coughs)
A chocolate chip?
No. No!
No!
- No!
(Sputtering)
Tohru! I need that
wombat eye today!
Uh, oh, coming, sensei.
Uh-oh!
This counterspell promises
to return that which is lost.
Wongai, womai.
Come on home, Jackie!
I lost this kite
when I was
a young boy.
And I have been
looking for this sock.
Hello? We're still
short one Jackie.
Waah!
Rampaging rhino rams!
No rhino!
No ramming!
You're going down, chan!
Arr!
Huh? Aah!
This antidote will
release from detention
he who is trapped
in another dimension.
Uh, Jackie?
(British accent)
It's just me,
but thank you ever so much
for freeing me
from that beastly limbo.
Not Jackie.
(Sniffs)
Ah, lunch!
Uh, cookie?
What's a cookie?
(Roars)
Go away!
I must find
another spell.
Ya think?
I'm on uncle's
spell book.
Yes, uncle, right here!
Aah!
This is a lousy
spell book.
From the deepest reaches
of the void, we compel you.
Bring forth our Jackie!
Arr! Unh!
Let's try a different
kind of spell.
Bring forth
a sign of Jackie.
Any sign'll do.
I am trying!
Arr!
It is Jackie
communicating
with us!
No! Look at
your computer, Jade!
Your computer!
Chan!
I will help myself
to the bands,
after I delete you!
Aah!
Gazelle bounds
on stepping stones!
Can you ask Jackie
to communicate
with words next time?
English words? Oh...
Aah!
Huh?
Jackie, where are you?
I'm here, Jade!
Hear?
Time to get within
shouting distance.
Aah!
Excuse me, Jade.
No, Jade! Wait!
Aah!
Oh, long way up.
But I will get someone
to lend me an ear!
It's no use, uncle.
These counterspells
are lame-o.
Billy goat scales mountain.
(Mutters to himself)
What?
These pages
are stuck together.
Jade, you have used
half of one spell
and half of another.
Combined, these spells
would not disappear Jackie,
they would shrink him
to the size of an ant.
Great! That means he's
somewhere in...Here.
Aah! Watch your step!
Check your shoes!
Tohru!
Toh--unh!
Hot cha! I will
bring Jackie back
in a Hong Kong minute.
That's what you said
4 counterspells ago.
Antidote for
disappearing spell: Hard.
Shrink spell? Easy.
Hurry, uncle.
No, wait!
I cannot return
to normal size in here!
Behold the bands of Shiva!
Uh, yes, they're
very pretty, hak foo.
But please, if we
do not leave here fast,
tohru will be
in grave danger.
So I heard.
I shall defeat
my 2 greatest enemies today.
Yah!
Ow!
Ah!
Arr!
Spider eats fly!
Spider eats earwax!
I--I hear voices.
Jackie's voice.
Screaming about--
about spiders!
Uh, don't
lose your head
now, tohru.
Jackie'll
be home soon.
Kwai jong,
kwai jong,
kwai jong.
Oh!
Unh!
Ooh!
- Ooh!
Uncle: Kwai jong,
kwai jong,
kwai jong.
No, uncle!
Stop the spell!
Kwai jong, kwai jong,
kwai jong, kwai jong.
All done.
Tohru! You must
stop uncle!
I am inside your head!
Aah!
(Gasps) Sensei!
Jackie says
he is inside my head.
(Gasps) There is no room
to grow inside there.
You mean
tohru's head is
gonna go scanner?
I cannot reverse
the incantation.
Ah-ah-ah-choo!
Jackie!
Gesundheit!
Ah, relief.
(Groans)
Uh, new haircut, hak foo?
New arms.
To tear you
limb from limb.
Uncle, may I?
Only this once.
Xia xu, xia xu,
xia xu, xia xu.
Hak foo!
Aw, not again!
Good work, Jade.
Aw, not really.
I was trying to
make him disappear.
Hello? Kidding!
Hey, Jackie?
Yes?
What's your favorite sport?
The basketball
is the best.
It's the best
...and you're sweating,
and techniques, good.
And movement,
and the mind,
in that second,
what are you doing?
Ok, back up--
that's basketball.
Wow. You gonna--
chi-chung.
Huh?
I can beat
Michael Jordan.
Maybe, I don't know.
With my
martial arts together.
Poom! Chlan!