"X" marks the spot...
The spot where
Angus mckutcheon
finally gets his...
The legendary
treasure of
greenbeard the pirate.
Haggis!
Aye, that's me.
Take us in.
20 years! 20 years
I've searched.
And now that I've
found it,
I'll be filthy rich!
Unh! Ahoy?
Get your mitts
off my Booty!
Uh, excuse me?
(Growls)
Hello. My name
is Jackie.
The only one gettin'
rich off this treasure
is mckutcheon!
What about haggis?
Ah, shut it!
I'm sorry, but this find
belongs to the museum.
Your name is
"the museum"?
Uh, no, the historical
museum of San Francisco.
I'm donating
greenbeard's treasure,
not getting rich.
Ah, shut it!
And, uh, since
I did find it first...
Would you like
these instead?
Haggis! Sic!
(Yelling)
I'll cleave you like
an aberdeen ham,
you wee piglet!
Unh! Uhh!
(Laughs evilly)
Mine! All--
sorry.
How did they get there?
Let me be
perfectly clear.
I don't want
the gloves!
Unh! Uhh!
(Groaning)
Whoa!
I knew you
were a pushover.
Waah!
(Coughing)
Haggis! Get him!
Haggis: Oh, haggis has him.
(Gasps)
Haggis! No!
Haggis!
I promise to call
the coast guard.
Bye-bye.
Curator:
Excellent work, Jackie.
"The glorious gold of
greenbeard's treasure"
will be my most elegant
exhibit ever.
I'm glad
you're so--huh?
How did they
get there?
Well, they shan't
remain there,
I can tell you.
My exhibit is
greenbeard's treasure,
not greenbeard's gloves.
Hmm.
Jade: Uncle!
Tohru! Hello?!
The game never ends
if nobody moves.
How can tohru
contemplate a move
with you yelling, Jade?
I thought it was
your move, sensei.
Ugh.
Jackie!
Unh!
Are these from
greenbeard's ship?
Can I keep 'em? Please?!
I've been reading
all about greenbeard.
You've been reading?
For pleasure?
Tch. Not like
there's anything else
to do around here.
"The meanest pirate
of them all,
greenbeard swore
he would keep
stealing forever,
even after he died."
Arr!
How cool was he?
There is nothing cool
about stealing, Jade.
(Whiny)
Ohh.
Crime does not pay.
If captain black
had not pulled strings
after I left
the dark hand,
I would be in prison
right now.
Instead, he lives
under the supervision
of his parole officer.
So tohru is free--
ai-yah--
to lose as many games
of mah-jongg as he likes!
(Sighs)
Thank you, Jade.
No. Thank you, Jackie.
Uncle can sell these.
(Snoring)
(Knock on door)
Uncle: Welcome
to uncle's rare finds.
How may I
help you?
Had a break-in
on this block
last night.
We're checking alibis
on all prior  offenders
in the area.
Uncle: Tohru
was here all night.
He is good now.
You may go.
(Gasps)
Officer: You have
the right to remain silent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against
you in a court of law.
Tohru, what have you done?
Tohru: Please
believe me, sensei.
I did not--
(chanting chi spell)
So, do you think--
could you please
pull a few more strings?
I want to, Jackie,
but my hands are
tied this time.
I really thought
tohru had left
his past behind.
So did I.
But the sad truth
is some people
never change.
Well, thank you,
anyway, captain black.
Wait! Call him back!
What if tohru was framed?!
There were
no evil spirits
in tohru's body.
If the forces
of darkness
did not reawaken
his criminal side,
I am to blame.
I did not provide
enough discipline!
We can't give up yet.
Tohru's innocent until
proven guilty, right?
(Groans)
We are all upset
about tohru, uncle.
Of course
I am upset!
Tohru had work
to do!
Now you must
move all these
antiques!
(Gulps)
(Groans)
(Sighs) Tohru never
used to groan like that.
Ow! What was that for?
Discipline!
I was too soft
on my old shopkeeper
and look what happened.
He became a criminal!
(Sighs)
(Groans)
Ohh. Finished.
Tohru never
used to get sore.
One more thing...
Lick this envelope.
(Yawns)
It's late, uncle.
Maybe we should just
spend the night.
It is very quiet
without tohru.
So, keep it down!
Uncle needs his rest.
(Snoring)
Uncle, I think
this bathtub has
spiders in it.
(Moaning)
Thank you.
Daah!
Diamonds?!
The gloves!
Stop! Thief!
Waah!
I told you
to keep it down!
Uncle! The gloves!
They're alive!
You are dreaming,
Jackie.
Go back to--
bwaah!
Ai-yah!
(Murmuring)
Hold still!
(Ticklish laughter)
Ohh! Stop!
Huh?
Ugh!
Daah!
Now can I keep 'em?
Greenbeard's life
of crime may be over,
but his gloves
are still stealing.
Tohru  was framed,
sort of.
We must
tell the police.
Release tohru now!
Aren't you
the evil-spirits guy?
Tohru did not steal.
The gloves are to blame.
Jackie!
Maybe this
was a bad idea.
Get up! You do not
fool uncle!
Now, why don't
you folks just get
some rest, and we--
gloves are evil!
Tohru is innocent!
End of discussion!
Uncle, please
don't yell at
the nice policeman.
Jackie's right.
Let's just take
the gloves and...
(Gasps)
(Tohru struggles)
No! I do not want to...
What part
of evil gloves do
you not understand?
Tohru is innocent!
(Gasps)
One more thing--
we'll be right back.
Uncle: Aiy!
Tohru broke out of prison?
He is not innocent now!
Jackie: The museum!
He must be
after the treasure!
Tohru's not,
but the magic mittens
on his hands are.
Keep
the police busy.
We can't let them
see tohru.
Forgive
my earlier rudeness,
sergeant.
I wish to apologize
by telling you
my life story.
Doughnuts!
Whoa, hey!
Don't all crowd
around the window.
That's bad
for digestion.
Tohru!
Jackie! I cannot
control my...
And in the summertime,
mother would cook
big bowls of mung beans.
Heads up! There you go!
Who wants sprinkles?
Don't come
to the doughnuts.
The doughnuts
will come to you.
Uh-oh! Um, stay where you are!
I'll go get more!
We have to--gaah--
remove your gloves
from your hands!
Sorry.
Bwaah!
Most sorry.
Ha ha! Huh?
Uh-oh.
Why hasn't
the alarm gone off?
Perhaps they
disabled it.
Steal greenbeard's loot
from mckutcheon, will they?
Well, mckutcheon's
stealing it back!
The museum.
I know where we are,
you daft...
You!
Hello again.
You know them?
Whoa! Who's the old lady
with the mustache?
Haggis! Sic!
(Babbling)
Cool.
Nobody grabs
my Booty twice!
You're goin' extinct!
Unh!
- Bwaah!
Jackie!
(Babbling)
Aah! Me kilt!
Ohh! Eeh!
Oogah boogah!
That's caveman
for "we win."
Whoa!
Uh, guys?
Stop!
I don't think
the gloves
are listening.
Maybe they'll
listen to this!
Oh, gloves!
I'm stealing
your Jewel.
Both: Whoa!
Come and catch me!
Jade, what are you...
You want it? Fetch!
Good-bye, sticky fingers.
Yes, but now this
will be even more
difficult to explain.
Wait! I have not
told you about
fourth grade.
Please, just...
Hey! Freeze!
(Whistles)
Heh. It was
the gloves?
Guess we'll have
to kiss your Booty
good-bye.
Angus: Shut it!
And my people were
part of an undercover
sting operation
to catch these notorious
modern-day pirates.
Sorry about the mix-up.
Never would've guessed
you guys were agents.
Of course you're
all free to go.
(Sighs)
Thank you all
for helping to
clear my name.
We shall see
how thankful you are
after uncle trounces
you in another game
of mah-jongg!
Hey! Uncle's
frowning again.
That means he's happy.
Got it!
And section 13 did
locate the gloves,
right?
Huh?
Hey, Jackie.
Have you ever
been bullied?
When I very,
very young, yes.
When I don't like
being bullied,
I go to beat somebody.
Ok, what happen?
I win.
But one day,
I'm gonna lose.
After that,
after I get hurt,
somebody bullied me,
I just, "yes."
Why? Because
this guy get beaten
by somebody one day.
There's
so many tough guy
in the world.
They get
in trouble some day.
Don't try to be
a tough guy.