Previously on
Jackie chan adventures...
Mom, dad!
What brings you out
to Hong Kong?
Oh!
Jade: Jackie?
I'm at the airport!
Shendu's flying to Australia!
The book of ages,
where all history's
magically recorded!
Jade: Are you telling me
shendu rules the world?
Each of the 8 emperors
has his or her own domain!
When shendu wrote in it,
he must have
rewrote the past!
(Gasps)
I'm in demon world!
Why don't I remember
any of it?
This is from the book,
and it's about me.
It didn't get rewritten,
so neither did I!
If the book's not here
in shendu's library,
there's only one other
place it could be.
Australia.
This will let us grab
the 12 talismans
that give shendu
his magical powers.
Chan!
(Roars)
Jackie!
Huh?
- Huh?
How can it be?
Huh?
My talisman!
I'm sorry, I'll give
it back, thank you!
Uhh! Oh!
Ohh!
How did I do that?
And why
do you not
catch fire?
Dog makes you immortal,
ox makes you super strong.
What else we got?
Speedy rabbit,
levitating rooster,
invisible snake,
and explosive dragon.
Ooh! Good ones!
Ohh!
Grr!
Maybe we better not try
for the other half dozen.
Grab the supplies!
Forbidden magic's
gonna be hard to come by
out there in demon world.
Tear them apart!
Grr!
Uh-oh.
Levitation plus speed
equals flight.
Huh?
- Huh?
Whoa!
- Whoa!
Stop them!
Whoa!
Oh! Dead end!
Dragon blast.
We'll outrun 'em...
By a hare.
Aah!
- Aah!
Centuries of history
altered.
Your very memory erased.
And still, somehow,
you defy me.
I shall find you, chan,
and I promise you,
I shall erase more
than your memory.
Jade was right, uncle!
I  am a hero.
We can infiltrate
the fortress,
find the book of ages,
and correct history!
Ow!
There is
a big army of ninjas
at the fortress
in no man's land!
No magic trinkets
will help us because
we will be outnumbered!
Uncle's right.
He is?
If we're gonna
pull this off,
we're gonna need
more muscle.
We're gonna need...
The j-team!
Ooh? Huh?
I see no one here
I would choose
as my apprentice.
Well, look again.
Uhh! Uhh!
He's...Big.
(Thundering footsteps)
(Uncle gasps)
But po Kong...Is  bigger!
Unh!
We must be
in her domain.
Looks like shendu's
keeping all his enemies
under demon watch.
More salt for my meal,
or I shall...
Devour you all!
Our hero cannot stop
a demon that size!
You're right.
You do it.
(Gasps)
M-m-m-me?
There's only
one surefire way
to stop a demon,
and that's to
show 'em the door.
Mmm!
Huh?
Chan?
Page 94, follow
the instructions!
You run interference!
Bwaa!
Jackie!
Leap and kick!
Uhh! Oh, gee!
(Groans)
Aah!
Bwaa!
Ohh!
Oooh.
Uncle, hurry!
I do not have
the symbol
of the immortal
who defeated her!
Fire was sword,
water was gourd,
sky was flute...
Bwoh!
Mmm!
You are going
to be scrumptious!
Earth was flower,
wind was fan,
mountain was...
Drum!
Tohru!
You--you know my name?
Talk later.
Bang the drum
3 times.
(Coughing, sputtering)
(Chanting)
Aah! Ah!
No!
Bwaa!
Oh, ohh.
That was
a very good spell.
(Cheering and laughing)
(Both grunting)
No mercy, gladiators!
Battle to the finish!
(Both grunting)
El toro will win.
El toro is the greatest!
(Uncle chanting)
Waaa!
Huh?
Fancy fan-work
courtesy of paco--
El toro's
biggest fan!
Finally we can remove
these ridiculous masks.
El toro fuerte  never
removes his mask.
What?
No music
while I bathe?
Sing for me,
my little
caged songbird!
Tweet, tweet.
(Uncle chants,
flute plays)
What? Who's
playing the flute?
I despise the flute!
(Uncle chanting)
No! No!
Who  are you guys?
Everybody,
- say hello to viper--
the craftiest member
of the j-team.
"Team," huh?
It's a wrap.
The j-team is
reassembled,
and hsi wu's
singing career
is down the drain.
(Thunder rumbles)
Uh, guess
you didn't know
hsi wu was scrubbing up
'cause he was
expecting company.
The thunder demon!
Jackie: Ah! Watch out!
(All yelling)
Aah! Oh!
(Grunting)
Heh. Time flies
when you're having fun.
Viper: Give me
your hand, sweetie.
(Grunts)
(Growling)
(Grunting)
Leap and kick,
leap and kick,
leap and kick.
Go, Jackie.
Your mouse man
is good, Jade,
but El toro
is the best!
No time
for that now, paco.
How's that
portal spell
coming, uncle?
You did not mention
that the thunder demon
would be in this domain!
We do not have
the symbol of
the immortal
who originally
defeated him!
(Sigh)
And it's not like
we can
pull castanets
out of thin air.
Castanets?
I prefer
the maracas,
but they
are too large
for my pockets.
(Grunts)
Ohh!
Sorry.
(Uncle chanting)
(Clicking)
(Grunts) No!
What are we waiting for?
To the book of ages!
Chan!
So he  is
behind this!
And things were
going  so well.
We were even
almost beginning
to like you, brother.
(Sputters)
What do you mean?
I was just
coming to visit...
Hsi wu?
He has been banished
to the netherworld!
Technology?
The child!
She somehow
escaped
the historical
alterations.
And if she knows
the history that was...
Then chan now
knows of the book.
What's up,
Mr. pouty snout?
(Sighs)
I do not belong
with these heroes.
The ox
made me strong.
Without it, I'm--
hello? The talismans
never made Jackie chan
a hero.
You didn't even  like
to use 'em.
Courage, brains, and heart
are your secret weapons,
and you've
already got those.
All you need
is proper training.
Jackie, I can teach you
what you taught me.
You game?
Game.
Cool! First lesson--
the ancient art
of butt whoop
starts with breathing.
The breath flows
to the fingertips,
then down to the toes.
Jade: The book lies
behind those walls.
Ready, team?
Let's make history.
There is no way in.
Both: T'ch!
Guys in pajamas.
They don't look
so tough.
I  am good at this.
Duh.
The mouse man
is not bad, but--
don't start.
(Grunts)
Haagh!
Uhh!
(Whistles)
And they didn't even
use the talismans.
(Rumbling)
Quick!
The spells!
What spells?
(Demonic laughter)
(Demons roar)
Quickly! Locate
the book of ages!
We better split up.
Bai tza: Destroy them!
(Roars)
(Growls)
Shendu and his
accursed talismans.
(Grunts)
(Gasps)
You're not
the only girl with
tricks up her sleeve.
(Shrieks)
(Snarls)
But you are
the only one
who can do that.
Behold my mastery
of gravity!
Unhh!
(Grunts)
Behold my mastery
of, uh,  pollo.
(Both grunting)
Jackie, help uncle search!
Stop fooling!
Fooling?
I'm not immortal!
Pff! Excuses!
Gaah!
Bingo!
There it is.
The book of ages?
Locate the page
shendu altered
so that we may
change it back.
No problem.
Look for a page
with a missing corner.
(Gasps) Unhh.
(Sinister hiss)
Whoa!
(Grunts)
(Groans)
(Grunting)
T'ch. There's, like,
5 million pages here!
Shendu: Get away
from that book!
(Groans)
Surrender.
Your team has been
neutralized.
Big whoop.
If I can't find
shendu's changes,
I'll make
some of my own.
"And then Jackie
grew 20 feet tall."
(Growls)
- (Gasps)
Heeyah!
Now Jackie
is the greatest!
You!
Jackie: Shendu!
The girl!
"Here comes...
Super tohru!"
(Growls)
Huh?
(Grunts)
"Say hello...
To robo-viper."
Like nuking fish
in a barrel.
(Shrieks)
My turn!
Hey, no fair!
Now El toro
is the greatest!
Jackie is!
El toro.
- Jackie.
- El toro.
El toro.
- Jackie.
You want to defeat
the demons? Yes?
Then write that uncle
banishes the demons
already!
Duh!
- Duh!
(Chanting)
Bad day...
For demons.
Demons: No!
I will have
my revenge, chan!
Yes!
Ha ha!
We did it!
Hotcha!
I have found
the page!
Uh, this means you
can change us back,
right, uncle?
Once we
make changes
to shendu's
changes.
Ooh, here!
Don't want to lose
my place in history.
Jade!
- Jade!
Mom! Dad!
Cousin Jackie!
Uncle!
What brings you
to Hong Kong?
Tohru:
Hong Kong moose world.
Uh, look at the watch
Jackie got me!
Paco: Moose world?
Can I go, too?
What mooses? We were
fighting demo--unhh!
Uh, traffic!
We were fighting
Hong Kong traffic
to visit you.
So I could show you
how much I've learned
in America.
We know you
have been doing
very well there,
Jade.
No doubt due to
cousin Jackie's
excellent
training.
In all honesty,
it is Jade who
sometimes trains me.
Hey, Jackie!
What kinds of
martial arts do you know?
So many, so many style
you talking
of martial arts--a thousand.
Most important,
whatever you learn,
it doesn't matter
karate, hapkido--whatever.
But everybody
has the same goal--
it's discipline.
It's not fighting,
remember.