Previously
- on  Jackie chan adventures...
Prepare for battle.
Daolon wong!
Enforcers: Argh!
Aah!
Unh!
Ugh!
Guh!
Busted.
Quickly, Jackie.
We must find
deja vu stone
before daolon wong.
Can you believe
dark wizard was
released from jail
for good behavior?
I do not think
the justice system
is prepared
to comprehend crimes
of magic, uncle.
(Gasps)
Blowfish indicates
stone is near.
What is so important
about a deja vu stone?
Whosoever
possesses stone
can transport himself
into his own past
and back again,
simply by willing it.
Daolon wong could revisit
all his past defeats.
(Grunting)
Ow!
Why would anyone
want to be defeated
over and over
again? Ow!
You are slow on uptake!
Daolon wong
is now powerless.
He would change
past outcomes
to regain his magic.
(Footsteps)
(Gasps)
The dark chi
master himself?
T'ch! The sly
niece-meister herself!
(Gasps)
The deja vu stone!
Jade!
Come on, Jackie.
I've helped save the day
72 times,
the world
half a dozen times,
and your butt more times
than I care to count.
And you have made
a mess of things
more times than I
care to count.
But I always clean up
after myself.
Just admit it, Jackie.
You need me. Hey!
Ha!
All: Daolon wong?!
Many thanks
for the memories.
Hyah!
Jackie?
(Echoing)
Uh, where'd they go?
Somewhere in time.
We must locate
their whereabouts.
How? History's
a big place.
Deja vu stone
allows one to travel
only into
their own past.
Jade:
Whoa! Mondo rewind.
But which Jackie
is the one we're
looking for?
According to uncle's
locator spell,
that one.
Funny. I have
the strangest feeling
I have been here before.
Chan! The tal--
oh, tohru! Am I
glad to see you!
One moment, I was
in the far east
confronting
daolon wong.
The next,
I am here in--
yargh!
Waah!
Grr!
Yargh!
Waah!
Tohru, what has
gotten into you?
It is as if
you are--
the talisman.
Working for
the dark hand.
The deja vu stone!
I have been here before!
Aah!
Yargh!
And I do not think
I enjoyed myself!
Whoa!
Grr!
Yargh!
I do not see
deja vu stone.
Daolon wong
must have it.
So Jackie's
stuck there?
And why isn't
wong with him?
Perhaps because
the ex-wizard
was randomly hurled
somewhere into
his own past.
We must help Jackie
with portal magic.
Unh!
Heh! I knew you were
going to do that.
I'm sorry to leave
a future friend
in the lurch, tohru.
Chan!
Both: Aah!
Ooh!
Hey, didn't
Jackie get out
of this scrape
in one piece
the first time
around?
When one revisits past,
one risks changing
its outcome.
Ooh! That's is not
what happened
the first time.
But this happens next.
Unh!
Waah!
You did it, unc!
So where's Jackie?
Portal magic good
for quick escape,
but only way back
to present time
is through the power
of the deja vu stone.
(Gasps)
Portal magic
will allow Jackie
to visit more memories,
where he will hopefully
locate daolon wong
and the stone.
How did I--
where am I?
Oh, no!
Oh! This is one memory
I have been trying
to forget!
I outran the train before,
I will do it again!
Unh! Aah!
I must be out of shape!
Uncle, when you
said the past
could change,
did you mean--
if Jackie makes
wrong move,
he may never
come out alive.
Yaah!
Aah!
Whew! The past
sure is tense.
Humph! Jackie must learn
to be more careful.
So, where to next?
Where Jackie stops,
nobody knows.
Ugh! Aah!
A broken leg?!
But I did not even
hit the ground!
Jackie!
Oh, Jade!
Do you see
the mess you have
gotten me into?
Gee, Jackie,
I already admitted
it was totally my fault
you slipped
on my gnomekop action figure
and busted your leg.
No, not that!
If you hadn't
gotten in the way
and allowed
daolon wong to take
the deja vu stone,
I wouldn't be
lost in time.
Huh?
Ugh! Never mind.
You are
the past Jade.
You wouldn't know
about that.
Uncle,
do you think
Jackie's right?
Did I really
mess things up?
Humph! Nonsense, Jade.
Jackie needs to watch
where he's walking.
Not the broken leg!
The deja vu thing!
I stood there
like a dummy
while wong
snaked it from me.
It's all my fault
Jackie's stuck
in rerun-ville.
Ohh!
Jackie!
Aah!
Gee. Couldn't you
send Jackie
to a less
life-threatening
roller coaster,
like the pukinator
at moose world?
Uncle has no control
over portal direction.
It is process of
trial and error.
Bad day, bad day,
bad day!
Mostly error.
Aah!
Whoa!
After him!
Oh, magic hole,
please open up!
I do not know
where you come from,
but I am ready for you
to take me away from here!
Whoa! Look at
Jackie go!
Hmm.
Guess he does do ok
without my help.
Aah!
I'll give Jackie
a 9.2 for thinking
on his feet,
but we really
work much better
as a team.
Jackie: No! No, Jade!
Do not get on that plane!
Heh heh! See?
Teamwork!
You never listen.
Not this.
Anything but this!
(Huffing and puffing)
Aah!
Ohh!
Ok, things can't
get any worse
for Jackie.
Unh!
Turning into statue
is better?
Heh heh.
- Depends who you ask.
Jackie: Quick, Jade!
The antidote!
No!
T'ch, you'd think
I woulda got it right
the second time around.
Your past self
does not know then
what you know now,
Jade.
Maybe--
urk--
this is preferable to--
ohh--
being cursed
to relive all the--
uhh--
worst moments of my life!
Whew!
Jackie was very close
to becoming pigeon roost.
Uh, let's hope
he doesn't become
dragon chow.
Uhh!
Of all the villains,
I had to bump
into shendu?
Uhh!
Cute.
Bwaaa!
(Gasps)
Invisibility.
Bwaaa!
Monkey see, monkey do!
Aah!
Ooh!
If memory serves,
here's where I make
a star entrance
and save the day.
The strength talisman.
Good one.
I know, Jade--
bwaaa!
Jade?!
How did you--
your hands!
I get it,
that must be
some uncle magic and--
(Gasps)
Bwaaa!
Ugh!
I blew it again!
I distracted Jackie
just like I did today.
Does twice make a pattern?
Oh, no!
Valmont has
the dragon talisman power!
Ah, now things are
getting interesting.
Uhh!
Ohh!
Respect your elders.
Uncle! How do you
spray for bugs?
Ow!
One more thing...
Ha ha!
Who else wants
a piece of uncle?
Ok, but have you
saved Jackie's butt
72 times?
I'm the one who always
gets him out of binds.
Uhh!
Do not waste
your strength.
Someone will come.
This is a job
for supermoose!
¶ Dope Dee dope Dee Doe ¶
guh-huh.
Heh. Well,
almost always.
Could it be?
Jackie: A view?
In a nice, cozy,
danger-free hotel?
A happy memory?
Wha? Bwaaa!
Jackie, don't worry.
I can explain everything.
(Creaking)
(Together)
Heh. Hi, Jackie.
So I'm quite the rascal.
But it's not like
I'm evil or anything.
Jackie: Jade?
I couldn't help it.
I was possessed!
Did uncle ask you
to tattoo demon face
onto your leg?
No?
You do not see
uncle walking around
being evil, do you?
Uh...Unc?
(Snarling)
Uncle could not help it,
was victim of chi vampire.
Oh, yeah,
- and I had a piece
of your mind.
You must keep
vampire uncle busy
while I learn
how to subdue him!
My master will feast
upon your  chi!
Please, learn fast!
And while you're at it,
learn a way to send me
back to the future
where I belong!
Uncle, isn't there
some way to,
I don't know,
make the portal
magic work faster?
There is one way,
but it is
very risky.
Riskier than
an up-close look
at po Kong
- the mountain demon's
tonsils?
Megadose of garlic.
Whew!
Too close.
(Gasps)
It is as I feared!
Bad day! Bad day!
What's happening,
uncle?
Garlic has accelerated
portal magic,
causing Jackie to bounce
against walls of time.
Jackie:
Bad day! Bad day!
One more thing.
Duh. T'ch.
Duh. T'ch. Duh.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
If this doesn't
end soon,
I'm gonna hurl.
Uncle becoming
very dizzy.
Aah!
Ohh. Where'd
he go this time?
Ah!
Brrr!
We have found
daolon wong,
but not deja vu stone.
Their struggle
must have caused
stone itself
to be randomly lost
in one of their
past experiences.
Uncle!
Aah! Uhh!
Huh?
Uh...Hello.
Uhh!
Hmm.
Portal magic?
See the oinker
at 12 o'clock?
Yes, that is
very nice, Jade,
but I am really
not supposed to be here--
oh.
There!
Check it out!
I helped!
The deja vu stone.
Uh, yeah, whatever.
Aren't we looking
for the pig talisman?
Uhh!
Tohru!
Many thanks
for leading us
to the prize.
You are not welcome.
You!
Why so afraid?
He is an old man.
Uhh! Ohh! Uhh!
Ohh! Uhh! Ohh!
Uhh!
That will teach
foolish tohru
to mess with uncle
when he is powered
by immortality talisman.
Oh. Do not tell
faithful apprentice
uncle said that.
Come on, Jackie!
Grab the stone
and will yourself
back here.
Hyah!
Since you seem
to have things
well in hand, uncle,
I will take my leave.
(Gasps)
The stone is mine!
Who is that?!
And what is
with this stone
you all keep
jabbering about?
Whoa. Wong
snaked his way in!
Aiyaaa!
(Breathing hard)
Take me back
to the beginning!
So here we are,
back in the old fool's
trash heap.
That is old fool's
rare trash heap to you!
Wait a sec.
Jackie went to
the wrong beginning:
The first time
we met!
Wait. This can't
be right.
Where are uncle and--
give me that!
Ohh!
Jade.
Jackie is right.
I do get in his way.
You're Jackie chan,
the archeologist?
I bet
you are looking
for the shield
I brought back
from Bavaria.
We're looking for--
how'd you know?
He has it.
Chan is lying!
Do you not recognize
your master?
The only master
we have is big v.
Chow: And he's gonna
wanna hear all about
where you stashed
the shield.
Way to rewrite
history, Jackie.
Did they buy anything?
No.
You are terrible salesman!
Who are
you calling?
Jade's parents.
She must return
to Hong Kong.
But she just arrived!
What? No way!
Who's gonna help
save the day?
The world?
Jackie's butt?!
Uncle,
you must trust me.
It will be
better for Jade,
for us,
if she does not stay.
No, Jackie.
Hang up the phone.
You need me.
Hyah!
Jade is in the house.
I got your back,
Jackie.
Man: Hello?
Uh, sorry.
Wrong number.
Uncle: Jackie,
next time you
make crank call,
phone local.
Living with you guys
is gonna rock!
(Sighs)
You have no idea yet
just how much.
(Gasps)
You speak English!
Now, return me
to the present.
Jackie!
You do need me!
Jade,
how did you know?
Where did Jackie go?
I'm glad you decided
to keep me around.
Let us just say,
I realized that perhaps
you have saved me
a time or two.
T'ch. Try 72.
Hey, Jackie, do you
believe fortune tellers
can predict the future?
Uh, actually,
I don't believe.
I only believe myself.
Work hard, learn more,
helping people,
always give people
second chance,
then you have
a good future.
That's what I believe.