And now that I'm finally
rid of that pestilent
lizard shendu,
the dark hand
will rise agai--
uh, valmont?
Your pancakes
are gettin' cold.
Mmhh. Mmm. Mmhh.
Speaking
of temperature,
we shall need to acquire
some serious heat
if we're to embark
on our epic crime spree.
Now you're talkin',
big v.
So, what's the plan?
You three will break
into section 13
and steal the talismans.
Whoa!
Again?!
Uh, bustin'
into section 13's
kinda risky.
Besides, v,
we don't do
flunky work anymore.
Not unless
we're gettin' paid.
Uh...True...
This demon nonsense
has depleted
dark hand finances...
But you know
I'm good for it.
Ok, but you gotta
make us partners.
Call yourselves
vice presidents
if you wish.
Just bring me
those talismans!
Hey!
What?
I didn't eat.
(Thunder)
Darkness shall begin
its reign.
(Snoring)
Huh?
Huh? Huh? What? Hmm?
Uh...Sensei. What is it?
Uncle has the willies.
(Beeping)
(Sighs) Some herbal tea
to lull me to sleep.
Hey, Jackie!
Uhh!
Oh! Jade!
You should be
asleep.
So should you. And
I know just the thing
to help you unwind.
First we strap on
rollerblades
and set up
trash-can goalposts.
Then we slip
a few talismans
out of the vault.
Just because
I can't sleep
doesn't mean
you don't have to.
I am near.
How did you
get in here?
Freeze!
Whoa!
Mmhh!
Mmph!
Daolon:
The talismans of shendu...
So close I can feel
the 12 powers
of the Chinese zodiac.
(Thud)
Shh!
Sweet. No guards
in sight.
Shh!
Man, security
here stinks!
Shh!
I told you
- security here stinks.
5...6...
7...
Guards must be
on coffee break.
And monkey makes 12.
Oomp!
We'll take those!
Who are you,
anyway?
Ooh, ooh, I know.
He's the drummer
from kiss.
All: Whoa!
Who are you?
(Gasps)
The dark hand!
Daolon wong!
Uh, daolon wong,
the dark hand.
Jackie!
Aah!
Jade?
They have
the talismans!
Who?
Score.
You gotta be kidding me.
Gan! Ren! Chui!
Where'd they
come from?
Be cool. Be cool.
All: Chan!
Retrieve
the talismans.
What he said.
Jackie!
All: Whoo!
Ooh, daddy like.
The child!
All: Huh?
(Chanting)
Tohru! Now!
Go, uncle!
My warriors...
Imprisoned?
How did you locate
the lost urn of wei Cheng?
I know a thing
or 2 about antiques.
Keep the warriors.
Aiyaa!
Both: Uncle!
I will take the talismans.
Ready, aim...
Vaporize.
Waa!
Whoop!
She's got 'em!
Both:
Ooh! Unh!
Jade: Jackie!
Jackie!
You must not let daolon wong
have the talismans!
Ok. No one
will have them.
Ratso: They're gonna blow!
Uh-oh.
Oh, well.
Ah.
Jackie,
you blew 'em up.
(Sighs)
It is finally over.
Ow!
Not over.
It is just
beginning.
It is?
Talismans
- can be destroyed,
but the powers
they contain cannot.
The magic has been
set free,
scattered
to the winds.
Which means daolon wong
will try to find them.
You mean,
Jackie just started
the talisman hunt
all over again? Cool.
Unh! But where
did the magic go?
With no vessels
to contain them,
the powers will return
to their owners,
the 12 animals
of the Chinese zodiac.
Hello. The Chinese zodiac
is way ancient.
Those animals are history.
As such,
the talisman magic
will be drawn
to noble animals:
Those most worthy
- of their regal ancestors.
12 living creatures
each about to receive
an extraordinary gift.
What have I done?!
Do not just stand there!
Get cracking!
Uncle: You must
locate each animal
before its power
can be claimed
by the forces
of darkness.
Jackie.
What's going on?
More than you can
possibly imagine.
Well?!
Uh...
That thing about
making us partners?
don't worry
about it.
If I were employing you,
I would  fire you!
You three...
I require
your assistance.
So...What's the gig pay?
(Chanting)
Aah!
You're orange.
You're bald.
Freaky.
Bow before me,
dark chi warriors.
Finn don't bow
to no--
uh...Ow!
Whoa!
Hey!
You are no longer
mortal men,
but powerful servants
enslaved to do
my bidding.
Now, see here!
Finn,
ratso, and chow
are  my servants,
and I will thank
you not to--
aaah! Hey!
Ahh, it would seem
good fortune is mine,
for one
- of the talisman's powers
remains near.
Come, my warriors!
Are we supposed to--
wait!
You can't
just leave me here!
Release me at once!
(Chanting)
Any sign of daolon,
uncle?
I thought we were
looking for animals.
Sensei says
each animal requires
a different locator spell
to lead us to it,
but we do not have time
to research them all,
with daolon on the loose.
Oh, we are
getting something.
It's...A woman.
She's got soap.
My mastery of spells
is no match for daolon's.
Wait! There's more.
Jackie: It looks like
daolon is going to...
A dog show?!
Daolon has located
the power of immortality.
(Arf)
Oh! That stray
is harassing
my Jasper-wasper.
Security!
Which is the beast
that I seek?
If I destroy all of them,
one would remain standing...
The one which holds
the power of immortality.
Jackie, the power
of immortality resides
in one of the dogs!
But which one?
Oh! Jackie!
Huh?
Hyah!
Quickly! We must take the dog
where daolon's magic
cannot reach!
But  which dog, uncle?
Were you not listening?!
The most noble one!
But--oh!
Excuse me.
Pardon me.
Giddyup!
Get along, little doggies.
(Arf)
Gan! Ren! Chui!
Whoa.
There is something
different about them.
They got
- a dark chi makeover.
Warriors, get them!
Get along,
little doggies!
You can trap
the dark hand guys
in another urn, right?
There is only one
urn of wei Cheng,
and it is already
occupied!
I am so buff!
Hey, we can fly!
Groovy!
Run!
Tohru.
Whoa.
Hey, buddy.
Sweet.
Score!
Attack!
(Roar)
Good dogs.  Good dogs.
Whoa! Bad dogs!
Bad dogs! Bad dogs!
Whoa!
Aah!
Stay.
Face it, tohru.
You're no match
for...Uh...
Whatever we are!
No.
Hiya, scruffy.
Good boy. Good boy.
Uncle, walk the dogs.
Whoa! Aah!
Scruffy!
Mongrel, be gone!
(Gasps)
The immortal.
That is the noble dog
we have been
looking for?
Jade, shoo.
Aww!
Scruffy!
Surrender your power
to the forces of--
(arf!)
Aah!
Scruffy! Here, boy!
Aw, cute.
Too bad you gotta
hand him over.
Jackie!
Hey!
Chan!
My hammer!
Hunh!
Huh?
No way.
Guys! Check it out!
Remote control.
Rock 'n' roll.
Bwaah!
(Chuckling)
It's like playin'
a video game.
(Uncle chanting)
I may be an old dog,
but I have new tricks.
Whoa, down, boy.
Can we keep him, Jackie,
please?!
Uh...
Of course we keep him.
Yay!
Go get it, boy.
Until uncle
can transfer the power
into a new vessel,
the dog is
a living talisman.
The little fella
really should stay
where it's safe, Jackie.
But section 13
isn't safe.
Daolon already
penetrated security
once.
Magic defeats magic.
A good chi spell will keep
daolon and his warriors out.
One more thing.
Ow!
Get cracking!
You have 11 more animals
to locate.
Jade: Hey, Jackie...
Yes?
What do you do to
stay in shape?
Basically training
with my stunt guy,
with my students,
3 hours a day.
Also boxing--
the rhythm--
bam bam bam bam.
Lift weights,
badminton school,
jogging, ping-pong.
Move your whole body.
Training is
very important. Yes.