Aah!
Please! Be gentle!
That Mayan calendar wheel
is more than
1,000 years old!
Whoa!
Aah!
Stop!
Nice wheel!
Here, wheel!
Please!
Excuse me,
sorry!
That should
buff right out!
(Gasping)
(Gasps)
Whoa!
Aah!
(Grunts)
Captain black: Been
looking everywhere
for you, Jackie.
I have
a high priority
assignment
especially suited
to your talents.
Baby-sitting?
Not baby-sitting,
body guarding,
and this isn't
just anybody.
You'll
be guarding leli,
the king of tangra.
Jade: A king?
Cool.
Count me in!
Sorry, Jade.
This is a diplomatic visit.
The king can't see anyone
who doesn't have
level "a" clearance.
Besides,
don't you have
a book report
to work on?
Jackie,
why bother reading
about some president
from
a gazillion years ago,
when I could
be meeting
a real, live king!
I'm sorry, Jade,
but you heard captain black.
So the king
can't see anyone
who isn't cleared, huh?
It is most important
to observe all formal customs
in the presence
of his majesty.
Eh,
I will do my best.
Nice digs.
Undercover security.
This king
must be all that.
Jade: Whoa,
the dude's  barely that.
May I present leli,
the king of tangra.
And shaktar,
his royal tutor.
Tangra, where
a kid can be a king.
Whoa!
Mr. chan,
it is customary to perform
the song of welcome.
Oh, yes,
I would love to hear it.
It is  you who is
to sing, Mr. chan.
Me?!
Later. What I would
truly like to do
is to explore
the city.
And so you shall,
my king,
but we are past due
for a ceremony at city hall.
Your car awaits.
Looking out the window
of a limousine
is not the sightseeing
I had in mind.
A limo ride
sounds good to me!
Whoa.
These suits and ties
aren't security,
not with those
- "have a rotten day" tattoos.
Leli: Look!
The golden gate bridge!
Did you realize, shaktar,
that it is so expansive,
that as soon as a crew
finishes painting it,
they must start over again?
I was not aware of that,
my king.
And there!
That is bayview stadium.
How I would love to witness
a baseball game.
Fancy hotels,
luxury cars...
Yeah, I could
get used to this.
(Crowd applauds)
Mayor: And so,
it is in the spirit
of friendship
and cooperation
that I present you
with this key
to our fair city.
Thank you,
San Francisco, thank you!
You are too kind.
You really know how
to make a Princess
feel welcome.
(Gasps)
Stop!
Jackie: Uhh!
Oh, photographer.
Heh, sorry.
Uh-oh.
Jackie!
Jade?
Ooh!
- Ow!
King leli!
Bad men!
Sorry,
I'll give it back!
Thank you!
Uhh!
Kidnapper: Oof!
That was amazing
the way
you defeated those
men single-handedly!
Hello, what am I?
Invisible?
Oh, yeah.
And you have never
seen those men before?
A trying day,
your highness.
But now it is time
for your meditation period.
Then we will turn
to your studies.
I have not yet
taken a ride
on a cable car.
I want to sightsee.
I'm sorry,
your majesty,
that is not possible.
Those bad men
are still at large.
You must remain indoors
and under close watch
for the rest of your stay.
Now, now, your highness.
All is not blue.
I have the royal chefs
working on a wonderful dinner.
Broccoli stew.
Broccoli  souffle,
my king.
Yuck!
Double yuck.
Meditation,
studies, broccoli.
Why is there
never any time
for fun?
Uhh.
And why
is this couch
so lumpy?
I am not lumpy!
We will leave you
to your meditation,
your majesty.
(Sighs)
Yes, yes.
As always,
you will not
be disturbed
until I return
in 4 hours.
4 hours?!
I am so out of here.
Ohh!
Soon as
the coast is clear,
I burn rubber.
Huh?
Announcer: And it's
the bottom of the 8th.
Prospectors are up by 3.
Oh, king,
I like your style.
Announcer:
...Swing and a miss!
Munson's having
a great day on the mound.
8 ks in the last 3 innings.
And the pitch...
Strike 2!
Full count, runners
on first and second.
There's the pitch.
It's a sizzler
down the left field line.
Aaron scoops it up
and sends it to third.
And he's overthrown...
Soy beans?
Thanks.
Both: Aah!
Who is there?!
Reveal yourself!
Wh-wh-who are you?
I'm, uh,
part of your
security team.
Jackie's partner.
Name's Jade.
And you can
become invisible?
Can all bodyguards
do that?
Only if they have
one of these babies.
Ahh, a talisman.
A  magic talisman.
May I see?
How does it work?
You just squeeze it
in your hand.
Uh, but I don't think--
yep, heh,
you learn fast.
Ok, now open your hand
to become visible again.
Uh, king?
Your majesty?
Leli?
I can't believe it.
Leli...
Pulled a Jade!
With this tea, we drink
to the northern mountains
and the Southern seas.
(Floor creaks)
Oh, ok, king,
I know you're here...
Somewhere.
Heh, mosquito.
Got it.
Cable car!
You seen a kid
about 8 years old,
wearing...
(Sigh)
He'd stay invisible.
May I buy
one of your sodas,
please?
I'm so thirsty.
Ok, hon,
but they're warm.
Perfect!
Gotcha!
You are so busted!
Uhh! Ohh!
- Don't even
think about it,
and don't say a word
until we get
to the next stop.
(Gasps)
The king is gone!
Game over,
your highness.
I am sorry, Jade.
Let me explain.
No! Let me explain!
You may be
Mr. big shot king,
all I gotta do
is snap my fingers
and get whatever I want
in  your country,
but here,
in the U.S. of a.,
what you did
is called stealing.
I only meant
to borrow it
so I could escape.
Well, even
borrowing something
that isn't yours
is wrong...
And I should know.
And what
- do you mean, escape?
You've got it
made in the shade.
You have no idea
what it's like being a king.
Everything
is pomp and ceremony.
There's never any time
for normal things.
No time for fun.
Oh, I guess that could
get kind of boring.
I suppose you will
be taking me back now.
King,
you're about to go
on the "j" line tour.
Oh, my king,
what cruel fate
has befallen you?
(Cell phone rings)
Hello?
Black: Jackie,
we have a security problem.
Yes, I know.
You  know
the snake
is missing?
What snake?
The snake talisman.
You just said you knew.
Power of invisibility...
Jade.
I'm losing you,
Jackie.
Good news,
captain black.
I don't think the king
has been kidnapped.
Kidnapped?!
-What are you--
-ohh, uh,
I have to go!
I'll call you later!
Bye-bye!
Is it about
the boy?
I believe his majesty
is safe and out exploring
with my niece.
Oh, this
is wonderful news.
Not for my niece.
I will find them.
I will join you.
The boy has often
spoken of places
he wished to visit,
but first,
I must inform
the others.
Yes?
Understood.
The boy is out
in the open.
The next call
will tell us where.
Then
we make the grab.
Leli: Ha ha ha ha!
Come look!
Look over here!
Ha ha ha!
(Both laugh)
Whoa, yippee!
We ought
to be getting back.
Please,
there is one more
place I must visit.
And there's
the pitch!
It's gonna
be close!
The runner slides!
He's safe!
Jackie: Yes,
but  you are in trouble.
Both: I can explain.
We have located the boy.
Bayview stadium.
The talisman.
Heh, found out
about that, too, huh?
(Crash)
(Gasps)
Stay where you are
if you want the boy
to remain unharmed.
Uhh! Help!
Jackie:
No, captain black,
no word yet
from the kidnappers.
Yes,
please send a chopper.
I want Jade
and the, uh,
our reptile friend
back at section 13,
where they won't
cause any more trouble.
(Beeping)
It's a ransom note.
Shaktar is to deliver
the crown jewels of tangra
to a warehouse downtown,
alone,
within one hour
or we will never
see the king again.
(Gasps)
The crown jewels?
They are tangra's
most valuable treasure!
How do you worry
of mere baubles?
The boy
is in danger!
I will come with you.
But they requested me,
uh, alone.
We...Must do nothing
to jeopardize leli's
safe return.
Exactly.
These are bad men.
We cannot be sure
they will honor
their word.
Jackie,
let me come,
please?
Leli's
my friend.
I know that, Jade,
but it is
too dangerous.
Captain black
is on his way.
He will
be picking you up
by helicopter.
But Jackie...
You will return
the talisman
to the vault,
do your homework,
and go to bed.
(Scoffs)
Please,
bring our king
safely home.
I will not fail
his majesty.
Shaktar's hooked up
with the kidnappers!
I will see you
in the morning, Jade.
Jackie, wait!
(Helicopter arrives)
Jade?
Time to head back
to the old...
Jade?
I have brought
what you asked.
Your highness!
Are you all right?
Bring
the crown jewels to us,
and then
we let the boy go!
Whoa! Oof!
What sorcery is this?!
Nice try, shaktar,
but your cover
is blown.
Both: Jade!
And no ice
for you boys
till leli
is down here with me!
Oh, shh, Jade! No!
The whole thing's
a set up, Jackie!
What is going on here,
shaktar?!
We told you
to come alone!
Come alone? Hello?
What's  that tell ya?
Shaktar hands over
the jewels, let's 'em
keep leli,
then they fax in
another ransom.
What nonsense
does she speak?!
I don't know.
Jade, you have gone
too far this time.
Jackie,
shaktar's got a tattoo
on the back of his neck,
just like
the other bad guys.
Look for yourself.
I'm sorry, shaktar,
but may I see
the back of your neck,
please?
But I thought--
shaktar: You thought wrong.
A simple plan.
Pawn the crown jewels,
use the funds to train
an elite fighting team,
and then a palace takeover.
But why?
Why? Because serving a king
is beneath me,
and I detest children.
Yeah? Well, you're gonna
have to get past one
to get your mitts
on the crown jewels!
Jade, no!
With pleasure.
Whoa!
Jade!
Aah!
Oh!
But how?
It is my mental kung fu.
I practice it
while meditating.
Care to see more?
Now,  that was good.
Guess now you're
an army of one.
As long as I have
the jewels.
Shaktar, no!
Perhaps we should use
the invisibility talisman
and assist.
Jackie doesn't need
any help.
Besides, if he gets
a serious workout,
he may forget all about
grounding me.
Uhh...
Jackie chan,
for heroism
in the service
of the royal family,
I present you
with the star
of tangra.
Thank you, your highness.
Oh--
please,
do not bother.
I always thought
it looked foolish.
I much prefer
the high-five.
Whoa--unh!
Thank you
for everything, Jade.
You gave me a day
I will never forget.
Hey, even a king needs
a little vacation.
Perhaps someday
you will come visit?
We could play some ball.
You're on.
Hey, Jackie, is it hard
to be a celebrity?
You get a lot of things,
you lost a lot of things.
One day I sit down
in a shopping mall
coffee shop,
my friend said,
"I saw somebody
wanted your autograph."
As soon as I sign, 2 hours.
I just keep signing,
keep signing.
I really don't have
a private life anymore.
The good things, really,
I can get a lot
of free gifts.
Somebody give me one shoes,
I say, "can I have another
hundred pair?"
Somebody give me
exercise equipment...
"Can I have another
couple sets?"
Then I select
which high school,
which charity--I just give.
That's the best things
becoming famous.