I'm in the woods.
I'm tired, cold, and hungry,
and I'm being hunted!
Aah!
Jade, I thought
you were going
to gather firewood.
Hello. Have you learned
nothing from the movies?
Whoever gets the firewood
is always the creeping
terror's first victim.
So that's what happened
to the other little girl
I sent out for firewood.
Very funny.
I thought
Mr. excitement there
was going to guide us
straight to
the low-cost temple.
"Lotus" temple,
and I didn't ask you
to come along.
Yeah, well, I didn't
want to miss out
on all the fun.
Ancient wisdom:
Crouching tiger
is invisible
until teeth flash
in moonlight.
Well, duh.
Can we go home?
Jade, it's
very important
that we locate
the lotus temple.
Somewhere inside is
the scroll of hung-chao.
It holds inscriptions
of great power.
Ancient wisdom:
Words are breath that blows
the fire of knowledge.
Yes! And our fire
needs wood. Go.
Oh, stay in sight
of the camp.
Stay in sight,
like, I was going to...
Get lost.
Oh, boy. This is
exactly what happens
before the creeping terror
shows up.
No problem.
I'll just retrace my steps.
Uhh!
Aah!
Ok. This was
not here before.
(Crying)
Ohh.
You should
not be here.
Why? What's the matter?
Why are you crying?
Run from this place.
Please!
(Roars)
Whoa. Talk about
a mood swing.
Jade! Ohh, I told
her to stay close.
She never listens.
Ancient wisdom:
The foolish monkey
chases its tail
and catches trouble.
Mm. I should have
brought a map.
Jade!
(Growls)
Uhh!
Ohh.
Aah!
This is exactly why
I didn't want
to go get firewood.
(Roars)
(Growls)
Aah!
Whew.
(Growls)
Whoooooa!
Grrrrr.
Aah!
(Roars)
Psych.
(Roaring)
Whoooooa!
(Roaring in pain)
(Breathless)
I humbly...
Beg forgiveness.
It is the power
of the lotus temple
that changes me.
I am forced to guard it
against all intruders.
Yeah, well,
you should put up
a beware of monster
sign or something.
If you heard my tale,
you would understand.
Please.
Oh, man.
I'll listen...
As long as
you don't get
all "grrr" on me.
5 years ago,
on an evening like this,
I wandered into the forest
against my father's wishes.
It grew dark,
and I was soon
lost in the bamboo.
Hey, same here.
Then, under the light
of the full moon,
the lotus temple appeared.
I thought
it was a miracle,
saving me from the cold.
The next morning,
with the first
rays of the sun,
the temple began
to disappear,
and I vanished
along with it.
Hold the cell phone.
Are you saying
this place only
exists at night?
Yes, and only
under a full moon.
Anyone trapped within
when the sun rises
becomes a temple guardian
and may never leave again.
Pretty good fairy tale,
but there's one hole
in your story.
Why weren't you attacked
by a temple guardian?
The previous guardian
found the means
to escape.
I've searched 5 years
for that secret,
but have not found it.
I miss my family so much.
Hmm.
I'm all about
beating the system.
Let's see.
You only go monstery
about intruders,
right?
So if you ask
for my help,
I'm not intruding.
I'm helping.
Please, would you
enter and assist me?
But if I grow horns,
flee at once!
You got it.
I am xu-lin.
I'm Jade.
Jade! Jade!
Oh, where is she?
Bwaa!
Perhaps the little
monkey is closer
than you think.
The lotus temple.
Are you coming?
I will wait here.
I would not want to...
Intrude.
This is the library.
Here lies the wisdom
of many ages.
Wow! I'll bet the secret
to escape is written
on one of these.
Aah! Aah! Aah!
Xu-lin?!
Jade!
I'm changing.
There must be an intruder.
Run, Jade! Hide!
Hey! I'm a guest.
But I sure feel
sorry for whoever--
uncle Jackie!
Jade?
(Growling)
Bwaa!
(Growls)
Uh, heh heh.
- Aah!
Bwaa!
Uncle Jackie!
Oh, man!
Which way? Which way?
Unh! Ohh!
Excuse me,
I'm just looking for...
Bwaa! Aah!
Ow!
(Roars)
Huh?
(Gasps)
Aah! Unh!
(Coughs)
(Roars)
Unh!
(Gurgling)
Bwaa!
The scroll of hung-chao.
Dah!
Oof!
(Coughing)
Ohh...
Yaah!
Huh?
Uncle Jackie!
Are you--
what have you done
to xu-lin?!
She was a monster.
She attacked me.
Ohh, ohh.
Duh! It's her job.
She's the temple guardian.
It's a bizarro
temple power or something.
It turns her
into a monster
whenever
there are intruders.
Intruders?
I would not
want to...
Intrude.
You knew about
the temple guardian.
Of course. Ancient wisdom:
The worm realizes
he is bait
only after
the fish bites.
Yah!
- Whoa! Ohh!
Hyah! Yah! Yah!
Yah!
Ugh! Intruders!
Tell me you aren't doing
what I think you're doing.
Unh! Ugh!
Uncle Jackie?
(Growling)
Jade! Run!
No! Wrong way! Wrong way!
Xu-lin! Stop!
That's my uncle.
He's to help you, too!
(Roars)
I don't think
she wants my help!
Ah, yes.
Intriguing.
Jade: Oh!
Jade!
I'm ok.
Help xu-lin!
Jade!
(Xu-lin moans)
Ancient wisdom:
The cornered rat
finds peace...
In eternity.
The door!
Uncle Jackie, wait!
Ow!
I tried to tell you,
she's trapped here.
It's some kind
of curse.
Ohh.
Leave me, Jade.
Escape while
you can.
No! We're going
to find a cure
or an antidote
or something.
Right, uncle Jackie?
We will try.
Unh! Aah!
Jade, I'm changing.
No biggie.
Stay calm.
Just try
to remember,
I am your guest
and uncle Jackie...
He is invited.
Good girl!
No more palm blasting!
You think that
is the only power
granted by the scroll
of hung-chao?
Haison! Haison! Haison!
Xu-lin, what happened
with the monster bit?
Go hulk already!
Too weak.
Huh? Unh!
Ancient wisdom:
The wise man
never walks out
on free
entertainment.
Hey! How come you
can leave the temple?
Xu-lin? Wake up! Wake up!
Get him, uncle Jackie!
Get who?
Jackie,
your hands! Look!
Huh?
No more palm blasting!
The inscriptions.
Give armor-boy a taste
of hung-chao mojo, quick!
No!
Xu-lin! Come on!
Ohh.
Both: Uh-oh.
(Roars)
No!
Fung dah! Fung dah!
Ruh!
- Fung dah! Fung dah!
(Monk straining)
Uncle Jackie,
the sun's coming up!
Good.
You don't understand.
The temple vanishes at Dawn,
and anyone inside
goes with it.
How many crazy rules
does this temple have?
You go! I will save
xu-lin!
Raah!
Come on!
It will not work.
The power of the temple
will not let me leave.
The armor...
It can leave
the temple.
Yes!
Jackie:
Whooaa!
(Coughing)
Whew.
Noooo!
Heh.
Easy come, easy go.
Oh, thank you
for freeing me.
At least the scroll
of hung-chao is destroyed.
No one else will learn
its dangerous secret.
You know, I'll bet
we could redraw
those inscriptions
on your hands.
I mean, it'd take
a few tries--
Jade, playing with magic
is too dangerous.
I only hope
to once again
see my parents
and have nothing
more to do with
magic ever again!
Come on.
Where's your spirit
of adventure, xu-lin?
Ancient wisdom:
Wise monkey knows
when to stifle spirit
of adventure
and concentrate
on schoolwork.
You just made that up.
No. It's old,
very old.
Hey, Jackie, where
did you live when
you were little?
After my father,
for the living,
he had to go to Australia,
American embassy.
As soon as my father move,
then I have nowhere to live,
so they put me
- to the martial opera school.
Inside, just like
the movie called  fame.
One thing's different is
we have to stay there.
We stay, live there,
eat there.
Teach you how to dance,
how to kicking, punch,
somersault, acrobatic,
all kind of things.
School is very,
very important.
Education is
very, very important.