Ohh.
The lengths to which
I will go for...
An  oni mask.
Grr!
Ooh.
I know what I'm wearing
for Halloween.
(Muffled yell)
Uhh!
Waah!
Ohh! Hyah!
Uhh!
Happy Halloween.
Looking for a mask?
That one!
Uhh!
Whoa! Ooh!
All: Ohh.
Heh.  Oni?
Nice try.
Ohh!
Uhh!
Chow:
It's in here somewhere.
Trick for you,
treat for me.
Jackie: I have the mask
right here,
safe inside section 13.
Uncle: So there is
no need to make
mask removal potion?
Not this time, uncle.
The only masks
you will see tonight
will be on the faces
of trick-or-treating children.
Aaaaah!
Oh, Jade!
Who is Jade?
I am oni boo-boo,
mistress
of the dark.
Ooh. Makeup?
Ohh.
Jade, you shouldn't
scare people like that.
Tch. Scaring's
the whole point
of Halloween, Jackie,
and I have to win
the scariest
costume award
at school tonight.
But of all things,
you had to choose--
I don't know anything
scarier-looking
than an  oni demon.
Do you?
Now, come on.
Time's a-wastin'.
We have to get
at least an hour
of trick-or-treating
before the fright fair.
Whoa!
Jade: Captain black.
Nice chicken suit.
Actually,
bald eagle.
And it seems
you're the only one
who read my "dress
for the day" memo.
Buenos noches,
mis amigos.
You and
El toro fuerte.
This is no costume,
captain black.
This is a way of life.
Pollo?
(Sighs)
Bald e--
oh, never mind.
El toro, I'm so glad
you could join us
for Halloween.
And next year,
you and Jade
must join us
in Mexico for  El
da de los muertos,
the day of the dead.
Where is
the boy wonder paco?
Paco: I think
you mean...
El paco fuerte!
Are you prepared
to face wrestling's
second-mightiest champion
next to El toro?
Let's rumble,
tumbelina.
No, paco.
Someone
could get hurt.
Someone?
Meaning me?
Uh, no. Um...
What I meant
to say is, uh...
Never forget
the first rule
of  lucha libre.
No wrestling
outside the ring.
You think wrestling's
second-mightiest champion
can be defeated
by a girl?
Oh, no!
- Of course not, paco.
Hands down, you're
king of the ring.
But the queen of scream is
gonna beat the pants off you
in tonight's
costume contest.
You do not think
my mask is worthy?
Sure...
If you're going
as a skier.
First prize goes
to the scariest
costume.
Heh heh.
Look at the time.
We had better get
trick-or-treating
before the witching
hour strikes.
Yes! Come, children.
Perhaps I am not cut out
for this "Halloween."
Ooh.
A face even scarier
than Jade's.
Chow: No.
Not it.
Nuh-uh.
No.
Aw!
We're missin' out on all
the trick-or-treatin'.
Gentlemen.
Whoa!
Tarakudo!
Pop quiz.
Why is Jackie chan
not also here,
searching for the mask?
Uh...
Answer--because Mr. chan
already has the mask.
Ohh!
I knew that.
End of quiz.
Now for the pop.
Aah!
- Aah!
Ohh!
- Ohh!
Can we knock on
uncle's door first?
My demon duds'll
blow his mind.
Oh! The  oni mask!
Where is paco?
Where is the mask?!
Do you think
I am scary now?
Ohh!
- Copycat!
Jade, I do not think
paco is wearing makeup.
Oh.
Uh-oh.
Paco,
your face?
Uh, paco is
wearing a mask
which we must have
magically removed.
Immediately.
I am sorry,
but we  luchadores
never remove our masks.
That is my paco.
El toro, that is
no ordinary mask.
Jade: Paco...
Just stay calm
till uncle gets here.
Then we can put
this whole thing behind us
and get on with
our trick-or-treating.
Trick-or-treating?
A fine idea.
Paco!
No!
(Rings)
Hello?
Jackie, uncle is
very busy right now.
(Doorbell rings)
Tohru!
Candy!
Coming,  sensei.
Bzzz! Bzzz!
Arrr, Matey!
Raaagh!
Why must uncle devise
removal potion now?
Very nice Japanese
oni demon costume.
Happy Halloween.
Thank you, good-bye.
Nice?
Nice?!
I am scary!
Grr!
Who put new  oni mask
on face?
How could you
not see him
when he was right
under your nose!
Uh,  sensei?
Aiyaaa!
Quickly, tohru.
We must prepare
mask removal potion.
I have  mucho competition
in the scary department.
Believe me,
you have
no competition.
Ohh! Are you
the great pumpkin?
Uh...Indeed.
And I'm here
to show all ghoulies,
goblins, and demons
how to be as scary
as they can be.
Teach me, great one.
All you need to do
is feel the power,
call upon the darkness
within...
So, this mask is stuck
to paco's face?
And we need to unstick it
before paco figures out
how to summon
his shadowkhan.
(Doorbell rings)
Whoa! Those are
some crazy...
Costumes?
Trick or treat.
Grr!
Paco:
If you offer no treat,
then we must trick!
No!
No! No! No!
Go away!
(Whimpers)
Mmm.  Delicioso.
You passed
your first test
with flying colors.
Next on the to-do list:
Bathing the earth
in darkness.
El toro: You there!
Step away from
mi paquito.
I'm sorry.
This little devil
bows to a new
master,
masked man.
Indeed, El toro.
I am no longer your
little towel boy.
I am El paco diablo!
Who is this
cabeza gigante?
Taraku--oh.
Yes, that is
a very lovely costume,
but I am busy right now.
Do not touch
the mask, children.
Jade: Uh, guys?
I don't think these
are trick-or-treaters.
Shadowkhan.
Slimy, slithering,
made-for-Halloween
shadowkhan.
Yaaah!
Uhh!
I hope uncle's almost ready
with that potion.
Twick or tweat.
Bzzz. Bzzz.
Happy Halloween.
Uncle: Tohru,
scale of lizard!
(Doorbell rings)
Tohru, door!
Bzzz.
- Happy Halloween.
Uncle: Tohru, wolfbane!
(Doorbell rings)
Door!
Uncle: Sulfur root!
(Doorbell rings)
Door!
Eye of newt!
No, left eye of newt!
(Doorbell rings)
Door!
Special ingredient.
Tentacle
of Japanese octopus.
(Doorbell rings)
Door!
(Gasping)
Trick or treat.
Tohru, uncle needs
octopus tentacle now!
Uncle: Candy?
Oh, no.
Aiyaaa!
Gnarly, dude!
Uhh!
Uhh! Uhh!
Ohh! Aah!
Uhh!
Sorry.
The shadowkhan are
excellent minions
of darkness,
are they not, Jade?
Tarakudo:
Spiffy costume,
little lady.
Rehearsing your
inevitable return
to the dark side?
Maybe so, tarakudo.
Jade: Stop!
I, oni boo-boo,
call upon
the darkness within me
to command you ninjas
to stand down!
Heh heh.
Worth a try.
Still you attempt
to outdo me?
Ha ha! We shall see,
once and for all,
who is truly
the scariest.
Shadowkhan!
Jackieee!
No!
Uhh!
- Aah!
(Together)
Ohh.
Jackie,
how is it possible
to defeat
a floating head?
Hmm.
(Doorbell rings)
Uh, trick or treat?
Gracias, but I am
on a special diet.
Do you have onions?
Uhh!
Let go of me,
you slugs!
Jade! Uhh!
Jackieeeeee--
uhh!
Aah!
Tsk, tsk, tsk,
Mr. chan.
No mask?
Tarakudo: Much better.
Jackie o'lantern.
And now it's time
to send you to
the pumpkin patch.
(Sniffs)
I would prefer...
The onion field!
Aah!
Aah! My eyes!
My eyes!
But where are
paco and Jade?
Paco wants to prove
he is scariest.
Tohru...
Jackie: Meet us
at Jade's school
with the mask
removal potion.
Uh, we will
be there,
uh, shortly, Jackie.
Do not worry, tohru.
How hard can it be
to find boy
in ghost costume?
(Gasps)
Hey, come on.
You kids need a ticket
like everybody else.
What are you?
Eww!
This job don't pay enough!
(Roars)
(Excited yelling)
Ha ha.
No contest.
I am the scariest,
which means you
no longer need
to wear a mask.
Heh. But I'm not
wearing a mask.
I know.
I am the winner.
And second place...
Loses face!
(Gulps)
(Weakly)
Let's rumble.
Rrahhr!
Halt!
El toro: There will be
no fighting here.
Grr!
And why not?
Uh...
Because you know
the first rule
of  lucha libre.
No wrestling
outside the ring.
I would not want
to break any rules.
Now, El toro,
prepare to surrender
your title
to El paco diablo!
I will simply keep
the little one pinned
until your uncle arrives
with the magic potion.
Do not let paco's size
fool you, El toro.
Cabo cannonball!
Hrrahh!
Ooh, that's gonna
leave a mark.
Where is uncle?
Dude, check out what
this big Bumblebee
guy gave me.
It's like some kinda
suction cup candy.
(Together)
Ooh, cool!
Please, you do not want
to eat that.
Hands off, dude.
It's mine!
Trade you.
Natchez knee-dropper.
- Ohh!
Ohh.
I will pin paco
after a brief siesta.
We gonna wait for
El toro to tag us,
or are we gonna--
Jade! Uhh!
Palenque pile-driver!
Jalisco hammer-down!
Tijuana twister!
Ohh!
Smash him,
El toro!
Jade, it is still paco.
Heh heh.
Sorry.
I was
in the moment.
Ohh.
You know the second rule
of  lucha libre,
don't you, El toro?
The winner may remove
the loser's mask!
Uncle: Speaking
of mask removal,
¶ uncle has
a treat for you ¶
float like a buccaneer,
sting like a bee.
Aiyaaa!
You did not tell uncle
new shadowkhan can
stretch like Taffy!
Jackie!
Uhh!
(Gasping together)
Uhh! Aah!
Aah!
Well, there goes
our last pair
of free hands.
Unless you count
demon boy.
Paco, you must
remove your mask.
Why would I want
to do that, loser?
I am not talking
to you, demon.
I am talking to the paco
behind your mask.
But, El toro,
you know the  luchador
must never remove
his own mask.
That rule must
now be broken
by both of us.
(Gasps)
El toro...
Why?!
Now, paco,
it is your turn.
El toro: Use the potion
to remove the mask!
Do not listen!
¶ La la la la
la la la la ¶
no!
I must remove
the mask.
Uhh!
Jade: Do it, paco!
Go for the potion!
Magic must
defeat magic!
Remove the mask.
No, remain a demon!
Remain a demon!
Remove.
Remain!
Uhh! Remove!
Remove the mask.
Yes, paco!
Uhh! Uhh! Uhh!
Nooo!
Waaah! Waaah! Waaah!
Buh-bye.
No more Halloween
horror from you.
El toro,
I think I have been
a very bad little  luchador.
Paquito, you may be
small of stature,
but your
inner strength
knows no bounds.
Jade: Here, paco.
I think this
belongs to you.
Because I was
the scariest?
Puh-leeze!
That honor would
belong to  moi.
But tonight,
you're the champ.
You should have
seen yourself
smacking your
bad self down.
The palenque piledriver!
Hunh!
The jalisco hammerdown
huwah!
The fuerte face-puller!
Yaah!
Paco, you were in the zone.
Hey, Jackie,
do you like scary movies?
Scary movies, yes.
Actually...
Because I'm a filmmaker,
I like scary movies,
drama, comedy, action.
But when I watch
a scary movie,
not nighttime.
You know, really,
after you are watching
you fall asleep,
you can't sleep.
So, comedy at night.
Daytime, scary.