Roberta, why are you up?
It's not even morning.
The goats--
they're afraid, mama.
Maybe it's the...
(Whispering)
Chupacabra.
(Laughs)
Oh, little one,
there is no chupacabra.
It's just a story
we tell
so that small
children will stay
inside at night.
Like they have
been told to?
But the goats?
They will be fine.
(Growling)
(Banging)
(Gasps)
(Howling)
The chupacabra is real!
(Baaa)
Jackie:
Incredible!
Incredibly boring.
What kind of
lame pyramid is this?
No mummy curses,
no booby traps,
no bonus points?
Oh, this is not
a video game, Jade.
This is
important research.
(Growls)
I have had enough work
for one day.
It is quitting time.
Bye-bye.
Faster!
Go faster!
I am not a horse!
Faster!
Go faster!
(Cell phone rings)
Hello?
Senor Jackie,
it is I, El toro.
I have
unfortunate news.
An ancient evil
plagues my people.
It is the goat-eater...
The chupacabra.
Chupacabra? But that is
just a fairy tale!
No...It is a real evil
from which grown men hide
like frightened children
and no goat is safe.
Uhh, Jackie?
Uh, El toro,
I am a little busy
right now.
May I call you back?
El toro: Of course.
But the sun
will soon set
and I need your help,
my friend.
I know of ancient tablets
which tell the legend
of the chupacabra.
They may reveal a method
to rid us of the beast.
I need you to translate.
Jackie: As long as
nothing chases me!
Aah!
- Aah!
We'll be there,
El toro.
Jade: You know, you should
really get voice mail.
Hola!
Eww. You didn't tell me
paco would be here.
It is good
to see you, too,
seorita Jade.
(Kiss)
Come, Jackie. We must
prepare to battle
the chupacabra.
Wait, wait, wait!
You said you only
needed me
to translate
ancient tablets.
There is no time.
The beast attacks
by dark of night.
This rocks, paco!
Jackie's gonna kick butt
on the chalupa-cabra thingy.
No. El toro will
destroy the beast.
No. Jackie.
The mouse man?
Jackie is not
a mouse man!
Is too.
- Is not.
Is not.
- Is too.
Is too.
- Is not.
Mother: It is just
as we told El toro!
The chupacabra
attacked our house!
And exactly what did
the creature look like?
It was giant...
With glowing red eyes!
Fur! Fangs!
Oh! Claws, too!
And it howled like this--
"arroooo!"
Yep, sounds like
a Chimichanga to me.
Now do you
believe?
I believe that we are
talking about a coyote.
What?
Aah!
That is not a coyote!
(Roars)
Everybody inside!
Bolt the door!
Hello, Mr. chupacabra.
You look like you're
having a very bad night.
Do you have a splinter
in your paw?
Perhaps we can help.
(Snarling)
Waah!
Stay beside me, Jade.
I will keep you safe.
(Growling)
Sorry! No solicitors!
Is there
another way out?
No!
It's after the goat!
Let's just give it to--
don't even finish
that sentence.
Yaah!
Jackie:
You do not want to eat me!
I am not a goat!
(El toro groans)
(Snarls)
Fear not!
The beast is no match
for El toro, the bull!
And El Jackie,
the, uh, the chan!
Hyah!
- Hyah!
(Growls)
Jackie: Huh!
Ow!
That's one point
for Jackie.
No. That's one point
for El toro.
Jackie made
contact first.
Did not.
- Did too.
Did too!
- Did not!
(Growls)
Never touch the mask!
Unh!
(Both grunting)
You all right?
I am fine.
A scratch here or there.
Mother: El toro,
you have saved us all!
You destroyed
the chupacabra!
It was not me, paco.
It appears that sunlight
is the Victor.
That's one point
for sunlight.
It does not matter.
El toro is the greatest
hero in the world!
Jackie is.
Is not.
Is too.
- Is not.
Is not.
- Is too.
Children, please.
We must celebrate!
(Music playing)
(Laughing and talking)
The goats are afraid...
As if the chupacabra
is near.
Oh, that is
crazy talk.
Perhaps not, my friend.
Do not let
the children know.
The beast wounded me...
But it is a small injury
to which I would
normally give no notice.
I fear that I have
been tainted by
the creature's evil...
Infected by its
ancient malevolence.
Take me to the tablets
you needed me to translate.
The beast hunts by night,
hides by day...
It feeds on
livestock and goats...
Sunlight will
destroy the beast.
Ahh, my friend,
I fear you must
translate more quickly.
I feel like I am missing
something obvious.
Oh, wait! Here it is!
(Growling)
"Beware of
the chupacabra's claw...
"The evil can be transferred
from beast to man
and the man will
become the beast!"
Bad news--aah!
(Roaring)
Ohh!
Run! Run! Run!
The chupacabra is loose!
Nice costume.
We go together.
(Roars)
(Screaming)
Aah!
Huh? I thought
the candelabra thingy
was history.
Hey! I recognize
that mask!
Yoo-hoo!
Yummy goat right here!
(Roars)
I did not mean to touch
your mask. Sorry.
Jade: That's one point
for Jackie...
For whatever
you just did.
Jackie's so fast,
sometimes the eye
can't catch it.
Where's El toro?
Paco, that was El toro.
It's the curse
of the chupacabra.
El toro is
no longer the bull.
He is...El toro'cabra.
Noooo!
Don't worry. I already
called for help.
The flight was delayed,
the food was terrible,
the movie had no plot,
and I had turbulence!
Can you cure
El toro?
Do not rush the chi!
(Exhales)
I have all but
one ingredient.
A powder made
from capsicum.
I have never heard
of capsicum.
It can break
the chupacabra curse?
No! It is only
one ingredient!
Does no one
listen to me?
One more thing!
To find the best capsicum,
we must visit the wise elder
atop El picacho del diablo--
the mountain of the devil!
Can you move
any more slowly?
Why do I have
to carry everything?
You want the children
to break their backs?
And my hands hold the map!
I would feel
a lot better
if that map
were right side up.
Look, uncle knows
what's what.
We'll be fine.
Don't worry.
My worry is only for
the world's greatest
hero--El toro!
Because his fate
is in the hands of
a puny mouse man.
Jackie is not
a mouse man!
Is too.
(Gasps)
(Roaring)
Jackie:
Go! Go! Go!
Paco: El toro!
It's me! Paco!
I do not want to hurt you!
El toro--I mean,
Mr. El toro'cabra,
we do not have any goats.
Why are you attacking us?
Jackie: Oh! The mask!
Paco, drop
the mask and run!
No! I will never
abandon the mask of
El toro fuertes! Aah!
Hah! Hah! Hah! Hah!
Throw him this!
You are not an animal!
You are the bull!
(Growling)
Oh, ok,
bull is an animal,
but it is only
a nickname! Oh!
Ok, that's one point
for Jackie,
but I don't like
this game anymore.
It will be
"game over"
in a minute.
I cannot
let that happen.
El toro, this way!
It's me, paco!
Don't you remember?
I am your greatest fan!
Let me help you!
No, paco! Don't!
(Howls)
Sorry again,
but we had to get you
out of the sunlight.
Jackie, my friend,
you have succeeded!
You have lifted the curse
of the chupacabra.
I am El toro again!
Thank you!
Uh...
El toro!
I saved your mask.
I do not understand.
We didn't do anything
to lift the curse.
Aah! The sun!
I--I am still cursed.
That explains
why the chupacabra
only hunts at night.
Take it. I do not
deserve to wear it.
I am still
the goat-eater.
Stop whining!
We just need to find
some capsicum!
But you said it is
on top of the mountain!
We'll never make it there
and back by nightfall.
And by then...
By then I will have
become the beast
once more.
Uh, excuse me, elder...
Can you tell us
where we might find
some capsicum?
We need capsicum
for an antidote.
I do not give out
my capsicum
to just anybody.
Go away.
But my friend has been
turned into an chupacabra!
(Gasps)
Chupacabra!
Here.
- All the capsicum
you could want.
(Grunting)
No! Must fight!
To remain human!
Aah--arooo!
El toro, we have the--aah!
(Snarling)
El toro!
Paco: No!
(Roars)
Always make a backup.
Make sure he drinks it all!
(Roars)
Ohh!
Skael!
(Gagging)
The magic is not working!
Maybe I should have
put in more wood spurge.
Ol'! The bull is back!
El toro! Your mask!
Thank you.
I knew you would
keep it safe.
One more thing!
El toro,
do not go swimming
for half an hour.
Now, let me go home!
Jackie's back to
mucho bonus points.
Admit it, paco.
He's the greatest.
No way! El toro gets
mucho mega bonus points
for living through
the chupacabra curse.
Your mouse man is
the second greatest.
No, he's not.
Yes, he is!
No!
- Yes!
- No!
Man: Hey, Jackie!
Who's your role model?
When I was young, of course,
some of my teachers,
I just think they're great.
But later on,
when I'm growing up,
when I'm making a movie,
then I find out
my role model--
Charlie chaplin, Harold Lloyd,
buster Keaton.
How difficult
that they made a movie.
Because in that day,
silent movie without
all the special effect,
without all the protection,
they still do a great stunt.
That's my goal.
One day, I want to be them.
Anybody better than me,
that's my role model.