Sold for $200.
The next item up for auction
is a porcelain lamp
featuring, well,
an unusual rat motif.
What am I bid
for this piece?
$100.
Do I hear 150?
200.
Smashing. Do I hear--
250!
-300.
-350.
-4!
-500.
-6!
-7!
-8!
-9!
1,000.
2,000.
That's all
I got, tohru.
Think they
take nunchucks?
$2,000.
Going once...
Going twice...
Sold for--
aah!
I'm sorry.
I'll send you
a check, ok?
Huh?!
Unh! Oh!
This building
should be condemned.
Whoa-oh!
Unh!
Hmm...
Hey! My hat!
This area's
restricted!
We're blowin' up
the--oof!
Whaaaaa!
Yes! Yes!
Noooo!
Another train wreck,
Jackie?
Uh, I was going to
ask you the same thing.
Do baboons live here?
Jade, you must learn
to clean up after--
you've got it,
Jackie-o.
Tell ya what--
- I'll clean the whole place,
and you can reward me
with, oh...
I don't know,
a turbo troll?
You already have
one of those.
Uh-uh! I have gnomekop.
Turbo troll
is his mortal enemy,
and if I get both of them,
they'll fight each other.
Everyone's collecting them,
Jackie.
Can I please have one,
please?
Mmm, we'll talk about it
when you finish cleaning.
[Chuckling to himself]
Gnomekop:
Gnome power!
Jackie: Oof!
[Gasps] Gnomekop!
Must find
turbo troll.
[Sighs in relief]
It's ok, Jackie.
Nothing's broken.
Oh-ohhhh...
Jackie?
Ooh! Ah!
Ow! Ooh!
Run down the side
of an exploding
building--
no problem!
But step
on a child's toy,
break your bones.
Wah ha ha ha!
Sounds like
a Chinese proverb...
Oh! It's all my fault.
Huh! Jackie
is young and strong.
He will heal
quickly.
Accidents happen, Jade.
But do you now see
the importance
of tidiness?
I'll make it up
to you, Jackie.
I promise.
How's my patient?
Ha!
According to uncle,
strong enough to do
his research.
Hey, who knows?
Maybe this rat
is the heal-a-broken-leg
talisman. Hmm.
All tidy.
Not a toy in sight.
Gnomekop:
Must find turbo troll!
Must find turbo tr--
[nervous laugh]
The power of the rat
brings motion
to the motionless.
Hmm...
Need anything?
Uh, no. Thank you.
Warm up your tea?
I just need quiet
so I can concentrate.
I'll just fluff
your pillow.
Ooh!
Nice and fluffy.
Uh, Jade,
I can take care
of myself.
Remember,
within every weakness
lies strength.
Whatever you say,
Jackie.
Here. Let's just move
you a little closer
to the desk.
Oww!
Sorry!
Waa-aah! Aah!
Jade: Sorry!
Turbo troll!
Towels! Towels!
Belt blaster!
Jade: You sure
you're ok?
I'm fine. Ah,
where's the talisman?
[Gasps]
Man on p.A.: Full alert!
Intruder in the compound!
Full alert!
And when
we came back,
the lock was melted,
and the talisman
was gone.
The dark hand--
they've located us.
Black to vault,
report!
Condition blue,
sir.
The other talismans
are secure...So far.
This is all my fault, too.
If I hadn't spilled
that stupid tea...
I'm gonna find--
gnomekop?!
Must find turbo troll!
Whoa.
Who goes there?
You've never said
that before.
Come here, you.
Hey!
Jade!
-Aah!
-Whoa!
Leg, leg...
Jackie, something's
wrong with gnomekop.
He's--
please, Jade. I've had
all the gnomekop I want
for one day.
-Jackie!
-Gnome power!
Ohh!
Aah! Whoa!
I know where you live!
That toy should be
taken off the market.
I tried to tell you.
He's not just a toy
anymore.
He's alive! Alive!
Oh, what do you mean,
he's--
[gasps]
Motion to the motionless.
Weird talisman
power, huh?
We found nothing
in the debris, master.
The rat talisman
is the key to
my freedom, valmont.
It will reanimate me
into flesh and blood.
Ooh. You mean
you'd get back
all your
dragon powers
and stuff.
No. Shendu
will still require
the other talismans
and our continued
assistance for that.
Judging my experience,
I will remain in this
petrified state forever,
and you will never
lay your eyes
on the lost treasure
of ching shian.
2 words--
mouse hunt.
And the talisman
must've dropped inside
and transformed the toy
into a living, breathing
thing.
Jackie, when you fell,
did you hit your head?
Captain black,
look!
Yeah, he was
right behind you.
Of course he was,
Jackie.
Jade, no!
Gotcha!
Unh!
[Embarrassed laugh]
Loose thread.
All gone.
Thank you, Jade.
Gnomekop:
Must find turbo troll!
Turbo troll...
[Jackie and Jade
grunting]
That phone booth is not
wheelchair accessible.
Oh, you! Don't move!
Unngghh!
Stay back, Jade.
No, Jackie.
You have a broken leg.
And gnomekop is
my responsibility.
Eee-yeow!
Got you!
Belt blaster!
Whoa!
Aah!
Sorry.
Stop.
Gnome power! Unh!
[Gasps]
Jackie!
Whoa-oh-oh!
Brakes.
Brakes, brakes, brakes!
-Whoa!
Whaaah!
Oof!
Oh. [Panting]
Whew.
Gnomekop?
I can't escape you.
[Gasps]
Hang on,
Jackie!
Sorry.
I'll bring it back.
Thank you.
Jackie!
Unh!
How's the leg?
Where is turbo troll,
scourge of the elfin realm?
Uhh! Enemy mine!
There he is, Jackie!
Jackie?!
Unh! Unh!
Coming!
Turbo troll?!
[Gasps]
A battalion!
Why would he
come to the mall?
Maybe
he's a mall rat?
Gnomekop: Must destroy
turbo troll!
[All shouting at once]
Grrr! Rrr!
Gnome power!
Ohh! Come on!
Conceal me,
brothers.
Oh, my gosh!
Turbo troll captured
the gnome Princess!
That cad will pay!
Gnome power!
He's crazy.
He could hurt someone.
Yeah! Like you!
[Yelling]
Aah! Oof!
Jackie!
Huh?
[Struggling]
Troll armies
are amassing.
Gnomekop must
be liberated!
What is it
going on about?
Turbo troll is gnomekop's
archenemy.
See, the emperor
of troll castle
hates gnomes
'cause gnomes
possess magic from
the great crystal,
so gnomekop uses
his power belt to...
[Nervous chuckle]
I, uh, collect 'em.
Shendu: Enough of
sprites and fairies.
The talisman,
valmont.
Yaaugh!
Gnomekop escaped
the bald-headed
giant's fortress.
He will escape you
as well.
Baldheaded giant?
Could he mean
captain black?
Does it matter?!
Give me the talisman!
Shendu, if this gnome
escaped from section 13,
then perhaps
it can lead us there.
[Hissing sigh]
The other talismans.
Mighty warrior,
we just received word
that turbo troll
has claimed
the baldheaded
giant's fortress
as his stronghold.
Aarrrhh!
I will have his head!
No sign of him.
Sure does a lot of damage
for a runt.
Jackie!
[Sniffing]
He's going down--
whoa!
Shh!
Look.
He's retracing
his steps.
But they'll follow him
back to section 13.
I'll warn captain black.
You do that.
He'll love the part
about the dark hand
teaming up
with a magic gnome.
Well, do you have
a better idea?
Remember that turbo troll
I've been wanting?
Jade: Psst!
Yaah!
Turbo troll rules!
Must destroy turbo troll!
You sure Chucky
ain't lost?
Jade: Yaa-aa-aaugh!
Aaarrr!
Here he comes.
[Grunting and groaning]
[Nervous laugh]
Oh, no!
Turbo troll is near.
You wanna sign my cast?
Leave him alone!
He's disabled!
Waaah!
Ohh!
Jade:
Jackie!
[Gasp]
Have a nice swim, chan.
Hope you
haven't eaten
for an hour.
Jackie!
You, fan boy...
The doll.
[Sniffing]
Turbo troll is near.
Argh! Unh!
Hey!
Gnome power!
Here he is...
And there he goes.
Huh?
Whoa...Wha?
Ow! Ow!
Grrr! Grrr!
Hang on, Jackie!
[Panting]
Jade!
Jade?
Aah!
Oh! Ow!
Grrr! Grrr!
Whoa.
Whaaah!
[Whistling]
Here, boy.
Gnomes
can't swim.
Jackie: Jade,
remove the talisman.
Argh!
Unhand me, giant!
Oh-aaah!
Jackie!
Whoa!
Gnome power!
Waa-aa-aa-aa-
aa-aa-oh!
Aah!
Oh.
Unh...
Not again.
Your majesty,
king of gnomes--
-come here!
-No!
I'm sorry. I'll
bring these back.
Thank you-ooo!
Gotcha! Ooh!
Gnome power!
Aah!
No way.
Where is turbo troll?
In his pants.
Must destroy turbo troll!
No! No!
No-o-o-o-o!
Run away!
We must retrieve
the talisman.
You're kidding,
right?
Jade: So while Jackie
distracted giant gnomekop,
I climbed up top,
crawled inside his mouth,
and got the talisman.
You did very well, Jade.
Yeah, except
for the part where
I slipped and fell off
and landed on Jackie.
Oh...
Agreed.
Oh!
Puuh!
Jackie is young
and strong.
He will
heal quickly.
Hey, Jackie, have you
been seriously hurt
doing your own stunts?
Yes. So many times.
My eyes, my face,
shoulder...
Nose 3 times...
Elbow, elbow...
Cannot remember.
My jaws, knees, knees.
Cut. Ankle, ankle.
All of my teeth gone.
I hurt. Cannot remember.
Cannot remember.
But most important,
you remember.
Don't do any
dangerous stunt at home.
Only in the movies.