I cannot believe
I am stuck in the jungle
with such a spoiled brat.
You invited me.
I was talking
about him.
Mr. Smith! Please,
we must stay together.
There are many dangers
in the bush.
Eh, yes, yes,
so you keep saying.
Hop to it, Larsen.
Why don't we ditch
frick and frack
and have some real fun?
Go swinging
with the monkeys
or wrestle a crocodile?
What do you say, big j?
I'm sorry, Jade,
but you must learn
that growing up
sometimes means
having to do things
that are not fun.
Like guiding
obnoxious jerks
through the jungle
just 'cause they
give lots of money
to the museum?
Uh...Yes.
In that case,
- I never want to grow up.
What am I saying?
I can't wait to grow up.
Get my own car,
cell phone--
which, now that you
mention it...
I didn't mention it.
Smith: Oh, Mr. chan...
(Sighs) Yes?
Uh, why don't you
take a fiver
while Larsen snaps
a few photos?
Oh. Please, Mr. Smith,
this is no place
to dawdle.
Well, how do I look,
Larsen?
Very vibrant, sir.
(Twigs snapping)
(Gasps)
Do not move!
Black panther!
Shoo! Shoo-shoo-shoo!
(Growling)
Uh, Jackie?
I think that only
works on bears.
Haah!
Nobody move.
Aah! Throw me
your camera!
That is
a $4,000 zoltex
with a hand-ground
German lens and--
grrr!
Whew!
And if you want
photographs,
buy picture postcards
at the airport!
I am through
warning you
about the dangers
of the bush.
This happens again,
we turn back.
Oh, all right, Mr. chan.
You've made your point.
No dawdling.
Speaking of which,
it seems to me
that if we continue
on this path,
it will take 2 days
to reach the lost city
of the muntabs,
but only 2 hours
if we climb over
that mountain.
If I had a cell phone,
we could have called ahead
for a weather report.
According to my map,
the lost city
of the muntabs
should be right...
Well, now we know
how the lost city
got its name.
This map can't be wrong.
I--I--I paid a fortune
for it!
I warned you when we
began the expedition,
Mr. Smith.
The map might be
a forgery.
There has never been any proof
that muntab ruins exist.
What's so great about
these muntabs, anyway?
Ancient legends
speak of
the muntabs'
extraordinary health
and long life.
Ooh! Just imagine
what secrets
their artifacts
might reveal.
I suggest we turn back
before the storm
grows any worse.
I refuse to give up
so easily!
I can't. I won't!
Whoa.
(Squeaking)
Ohh, the muntab cloak
of invisibility!
The what?
Some legends speak
of the muntabs'
mastery of mirage--
a mixture of science
and sorcery
that allowed them
to shield their city.
It's definitely a wall,
and if there's a wall,
there must be a door.
(Gasps)
I found it, Larsen,
the lost city
of the muntabs.
Bully for you,
sir.
We must proceed
with extreme caution.
There is no telling
what lies...
Ahead?
It's like
something out of
a Tarzan movie.
It's fantastic.
Muntabs, Larsen.
They still exist.
So it would
appear, sir.
You know, if I had
a cell phone,
we could be
calling 911.
Not now.
Quickly, Larsen.
Take a picture.
No! Do not make
any sudden moves!
(Murmuring)
Eh, wait!
Uh, please!
We mean no harm.
Uh, I am
an archaeologist.
We are just visitors,
uh, accidental tourists.
(Murmuring)
Sorry. I did not
want to do that.
Uh, better come up
with some more stuff
you don't want to do,
quick.
Huh? What is he,
a coward?
It's called capturing
the high ground.
Hello? Martial arts 101?
This is a very bad way
to work out disagreements.
How about we sit down
and--ooof!
Ohh! (Grunting)
(Grunting)
Jackie!
(Gasps)
Ohhh!
Please, I don't want
to hurt you.
(Growls)
I warned you.
(Crunching)
(Grunts)
You don't know who
you're messing with!
Once my uncle Jackie
gets hold of you,
you're history!
Jade, please.
You will anger them.
A bit late for that,
I dare say.
(Gasps) Their chief!
Well, talk
to him, chan.
You're the expert
on aboriginal
cultures.
Huh? Uh...
How about that rain?
Outsiders
not welcome here.
Eh, we come
in peace.
In fact,
we will happily
leave in peace.
Hopefully one piece.
This...Weapon?
Heh heh. No, no.
A ca-me-ra.
Push the button.
Go ahead.
(Everyone gasps)
(Muttering)
Light in a box.
(Chief laughing)
(Muntabs laughing)
Oh. Ha ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha hee hee!
(All laughter stops)
(Clears throat)
You see, we mean
no harm.
Chief: One way to be sure.
A test.
Behold cave of truth.
Only pure of spirit
may pass through unharmed.
Well, if you're
asking for
volunteers...
Him.
Huh?
Um, so what happens
if he doesn't
make it through?
Then you shall
all suffer
a fate far worse
than his.
Uh-huh.
Come on, chan!
Get your game face
on! Let's go!
You can do it, Jackie!
I know you can!
I'm almost positive
you can.
Uh, just between
you and me,
what are his chances?
Many have entered
the cave...
And?
None have emerged.
Ohhh.
(Gasps) A white rhino!
But you are extinct!
Ahh. Another
muntab mirage.
Aaaah! Not a mirage!
Bad day, bad day!
Sorry. Good rhino.
I don't hear anything.
Is that a good sign?
Aaaaaah!
D-ohhh!
Aaaaaaaah!
Very bad day!
(Rumbling)
Chan!
Please, Jackie.
His heart
was not pure.
You will all pay
for your lies.
(Coughing)
You should really
reinforce those walls.
Cave is very flimsy.
What'd I tell you?
My uncle is pure of heart
and tough as nails.
Ohhh.
(Playing in rhythm)
Eat, eat.
Thank you.
You are very generous.
Generosity
not given.
It is earned.
Oh, that's
very wise, yes.
Uh, one would expect
a chief of such wisdom
to be an old man,
but you, uh,
not a gray hair
or a wrinkle.
In fact, not one of you
looks a day over 35.
It is a blessing
to have wisdom of age
and body of youth.
Oh, I couldn't agree more.
So how do you do it?
Uh, diets? Exercise?
Our ways
are muntab ways.
Oh, come on, chief.
I'm prepared to offer
plenty for your secret.
Do you know
what this is?
Money. Major  dinero.
Hmm. Prefer cloth.
Huh. Tell you
one thing, chan.
These people
may look good,
but they are backward
as all get out.
(Laughter)
Come, Jade.
We play.
Hello.
Cool, abila.
2 dolls for
the price of one.
Want to play
with her?
Uh, thanks,
but I'm a little old
to be playing with dolls.
Oh--not that there's
anything wrong with them.
I mean, when I was
your age--
what are you,
like, 7, 8?
Heh. 230.
(Laughs) Oh, right.
Jade, I want to
show you something,
but you must promise
to keep it a secret.
My nickname? Fort Knox.
Secrets go in,
they don't come out.
Honored guest,
tell me, what
brought you here?
How you
find muntabs?
Mr. Smith
purchased this map,
and we began
searching for your ruins.
Uh, I mean,
not ruins. I mean,
we had no idea
that your people still...
Uh, that you were--
ah! Entertainment!
Honored guest,
please join fire dance.
Oh, uh, well, thank you.
But I am not much
of a dancer.
Not wise to dishonor chief.
This ought to be good.
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Honored guest spoke truth.
Not good dancer.
(Gasps)
Chalice of life!
It is gone!
Chalice of life?
Muntab: Chalice!
Second muntab:
Where's the chalice?
Return it, now!
Uh, but I did not
take your chalice.
See?
Lies!
Hold on!
Jackie went through
that truth tunnel thing,
didn't he?
So he's pure
or something, right?
The young one is wise.
You betcha.
Smith.
Ugh. We are doomed.
What do you mean?
Chief: Chalice filled
with water from altar
gives muntabs
eternal life.
Stay young forever.
So, you weren't
kidding. 230?
I will be 231
next week.
Uh, happy birthday?
Without chalice,
we will grow old.
And Smith
will be immortal?
2,000 plus years
of obnoxiousness.
Yuck!
Jade!
You must gather
your warriors!
Smith couldn't
have gone far.
We'll stop him!
We already grow weak.
With no chalice
to refresh us,
we will perish
in the jungle.
It is too late.
Too late? Come on!
Where's that good
old muntab--
uh, I mean  young
muntab spirit?
It's never too late.
You are so young,
yet speak with the wisdom
of an elder.
See, Jackie?
He won't even
let me have
my own cell phone.
Ugh! Jade!
(Both panting)
Jackie!
Everything I've
ever hoped for,
Larsen,
right here, right now.
Eternal youth!
Eternal life!
Perhaps you would
like me to sample
it first, sir?
To make sure
it's safe.
Oh, no, that won't
be necessary.
You don't think
I'd leave you out
of this,
do you, old friend?
After all your years
of faithful service?
Well, I had hoped--
Larsen, I want you
by my side
to serve me forever.
Oh, goodie.
Shake him off!
Whoa!
Ugh! Gah! Ugh!
Gaah!
Whoa!
Larsen, cut the ladder!
Is that really
necessary, sir?
What harm could he
possibly do you now?
Do it!
Well, don't just
sit there, Larsen.
Take the controls!
You're not stopping me, chan!
What did you do?!
Parachutes!
Oh, none for us, thanks.
You see, Larsen and I
are immortal now.
Want it?
Good-bye, Mr. chan.
Yaaah!
Ow! Unh! Unh!
Ow! Ooh! Unh!
Ohh!
Guess what I caught?
My camera!
Completely ruined!
Well, that's it, Larsen.
I'm docking your wages
for 75 years.
Yes, sir.
(Gasps)
Abila?
Jade.
Thank you
for saving
my people.
You are brave
and generous.
As a wise, young chief
once told me,
generosity is not given,
it is earned.
Uh, Jackie,
that was Smith's map.
Yes. No one will ever
find the muntabs again.
Hello? How are we
supposed to find our way
back through the jungle?
Well, Larsen...
How do I look?
Very youthful, sir.
I think I need
to be changed.
Oh, goodie.
I am sure
this is the right way.
You said that
6 hours ago.
Of course, if I had
my own cell phone,
we could call
captain black
or a taxi or something.
This is really
not the time, Jade.
Hey, Jackie.
If you could have any wish
in the world, what would
you wish for?
Peace.
We already have so many
natural problems.
Earthquakes. Tornados. Hunger.
We've been killing
so many people.
So many fighting going on.
We don't need
human problems.
Really. I really need peace.