(French accent) Jackie.
Amber, it is good
to see you again.
I'm so pleased you could come.
The painting
is right through here.
It is not listed in
our official inventory.
It might be quite valuable,
if it is authentic.
That is what I am here for.
Northern song dynasty,
11th century,
ink and pale color on silk.
It's beautiful.
An authentic
Chinese masterpiece.
C'est formidable.
One moment while I fetch
the authentication forms.
Hey!
Put that back.
Huh?
Yaah!
All right, Mr. fold-up man,
thank you for showing
the painting some fresh air,
but I will take that back now.
No!
Not fair.
You claim a fold-up man
stole ze painting,
slipped between the bars,
transformed into a bird,
and flew away?
I'll show you.
He bend like this,
folded like that,
twisted over, then again,
then he look just like this.
Uh, but more bird-shaped.
Monsieur chan,
I will thank you
not to destroy my notes,
s'il vous plait.
Heh heh.
Hi, Jackie.
Jade, you were supposed to be
taking a tour of Paris.
T'cha. You've obviously
never been on a tour bus
with uncle.
You drive too fast.
How can uncle
see the sights?
Slow down.
I told him I was
having lunch with you.
He bought it.
What's with the look?
Did that painting
turn out to be bogus?
No. It was a true masterpiece.
But a fold-up man stole it,
turned into a bird,
and flew away.
Fold-up man.
That is what
the police said, too.
Ah, poor Amber. She will be
in trouble with her bosses.
I must retrieve
the painting somehow.
Lucky you got me.
I read in
a comic book once--
to catch a thief,
- you must think like a thief.
But I am no good
at thinking like a thief.
Yeah, I know.
That's why I recommend
we find some expert help.
Viper!
Jade.
What's with him?
Nothing. He's just
having a hissy
about you being
a bad influence on me
because you're a thief.
Former thief.
Now
I'm a security consultant
for the becktul corporation.
And Jade tells me
you need some assistance.
No, thank you.
I have enough problems
with one criminal.
Oh, come on, Jackie.
Viper's a good guy now.
Here, viper.
The painting stealer
left this behind.
Where did you find that?
Ah, yes.
They call him origami.
Huh?
You know this guy?
I've heard only a rumor
of a mastermind
who leaves origami animals
at all his thefts,
like a calling card.
And can he fold himself
into different shapes?
I've never heard that.
There is one person
who might know more.
But...
But what?
But you don't want my help.
The fox. This is
home base for every
crook in Paris.
The proprietor
is an old friend.
Cool. A wretched hive
of scum and villainy.
Come on.
Jade...
If I let you come inside,
you must do everything I say.
First, touch nothing.
Second, see nothing.
Third, talk to--
hey!
Ooh.
Excuse me.
- Just passing through.
Waah...My bad.
Gooh! Do not get up.
I am new here.
I do not like this place.
(French accent) Viper,
I heard you went legit.
You heard right.
Listen, fox,
I need some 411.
What can you tell me
about this?
Ah,  oui. Origami.
He only steals the finest
of far-east art.
They say he has
magical powers.
Cool.
The way I heard it told,
he was just a small-timer:
Vending machines,
picking pockets,
little penny-ante heists,
until one day,
he found an enchanted
square of paper
with the power
- to transform the paper...
Well, let's just say
it remade him.
Now he has some kind
of folding power,
if you believe
that sort of thing,
which I don't.
But it is true. I saw origami
with my own eyes.
(Gasps) Did you see
his henchmen:
The easter bunny
- and the tooth fairy as well?
That was useless.
I already knew
the thief could fold up.
Yeah, but now
we also know
he only steals
- the finest far-east art.
Hey, the kid's
a good listener.
How come you never listen
to the things I say?
For example,
stay with uncle.
Oh, man.
Kuniko kasahara
of kasahara exports.
He possesses more far-east art
than the far east itself.
It's just a matter of time
before origami shows up
to rob the place.
Look, we have to warn
Mr. kasahara.
Have you never
heard of a stakeout?
That means we hide
and keep watch,
with the emphasis on hide.
Hey!
Hello, Jade.
Glad you could make it.
May I help you?
Mr. kasahara, sir,
your art collection
is in danger.
There is a thief who,
uh, is very resourceful.
I would like to offer
my assistance.
Please leave my doorstep,
mister...
Chan. Jackie chan.
Go away, chan Jackie chan.
I will not pay
for your protection.
My protection? I'm not
trying to blackmail anyone.
Huh? Viper?
Ahh, Jade?
You are supposed
to be with uncle.
T'cha.
You are driving too slow.
I want to see all of Paris
before I get old.
Don't have a cow.
I told him I was
meeting you for a movie.
Shh! Someone's coming.
Oh, it's just
that kasahara dude.
Jade should
not be running around
rooftops with thieves.
I'm not a thief.
Better she learns how to
catch bad guys from a pro.
Jade does not need to know
how to catch bad guys.
But you do.
Whoa, he's folded.
He's origam--aah.
Ah, another masterpiece
for my eyes only.
It's him.
Kasahara is origami.
That painting does not
belong to you.
Ah, Mr. chan Jackie chan.
Return the painting
to the university.
Why? So it can end up
in a museum?
Aah!
No more games.
I know who you are.
Origami.
I'm sure we both agree
there is nothing to be
gained
by my denying it!
Jackie!
Jade, wait.
Jumping into a fight
before you're needed
usually makes things worse.
But...
Ok, now he needs help,
but you stay here.
Oh, man.
Ow!
Ooh. Paper cut.
That's the worst.
Both: Yaah!
Unh.
Jackie, swords.
Scissor beats paper.
Police. Stay where you are.
Detective, I found
the fold-up man.
He's over here.
What is this madness?
Mr. kasahara, sir,
are you all right?
This man is crazy.
He is dangerous.
He destroyed my gallery
and attacked me with my own
12th-century swords.
No! He's lying.
He changed back
to a normal man.
It's true.
Kuniko kasahara is origami,
the master thief.
Mmm, are you not
a thief yourself, huh?
La viper, I believe.
Uh, run.
Huh?
(Panting)
After them!
Jade: Well, now we
know kasahara built such
a large collection
of far-east art.
But now the police think
I am crazy and dangerous.
You know what we have to do.
We have to catch origami
in the act.
You will stay with uncle.
Breaking into the louvre.
I've been planning this
in my head for years.
Remember, we are here
to catch origami.
Do not steal anything.
Don't you trust me?
No, I do not.
Jade?!
T'cha, like a daytime
tour with uncle
was so much fun,
you thought I'd wanna
go on a nighttime one?
It is too dark
to see anything.
Is not Paris
the city of lights?
Make it brighter.
And I actually told uncle I'd
be meeting you at the louvre.
You are a bad influence.
Moi?
Aha. Right where
it's supposed to be.
The ming exhibit.
Be careful. Any one
of these paintings
could be origami incognito.
There he is!
(Alarm sounds)
What?
Whoa.
Bad day, bad day, bad day!
Hyah!
Viper!
I knew she would
betray us.
I heard that.
See, Jackie? I told you
viper's a good guy now.
Hmm...
Halt! You are all
under arrest.
You don't want us.
You want the fold-up man.
Eh,  oui, oui,
à the paper fold-up man.
I have heard all about it
for the last time.
No, no. He is right there.
(Grunting)
(Gasps) A fold-up man.
The urn is too heavy
for him to fly away.
S'arreter!
Is this one of those times
when it's better to wait
before jumping in?
No.
(Tires squeal)
Oomph. Fine.
You take the wheel.
I'll just take this.
(Car horn honking)
Sorry, uncle.
I'll see you later.
Don't miss the louvre.
Bye-bye.
Stealing a police car.
Shame on you.
Didn't you just
steal that urn
from Mr. kasahara?
That is different.
Here he comes.
Uh, I can't see anything.
Stop. The tower
is closed.
Jade?
I'm fine.
Viper, look after Jade.
Call the police.
Wait. Did he just ask me
to look after you?
Duh. Jackie likes you.
How about that?
Origami, look at me.
I have a rare porcelain urn
from the kilns of jingdezhen.
Ohh.
Come on, come on, come on.
Aah!
Ohh.
Waah!
Uh, wrong floor.
Well, chan Jackie chan,
it appears you are down
to 2 options--
hand over the urn or jump.
The police already
know the truth.
They saw you
try to fly away.
They will think
it was only their eyes
playing tricks on them.
No one believes there can be
a paper fold-up man.
All right.
You win.
Hey! Ohh!
(Grunts)
Ah...
Merci, Jackie.
Was the thief a fold-up man,
like you said?
Uh, no. My eyes
played tricks on me.
It was just
a normal thief.
Just a normal thief,
huh?
Then I guess you really
didn't need my help.
That is right. No help.
I understand.
Ow.
Do you know how long
I was stuck in that bus
with cheese on my face?
I said I was sorry. Ow!
Hey, Jackie...
Yes?
Where did you grow up?
I grow up in Hong Kong...
In apartment...With...
French embassy.
My father was a cook,
my mother a maid.
So when I was young,
I speak perfect French.
The ambassador--
she's very good.
She loved me
playing with her children.
Except when I sleep,
back to behind the kitchen.